www.SubDESU-H.net
I'll confess.
During the year after our marriage through a matchmaking service,
I had another side of me that I kept hidden.
It's the real me, that you should never know.
Umm, dear?
What?
What is it?
Well...
No good, I just can't tell him.
It might rain this evening, so take this umbrella.
Oh, thank you.
I'll be off then.
See you.
If, by any chance,
you suddenly discover the truth...
I know that I can't hide it forever.
But still...
I...
Sexification
Persona
Housewife
Okay, I'll start rolling the camera now.
No...
Yumicchi, nice expression there.
Here Mrs. Housewife, look towards the camera.
No...
I mustn't.
It's embarrassing.
You really have large boobs.
These are at least G Cup.
Don't touch me there.
Mrs. Housewife, you're already dripping down here.
No... please stop.
This position is...
Your pussy is completely exposed.
Truly an embarrassing position.
No, please don’t say that.
Mrs. Housewife, I heard you're a newlywed.
All of this started with a deal made to repay the debt of a friend.
I wonder what Mr. Husband would think if he found out about this?
Before I knew it, I was already carrying the burden of paying a 3-million yen debt.
Here, now you must say "ahh."
The way you lick this cock looks really lewd.
Darling, I'm now in the middle of filming an AV.
This tight-fitted stocking is holding my cock tight.
I already know about it, that you're just as horny as you were in high school.
I've also heard about it.
Our director probably researched about it.
That's just how our director works.
Her tongue is wrapping around my cock.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to deliver you a load of cum that's not from your husband!
Besides, with this body, it's impossible for you to be truly satisfied with just one man!
We need to properly load if off on her.
I'm having sex with other people in order to save money.
Does your husband know
that you were a real bitch back then?
I heard that she already did it with more than half of her club's members.
She's secretly known as the Grand Comfort Station.
I've given lots of blow jobs to other men without you knowing it.
I get horny from cocks other than yours.
Mrs. Housewife, it's okay isn't it?
I'm going to cum inside you.
Yes, please cum in me.
You're getting all dirty now with other cocks.
If you see what I am now, what would you think?
If you knew how vulgar a woman my other side is,
would you...
Oh no...
Getting deeply penetrated feels great.
Mrs. Housewife, you're the best.
I want to cum more.
I'm sorry, dear.
Sex Video
Hey,
this is the video that we filmed before we became really popular.
You really are erotic, Yumicchi.
It was right for me to ask you to create my next AV.
Yabe-kun, please don’t say that.
It's embarrassing.
What are you talking about?
You were really horny here.
You actually feel happy about this, don't you?
You've just exposed your lewd self to all the men in the country.
You get to pay your debt, while still being able to enjoy every bit of it.
It's more than you could ever ask for!
Dear, I'm also going to appear in this new AV.
Okay Yumicchi, we'll start filming now.
Just try to relax naturally.
It's a sex video that I've never told you about.
No...
Look, your nipples are already getting hard.
Don't...
The sensation of someone else playing with my nipples...
You get aroused quite easily, as always.
If someone does it like that, then I just can't...
It's becoming etched into my mind.
Even with this really sexy body, your high-class white collar husband still doesn't get satisfied?
No, please don't say that.
What is it that I shouldn't say?
You actually love this, don’t you?
You just need to remember,
how you were when you were still a student.
All the boys at the film research club really enjoyed how we tried to bet on who would own you.
I think Sugiyama won that time.
He was really excited by it.
That time you were done at least three times.
Though everyone still got their go, one by one after that.
Stop that already.
Stop talking about the past...
What are you saying?
You’re already dripping down here just by remembering that time.
It was about that time when I decided to create AV's.
Whenever I see how erotic your body is,
I always think about how it would be a waste if we don't show it to everyone.
It's throbbing really hard.
Yabe-kun, forget that already...
Oh, can't wait for it anymore, eh?
Here now, get all horny while the camera's still rolling.
Do it as if you're looking forward to being seen by all the men who will watch this.
Yes...!
Dear, do you think I'm a bad woman?
This is great.
I enjoy seeing men go crazy for my body.
Yes!
I've loved sex for a long time
and I've already done it with a lot of other men.
But... when I met you,
I decided to stop doing this.
Oh yes...
It's hitting my spots.
This cock is amazing!
Thrust it into me more!
Oh no, it feels too good.
My oh my, getting all dirty with a cock that isn't your husband's.
No...
That's because, your cock makes me really horny.
Oh no, I'm going to cum.
It's good.
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum.
I'm already there.
Let's...
Let's cum together!
Okay, I'm going to let it all out on you.
If this continues, then I'm going to revert back to my old self.
We sure filmed a good one again, Yumicchi.
Let's keep up the pace for the next video, okay?
Are you getting scared of being found out?
If we continue this...
I'm going to revert back to my old self.
Revert?
You're still that old self of yours.
The old self that was receiving cocks from different men.
That's not true.
The fact that you easily agreed to filming these AV's is already proof of that, isn't it?
That's... because I need to repay a debt...
Is that the only reason?
Could it be that you're also feeling unsatisfied with just having your husband as your partner?
You're not the type of woman that gets satisfied from only one cock.
You’re just forcing yourself to.
What should I do?
Just follow what your heart tells you.
Now then, I'll send you a message the next time we need to meet.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Exhibitionism in the Park
Today, I lied and told my husband that I was going out to have dinner with some friends,
and instead went to a nearby park.
This is all in preparation for an exhibitionism-themed AV.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey there Yumicchi.
This is actor Iguru Katou.
Nice to meet you, Yumi-san.
Nice to meet you too.
Okay, the filming equipment is already set,
so we only need to pick a spot and then we'll get started.
Okay...
I prepared dinner in advance.
Just get it from the fridge and heat it up, okay?
Okay.
I don't think I'll be out for long.
I'll be going now.
I wonder how many films we've made already.
With each occasion, the guilt I feel becomes less and less.
My body is gradually filling up with ecstasy.
I won't be able to resist this sensation soon.
Here.
People seldom walk around this area, so it should be fine here.
Okay.
You know, I have been looking forward to meeting you, Yumi-san.
Yabe-san showed me the AV that you previously made.
Then I thought,
that this woman is the real deal...
A bitch.
Hey...
I've heard that you're a married woman who does AV's to pay some kind of debt.
No...
But your mind is actually thrilled by the idea of betraying your husband this way, isn't it?
No!
Stop, this is embarrassing.
You really are a bad woman.
Acting like the loving housewife,
but actually, you love seducing other men.
That's not true.
Here, expose your butt.
We're going to do it here?
Someone might see us.
I think anyone would be happy to see your lewd body.
What are you saying?
There might even be a few watching nearby already.
No, don’t...!
It's the first time I've done this.
My sweet spots are being stirred up.
Oh no, I'm going to cum.
I'm already at my limit.
No, wait...
I just came, if you continue doing it that intensely I'll...
You'll what?
Here, cum some more!
It's coming out!
I don't think I'll be able keep showing you my fake side anymore.
Now let’s have a clear shot of you having sex here.
No, don't...
Don't be this intense so soon...
You're already dripping wet, so what are you talking about?
This is amazing.
Yes...
It feels too good.
Wait.
Someone's there.
Stop...!
What's wrong with that?
Then let that person see better.
How you get all dirty with a cock that isn't your husband's!
No, please!
I can't keep my voice down.
I keep moaning out loud.
Someone's watching us.
Are you okay with that?
More people might come over with that loud moaning of yours.
I don't care anymore.
I don't care anymore if anyone sees me having sex here.
Keep it up!
Thrust your cock deeper inside.
I want to feel it more!
I want more of it!
Wow, your cock is already very deep inside.
Oh no, I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming.
Oh no.
It ended much later than I thought.
I have to get home quickly.
Yumi.
Dear...?
Why are you here?
Yumi.
Perversion
Stop, dear...
You're too intense suddenly.
Shut up, you have no right to order me around!
Please, don't be too rough!
Just how many cocks went in there already, huh!?
Ten?
Twenty?
Thirty?!
This tastes great.
These dirty and dark cocks are delicious!
It's really stiff.
How does it feel?
Being done by your husband while all of those AV's are playing on the screen?
I'm sorry.
Dear, I...
Yumi, you're still getting horny at this time?
I'm sorry, but this is how I am.
I was really a sex-loving bitch before.
That's why, I only did it at first to repay the debt.
But it became more and more enjoyable to do.
It felt good to be able to taste many cocks like that.
I'm sorry dear.
Please punish this horny me with your cock!
Semen is overflowing.
Please, please have more sex with me.
I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry dear...
Let's get a divorce.
Man, that was a really nice act!
You can be a great actor, Mr. Husband.
Yabe-kun...?
Was it filmed well, Yabe-san?
Yep, it was perfect.
Aside from that one camera, there are also other hidden cameras installed in the room.
This will be a big hit.
What's the meaning of this?
Actually, the one who asked us to invite you to do an AV...
Was none other than him.
Mr. Husband.
He confessed that he's the perverted type that gets really aroused seeing your AV's, Yumicchi.
This is the first time I've really felt excited.
Dear...
Yumi, it's not just you who has a hidden side you know?
www.SubDESU-H.net