www.SubDESU-H.net
I-I'm taking them now!
Umm... Can you please smile a bit more?
You...
Do your best leader!
Leader!
Th-Then next, your panties...
Please take off your panties!
D-Damn...
Hey, is this okay now?
Take whatever pictures you want.
The center is completely pink!
So erotic...
I... I can't hold it in anymore!
Please let me fuck you now!
Kizaki-senpai, please let me!
N-No! Don’t stick so close to me!
Damn.
I'm letting this guy...
...do me like this wildly.
Don’t use your cock to play with my butt!
Senpai! Caldina-senpai!
That's... No...!
No way...
It won't fit in...
...like normal.
It's in!
My cock is halfway in senpai!
I can't get it all in yet,
but it's already fitting nicely inside.
Pisu
Sub
Hame
Desu
!
-H
W
3-D
Girls Circle
Kizaki
Caldina
So it's you who is gonna take me on.
Gamble Battle over!
The victor with 4 out of 5 wins:
Tamao Tsukamu!
Tamao Tsukamu won against Kizaki Caldina in the gamble battle,
and is now making a sex video.
This will eventually trigger an orgy with the aroused girl group around them.
He is quite something, that Tamao Tsukamu.
A gamble battle is not such a big deal in itself, but...
with these turn of events, he will be able collect a plethora of sexy photographs involving a lot of girls.
As expected of someone recommended by Konome.
Indeed.
We should seriously evaluate him as a candidate for the next student council president.
He can also be a good asset pawn for my business.
Alright then.
Senpai, senpai!
I am fucking a rascal with such a beastly cock,
for the first time!
Hurry up and get on with it.
Until it's all in.
You move in a weird way and it just stays around the entrance.
Sliding till midway all the time...
I feel bad that it doesn't go further inside.
Senpai, this is an honor.
Someone as cute and beautiful as you... letting me fuck you so deep...
That's...
Your insides are wriggling back and forth.
It's because you're making a mess out of me like this.
Idiot.
Idiot!
This time,
I'm on top!!
Seriously, it's really huge...
Oh no, I'm going to cum!
Because of someone like him... him!
Damn.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
This is the very first time that someone has come inside me.
Hey, all of you...
Since when...
Don't take pictures!
I'm sorry, leader.
But when I saw your beauty and sensuality
I just couldn't help but message the others about it.
Leader wasn't always like that.
I never could have imagined you being promiscuous, ever.
I'm so happy to have witnessed you having sex!
Why is it still getting bigger inside?
I-I'm sorry.
But when I think that these girls are looking at us...
You idiot!
Don't take pictures!
Just stop taking it I said!
Oh my, I can't take this anymore...
Leader, smile!
Leader, you're so beautiful and erotic!
Please do it with us, too.
So cute, your nipples are like a girl's...
We just weren't able to resist when we saw this big cock and that awesome sex.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Okay! Tamao-kun, here you go.~
U...Umm...
Okay, next are panties.
Panties, panties!
T-back!
Oh crap, mine's drenched.
Here, take mine.
It's the smell of a girl!
Alright~
Take that perfectly sized cock and put it inside my pussy please!
Y-Yes!
Great.
This... your's...
Great, it's great!
Seriously, not only is it huge,
it has a great shape as well!
Ouch...
I got myself creamed...
Hey, hey Tamao-kun.
Take a look this way. There are still a lot of pussies to go around~
You can use them however you want.
Oh no!
This is really something!
My insides are getting stretched.
It's an amazing feeling!
This is bad! This is bad!
This can't be...!
No, no!
Amazing!
This thing is really stiff.
My pussy gets really wet when it rubs my insides.
Please, take my email address!
Save it on your phone.
Don't worry about anything.
Just call me anytime and fuck my pussy!
That's unfair!
Take mine too!
Mine too!
Me too... once more...
Ejaculate inside my vagina.
Yes!
If it's for Caldina-senpai,
I'll do it as many times as you want.
Here we go, I'll take it now.
Peace!
But... are you sure about this?
About Kiritani Konome...
Even though she is your fiancé, she has been doing much more than just assisting Tamao in his endeavors.
We noticed a lot of her actions which were executed without our consent.
Kiritani Konome...
Is she planning something behind our backs?
The Kiritani family has been exercising considerable authority for a long time.
Meaning she's a lady of noble descent.
Also, her grandfather, Kiritani Matagoro, is also considered an expert swordsman.
Not only that, they are also well protected by the national police.
In other words, they are considered elite citizens.
Of course if anything dangerous happens, I'll gain political protection.
So this engagement actually holds merit for me.
Even though it was a political wedding that was decided by our families, but...
Ever since she was first introduced at the age of eight,
I always noticed a silent resentment in her for this union.
This is a good chance.
I'll crush Konome's plans, along with her self-respect and noble upbringing.
I'll discipline her in a way worthy of becoming my wife.
Is something wrong?
Nothing...
I just thought it would be fun to take Konome's virginity and sweep her away right in front of Tamao-kun.
Amazing.
Tamao-kun really is a strong one!
www.SubDESU-H.net