Men!
And the winner of this year’s all girls' Kendo match is...
From Shousei Academy.
Kiritani Konome!
Class 2-C
Kendo Club
Tamao
Tsukamu
Sen… pai…
Konome-senpai. I love you.
I love you!
Also a men!
Pisu
Sub
Hame
Desu
!
-H
Tamao-kun.
Is Tamao Tsukamu here?
Girls' Kendo Club Representative
3rd year student
Kiritani
Konome
Y-Yes!
Thank goodness.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
O-Okay...
This place isn’t the best, so... will you come with me somewhere else?
Y-
Yes!
Kiritani Konome-senpai, you’re just too beautiful!
Winner of the all girls' Kendo trophy.
Vice President of the student council, adored by all students.
She’s bright and clever, the underclassmen love her,
and her bust measurement is in the school’s top three!
And her butt isn’t too far behind on destructive powers.
Konome-senpai is just too wonderful.
So wonderful it makes breathing around her difficult!
But she wants to ask me to do something? What could it be?
Could you unhook
my bra for me?
Hey, can I see your dick?
Please fuck me!
This is the place.
The Student Council room?
Sorry Tamao-kun, but this is a really strange and sudden announcement.
I might get you wrapped up in something strange.
I really am sorry.
But I want to put my faith in you!
I think you can do it.
I want you to help me out.
Okay!
Wow! I’m not really sure why or how, but springtime has come for me at last!
Student Council Room
You are Tamao…
Tamao Tsukamu-kun, correct?
Nice to meet you, Tamao-kun.
I am the Student Council President, Sasugaki Kunitake.
Student Council President
3rd year student
Sasugaki
Kunitake
So you're Konome's junior?
I see.
No matter how much I lust after her, it’s pointless.
She’s engaged to the President.
Tamao-kun.
I want you to carry out a special duty for the Yearbook Committee.
Oh... Well, I don’t mind...
Well, I’m not surprised at your blank face.
However, it’s a very difficult job.
First, take a look at this album.
This page is the class picture.
Our memories!
The next page is photos from that class’s culture festival and P.E. festival.
Also, pictures from the yearly school field trip and other events.
You will be in charge of the NEXT page.
W-WHAT?!
Mika, Hikari
Inaho, Yoshino
Take a look!
It’s the Hamedori graduation album!
Hamedori is a term for taking sex photos/videos, so the “Hame” in the title references this.
WHAT?!
This is our school’s legendary Hamedori Album, Tamao-kun.
As a second-year student, you must support a third year student in the Hamedori.
With Konome, you must complete this Hamedori Album!
I’m sorry, Tamao-kun!
Sorry to get you caught up in this so suddenly!
If you really don’t want to, you can always refuse.
I really am sorr—
N-No!
To think that you chose m-me...
I’m so horn... so happy!
If I can do anything to help you...
Just say it.
Let me do it!
Thanks, Tamao-kun.
And that’s how I joined the Yearbook Committee.
The Yearbook Committee meets after school.
Class 3-C
Inamura Satomi
Konome-senpai contacted me about meeting the third year students.
Class 3-A
Kishinaga Keiko
Going-home-from-school Club
Here.
Class 3-D
Library Assistant
Momose
Kumi
Um... Here.
in places where no one would be, to collect their photos.
So, check their photos.
I-Is that really okay?
We need to check them.
Okay!
I understand.
Woah, this is just... it’s not...
I’m sorry!
No... Well, you're a boy so you can’t help it.
You can stick out your chest and be proud of it.
Impossible for me to
stick out my chest
as much as YOU do.
Class 3-B
Prapan Club
Kitazawa
Youko
There were way more female senpai submitting photos than I’d anticipated.
Their partners were people who looked like their boyfriends,
Class 3-A
Asou
Sasha
as well as random old men – a huge variety.
Class 3-C
Going-home-from-school Club
Hamano
Yukina
I had no idea that my female senpais were so crazy...
Class 3-C
Bicycling Club
Kawamura
Saki
But it's clear from these photos that they are all sex-mad.
Class 3-A
Akiyama
Nanami
I gathered the photos from about two or three different girls per day.
And two weeks of this sneaky activity passed.
Class 3-D
Michisato
Madoka
This is Michisato Madoka from class 3-D.
Kiritani-san!
Hello!
Sorry to call you out here.
I'm Tamao... I head the special Graduation portion of the Yearbook.
Yeah. Hi, I’m Michisato.
And so, your submission photos for the book...
Well, you see, last week, I broke up with my boyfriend.
And I’d love to give you some naughty photos for the book since it sounds like fun,
but there’s no one to take them with.
Oh, in that case, we can leave you out.
Hm, but maybe...
Tamao-kun, right?
Yes.
Are you... free?
M-Michisato-san, Michisato-senpai!
You can’t! We can’t!
But I have no other choice.
I don’t have a boyfriend right now.
Doing it with you is my only choice.
And look. You want it.
D-Don’t say…
Wow. It seems so big, doesn't it?
Kiritani-senpai...
Senpai... Um...
What should I do?
Well...
When I asked you to do this job,
I knew that this sort of thing would eventually happen.
So please, don’t mind me, just do your best!
Th-That’s easy for you to say...
Well then, since we have Kiritani-san’s permission…
Do you like big tits?
Here.
Try saying “ah”.
Konome-senpai, I’m so sorry.
But it’s impossible for a boy to hold back!
I’m so happy you like it.
Hey, are you a virgin?
Yes!
I’m so happy.
I’m only one year older than you, but I’ll teach you lots.
You sure are alive and well... ”down there”.
H-How pathetic...
I’m a man... but they’re watching me lose control.
Well then, I’ll take it off.
I’ll expose your dick.
Wow! Amazing!
It’s very... very big.
Don’t look at it! It’s my dick!
It’s so big, but it’s cute with the skin.
Well then, Kiritani-san, will you take my picture?
I will.
Okay... here I go.
How embarrassing.
Misa... I’m almost... I’m sorry!
Sorry. It’s your first time, right?
Go ahead and cum lots.
I’m sorry!
I didn't mean to cum in your mouth.
She swallowed!
No, it's okay.
You are really amazing.
You got even bigger when you came just now.
Well then, let’s do the real thing now.
Y-Yes!
P-Please.
Never mind.
Eh?
Woah! This is...
I’m doing it n-n-naked!
Warm!
But I didn’t put the condom on yet.
It’s my naked dick!
Yes. It’s bareback fucking.
Are you sure?
This is my first time doing it without a condom.
In exchange for your virginity...
I’ll give you my bareback virginity.
I’m honored.
Make me feel really good, okay?
It’s okay, move your pelvis more.
Okay!
It’s so warm and wet...
It feels so good to open her up with my dick!
You’re so good.
Yes. Yes!
Your dick keeps going deeper.
Well? Does it feel good?
Y-Yes. It feels good.
Hold back as much as you can.
Once we both feel as good as possible, you can cum inside all you want.
I’ve never felt this good before.
Is it because it’s a naked dick?
Or because you’re good?
Again...!
Hey, what’s wrong?
Your dick is...
I'm cumming!
I’m gonna cum!
No! I wanna cum first!
I’m cumming.
No!
Then,  Michisato-san, I’ll take your picture.
Face me and stick out your tongue.
Okaaaaay.
Tamao-kun...
Nice pic.
Then, use that pic, Kiritani-san.
O-Okay, I will.
Then...
Please, let’s fuck more.
Let me taste your awesome dick more.
S-Senpai...
Yes!
Me too... I want to fuck your pussy some more too!
Wow, so awesome!
Tamao-kun... Tamao-kun!
Wow! I can’t stop it!
I’m cumming!
Yes! Cum! Cum!
More... is coming out...
Your mouth... You’re so good at it.
It feels so good.
I want to keep it in your mouth forever.
Your mouth... I’m cumming in your mouth.
Let go. I’m cumming.
How amazing. It fits between my tits so nicely. What a snuggly Mr. Dick.
It’s not just your tits... your pussy!
Your pussy... It’s so hot and smells good.
A girl’s body is so soft and sexy... everything feels great!
No! Don’t!
Senpai... again... keep it up.
I’m cumming... cumming inside.
I can’t take it... I can’t!
Michisato-san left.
She seemed... satisfied.
That was just...!
I’m sorry! I lost control of myself there!
I embarrassed myself in front of you again.
Senpai...
Face me.
Konome-senpai is... wiping my dick... for me.
My body belongs to someone else, so I can’t do anything for you.
But wiping you off like this is part of my job on the album committee.
Squeeeeeze
Hmm?
It’s hard to tell when I’m covering it with tissue, but... you sure seem big.
Don’t say... Senpai, I...
I fucked someone else in front of you.
I don’t mind.
I asked you to do this.
And I’m sure there will be more days like this in the future.
So don’t mind me, and just do your job for the album.
Okay.
U-Um, Senpai!
I’ll do my best for the album!
And can I just ask... one question of you?
If this sort of thing happens again, will you wipe me off?
Sure. You can count on me.