Eh? M-My favorite position?
Missionary position? Doggy style?
The feeling when you come? Come where?
O-Oh, that kind of come.
O-Of course I knew that!
Eh? F-Fellatio?
T-Tit-fuck?
We high-class ladies must be good at f-fellatio.
Uh, yes! Gentlemen love women who're good at it!
Squirting?
Oral sex?
Bully the squirrel and chestnut?
TL note: Kuri (くり) means clitoris, however it can also mean chestnut.
O-Of course I-I can do that!
Sex adds elegance to a woman?
Fellatio, tit-fuck... I wonder what they mean...?
I have to try them out!
It's
not
like
I
grew
up
like
this
just
for
you
!!
By
SubDESU-H
Okisaba Kaoru
You're late!
I told you to come within three seconds if I called you! You're worthless!
Well, whatever. Lift your head.
You're that new apprentice butler, aren't you?
Well, I guess you'll do.
There's something I want to keep secret from the others.
You can keep a secret, can't you?
Of course. You'll do whatever I say, won't you?
I see. If anyone were to find out,
then you know what would happen, don't you?
Right. Lock the door and come into my bedroom.
Huh? I said that it's okay!
Do what your master says!
C'mon, don't just stand there! Take off your pants!
Take off your underwear, too.
Don't give me excuses!
You said that you'd do whatever I say, didn't you?
Don't you get it? It is very rare and honorable that I am asking something of you.
C'mon... If you understand, then take these off.
I-Is this a man's...?
Oh? It's so cute and small compared to what I remember seeing in movies.
W-What's this?
I-I haven't heard anything about this!
D-Do you know what a "fellatio" is?
I see. Then show me.
Are you still against me?!
This is an order! Do it!
Jeez, you should have obeyed in the first place...
Eh? Wha-?
W-What the hell are you doing?!
Do you really want to die?!
Eh? That was "fellatio"?
O-Of course I knew that!
C'mon! Let's keep going! Sit in that chair!
T-This ugly thing...
D-Do I have to put this thing in my mouth, servant?
I already said I knew that! Just shut up!
H-Here I go.
It's salty...
Huh? Use my tongue?
Like this?
Is this okay?
T-This is too easy!
Something slimy is coming out...
What is this? It means that you're feeling good?
I-I see...
W-What do I do now?
Faster? Like this?
What's going to happen now?
You're gonna cum? What do you mean?
Do it more?
W-What is this?
You might cum?
You're gonna cum?
Huh? It's gotten so hard!
You're gonna let it out? What do you mean?
What is this? It's hot-!
No-! S-Stop it, you idiot!
Is this a man's...?
It tastes bitter.
It's not very tasty...
Next, we're going to try a "tit-fuck".
Eh? W-Wait...!
D-Don't think that you can get away with this too!
Eh? Do I have to take it off for a "tit-fuck"?
Jeez, how did something like this happen?
It can't be helped. Fine then! Take it off!
Why is a servant like him doing...?
W-What? Don't look at me so dirtily!
It's not like I grew up like this just for you!
What are you doing?
W-We have to get ready?
You're loosening up my breasts?
If you're lying, I won't forgive you!
We should swap places?
No way!
Don't play with my nipples!
Fine then! We'll switch!
To think that I've had to kneel in front of a servant twice already...
I get it already! I'll do it!
I-I know! I just have to put it between them, don't I?
I-I'm g-gonna get started!
Up and down? L-Like this?
Does something like this feel good? How stupid!
W-What? Do it faster?
You only d-deserve this much!
Sheesh, men are so simple!
For them to like something like this...
What's this? Something is coming out of the end...
It's slimy and smells strange...
It's not semen, is it?
Does it mean that this feels good too?
How is it? I bet it feels too good.
T-There isn't anything that I can't do!
W-What are you trying to do?
What are you...?
Don't-!
Stop it-!
T-This is-!
Stop it at once!
I order you-!
W-Why do I have to suck your dirty thing again?
T-This isn't funny! I-I'll kill you!
Don't! I-I can't bear this!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
How dare a servant like you spray such t-thick and disgusting stuff onto my face twice!
I-I'll never believe you covered me in so much! N-Not even in a hundred years!
Sex!!
I can be high-class!
Fellatio?
Tit-fuck
Squirting?
Hmph! Whatever! We don't have much time since we're going to try them all out tonight.
To think that I have to have my body f-felt up again...
Be prepared for punishment if you dirty my bed with your disgusting fluid!
T-There's no way that you'd make me feel good...
I-It's easier to squirt if you're feeling good?
Eh? D-Don't be silly!
Hey! W-Where do you think you're touching?!
Y-You can't do it directly-!
I-It doesn't feel good...!
There's no way that I'd feel aroused from being kissed and played with by a servant!
T-This position is-! If I can't squirt after being rubbed like this, then...!
No-! Don't pinch me there!
You mustn't! Something is coming out!
It feels so good-! What is this?
I came? Is this what cumming is?
This fuzzy feeling is cumming, isn't it?
What...?
H-Hey-!
Do you really want to die that much?
I-I didn't ask for this!
I-I did say that we'd do everything,
b-but I haven't caught my breath...!
You idiot! Don't look! Don't look at me so closely down there!
What is this? It's wiggling inside me-!
His tongue is inside me-!
It's overflowing!
Cunnilingus? Is this what cunnilingus is?
It's dirty, so don't say it tastes good, you idiot!
I-If you're going to put it in, hurry up-!
T-This is just something I have to d-do to become an adult!
I-It didn't have to be you!
T-That's right! It just happened to be you!
It's not like it had to be you, so don't be mistaken!
T-That's the spot, isn't it?
Y-You're going to put that disgusting thing inside me there, aren't you?
W-What are you...?
Are you teasing me?!
How dare you!
J-Just hurry up and put it in!
Drill your disgusting thing deep inside me!
H-Hurry up and make me a woman!
Don't thrust, you idiot! Pull it out!
T-This is-! I-It hurts!
N-No more! I don't want to have sex anymore!
You-! Can't you obey my orders-?!
Fine, then! Keep going!
D-Do it s-slower!
That's it. This speed is okay...
It doesn't hurt as much now...
It's rubbing against my insides!
T-This is sex, isn't it?
T-This, this is...!
What's this feeling?
Am I getting aroused?
It feels like I'm gonna cum again!
This isn't possible! Why am I feeling good from the likes of you?
Don't! Stop it-!
It's going in too deep! It's reaching my deepest spots!
Don't knock against the end!
There's no way! There's no way that I could cum from this-!
No, I'm cumming!
No...
W-What now?
Is this doing it "doggy style"?
I don't like it! It's like we're animals!
How dare you! W-What did you say?!
How dare a servant talk like that to their master!
Don't! If you move, my body starts wanting it!
If you keep teasing me-!
You idiot! Like I could say such a thing!
Jeez, fine! I'll say it!
I-I want it! I want your cock!
I want you to put your cock inside me!
Servant, put your cock deep inside me and make me feel good!
Yes, yes! This is want I wanted!
I love it! I love your cock!
No, this isn't me... I'm making such an unrefined expression!
N-No! T-This isn't me!
No! This isn't like me! It's not! It can't be!
I-I don't want it! It's embarrassing, but it feels amazing!
Do it more! More, more! Thrust more!
My breasts are shaking around! Do it harder!
H-Humiliate me more!
Pound me more! Do it harder! Do me like an animal!
So good-! It feels incredible! More! Do it more!
I-It's so good! I love your cock, servant!
I'm gonna cum! A person like me is going to cum from a servant's-!
More! Thrust more!
Mess up my insides with your dirty cock!
Cum! Make me cum a lot!
Make your master cum!
So good! It feels so good!
It's scraping against my broken hymen!
Your hard cock is grinding against me!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I've been cumming constantly from feeling so good!
It's amazing! It feels too good!
No-one told me about this!
But if I remember this, I'll turn into a dirty girl!
Amazing! It's amazing!
It feels like your grinding is making me melt!
Your cock is melting me!
I'm taking it in so easily!
M-My pussy is taking your cock in so easily!
It's dribbling and loving your dirty cock, servant!
So good, it feels amazing!
Grope my breasts more!
Amazing, do it more!
This feels incredible. It feels like I'm melting...
More...
Amazing-! I feel like I'm f-floating if I touch here while we're doing it!
No, I can't hold it in!
I've cum so much that I can't speak clearly...!
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Cum! Cum with me!
Okay, you can cum inside!
Drench my insides with your dirty semen!
I'm cumming!
You came so much...
Now then, I think that we've done everything in the notebook.
Hey, what do you think?
We're finished then, aren't we?
You were doing whatever you wished to your master, weren't you?!
I wonder what kind of punishment I should give to this lewd and beast-like servant who doesn't know his place!
Well, I'll let you off this time,
After all, I was the one who asked you to do it...
But! This is the only time I'm letting you off! Dismissed!
Hey, there are other lewd things we haven't done, aren't there?
I see, then come again.
Keep it a secret, okay?