Due to the excessive heat waves, that summer was extremely hot.
Everyone would strip off their clothes to cool down.
The sales of ice cream and ice blocks also went through the roof.
Coincidentally, in this boiling summer,
my father was appointed to a long term, holiday job at an overseas branch of the company.
Before leaving, he said to not mess around while he's away.
So he assigned me some home tutors.
I was living some exciting summer holidays... With these 4 beautiful tutors.
Sub
DESU
-H
Presents
Kateikyoushi no Oneesan II
You get excited too quickly, Touya-kun! It's just a chore!
S-Sara-san, why so suddenly?
T-That's right!
It's because we teach him in swimsuits he...
Oh, Rio-chan?
I was extremely nervous that time as well!
What?
Wearing something like that...
If he weren't aroused, then I would have been even more embarrassed!
W-Well, that's...
When that happens, I get so excited and want to start titfuck him!
I would rub his cock with my breasts like so.
I would lick him with...
Then I would start to get aroused by it!
Geez Sara-san!
I bet you were rubbing yourself somewhere too!
Oh, but~! He was so hard!
I couldn't hold back...
I-I wonder... if Touya-kun prefers women with big breasts...
I don't think so.
Your breasts are beautiful too, Rio-chan!
W-Wha? That's not what I meant...
Gosh, Sara-san!
Hm?
Hey Touya, did you finish that textbook?
N-No, there was a part that I couldn't understand...
Oh no, it dribbled down onto my chest.
N-Nagisa, d-don't!
Wait! Touya is watching!
No... Touya, go to my room with that textbook...
A-Amane-san...?
G-Go to my room...
Y-Yes.
No...!
Amane-chan, are you getting aroused?
Of course not!
I-I can't stop...
What?
U-Um, this is, uh...
Y-You bastard...
What are you lookin' at?!
I-I'm sorry... I didn't mean to stare...
Since you saw me do such an embarrassing thing,
I'll have you do the same thing.
Huh?
I'm saying that you have to show me how you masturbate as well!
Huh?!
What? Then we'll call it even.
U-Um, well... Saying it so suddenly... I don't even have any material either...
M-Material?
If I could see your private bits like before, maybe I could...
W-What are you saying?
N-Never mind, I knew you would say no.
Geez, you're so... Fine then, it can't be helped...
S-See? Is this fine?
Hurry up and show me.
Y-Yes.
Huh? You're going to do it up this close?
H-Hmph!
For someone to be that erect from just looking at breasts...
You're really a pervert.
W-What's this?
Touya's cock is so large...
I-Is he getting that excited from seeing my breasts?
Amane-san... I can see your panties!
W-Wouldn't you feel more excited this way?
You should be thankful for my extra service...
A-Amazing... I can feel Touya looking at me...
His gaze is digging into me down there...
My body, down there, is getting hot...
N-No... If I see you stroking your cock so much,
I'll get excited too!
I-I can't hold back!
A-Amane-san?
It's hot...
Your cock is so hot.
I'll help you out, so you better cum soon.
A-Amane-san... That's somewhat... Very erotic.
You d-dummy! It's your... It's your fault!
W-Wait Amane-san!
That's too-!
Pre-cum is coming out of Touya's cock...
I-If you do that a lot, I-I'll cum...
Just let it out already!
I'm already stoking down here...
W-Why?
E-Even if I am just doing fellatio...
It feels much better... than doing it by myself!
My body is getting hotter! My pussy is... My pussy is-!
Amane-san... I'm about to-!
Hurry... Hurry up!
I-I can't stop!
If this goes on, I might cum first!
No, I can't hold on-!
Amane-chan! Are you in there?
P-Please wait a sec-!
Touya-kun, you were here!
Y-Yeah...
Sorry to disturb you in your studies.
Anyway, I'm just going to go down to the convenience store.
Is there anything you might need?
N-No, not really.
How about you, Amane-chan?
I-I don't have anything in particular either.
Oh really?
Then, I'll be off.
I-I drank it, Touya's semen, I drank it...
Kateikyoushi no Oneesan II
I-Isn't this-?!
It was in the basket in the changing room...
Are these perhaps yours, Touya-kun?
N-No way! T-These probably belong to Nagisa-san or Sara-san...
O-Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
Y-Yeah.
H-Have you used these before?
N-No, I haven't.
U-Um, um so... If you would like,
would you like to try this with me?
What?
I-I haven't used something like these either...
They interest me, so I thought we could try...
O-Or rather, learn about them...
What do you think?
There's no way I could turn down such a tempting offer...
So then, I'm gonna do it.
I-It feels so good!
W-What is this feeling? It feels strange, like it's tickling me...
My breasts feel like they're throbbing...
T-Touya-kun?
If I do it under this, it would feel so much better.
N-No don't! If you do that, I'll-!
R-Right there! On my nipple! Please be gentle with it!
A-Amazing... Rio-san, your nipples are so hard!
N-No! Don't say such thing! Don't say such lewd things!
It's embarrassing...
W-Wait, Touya-kun!
You're going to do it down there too?
Touya-kun... You're twitching down there...
I'm sorry...
I can't help myself becoming like this when I look at your lewd bits.
T-That's unfair...
L-Let me make you feel good too!
Y-Your cock... It's getting so hard!
For you to get aroused from me playing with your ass... You're so lustful!
Rio-san, you're soaking also-!
I can feel it! I can feel my lewd juices leaking out...
Your sticky juices is making the rotar slip-
W-Wait! Wha?
I'm sorry, my hand slipped...
Rio-san, it's going deeper and deeper...
No~!
You're so horny here, Rio-san!
It's not coming back out!
Touya-kun, you're having fun by embarrassing me with your comments, aren't you?
Your cock is twitching too!
Me too!
R-Right there... Yes, it feels good right there-!
Rio-san! I'm about to-!
It's fine! I'm about to cum also!
You can dirty my face so-!
Together... Let's go together!
R-Rio-san!
Rio-san!!
You guys seem to be having a lot of fun!
Eh?!
I'll get excited if I hear voices like this!
You could have knocked!
I did knock, however, your voices were so loud that you missed it!
Sara-san, why are you dressed like that?
I thought I would do it...
Could I get those back?
N-No, this isn't...
This is more of an education, or rather...
Hmm?
The other one is in such a place?
Huh?
That felt so goo- n-no! This isn't-!
You shouldn't use other people's things without their permission.
I think I'll have to punish you two!
We're gonna have a lesson like this?
We're teachers you know!
We have to teach things other than having sex!
It seems like your comments aren't matching what you're doing...
So Rio-chan! Start your lesson!
Y-Yes! So then, starting from where we left off last time...
The heading "mairesetetamawazu" on page 16...
This word consists of the double honorific of "se" and "tamawazu."
Touya-kun is staring at me down there!
D-Don't look so much!
It's embarrassing and...
Amazing! His cock is so erect again!
Touya-kun, lick me down here...
Sara-san?
I've put the other rotar in my ass...
I left my pussy free just for you! So come on, hurry!
S-Sara-san...
T-That's it...
That's it! Lick me deeper-!
Lick up all my naughty juices!
Sara-san... She's being licked down there!
T-The rotar in her ass... It looks like it feels really good!
N-No...
My body is heating up just from looking at it!
It's good... It feels good!
It looks as though Rio-chan wants to feel good too!
I want him... I want him to put his cock in me!
I-I can't hold back anymore!
I'm getting hot down there, I can't hold on!
Rio-chan! Say it properly!
If you do, I'll let you do as you wish!
I-I-!
No more!
I want his cock!
I want to put Touya-kun's cock inside me!
Y-You said it! Rio-chan, take your prize and do as you like!
T-Touya-kun's cock is so hard! It's hard and big!
I-I'm going to put it in okay, Touya-kun? Please watch me...
O-Okay-!
It's so hot! My pussy feels good, it feels so good!
Your dick is amazing! Can you see where we're connected?
R-Rio-san... Rio-san, your insides are tight! It's rubbing against me!
I can see your lascivious body clinging onto me!
No! Don't say such things! It's too embarrassing!
I can't stop, I can't stop myself!
Even though it's embarrassing, it feels too good to stop!
I-I'm starting to feel more aroused when I watch Rio-chan act so turned on!
Touya-kun! You're slacking down here!
Please thrust your tongue into me! Lick me in my deepest spots!
That's it! It's coming-! My ass is-!
Even my pussy feels tingly! So good!
T-Touya-kun! Thrust me more! More! Mess me up here!!
It's big... It's big, it's so big!
Touya-kun, you're cock is twitching, it's getting large inside me!
When we cum, let's do it at the same time!
Let it out inside me! Give me lots, let out a ton!
I'm gonna-! I'm gonna cum! Something large is coming!
Let it out inside me! Fill up my uterus!
I-I-I'm coming~!!!
Of course, this is not the end...
Tomorrow, my sexual lessons will be awaiting again.