Good morning.
Ah Oka! Welcome back!
Hi.
Are you all better now?
Yeah.
Chief Okasaki, are you sure you’re ready to come back to work?
Yeah. Guess so.
But I’m glad that the surgery went well.
You weren’t allowed visitors for so long that we all got worried about you.
Sorry to have worried you all.
I’m back to push you hard now, so brace yourselves.
Aw, be gentle, Chief.
About that...
I’m not your “Chief” anymore. I’m your “Producer”.
Oh yeah, forgot.
Sorry about that.
Oh yeah, by the way, why did Haruna-san suddenly get sent off on assignment?
Not sure.
Tabita! Are ya gonna slack off all day?
I ain’t slacking off...
Don’t you talk back to me!
Guess there was no need to panic and buy these.
I’m surprised to be sitting in this seat again.
It seems God wasn’t ready to cut me off yet.
Or maybe not...
I don’t think God would show any mercy to a gang boss.
It might be more proper to say that the Devil helped me with this one.
Fine by me.
I’ll use the Devil for my means if that’s the case.
And I’ll get even more power and money than before.
Slave Caster
~Lewd Trap~
W
Higahara
A transfer?
That’s right.
But why?
Why?
Don’t tell me you FORGOT about the fiasco that happened on your prime time news cast?
Shimura Yumi is still new.
I admit she made some mistakes on air, but calling it a “fiasco” is a bit much.
Do you understand what it is exactly that keeps a production afloat?
It’s the sponsors. Sponsors.
If we lose our sponsors, we can’t make a TV program anymore.
Because of her, our ratings for the prime time news have plunged.
This also means that the viewership of our sponsors’ commercials has plunged.
This is a serious problem that YOU are responsible for.
But she's made many little mistakes before and you never mentioned transferring her until today!
This has already been decided, Haruna.
You will be transferred immediately.
I will see to it personally that the evening news is wrapped up.
Wrapped up?
Just a minute, there’s no need to cancel the program!
I have nothing more to say to you.
Go back and pack your things.
Something stinks...
His reasoning is too cruel and illogical.
And speaking of stinky, I still don’t understand why Okazaki was made the producer.
I thought he’d follow in my footsteps and become a director.
Okazaki, eh?
He’s been acting strange for a while now.
Like there’s something on his mind.
And another strange one is Shiratori Mariko.
Something stinks.
I need to draw up a plan for a new program.
A kind of program that can really showcase Mariko in a way the evening news couldn’t...
Well. I can always plan that later.
Shiratori Mariko
What’s wrong?
Has it been so long that you’ve forgotten the face of your master?
Mariko...
That is not true.
Is your health okay now?
Yes, very.
Now I can continue to take care of you.
We haven’t fucked since before I was hospitalized.
You’ll have to drink it all.
That’s right.
Very good, Mariko.
It’s... I’m cumming, Mariko.
How was it?
Was it delicious?
Yes.
You’re soaking wet, Mariko.
You want it that bad?
What’s wrong?
Have you forgotten what you’re supposed to say when you want it?
Master...
Master, I want your hard dick to bang up my pussy.
If you really want it that badly, why don’t you put it in yourself?
Harder... Harder.
Move your hips more.
Very nice, Mariko.
Your hip movements and the tightness of your pussy are your best attributes.
I’m cumming, Mariko.
I’m shooting it all inside of you.
No! I’m begging you!
Not inside...!
It’s coming.
No!
Are you leaving, Okazaki-san?
Oh, Haruna.
Hi, Okazaki.
There’s something I wanted to ask you.
What about?
It’s about my transfer.
You know something, don’t you?
Can you tell me?
You don’t need to hide it.
I won’t do anything to hurt you.
But I’m not hiding any...
Tell me, Okazaki!
I told you, I don’t know anything.
I’m sure you heard the reason when it was ordered.
But I want to know the real reason.
My gut is telling me something is up. I know there’s more to this than what I was told.
I also know that YOU’RE involved in it.
You need to stop asking so many questions...
Unless you want a worse fate than a transfer.
Well, go ahead and snoop around all you want.
I doubt you’ll find anything.
I KNOW I will find something.
Mark my words.
Production Department
What’s up?
You’re early today.
Mast...!
I mean, Producer Okazaki...
You’re a little early for rehearsal.
Um... yes.
Sorry to intrude.
Haruna...
Hi there, you two.
Shiratori-san, sorry about that.
I wish the evening news didn’t have to end.
I hope you get a good part on another program.
Thanks.
Good luck to you too, Okazaki.
We’re expecting great things from you.
See you later.
Excuse me.
That Haruna...
Taking a sweet and friendly attitude with me...
No! I’m begging you, not inside!
I suppose it’s a nice change that she’s finally putting up a little fight.
Hey there, Bastard.
It’s been a while, Onuki.
You really are a strange creature.
I thought for sure you’d die from that mysterious illness.
Sorry to disappoint you.
But I sure am jealous.
A producer can sit at his desk and sip coffee all day and keep getting raises.
Yeah. And my subordinates are hard workers, so it’s even easier on me.
Do you still intend to carry out your duties with the mob as well?
Yes, I do.
Listen, I just set two goons on that writer you were supposed to take care of.
I told them to train Yukimura Kaori.
And both of them gave me the go ahead.
They trust me.
Like someone else I could mention.
I agree, I’m confident you can take care of Kaori.
But the real issue is, those goons don’t really like the idea of working for you.
Though I don’t blame them.
You’re the one who slipped out of the Kaori case and used gang money for a personal surgery!
It’s because I have no real interest in Kaori.
It’s tough for me to devote myself to a job I care nothing about.
But if you defy the gang, they’ll kill you to keep you quiet!
Oh, that’s too bad.
I guess it’s not bad.
If you die, the gang and myself will be better off.
And your TV station will be better off without their producer that does nothing.
But can I really die without inflicting harm on anyone else?
Is that because the weather has been so nice lately?
Your life is short.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
YOUR life is short.
Mr Onuki.
Okazaki thinks he’s so amazing with that stupid smug smile on his face!
Kaori!
Yes!
Do you remember Okazaki?
That asshole.
Yes...
He said he wasn’t interested in you.
He said he didn’t care when I told him that I was in charge of you now.
Shit, he made such a fool out of me.
Shit!
That hurts...
Okazaki, you little shit.
You dickhole!
Not yet. Don’t think it’s over now.
You’re gonna DIE, Okazaki.
I’ll fucking KILL you!
Please have mercy... mercy, Master...
It will take more than that to calm my anger.
Don’t you forget it. Don’t you forget it, Okazaki.
Okazaki... Okazaki!
Bring it on.
I’ll turn you into a lady who cries and begs me to let Okazaki’s laughably small dick fuck you.
Then you’ll get canned.
Have you heard of the producer Okazaki?
Yes, I have.
He uses this exit when he leaves for the day, doesn’t he?
Yes, he does.
Do you know what time that happens?
I don’t know that much... but I do know that he uses this door a lot.
Then, is he ever with someone?
For example, does a strange looking man meet him here?
Now that you mention it, every time he leaves, a woman leaves right after him.
Could they all be the same woman?
Not sure.
Though I get the feeling they were all really hot.
I see.
Thanks for your help.
And keep up the good work.
He was asking questions through the backdoor...
There must be some sort of information he’s looking for.
Hello?
This is Okazaki.
I have a favor to ask...
Got it.
We’ll meet at the usual place.
Ah yes, and one more thing.
The security guard stationed at the back exit... Get rid of him for me.
No more, Master!
I can’t... I can’t...!
If you... go that deep... I’ll cum right away.
I’m cumming too.
Take all of it in.
Oh, Master!
Producer Okazaki is here to see you, Chief.
Excuse me.
What do you want?
There’re some questions about Okazaki that I want answered.
Did he do something wrong?
Don’t you think he’s not qualified to be a producer?
How so?
He has no passion or interest in his job.
And he uses the services of strange women and is embezzling the profits.
He ignores orders from the gang and TV station and is turning his female employees into sex slaves.
That is why I think it would be best to eject him from the gang as soon as possible.
Onuki-kun.
Yes?
This will eliminate my problems.
And my profits will double, too.
Okazaki is doing good work.
There is no need to demote him or eliminate him.
But why?!
Okazaki is betraying the trust of this gang!
Nothing good will come from leaving him be!
Forget about Okazaki and continue Yukimura Kaori’s training.
Aren’t you a little too soft on her?
The last blowjob she gave me was weak.
But Chief!
Onuki-kun.
Don’t have any more dealings with Okazaki from now on.
Understood?
I understand.
Excuse me.
Hello?
That asshole.  He smiled!
He’s mocking me!
If the boss won’t get rid of him, I will.
I’ll fucking kill him!
You’ll DIE, Okazaki!
Zun Kikki
Thanks for coming out today!
Well! Let’s say goodbye with some exercises!
You like that?
You dirty whore.
Keep this on at all times under your costume.
It’s a special toy that keeps the motor constantly running against your clit.
Show me a little more spunk, okay?
Oh my?
Kaori, what’s wrong?
You don’t look very happy.
Give me a happy dance, okay?
Yay!
Hurry... hurry and finish...
All done!
Hurry... hurry and finish.
Hey, kids, thanks for coming!
Today’s guest was Yukimura Kaori-chan!
Currently not in use
Please use a different bathroom.
No...
Please, let me go.
Oh dear, you’re pissing yourself?
What a nasty ass you’ve got.
I’m begging you...
If you push, it’ll come out.
Let it come out, then.
You’ll be relieved.
Oh no... It’s coming... No!
Wow, you’re really letting that piss fly.
No! Don’t watch!
Don’t lie to me.
The idea of me watching you piss really gets you off, doesn't it?
Maybe I should show this tape to Okazaki.
If he wants it, I’ll shove it in his mouth.
Okazaki and Shiraki, eh?
A two-shot of a producer and a popular actress.
That’d make an interesting picture.
I can use it.
I can definitely use this.
Now which magazine should I sell this to?
Onuki-kun.
Ch-Chief...
What is it?
Just a little something...
You’re walking around with a video camera?
Is there anything interesting on here?
Onuki-kun, I thought I told you to stay away from Okazaki.
Well... err...
I’m confiscating this from you.
Ah yes.
Be sure to keep me updated on Yukimura Kaori’s training.
Shit.
Very nice, Kaori.
Very good, sir.
Very nicely done, Kaori.
The Chief would never dream she’d bug him while they fucked.
There’s something going on between the Chief and Okazaki.
When I was taping Okazaki, the Chief conveniently showed up to take away the camera.
That would NEVER happen by coincidence.
Chief, Producer Okazaki is here to see you.
Okazaki is?
Let him in.
As you wish, sir.
Excuse me.
What is it?
I was told you wanted to see me.
You were? But I didn’t summon you.
Is that so...
I apologize, sir.
I guess I misheard.
Never mind. Don’t worry about it.
There’s something I want to ask you...
Chief, shall we have this conversation elsewhere?
This room is buzzing with annoying flies.
“Flies”?
Come, Chief.
Let’s go to a place where there aren’t any annoying and stupid flies like Onuki zipping around.
Maybe to a coffee shop.
Good idea.
I was just about to take a break anyway.
Could it be... they found out I’m bugging them?
Yeah, right.
Just a coincidence.
He really is annoying.
I’d better get rid of him as soon as possible.
Mariko, are you here?
Master... please put this inside me.
Master!
Please let out your hot self inside me!
I had originally planned to cut down on my secret jobs to make life easier...
So just one second with me makes her happy, eh?
From Haruna
Meet me tonight
at 9pm at the
restaurant, “Grand Basil”.
I’ll text you the address later.
Mariko-san.
Why are you going this way?
Just something...
We’re already closed here.
Enter from the back, please.
Is it already that late?
I can’t use the company taxi.
Thank you.
Um, Adachi-k...
Don’t even try.
I already have orders for where to take you.
Shiratori Mariko
Good evening.
I’m Shiratori Mariko and this is Prime Time News.
Our broadcast begins today with the ship that crashed at 2pm this afternoon.
And here’s a special bulletin.
Regarding the serial arsonist in Tokyo.
It turned out to be a four-member gang of students.
They were otherwise good students.
The motive for their crime is currently under investigation.
For the Asian tournament to be held in China next week,
Japan’s representative arrived in China today at Seishimura.
Japan’s representative will enter the stadium tomorrow and begin training.
Starting last we... last week, the Sumo wrestling festival, was unable to progress.
Those in charge were...
Excuse me. The tournament was rescheduled.
No!
And now, here’s the weather report.
Oh no... no more...
Kaori!
Yes!
Do you remember Okazaki?
That fucking asshole.
Yes...
He said he wasn’t interested in you.
He said he didn’t care when I told him that I was in charge of you now.
Shit, he made such a fool out of me.
Shit!
That hurts...
Okazaki, you little shit.
You dickhole!
Master...
Master, please shove your mighty rod inside me!
Yes! You’re so wonderful.
Master... I... I...
Master...
Not yet. Don’t think it’s over now.
You’ll fucking DIE, Okazaki.
I’ll KILL you!
I’m so sorry... have mercy, Master...
It takes much more than this to calm my anger.
Don’t you forget it. Don’t you forget it, Okazaki.
Okazaki... Okazaki!
Bring it on.
I’ll turn you into a slave who cries and begs me to let Okazaki’s laughably small dick fuck you.
Then you’ll get canned.
Have you heard of the producer Okazaki?
Yes, I have.
He uses this exit when he leaves for the day, doesn’t he?
Yes, he does.
Do you know about what time?
I don’t know that much... but I do know that he uses this door a lot.
Then, is he ever with someone?
Like, does a strange looking man meet him here?
Now that you mention it, every time he leaves, a woman leaves right after him.
Could they all be the same woman?
Not sure.
Though I get the feeling they were all very hot.
I see.
Thanks for your help.
And keep up the good work.
He was asking questions through the backdoor...
There must be some sort of information he’s looking for.
Hello?
This is Okazaki.
I have a favor to ask...
Got it.
We’ll meet at the usual place.
Ah yes, and one more thing.
The security guard stationed at the back exit... Get rid of him for me.
No more, Master!
I can’t... I can’t...!
If you... go that deep... I’ll cum right away.
I’m cumming too.
Take all of it in.
Oh, Master!
Producer Okazaki is here to see you, Chief.
Excuse me.
What do you want?
There’re some questions about Okazaki that I want answered.
Did he do something wrong?
Don’t you think he’s not qualified to be a producer?
How so?
He has no passion or interest in his job.
And he uses the services of strange women and is embezzling the profits.
He ignores orders from the gang and the TV station and is turning his female employees into sex slaves.
That’s why I think it would be best to eject him from the gang as soon as possible.
Onuki-kun.
Yes?
This will get rid of my problems.
And my profits will double, too.
Okazaki is doing good work.
There is no need to demote him or eliminate him.
But why?!
Okazaki is betraying the trust of this gang!
Nothing good will come from leaving him be!
Forget about Okazaki and continue training Yukimura Kaori’s training.
Aren’t you a little too soft on her?
The last blowjob she gave me was weak.
But Chief!
Onuki-kun.
Don’t have any more dealings with Okazaki from now on.
Understood?
I understand.
Excuse me.
Hello?
That asshole.  He smiled!
He’s mocking me!
If the boss won’t get rid of him, I will.
I’ll fucking kill him!
You’re fucking DEAD, Okazaki!
Thanks for coming out today!
Zun Kikki
Well! Let’s say goodbye with some exercises!
You like that?
You dirty whore.
Keep this on at all times under your costume.
It’s a special toy that keeps the motor constantly running against your clit.
All done!
Hurry... hurry and finish.
Hey, kids, thanks for coming!
Today’s guest was Yukimura Kaori-chan!
Currently not in use
Please use a different bathroom.
No...
Please, let me go.
Oh dear, you’re pissing yourself?
What a nasty ass you’ve got.
I’m begging you...
If you push, it’ll come out.
Let it come out, then.
You’ll be relieved.
Oh no... It’s coming... No!
Wow, you’re letting your piss fly.
No! Don’t watch!
Don’t lie to me.
Me watching you piss really gets you off.
Maybe I should show this tape to Okazaki.
If he wants it, I’ll shove it in his mouth.
You’re late, Mariko.
I apologize, Master.
Now, don’t worry.
I pet my horses, I don’t kick them.
I’ve been neglecting you lately, haven’t I.
I’ll make up for that plenty today.
Oh no!
Don’t!
Did you cum already?
Don’t you want me now?
I’ll make you cum even more, Mariko.
Oh, please have mercy!
Please, stop!
Stop lying.
A filthy slut like you can’t say no to cumming.
Your insides are perfect.
Yes. You’re perfect.
Mariko, I’m the one who molded you into who you are.
I’m the one who makes you get off so easily, even in your ass.
You... You belong to me!
Come on. Suck it off like you always do.