Whoopsie.
Can I get a something other than this apron?
Th-This outfit is still a bit embarrassing in a way though.
This is it!
Hospitals equal nurse outfits!
This will do, right?
Yup, it'll do just right.
Oh my!
Wh-What's going on?
Gosh, forgetting the skirt... it's embarrassing!
Sorry about that.
There, that's good.
Wait, this is still useless without the top!
I can't change into two pieces of clothing at once.
Whoa! What in the world are you doing?
Just wait for me, Shin'ichi-san!
Oh no, this skirt is too small!
This is standard size you kno-
Shut up!
Doctor, I want your thing too, Doctor.
Doctor Amano,
stir it hard for me one last time.
Doctor...
I'm...
How wonderful,
Doctor Amano.
Huh?
Not in here?
Shin'ichi-san?
Are you not here?
I wonder if he'll notice it if I place it on his desk?
Oh, s-sorry...!
Umm...
You're kidding, right?
Flue, Flue save me!
No, no!
No...!
Don't...
Flue.. what's wrong with you?
No...
Stop, stop!
Wait, don't... don't!
It's in.
I'm being fucked.
It's pushing in me.
I'm sorry Shin'ichi-san...
My asshole that I haven't even
let you fuck yet is already...
Eeek!
No!
Jeez!
That'll be enough, Saya-chan.
Wait, no...!
What, what in the world is this?
This is terrible.
You lied to me about doing overtime!
You can't intrude while I'm feasting
on your beloved, Miss.
Th-This is...
You definitely did something to Shin'ichi-san!
Oh? Why would you think that?
See? You have that with you!
What I wanted to say...
... Is how are you absolutely sure
that he really loves you?
Because... we're husband and wife.
Then I believe you'll both enjoy this!
W-Wait!
Shin'ichi-san!
Darn.
Things have now gotten complicated.
We can't just let them be.
What were you doing?
That technology didn't come from Earth!
What do you mean?
In any case, let's follow them.
You don't have to say that!
Hurry!
Lusts, desires...
The form that completely pulls
out what's normally hidden,
how lovely it is to see.
What's happening now?
Don't tell me that's she's the fugitive?
So she wasn't alone after all?
That's not him.
In fact, it isn't even alive!
What? But...
That was the alteration chip we attached to
ourselves until we arrived on this planet!
That's...!
The Space Disk!
Shin'ichi-san!
Part of their organic energies are being sucked
out, however we can still revive them.
More importantly,
it'd be really troublesome if she were to go all out on us.
Your orders?
H-How?
Shall we try eliminating the opposition?
You don't have to tell me that twice!
Whatever happened to our guardian super housewife?
It's not in its complete form yet.
Why?!
Didn't you design this embarrassing outfit on purpose?
Arriving here in such a naughty outfit...
Seems you want to do some kind of sex play too, Miss!
First we'll have our graceful battle,
then I shall drown your body in pleasure!
Okay, we're in performance mode now.
I never imagined that humans on this planet
had the technology to wield the likes of us.
A miscalculation.
I have to hurry and save Shin'ichi-san!
No!
I'm starting to feel weak.
Do something about this, Flue-san!
Th-This is...
She's redirecting all the carnal energy
she has absorbed to us!
These readings...
They hold a negative property to that of normal sex!
Oh no!
I can't control and redistribute both
of these energies at the same time!
If this continues...
Mika-san will eventually incur heavy physical damage!
I have to redistributed again somewhere...!
Preparation complete.
Mika-san,
Mika-san, please fight.
We're going to attempt to disintegrate
the symbiotic entity on her.
Please help me out.
What should I do?
Please knock her unconscious.
How?
Don't I get a weapon or something?
I'm unable provide anything that
could cause direct physical harm.
Just give me anything!
She must receive punishment
for harm in my Shin'ich-san!
What the heck is this?
It suits you... here she comes!
You...!
Mika-san...
No violence, okay?
An... angel?
You shall now receive...
Punishment for harming my sweetie!
Hey...
Is it possible that those weren't the only
symbiotic entities that came here?
Well... yes.
Then, more things like this are bound to happen?
Yes, I suppose so.
How much of those strands do
I still have to collect anyway?
About... 700,000, more or less.
Seven...!
I don't think I can collect them all in my entire lifetime.
You and I will have quite the long journey.
Let's get along well together, okay, Mika-san?
So, I'm going to experience those
kinds of bad things everyday?
I wonder.
However, our top priority is to capture the escapees.
Dealing with these entities is just
part of our personal mission.
It's okay, turn it on.
Okay.
I'm, I'm already...!
you know...
I just saw an angel.
She looked just like you.
A cute angel...
Amazing!
It's the same one as the angel's, Mika!
Hey...!
Oh yes...
Amazing, this is amazing, Mika!
It's as if I'm having sex in a dream!
Oh no...
L-Let's...
Let's cum together today, okay?
I'm, I'm...!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
This is quite euphoric.
That was the best, Mika.
For me as well.
When did you put on that apron?
I'm sorry,
I'll take it off right away.
I guess it feels a lot better to have sex naked.
Mika?
Oh, come on!
But...
I think I'll love this!
Couldn't we have solved the problem
better if we teleported earlier?
Sorry... I forgot!
My Wife is an Angel?
Michael
02: Captured? Decisive Battle! A graceful transformation