As the train runs through the city,
you're hemmed in by a crowd of strangers.
A bunch of people you don't want to be touched by.
Even cute girls are shoving you...
You must not touch the skin of those maidens.
Nakabayashi Chika
Occupation: Office Lady
Blood Type: A
Hobby: Touring ancient ruins
Within this enclosed space within society,
This lonely city makes your son grieve.
Lee Honmei
Occupation: University Student
Blood Type: B
Hobby: Cooking
You're damned if you touch,
and you're damned if you don't.
Miyanomori Mika
Occupation: University Professor
Blood Type: O
Hobby: Listening to classic concerts
If you don't listen to me, "the finger" will attack you.
Chikan Juunintai
Ten
molester group
You're working hard even on the weekends.
Yes.
How is it? Is it going well?
Uhm... it won't have the result we expected.
I see.
I think you need to try another idea.
Keep all this data.
Ok.
Maybe the time will come when this will be useful.
Cryopreserve the specimen too.
Yes.
Uhm... prof...
How about having dinner together after this if it's ok for you?
My friend told me about this new chinese restaurant near by...
Sorry, I want to go home and continue my thesis.
I see...
I'll leave the rest to you then.
Good work.
Today again...
She can just have dinner with me sometimes...
*censored* *censored* Please watch your step.
A woman...?
It's alright, I won't hurt you.
It's alright.
but... no...
You're not wearing a bra.
P...please... stop...
Don't say that.
Look.
It's already like this.
Relax.
Leave your body to me.
Eh...?
I will make you feel good.
Hey...
Hey... just relax...
You're not wearing panties either.
Look, it's starting to feeling good right?
N...no...
Oh? Is that so?
Then why...?
Why're you already this wet?
Please hold your voice.
We're inside the train you know.
*censored* *censored* Please watch your step.
Why did I...
Why did I do that?
Next stop is *censored*
The door will open on the right.
Damn...
Ouch...
Eh?
You...
Come with me!
Lee Honmei
You're an exchange student from China eh?
What are you doing here in Japan?
I'm sorry.
If you're going to apologize then don't do it!
I'm sorry... It's just, I don't even know it myself and...
Suddenly I...
Let's talk a little longer.
Then if I can prepare 1010k yen, I can grope any kind of girl I like?
Well, yes.
I have 2 weeks stay remaining here in Japan and I need to go back to China.
But I have one regret (what i mean is I has one more thing I wanted to do before going back to china).
I beg you, let me ask this of you.
The next stop is *censored*
If you're going to *censored* line, please change cars.
I see, so she is the one thing you regret.
Yes...
Miyanomori Mika
She is your professor and the person who you like most.
Yes...
Why don't you confess to her immediately?
No... it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm going back to China anyway...
So I have no reason to be with her.
It's just... I wanted to touch her...
I think that's one of my problems.
It's alright for me even if it's only once.
If I can touch her body, I won't have any regrets in Japan!
Well, I'll accept it if you give me the money.
Hey, does she riding this train every morning?
Yes...
She's at the laboratory every morning at 6 am so..
Uhm...
If it's vacant like this...
You have to give up on the mornings.
There's a train coming in 3rd line.
Please stay behind the yellow line.
Does she going home at this time?
But there are times when she goes home late.
She is a workaholic so...
But at this time around, most of the train is crowded.
Let's do our plan at night time.
Eh?
Woman only?
It's off the peak time in the morning and riding the woman only car at night?
She's a tough target.
Uhm... can we do it?
Hmmmm, nothing is impossible for the Chikan Juunintai.
Here comes the Woman Chikan Juunintai!
Woman Juunintai?
Yeah, if it's like this, then there won't be any problems in the Woman only cars right?
So, let's begin our simulation.
Simulation?
6mins
5mins
3mins
2mins
4mins
Shibuya
Shinjuku
Ikebukuro
Itabashi
Juujou
Akabane
The door will always open on the right side.
And we can't stay long.
We much finish with our plan within 6 mins between the *censored* station and the *censored* station.
Doors open!
Target Locked on.
Ok then, think of me as the Professor and make your move.
Eh?
We must make a situation the same as the actual or else this simulation is meaning less.
But the professor is taller.
Shut up, don't be picky.
Look, time is ticking.
Yes...
Here I go...
No! You must start with the ass first.
It's game over if she scream because you suddenly groped her right?
Yes...
First, you do it slowly.
And gradually put more force into it.
Slowly... slowly...
Slowly put in more force.
You can use both hands.
Don't rush.
Spend time on the first move and...
Slowly... slowly... and add a little force and..
Good, at last you're going to grab the breast here.
First do it gently here too.
Ok.
To make her not panic, you must make her feel good.
You're a girl too so you would know.
Yes... go on...
It's alright when you come to this point.
Then go ahead and do as you like.
Your nipples are erect and feels so good.
Hey you...
Please don't move.
I can't do the simulation.
90 seconds remaining.
That's enough.
You already get the situation right?
No... there's still some time remaining.
Hey...
We're going to simulate the same situation like the actual one right?
Yes but...
How is it? It feels good right?
What are you saying...?
30 seconds remaining, prepare to withdraw.
How long are you gonna do this?
That's the withdraw call.
If you can't follow the order, I'm not going to work with you.
I'm sorry, I got fired up...
It's not only you but we also might get arrested.
Yes...
Don't forget your withdrawal timing.
If you think it will take longer, use that.
Ok...
Molesting is a crime
Target Locked on.
Kick off.
What are you doing? Time is ticking...
Sorry, but I'm not type of woman who gets happy when touched by an unknown person.
Lee-san...
The door will close.
Hey, why did you come back?
Girls, this is an extended game, 5 minutes remaining to *censored* station.
1 minute remaining till the *censored* station.
*censored* station *censored* station, please watch your step.
What are you doing? Let's withdraw! hurry!
No... I don't want to be apart from her.
What are you doing?
Damn... another extended game, I better receive additional payment for this.
There's a train coming in the 3rd line.
Next, it's my turn.
Eh?
What a cute ass.
I will surely demand better payment for 2 people...