www.SubDESU-H.net
Mistress...
Onee-sama!
Onee-sama's man-thing is going inside me...
Stop it...
Your body smells so good!
Indeed it does.
No!
W
Ikusa Otome
Valkyrie
~Twilight for the War Maidens~
Chapter One
「                   」
Cajoling
Onee-sama, you can't! Please return to your senses!
Father, please save me!
Onee-sama, Onee-sama, please regain your mind!
Your pussy feels so good!
No! Take it out... Onee-sama!
Amazing! It’s so hot inside you!
This is wrong! You can't rape me!
Odin-sama! I'm very sorry.
Mistress, you're so tight!
Onee-sama, you're hitting me so deep!
My hips won’t stop!
How depraved we are.
Onee-sama, I can't hold on much longer!
Me neither, can I cum inside you?
No, you can't, Onee-sama!
No, no, it's so rough!
No, don't do that!
Mistress, please bare my child! Please bare a war maiden's child!
No, I can't... it cannot be allowed!
Onee-sama, please don't cum inside!
Your pussy is tightening so much!
Onee-sama!
I'm going to cum! Please let me cum inside you!
No, don’t!
This is how the captured war maidens are “broken”.
It’s because I have their power source, their rings.
If you let them drown in pleasure,
without any rest, so that their power is weakened - poof !
Yeah, it seems so.
Are you listening, Fafnir?
Of course I'm listening.
Seems like you're doing a good job.
Duke...
Duke, please, let me rest for a bit.
I keep telling you, I'll let you rest when you've satisfied me.
My boobs, ass and pussy are all tainted by you! What else do you want?!
That's something you girls don’t need to know.
What are you saying while jiggling your tits with a man inside you?
No!
Reia, of all the war maidens, aren't you the one who is most consumed by pleasure?
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
No! Don't talk as if I'm doing this of my own free will!
Aren't you?
No!
I'm cumming again... I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Not inside again...
Intercourse...
Looks amazing...
I wonder what’s happening to me...?
After watching that Valkyrie...
Something’s... wrong...
Something’s coming... it’s coming... coming!
I'm cumming!
Damn it, I can't calm down!
Shall I do it for you then?
Fafnir...
What are you...?
So you were a virgin!
Stop it! Don’t say it!
O-Ouch!
It hurts!
Duke... it... it’s starting to feel good...
It seems like you're starting to like it.
Do it more, Duke!
Are you doing the same things to the Valkyries every day?
This isn't enough for them.
What they go through is a pleasure hell called the Torment of the Flesh!
Torment of the Flesh...
I can give you a taste of it if you're interested.
Oh yes! It‘s hitting me so deep!
Not there!
Do it harder, Duke!
Amazing!
Duke!
Yes!
Duke! Duke!
You're so rough!
Duke, I can’t take it anymore!
I'm cumming!
Duke, Duke!
I'm cumming inside you now...
Yes! Please cum inside, I'll take it all!
I'm cumming!
What's this supposed to be?
I know that you think I'm suspicious.
So I thought I'd prove my loyalty with my body.
How is it? I'm pretty confident in its softness.
My boobs feel so good!
I’m getting aroused just by doing this!
Your dick is getting all slippery.
It’s so perverted! It’s too perverted!
So this is the Duke's dick that Valkyries go crazy for!
Oh, my... how shameful...
How is it, Duke?
Does my "mouth-pussy" feel good?
You talk too much. Shut up and suck my dick.
Your dick... is so delicious... Just sucking it... makes me feel...
I'm about to cum!
I can tell. It’s getting bigger!
It’s okay. Cum a lot! Cum lots of semen!
My boobs are so hot!
Duke’s dick is making me... oh...
No! I'm cumming!
Thanks for the meal.
Duke...
Duke's dick is getting bigger inside me!
If you churn my pussy like that, I'll go crazy!
I don't mind. Drown in pleasure for all I care.
Duke, does my pussy feel good?
It knows how to please a man. It should be called "ero-pussy".
I'm so happy Duke! More! I love this dick!
Duke's dick is perfect for my pussy!
More! More!
Do it harder!
Duke!
Ah, so strong!
You're pounding my pussy!
I love your dick!
I love dick!
It’s making such a perverted noise!
Your dick’s rubbing against my pussy walls! It’s turning it inside out!
Oh, no... wow, this feels too perfect. Y-Yes!
So rough!
Make me cum with your dick!
No, no! I think I love your dick!
Duke, I'm about to...!
Let me cum!
Let me cum with your semen! Pour it all inside me!
Hey, Duke!
What is it?
Um... well...
If you have something to say then say it.
Well... um...
How is the breaking of the Valkyries going?
Very well, according to plan.
I see... glad to hear it.
Not only the Valkyries, but aren't you with Loki and Fafnir too much these days?
That’s why... um...
Could it be that... you want me?
N-No, you're wrong!
I'm just... asking as your guard...
If you want me, then you can come to my room anytime.
I'll be waiting.
I keep telling you, it’s not like that!
Duke!
It feels so good!
Even though I want to deny it...
Fenrir...
What’s the matter at this time of night?
Um, this is, well...
You want it?
No, you're wrong!
I... I thought that you were all alone, so...
You wanna come in?
W-Well, if you insist.
I'm just sitting next to you.
This smell brings back memories.
Are you okay with just sleeping next to me?
Of course! I'm different from the others!
I'm not addicted to sex with you...
I'm not lonely...!
This personality of mine...
I don’t even like it myself.
Even tonight...
To tell the truth...
I wanted you to make love to me.
So I came here.
Then enjoy tonight with me.
Why are you here?!
I was all alone too, so I came to the Duke.
What did you make me swallow?
It’s a cocktail of aphrodisiac and Duke's semen.
Fenrir...
My body is...
burning...
The winner is the one who makes Duke cum first.
Understand, lizard woman?
I'm not gonna lose to a wolf woman!
Your dick is too swollen!
Don't get so big!
Such a perverted smell... amazing!
Amazing. It’s grown so much!
You dick is delicious!
Duke's dick is getting bigger!
Are you cumming, Duke?
Hurry up and let out your semen! Hurry! Hurry!
Duke, I can't stay calm anymore!
My pussy is pulsating, begging for a dick!
I beg you Duke, my body is burning up. I can't help it!
Please shove your long hard dick into me!
You're doing me first, right?
It’s obviously me. Right, Du-
No complaints allowed!
Both of you at the same time!
I can feel it!
More! More!
Duke, it feels so good!
Oh no! It feels so good!
My hips are moving on their own!
It’s too good! I can't stop my hips!
She's looking at me!
It’s so embarrassing!
No, I can't take it. I'm gonna cum right away! Such a big dick in my pussy!
You're so tight, Fenrir!
Yes, there! No!
Amazing! Oh no... Oh, yes!
So rough!
More! Do it harder!
More! More! I’m begging you!
I can't stop my hips!
Do it harder!
Duke! Yes, there!
Amazing!
So intense!
Duke, I can’t...
So hot! My pussy is burning!
Yes! Do it harder!
So deep... it’s hitting my womb!
Oh no... It’s too good!
Duke!
I'm cumming! It’s coming!
I hope you understand, Duke.
The world must face destruction...
Beloved Duke.
Please don't die!
www.SubDESU-H.net
Tatakai ni kono mi o sasagete
I offered my body to war,
Kako o sute
forsook my past,
Ayumi tsuzuku ikusa otome to shite no kono michi
and continued to walk along the path of the war maiden.
Seigi no tame to oshi-goroshita
In the name of justice,
Mune no oku no yokujou ga
I pushed back the desires of my heart.
Mezameteku
But they’re beginning to awaken.
Yoroi o matoi mamori tsuzukeru
I put on my armor and continue to protect.
Kegare shirazu datta goro no
I used to not know what it was to be dirty.
Kizukanu uchi ni okasarete yuku junketsu mo some kaere
But before I realized it, I was violated and my chastity was soiled.
Yogotte yuku
Now I drown in filth.