Eh?! Hospitalized?!
Yeah. I'm going to have an operation so I'll be gone for a little while.
What illness do you have, exactly?
Are you okay?
Sorry, I can't explain now...
But I'll be back.
I see... I'll miss you.
After I became a girl, Sogahara, you really helped me out, and I still have a lot of questions.
And you know, what is  a period?
My stomach hurts so much.
I'll be back soon.
SubDESU-H Presents
T
akumi was
C
hanged into a woman
A
nd is fucked here, there, and everywhere
This is the tale!
Since then, I've always been with guys - whenever I had spare time.
Day after day I see more men
Oh no! This is crazy!
Oh, melon bread!
Please eat it.
Those guys are weird, and things started getting freaky. It was difficult going along with them at first... But...!
But now I am addicted to sex.
It's been over a month now...
My body stinks of cum and I think other men can smell me.
Every day I take this train, and every day an old pervert feels me up, and I like it.
I can't take it anymore, please fuck me like usual!
Eh?
Do you want to go to a hotel?
I think I can do this while Sogahara is gone. It's safe.
I can do as I please.
Okay.
Here I am, in a dirty hotel, having sex with an old pervert, I have no future...
You're pretty.
You're the prettiest girl in the whole world.
What did you say?
You're an idiot, old man!
Yes!
It feels so good, I feel like my head is melting.
Okay I'm cumming now!
All my semen is coming out!
Cum!
I'll fill your pussy with cum!
Very nice!
Does that feel good?
Cum!
Cumming feels good!
As I thought, you're cute, aren't you?
Hey, next time let’s go on a little trip.
Trip?
I'll call my friends and reserve a room at a hot spring,
We'll drink sake and eat and have sex all day and all night.
How does that sound?
I have no choice - I'm at the point of no return.
Today I'm going to introduce a special guest.
Wow!
How beautiful!
Lots of old men.
Um, my name is Takumi, and I'm his new girlfriend.
I called you guys here because Takumi-chan wanted to meet you.
I'll show you a traditional Japanese dance.
Hai! Hai!
Okay! Please clap your hands!
Hai! Hai! Hai!
Oh! I forgot, this dance needs this.
Eh?
This thing...
All right!
Yeah!
This is great!
I must look pathetic now.
Oh no, I think I'm cumming just from imagining how I look!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Wow!
Right on!
What’s next?
Show me more of your talent.
This is luxurious
Where can I eat?
Oh wow! This is so beautiful!
No, not there...
Hey, why not put her cum on the sushi, then eat it?
N-No...
Don't...
It feels so good!
Do you know about seaweed sake?
I'm... I'm cumming! I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
She’s cumming! She's cumming!
Do you feel good?
Yes!
So good! I feel so good!
It's different from boys your age, right?
Yes, completely different! Your tongue works so great.
Hey, you guys, it’s time to put your black sea cucumber in her pussy!
I'm so wet, if someone puts something inside of me... I'll pee.
Wow! Amazingly tight!
Young pussy is great!
I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cum-
Takumi-chan, I like to do it from behind.
Old man your dick is really curved.
Oh no, I'm cumming again.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Cumming!
Good...
Spermbucket Takumi-chan, show me your smile!
Yes, that's good!
You overdid it.
You should stop having rough sex. You need to wait until your body is stable.
Huh? Stable?
What, you didn't notice?
You're pregnant.
Pregnant?
I have a baby inside me?
It's been five months since I found out I was pregnant.
I've gotten used to this situation.
I meet up with some strange man from the internet.
Get in some stranger's car...
And I'm well aware of what's supposed to happen next.
Hi, I'm Takumi. Nice to meet you.
Your belly has gotten so big.
It must be difficult to walk around.
Well, a little bit, but I still wanted to meet you. So I could stand it for you.
Oh, you're so sweet!
Wow! Takumi-chan, you're really good at anal!
Who taught you? Your boyfriend?
I don't have anything like that.
It hurts!
Oh? You don't have a boyfriend and you like anal sex this much?
You're a nasty girl.
Do you really love anal sex?
Yes... I love it in my ass.
Yes, I love 'push push'.
Takumi-chan, you're drooling all over.
Because it feels so good!
Gimme a break. The bitch is pregnant?
I’m not a bitch!
Huh? What did you say?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm an anal sex-loving, pregnant bitch.
Wow! You look so innocent...
But you're sex crazy!
I'll give you a reward!
I'll fill your asshole with cum.
Wait, stop, don’t cum inside me!
What are you saying?
I know you want this, I can't stop now!
Don’t stop, I was just kidding.
Please, cum in my asshole!
Well, what do I do now?
Now I don’t feel like cumming.
No, don’t stop!
Hey, cum inside me! Hurry! I'm about to cum!
Please, 'push push' more!
Let’s stop today. I'll finish next time.
Hurry up, please!
Fuck me, I can pay you!
Hurry up and fuck me!
Hurry up and cum inside me!
Eh? You'll pay me money?
Then...
My belly is hot!
Wow, that felt so good!
But in this situation I really am just a walking doughnut.
I should think about...
Oh, I have an appointment!
Wow! A suite room in a hotel.
Wow! This is great!
This is the most expensive room in this hotel.
Come in, please.
I'm coming in.
I'm Takumi.
You're...
Long time no see.
You really are Takumi-kun.
So-Sogahara, you've been released from the hospital?
What's going on?
Your belly is so big.
How many months along are you?
H-How do I say this...
I don't want you to see me like this...
Why did you call me?
When I saw your website...
I understood your situation.
Anyway, I'm your customer tonight.
Customer? But you're a girl!
This is girl to girl.
It’s okay, don’t worry about it.
Don't worry about it?
But I guess you really like men?
N-No...
Wow, your underwear is really daring. You slut.
Oh no! You're already wet.
Oh! is this semen dripping from your ass?
It smells like semen.
Before you came here you had anal sex.
T-That's...
Isn't this enough?
No.
Open your mouth, stick out your tongue, and kiss me.
This is different from a man.
This tongue is small and these lips are so soft.
This is really a girl.
I’m embarrassed...
You really don’t like being with me?
No, it's not that.
I always had a crush on you, that’s why I really don’t know what to do.
I'm really confused.
I really wanted to do this, Takumi-kun.
I want to have sex with you, Takumi-kun.
Takumi-kun I know you've had sex many times.
I'm still a virgin.
Eh? Eh?!
S-Sogahara, wow! Your body...!
How about it?
I went to the doctor and got gene therapy as well!
I can produce sperm too.
Before you came to the hotel, my dick was so hard.
Now I can't take it anymore.
Wait, I can't take a dick that size!
It's too big...
It's inside! I did it, my virgin dick is inside Takumi-kun!
I'll finish quickly since I have been waiting for this for a long time.
It feels so warm inside you, it feels so good!
Takumi-kun, I'm moving it.
When you pull out of me I feel my guts coming out!
It feels so good inside you, Takumi-kun!
Takumi-kun I'm fucking you so hard cum is leaking from your asshole!
Holy crap! It's never been like this before!
Your body is really nasty!
Huge tits, cum leaking from your asshole...
You really love dick, don’t you?
I'm sorry, I really do love dick.
I'm weird, I really love dick.
I think I'm the only person who would love someone so fucked up like you.
I will, I will!
I'll be your woman.
So stay with me so I won't be alone anymore!
Please fuck me every day with your big dick!
Takumi-kun, you choose a man just because of his dick?
T-Takumi-kun, if you do-
Your pussy is so tight it's squeezing my dick.
Your pussy... Your pussy...
Takumi-kun’s pussy is great!
Love you! Love you! I love you!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming in Takumi-kun’s pussy.
Give me lots of cum! Fill my stinky pussy with your cum!
Cum inside my pregnant woman’s pussy!
Give me a lot of cum and I can be pregnant again!
I love this. I've never felt this great...
I love you. I love you!
Sogahara, I love you.
Hey, let’s do it again!
Eh?
Spring has come twice since I became a woman.
Wow this baby really isn't cute.
It looks nothing like the parents.
That's why I think it is cute.
Have you decided on a name?
The baby’s name is Ryosuke, Takumi-kun decided.
There were many paths I could have chosen from.
I should have done that, that day.
I wish this person would have been with me that day.
But I can choose only one life.
I think it's good that I'm a woman.
I finally think that.