Would you please stop it, Duke.
No more. I can't bear this anymore.
I see. So you don't care what happens to the land of truth, right?
Ariya, war maiden of the early morning moon.
No doubt, war god Odin will grieve.
The godly weapon you acquired will surely be destroyed.
I got it.
Don't lay your hands on the country.
I can't quit with that attitude of yours.
Open your legs and try begging.
You piece of shit!
Come on, hurry up.
Penis... plea...
I-I can't. I can't say it.
You'll say it!
Now, what's up?
Why do you want this?
Please put your... penis... in my... pussy.
All right. That's the way.
How thrilling.
Hearing these improper things...
...from a prideful war maiden.
It's ok. Raise your voice if you're feeling it.
Fuck you!
There's no way I'd feel good being violated by you.
Oh, I see.
In that case...
I'll be introducing another guest to you. All for your sake.
G-Guest?
You should know that one very well.
Your impression of her might be a bit off though.
Oh, that's unfair, Ariya.
Only you're getting a dick shoved up your pussy.
Let me introduce you to the Black Valkyrie.
Reia.
"Black Valkyrie"?
Reia, have you-
Yes Ariya, I have.
I served my master.
And I want my pussy screwed much more.
Reia, what are you saying?
Your nipples are so hard...
...you actually want your pussy done by Master too, right?
S-Stop it, Reia.
I can't believe it.
That cheerful and innocent Reia is...
Give it up.
This Reia gets aroused...
...just by saying obscene words.
T-That must be a lie. This just can't be true.
Reia!
I'm so sorry, Ariya.
I can't think about anything other than my master's penis anymore.
I'm a naughty war maiden.
W
War Maiden
Valkyrie
「Master, please forgive me for being naughty...」
Episode One   「Fallen Goddesses」
It all started when I - the Blue Sky war maiden - was sent to stop the war.
And he...
And "Master" tricked me into being captured by a band of Dark Knights.
Demonic Front Line Fortress
P-Please. Kill me!
Please kill me, Duke!
Ladies and gentlemen...
...take a look at this.
The last lewd war maiden that has fallen into our demonic world.
Furthermore, the City of Midgard will become part of our demonic world soon, too.
It's time.
This is the heaven world's most powerful war maiden.
Ariya, who has been bestowed with godly power by the war god Odin himself.
A-Ariya!
I never thought that "you" would come.
Is that the appearance of a Valkyrie, one of Odin's swords?
Be ashamed, Reia.
Th-That's...
Duke!
You will pay with your life for embarrassing a war maiden to this extent!
As to be expected of a war maiden chosen by Odin himself.
Coming this far with just one blow...
I swiped almost all your underlings away.
You know what this means, right?
Well, we'll see about that.
Right, Reia?
What?
Forgive me, Ariya!
R-Reia, what are you-
Let go!
Reia, you...
Even the heaven world's strongest war maiden...
...is just a normal woman if you take her ring, the source of her powers, away.
And it's even worse to have it stolen by your comrade, Reia.
So you're a traitor, too?!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Ariya, if I don't do this, many lives will be at risk.
A-Ariya!
We of the demonic world are almost there.
K-Kill me!
You'll regret not killing me now!
How admirable.
Reia also wasn't aware of being a normal woman at first.
Right, Reia?
Don't compare me with a traitor!
Whatever.
I'll just let this body understand.
Reia, begin!
Yes.
What do you think you're doing?
Please let me serve you, Master.
S-Stop it, Reia. Why would you do such a thing with your breasts-
What's going on?
It's resonating...
A-Ariya...
...this is a magic chastity belt that vibrates when Master is getting aroused.
Quit joking, will you!
I'm not joking.
I'm getting turned on...
...thanks to your miserable appearances.
S-Stubborn jerk!
Reia, what do you call the thing you're working on?
What?
Try saying it.
You're going to turn me on more by saying lewd words.
Th-Tha... That's... I can't...
...s-say it.
You'll say it.
You'll feel much better then.
This is a-
Stop it, Reia. Don't follow his orders!
I'm sorry, Ariya.
This is a p-pe...
A penis!
A-Ariya!
Hold on, Ariya.
If I make Master cum, the chastity belt should stop vibrating.
Hey Reia, there's another word that's even more lewd, right?
T-That's...
Wow!
C-Cock...
Cock!
You...
Ariya, I'm sorry...
The end, huh?
Reia...
Well then...
Show me what yours looks like.
Duke, you rotten...
Don't look, don't look!
A goddess' flood, huh?
Who would've thought a godly sworn war maiden would be such a slut.
Please, don't look.
Well it saves me a lot of effort if you're that wet.
You're not going to-
No, stop it!
There's no way that this big thing is going to-
How cute.
You and your pussy, that is.
You're wrapping around my thing.
As if you were longing for cock.
That just can't be.
I'll let you feel all the way inside.
Odin... Odin-sama!
A-Ariya!
How does it feel to have become a woman?
What's up? Your voice is messed up.
Odin-sama...
I... won't... lose...
How brave.
It's to be expected from the ultimate war maiden.
Isn't that right, Reia?
Don't look!
I'm sorry, Ariya.
Scream! Moan! And turn me on!
If you do, I'll stain your beautiful body with my sperm!
Don't. Please stop!
Please stop...
Ariya.
Stop it. I don't want this. No... No!
M-Master's so big... so big inside Ariya...
No!
Stop!
The body I gave to Odin-sama is...
Ariya's body is covered in Master's semen...
M-Master...
I am to invent a taming item?
Exactly. You should have had plenty of experience.
The wand of hymen recovery.
The drug for curing people with mother's milk problems.
You've even made medicine out of your piss once, right?
S-Stop it. Don't make me remember that one.
I won't.
I want you to use your experience to invent a new item.
"I don't want to".
...is what I can't say, right?
This is an order!
U-Understood.
But-
But?
Am I going to be trained with the item that I made myself?
Oh... I see I haven't told you yet.
The item is for taming Ariya.
What?
For Ariya?
What? Did you perhaps want it to be used on yourself?
N-No!
I don't...
I'm going to invent an item for Ariya...
It tastes like Master...
Tasty... so tasty...
Let me lick you more. I want to eat you up.
The item invention...
Are you happy with her doing it?
If it's about dirty things, I can do much better than her, I think.
Well, shut up and watch.
I have some sort of idea.
Please, don't look at this appearance of mine.
These subs were done by SubDESU-H.net. These ungrateful assholes just stole our subs.
Please punish the bad girl Reia!
Stop it!
Ariya...
So big, hot and twitching...
...it's disgusting.
Ha, but don't you feel good?
A-As if. As if this would make me feel good...
Come on, rub harder.
I won't stop until you've made me cum.
Fuck you!
Making me do this in this embarrassing pose.
What are you going to do next?
Oh well, that can't be helped then...
No, you promised...
...that you wouldn't put it in if I made you feel good.
My chastity belt is vibrating again...
M-Master is doing her again...
Yeah like that. Keep moving your hips like that.
Fuck you!
I'm not moving my hips.
Your body's honest, Ariya.
God damn it. Shit.
E-Even though this is wrong, I can't hold it much longer.
I'm so wet already...
You're good.
Try doing it harder. My cock and your pussy evenly, that is.
I can't do it harder...
Ariya...
M-Master's feeling it. Ariya makes him feel good...
Oh no, my fingers won't stop.
I-I want it. I want a penis, too.
I need it!
Here, look.
The spot where your pussy swallows up my cock.
It's a lie. A lie.
Can't see. I can't see it.
Now, take it.
Take my demonic sperm!
No. I don't want to.
You rotten piece of...
Wait... wait!
No more... no more...
No!
What's going to happen to me from now on?
I don't want to sink any lower.
Tch.
Duke could've just killed her.
What a hassle.
Oh, stop taming Ariya, you say?
Please forgive her. She can still turn back.
She can still return to normal.
In exchange for her...
...you can do whatever you want to me.
You're saying you'll satisfy all my desires?
Y-Yes.
Hurts...
Be honest with yourself, Reia.
In reality you just wanted my cock.
T-That's wrong.
I - as one of Odin's war maidens - want Aryia to-
Your body's saying otherwise.
D-Don't. Don't mess up my pussy.
If you wish for it I can become yours alone.
N-No. I... I...
Is it all right if I take care of another woman like this, then?
It's... not!
...is what I can't say.
Come on. Be honest.
You don't want another woman to be loved.
Y-Yes...
I-If you...
...if you belong to another woman, I won't be able to take it.
I knew it all along.
You want to be screwed by me, right?
Yes, I want to be screwed.
Duke, I... I'm...
Pussy... Please let my pussy be the only one to be teased.
Duke!
I'll give everything to you!
So please just look at me!
You've fallen, huh?
Eh, what?
W-What's that?
You summoned it yourself, Reia.
You're going to be reborn.
What? No way.
No!
No, don't come closer!
Don't come closer! Don't!
But...
...I don't want to give it to Ariya.
A war maiden being violated...
...having ugly emotion equal to a human's...
...armor dyed in black...
...the former war maiden is...
...returning as "Black Valkyrie".
Just as the legend said.
That's me.
The real me in an indecent armor.
Come, Reia!
Yes, Master!
This is how I became the meat for Master's purpose alone.
I have been reborn as a Black Valkyrie.
Everybody, please, have a look at our real appearances.
Ariya, a Valkyrie chosen by Odin himself...
...has a lot to show you folks.
To see Ariya-sama in that state...
Reia, what are you up to?
It's okay, Ariya. Don't worry.
We'll be showing ourselves to the townsfolk.
What?
The "us" when we feel really good.
Let's have some fun, Ariya!
Look. It's a special item made for your sake.
I hope you like it.
N-No... that thing is...
It'll train you... not gently, though.
S-Stop it!
No... Stop it!
Please stop. Stop!
Don't look. Please don't look at me!
Ariya-sama...
I-I'm being watched...
...in this embarrassing state... by humans...
It's ok. Don't push yourself so hard.
Ariya, besides being war maidens...
...we are women.
R-Reia...
Now, let's have some fun.
S-Stop it!
All but that...
No!
Oh no.
It's coming out...
I can't stop.
Ariya-sama...
Valkyrie-sama...
Odin-sama... please forgive me.
You squirted so much... it seems you liked it, Ariya.
Stop! Stop it! Please make it stop!
No I won't. Now I want to put it in, too.
P-Put it in?
What are you doing?
This is a seed that hatches inside a girl's womb.
You don't mean it's...
It's coming.
It's itching inside my stomach.
Hot! My pussy's so hot...
N-No way... there's this thing between her legs...
Oh wow...
Such a big cock.
It's so stiff, and it's twitching.
Oh my god... that can't be...
No... no...
I can't put it in if you don't make it wet, you see.
My bad, Ariya, but...
...I'll be the first to fuck you up the ass.
Your ass is so hot and tight.
I'll cum straight away.
My ass... it's in my ass.
Please stop it...
No!
What's going on?
It's rubbing against my insides...
How is it? My cock feels good, right?
Reia, don't...
What should I do? I... can't...
I feel so good... your cock makes me forget everything...
No...
I think I'm going crazy, too.
So good...
No!
Ariya, your ass is amazing!
Oh god, I can't... cock... cock!
Ariya-sama!
Valkyrie-sama!
Ariya!
Ariya-sama!
I'm... cumming...
Your ass is awesome!
I'm cumming... I'm gonna cum, Ariya!
My pussy and my ass are exploding!
Reia, I'm going to cum... I'm cumming...
We're cumming together.
The perverted goddesses are cumming together!
Ariya!
Reia, I'm cumming...
...I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Cumming!
My my, Odin's pets are covered in plenty of cum...
It's over if a war maiden becomes like this.
Duke, this is the nice idea you were talking about, right?
Penis... penis...
The day of the eclipse is arriving soon.
This will be their end and the beginning of the reign of darkness.
Ariya...
Ariya-sama...
Valkyrie-sama...
Ariya...
Valkyrie...
Wow...
Let's fall down... together...
...Ariya...
To Be Continued