SubDESU-H.net
What is the meaning of this?
Alicia, my dearest sister...
Prim, I apologize for raising my voice.
But...!
This is just too much!
It cannot be forgiven!
Prim, are you injured?
I'm fine, Alicia.
But I’m frightened.
Our forces are running thin in the East Woods.
Send in reinforcements at once!
Make haste!
Don’t let any more of them breach our lines!
The way things are going, they’re sure to send surprise reinforcements.
Which means now is our most crucial hour...!
My people... please stand fast!
Lady Alicia!
What? Preposterous!
Not even one has escaped capture?
Lady Alicia! Please be careful, it’s dangerous over there.
How could this be...?
No... Please stop it.
No!
Now, we're all eager to start!
To start defiling these pious sisters who devoted their lives to the goddess!
They keep begging me to let them fuck their brains out!
You bastards, how dare you...!
You are the Princess of this land, are you not?
Well, you have the best seat in the house to witness this.
This wonderful show that’s about to start!
Show?
That’s right.
These poor nuns were abandoned by you.
And now you get to watch them get gang-banged.
You fool! Stop it!
Violating those girls is something that is unforgivable!
Oh? Then, Princess, come over here.
And take their place?
That voice... is that you, Princess?
Please turn away from this scene.
She’s right.
Please, leave us be – you have important fighting to do elsewhere.
Just stop this treachery... stop it at once!
Are you a fool?
Stop it? Who the hell would obey that order?
No matter what happens, protect your subjects, and please fight...!
That hurts...
My virginity... my virginity... was taken by a monster...
It burns...
My loins are in pain... they’re on fire.
No... If I let myself cry, the Princess will be sad.
O Goddess, please bestow upon me the strength of endurance...
No... So dirty!
No... not there...
That's where I pee!
Why are you licking it?
No... not there... don’t lick it!
Your tongue – don’t slide it inside!
No... not there, don’t lick it...
I was raised to think that this is disgusting... but I...
My body is getting hot.
What is this...? It feels... good... Am I...?
Oh no, not there. Don’t lick it!
It’s going inside...
My body is... overflowing with juices...
I’m cumming... cumming... cumming!
O Goddess... forgive me... for soiling...
No!
Don’t... not there...
That hurts!
Don’t pull my nipples... my breasts will stretch out!
Don’t bite my nipples... they’ll come off!
A monster... is cumming all the way into my throat... and I feel like I’m going to vomit...
That hot semen... I’m being forced to drink so much of it.
So stinky!
Too stinky!
And it’s not only on my face.
My breasts and my nipples are covered in sticky semen!
No...
Please, don’t cum anymore.
It won’t go in... it won’t fit!
My breasts... are so hot...
This is stinky. Ew!
What a lovely sight.
These pure sisters who devoted their lives to the Goddess.
They’re moaning in ecstasy and covered in semen.
All lies... we are not moaning... in ecstasy...
Why don’t you understand that your moaning whimpers and gasps for air arouse males so?
Well, it does. It makes us want to fuck you.
N-No... that was not my intention...
Now, fair Princess. What is your next move?
Will you abandon them?
I would never abandon them!
Well, we’ll give you plenty of time to make a decision.
In the meantime, we’ll have our fun!
These sisters are just going to get fucked –that’s all.
Please, Lady Alicia... We beg of you – leave us.
Yes, please.
Avert your eyes and bear this with us.
Lady Alicia...
I know!
If I don’t withstand this, their sacrifices will have been for naught.
I know that!
But... Is this really for the best?
Is it?
If I let these girls suffer... am I a true knight?
Oh, the poor thing is crying.
Well then, I guess that’s our cue to get going!
No... Please stop...
No!
Stop it...
Oh? Did you say something?
Your voice was too quiet to understand, sweet Princess.
We surrender.
But that’s... too extreme...
Please, withstand this for a bit longer.
Lady Alicia!
We surrender!
Origa-sama, does this feel good?
You sure are a big pervert!
How are you feeling, Princess?
Minister?
What are you doing here?
This battle... I heard it ended when a bomb was detonated at the inside gate...
It couldn’t be...
Minister?!
Yes, as you deduced, Lady Alicia.
You bastard!
Have you no shame?!
This battle was certainly... certainly one that I didn’t have to lose!
But even so...!
You will now be used as prime merchandise, Princess.
In that letter,
I read that mercenaries defected to the queen in the West.
And that an abnormal number of new nations were being created.
And what Volt proclaimed was...
A nation of service.
A nation where all female inhabitants would satisfy the sexual desires of any man who came their way.
These subs were made by SubDESU-H. Visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I refuse!
I am sick of being used as your tool!
What is so amusing?
If you refuse, your precious subjects...
And little Prim might fall into trouble...
I assume you understand what I’m implying.
You beast...
How far would you go?!
I will not move.
I will not.
How vulgar...!
Will you reconsider, Princess Alicia?
I suppose obeying is... my only choice.
You are wise, Princess.
You understand full well that you are in no position to bargain.
Good.
It's a very good pose you’re making, Princess Alicia!
Perhaps this is... divine punishment I brought on myself.
For causing such suffering to my poor subjects...
I deserve the same.
I deserve to suffer.
What a wonderful expression you’re making.
Princess Alicia.
Is this my punishment?
This punishment... is just too painful.
It seems as though you wish to say something.
Won’t you say it?
Not... really...
A kiss... my lips...
Beasly’s lips are pressed against them.
I try to evade him, but... he bites my tongue.
I think this feels bad, but...
What is this sensation?
So hot...
I think you’re about ready.
Oops, what bad manners you have, Princess.
The real fun begins now.
What...?
N-Not down there...
Don’t rub...
"Down there"?
What is "down there"?
Well, it’s...
M-My... you’re rubbing that place...
No... stop!
Stop it...
That is... wrong!
No, I will not stop, Princess Alicia.
The two petals of your flower are rubbing pleasantly against my dick.
And it feels wonderful.
I’m telling you – stop it! If you’re that rough with me, I’ll...
Oh, Lady Alicia, I think you know full well what’s happening.
That a part of your body is undergoing a transformation.
Wh-What are you saying?
Then I'll make it so you do understand!
That hurts!
Don’t push it inside...
I think you probably realize now that inside of here is where your most sensitive spot resides.
I know!
I feel something getting harder... please, don’t rub it!
This is your clitoris, Princess Alicia!
Inside this little piece of anatomy, you hold the same capacity for pleasure as a man’s penis!
What? What?
No!
N-Not so hard... I feel...
Not there... not my clitoris... please stop!
Don’t! Don’t!
I feel something...
Can you hear your moaning? Can you hear your wet pussy, Lady Alicia?
No...
I don’t understand!
Princess, your pussy is dripping with love juices.
But...
"Pussy"?
My loins?
From my pussy... love-juices...
Would you like to see it?
See my dick covered in your love juices?
That’s enough!
Aren’t you satisfied yet?
Oh, please!
What red-blooded male would stop at this point?
Look at the color, the smell, the temperature, the firmness.
This is the mark of manhood - a cock.
Princess Alicia.
It’s so hard... and so hot... that I might be burned.
So this is... a man’s... a man’s semen.
It’s called a "cock"?
What a naughty sound that is.
A man’s cock.
I think I’d like you to make it so more semen comes out, Princess.
So... Princess Alicia. You must watch.
Th-This pose...
How dirty.
A man’s cock...
And surrounding it, such thick, hot juices...
Are those my love juices...?
What a sweet, fishy smell. That is proof that you are aroused.
N-No, it’s a lie!
It is not a lie.
See?
Well, well, well.
The insides of a proud, chaste princess are clear as day.
The thin, flower petals of flesh are a pretty pink.
Just kill me now – kill me!
Those words suit you, Princess.
Then I won’t hold back – I'll have my meal now!
Look, look, it’s about to enter.
In the proud and pretty Princess’s virgin pussy, a dark and dirty traitor’s cock is about to...
No, no, please stop!
Even your vagina itself is soaking wet. And just as tight as I expected.
I love virgin holes.
S-So tight...
Why is he so thick?
It hurts... I can’t breathe...
I feel like the core of my body... is exploding.
It’s inching in... inside of me...
That traitor Beasley’s ugly dick...
He’s stopping... is this the end?
Oh? Looks like I’ve arrived...
"Arrived"? But where?
At the proud Princess’s mark of purity... at your hymen!
Oh no!
You are quite the complainer...
I guess it can't be helped. Then I won't delay in complying!
No!
Oh...? My hymen... was broken... by his cock...
How does it feel? How does it feel to have your hymen torn by your traitorous Minister?
All I did was break your hymen, I’m going further in now. Go!
He’s going in...
In my pussy... his cock is going... deeper and deeper...
Now... Everything is in, Princess Alicia.
From the tip to the base.
But that’s not even the best part.
Oh no...!
If I hold it together, my precious subjects... and Prim will be spared.
No matter how proud and pure the woman, under her clothes,
she’s just another female eager to experience the pleasure and pain of a dick.
However!
I don’t want you to turn into a woman that only exists for animal sex!
I still want you to retain your pride and strength as a princess.
I want to turn you into a top breeding bitch!
Ridiculous!
That can’t be... you’re such a hypocrite!
Not at all. You will never leave my side.
And like a precious jewel, you will be polished into a prize bitch!
Princess Alicia!
A kiss... Don’t kiss me!
His cock’s movements... are different from before.
What is this?
W-While kissing me... he’s messing up my vagina...
What?
My body feels strange...
The kiss... and my pussy...
Something... something is coming.
No, this is different...
If this keeps up... being raped by Beasly... will make me cum.
Am I about to cum?
I can’t!
It’s a lie. It’s a lie!
No... I don’t want to cum.
But I feel it.
Your tongue, your cock, take them out. Take them out...!
I can’t take anymore...
Deep in my body, his thick cock is getting harder.
Oh, I’m cumming too, Princess! Princess!
I’m cumming... cumming!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
I’m cumming!
Princess Alicia!
Behold the splendor!
My semen is squirting inside of you!
It’s coming in...
From his cock... semen... coming inside of me.
I'm still not finished, Princess Alicia!
No!
I’ve been waiting for this!
For the day when I could steal your virginity, then fill your pussy deep with my semen!
Someone... help me!
Someone... unlock this...!
I can’t take it!
Don’t enter me anymore!
Don’t cum in me anymore!
Do you have any idea how long I’ve dreamed of violating your proud, clean body with my dirty dick?
No!
I will not let you escape.
Not until you are full of my seed.
I will fertilize you completely, Princess!
I’m cumming! I’m cumming!
No! He’s cumming... deep in my pussy!
Prim...
You... lied... to... me...
SubDESU-H.net