Tsundere Inran Shoujo Sukumi (Shy Slutty Girl Sukumi)
.........
I had to come to school on the third day of summer vacation just because I left my notebook here...
This year’s pool classes sure were nice.
W
Tsundere Inran Shoujo Sukumi
Shy Slutty Girl Sukumi
I hope no one finds me.
The stupid and thoughtless me who had to come here on summer vacation.
What’s that voice?
It’s coming from the changing room.
It’s a girl...
Is that... Natsumize Sukumi? She’s in my class...
This feels... great...
If I touch it this much, it’ll seep through.
Right here...
Feels so... feels so...
Good!
“Good”?
Wh-wh-what are you doing there?
Sorry!
Hey, you... You’re... something-yui!
“Something”?
Stop peeking in through the window and just come in already.
Wh-why are you hard?
And even worse, why is it out?
I couldn’t help it!
You were so... well...
So you were watching!
You were watching me masturbate...
You pervert!
B-but...
Who said it was okay to hide!?
Hiding it like that is in bad form!
Then what should I do?
L-let’s see.
Touch it.
Jerk yourself off.
B-but I...
You can’t do it?
No. Not now...
Okay, I get it.
Then...
Um, Natsumize-san, could you mean...
I’ll cry out. “Help me! He’s raping me!”
W-wait!
Then will you do as I say?
I couldn’t really tell earlier, but damn that thing is big.
Sheesh, for someone with such a girly face, you sure are...
Now, stroke it.
You’re actually doing it.
You told me to!
Well, that’s a boy for you.
How stupid.
And now it’s even more swollen.
What’s so exciting for you anyway?
W-well, Natsumize-san... when I saw you masturbate...
You are the prettiest girl in our class, after all.
D-don’t think talking to me like that will flatter me!
Then... How about this?
Well?
What do you mean “well”?
Doesn’t this excite you?
Well...
What if I do this?
N-now are you excited?
Yeah.
And what’s beneath...
Touching it directly feels so good.
Wh-what about you?
Yes, I’m very turned on.
Really? You’re really turned on by this?
Pervert.
Well, you’re making such nice moaning noises,
and you’re so pink and pretty...
Hey! Don’t say things like that!
Oh no!
Me too...
I’m cumming!
Geez!
Touching your dick in front of a girl.
You really are a pervert.
Yeah, well...
I’ve got it!
You should come here every day at this time.
Every day?!
Then maybe I’ll scream...
Okay, I got it! I’ll come here every day.
Good.
A white suit.
What’s it doing here?
You want me to wear that thing?
Yeah. I think you’d look good in it.
What the hell. I’m already wearing a swimsuit.
Why do I need to change into that thing.
Well, a white swimsuit is a bit special... I guess...
Do you have a school swimsuit fetish?
Well, I’m... yeah.
Oh, too bad.
Because I hate school swimsuits.
Ah yes, ah yes.
So that’s why your dick got bigger back then.
Well, that...
See?
I knew it.
You’re already so big.
Your body doesn’t lie.
It’s throbbing.
I guess you were stroking it like this.
What’s with that face?
Does it feel good?
So this feels good, eh?
Is this enough for you?
I’m saying, are you okay with just this?
I want your...
You want my what?
Your pussy!
I want to touch it.
No.
Why not!
Why are you acting like this?
Because...
Oh well, fine.
Wh-who said it was okay to touch it directly?
Oh no!
Now I won’t be able to stop!
Sukumi... I’m almost...
I won’t let you cum.
But I... But I...
But you what?
What’re you doing?
I want my dick in your... in your pussy!
Wait a minute!
Hey! Pushing me down like that.
Are you retarded? You pervert!
Sorry.
It’s a bit lower.
R-right there...
It’s coming inside.
It hurts!
Something so big is coming inside!
I’m sorry, Sukumi, but I can’t stop.
It’s so full!
My pussy is filled with your cock!
I’m going to move, Sukumi.
Don’t!
It’s spreading open!
It’s spreading so far!
I can feel it throbbing inside!
It’s moving.
The gross cock is moving inside of me!
It hurts, but it feels good!
I’m going to speed up.
Oh no! It’s my first time!
I feel so hot! So hot!
The penis is getting thicker!
This is sex... I’m having sex with Sukumi!
Shut up, shut up!
You are... not doing that!
Sukumi, you’re making such great sex sounds.
No I’m not!
Now it’s feeling good for you?
You think it could... possibly feel good?!
Pulling in... and out... no way it could feel... good...
It’s hitting so deep.
Hitting all the way!
The dick... the dick is coming all the way inside!
It wants my uterus!
Oh no!
I’m almost...!
Me too!
I think next time should be better.
Let’s do it again tomorrow, Sukumi.
Uh, so I happened to find this.
Stop being so stupid and take out your dick!
O... kay...
You’re a pervert who gets off on school swimsuits, right?
So why should I wear a school uniform?
S-sorry
There, see? You’re so stupid and perverted that you’re getting off on my foot.
See? See? See?
It’s no fair for only you to have all the fun!
That’s a mean thing to say.
Yes...
Oh yes, right there.
Lick it more.
Front to back.
Yes.
Oh yes.
This is very nice.
Sukumi.
Did you cum?
Retard!
Don’t ask me that.
Okay.
Sit on the bench and turn around.
What are you doing?
Shut up! And don’t look!
Okay!
It’s not because you’re here.
I’m wearing it because I want to.
Thanks.
No.
I’m not letting you have your way today.
I’m not the type to always give you your way.
I’m gonna fuck your brains out today.
Prepare yourself.
See? You’re coming inside.
Are you even watching?
Yes.
All the way inside... this thick dick is coming inside.
Do you like it?
It feels very good.
There’s still... more to come...
What’re you doing without my permission?
Sorry.
Idiot! What the hell are you doing?
Does this feel good?
I don’t... feel... good at all!
It’s so tight.
Are you cumming?
Of course... I’m cumming before you!
We came at the same time.
No... we... didn’t...
I... didn’t cum at all...
What are these things doing here?
Oh yes!
That’s my butthole!
So that was the dream, eh?
Why do I have to be fucked in the ass by an octopus?
Su-Sukumi, are you interested in anal?
Wh-why would I be?
What’s this thing?
Hold on to it better.
Huh? Where is it?
The tail and the...
Ah, here it is.
Idiot!
Why are you touching me without my permission?
Stop teasing... hey, cut it out!
Sukumi. Wear the cat ears.
Why?
Why would I...?
Because you’re going to be my kitty-girl.
Stupid! Don’t do more than...
Look, the ears...
Fine, I get it. So don’t be so rough!
Moron!
Sukumi.
If you’re a cat, then you have to act like one.
I won’t... oh, meow!
Your cock feels so good, meow!
My butt feels... My butt... so good, meow!
Does it feel good?
Of course it doesn’t feel good, meow!
Seriously?
It does feel good.
Having your dick thrust into me, Master, and having the tail in my asshole – it feels so good, meow.
Well said.
Here’s your reward.
Huh?
Come in deeper!
All the way inside, Master!
Thrust your thick cock deep inside!
This feels so great, meow!
Every time we move, the tail twirls and feels good, meow!
This is great!
Stir up my insides with your cock, meow!
This feels too amazing, meow!
Oh no!
I’m cumming, meow!
Meow!
It looked like you really enjoyed that.
That’s not true, meow!
Hey, that hurts.