SubDESU-H Presents
There is a luxurious prize for the winner.
Gambling is an everyday occurrence.
The loser well be devastated.
That is...
The rule of the underground fighting competition.
How unfortunate are you, this will be my 4th consecutive win.
Why...
Why am I being... with this guy?
Oh. . I think you’re not satisfied with this.
Queen of masochism.
I’m not a queen of masochism. . ah!
You feel it even though it’s a light spank.
No.
It touches the stomach.. .the cervix.
The pleasure is strong.
I’ll release it again inside and finish today.
Noo stop it.
No.
It's all blank inside my head.
And I’m starting to enjoy it!
I’m cumming, I’m cumming!
It feels so good.
Black Rose Side
Black Rose, she is a genius martial artist that mastered different kinds of martial arts.
But because she’s strong no one can fight against her in the upper world.
And queen of kokou who came into the underground fighting arena.
But she was even too strong here.
Because she gained many wins, a bet cannot be placed on a fight.
It’s been a while since the last fight, she who starves for a win today.
The audience who are watching.
The gaze.
I’ll monopolize them all.
Her opponent is the machine made by the organization which administers the underground fighting competition.
I don’t know if you’re an android but I’m gonna win.
What's with this response!
He’s fast!
This can’t be, he’s faster than me!
Damn!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
You’ve watched many fighters being treated like this right?
Stop...
You’re moaning even though I just touched your boobs a little.
I’m being touched by guy like him in here.
I’m feeling it.
You’re a queen that's always on the attack but you’re weak when you’re touched eh?
It’s not.
Then let’s ask the mouth in the bottom.
No not there!
Hey, this is not sweat.
I haven’t caressed you that much.
I think this wetness is not normal.
W-What are you... Ah!
No!
Not there... No...!
Maybe you started feeling it since I touched your boobs.
No...
I want to deny.
But I can’t say it properly.
No!
How mortifying, with a guy like him.
I am getting to know your true instinct.
It's impossible.
I’m an invincible queen.
I’ll give punishment to the bad queen.
Don’t mess with me!
Stop!
Hmmm you feel it when I spank your butt?
What is he saying?
Then what with this wetness?
That is...
Is the queen a masochist? Feeling it while touched?
Impossible.
What?
What now, you’re not going to counter attack masochist queen?
I’m a masochist?
No it's not that.
I’m a queen among the martial artists.
I’ve been watched by the audience, I’ve been watched!
No!
You’ve been watching many female fighters being raped right?
Didn’t you have any desire to be raped someday?
Okay then, the fight is finished, you being the loser.
This will be a service for the audience from here.
What are you going to do?
What? No!
Finally, it’s the time for queen to fall.
Expose to the audience all you’ve got.
To... everyone?
Your reaction is getting sweet and dirty.
Is it that good being licked while watched by the audience?
I’m not a masochist!
I don’t want to accept...
I don’t want to accept it but...
My body’s reaction won’t stop.
It will be serious starting now.
No... Stop!
Is that ok for you? The audience is watching.
They are watching, I’ve been watched...
Go cum as you are watched by the strong gaze of the audience!
I’m cumming!
Its hot!
Watch me... You guys... Watch me...
Even though you have many body guards, you’re only the one to fight in the ring.
I’ll finish this in one blow!
You’re naïve.
He’s different from the others.
What’s happening?
I’m being... I’m being...
There’s more.
Now!
How is it? Is it hard to breathe?
This guy...
No... No way...
It's show time.
Again?
I’ll tell you the reason how I got strong.
It's because the organization remodeled my body just like them.
How is the taste of mine which has been remodeled and got strong?
So?
What?
You feel it when you got knocked down?
You’re really a masochist.
More, harder!
Good.
You like it right?
Suck it all properly.
How mortifying...
No... Don’t lick it deeper.
No not there!
I’m going to release it, open your mouth!
Suck it all.
Smell of sperm of the man and this hotness.
It's wonderful.
I can’t hold it any longer, my body throbs.
I’m going mad.
Please give me plenty in here.
As what you said, I’m going to have fun in that place.
It stirs inside me and it's coming through.
Deeper, I can’t hold it I can’t.
I’m going to break.
How is it!? Let me hear.
The feeling of the dick being pushed inside!
This is my first time, it's going in deeper.
The dick is getting hotter and hotter inside me.
More.
Make it more intense!
Your pussy is wrapping me and getting tighter.
Here here here here here!
No... No.
Let’s cum together!
Please!
I’m cumming!
You’ve fallen.
Come here.
You’re going to shake your hips in the end.
I want it.
My dick...
I want my dick.
Is it good?
Is it good inside me?
It feels so good right?
More.
I’ll put it in deeper.
Inside me.
It feels so good.
Here.
It's coming... It's coming in deeper.
It’s going to overflow!
There.
Please don’t stop!
It's getting tighter.
I’m going to cum.
Please cum with me!
More...
Please make me feel good more.
Please.