Oh? Really?
Good day.
Hello.
Good Day.
Have a safe trip.
S-Sensei...
Study Room
S–Sensei. We might be seen by somebody if we do it here.
Don't worry. No matter what we do, nobody can see us here.
Don't tease me...
No...
Sensei...
I– If you're that rough, you'll rip my pussy apart!
There might be somebody watching from below.
Nooo... It's embarassing!
I wonder how a real ojou-sama tastes.
Tl note: "ojou-sama" means "Girl from distinguished family"
S– Sensei, y-you're hitting me deep-
You're rubbing against the entrance to my womb!
Noo!
Release your cum deep inside my womb!
I'm cumming...!
Look at how she's being taken care of. She's got to be a virgin.
This looks like it's going to be fun.
S-Sensei...
How is this, Sensei?
It's the best.
I'm so glad. I love you, Sensei.
Swallow it all like that.
That's it, good girl.
SubDESU-H Presents
「 Virgin Territory 」
Traditional and exclusive, Sakuratani High.
Without being from an distinguished family or having excellent grades, normal people can't enroll into this school.
It's a real ojou-sama school.
Daughters of distinguished families, huh? What a joke.
Sensei! Sensei! Look over here!
Sensei, I don't understand this here.
Ahh! Teach me too, please!
Yes, yes. Everyone take turns, okay?
Okaaay.
They really are just like bitches in heat.
Hey Sensei, pay attention!
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Kirihara-san is always like that, right?
She is, isn't she?
It seems she has a lot on her mind.
That reminds me. I heard that Kirihara-san is getting consultation in your office after school.
That's not fair! I want to go to sensei's office too!
Hey now, I'm busy preparing exams. Your next class is P.E., right? Will you be alright not going to get ready?
Ok... You're no fun...
Yes... Let's go...
Kirihara.
You look depressed. Is something wrong?
N– No, I'm fine.
I see. If something comes up, you can come to me for advice any time.
Y– Yes. Thank you very much.
Her response towards me has improved considerably since we first met.
Pretending to be a distinguished teacher isn't easy...
Come in.
Um, I'm sorry about yesterday.
Sensei, are you alright?
It's a good thing you're light.
S– Sensei! I'm sorry!
It's fine, Kirihara. You don't need to worry so much. I'm just glad you weren't hurt.
I'm also glad you weren't hurt, Sensei.
If there's ever anything, I'd be happy to help.
Y-Yes!
By the way, have you been studying for the end-of-term exam?
Yes. I'm studying hard during breaks.
You really are an example student.
An example student? Not at all ...
With perfect attendance and excellent grades, if this isn't an example student, that what would be?
But... I don't really like being called that...
Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
No, no. You don't need to apologize!
I suppose being called an example student would make you feel like you've got to do everything perfect and put a lot of pressure on you.
Sensei...
This smells really good.
Preparing it like this gives it the best fragrance.
Itadakimasu.
It's getting late, so you should head home when you're finished drinking.
Um, I... I don't want to go home.
Hey now, what are you saying?
I was just kidding.
Oh, I see. A joke.
I'm grateful to you. Thanks to you, my father has started listening to me a little.
I see. I'm glad I could be of assistance.
You're just like an older brother, sensei.
This coffee you made is delicious.
Thank you. So you liked it?
It has a really... gentle taste.
Ah, what?
My body is... Getting dizzy.
Looks like it worked.
Like a big-brother, am I? What you'd expect from a real ojou-sama.
Faced with a man who lusts after her, she has no suspicions and leaves herself defenseless.
Beautiful. She's completely different from the other bitches.
For an ojou-sama, she sure has obscene breasts.
S– Sensei? This isn't a dream-?
S– Sensei? What are you doing?
Sorry about this, Kirihara, but now that I've come this far I can't stop myself.
Nooo! Sensei! I don't want this!
Kirihara.
You're so pretty, Kirihara. I'm going to taste you plenty.
Such a pretty pussy. Even the hymen is completely intact.
I can take your virginity, right, Kirihara?
S– Sensei, what are you doing?
It hurts!
Noo!
Sensei! Please don't move!
Kirihara, you feel really good.
Please stop this already...
What a... pleasurable cunt!
Please don't say tha–
No– no more.
Sensei, please stop. This is unfair.
Your pussy is making naughty sounds while rejoicing.
Please don't say that!
It's trying to milk the cum out of me by tightening.
Nooo! N-Not at all...!
Don't be so rough... Please!
Nooo! I can feel it inside me.
So incredibly tight. My cock feels like it's being pulled off.
I fucked that Kirihara Group's overprotected daughter...
It's all over for me now...
Sensei. Why would you do this?
Kirihara.
I've been in love with you since we first met.
But relationships between teachers and students are forbidden.
But...
When I looked at your cute sleeping figure, I couldn't control myself.
I'm terribly sorry!
S– Sensei...
I'm a failure as a teacher. I'll turn in my resignation and leave the school.
Don't say you're gonna quit!
Can you forgive the me who did such a terrible thing to you?
Well, uhm...
Yes.
Thank you, Kirihara. I really do love you.
S– Sensei.
Believing such a lie... Just what you'd expect from an real ojou-sama.