I don't sense any chimeras around here...
Brain Jacker!
Did you find anything out?
I'm going to investigate this vicinity a little more, just in case.
You two search another area.
Got it.
Are you okay being alone?
I-I'll be fine on my own!
I'll be able to coordinate myself easier this way.
Jeez, you should really rely on Ryuusuke a bit more...
A-Anyway! I'll be fine on my own!
Sure, okay.
Be careful, okay?
I know that Ryuusuke is a reliable ally.
But, I'm still...
By SubDESU-H
Female Trooper Brain Jacker-
The downfall of Venus Rin = Kaifon
Pegasus!
It seems like the next general in line for the Rin family won't be succeeding.
You bastard! What are you going to do to me!?
Well, of course,
I'm here to retrieve that armor you have.
Also, there is another personal matter to attend to as well...
What did you say?
I thought that, as a tutor, I should teach you the joys of becoming a woman.
Stop that! Don't touch me!
Saying such silly things... Your body likes it, Ojou-sama.
Shut it! There's no way I would-!
What is this? No-!
I've already injected you with aphrodisiacs, Ojou-sama.
I'm sure they'll help you be honest with yourself.
You coward!
I won't lose to this stupid drug!
No-!
No...
Looks like you're dripping lewd juices, Ojou-sama...
No, I'm not!
There's no way I could feel aroused from your-!
What a stubborn Ojou-sama.
I know you can't help but want my cock!
D-Don't tell me that you're...
It's impossible! There's no way it'll fit!
Stop it!
Don't push such a disgusting thing against me!
T-This is disgusting, you beast!
W-What are you doing?!
You breasts are much better than those of normal girls, Ojou-sama!
Get that disgusting thing away from me at once!
Stop it! I'm gonna make you regret this!
You just don't seem to give up.
Your silky skin and lips...
They feel fabulous!
Get ready to have your mouth ruined, Ojou-sama!
I can't hold back!
Make sure you drink every drop of it!
No...
It's filthy...
We're not done yet, Ojou-sama...
No! Don't defile me any further!
No! Let me go, let me go!
N-No!
Now, Ojou-sama, let us become one!
It hurts! Stop it-!
It's splitting me! You're gonna split me in half!
Now you've proudly become a woman!
It's all thanks to my teaching!
You bastard! How dare you take my...!
This is incredible!
You're taking my penis in so easily!
It hurts, it hurts!
My body is acting weird...
Of course it is!
There's no woman alive who wouldn't be overjoyed to make love with me!
Stop with the jokes!
Why would anyone want to do it with an ugly monster like you?!
I'm an ugly monster?!
I'll teach you not to speak such lies again!
D-Don't-!
Don't be so rough!
If you do it that fast, I-I'll-!
That's a good expression, Ojou-sama!
Now then, cum while I plant my seed in you!
No! I don't want to cum!
I don't want to cum from a guy like you, but-!
C'mon, cum!
N-No!!
So good... It feels so good...
It's filling me up...
I'll be impregnated by this monster...
If we have a child, I'm sure he can easily succeed the Rin family!
N-No...
Noo!
Cum!
Cum in my pussy again!
Are you done already?
Hey, please keep playing with my pussy!
Are you finally satisfied?
What's wrong?
I wonder if Brain Jacker will be alright...
She seemed a bit strange...
Yeah, she wasn't her usual self.
Maybe we shouldn't have left her alone...
I must be strong... I'm Brain Jacker.
I can't suffer that humiliation again...
W-What the-?!
A chimera?
How did you get so close?!
What's this?
I heard that Byakko was defeated, so I was expecting something more,
but you went down pretty easily.
Damn it! For me to not see her...
Damn you! Let me go!
You shouldn't struggle so much!
My spider venom is a deadly aphrodisiac.
I bet you're starting to feel good.
You've gotta be kidding me...
Don't think that this'll stop me from killing you!
S-Stop it-!
Oh, what a nicely colored pussy you have!
Stop it! Don't look!
W-What are you going to do?!
Don't get so hasty.
Now, my children will make you feel good.
What did you say?
D-Don't tell me that...?! Stop-!
Don't put that inside me-!
Stop it! The scales feel too rough!
You moan well!
Do you want another one, too?
Stop with the jokes!
There's no way that it'll fit!
No need to hold back.
How's this?
It's splitting me!
They're gonna break my stomach!
Stop pushing against my deepest spots!
We're not done yet!
The ones who go against the chimeras don't get off lightly.
Whatever you do to me, I'll-!
Stop it-!
They might break through the walls!
It must be hard on a ruin arms dealer for them to not die so easily!
It's breaking me!
They're gonna break me!
It seems like my children have taken a liking to you.
You'll contribute more holes to them, right?
Can you see? There are plenty of them inside of you!
If you struggle too much, they may pierce your insides.
That's a good expression, Brain Jacker!
It looks like my aphrodisiac is starting to take effect.
It seems like you're finally being honest with yourself.
No way, this is...
C'mon! Cum from my children!
You've got to be a huge pervert to cum from being fucked by snakes!
I don't want to cum!
I-I'm cumming-!
I can't take any more...
That was pretty quick.
Should I play with you a bit more before I kill you?
Amazing-! My stomach is so full!
No!
How is it?
What does it feel like to be raped and impregnated by snakes?
It's great-! It feels so good!
It's incredible-!
T-They're going wild inside me!
You mustn't poke me that deeply!
My pussy, it'll...!
Make sure to get pregnant and give birth to lots of baby snakes!
No! I'll give birth!
I'll end up giving birth to baby snakes!
No! I-I'm gonna cum again!
What a great sight!
I want to show the others, too!
I'll be credited for taking down Brain Jacker.
All I have to do is deal with Soul Eater and Fujiwara Ryuusuke...
Oh! Our lovely Ojou-sama is in such a horrendous state!
Pegasus!
Long time no see, Ojou-sama.
You came back to me, didn't you?
Cut the jokes! I came back here to kill you-!
Oh? Looks like you've gotten some fight back from seeing your beloved man once again!
Shut up!
I... I haven't lost yet!
How pitiful...
Ojou-sama, you've been defiled by such repulsive snakes, haven't you?
I don't want to hear that from you!
Very well, I'll show you how it's done.
Stay away! Don't touch me!
Ojou-sama, there is nothing to be scared of!
I'll cleanse you!
What is this...?
No... I-I can't control my body...
Now then, let's make love, Ojou-sama!
No! Not with the likes of you...
No, my body is moving on its own!
This seems interesting...
I am very happy, Ojou-sama.
You've finally returned to me, haven't you?
No-!
You bastard! What did you do to my body this time?!
That's wonderful, Ojou-sama!
No matter how you look at it, she looks just like a pervert giving a blowjob!
I understand your feelings, Ojou-sama.
You can't wait for me to put it in, can you?
No, you're wrong! Don't touch me!
No...
Why... Why is my body...?
Looks like Ojou-sama's pussy can't wait for his cock anymore!
No... No!
I'm not like that!
Stop it-!
No!!
You don't know how many times I dreamt of becoming one with you again!
No... I'm being defiled again...!
No! Don't-!
It's tightly clinging onto me!
You must have been very lonely!
No-! I don't want this!
Yes, it must be very humiliating to be raped by such scum.
Should I make you feel slightly better?
You bastards! When will you have had enough?!
Poor Ojou-sama, I'll make you feel good soon!
No, stop it!
Stop thrusting! Stop making me go crazy!
It's a race to see who can make this lewd Ojou-sama cum first!
N-No-!
Stop it-! I'll really lose it!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum-!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
We'll make you feel even better!
We're not done yet!
This is too much-! Someone help me!
Don't!
Don't-!
I'm gonna cum!
My butt is full, it's so hot...
P-Please let me go, I'm gonna die... This is too much!
Mikoto... Ryuusuke...!
Now Ojou-sama belongs to me.
Now then, come with me to the flower garden!
Wait just a moment.
I need her chip before she goes.
Brain Jacker!
Brain Jacker, get up!
Let's take this scum down!
Roger!
I-I'll kill you,
so that I can live freely again!
No way, impossible-!
For me to...!
Ojou-sama!!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Your resistance just makes my penis harder!