www.SubDESU-H.net
Don't come any closer!
For me to be here alone with a guy...
This is really the worst.
No one will be able to hear our calls for help in this downpour.
Are you alright?
It will be bad if you catch a cold here.
Shut up!
Don't touch me!
Sorry about that, she can't really deal with guys, you see.
No, sorry for being insensitive about it.
Mealtime!
It's mealtime!
Original Animation
The Devourer
Tsundere Stocking Kotone
~Slutty Ass, Two Holes to Fuck~
SubDESU-H
This isn't even a real haunted house!
And it just got worse because guys are in here.
And I thought this was the perfect place for a few scares.
It's only just a little bit far from the main town, but it's already devoid of any civilization.
Living here would be just...
We're staying here due to the sudden downpour,
but maybe there are a few spooks out here.
S-Stop that!
That's just not true!
Jeez Mami, why did you join the mystery club then?
Because you invited me here.
And forcefully at that.
Well, I can't deny that, but...
A seemingly deserted place near school...
Kotocchi, you did hit this one right on the head though.
But my net research says that this is the best place!
Hey, I told you to stop calling me Kotocchi already!
Why? It sounds cute.
I want to go home already...
I don't care if I get wet on the way.
We even ran into a few guys who were lost too.
This must be really bad for a guy-hater like you.
I don't think it's safe.
You almost got too close to a cliff earlier, you know.
I also don't think it is, but...
It's been a long time, but I never thought it'd be like this.
This is unusual.
This will be fun!
Yes, that's true.
Wait up, Kotone-chan.
Shut up, don't act so friendly with me.
I'm really sorry about yesterday.
I really didn’t know.
Stop following me!
Hey, where are you going?
Can we talk for a bit, Kotone-chan?
No.
Why in the world would I want to talk to you?
Just leave me alone already!
He seems to be one of the servants of this place.
Wouldn't it be bad if you went there?
I told you to stop following me already!
You're trembling.
Wait, I'm not going to do anything.
But this cold weather is really bad.
Please, believe me for now.
How can I trust someone who carries on about falling in love with me at first?
S-Stop, let me go...
See? It feels a bit warmer now, right?
It doesn't feel warm at all...
I told you it could be dangerous.
But you just keep on going and going.
Let me go.
Can I get a kiss?
The thing about falling in love at first sight? It's for real.
However, I must also consider the feelings of the other person.
Are you stupid?
Hey, we're done here, right?
Let's stay like this a little longer.
Take it as a favor, okay?
You don’t get to just declare things like that.
Then kiss me.
Is there something wrong with your head?
Idiot!
Why? Why would you hate guys so much?
Why do I have to tell you that?
Cause that would make us even.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to push yourself.
I was kidnapped a long time ago.
Taken by a guy.
Stripped...
Fondled...
And then...
Kotocchi, are you okay?
Kotone-san, are you alright?
I was really worried.
I wondered where you had gone to.
You really went overboard.
Come with me for a bit.
N-Now, we're really even.
Never thought this would be simple.
Oh Kotocchi.
Stop calling me Kotocchi.
Wow, talk about being in a bad mood.
We were really worried, you know?
S-Sorry then!
Why don't you get used to it already?
Those guys don't seem all that bad anyway.
Mami, in fact, actually seems a bit interested in one of the guys in this mansion.
W-What are you saying all of a sudden?
Love at first sight, huh?
Looks like there was something good about this downpour after all.
Hmph, love at first sight is just...
Kotone-chan, are you planning on going to the basement?
Earlier at dinner you said you would.
You can't do that, you know.
Shut up.
I'll do whatever I wish like doing.
Then I'll go with you.
No thanks.
U-Umm.. I was just exploring the place a bit.
Like, I wonder what's in these rooms?
Jeez, why did you come here with me?
Let's talk for a bit.
No.
You told me some of the things that hurt you.
You see, me too, I think it's a bit easier for me to say this now.
Well...
I can't get it straight.
You are standing straight, aren't you?
That's not what I meant.
Look a bit higher, at my dick.
Stop kidding me!
What in the world are you talking about, you idiot?!
Pervert!
I'm serious here.
I'm in dire straits because of this.
I'm already at this age and yet...
That's why...
I'm thinking of what will happen to us due to this.
To us? There's no 'us' to think about.
I really can’t do anything about it.
That's why I just tried to suck it up and live with it.
However, after meeting you, I...
I can’t believe this.
I never really believed in love at first sight.
I'm actually surprised that it really happened to me.
That's why...
I feel like I want to do something for you, for us...
Don't just go declaring things.
That's just... Men are all the same.
I hate them.
Hey, can I kiss you?
Don't get cocky!
But, you did it to me earlier.
I did it so we'd be even.
That's all.
Can you really do that to someone you don't like, Kotone-chan?
Well, that's...
What am I doing here with this guy?
His tongue is trying to get inside.
We're really kissing.
Was this how they did it?
No, don't make me remember...
It's okay, I'm going to overwrite those memories.
No, what's wrong with me?
I don't like it one bit, and yet...
What? I-It's getting big?!
I haven't been able to do this in years.
With you I...
I get it already.
Just keep that away.
H-Hey, can I put this between your breasts?
Quit messing around!
It's all because of you.
I don't want to turn back anymore.
That's just...
Do I just have to rub my breasts around it?
What am I doing?
I think I've gone crazy.
Doing something perverted like this...
Kotone-chan, this is amazing.
I can't believe that I can get like this.
Having this thing in front of me, between my breasts...
Oh no, down there I...
This is embarrassing.
That's good Kotone-chan, I think I can reach my climax.
Keep going faster.
After so long I can finally...
Looking at this makes my body feel hot.
I don't like this, I'm...
That's good, do it faster.
Amazing, it's still stiff.
Hey, Kotone-chan, I...
No! Hey, what are you doing?!
Stop!
You also got aroused that it made you wet, right?
Your panties look really wet.
No, that's...
It's alright, I think it will be okay here.
I won't do it in your precious place.
No, that's not...!
It won't fit in!
St-Stop!
No... My insides are burning!
No, it's entering the wrong hole...
I can't believe this.
That thing is actually inside me.
Don't, it hurts.
Stop, please...!
What is this?
It's pouring inside me.
Something sticky is entering me!
K-Kotone-chan, I'm sorry I...
Just forget about it.
I knew it.
The other Onii-chan is enjoying himself.
It's been a long time.
I'm going to enjoy this bit by bit.
I don't want to be involved with you anymore.
Stop talking to me.
I'm really sorry about yesterday.
I haven't felt like that in a very long time.
I got too excited over my recovery.
D-Don't tell me that!
Stop saying stuff like that to me.
Let me go!
I don’t want this anymore.
Why...?
Even though you did that to me I...
Do you hate me now?
I hated you from the very beginning, stupid!
No, really I...
Why am I doing this?
W-What are you doing?
Stop this right now...
It's okay.
I'll be gentle this time.
What are you talking about?
It's wet.
No, let me go!
I don't want this!
Really?
No...
Kotone-chan, your heart is pounding.
That's, not true...
Just once more...
I want to do it once more.
Please, can you get it aroused again?
You're saying those things again...
I don't think I can do it with anyone else.
You're really getting full of yourself.
I think you're a lot better off with it limp.
I want to do it properly with you.
Hey, can you show me your pussy?
No, this position is...
Amazing.
I can see everything.
You really are a pervert.
Don’t!
It really looks lewd, Kotone-chan.
Is your hate for guys gone now?
S-Stupid.
I hate them,
and that includes you.
I hate them!
But you’re showing this to me right now.
No, my thing down there is being licked.
Your pussy is throbbing, and it's really wet.
No...
It's not...
What is this?
What's wrong with me?
I'm...
Ow, don't put that in.
Don't put it in!
I'll be gentle, it'll be okay.
It's a virgin pussy.
Don't move it.
Stop twirling it around.
Someone might see us here.
You're right, if we don't finish this quickly someone might see us.
No, no, not there!
Your love juices are starting to overflow.
Don't say that.
No, stop...
My mind is going blank.
No, don't push it in!
It's flowing out.
I'm going to cum!
Does it feel good, Kotone-chan?
No, it won’t stop...
No, it keeps coming out...
That's...!
No, please I really don't want this!
Kotone-chan, this is amazing.
It really has become aroused,
and you also feel aroused by being rubbed inside.
That's not true...
No, don't...
I can put this in, right?
I want to put it in.
My penis right here, inside this spot of yours.
No, you definitely can't!
I'll get pregnant!
No!
It's overflowing with your horny fluids.
Since you don't want to get pregnant...
No, not there again!
That doesn't go in there!
But you won't get pregnant here.
Don't worry, I'll take it slowly.
No, it's going inside my ass again!
It went in easier than yesterday.
Your ass must also be feeling good.
It's not, and it feels gross!
Pull it out, no...!
It's opening up, widening...
I don't want this!
Don't move, don't...!
This doesn't feel good at all!
That's not true.
Look, it's even wetter than earlier.
No, not there...
It doesn’t feel good, it's too hard on me and yet...!
No, please stop this already.
No big dicks anymore!
Does it feel good being penetrated here?
No, it doesn't!
Please no.
No more dicks!
Pull it out!
My ass...
Oh no, your dick is... My ass...
Kotone-chan, let's cum together.
No... No, this is just too harsh, too perverted!
No, I don't want to, but...
I'm going crazy...!
It's flowing inside me.
Kotone-chan, you'll have to keep all of that in you for the night.
It'd be bad if it leaks out.
What? You've got to be kidding...
Later on tonight, show it to me again please.
No, I can't keep this in until late at night...
This can't be.
This is just...
We can't go home again due to the rain.
It's still raining.
Hey Kotocchi, what were you doing?
Are you alright, Kotone-san?
Good night.
What's wrong? Weren't you going to explore the place?
You said so earlier during breakfast.
I'm going to sleep.
So no exploring today I guess.
I guess I'll just read a book or two.
Mami, you're such a busybody.
Yuuri-san, you're quite bothered too, right?
By that person called Kamishiro.
Wh-What are you saying all of a sudden?
I was just a bit curious, there's nothing more to it.
Yuuri fell in love at first sight?
No way.
He seems a lot more down-to-earth compared to the other guy.
It seems so, you don't see those types very often.
Yep, that's why I was interested.
Interested, huh?
What's with that tone?
Yuuri, has her sights on that person...
I'm quite interested you see.
I like you, Kotone-chan.
Love at first sight is just impossible.
It's all thanks to you, it's been a long time since I felt like this.
No, this isn't real.
I hate guys, I really hate them!
I hate him too!
Him too...
What is happening to me?!
This definitely isn't true.
Making me like this...
This isn't love... or anything!
This is the worst.
Nii-sama.
The girl in the basement is starting to get annoying.
She seems to be hungry again.
That was fast.
It's been a long time so I thought we'd enjoy this a bit longer though.
Let's put an end to this then.
Tell this also to the other me.
Nii-sama.
More...
Fill my insides more.
But that was really gross, right?
Yeah, it sure was.
That person then rushed towards me with a surprised look.
It was really scary.
You sure had a bad day because of that.
I know, right?
So what...?
In here.
So you really came.
You told me to come.
Yuuji.
Call me Yuuji.
A-Always doing what you want...
What's so funny?
So you held it in.
It's in here, right?
That's just because you asked me to do so.
Wait, not here...
I'm embarrassed...
Kotone-chan, I can see it all.
No, hey this is really embarrassing.
Hey...!
No, don't Yuuji!
Kotone-chan, were you playing with yourself earlier?
Your pussy is twitching and throbbing wildly.
I don't do that...!
That's just gross!
Oh really? I'm not going to do it if you don't tell the truth.
I don't care, I won't tell, I'm not doing it with you Yuuji.
Are you sure? It's really overflowing.
Do you plan on doing it by yourself again?
Again? What the hell do you mean?
A while back you...
I knew it.
You just can't resist it.
No!
So?
I don't want this, why do you have to tease me like this?
I want everything from you.
I'll do more than just overwrite those memories.
At this rate, my first time will be...
Am I experiencing love at first sight too?
You were also in love at first sight, right?
I... I said that's not true.
Even you are also interested in Kamishiro-san!
Mami, what are you saying?
I'm not!
For things to turn out like this...
This guy will soon...
No, this is Yuuji, this is Yuuji...!
Kotone-chan, I've thought of something that will make our first time more special.
Kotone-chan, you seem to love anal sex.
W-What? What's going on?
Wait...
What's this?
What is this? Why are you doing this Yuuji?
Your ass seems to be craving for it, I wanted to help the poor thing.
I don’t want this Yuuji, stop this!
Save me!
Your ass loves it, right?
Yuuji... Yuuji...!
Don't worry, I'll be the one to take you for first time.
N-No, Yuuji!
Please, stop this!
I don't want this.
I'm taking everything from you.
No!
It's rubbing hard inside me.
In my ass and my pussy!
It’s inside, Yuuji's thing is inside, but...!
Your virgin pussy feels great.
You feel great too, right?
No, Yuuji.
I don't want this.
I thought you'd be happy with this.
No, this isn't...
This isn't how things should be Yuuji!
Only with you, Yuuji, would I...!
It feels good, right?
Both your pussy and ass feels great, right?
Yuuji!
It feels good.
I'm melting... My ass feels like it's melting...
Yuuji, please...
Okay then.
After I cum inside.
You can't, I'll get pregnant!
You can't cum inside, Yuuji!
If I can't do it with you,
then I'll just have to...
Yuuji, but... but...!
You're about to cum too, right?
I can tell that you're trying to hold it in.
No, don't please...!
Don't!
No...
It felt so good that you just pee yourself again, Kotone-chan.
It's my first time, and yet...
www.SubDESU-H.net