www.SubDESU-H.net
Everyone, good work.
Today is an important party, as well as a business event.
I'm counting on you all.
Once we get through this party,
everything will finally end.
Just a little more,
so hang in there.
W
The carnal banquet
Welcome!
Oh, if it isn't Sachie-san.
We're looking forward to your services again this year.
Of course, with pleasure!
We're here, Marie.
Oh, welcome!
Yukari. Franchesca.
He's here, right?
He's here, but he will be busy waitering for awhile.
But don't worry.
He can still satisfy anyone no matter how tired he gets.
I'll prepare a room so just wait here.
Everyone.
For all those who were able to attend to Mamiya's party,
I thank you all very much.
There are new staff members, as well as new items.
I've prepared everything in accordance to everyone's expectations.
There is also the traditional auction,
so please look forward to it.
This woman was a virgin just recently.
Her young age still leaves her quite inexperienced,
but I suppose that is also part of her charm.
Umm, my mistress,
what should I do?
Simply lying down there will do just fine.
She's currently being offered at a special price today.
Customers who are interested in doing the real thing would have to provide a set amount.
However, if you want anal sex
then do as you please.
Mitarai-san, no need to feel nervous.
It will feel a lot better soon.
How about a few drinks?
It's filled with very potent invigorating ingredients.
As expected of Mamiya-san's medicines.
Suddenly I now feel warmed up.
Hey, Sachie-san.
If you won't mind, can I have a drink of your pee again?
Eh, again?
Please don't look too much.
It's Sachie-san's pussy.
It looks very clean.
How lovely.
Here, have some Sachie-special concentrated juice.
It has a fine smell and taste.
Truly the best.
Sachie-san, could you please take care of mine this time?
I understand.
I won't be able to resist doing it anyway.
Oh?
So the special wine has already taken effect.
It's already very stiff.
If it's like this you're sure to be still active for at least 10 more years.
Sachie-san, please take mine too.
Of course, certainly.
How is it?
Your hand control is perfect.
I feel like cumming anytime.
Sachie-san, I'm still far from done here.
My, my, well then...
Wow, I can't get enough of this!
Sachie-san, use your mouth on mine too.
This is a new drug made by Mamiya.
It is a potent one that takes effect very quickly.
No matter how bad your erectile dysfunction is
your cock is sure to become very lively again.
Wow, all of your cocks have already...!
But I still have something that's even better.
Use this along with the previous one
and you'll tread even deeper into the pleasure paradise.
You're not going to use it, Marisa?
Of course I will.
Hey mister.
Can you put this in me?
Here, mister, put it in me quick.
Now everyone, let's have a good time.
Wow.
Your thing here is amazing mister.
Marisa-chan, this is superb!
It's still a hundred years too early for you to start judging, mister!
I'll be the one to do that instead,
so just keep going.
Yes, that feels great Marisa-chan.
It feels really good.
Marisa-chan's pussy is totally wrapping me tight.
Oh no...
I can't hold it in any longer.
With this dirty darkened cock...
I'll thrust deep inside Marisa-chan's pussy.
This is wonderful, Marisa-chan.
Thrust it...
Thrust it deeper into me!
Squirt it all on me.
Sanae, if you keep fondling my nipples like that,
I'll quickly cum!
But your body is just so gorgeous, Marika!
I'm starting to feel envious.
You feel stuffed here already, right?
I know.
No, please don't say it aloud Kaoru.
It's embarrassing.
I'm going to properly give you "comfort",
so just stay still.
You already have this splendid thing
while also having a pussy.
You're really an inherently perverted human.
You feel pleasure regardless of whether you insert this to a female, or you get penetrated by a male.
No, I'm going to lose it!
You say that,
but you really want to lose it, right?
Ah...I can't hold it anymore...
Hey, Marika.
I'm going to use your pussy, okay?
Okay, just come.
I'm getting really aroused too.
And it feels quite uncomfortable, so...
Hey, you're being too intense all of a sudden!
But you love to be done like this.
No, don't say that.
Marika, don't just hog all the fun,
let me have some too.
Wow, it's really wrapping around me tightly.
You two are really good.
Yes!
The form, the shape.
You're really a fine male at this single part.
Please don't say that.
It's embarrassing.
My penis secretions are coming out!
Hey, Marika.
I'm going to cum inside you.
It's okay, right?
Cum in me.
Cum lots inside me.
Release it...
Release it in my mouth Marika.
Oh no, I'm going to cum!
It's going to cum out!
Lots of Marika's semen...
www.SubDESU-H.net
Hang in there, Mitarai-san.
We just need to get through today
after that, we're free.
Sawatari-san, it's work time.
There are customers waiting in the room on the second floor.
I'll leave it to you.
Oh, so you're here already?
So this is Marie's prized penis.
It's surprisingly normal.
I've heard that Marie was able to rejuvenate into her youthful self thanks to this.
We've already heard enough of her bragging
so we came here to have a full taste of it.
Now, do your work already.
But I can't just do it immediately.
Oh, so you can't get it erect with us?
My, how rude.
Here,
you can try playing with your thing while looking at mine.
That's right.
There's one here too.
I understand.
Wow!
His glands are swelling up.
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
This semen has a very creamy texture, amazing!
This is great.
This is...!
It melts naturally in your mouth.
Such a great thing!
Now I'm envious of Marie!
Please mister, you need to use a condom...
You can't insert it in raw.
I'm going to get pregnant...
Anal...?
Please use my butthole gently.
My butthole...
My butthole feels great!
What? Mister you came again already?
Whilst I'm still yet to be satisfied.
How impertinent.
The rest of you,
If any of you tries to cum before I get satisfied,
I'll bite these cocks off.
Now then everyone,
let's now start our traditional auction event.
We'll start with one of the most prized items.
Please have a look.
A person with no future outlook,
while still having a large amount of debt.
Both the mother and her child are now settled to be disposed of via purchase.
I'm sorry Makoto, for being a no-good parent.
It's okay, this can't be helped mother.
Today, we display them as a sample selling item.
Presenting, the parent and child sex show!
A female who's near her expiration date.
And a handsome boy with a monstrous penis.
We kind of went overboard with certain dosages for them,
but this item is still perfectly usable.
Mother...
Makoto...
Look Makoto-kun.
The day that you have been dreaming and waiting for is finally here.
I want to put it in.
I want to put it inside you mother!
Very well then Makoto.
Put it in me.
It feels warm...
It feels warm!
I never thought mother would feel this good!
Well, Mikako-san?
How does it feel to be raped by your own son?
I didn't know,
that my son's cock would feel this great.
Makoto...
Thrust it into me more!
Now everyone,
in celebration of their departure,
let's give them a blissful shower of semen!
For you to get out and escape after just a short break...
Really now, you still have to keep us company.
My mistress, I believe that this job...
indeed suits me.
Welcome!
We have been waiting for you.
We will guide you to the interview area.
Please follow us.
www.SubDESU-H.net