You told me not to worry.
It’s something that can’t be helped.
Nee-san...
You want to see your big sister’s skin?
I'll do anything you want.
You’ve gotten harder again.
Are you excited?
Cum whenever you want, Shun.
Shun!
So much!
You can always rely on me, Shun.
Don’t hold back.
Oh no...!
I can’t...!
This is so lewd!
Shun’s... my younger brother... but just touching him—
Makes me so hot.
If people found out that that... excited me—
They wouldn’t accept me.
But I have to accept what I can.
These feelings... bind me to Shun.
Please comfort your sister, Shun.
I want Shun to make love to me.
I want him to violate me.
The fact that we’re siblings doesn't matter.
I love Shun!
Shun!
My darling... My darling!
SubDESU-H Presents
-The Lewd
Family 2~
The cool-headed Kaguya
Comforted by the bewitching, lusty, long black hair
Shun?
So you came back?
Nee-san! Why are you in your underwear?
It’s hot today.
I'm comfortable like this.
B-But you can’t go around dressed like that!
But you’ve always seen your sister’s skin.
What a strange boy you are.
Th-That’s not what I meant!
Shun, where are you?
Oops. I was looking for Misaki.
You two have been getting along well, haven’t you?
Yeah! With the misunderstanding cleared up, we’re just like before.
Well bye, Nee-san!
Shun...
Are you...?
Onii-chan!
I can’t hold back anymore!
Not yet, Misaki.
Can’t you listen to my orders?
But... But...!
I’m so embarrassed, Onii-chan.
You pervert. You meanie!
Making me dress like this... You bully me!
You’re the one who dressed like that.
But you looked like you wanted me to.
It’s not MY fault!
My butt, too... It’s whirling around. Turning me on.
I feel it all the way inside my butt... You really are a pervert.
Onii-chan, you’re amazing!
Your cock feels so good!
I’m gonna collapse!
Onii-chan!
Oh no! Onii-chan!
I can’t take it...
I can’t hold back anymore.
Oh no.
I’m peeing myself.
Aw. You’re just a bad girl, Misaki.
You need punishment again.
Please. I want you to punish me, Onii-chan.
Shun...!
You're... with Misaki?
Is that so, Shun?
You are—
You chose Misaki over me?
So today, I’m gonna go buy some clothes!
I’m taking Shun along to carry my things.
Oh, dear, Misaki, since when were you two so close?
Hey, don’t say that! I never said we were close!
Something wrong, Kagu-nee?
Oh, I see. You’re going out, huh?
Have a nice time.
That was... Shun.
But he seemed different.
Those eyes.
Just one look at them almost made me cum.
Is that Shun’s true form? The side of him that accepted his fate?
Shun...
This is bad.
I mustn’t obsess over this.
Nee-san.
What is it?
Are you back?
That was rude of you to come back without saying anything.
Where were you?, too, Nee-san?
Well... Nowhere, really.
What about you?
Nee-san. I need you today, too.
No!
Today I... can’t.
Yes, you can.
Nee-san.
S-Sorry.
M-Move aside!
Nee-san, do like you always do.
I can’t... Not today.
But why?
You always do it!
Stop it, please!
What’s wrong, Nee-san?
Y-You have Misaki.
Don’t you want Misaki instead?
Misaki... Misaki is enough.
For you... and that...!
So you were peeking yesterday.
And then you consoled yourself.
But that was—
You must misunderstand.
Sorry, Nee-san!
Sorry for hurting you.
I'm a coward.
But you have Misaki!
I want you.
I've always seen you as a woman.
As a woman I loved.
You can’t... That’s a lie!
You did that with Misaki!
You’re just trying to trick me!
I love you!
So... I don’t want to destroy our current relationship.
But... my feelings are genuine!
It’s not because of my blood.
I was... I was only in love with you.
But I thought you didn’t want me.
So I held back.
But I love you.
I’ve always loved you!
Shun...
I’ve been waiting for this forever.
It’s okay.
Thrust in quickly. The pain will be over faster that way.
Shun’s penis... inside his sister... Shun...
Shun...
Move however you want.
That would... please me.
Shun... I want you all the way inside.
Shun...
The pain... is slipping away.
It feels... so good...?
Shun’s penis is stirring up my insides.
I’m losing my... mind!
This feels... so good!
You’re coming... deeper than anything... before...!
I’ve never felt you so close to me.
Shun!
I... belong to you!
I can’t... live without... you!
My body is going numb!
I can’t think of anything!
Shun!
I can’t... hold—
Shun... don’t—
No more!
Shun... you came so much inside of me!
Shun... Shun!
I love you!
Shun...
Shun!
I had no idea you felt that way about me.
Nee-san...
But first it was Misaki, now your big sister... Is Mother next?
Or maybe your big sister was your last?
Both of you—
What are you saying, Nee-san!
Never mind.
From now on, choose only me.
I belong to you now.
Look, Shun.
You need to eat this too.
Yeah... I know.
What’s this atmosphere?
They seem closer.
Could it be...?
You’re harder than usual.
Do you really like anal stimulation that much?
It’s something we both have, but you really seem to enjoy it.
You’re about to cum, aren’t you, Shun?
Go ahead.
Cum a lot.
From your sister’s hand and tongue, cum a lot!
Shun
That was more than usual.
So you enjoyed it? I'm glad.
Shun! Next, make me... make me feel good with your sucking!
Your tongue is so deep in my pussy.
Yes, there!
I feel your tongue moving... My pussy is throbbing. It knows.
Again... so hot—
And it’s so hard.
Yes! Right there!
You’re so manly, Shun.
Your cock drives me mad.
Shun...
Your cock...!
Shun!
More!
Make me feel even better!
So you have interest in this hole as well.
I feel a throbbing in there... though I wouldn’t have expected it.
It feels so...
My butt... is with you.
Filled... my insides... are full.
You're inside me now.
And I feel... strange.
Nee-san, are you okay?
I belong to you.
I'm fine with anything you do to me.
It’s coming out!
Shun!
Does this feel good?
Do you like your sister’s butt?
Nee-san.
I love it.
Really?
If it pleases you then... I will.
Shun...
No... What’s happening?
My butt—
Oh no!
I’m getting off... from my butt!
Amazing!
I never thought—
It’s my butt, but—
I’m feeling... from my butt—
From my butt... I’m about to cum!
Shun!
Cum with me!
You came in my butt!
I never thought it would feel like this.
Shun’s cock is... coming out.
Jesus! Kagu-nee, how could you...?
He said I was the only one. Stupid Shun!
Since he said he’d accept his fate, he’s been so selfish!
Misaki?
And so? What will you do about it?
Th-That’s right!
You chose me, right?
Tell Kagu-nee that too!
No, but I—
Shun, you said you’d give everything to me.
That should do.
What are you saying, Kagu-nee!
You just imagined that! It’s a fantasy!
Shun!
Choose one of us!
That’s easy for you to say!
You wishy-washy asshole!
It’s okay, Shun.
Big sister is patient.
Answer when you’re ready.
Wha—
But I can—
I can be patient too!
Which means—
I guess so...!
Yes!
Shun!
Shun, your tongue...
Yes!
This feels great!
Shun!
This feels good!
No... Kagu-nee... not there!
You’re very sensitive down there, aren’t you?
No!
Not so... Oh no!
No... What’s going on?
This just... feels too good!
Oh, stop it!
I can’t—
No!
Shun...
Shun hasn’t cum yet... but just Misaki—
N-Next... do me!
So perverted!
Onii-chan is inside of Kagu-nee!
Having you... watch me, Misaki... is too good.
Shun!
Since when have you gotten... so big...?
This is awesome!
Misaki... Not there!
It’s all the way inside.
With your penis... and Misaki’s tongue... I’m going to break apart!
Amazing!
My body feels like... it’s going to float!
I am so—
Shun...
I’m at my limit!
Yes... with your penis—
Shun’s semen—
Inside... of me—
Shun... your baby’s seed... is pouring out.
Shun...
You were wonderful.
Shun’s semen!
Kagu-nee, you hogged him!