S-Senpai!
There's more coming out soon!
Here you go!
No!
Hey, don't you keep lurking like that.
We haven't even started yet.
Triple Ecchi
Shigure's Chapter Again
Hey, would you come to my house tomorrow?
S-sure!
I've been invited to Senpai's house.
Does that mean...?
So huge!
Father, didn't I already refuse?!
What are you complaining about?
I don't have any intention of marrying that person!
Even if you say something like that-
So I'll be her scapegoat to refuse her parents' marriage proposal...
Don't decide by yourself!
Why don't you just accept it, he's the perfect one.
But, it's just as I thought rich people's houses would be like...
It's just not right for me, Father!
It's spacious and even the ceiling is that high.
You're going to argue with me?
It's not like that!
It's different to common people's houses...
Then just accept what I was saying before!
It's still hot, so be careful with it.
Yes... thank you.
Let's talk about the other person in here, who are you?
Y-yes!
I'm so sorry, I'm Shigure-san's private pleasure-
That's right, let me introduce him.
He's Kita Komatsu-kun.
He's the only man I intend to marry, and we've been going out for a while.
[Intend to marry]
Wha-
Is... Is that true?!
Of course it is, right? Kita Komatsu-kun.
I'm sorry, but from what family do you came from?
What's your parents' job? How much do they earn?
Father, that's so rude of you!
What are you talking about? It's important!
My father's job is just a plain salaryman,
Don't think so highly of yourself just because you have a better life and job.
we still have thirty years of mortgage payments left.
I'm just thinking about you!
And... we also have one little hamster in there.
You just don't have to say it like that!
Shigure!
Are you sure that you like him and are going out with him?
Eh... of course I am. Right, Kita Komatsu-kun?
Eh?
Just now-
You're hopeless, he's already going out with crying just now.
What should I do with you?
You're always thinking of yourself and never thought about his feelings at all.
I'm sure that you're just playing with his feelings all the time.
Now you dare say that you're going out with him.
What have I done...?
Kita Komatsu-kun!
Hey, Shigure!
So you're here.
Senpai, you're getting married?
That's right...
I can't really argue with what my father said.
But I have no intention of getting married right now!
He's wearing such formal clothes right now? Even wearing a tie.
Is that so? He's done that much to come here.
How long are you going to keep weeping like that?
Take off your clothes. It's sex time.
Eh? Right now? I don't think that's a good idea-
What are you saying?
When it gets like this, we just have to fulfil our desires.
It smells nice, even her lips are soft...
These lips are where Senpai's tongue-
Her tongue isn't going inside me...
I... I never kissed anyone like this before, so I know nothing about it.
I'm sure that you also want to do this, right?
I have to admit that I'm still inexperienced with this.
I'll let you decide how we'll have sex today.
S-Senpai!
Then, I want you to show me your pussy.
Eh? S-sure...
Aren't you always looking at it?
Why are you asking something like that?
That's okay, I just want to see it.
As I thought, he's getting cocky.
Ah, you have to open it so I can see it clearly.
Quickly open it up!
Hmph... you're so forceful.
Before, I was the one who always give an order to him,
I'm feeling so embarrassed right now...
Didn't I already get used to something like this?
Is... Is this okay with you?
If you don't move your hand, I can't see it.
I know that.
No, I feel so aroused right now!
It's too embarrassing for me! I can't endure this at all.
Um... could we just stop it right now?
No, you can't.
Wa-wait-
Wow, it's amazing. I can see Senpai's insides so clearly.
You idiot!
He's looking at it... He's looking at my embarrassing pussy...
I can see how soft your pussy is.
I can't hold it back after see something like this.
We always did it so quickly before, now I can see your pussy clearly.
Just stop talking like that.
I'm going to lick it, is that okay?
Don't ask something like that over and over!
It's squeezing my tongue.
No!
It's in, his tongue is inside me.
Th-that place, if you do that-
W-wait a minute, let me rest a bit.
No way, it's just getting fun.
He know that I'm embarrassed right now...
I love... I really love you, Senpai!
No, you can't do that!
Senpai answer me, do you really like me?
Why should I answer that weird question?
If you don't answer, I'll just put this inside you.
No... wait, if you put it in right now-
Your embarrassed face is so cute, Senpai.
T-today I feel so strange.
No, wait-
It feels so warm inside you...
No, if you put it in right now-
No! I'm going to-
Do you like the way I'm moving?
Tell me honestly.
Even if... you say something... like that...
It's hard to breathe like this.
In here, right? I just know it.
I'm not your private pleasure thing for nothing.
No!
Though I can't say right now if I like you or not,
I just know that I don't want to have sex with anyone but you.
That's why... please let me rest a bit...
I'm so happy, Senpai!
Wait, stop moving!
I'm sorry, I'm so happy that I can't stop my hips.
It's yummy.
No, if you do that-
No, my nipples! You're sucking them while fucking my pussy!
Please let me go... just let me over with it...
In here, I'm cumming in here.
No!
I'll cum a lot inside Senpai's deep pussy.
No... No... I'm going to cum!
It's too good for me...
No-
No!
Your cum is too much for me, it makes my womb feel flabby...
Even you could cum a lot like this...
You're a pervert, aren't you?
Senpai...
Well, I'm also like him.
They fit together in there, and Shigure's also kind of interested in him.
Th-that's not it...
Don't you think he's the same as you?
Even though you cried when you asked me to marry you, I'm sure he'll be perfect as your son in law.
Settled as
son in law
You know after seeing them doing it, it seems that I want to do it.
I've an important meeting to attend tomorrow...
No way, it's been a while since you've been my private pleasure thing.
No... No way...
Hey, did you see that guy over there?
He's kind of cute, like a little squirrel.
Hm... I want something cooler than just cute for now.
It's good to meet all of you...
Hello, you there!
Is that the time already?
S-Senpai?
If we don't hurry, we'll be late for the movie.
Why are you just standing around?!
Come on, let's get going!
I'm so sorry, Senpai!
Why are you apologizing?
That was nice of you to say 'it's good to meet you' to them.
Maybe I'll get another boyfriend when you're not around, right?
No... It's nothing... like-
Do as you like, you cherry boy!
I don't really have any intention of going out with you.
But, what's with this uneasy feeling I have...
Jealousy!?
Th-that can't be!
That can't happen to me!
Hmph... at a time like this.
Geez... you're blushing like that.
You're such a perverted boy.
I can feel my pussy is already really wet.
You said that you like me before...
I won't let you get away with this anymore.
I'll make you cum by yourself from now on, you perverted squirrel.
Shigure, Kita Komatsu-kun has come for you.
Senpai!
I'm so moved knowing that you're masturbating while thinking of me.
W-wait a minute-
Why don't I let the two of you have a good time, okay?
Mother?!
I can't believe that Senpai is thinking of me...
Wait, if you put it in right now-
I'll make love till your womb loves me back.
No-
No!
You're so cute when you blush like that, Senpai.
Why don't you say that you've liked me since before?
Hey, you just said that you like me.
Just said that you really like Kita Komatsu-kun!
Hey... Hey...
Geez... you're acting so high-and-mighty.
Who would say...
Who would say that to you!?
I'll make you pay for that, Kita Komatsu-kun!
Senpai, you're scary!
I'll make your thing bow to me.
There... there... there!
I can feel that your thing is shivering inside of me,
you can't hold it anymore!?
I'll make you pay for all of what you did to me!
No, I'm going to cum soon!
That's okay, just let it out.
But, today would be Senpai's period...
Why... Why do you know that?!
I always check your period in my notebook.
Huh? What's that? You're always doing stupid things!
It's bad, please pull it out!
Even though it's my period, there's no way I could pull it out.
When I'm feeling this good...
No!
It's cumming!
I can feel it in my womb!
Moving out!
Yay... yay, let's go!
Okay, I'll be the first one!
One year later
So, where's Shigure right now?
He's locking her husband in their room.
It seems that girl couldn't hold it anymore, It's been a while since the last time they've had sex.
With that condition, I'm sure we'll have more grandchildren soon.
Hey... my breast milk is pouring out like this.
Why don't you suck it up?
Yes!
It's good to see you again, penis.
I'll suck it up!
This is...!
The feeling of this penis moving inside me!
My body just couldn't hold it anymore.
I'll make sure that you're going to let it all out inside me.
We're going to make a new record, do your best.
My husband.
Y-yes...
No!
Don't you dare say no!