So, you're here because you want to do something about your sister's hatred of men, am I right?
That's correct.
"Men always think about indecent things".
"I hate them!", is what she's always saying.
Indecent things, huh...
But, in reality, they're not all thinking about such things, right doctor?
That's true.
If this keeps up, she'll never get a boyfriend...
...that's just too sad.
Well then, Futaba-san...
You can call me Yuna.
Yuna-chan.
Why don't you tell me the good points and the charm of boys in your eyes?
The charm of boys?
That's right.
You see...
...boys want to make you feel good.
...feel good...
Exactly.
But to make that possible...
...the girl needs to know how to make the man happy.
It's give and take.
You will cooperate with me for your sister's sake...
...and study the ways to make a man happy.
Got it?
Yes.
You will learn for your sister's sake!
For my sister's sake...
That's right.
You know what this is, right?
That's a penis.
Try licking it.
Licking it...?
Like this?
Lick its base more from below, like licking an ice cream.
...Ice cream...
It's gotten bigger somehow.
That's good.
When that happens it's proof that the boy's feeling good.
So this feels good?
This is a man's semen.
It tastes strange.
Exactly. Remember it well.
Doctor, did you feel good?
Yes. You did well, Yuna-chan.
Yuna-chan, next up will be...
Hey, Doctor Fujimi...
You were introducing yourself until now.
And now you should welcome the man to your special place.
As exercise.
It tickles, but it feels good.
Remember how good it feels from now on.
For your sister's sake, you see?
Wha... huh?
You fell asleep.
I didn't want to wake you up.
Oh, I'm sorry... um...
Seems like you could use some relaxation.
Oh, I somehow feel much less burdened.
That's good to hear.
All that's left is bringing your sister here, right?
Yes. I'll persuade her this evening.
Oh, and tell her friends it's okay to join her.
In our case, this may give us a lead on something.
I will.
W
Hypnosis
Humiliation School
Episode One
Simulation
Hypnosis
Hey Aoi, is something the matter?
Huh? I was arguing with Yuna last night.
Arguing? Why?
She keeps pestering me to go to counseling.
Ah, is it about-
Yeah. About my hatred of men.
She treats me like I'm sick.
"You can be cured now", she says.
With counseling?
Yup.
But you know, right...?
Men are...
...idiots, perverts, the worst...
There's a few who try to look cool, but on the inside they're all the same.
Don't let yourself be fooled, Yurine.
Well, I understand how you feel too, Aoi, but-
What? Even you became a man-lover?
Oh, you have a brother complex, that's why.
"As long as Onii-sama is there, I'm fine!" right?
Huh? If you say it like that, it's a little bit embarrassing.
You're blushing.
I admit that your brother's cool, but...
Huh?
What are you looking at?
You!
Quit peeking, will you?
Still starting fights with boys?
Oh, Yuna-chan.
Sister...
...let's try consulting Doctor Fujimi for once.
You're mentally ill, so...
...you'd better have yourself checked by a professional.
Like I said, why does this have to be a "sickness"?
Because it isn't normal!
Yuna-chan, was that counseling session that good?
Yes.
Come on, why did they even made this counseling room?
What's there to talk about so much?
That hurts.
Is something the matter?
Never seen you here before.
What's your business on this campus?
To give you a hint, I'm patrolling.
Further, a list of persons in question.
That counselor...
...is that you?
Name's Toshikazu Fujimi.
Glad to meet you.
And you are?
I'm Reika Shirogane.
I'm this school's student council president.
I never thought there would be anyone who didn't know this.
Positions as yours must put you under great stress.
You can come in for consultation anytime.
I hate to say but...
...I'm used to standing of top of people.
I've been doing this for a year now, and...
...as the daughter of the director, I've been prepared for this.
I see.
Excuse me, but...
...I don't think you will have many opportunities for your business here.
The student council is putting a lot of effort into solving everyone's problems and worries, you see?
If that's the case, that's good.
Problems that must not become public knowledge, and unconscious problems, are a hassle.
For instance...
...if one is put under so much pressure one cannot go on without obedience.
What are you implying?
Well, you also should come to the counseling room for once.
I'm fine.
The Futaba sisters and Yurine Miauchi.
Yuna was talking about her.
About her affection for her brother.
Before the main event I should tame the brother-complex girl...
...and build up some defences against outside interference.
First should be some actual results.
Arimine, have you heard of the reputation of that counseling room?
Yes. It's quite famous, but...
Do you think it's because a lot of our students have been bottling up their worries?
Yes. I think that might be the reason.
You're saying that we, the self governing student council, have our hands bound?
No, not at all.
There's nothing wrong with you being our president.
It's because counseling is more than a private talk. More like fortune telling.
And can we put our trust into fortune telling?
N-No.
Arimine, before doing the aggregating today...
...you're not allowed to go home.
U-Understood.
Brother...
...watch me in this embarrassing position, please.
Yes, I'm watching you.
I love you, brother.
I keep on doing indecent things when thinking of you.
I'm a woman with no shame.
No!
My pussy!
You're making "Yurine" sounds.
Don't say that.
How about me helping you out?
That would make me happy.
That feels good, Yurine.
You'll make a nice wife.
Brother's tongue is...
licking me down there.
Yurine, I want to enter you.
I want to be linked with you.
All right?
Please make yourself at home, brother.
Brother, brother!
Pass! I'm here!
That guy again.
What are you looking at? Enough already!
Huh?
Don't feign innocence. You were staring at my breasts again, weren't you?
No-
Oops.
Aw man, what's with that?
I got the wrong idea because they were looking my way.
Sis, I saw that.
Made me feel like you're nuts.
Well, everyone misunderstands at some point, but...
...this one was quite...
Come on, Aoi...
...I really think there's something wrong with you.
Despite having to watch the boys around you, you hate them.
That's a big burden, I think.
That story again?
That's why I'm saying you just should go to counseling once to get rid of that burden.
Now even you're recommending it?
Exactly.
It's for your sake.
In your current state.
See, even Yurine is agreeing with me now.
Sis!
Huh?
Try going there once.
Come on. It won't hurt.
I got it.
I'll try it.
That counseling.
How's that? It's a bit of a rare aroma though.
That's a strange scent.
It has relaxing effects to make you lose your tension.
Your hatred of men is cured, but your impression of men is still bad, you say?
Yes. I still hate them.
They're dirty and slutty.
If you put it like that, there's not much to tell you.
Let's try changing perspectives.
Your sister hurt her heart for your sake...
...how do you feel about that?
How do I feel? Well, it's nerve racking, but she's worrying about me, so...
You don't hate your sister, right?
Of course not. She's my only sister.
How about trying to challenge your hatred of men for your sister's sake?
For Yuna's sake?
Exactly.
It's your sister who'll be happiest about everything you achieve here.
Right.
You must know about real men for your sister's sake.
For Yuna's sake...
That's right.
Men and women do this to get to know each other.
No. I don't want men.
It's for your sister's sake.
You can't make your little sister worry all the time, right?
Don't worry. It's not dirty and not scary.
That's a lie! Indecent... and perverted things are not all that I'm thinking about.
That's not what I meant.
It's about feeling good and becoming a good partner.
Do you not want this? Feel disgusted?
No.
It feels good, but-
That's good, but...
...is there still something you don't want?
I can't stand the smell of men.
Smell?
They stink of sweat and...
...that strange smell.
No!
I hate this smell!
Well then, first you have to come to like this scent.
Aoi, how was yesterday's counseling?
About so so, I'd say.
So so?
What? You said you'd understand a bit more about boys.
That's what I wished for.
There's no way I could change that quickly, right?
That's true.
Oh, I see.
Don't worry.
Doctor Fujimi said that he'd turn Sis into an adult woman.
What are you saying? That's creepy.
Hurry up, let's go. Alright.
What is this?
Why does it fascinate me?
There may be some side effects when confronting boys.
It'll stabilize eventually.
This is a side effect?
Fight!
Oh!
Fight-Oh! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
Was the smell of boys always like this?
Oh no. What's going on? My body's strange today.
What a terrible smell.
It's really filthy.
Stinks! It stinks so much, still...
I wonder...
...even though it's wrong to do such a thing.
My nipples are stiff.
This feels good.
Oh man...
...I can't stop.
You're quite restless, aren't you?
Yes.
My feelings are unsteady somehow.
Does glancing at boys interest you?
No. I wouldn't say that.
Hmm...
As a way to calm down...
...how about learning about the tea ceremony or something like that at a friend's place?
At Yurine's place?
Yes. It's a stable environment...
...and I think you should have that experience.
You're right.
Might be a good idea.
Well then, go ahead and try it.
I wonder if Yurine's already arrived...
Brothers, give it your best, will you?
To have you here and holding a tea ceremony with me makes me happy.
Brother, please don't hesitate to diddle me.
It's probably about time for you, Brothers.
Please.
Yours is amazing.
Brother's tea is so much. I'm happy.
Delicious.
What are you doing, Yurine?
Doctor!
Shh!
Let's keep what we're seeing here a secret.
Okay?
Okay...
Sis! What's up, sis?
You don't look well.
It's nothing.
You'll help me with the theater club's training, won't you?
Yeah, I know.
I love thee, thus I am such an improper woman!
Fiddlesticks!
Your... heart...
Sis, come on, put more pep into it.
Okay.
Oh, and don't mind the audience.
This smell... it's a boys smell...
I am aware that this is wrong!
But I cannot touch thee!
This leaves me no other option than...
I'm sorry!
If I were to answer your longings...
...I wonder...
...how much satisfaction that would bring?
Sis, what's wrong?
Somebody... please...
Aoi-kun.
You were finally honest with yourself, right?
Doctor Fujimi!
This may be a great opportunity.
Let's show Yuna-chan that you've cured your hatred of men.
Well then, would everybody help us out here?
This smell... I can't get enough of the scent of boys.
Sis, you're too hasty.
Please... more of this smell. Give me more of it!
I want it too.
I would like to request something as well.
Doctor Fujimi!
This is Doctor's... hurry up and give us plenty.
You two really love cocks, don't you?
I also want Brother's cock.
Yurine-chan too?
How's that, Brother?
It's great, Yurine.
Okay then. Line up your faces.
Brother's semen!
Awesome smell!
More! Screw me more! Shoot and spray it more!
Have your way with this shameless sister, my brother.
Yuna's a pervert. Screw me!
So dirty!
Cum inside!
The hot stuff is coming!
Okay then. Everybody spread your legs.
This should be a front page.
Doctor's dick is hot inside! Feels good!
Brother, here too please!
Indecent! Brother's hand is so indecent!
My clitoris feels so good!
This stuff smells so good!
Shoot it all over me!
So much of brother's... I'm so happy!
HypnoSis taming experiment.
Well, wasn't that a great success?
But the clean up will be a hassle.
Hey, how about that guy?
What? That guy over there's cooler!
It's strange seeing Aoi going after boys.
Well, isn't that normal?
Exactly. Remember that well.