Is it like this?
I'm going to show my underarm, right?
SubDESU-H Presents
Cosplay Roshutsu Kenkyuukai
Kosuroken
Day 2
I didn't think that Aya-tan would wear the erotic swimsuit I gave her.
You did order me to wear it, right?
And... I'm wearing this because it's hot today.
I was in trouble yesterday.
I was even given cumshots by everyone.
And by the time I noticed it, I came again.
But... this is for the money.
No... I'm being threatened!
I'm dying, imagining all of the people looking at me when I came out of the locker.
But I did get excited being watched by everyone.
I'm feeling horny.
No... it's gotten this big...
That part, too... it's swelled up.
It's hot...
You were so cute and erotic yesterday, but...
You're getting nicer today!
Thank you so much!
By the way, there's liquid flowing in your tight...
What happened?
Eh!?
This is... my sweat.
I'm getting sweaty!
Oh, that's strange.
The swimsuit is pressing into my pussy, and it's twitching...
I think I'm going to come just from this.
The string... I'm being assaulted by the string...
It's embarrassing, but...
My pussy is already wet with love juice...
Oh no... it's producing a dirty voice and...
if it presses in so much... more of my juice will flow out.
Aya-tan, did you notice that your swimsuit's color is changing?
Eh!?
It's because of the special pigment in the swimsuit's fabric!
It's reacting to the heat and pheromone secretions from your tight pussy.
Heat?
This is uncool, so please make it fast.
I understand, Aya-tan.
Your tights are full of love juice...
I told you, this is my sweat!
Yes, it's sweat right? Sweat that happens to be full of pheromones?
I... can't help it, you know?
It'd be unnatural to feel nothing while wearing this erotic swimsuit.
Ah, it's pressing in more, and it feels so good.
I'm a strange person, to have these feelings even though people are watching me.
They're watching me...
They're watching me!
Aya-tan, it's not good to hold it in, right?
Oh, no... they started it again...
They started masturbating while looking at me.
If they do that, I'll get more excited.
Those red-black big dicks...
They're touching and rubbing...
But I won't masturbate in front of people like yesterday.
I won't do something embarrassing.
My tits are getting numb...
My nipples are being rubbed by the swimsuit.
My pussy is hot and my clitoris is struggling, inside...
It's like it will explode if I don't let it out...
It's so itchy, and my tights are so wet...
Hey Aya-tan, you're having too much fun on your own.
Yes, she is.
We should let her service us.
What's the matter, everyone?
We want you to comfort us, using your hands and mouth.
Using my mouth...?
Are you talking about "fellatio"?
I've never done that!
And besides, that big one.... Aya's mouth is too small.
That won't fit in my mouth.
It's all right, you can lick it at first.
I just have to lick it...?
It's too cruel to have to give a blow job in front of so many people.
But... the one who threatened me might be watching me, so I can't help it, right?
This is a big bonus for you, OK?
It tastes... weird...
I'm licking a man's dick in front of many people.
It doesn't matter, since I'm cosplaying...
Dicks don't taste good...
Yes... this must not taste good...
Erect dicks are hot, eh?
It's my first time sucking one.
It's weird... it's getting tastier.
Oh, so you started already!
Aya-tan...
I see, Aya-tan really likes dicks.
By watching it and sucking it, right?
No, I'm not...
Say it clearly...
Yes... I love dicks...
This weird shape, and the taste...
and...
this dirty recovery...
There are many dicks... these are all Aya's.
If I'm sucking a dick... my pussy gets wet too.
The embarrassing juice is flowing fast.
The dicks are so tasty right now.
It's getting bigger inside my mouth, and...
Everyone, you don't have to hold it. You can release it onto me.
Aya-tan!
Today's first dick syrup... it's so dense and tasty...
I'll do my best to suck this... feel it and release it onto me!
The dick... give me more dick syrup!
Please give me more!
...I'm still alive!
Thanks to Aya-tan, our photo shoot is successful once again!
Everyone, were you able to release and refresh yourselves?
We're not Aya-tan, though.
Aya-tan, this is a transformation stick.
Can you transform using this?
Oh, I know this.
This is a magic stick!
You mean I use it like this?
No! You're going to stick it in your boobs when you do the transformation pose!
Eh? I'm not sure what you're saying.
Is it like this?
Or...
is it this?
I know! It's like this, right?
No...
Well...
And then I'll do it like this, right?
Oh!
I do know a little about otaku, you know.
Those witch girls recently are weird.
To transform themselves with this pose...
But... I know how they feel.
I see, girls get horny with this,
and they transform through this.
My tights are getting hot again...
How about this?
Why did it become like that?
Yes! Just keep going!
Eh!?
It's thick and hard.
Aya-tan, what I said earlier was a lie!
You can stick it in into your tights!
It's the second stage of the transformation!
You... are you sure?
If you deceive me... Aya will refuse this photo shoot.
Aya... transform!
The rugged part of the stick is stimulating my clitoris...
I see. This is the reason the witch rides the broom stick...
So dirty!
You make a great perverted witch!
I'm not dirty...
I just wanted to be a witch.
I'm going to cast a spell on Aya-tan!
A spell...
Yes, please cast a spell on me!
Huh? What a reversal!
Eh?
Magic is useless.
The power of a man depends on his popularity and his muscles.
No!
What are you doing?
Oops!
No!
If you want to take a photo, then take it!
What are you doing?
We already saw Aya-tan's legs widen like the letter M.
Oh, sorry about that...
Um... can you put me down?
No... this is good, too.
This is a nice view!
It's a picture opportunity!
Yes, it is...
No...
I don't like this pose. It's like I'm a kid, peeing!
Look, everyone likes it.
Can't you show it with your guts?
If you do that, my panties will press in and my pussy will pop out!
No...
Everyone is looking at my pussy...
If it's like this, there will be a lot of juice flowing out of my pussy.
All of my parts will be clearly seen.
I don't want this to be seen.
It's so embarrassing...
It's embarrassing, but...
Why is it my hands are moving...?
No... don't watch me.
If you keep looking... I'll get wetter and more of my juice will spill out.
Look, it fills up like this.
You wanted to see this, right?
Oh... you can do it if you're onto it.
It's a dick!
What do you want to do with this?
I'm going to rub it using my love juice...
I'm going to service it...
Good, then get to it!
Wow... it's so hot and hard, and it's twitching and pumping...
It's so rough and rugged and...
I will going to wet this more with my love juice...
I'm getting hornier by rubbing the dick in this position...
because it's like the dick is growing out of my pussy...
Oh... the syrup is filling up...
I'm going to mix it with my love juice...
The ass... that's an asshole...
The pussy isn't there...
It's an asshole, but... I can feel the pressure from the dick.
Is this anal sex?
It hurts...
My ass is going to rip!
There's a dick inside my ass...
It's not even a hole for sex, but...
I didn't know you could have sex using the ass.
My anus is spreading!
This is so perverted!
Still... even though it's my ass, I'm starting to feel good.
It's so good, it's almost like the pussy.
The dick is in my ass...
My asshole is full of dick...
My stomach is being filled with a big dick!
My nipples are getting large, too.
My milk... Aya's milk is leaking out...
My ass feels so good...
My ass is being raped, but...
my pussy feels lonely.
It's begging for it!
I want a hot dick.
I want it inside Aya's pussy...
Aya... can't reach the dick...
Bring it close.
I don't want it to be so far away.
That dick is big...
I want it stuck in me deeply.
That might be... ah...
Release it...
Please release yourself into Aya's ass!
These smelly things...
I'm going to be full of sperm again... I'm going to be dirty again!
It's so good.
All this sperm makes Aya's body feel so good!
But my pussy is still lonely.
I want... I want dick... I really want the dick!
Ah... that is...
Stick that in here... stick the dick in here, please...
Ah, it's in!
The dick is inside me!
That big dick!
The tip is so hot! It's so hot!
The two... my two holes are being...
My two holes are being filled with my favorite, stiff dicks!
There are two dicks inside Aya!
They're rubbing inside me, and they're abusing me!
My first anal...
and my first time in the pussy... this is so messed up!
It's so good!
Dick!
These hard things are rubbing inside me.
My anal and pussy are being pounded!
This is so good!
I'm a maiden, but I'm becoming a dirty whore... a slut.
I'm coming...
My asshole and pussy, my clit and my nipples feel so good!
My juice is coming out!
The dicks are getting big inside!
Please release Aya's favorite muddy sperm into my pussy, faster!
Aya is a dick maniac who can't bear it being released it inside my pussy and ass.
You must release it all inside me!
Release it inside!
You just released it inside my pussy and ass.
You're releasing it inside my ass.
The dick is releasing sperm into my pussy, too!
I'm coming,
I'm coming!
Aya is coming and being filled up with sperm!
You're coming too much inside my pussy and ass!
If you release this much, I'll probably get pregnant.
And my ass... it'll stretch, and won't go back to normal!
I can't go back to the store like this!
I didn't even want this, but I'm glad I came to this photo shoot!
Aya is a dick loving, perverted, cosplay sperm slave!
I can't go back to the store today.
It's because I can't even remember how many men I entertained today.
The mail... I don't want to read it...
I'm sure the manager is mad at me.
It's all because of this unreasonable email I received.
Message sent
Yes
No
**Order**
Come to Comitsue's cosplay hall,
wearing your uniform from the cosplay cafe.
I will give you as much money as you want.
!!Caution!!
You must obey all the requests from the men!
Oh?
I just remembered...
about the prank mail I sent to my friend while I was drunk.
I even sent a stupid attachment to disguise myself.
The suspect was just me...
Really... there's got to be a limit to fooling yourself.
However, after that day my lifestyle changed a lot.
Hey, don't spit too much sperm out.
You did say you wanted fresh sperm milk.
If it sticks on the uniform, the smell won't be easily removed.
Here Aya-tan, open your mouth.
Revealing my identity on that day was the catalyst.
My fans sought me out, and found this place.
They all started to come by when they could.
They come here to... well, it's the name of the circle.
How was it, master?