Nooo!
P-Please stop, Tomonori-san!
Nooooo!
SubDESU-H Presents
Second               Volume
Haha Sange
Good morning.
Morning. It’s unusual for you to sleep late, mom.
Really?
So, Tomonori didn’t come
back yesterday either, eh?
Y-Yeah. He hasn't been home for 4 days...
4 days, huh?
Well, he's in puberty too, you know...
I'm sure he wants to play around too...
So you haven’t heard anything from him...?
Uh, no. Nothing.
I spoke to him on the phone yesterday.
Eh?
He and his friend had a game they wanted to play,
and he's staying over at a friend's,
so he won't be home for another 2 or 3 days.
He said he’s still going to
school every day, though.
I see.
If he’s staying in contact,
then there’s no need to worry.
Sorry about his being so sudden, but I have to
go on another business trip starting tonight.
It looks like it'll be a long one this time.
Take care of the house while I'm gone.
So suddenly? How long will you be gone this time?
It’s work, so it can’t be helped.
Please have my luggage ready for me
when I come home later to pick it up.
I’ll call first.
Also, since you’re a mother,
try understanding the children's actions.
Tomonori hated parting with his real mother,
and so he might a bit unstable from time to time.
It'll become troublesome if he
were to commit suicide...
What? Aren’t you worried?
Worried? Why on earth would
I be worried about my son?
Oh, you’re still not ready?
You’ll be late for school.
Okaaay.
What’s wrong? You’ll be late.
Um, did something happen
between you and Onii-chan?
Huh? N-nothing at all.
Why do you ask?
Because when I was speaking with him
over the phone, he kept asking about you
I see...
I'll be meeting Onii-chan tonight. Do you have
anything you'd like to say to Onii-chan?
Noooo!
S-stop!
For you to do something like this…
...you'll destroy this house…
...you’ll destroy our family!
This house? What are you playing family for?
You cockroach! You crawled into this
house and threw my mother out.
If family is so important, come sink
yourself onto your son.
I-If I use my mouth on you, things will be back
to normal tomorrow right? You'll stop this?
Stop it.
That’s enough.
So, we’re good now?
I won't be satisfied with just this.
Noooo…!! Stop it... Stop this!
Don’t do this.
Please... We're mother and son... We can't do this! We can't!
Noooo!
Stop! Stop! Forgive me!
Mom?
Hmm? Oh, right...
Could you tell him that I’m worried about
him and would like to talk to him?
Sure. No problem.
Noooo!
Don't! We’re mother and son!
Stop it! Stop it -it -it!
Nooo!
Stop, please!
It’s wrong! It’s wrong!
Why, Tomonori-san?
Shut up. You’re the worst kind of woman.
That's why from now on you’ll be my sex slave.
Understand?
Seiichi-san… please come home quickly.
This is the first time
I’ve been to a place like this...
I’m a little nervous.
I-it’s my first time here too, you know.
Onii-chan, let’s take a bath together.
Okay.
It’s my first time taking a bath with Onii-chan...
That kind of makes me happy...
Even though it's a little weird,
I’m getting a little excited...
T-That's right... I might be a little nervous myself...
What?
I was just thinking about how happy I am.
Eh?
Because I’ve finally met with the person I love again,
and we're able to be together like this...
There...
Don't... Onii-chan... There...
You’re so wet. Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Amazingly goo- good.
Onii-chan, I love you. Don't... There...
You’re even wetter than last time.
Well, it’s because I love you.
This time I’ll suck you.
So? Does it feel good, Onii-chan?
Yeah, it’s good.
I’m close. I’m cumming!
Sorry. I couldn’t help it.
That’s all right.
Cum as much as you want, Onii-chan.
Give all your sperm to me, okay?
Come here, Onii-chan.
Your penis feels so hot!
It doesn’t hurt, does it? I’m going to move.
No, I’m fine. Push all the way in and cum inside me.
Yes… I feel so good, Onii-chan!
Push it deeper. Deeper into my pussy-!
Amazing. Onii-chan, it's good...
Onii-chan, it feels good... I love you... More, and more-!
It feels like I'm about to cum. I’m about
to cum. Cumming! I’m cumming!
Ohh... Even though I told you could release it inside...
Sorry. By impulse, I- ...
Let’s do it again. This time cum inside
me properly, okay?
Good morning.
Good morning. What’s up? You seem
awfully cheerful this morning.
Hm, do I? Oh, yeah. Yesterday I told Onii-chan
you were worried about him.
I see.
He said he would probably
come home tonight.
I see.
No. Stop, Tomonori-san.
Don’t. Please stop.
Marie is upstairs. If you cry out,
she’ll hear you.
Do you want your adolescent daughter
who's still just in high-school to see you
having sex with your son, Hanae-sama?
What're you saying? Of course not.
You say no, but you’re wet, aren’t you?
You’re enjoying this, aren’t you?
What are you saying? Don't misunderstand!
It’s just my body. In order to protect me,
my body becomes aroused and wet to try to
protect my womb and the inside of my vagina.
Shut up! Your fucking annoying!
A sex slave should be quiet and get fucked!
No! Please don’t do this!
If you get any louder, you’ll wake up Marie-chan.
So good. I’m going to cum inside you.
No, don’t cum inside!
Listen up. After you’ve cleaned the floor and
taken a shower, come to my room.
We’ll continue where we left off.
No, please stop.
Stop it, I can’t stand it.
Do you really want me to stop?
Your pussy's really aroused though...
Like I told you, that's not right-
No! Not so hard!
No! It’s coming out! No!
Amazing. You’re squirting so much.
The bed's soaked... Were you holding
in pee or something?
Stop it already...
We're only getting started...
Nooo!
Don't! It hurts! Stop! It’s too strong!
Don't hold it there!!
What naive things are you saying?
Don't! Stop it!
It's still on the lowest setting. I’ll make you scream even more.
Nooooo!
Ah-no! No! Noooo!
No…
What’s wrong, mom? Your eyes are
swollen and your face is pale.
Oh, I just didn't get enough sleep...
Hmm.
Even though Onii-chan is home,
he hasn’t gotten up yet.
T-That’s true...
Don’t worry about that, Marie. Hurry and
get ready for school. You’ll be late.
Okay.
I’m leaving.
How was it?
You're really feeling because
of the thrill, aren't you?
As soon as Marie leaves you become
relieved and came, huh?
Honestly, you two are quite
the perverts, aren't you...
Tomonori-san, you’re not thinking… not Marie.
Of course I’ve already fucked her.
How could you? The big brother
having sex with his little sister...!
Just like you, it feels amazing to fuck her cunt.
Seiichi-san, I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
Husband!!
Why are you thinking of father while
you're being fucked by me?
That guy's probably at his lover's house going
at it with some young woman around now.
Those are his so-called "business-trips".
That’s a lie. There no way-
It is true.
No way...
If you think I’m lying, look on the
hard drive of his computer.
It’s full of pictures of all the women he’s been with.
And of course, from the time when my mother fell
I'll and passed away, there are your sex tapes too!
It’s a lie. You’re lying. Such a thing...
To think that Seiichi-san would do that… Leave me,
his wife behind and have an affair ...
And then I'd be violated by his son... And my daughter... had sex with you...
What’s become of our family?
We were never a family to start with.
We were just pretending to be one.
Did you just notice now?
Pretending… to be a family…
Then, we're really not... family...?
That's right. In the end, we were just playing family.
So you should enjoy it properly. Don't you think
it'd be better to just live feeling good?
You’re right. I don't have anything anymore...
I’m back!
Huh... Mom?
Is she upstairs maybe...?
Right there feels good!
More, more, all the way in!
There. Yes, it feels good, Tomonori-san.
Fuck me harder!
There! Your cock is so hard and amazing.
It feels so good!
So much better than Seiichi-san’s!
So good. I’m going to cum,
I’m going to cum soon...!
It feels so good!
I can't hold on anymore- !
What are you doing! Mother! Onii-chan!
What? We’re having sex, of course.
Would you like to join us?
Tomonori-san’s cock is great ...
What are you saying, mother!
You’re mother and child!
What are you saying? You’ve slept with Tomonori-san,
haven’t you? Sister and brother…
What? Stop! Nooo!
Marie’s vagina is so young and pretty.
Stop, mother! Don’t put your fingers in me! No!
Is that so... I'll stop it then.
Stop...
Marie’s pussy is so wet and delicious.
No! S- Stop, mother, stop!
And let me go, Onii-chan!
Sorry, Marie, mother has lost her mind, it's impossible.
So let’s just try to enjoy it.
S-Stop...
How about it?
Something like that.
I'd like a hentai about a perverted family
where the mother and the daughter has
an affair with their in-law son/brother.
Oh, make it two daughters where one of them is
in middle school and the other's in grade school.
Nothing like that exists.