Written appointment.
WRITTEN APPOINTMENT
2nd Business Department Section 4
Udai Kensuke
Due to recent business expansion,
we order you to work at the Matsunami
branch as a special worker for a month
starting May 1
April 25, 2015
The General Affairs Department
of Ninamori Corp
2nd Business Department Section 4
Udai Kensuke
As a accompany of business expansion,
we will order you to work on matsunami branch
as a special worker for month starting May 1.
The General Affairs Department of Ninamori Corp.
It's not that big a deal really.
Question and Answer
about long distance relationship
The failure and it's countermeasure of love
It’s just a month.
Ken-chan!
I’m glad I made it on time.
Ayumu.
Why are you so surprised?
I said I had a match, but I didn’t say I wouldn't see you off,
but the truth is I sneaked out.
You’ll be kicked out of the circle.
I'm fine as long as..
Ken-chan is with me.
To all passengers, please hurry up.
You’ll be back on your days off right?
If I can...
Hey, didn’t I tell you that it's only just a month?
It’s a whole month!
Momose Ayumu was my junior in my college days.
She confessed to me before I graduated and we started going out.
She’s my beloved girlfriend right now.
Ore
w
Kanojo
Shinjiteru!
I believe
in
her
Part 1 (second virgin)
Translated by SubDesu-H
Ninamori Corp
Matsunami Branch
Gen. Affairs Accounting Dep.
Business Department
Sannomiya?
By the way, who is that again?
My senior, the president of this circle.
I told you before right?
Oh I see, yes.
You said that he’s the son of a doctor and spreads the aura of being rich?
I didn’t say that.
It's true he’s not my type.
He's so kind and I don’t like being too friendly.
I need to go back to work.
If you don’t like him then tell him straight that you don’t like him.
I’m home.
Oh, she’s still not back yet.
I even thought of surprising her.
I think we need to buy a dryer.
Because Ayumu is going to graduate, we started living together.
We were just about to start our happy life but why did the company call and summon me to the main-
Sorry, I’ll be at office
this weekend so
I think I can’t go home
Kensuke
office for only just meetings?
I even prepared to fetch you
Take care of yourself.
Ayumi
P.S I said it. I’m going
to marry you
They are rather rude in handling a worker,
But because of that we can compensate for a while.
Hey.
Senpai.
It's all clean in here.
Ayumu-kun is good at doing household chores.
I only agreed to let you use the bathroom, right Senpai?
Please do it and go home.
I think you’re the one who wants to refresh right?
It's because you’re lonely.
I didn’t say that I’m lonely!
But what did you put in your mouth instead?
That means you’re lonely.
That was because of the wine.
Let’s stop behaving like we’re strangers.
By looking at your face, I know what the people I slept with think.
Please don’t start that topic, It was a mistake.
I think your boyfriend is a nice guy.
I think he will forgive you for doing this kind of thing.
I can be serious if you want to.
I can meet him and declare to become a rival.
I don’t want that.
Then we’ll be a sex friends.
I’m already like this because Ayumu-kun’s tongue technique is so dirty.
Please take the responsibility as a sex friend.
Then I’ll go home.
Ayumu.
You’re honest Ayumu-kun.
I see, if you do it once, it will be the same for 2nd and 3rd time.
This will be really the last time.
It's big.
Lokk at it properly so that you won't forget.
I don’t want to remember this.
Do you remember what happened the other night?
I don't remember that because I was drunk.
It was my mistake, I must forget this.
I need to forget.
I think I'll take a nap before Ayumi comes home.
No way...
You think that it's over now right?
No, I didn't...
I just thought that it's dirty. That’s all.
If you don’t cum quickly, I’m gonna bite it.
What a nice face.
If he saw that face, maybe he'd fall in love with you again.
Don’t say such foolish things, he’s not that dirty.
We don’t know, he might doing this with other girls.
You drank it all right?
I just didn’t want to ruin the carpet.
Beside, it's done right? Please go home.
Why don’t we have more fun? As sex friends?
We aren’t!
I don’t want to do this again.
Eh!? What!?
Don’t you remember what happened the other night?
You came just touching there right Ayumu-kun?
Isn’t it over just doing it with the mouth?
Why?
You just came right? Why is it still... no...
Didn’t I tell you, because of that I got excited?
No!
Ayumu-kun also got excited right? Look.
No, stop this Senpai.
Your boyfriend doesn’t know this right?
Your nipples get hard when your ass is touched?
No! Don’t say such dirty things.
No! Something is touching...
Something hot is touching...
S-stop!
Meaning this part is for me.
No that part is...
The promise..
Sure, I’ll promise that I’ll make you feel good if we’re going to be sex friends.
I’m sorry Ken-chan, I’m sorry.
Does that mean you’re going to accept becoming sex friends?
Right?
You will right?
I don’t want to.
I’m going insane.
I haven't done this.
I’m really going insane!
You’ll become my sex friend right?
Right?
It's coming deeper.
I shouldn’t do this.
Deeper.
No.
Don’t push!
Unfair!
This is my first time.
What then? You’ll become my sex friend right?
Tojimaen
You’re sleeping again.
You need to move your body,
Or else there’s no point of going out.
I didn’t think that Ayumi was that active.
Wake up Ken-chan.
I came since you didn't contact me.
I didn’t think you'd come here all this way.
Did you say something?
Uh-m-m...I didn’t
Ayumu, I thought you dressed more like a kid?
Kid?
You want a kid Ken-chan?
I want to do it without putting on a condom though.
Uhm.. hey..
I’m sorry about last time.
Because I slept early, we haven’t talked that much.
Then why don’t we play more?
Right?
Let's ride this next.
Let's go.
Ferris Wheel
platform
By the way, how did you get here?
Did you ride a train?
It’s been a long trip right?
Oh.. uhmm.. a bit..
Ayumu!
They are my friends from tennis circle.
What a coincidence!
Oh I’m so surprised!
We just got here.
So is he Rei’s boyfriend?
Yes, he’s Ken-cha… Udai Kensuke-san.
I’m Chika.
Momose, we're going to borrow Udai-san.
Eh?
We need to report about Ayumu to him right?
I’m Kuroki Izumi, nice to meet you.
Just a bit.
It’s alright.
Why don’t you have an affair too Kensuke-san?
Ayumu?
Your pushy Udai-san.
The coincidence is a lie right?
Are you the one who brought those girls?
Are you jealous?
The best thing about sex friends is, there’s nothing coming between us.
I don’t want to.
He’s near us.
Is he the one with you a while ago?
He said something condom.
Don’t worry, they can’t see us until we reach the top.
She wore it because she wanted to show it.
Hey-y-y pervert.
I guard her to don’t let show it except the special day.
Except the one she likes.
For example, if you beg to her not to wear condom even it’s a danger day.
Please stop this.
Do you want me to make your baby?
What are you thinking?
In a place like this!
I’m going to be angry!
The switch is on right?
Lets have fun.
No...
I’ll let ken-chan do it.
Today is for Ken-chan.
No!
Don’t touch that part today!
Please!
No-o-o-o.
You really don’t want to?
Not with the ass but do you want to stick it using with the mouth below?
No... you shouldn’t
But.. its hot and hard compared before.
What am I saying? I shouldn’t do this today.
But if you put a condom then..
Its beautiful, its really beautiful right?
I see so she’s alone.
Hey!
Udai-san, this one is more amazing.
Have you decided?
I didn’t say that I’ll choose.
At least you can do it with the ass, please...
I’m Ken-chan’s girlfriend.
I’m sorry.
I can’t balance my self.
W-wait!
I think it stopped.
I want to be like this more.
I think the effect of suspension bridge is real.
We’re surprised right?
But this is a thrill that we can’t experience.
Oh, I’m sorry.
Then, which one do you want?
If you put a condom then.. you can..
Your boyfriend only knows among the man right?
I thought of only Ken-chan is enough for this..
The you’re a second virgin.
Second virgin?
Its big.
Its coming in.
I’m, I’m sorry...
Ken-chan.
You’re not putting a condom.
Oh, I forgot.
No, please take it out.
Its ok with this right?
Because it feels so good right?
Its ok, right?
Its alright.
So you finally accept it.
Its different right now.
But..
Wow..
wow.. its so good