I'm mad, you know.
What's this about, anyway?
Didn't you just say that you don't like the Sagemiya family?
Didn't you just say "Let's try our best"?
"Try not to lose to the Sagemiyas", right?
Hmph!
Does it feel good?
Sorry, sis..
I understand that you don't agree...
But you don't have to apologize...
I am...
Yours...
Your sperm...
it's in my hands...
You are not alone in your suffering.
I am yours, you know.
淫落の血族
Inraku no ketsuzoku
SubDESU-H Presents
ミニ・美咲～意地っ張りなニーソ～ Mini Misaki, Stubborn Knee Socks
Are you going out?
What are you saying?
I just got home.
I see...
How about you?
I know you just went to Kagu-nee's...
Y-You know that?
I know because of how you smell.
What do you mean?
Can you still smell something?
It's nothing.
How filthy.
Filthy??? You..
No!
Don't come near me!
You're gross!
Eh~~
Wait...
Don't make that pathetic face.
"I will never lose...
Against the Sagemiya family"...
You said that before, you know...
That's...
I'm not saying you're bad.
I won't say anything, if you decide to accept it.
It's just....
You're weird and disgusting!
Hey...
Why are you so depressed?
Sagemiya blood...
The blood that is inside me....
How disgusting..
I don't want to... be bothered by this...
Shun...
My twin brother...
I didn't care about him when we were kids...
Stop it...
I don't want this anymore.
Leave it to your big brother.
If you let your body learn it,
You will accept it as well.
No...
I will never lose...
I won't, ever...
He's going to see it...
My whole body...
He will see it all...
My boobs...
They're vibrating...
This is good.
It's so good.
It's making a weird sound...
My pussy...
is being touched...
No...
The hard dick...
is coming...
It's coming...
It's opening up my pussy...
I can feel it...
I'm being stirred...
I can feel your hard dick...
I can feel your hard thing...
Feels good...
Thrust it...
Thrust it more...
We're like dogs, but...
It's so good...
It's coming in...
It's good...
This sex between siblings...
I really don't like it, but...
Even though I shouldn't do this,
It feels so good!
Your dick is bigger than before.
It's good!
This type of sex... feels great!
This kind of sex... it's good...
I'm cumming...
It's so good...
and I'm cumming...
It's almost over...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!!
It's coming out...
The sperm...
is entering my body...
What is this....?
This is great...
Big brother...
Seriously, what am I dreaming about?
I've never thought of being raped by Shun...
I will never lose to the Sagemiya family...
Oh, Misaki...
We could just wash our laundry together.
No,
It's okay, I want to wash mine separately.
Is that so?
Oh, by the way, have you seen Shun-kun?
Did something happen to him?
He's been in his room since yesterday.
I was thinking he might be troubled...
I don't know.
Maybe he's letting the little things get to him.
He'll eventually come out.
It's a waste to worry about him.
Misaki, you...
really need to be friendly to Shun-kun...
You're weird and disgusting!
It's not like I'm worried about him.
Yeah, it's just that I said that to him in the wrong way.
It's me. May I...?
Oh... yes...
What do you want?
Uhm... it's...
Everyone is worried about you.
Um, how should I say this...
It's... um... Sorry.
For saying you were weird.
What's that?
Eh?
It's because I said rude things to you, so...
Oh... I see...
So that made you worried.
Stupid! It's not that I'm worried,
I just felt I had done something wrong to you.
Yes... That's why...
Hey! What are you doing!?
Sorry... Misaki..
It's just.. I get like this when you're near me...
So...
You... were...
doing a lot of releasing last night?
I see...
So you're trying your best, too.
So, it's because of me, right?
I see.
You were fighting it, too.
It's not that you're counting too much on Kagu-nee.
Hey...
It's that...
I disturbed you, right?
Your...
Eh?
So... Um...
I'm going to help you out.
Help me?
I'm telling you to take off your pants!
Wait... Misaki...
Faster!
Why?
Why is it so big?
Amazing shape...
It's throbbing...
What a weird feeling...
Misaki...
Move your hands...
Like this?
Does that hurt you?
No,
It's good...
Can you continue moving?
Yes...
Can you hold it tighter?
Like this?
It's hot...
And... it adjusted to my hand.
More...
Eh?
Do I need to hold it even tighter?
How about this?
More...
No way...
More?
You... how troublesome...
You're no good.
Eh?
What do you mean?
Male masturbation is so troublesome.
How should I do it?
Uhm... it's... can I touch you?
Eh?
Touch me??
Are you kidding?
No! You can't!
You're just killing me, like this...
Killing you...
I understand...
I did say I'd help you, anyway.
Only a little bit.
I'll let you touch me a little bit.
Seriously, only a little bit.
No... Shun is grabbing my boobs...
No...
It got even bigger...
Misaki...
It's so good...
If you rub that hard...
I didn't think he would touch my boobs like this...
With his hands...
His dick is throbbing like it's going to pop...
Not so rough... No...
Misaki...
I'm about to reach my limit...
His dick is about to release semen...
No way...
So much...
No...
I don't know about this...
What's with you...?
Producing a smell such as this...
Squirting your dirty stuff on me...
No...
You can't... Hey...
No... I didn't want it to be like this...
I can't lose to the Sagemiya family...
Not... there...
I can't...
Not... this...
This is different...
It's totally different compared to doing it myself.
No...
Don't look at it... I said no...
No way... You've only just came... Why is it big again?
No!!!
No way...
That...
What he did...
It's so good...
It's so good!!!
What will happen if he does it with me just like in the dream?
Will I feel like I have to pee?
Bad... This is bad...
I need to get out of here...
Or else, something bad is going to happen.
I'm going to make a mistake...
You don't have to deal with it by yourself.
You can tell it to me anytime...
What is this?
I just did it to him a minute ago...
Calling Kagu-nee because he couldn't do it with me...
I helped him because he's trying his best.
Does that means I'm nothing to him?
I'm holding back this much.
Does that mean he will choose Kagu-nee because of me?
I see, he's that kind of man...
Yes, he's that kind of man...
Shut up!
Don't make a sound, you idiot!
Ah?
Because you didn't talk with me...
It's your fault, you know...
I deal with it, all of the way...
But you...
Calling out Kagu-nee because you can't do it with me...
I am not a fool!
Misaki...
Hey...
You let your dick get hard...
It's stinky...
You're so perverted for letting me suck you.
Being sucked by your sister...
Making this thing big...
I am no fool!
I'm always thinking about this...
Always going crazy...
And... I even do it with myself...
I can't stop myself.
I can't even do it like you and Kagu-nee do it.
I've thought of leaving here before I go crazy.
I'm going crazy, you see.
So...
But... you...
Sorry Misaki...
I won't forgive you...
I will never forgive you...
You will be mine forever...
Only mine...
Wanna put it in?
You wanna put it in, right?
You're letting it throb a lot.
Letting it fill up with fluid...
You really wanted to do it with me, right?
But I'm the one who is going to put this perverted dick inside.
Pervert!
Ouch...
Is.. all of your dick.. inside me?
Misaki... are you ok?
You wanted this, right?
You wanted to have sex with your sister, right?
You can touch my boobs however you like.
My nipples.... are also hard...
I feel it...
My body...
It's hot...
What is this...
So good...
So good!
I feel it so much!
It's so good!
Incest is... So good...
It's coming.. Coming...
Deep inside my pussy...
The hard thing... it's touching it...
Your dick feels good...
This kind of sex... So good...
It's coming and stirring inside me...
The dick is coming...
It's is my first time, and it feels so good...
It's so good...
This is so good!
No... no...
Really... I'm really going crazy...
Good...
This... no... I can't continue...
But it's so good...
I can't hold it...
I...
Good...
Is this because we are siblings?
Is it because you are my brother?
I'm cumming!!!
So good...
The sperm is coming inside me...
It's so good...
I can't focus my thoughts...
I never thought it would be this good...
No...
Really... if I feel this more...
No way... why? You just came, didn't you?
No... wait...
No...
Hey, wait...
We have to stop...
Hey..
I don't want to feel any more of this...
No...
Wait brother... wait...
I said no...
So much of this feeling...
No...
This is painful...
Hey...
Please...
Brother...
Listen to me...
No...
I can feel so much of his dick...
It's deep inside...
I'm being stirred up by brother's dick...
No...
Again... I...
Continue it...
He's going to release it inside...
I'm going to get pregnant...
It's coming...
I'm cumming, brother...
Brother's sperm...
Coming inside me..
Stupid! Pervert! Fool! Slow! Disgusting Pervert!
Even after I begged you that much, you still continued thrusting into me!
Really, you're so stupid!
Fool! Stupid!
I hate you, brother!
S..Sorry...
It's just that...
I will do anything...
Is that so?
Then, it's a promise.
From now on...
Forever... only do it with me.
Ok?