Subbed by SubDESU-H
Suzuki Mirano
Extremely Dirty
From the tip of Toya-kun's dick...
There's juice coming out of it...
It's like my body is getting hot...
Good.
I licked this much and...
It's getting harder.
The veins can be clearly seen.
Toya-kun's dick tastes...
So good and masculine.
You don't have to hold it in...
Release all of your dirt...
Fully inside my mouth...
Yeah, it's getting better.
Just go on with it.
Ok, I understand...
Yumi's drawings are really...
getting better than before.
It's because of the advice Kanzaka-san gave me...
Ok. So then, can that Kanzaka-san also let me look at the scenario?
Hey Rumi, I'm looking at it seriously so don't pull it.
Hey, Boss.
I'll check yours so get it ready...
Oh... Ok...
Kanzaka Itsuki-san.
He's from Soma Agency, which is an advertising agency, and he volunteered to work with us on our new adult games.
He is also known as S.A. manager.
He is an elite worker who is too much for our company which just started it's business.
Not only is he working for our company,
but he's also using his skills gained in the game manufacturing company
and gave me a lot of advice.
He's arrogant, but...
He's friendly, cool and he's like an approachable big brother.
Well, it's about something like that.
You're getting better in other things too.
Right?
Then, I won't be punished so you'll give me a reward for this, right?
Hey Sis...
Sure...
But I still have some work left to do so wait till next time.
Really?
It's a promise then.
Yeah.
Then, I'll be going.
Tsurumiku Style Game Manufacturing Co.
SubDESU-H Presents
Yume Kui
- Kuzuha Rumi Lesson Part -
Recently, this artist Fujinomori Akino-san is in the spotlight.
She's still a newbie but she has started to get popular.
So I think there will be even more fans soon.
Oh, I see her in magazines sometimes.
I see.
I think it's hard right now but
I think I'll try to put her in the cast.
Well, asking lovely Izumu-sama for this is the best choice.
Didn't you say the same thing to me, right?
It was even yesterday.
Is that so?
Oh... I see.
Oh, welcome Takatsuki-san.
Long time no see.
How are you?
Long time no see, Noe-san.
And the one right there is... Is that you Kanzaka?
Long time no see...
Hello, SFC Business Manager Takatsuki-san.
Why is a person like you in here?
I heard that you transfered to major business.
Yeah, I was dispatched by SA to them.
SA?
It's our rival company.
I think this is also an undesirable but inseparable relation.
Then, what are you doing here?
It's a bit of...
Chitchat coming along with information gathering.
You must do it while your in business hours.
You're disturbing Tempo-san.
Really... hey, we're going.
Yes...
Uhg... Who is that beauty going along with Takatsuki?
Ah, she's Kitahama Kyouko-san,
I think she's the daughter of the Chairman of SF company where Takatsuki-san is working.
She's in the hand of Takatsuki-san right now and
I think she's studying Business right now.
Hmmm.
Daughter of a Chairman...
Hello.
You're... Kanzaka-san right?
Are you here for work?
Well yeah.
I see.
Is it alright not to be at Takatsuki's side?
I'm useless.
No one expects much from me who is just working through the influence of my parents.
Ohhh.
What a waste, you're even beautiful.
That's also an excellent power.
You can aim high by using that.
But I...
Is that so?
But your eyes tell me that you're not satisfied with your current status.
Pure Maiden Adventure Game
Whisk it! Mikocchu!　Draft
Try reading this...
This is our new work's draft.
I suddenly want to hear your opinion.
This is the first time that someone has asked something from me.
Uhm... If it's ok with you, can I send you an e-mail?
I want to have a talk with you.
Sure, I'll be waiting.
It's me...
I see...
Tomorrow... in the Afureko studio...
I understand...
My stomach...
Inside my stomach...
It's like it's been stirred...
Faster...
It hurts...
Ok... You can come...
I will receive all Toya-kun's...
Come inside... me!!
Toya...kun...
Dubber's raw voice is really amazing...
It's unlucky for Yumi but it's good you came along right?
No... uhm... How should I say this.
When Yumi saw this, she turned all red and collapsed and...
I thought she wouldn't come along...
Well, I'll give Yumi a different reward.
But it's so embarrassing that the scenario I wrote finished by adding a dub on to it.
And I got horny because the dubber read the dialog so pervertedly.
No... that part is getting wet...
My nipples are also erect inside my bra...
Does the dubber also get horny?
Huh?
No... it's nothing.
What am I saying?
Sorry, you don't like it?
No... It was so sudden so... I just got surprised...
No... I feel weird...
And... Kanzaka-san is touching me and my heart beat won't stop...
Your breathing is rough... What's the matter Rumi?
What's the matter?
Did you get horny by hearing that kind of voice?
No... I'm not...
Stop...
Don't touch my boobs...
No... don't touch my nipples...
My nipples are sensitive right now...
No... Don't look at it.
It's wet down there...
It's embarrassing...
No... don't touch...
If you touch that part... it will get even wetter...
I can hear it making a dirty sound...
I'm feeling good in a place like this.
No... no...
If you do that more... I'll... I'll...
No!!
I think I rushed a bit...
Good job.
Oh, Good job.
Sorry for calling you out so suddenly.
No problem...
Inbox
Kyouko
Are you free
for dinner?
Reply
Sorry, I have an emergency appointment.
I'll bring you to a delicious ramen shop that even a Maniac like you doesn't know about next time.
Really?
I'll looking forward to it then.
Sorry, I think I drank a bit too much.
I've bothered you... even though I'm the one who called you...
No, I wanted to have some time to talk to you too.
It's not as good as a room but rest as you like.
Yes...
Pardon the intrusion...
Kanzaka-san... this man is...
Eh? what are you doing?
Hey hey, why are you surprised now?
Kanzaka-san... what's this...?
You remember I gave you a document before right?
Eh? Yes... I think that was Whink, Mikocchu the one which is about a witch...
What's with that...?
You showed it to Takatsuki right?
Eh? I didn't do that!
I think Takatsuki brought a new work at the journal company.
And the details of the scenario in the work are all the same as ours.
What's the meaning of this...?
No way... I didn't show it to anyone!
He didn't even tell me anything!
Ah... I gave it to you because it was you.
It's the truth!
Please believe me!
You can say excuses all you like...
No!
Stop, stop it please!
I really...
Stop...
I would never betray you...
Ou...ch...
Noooo!!
Don't look at it!
I didn't want to show it to a man like you who recognized me...
Was it an accident?
Yes...
A person like me who's already rotten... even Kanzaka-san will...
Yes, I like you even more.
A beauty who hides her secret in her bangs...
You're gorgeous and mysterious compared to the sluts out there...
Kanzaka-san...
No... If you do that hard...
Do you remember we're questioning you?
Don't get happy in a situation like this.
No, I didn't intend to...
Don't lie.
You're happy, look how wet you are...
I... really... didn't do anything to betray you.
Is that so?
Then I will rape you now with this...
I will listen to you if you confess.
I didn't do anything.
I see.
Then be prepared...
No!
Really, the new one's are tight as expected.
It hurts...
How is it now?
Are you still saying the same even though I've already taken your virginity?
No problem... If you're going to make me your woman then...
It's a happy thing for me...
You...
It's hard for me because you are not going to believe me...
Please... believe me...
I didn't do anything...
So you appreciate me that much.
Then Kyouko, are you still coming with me even when you're going to betray the SFC or doing any kind of crime?
Of course...
If I can be by your side then...
I will do anything.
Well then, starting today, you will be my slutty slave.
Master...
What's... What's this...?
My pussy is being stirred and rubbed by master's dick...
I'm... I'm going crazy...
Hey... it's still to early to be worn out.
It's deep...
It's reaching the womb...
My master is thrusting deeper to my womb...
It's too intense...
It's coming out inside...
My master's hot sperm...
Is filling my womb...
There's a lot of sperm...
I think it will fertilize...
What are you...
Oh, I thought of putting evidence of you being my slave.
It's a nipple piercing...
Isn't it good that it's like a princess style?
Wait...
Yo!
Kanzaka-san?
Uhm... The computer I used broke suddenly.
So I thought of buying a new one...
Then... as the payment of that time... I'll be the one to pay for the computer.
Really?
I'm glad that Kanzaka-san's mansion is near by.
I'm sorry, I think I let you buy an expensive one...
Hm? I think it's not that much.
But...
You gave the money and didn't even ask me anything.
I was a bit surprised.
Did you fall in love all over again?
Well...
I just thought that the part of you which doesn't say much is so manly and cool.
Well, as for that, I will let you work harder though.
Eh?
Hey.
What's with this naive scenario?
Did you think that you'll pass with this soulless H scene?
I haven't had any experience so it can't be helped if there's no feeling!
And besides... why is the Boss here?
And.. who is that girl anyway?
Hey Kyouko.
Yes.
Hey... why is that thing here?
Sorry Rumi-chan, I don't like this but...
I'm being threatened by Kanzaka-san.
Look, you can even make that face.
You can write if you remember that face.
But if you say you can't, then I will let you experience it.
What are you...
Kyouko...
Yes... master...
No...
Don't lick that part...
No... stop... let me go...
Good, you know it.
The more you resist, the more the man gets fired up.
I didn't know about that!
Stop...
No...
Don't lick it...
Uhm...
What should I do now?
Just masturbate right there as you like.
No way...
No...
Hey, I'm letting you experience this precious moment.
Don't moan and start typing before you forget the feeling.
I can't do that...
I can't type...
It's hot...
What's that...
I will help you out so that you can write more H scenes.
No way...
No! no! You can't!
Don't rub your penis...
Stop it...
Please... I beg you.
Rumi...
Have you ever seen an Ero game that stops when you say that?
No... no... no...
I haven't experienced it yet...
So that big and hard thing won't come in...
It's impossible that it will come in!!
It hurts... It hurts...
Stop it... stop it...
You can only experience that pain on your first time.
Have fun with it.
I don't want this pain anymore!
You'll feel good later.
You're writing it in your scenario right?
It's different between that and this...
Don't be rude...
My pussy is going to break.
Just type in the words.
If you can't type until the ejaculation scenario.
I will release it inside.
No...
Don't do that...
Hey!
Yes...
Where are you calling from?
It's Yumi.
I think she will be worried about you.
I need to call her so that she will not worry that you'll not be going home.
What are you saying!?
You don't want Yumi to get panicked right?
I will give you five minutes.
Satisfy Yumi in that time limit or else I will release it inside.
Also if you say unnecessary things, I will let Yumi come here too.
Eh? Wait...
Hello? Sis?
Yumi...?
Sis...
Where are you right now?
Why didn't you call me?
No... uhm... Sorry.
I haven't called you because I was doing a lot of things...
Uhhhh you just went out to buy a computer right?
I will get worried if you don't call me, even the store is already closed.
Sorry...
And... where are you now...?
I'm at my friend's house...
Friend? who is that?
Who's house?
Is she someone I know?
Uhm... it's a secret for now...
I will go home later on.
So please don't worry.
How long is the "later on"?
What's the thing you need to do at your friend's house?
I can go home after few days...
Sis... What happened? Are you ok?
Hey sis!
I'm ok... It's nothing...
I will come home in a few days.
Don't worry...
How unlucky... It's almost time...
I will do it...
I will do my work here... It's almost time...
I will do it properly from now on...
Yumi... please... understand...
Hey sis...
What happened?
No...
If you thrust that hard...
Good...
It's so good...
I didn't like this...
I really didn't like this...
But my waist...
I'm being penetrated by a dick,
and my pussy is all wet.
It's so good...
I can't bear this...
It's time,
as I promised, I will release it inside.
No...
Inside?
Inside my womb...?
No... no...
It's coming...
No!!!
Hey...
Sis...
What happened...?
What is that voice right now...?
What is that thing you need to do that far?
Hey... are you alright?
Yes...
Don't worry.