SubDESU-H Presents
The Invisible Stud Returns
Part Two
I won't forgive him!
Fujisawa-san has also been attacked?
This is quite a problem.
We can't do anything if we can't see the opponent.
Yeah, maybe I’ll bring the pill for self-defense.
It’s gone!
W-Why?!
Maybe that last time, the invisible man was here after all.
And he stole it?
M-Maybe it's possible.
Besides, where did you acquire that pill?
I-I was...
What? A mysterious old man dropped it?
What did he look like?
Leave it to me.
He looked like this.
You...
I remember it because the impact was strong.
Are you making a fool of me?
Who the heck will wear this kind of attire around this time?
No, you can't underestimate the urban area.
Excuse me.
Oh?
Welco...
I want meat bun and bean bun,  pizza takoyaki bun, 2 of each please.
Mie-kun, catch him!
Hyaa!! Damn, how about this!
Oh my!!!
Is it ok to do something like this?
It can't be helped, this is the only way to stop that invisible man.
What a weird attire.
It really is.
H-How cruel, you must be kind to old people.
You're the one at fault to begin with.
Yes, because of your pill, cruel things happened to me...
Mie-san, how can you say such things?
Anyway, lend us a hand.
If you don’t have a thing to catch the invisible man,
Then give us a pill that we can't see and a pill which will make us see the others.
Do you understand?
A pill which you can't see and a pill that'll make you able to see.
This lady is scary when you make her mad.
Hey...
What a bad reputation.
Yes I have it, I have it.
I have the pill so please don't take my life...
So then, good luck!
Is it ok to let him escape?
I think he's of no use even if he is here.
Well, maybe...
Then let us...
Wait.
You can’t.
Why?
We don’t know what you might do when you become invisible.
I’m happy that you know me very well, Fujisawa-san.
Ok, let’s take it guys.
But why now?
Well... we're testing it.
Wow, I can’t see you guys.
Alright, it's ok.
Huh? Mie-san, did you take the pills?
I can’t take it in this kind of situation.
But I can’t see you.
You joined the confusion.
I mean, I can see you guys all.
Whaaat?!
What does this mean?
Even though we became invisible?
Do you understand?
A pill which you can't see and a pill that'll make you able to see.
So that's what it means.
Ehhhh?!
We become the ones that are unable to see?
This is complicated.
I don’t understand.
Japanese is so difficult.
Then, right now it's only Mie-san who can see us?
Then what about the other pill?
Let me try it.
How's it? What can you see?
What's it?
I can see it.
What? An invisible man?
No, its violet.
Huh?
Loli’s is black.
Sensei's is sky blue.
Thin's is t-back!
What?!
Wait, you mean you can see the...
Eh? T-back?
Eh? Umm...
Don't you think t-back is too early for you?
Mie-kun, don't look here.
I don't think that's the problem we're facing now...
That's right sensei, it's not rare to wear t-back now days.
I wont forgive you if you see mine.
No, I mean...
Wow!
What's it this time?
If I focus, I can see under the under wear.
N-No!!!
My, my.
I’ll kill you if you watch it.
What’s it this now?
I’m sorry, I’ve gone too far.
What do you see?!
Anyway, you must get that old man back here.
Ok.
I’m off~
Wait, we can’t see so what about the store?
Did he leave already?
Really, he didn't think about anything.
We're done for if the invisible man is here.
Anyway, its dangerous to go out so let's stay put.
Sorry guys, I’ll treat you to some tea later.
What a nice view.
If I miss this moment, the name Mie-san will fall.
Hey hey Fujisawa, I think it's bad to be a cashier if you're topless.
Welcome, how about a rice ball along with my boobs?
I think the store will surely prosper if it’s like this.
But we’ll be scolded by the police before the income will increase.
Oh, loli is showing off her lower body while reading the magazine, eh?
Even if I sit down, men will let their's be big so this is the real "stand" reading?
Entry number 3, thin’s room play.
When I think about everyone watching me, I...
Oh no, it's so embarrassing.
Sensei, I can see it.
It's ok, I'm not shy to show my boobs anywhere.
Otonashi-san, total nudity is bad.
Oh, it's fine, you've watched it all the time.
Yeah, but if you’re going to watch, you must start from the young one's first, right?
Look, does anyone like my body?
I can let you touch it just a little.
I can’t hold it any longer...
Here I go!
Nooo! What?! Who is it?!
W-W-What? Is it the invisible man?
Yes, I’m the invisible man.
It's Mie-kun’s voice no matter how I hear it.
What are you doing while we can’t see?
I thought you went to find that old man?
H-He's over doing it.
I know it even if I can’t see.
Hey, what are you doing to my students?
Besides, this is a convenience store.
What about that old man?
If you’re going to attack, do it to me.
Sensei!
Stop it if you’re going to do it here.
I don’t know what the problem is now.
Sensei.
Run away while you can.
Sensei!
Don't worry about me, go quickly.
Hurry up!
Sensei let's go...
Sensei...
I said don’t do it here.
I-If you want to do it, then do it now.
I said don’t.
As expected from sensei, you cleaned it.
No...
Stop it, don’t lick there...
Then it's ok if it's here, right?
Sheesh, what do you think you are doing?
I’m sorry.
By the way, I’m over here.
You!
You’re here?
What are you doing?
No, there’s someone here who I can’t see.
If Mie-san can’t see it, then it's the invisible man!
Eh?
Mie-kun, don’t let him go.
Ok, hey don’t move.
Hey Mie-kun, my boobs...
You fool...
How about the invisible man?
He escaped.
You’re a fool.
That's because Fujisawa-san used such an erotic voice.
I didn’t.
You felt it and used such an erotic voice.
You used such a voice when I touched you.
I said I didn't!
Yesterday was quite troublesome.
I got this from the invisible man.
I never thought that you were the suspect.
I watched all your foolish moves.
Oh, what an honor.
At that time, even when I was there, you tried not to notice.
And you even lied that I was there and stole a pill,
And I figured it all out after that.
You watched it, what a pervert.
But I don’t understand, you’re the one who attacked loli, right?
Maybe there was another invisible man other than me.
Maybe so.
But it’s true that you took the pill and hid it, right?
If you say my actions are foolish then the situation is understandable.
How about a payment for not telling?
No.
Why?
What?! You don't like boys?
I think it's a trauma.
When I was young, I was inspired by a prince charming.
But real boys are filthy, foolish, pervert and rude.
I won’t deny it.
The first boy I did, he also just wanted to try it.
Is that so?
You've gone through quite a lot, huh?
From what I heard if you want to do it, I’ll comfort you.
What part of what I said did you listen to?
If you won't then I’ll tell everyone.
R-Really I can’t do it to boys.
Don’t say such things.
Eww, gross...
Oh?
So you did have it.
I’ll let you have a taste of the invisible man.
No, don’t touch it.
My nipples have been touched.
How’s it? How does it feel to be touched by invisible man?
That part... no it's wet!
Don't suck the nipples so much...
The finger is inside mine...
No... if you touch that too hard I'll...
No!!!
I did it...
Oh, a customer.
Welcome.
Eh? You can't see anyone? Don’t worry about it.
Here you go.
Thank you so much.
Well, lets talk a bit while resting.
By the way, how did you acquire the pill?
I picked it up when Fujisawa-senpai dropped it.
What?
But I didn’t know Fujisawa-san at that time.
I picked up the medicine bottle at the bargain mall.
I chased her to give back the bottle, but...
She disappeared.
When I saw the bottle, the instruction were there.
She used it to buy that bag.
That bitch.
But the pill was in the safe box.
Because I returned it before she brought it.
She gets scary when she doesn't have it.
Yeah.
So, what about the last time it was gone?
Ah, that time, you guys said you’ll use the pill to find me, so I hid it.
I remembered the code of the safe box.
Even if I reveal the secret it will be for nothing, eh?
But it's weird, right?
To like girls even though I’m a girl.
I don’t know about you liking girls or hating boys,
But I think it's ok.
You really think so?
Yeah, I don't mind it at all.
Mie-san...
But I heard the voice from below and where are you watching while talking?
Don’t mind that too.
But it’s a matter of time before you overcome your hate for boys.
Eh?
Don't you think so?
You got this wet when you were touched by a boy.
Don’t say such things!
But it's all wet.
No!
No!!
But it’s such a waste, you've got this nice body.
Yeah it is, but...
Oh, you said it.
Good morning!
Oh? Mie-kun?
Oh shit...
Yuri-chan!
You’re not here?
We’re here!
S-Stupid, don’t call her.
Change your clothes
Sheesh, are you skipping?
Hey Yuri-chan, what are you doing?
Uhm.. Mie-san just...
Mie-kun, where are you?
As I thought, the effect will wear off right here.
You were invisible just now, right?
Umm...
So it was really you?
No... this is...
Yes, it was all me.
W-Wait!
What?
Don't you want to know where I got the pil from?
Mie-san, the blood.
Hint 1: bargain hall.
Oh do you have an idea?
My, because of the bag, someone brought the pill.
I-I understand, what should I do?
Isn't it obvious?
Is that the only thing on your mind?
Yes!!
What are you looking at? Help me out here?
What?! No way!!
Huh?! Are you sure?
Yes, I am!
Wow! It's senpai's boobs.
No, Yuri-chan...
I’m sorry, senpai.
Wow! It's so delicious!
Please, don’t lick it that hard.
No, I wont!
Hey, she said her lips is lonely.
Wow! It's senpai's lips.
Wow! It's delicious.
It feels so good.
It's soft!
Alright! Next is here.
Firstly use the finger.
Eh?! I can’t do that.
Senpai's is right in front of me!
Don't Yuri-chan, please stop it...
That's good, do it more.
Senpai, I'm sorry. I’m sorry!
Ok, ok that's good.
After that, move the finger like this and that.
L-Like this?
W-What is this feeling?
I-It's wet.
Hey, what is this?
I've been found out.
Ok, ok, I’ll make you feel good.
No... no...
Mie-kun, stop it.
No don’t, if you move it like that, I'll...
Don't... I’ll cum...
Alright! Let it out!
No!!!
M-My pee is pouring onto senpai's body.
Wow!
Hey, let her clean it.
That too?
No. No!
Wow! It feels so good!
Hey, don’t feel good all by yourself.
I’m sorry, senpai.
I’ll do it for you.
Huh? What? That's alright, there's no...
No, you don't have to do it...
Wow! It's delicious!
No, no don't...
I can't stop shaking my hips.
Alright, I’ll give you my present.
What? Mie-kun what are you doing?
Don't... Don't let it out.
Senpai, it feels good, right?
Give it to me...
Senpai give it to me...
Sheesh, now you have to keep it a secret from everyone, ok?
Ok.
What's with that face?!
I’m sorry!!
See you later, guys!