SubDESU-H.net
I'm about to... burst.
Makoto
W
My Cousin, who's a childhood friend from a rural area will be coming over this summer vacation.
That crude, rough, and tomboyish girl.
I always got into trouble whenever I was with her.
Even so... I still liked her.
On that day...
Kouichi, you idiot!
My family moved away
leaving that argument unresolved.
I never met her again, up until now.
Ah, coming!
Ah, hi. Long time no see, Kouichi-kun.
Y-Yeah... Long time no see, Makoto.
You let your hair grow.
Thanks for the meal!
The food was really great!
Really? I'm glad.
I did my best to practice cooking, you know.
Ah, I'll be cleaning the dishes then.
Sorry for that.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Just make yourself comfortable for now.
Okay!
Was she that cute before?
She's very different from before.
Also, did she already forget about that?
Makoto, do you want to drink some tea?
Makoto?
Oh, she's asleep.
She really has become beautiful.
I need to apologize for that argument,
and that too properly...
M-Makoto-san?
Makoto...
No, no, this is bad.
What am I thinking?
Y-Yeah, I was planning to apologize earlier.
If I did something stupid, I will lose any chance to make it up to her.
But does she still remember our argument from before?
Or maybe I am the only one thinking about it...?
No... But...
Geez, what are you moping around there for?
Ah, busted.
What, your hair...?
Ignore that! Why won't you do something to me?
You like refined and long-haired girls, right?
Hey Kouichi, what kind of girl do you like?
Eh, why are you asking?
Just tell me!
Well, she has to be cute, feminine,
and has long hair.
What? That's basically the opposite of me!
My hair's short and I can't get it longer even if I want to!
Do you really hate me that much?
Eh? Wh— No... Idiot... I mean...
I've had it!
Kouichi, you idiot!
I thought you hated me...
And then you moved away soon after...
So you did remember.
There's no way I'd forget that.
It's been on my mind all this time.
Is it wrong for me to love you even now?
Get it already will you, idiot.
Makoto, I'm sorry!
I also love you!
I have always loved you for as long as I can remember!
But you...
Hey... Is it okay even if I don’t have long hair?
Of course.
But I'm rough and childish...
That's not true at all!
You're cute.
Really?
But... But... Wait.
So, why are you wearing that again?
I told you it's okay if you don't have long hair, right?
But, I feel embarrassed.
I feel like I'll be more honest with myself if I wear this.
Can't I?
Alright then.
No, my nipples are...
...getting wet.
Don't... No...
Makoto, you’re getting hot down there.
Kouichi...
Makoto, we are ready.
Wait...
Let me do it first.
Huh? W-wait...
I'll be inserting your cock here.
M-Makoto...
I'm okay.
It's tight...
Are you okay?
Don’t force yourself.
I'm okay.
It does not hurt.
Actually, it feels a bit good.
It's because I've been "practicing" while thinking about you.
I guess...
Practicing...?
You can move now, Kouichi.
Make sure you enjoy this as much as you can!
Hey, does it feel good?
Do you feel good inside me?
Y-Yeah.
It really... feels quite good.
Really? I'm happy.
I'm really happy...
Kouichi, do it more!
I feel it...
It feels good!
Kouichi...
Kouichi...!
Makoto...
I'm about to cum.
Keep going, please.
Feels like something exploded inside me.
Kouichi...
I am not done yet.
No, I don't want this...!
No, this is embarrassing!
Idiot!
Why did you take it off?
I want to do it properly.
I want to do it without that.
Okay, Makoto?
But, but, but...
If I don’t wear that,
you might end up saying "not cute", again.
I never said that in the first place!
You’re cute, just like that.
You're much cuter.
Didn’t I tell you?
I love you even now!
But Kouichi...
Kouichi...
Kouichi...!
I love you...
I love you!
So, why did you lie to me?
Eh... Normally you’d get embarrassed with that question right?
And we were still kids back then...
What's with that!?
I was embarrased asking that question too, you know!
And I had to needlessly do things just because you tried to hide your embarrassment.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I learned how to cook.
I tried to grow my breasts.
I wasn't able to fix my short hair though.
I'm sorry already... geez.
What's with the growing breast thing?
In any case, you were too hard to read in the first place.
Normally, you were so bratty.
And then you suddenly asked that...
So it's my fault then?
Kouichi-kun, just wait a little more.
Makoto, you're still putting that on?
I can make dishes better with this on.
Besides, aren’t you happy to have your dream girl standing in your kitchen?
I already apologized for that.
Hey, don't. It’s dangerous here.
No...
No... S-Stop it...
Hey could it be, that you get turned on whenever you wear that?
That's not it.
Idiot...
Then, why aren't you wearing any bra?
B-But...
How about here?
Don't!
So you're covered here.
No...
Actually... I was wearing this whenever I "practiced".
Whenever I was learning about sex... that's why–
Looks like my erotic switch got flipped.
So this is Kouichi's...
I didn't glance clearly before...
... but this big thing has actually entered my pussy?
Alright... I don’t know if I'll be able to do it right though.
Okay, go for it.
Am I doing this right...?
Kouichi...?
So it feels good for him...
I'm happy.
Somehow, it also feels good for me...
Kouichi...
Kouichi...!
It's been getting bigger...
Just a little more...
Wow, it's hot...
I-I'm sorry, Makoto.
So this is how he tastes.
I wonder if there's still some left inside.
Did it feel good?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, let's do it... Please.
Wow, you’re really wet down there.
Don’t say such weird things, idiot!
Then here I go.
It's in.
I inserted it all the way in again.
Hey, you...
Kouichi's big...
I think it feels better than yesterday.
It's good...
No...!
Idiot!
This position is embarrassing!
But it seemed like you were just going to cum by yourself.
You're way too ecstatic about this.
No...
No...!
Idiot...!
It feels tingly at my lower part.
Hey...
Hey...!
Rub it more here.
Wow, it really feels good.
No!
I feel like cumming.
Let's finish this facing each other...
On the bed...
Let's continue with this until we finish, Kouichi.
Yeah, here I go, Makoto.
It's hitting me inside.
Amazing, it's rubbing in!
In that deep place...
I feel so full with your cock inside me.
Do it, do it more!
Hit me more inside.
My nipples feel good.
That's it.
No... I'm about to cum!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming, Kouichi!
Kouichi!
Makoto, I'm about to...
Inside... Release it all inside me!
Kouichi...! I'm cumming...!
Makoto, you were very cute just now.
Idiot.
Geez, it's all because you interrupted me while I was cooking.
I'll get it prepared soon...
...so let’s eat it together.
Kouichi-kun.
Then afterwards let's do it again.
Kouichi-kun, it's already done.
Kouichi-kun?
He's asleep.
Hey, Kouichi-kun.
Kouichi-kun?
Hey, wake up already.
We'll be eating now.
Geez...
Hey, Kouichi!
What are you sleeping in for?
And you even made me cook food for you.
You...
You...!
Wake up!
Makoto...
Monkey...
What!? Who's the monkey!?
You're not referring to me, right!?
Oh hey, Makoto...
Good morning...
Don't you "Good Morning" me!
I'm asking you: who is the monkey?!
There are many living creatures with that name.
Eh... monkey?
You were really amazing back there.
Jumping on me like an energetic monkey...
So you’re really referring to me?
Unforgivable!!
Are you awake now?
Yea...
Wait... That outfit is...
Yep. It's a naked apron.
You are so slow, for noticing just now.
You're the naughty one who was pretending to be asleep.
Aren’t you the one who pretended to sleep?
But, that's really amazing!
It’s as if you're a real pervert.
What in the world are you saying!?
Do you know how much I "practiced" for?
You said that already.
Your "sex practice".
Even if you boast to me about your "single play"...
You really have become erotic, haven't you?
You think so?
So I'm erotic then.
Wow, she burst out of the can!
I was doing "that" thing, and "this" thing while thinking of you...
I'm really going to show it off to you now!
It’s the same even if you make your voice cuter.
Even if you're capable of running around mountains energetically,
you’re still the type who would try to catch large frogs instead.
I love frogs!
Especially the part where you don't know what they're thinking.
How about crabs?
I hate crabs.
They're painful if you touch.
That's not it!
I become slutty only because you are around!
It's the same even now.
The happiest moments were the ones that I spent with you.
Makoto...
Besides...
Besides, I haven't tried it out yet,
but I also want to try this place out.
Won't you?
You erotic gal....
Oh my...!
But you know,
You've been naked all this time as well.
Oh my...!
SubDESU-H.net