www.SubDESU-H.net
If this was going to be about school pictures, I meant to refuse.
Class 3-D
Going Home From School Club
Miyanagi
Sena
Pinup Idol
Hey... you, you know me, don’t you?
Y-Yes!
N-No way I wouldn't  know!
She’s... Miyanagi Sena-san!
A super erotic pinup idol who goes by the stage name of “Sena”!
She started her career two years ago...
...and her pictures always push the envelope on what’s “normal”.
This helped her rise straight to the top of the porn industry.
Swimsuits and string bikinis.
And pasties... coochie-covers... condom-swimsuits...
Dildos in her.
Slippery wet with lotion...
With every new release, her intensity goes up.
She keeps turning her fans on more and more.
Um, uh, I’m a huge fan!
Wow! Sena-senpai is right here...
Looking at me...
She’s looking at me!
Thanks.
And so...?
You two people came to talk to me even after I said I wasn’t submitting pictures.
Hame-dori: First-person porno
Does this mean you absolutely “need” my hame-dori picture?
Or rather, do you want to take one with me?
You want to... ”challenge” me, I suppose.
“Challenge”?
There are some students who refuse to be in the school's hame-dori album.
Among them, there's a celebrity that we simply must have in the album.
I want you to steal hame-dori pictures from all of them.
“Steal”?! But... how?
In addition to the hame-dori album, our school has yet another tradition.
And that is...
Gambling!
Girls put metaphorical chastity belts on themselves.
It is a woman’s decision to remove the belt for a man.
Whether that be for money or for life is up to the woman.
We will have a serious duel with a woman’s chastity on the line.
And that is...
Shousen Academy Girl-Gamble Challenge.
The VP of the student council, Kiritani Konome, shall referee!
Pisu
Sub
Hame
Desu
!
-H
W
So, Sena-san... Please state your rules for the challenge!
Hey, kid... if you’re my fan, how about this for an idea?
I make DVDs, photo collections... magazines – I do all sorts of work.
But among all my roles, there are two that are my favorites.
If you can guess which two they are, I’ll have sex with you.
If not...
That’s a rather difficult challenge.
She’s done photo shoots for tons of magazines.
I hear she’s a very busy idol.
Guessing the correct two would have the same probability as picking the correct two cards from a deck.
But, the probability is not zero.
The ground rule of a Girl-Gamble Challenge is that the girl makes up the rules.
It’s supposed to favor the girl.
The boy is supposed to overcome this impossible hurdle to steal the girl’s honor.
His one saving grace is that, as a member of the committee,
he is allowed to contest the near-impossible rules and request changes.
What will you do, Tamao-kun?
Um... Is that all I have to do?
Well then, Tamao-kun, your answer, please.
Okay! Then...
Well, he’ll never guess it.
I think it’s these two.
Why those...?
I can tell from your work that you have a very professional attitude.
It’s your mission to take on the camera and turn on all the boys who look at your pictures.
I get the impression that with each new work you want to get ever more intense.
That’s why I chose this magazine, which featured your first from-the-heart interview...
...and, with that in mind, your newest work.
These two are...
...seeing through a girl’s life philosophy like that...
I was so young when I did that interview.
It’s even more embarrassing than having my butthole show through a string bikini!
I thought you’d never guess correctly.
Oh, fine! You w-win.
You’re Tamao Tsukamu-kun, right?
I had no idea I had a fan who read so deeply into what I do.
Guess I lost.
Hame-dori, eh?
This is my first time, so please, since you represent my fans... be gentle, okay?
Okay!
...Wait, this is your first time?
Shoot in progress.
Do not enter
Sena-senpai...
Miyanagi Sena ...
Sena... Sena...
Oh, shit, I can’t hold back!
Sena-senpai...
Her butt!
Her naked butt!
It feels like a peach!
Sena-senpai’s... scent!
No!
Don’t... not so... don’t lick so much...
No... he’s obsessed... licking so thoroughly.
My nipples have slipped out occasionally during shoots, but...
No one has seen this part of me before.
This is... Idol Sena’s... live pussy!
But... is this really okay?
Even though this is a “challenge”, I still feel like I’ll be raping her if I win.
If you really don’t want to do it, then you can turn it down.
A Girl-Gamble is not compulsory.
But if you accept the challenge...
Wha... Senpai? Konome-senpai?!
You will be a person living in the realm of competition.
You understand, don’t you?
In the realm of competition, gender doesn’t matter.
What does matter is who wins and who loses.
And if you win, the girl must serve you.
Do the opposite of your instincts – plunge yourself into a challenge you'll probably lose.
And if you win, then you must wave your dick proudly.
Y-Yes!
N-Not so... Stop...
Oh... I really feel like I’m melting...
...my insides are falling out...
Yes.
I will do it.
I will steal your virginity from you.
I will fuck you.
I will be... your first man!
Sena-senpai... I’m inside!
This can’t be... it’s so big...
How is this... possible...?
Senpai!
Senpai... are you okay?
I... can’t hold back...
I’m sorry.
Does it hurt?
It’s not that it hurts...
It’s not that it hurts...?
You want me to say I'm turned on, right?
You just broke the hymen of the most popular fetish idol.
So don’t worry about how I feel.
Just do whatever you want.
Really? Sena-senpai!
Senpai... Senpai!
What... is this...
He came inside?
My insides are throbbing...
It feels good...
Senpai!
Um...
Wow!
I’ve made lots of fetish videos where I suck on and lick bananas and candy and the like.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
So even though this is my first time, I’m used to it.
You’re right...
I feel the impact of those images throbbing inside my head.
But it’s... my penis... so it’s hard to accept as reality.
But... is doing this alright with you?
Doing...
All this stuff... for me...?
S-Sena-senpai!
Um... I’m almost...
You won the challenge, right?
So I don’t mind sucking you off a little.
I used to be everyone’s favorite fetish idol.
But you turned me into a woman...
So please, don’t make me beg for it.
It makes me embarrassed.
Sena-senpai!
Yes... Yes...
This feels great!
Not again... I can’t stop it!
Sena-san... my name...
Can you call my... name?
Tamao-kun... Tamao-kun!
Tamao-kun!
Oh no... I’m... my mind is flying away...
Yes! I’ll try my hardest!
Please cum!
Harder! Harder!
Oh... please... yes!
So... um...!
Sorry about the quality of the camera, but, I’m taking a pic!
It’s okay.
I’ll let you take a picture of any part of me you like.
I see.
So he won.
That the challenge just so happened to be in a subject that was his specialty – beginner’s luck.
However, next time might not be so favorable.
Tamao Tsukamu-kun.
Just how much potential do you have?
I truly look forward to finding out.
The next Girl-Gamble... will actually put your life on the line.
You will bet your life against her.
www.SubDESU-H.net