What's wrong? Where did your determination go?
I-I can still fight-!
I can be pretty strong when I get serious.
How unfortunate, Fujiwara Ryuusuke.
You ran out of luck when you entrusted Soul Eater to this little girl.
I was a little worried before,
but now it seems that you don't have any fight left in you.
It seems I need to teach a lesson to such reckless recruits!
Now, then! We're going to start your instruction!
By SubDESU-H
The beautiful avenging girl Enjou Mei
Look at you...
You're small but you've grown quite nicely!
Y-You bastard!
It seems your nipples are rather sensitive...
That's-!
S-Stop!
You don't seem to understand how bad of a situation you're in...
Have you forgotten that I can kill you and your friends whenever I want?
Look this way and poke out your tongue.
Now lets get the show started!
N-No! Stop it!
Don't look at me down there!
No!
That's it! Scream and get me excited!
N-No-!
If you don't settle down, I'll eat all of you!
This is quite a nice sight...
You were a virgin after all.
That's quite disciplined compared to kids these days...
Are you starting to feel good?
You're wet...
No!
D-Don't! Y-You mustn't lick me down there!
No!!
Don't put in-!
You're starting to taste and smell like a real woman!
That's my-!
No!
No-! If you keep going, I-I'll-!
Please s-stop this-!
I...!
You came pretty hard, didn't you?
S-Say whatever you want!
I'll never lose to the likes of you!
No way...
Why is it so big?!
W-What are you going to do?!
No!
C'mon! Put it in your mouth!
This is a pretty sight...
Your mouth feels pretty good!
I'm going to cum, make sure you drink every drop!
Swallow it all!
Don't let any spill!
We're not done yet...
We're just getting started.
I'm far from satisfied, you know.
Stop...
No...!
Stop it! T-There's no way that'll fit-!
It's my first time! You're gonna break me!
No!!
I-It's spitting me! I-I'm gonna die-!
I'm going to die!
Get ready to be pounded!
It hurts, it hurts-!
Pull it out! Please let me go!
This is great! Your pussy feels fabulous!
N-No! S-Stop it-!
N-No!
I'm gonna cum soon!
I'm gonna release it inside you!
N-No way! N-Not inside!
It's coming out...
It's dripping out... No!
It's coming out! It's still filling me up!
I tend to cum a lot...
They usually get pregnant from doing it with me just once!
N-No... No!
How was your first time?
Do you know what this is?
What's this? I'm...
My body feels strange...
The drug I injected you with is quite strong...
It will make any novice shake their hips like crazy!
That's not fair!
No... Don't... I can't...!
You'll soon start to crave it!
It's a super-strong aphrodisiac that eliminates any first time pain!
Y-You've got to be kidding me...
It's hot-! What is this? What is this?!
No!!
Did you wet yourself in pleasure?
You don't need to hold back.
Hey...
C-Can you do me with this?
I can't hold back!
Please, put it in! Put it in!
If you say it properly, then I'll consider it...
Can you please put this cock i-into my pussy?
You finally said it!
Alright then, I'll show you the joys of being a woman!
Why...? Why have I...?!
I mustn't do it, b-but I can't hold back!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I-It's still coming out!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum from this again!
No...
Now then, I'll do you in the butt since we've all been waiting for it!
Your butt feels quite good!
His semen is coming out...!
It's filling up my stomach!
This is too much...
That felt great!
Hey! You lot!
How long are you going to sit there and watch?
Sorry!
We thought it would be better not to get in your way...
Why are you lot here? I don't remember calling for backup.
That fussy bird ordered us to.
Shut up!
Don't tell me how I should go about my business!
Well, whatever.
I've defeated Soul Eater.
Now, what should we do with her?
What a disgrace.
I'm cumming!
Don't!
More! Do it more!
Shove it deeper inside me!
No!
I'm cumming!
Oh boy, she's had it.
She's just a human, after all.
She lasted quite a while, though.
I guess we have to hand it to her for not dying earlier.
Shall we make her our pet?
So we can cuddle with her everyday?
No!!
What's this?
Mom, come quickly!
Mom, over here!
Run! Get out of here, you two!
Mom...!
I'm fine, so take Benio and run!
But Mom, you're...!
Mikoto, you're her elder sister, aren't you?
If you don't protect her, then who will?
But...!
Quickly! Get out of here!
No!!
What is this...?
Mikoto, take Benio and run...
How unfortunate.
For you to come across us on our way home...
I'm going to take out my stress from work on you guys!
Please! Please let them go!
I can't do that.
Human females are the best prey for us chimeras.
No... Forgive them...
N-No...!
Hey, I'm gonna leave this one to you guys.
Can we really have her? s
Do as you please.
Wait-! Please don't hurt my daughters!
I don't mind what happens to me as long as...!
Don't worry!
I'm sure your daughters are worried about you, so I'll bring them back!
No! Please leave my daughters-!
No need to thank me. I'll deal with them.
Stop it...
Please, please don't hurt my daughters!
Alright then!
Make sure you fill up this hungry female!
Sure!
I'll shove it into her deepest spots!
She's a bit lonely,
so make sure that she's entertained!
You're going to split me...!
I-I'm gonna die like this...
Please, don't be so rough!
Don't you go asking for favors!
We've got many waiting for their turn!
Make sure you tighten up that pussy!
It's going in too deep-! It's going to poke through!
How does it feel to have it going right to your uterus?
Puny human cocks don't go this far, do they?
Not so deep-! P-Please pull it out!
I-I'll really die!
I-It hurts!
M-My stomach is going to burst from the inside!
How does it feel to have your insides messed up on both sides?
She must be feeling so good that she can't even speak!
I wish we could show this to her daughters!
Oh, looks like she really might pass out...
She might die before Byakko-sama returns!
Hey, you brought that thing along, didn't you?
We should inject her soon.
Sure!
W-What was that just now?
It's something that'll make you feel good!
It's a strong chimera aphrodisiac that would make even an elephant cum like crazy!
N-No way...!
No... What is this...?
My body is so hot...
It feels like I'm melting!
No... It feels good!
Both my pussy and my butt feel amazing!
I'm sorry, everyone...
No, I'm gonna go crazy...
Looks like she's getting into it!
The squeezing feels amazing, miss!
So good! It feels so good!
Being raped by beasts like this feels amazing!
This is too effective.
You injected her with the undiluted solution, didn't you?
We're not keeping her, so it doesn't really matter if she dies.
She's squeezing me!
She's quite good for her age!
I'm gonna cum soon!
Me too!
I'm cumming-!
I'm gonna cum, too!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming-!
I-I'm cumming!
C'mon! Lose your mind to the pleasure!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Oh? Did she finally break?
Well, it was fun while it lasted.
I wonder if Byakko-sama is having fun with her daughters right now?
P-Please run, Mikoto... Benio...
Mom...
Mom!!
W-What the hell?!
Give them back!
Give Mom and Benio back!
Shit!
Wait-! Don't! Spare me!
Take this!
Mom... Benio...
I've avenged you.