I missed this place...
Aki-nee!
What're you doing in a place like this?
Yuu-kun, what is it?
Is the festival set-up okay?
It's already finished for today.
Anyway...
We used to play here together a lot, right?
We thought that we should be here in the summer.
Those were really fun times.
Yuu-kun, do you remember that?
SubDESU-H Presents
Maid Ane
2nd Day
Hey, come here!
Hm... It feels good.
What are you doing? It's dangerous in there dressed like that.
This water is kind of cold.
I wonder if it's the same as before.
Yuu-kun, you should come in here as well.
Hey, hurry in here!
Yuu-kun!!
You can't do that!
There's a deep current down there.
Come on.
It'll get deeper past that.
It's okay, you worry too much-
Aki-nee!
Akh, Yuu-kun!
That was close...
Are you okay, Yuu-kun?
Would you give me a break!?
I'm sorry, but we're lucky.
I'm sure we wouldn't be able to get away if it was winter.
A... Aki-nee-
W-What are you doing?
I can't help it,
let's just stay like this for a moment, 'kay?
This wind feels good...
Isn't that right, Yuu-kun?
Yuu-kun, do you want to continue where we left off?
Yuu-kun's thing is sturdy...
Hey, Yuu-kun.
Do it to Aki-nee's pussy... as well.
Yuu-kun's lips-
No!
If you do that any more...
Aki-nee... Aki-nee... I can't-
That's great.
Aki-nee, are you okay?
I'm cumming.
This time, let me make Yuu-kun feel good.
A... Aki-nee.
It's inside.
It's inside, Yuu-kun.
I'm going to move, okay...?
Does it feel good?
You're going too fast... Move slowly,
I'm going to cum...
No, please let me cum like this.
Even if you say something like that,
I can't hold it anymore-
I can't... hold it anymore...
Hang in there, Yuu-kun.
Just a little bit more...
I'll cum any minute now.
I can't... even hold it anymore-
Hey, Yuu!
Yuu!
What're you doing sleep around here?
Your mother is worried about you.
Oh...
Don't just say "Oh" like that!
What're you two doing sleeping here?
"Us two"?
Ah, Is that so?
What're you thinking?
Come on, I'll get you home right away.
Akie-chan!
You should wake up too, Akie-chan!
You're going home with your master, okay?
Yuuta, straighten up your body a bit!
Can't you even straighten your body properly!?
There, It's good now.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Do it properly, okay!
Okay, I'll make sure that I won't embarrass Aki-nee.
Thanks for coming here.
Sei... Sei... Sei... Sei... Sei...
Sei... Sei... Sei...
Sei... Sei... Sei... Sei...
Sei... Sei...
Masatsugu-niichan, do your best!
Alright!! Let's bump this up!!!
Alright, straighten it up!!
Aki-nee.
Sure, I'll come... I know Yuu-kun would be able to do that.
When it comes to ropes,
I'm the best after all, that's why.
Yes.
I'll make sure to come watch you, master.
Aki-nee, I wonder if you already came...
Yuu-kun!
Do your best!
Let's bump it once again!!
Alright!
Hey Yuu, watch out!!
Yuu-kun?
Yuu-kun!?
Are you awake?
Don't push yourself too hard.
It hurts...
Eh?
Is that so... that's what happened.
Aki-nee, who is he?
"Who is he"?
What're you talking about? The one with you earlier.
Yuu-kun, maybe it's because you rammed your head that hard.
Why's that?
Damn it!
Are you okay?
I think it would be best if you lie down for a bit.
Aki-nee!!
Why's that!?
Damn it... damn it, Aki-nee!
With that kind of guy...
Damn it!
Stop it, Yuu-kun!
You called me your master...
Didn't you call me your master!?
Aki-nee, you're a maid right?
Service your master then.
There, lick all over it.
There!
Just like before, do it until it's down your throat.
No!!
Eh?
This is-
In here.
Why you're doing that?
Aki-nee is a maid after all.
I'm only Yuu-kun's maid.
It's okay.
Come on in.
Aki-nee.
Here I come.
Aki-nee-
Aki-nee~
Aki-nee, I want you to be my maid forever.
From now on, Yuu-kun will be my only master.
Whenever... wherever you want, I'll stay with you.
Aki-nee.
It's great.
It feels too good.
Aki-nee... I'm about to cum.
I want to do it more.
As long you wish.
It feels... good.
Do it more.
You can't touch... my asshole!
You can't, Yuu-kun!
Why's that, didn't you tell me that you were going to do what I wanted?
No... Not there...
Yuu-kun... you're teasing me...
Please... please... be gentle with it.
What's that...? You're fine with this?
Then, I'll do it with this.
No... This is the first time that someone fucked my ass like this.
No way, Yuu-kun...
No, Yuu-kun.
I'm gonna cum from my asshole.
No, don't put your finger... don't put it inside my pussy!
Ple... please.
That place-
Cum-
I'm gonna cum.
Cumming... I'm gonna cum from my ass and pussy!
It feels good.
Yu... Yuu-kun...
Yuu-kun cum in here, Aki-nee can't hold it-
Aki-nee.
What's the matter, Yuu-kun?
It's a dream after all, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Yuu-kun.
I'm going to go right now.
Sure.
Be careful on your way, master.
Yuuta, thank god... can you wake up?
Mother...
Eh, am I going to the festival...
You don't remember at all?
You rammed your head and you wouldn't wake up at all.
You don't remember anything-
No, I remember a little bit of it.
You've been unconsciousness for five days.
Aki-nee.
Where's Aki-nee?
Akie-chan has been by your side since this morning.
She keep telling you "I'm sorry... I'm sorry".
It's not her fault, it's because I wasn't paying attention at all.
It's like... I've been having a strange dream lately.
It hurts...
Hey, don't push yourself like that! Just lie down a little bit more.
It's okay.
Aki-nee.
I understand that I'm the who's been pushing you.
It's been a while since we met and I'm just acting on my own will.
I'm the one who's at fault.
I'm sorry... Aki-nee.
Hey, Yuu!
You're late, I've been waiting for 10 minutes.
I'm sorry about that, something came up.
Can I just leave it to you then?
I've got some errands to run right now.
Could you take her around to see the village?
Hello, pleased to meet you.
I'll be moving here from Tokyo.
I'm Tachibana Rie.
Um... I'll be in your care for today.
She's my relative after all.
So she's going to start living here.
I feel sorry, but could you take care of her for now?
"Take care of me"? I'm not a little girl anymore.
But, you don't seem to be using a local dialect at all, do you Yuuta-san?
Sometimes I can't even understand
what Masatsugu-niichan says at all.
Yeah, in many ways he's never grown up.
What do you mean by that?
Do you think that you've already grown up more than him?
You're interesting!
Yuuta-san is interesting person!
You're the one who's interesting, Tachibana-san.
Ah, you can call me Rie.
Don't laugh.
Eh~
Stop that.
You're funny, Yuuta-san.