www.SubDESU-H.net
I'm sorry. Please let me think about it.
No way...
Kaito!
Kaito...
K-Kaito-san...
Kaito-sama!
Kaito-kun...
Tropical Kiss.
Tropical Kiss
Original Animation Disc
~Isn't Hanabi beautiful when her heart races? Chapter~
Isn't Hanabi beautiful when her heart races?
Yes, here comes your order now!
Hinata Hanabi
Momoi Ichigo
It's hot here, isn't it?
Himuro Rikka
Fuune
Certainly!
Aoi Matsuri
Miru
They're going to come pick you up soon.
Minazuki Izumi
Kurata Mariya
Yes. I'll be leaving it to you then.
Saotome Nagi
Nanase Rin
Katakage Fuurin
Kawashima Rino
Why is everyone here?
You're quite cute.
Want to hang out with me?
Please disappear from my sight.
Then, it really became hard for me.
Customers just kept flowing in, and I got no breaks at all...
How can she act all normal around me?
I'm the guy she dumped.
Ah... Hey, Kaito.
I have something to tell you later...
Kaito-sama!
I-Izumi...
Are you still not ready to marry me yet?
Hey now...
If it comes down to it, then I'll have to rely on witchcraft only...
Well then, how about we combat the population decline problem right now?
Really...
What in the world does the mistress of the Minazuki house
really find good in me?
There's no more reason other than the fact that you showed me that "thing" of yours.
"That" thing?
Wait, that was just an accident...
You pervert!
What's wrong?
You two haven't changed.
Popular aren't we?
But my first love was you.
Huh?
Me, too.
But you had Hanabi,
and I thought that you considered me nothing but an elder sister.
But after meeting you again here, I finally understood...
...that I still love you even now.
Nagi-san feels that way about me...
It was an accident.
The reason I suddenly disappeared after confessing to you at that time,
was because I had an argument with my parents regarding my future.
I was forced to quit my job.
I see...
I thought we would never meet again.
I really love you, Kaito-san.
At that time...
Matsuri-chan...
And even now...
Oh, perfect timing.
Moving away without saying a word.
Was that your way of escaping from me?
Many things happened back then,
but I still think about it now.
I want to make up for it.
Did you regret it?
I guess you really didn’t notice, huh?
This is my answer.
Listen.
I never would have invited a guy that I didn’t like, you know.
I never had any regrets.
You're late.
Where have you been?
I walked Rikka back to her place.
Hey, how close are you with Rikka-san?
That's none of your concern.
You dumped me, remember?
Y-You're mistaken!
I said those words at that time...
...because I felt like teasing you a bit.
Huh?
I was going to apologize and confess that it was a joke.
But then you suddenly moved away...
I then realized I had done something that couldn't be undone.
I quit my university and came here looking for you.
You did that for me?
Please believe me.
I've loved you ever since we were little.
It's now... my turn to wait.
Who in the world... should I choose!?
What's wrong? Something on your mind?
Well, lots of things.
I must say, she's grown quite a lot.
Oh yeah, I'm about to take a break.
If it's okay with you, why don’t we eat-
Kaito, what are you slacking off for?
I'm not really slacking off.
Oh, you’re there.
I was already here!
Sorry, I didn't see you there.
Shall I refer you to a good ophthalmologist?
Shall I refer you to a good plastic surgeon?
Shall I teach you something about growing breasts?
No, thanks.
So you were a little worried.
Kaito-san, if it's okay with you, why don’t we eat lunch together?
Kaito-sama, let's have lunch together!
Kaito is having lunch with me.
You don’t get to decide on that!
Shut up.
It's because of that attitude that he won't be going out with anyone else.
Whose attitude are you talking about?
Do I really have to spell it out for you?
I'm pissed off...!
Kaito-sama...
I want to go with you, too...
Kaito-kun, want to go grab some lunch?
Fuurin forced me to wear this, so that I can help with the work. It couldn't be helped.
Why did you just go off like that?
Rikka's not that bad of a person, you know.
So you know a lot about her.
I didn't know you both would be that close just because you were neighbors.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing...
It’s always like this, so don’t worry.
How is it?
I'm almost done.
Shall I clean this up?
You don’t have to.
I'll make a meal then.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Hanabi's cooking is really great!
I can finally cook something for you after such a long time.
So where's the kitchen?
I'll cook.
Hey, reconsider that idea.
I said I'll cook.
Just sit comfortably there, Hanabi.
But...
I'll be making the meal.
Lots of liquor here...
What’s wrong?
I-It’s nothing!
Okay, it's now connected to the web.
Thanks, I'm just about done here, too.
Okay, let's go home now, Hanabi.
What’s with that? I just made you a meal, you know.
Let me ask this first. Is it "instant"?
It's homemade.
You aren't getting away!
What's wrong?
Rikka... Rikka's cooking, you see...
I-It doesn’t taste good?
It's so bad you'd think it wasn't from this world!
How rude. Just eat it.
What did you make by the way?
Special wild udon and cheese miso soup.
It's done. Enjoy the meal.
This is good!
I never thought I'd be eating your meals again.
I also didn’t think that I would be able to meet you again.
I was surprised, too.
Well, I'm the one who's more surprised here.
No, that would be me.
No, it's me.
It’s me!
See you tomorrow then. Thanks for the meal.
Kaito, I'd like to give you something.
I-It's beneficial to have in case something happens, right?
I-Is that so?
I want to have one to your room as well.
O-Okay.
I have to make a decision.
Is something on my body?
Not really.
How weird.
Nothing is visible at all.
Hey.
Oh, you're both early.
Don't mind it.
What are you smiling at?
My, we're all together today.
What's this? Bath time with everybody?
Even I can't measure up to those.
Monstrous...
Oh, everyone's here, too.
Looks like everybody's here today.
Feeling a bit better?
Just a tiny bit.
Is Kaito-san unable to swim?
He almost drowned when he was a kid.
Then if he ever drowns, I'll be the first one to give him CPR.
Kaito-san is the type that is easily cornered into accepting things, huh?
That's impossible for me.
How about having him take responsibility for fondling your breasts?
What in the world are you talking about?
But you want to do it too, right?
K-Kissing?
Not just that, but lots of other "things".
I-I'm not really into that...
As for me, I want to do it.
I really don’t want to do it, but if he feels like doing it then...
I definitely want to do it.
However, I probably won’t know how to kiss properly.
Have you done it already, Hanabi-san?
Eh? I-I'm...
So you haven't.
Okay, I admit it! But you also...
What did you call me for?
It's great that it's clear tonight.
Oh yeah, it’s Tanabata today.
So you finally remembered.
Let's hope the title sells well
-All Staff Members
To be released
from being a NEET
We were writing on vertical cards earlier.
I see.
What kind of wish did you ask for?
My wish is something that can't be granted.
What’s with that? Can’t it become true?
It won't. Ever.
Well, you have a chance,
so how about wishing for something that would be granted?
A chance, huh?
Don't you have any such wish?
Then...
Would you be willing to kiss me here?
Kiss me.
H-Hey, what's wrong with you?
Didn’t you say earlier?
This is what I wished for.
B-But...
You can't kiss me because of Rikka-san?
You did it already, right?
A kiss with Rikka-san...
It's been bothering me for a while,
but what’s really your relationship with her?
What's between you and Rikka-san?
Wh-What's with you suddenly?
It’s obvious that I'd be worried whenever I see you two together.
After coming here, I worked as a bartender.
Rikka loves to drink.
So we usually had a few drinks together.
There was a fireworks display that night.
Then I remembered it again,
even though I wanted to forget about it,
how I loved you so much.
I was already drunk, and I talked about you to her.
She said I was unmanly.
Then I just impulsively...
I was the worst.
I was supposed to be in love with you,
but I did that to Rikka.
Is that so...
So something like that happened.
I don’t really... mind that...
Then why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault that you had to go through this.
It’s not your fault.
It's me who rushed into things.
Do you love Rikka-san?
I don't know.
I want to fix things again.
I want to say instead that I've been waiting for you to confess to me.
If I did that then we'd already be...
I want to go back to that time...
I want to go back to that time
-Hinata Hanabi
Let's hope the title sells well
-All Staff Members
Guess I'll have to give her some time.
Hanabi, you’re in there, right?
Open up, I know you're there.
How long to do you plan to mope around like that?
You'll never change because you're like that.
So that's what you want to do, huh?
Kaito, just leave that woman.
I'm here for you.
Anyway, want to do it again after a long time?
No, you can't!
Mission successful.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let’s start then.
What's the meaning of this, you flat-chest?
Shut up, you bitch.
What did you say!?
Hey, what are you doing?
Who are you going to choose between us, Kaito?
Will it be me or her?
I'm going to save...
...both of you!
Are you awake now?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Both of you were drowning earlier, right?
That was a setup.
I had a bet with Hanabi.
To see who you will save when both of us are drowning.
A bet?
The result was...
I think he will save you.
Me?
Your existence is very important to him.
I think he will try to save both of us.
Me and you at the same time.
What's up with that?
I'm really sorry.
I reconsidered my actions.
Maybe it was a little too much.
Just a little?
Well then, the loser will now take her leave.
Hanabi knew you better than anyone.
It's the truth.
Thank you, Rikka-san.
What happened?
It’s a secret.
Between us girls.
Is that so?
I'm sorry to have kept moving away from you like that.
I wanted to tell you something.
What is it?
You said you wanted to go back to that time, right?
I don’t want to.
I am who I am now because of what happened that day.
I wouldn’t have been able to work here.
Besides...
Keeping good relations despite not having or receiving a straight answer,
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
that's just too much to ask of me.
Learn to realize the most worrisome point.
Geez...
It's because I met you again
that I am able to love you more than before.
Kaito...
I love you, Hanabi.
I've made you wait for a long while though.
Yes, I love you, too.
Aren't you going to say that you want to think about it?
I won't do something like that anymore.
What!?
Kaito-san and Hanabi-san...
...are now dating?
Is that true?
Yes.
We've already decided.
It's all because I didn’t have enough screen time.
If you give up, your love is all over.
Ohh... Congratulations anyway.
Your tribulations are just starting from this point though.
What?
Hanabi's pretty stubborn, so they'll probably argue about simple things.
I know she'll get discouraged, and then say "I don't want this anymore".
Then I will claim Kaito-sama when he gets depressed.
H-Hey, that won't happen!
Kaito, if you ever become unsatisfied, you can come to my place.
You can also come to mine.
You're always welcome.
I'll be listening to your troubles.
Totally fired up to steal him away, aren't you?
I won't let you all do that!
This is going to be difficult.
Tro-pi-cal Kiss!
Kaito, pat my head.
There, there.
Tendency to shift personality noted.
This is something to be studied.
You can’t do that. Don’t mix your intimate moments with work.
It could be that they are just showing off.
Dark aura... dark aura around you, Hotaru-chan!
I can't move anymore.
You won’t be able to take a break with that.
It'll be just the two of us here for a while.
Why don't you try sleeping on the table?
I see. Then maybe I'll do just that.
Sorry, I'm going to apologize first.
Huh?
What are you doing?
It's because I saw your tits and lower part like this...
That doesn’t mean you can do it!
Keep quiet! What if someone comes in here?
You can just stop doing this, right?
It's more impossible for me to stop this when I see your breasts like that.
Th-That doesn’t mean...
We can't do sexual stuff here.
Then, I'll just fondle it.
You breast groper...
Just fondle it, okay?
Do it more gently.
Can you feel it?
I don't really know.
Then we'll have to be more direct.
This is embarrassing.
There... It feels a little...
Here, right?
No...
We're through.
Just the breasts, right?
That's right, but...
Our break time is also limited,
and we have to eat lunch, too.
N-No way... But Kaito, also...
What do you want to do?
Do it.
Do what?
Please do it until the end!
Then, can you lick this?
Eh?
It's okay if you don't want to.
I-It's not that I don’t want to, it's just that...
I-I don't know what to do.
H-Here I go then...
Wrap your lips around it and then move it in and out.
Feeling good?
Yeah, please continue.
That's good.
Your tongue is...!
Huh? Are you alone, Kaito?
Well, Hanabi is...
Fuurin?
Is your lunchbreak not over yet?
H-Hanabi is currently getting a meal for us right now.
Wh-What are you doing here?
My bunny band doesn't seem to fit right today.
Fitting? Really?
I think I have a spare one here.
The bunny band that I'm using is quite special, you know.
It twitches naturally, and even turns...
Huh?
What's wrong?
I-It's nothing.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
I'll make sure she doesn’t notice.
What's that? Something seems suspicious.
Don't come near!
Th-There's nothing in here...
Crap! Are we busted?
Oh, there it is!
See you later then.
Celebration!!
Tropical Kiss
~Slippery Wet Diet?!
The warrior that has to eat
Matsuri Chapter ~
December 28, 2012
Orgasmic Face Heaven
Sale Announcement!
My heart just stopped beating back there.
This is punishment for being a pervert.
I won't forgive you.
This is bad. It feels really good!
This is payback for what you did earlier.
Hmph.
You aren't satisfied with just ending it here, right?
Yeah. Are you okay now?
You're a pervert so it revived quickly.
I'm not a pervert.
Then what's this?
W-With this position?
I want to try it out.
This is embarrassing.
It feels like I'm being forced to do it.
A-Are you okay?
It hurts...
Don’t pull it out!
But...
I'm okay.
Just move about as you please.
A-Amazing...
I think that felt good.
Is that so? Then...
It’s good...
It feels good!
Your body's the best!
Your big and stiff cock is also too great for me.
You'll get used to it in no time.
You're right.
Soon, I won't be satisfied if it's not your cock.
Kaito, I think I'm feeling a little weird.
What strange feeling?
My body feels tingly. It’s weird.
Okay.
You're gradually tightening up inside...
Because it feels so good!
I'm also at my limit now.
Don’t release it inside!
Hanabi, I'm about to...!
Me, too...
K-Kaito... I can't ....
Hanabi...!
Idiot, I already told you not to release it inside.
What if I get pregnant because of this?
I'm sorry!
But if that time comes, of course I'll--
What's with this? This bunny band also doesn't fit me!
Hanabi, so you’re back.
Y-Yes...
The meal was finished already, right?
Y-Yeah.
Really? So the "meal" was Hanabi, then?
Wh-What are you...?
It's dripping.
I also saw you doing fellatio earlier.
That's why I told you not to release it inside!
Ah, the sweet mistakes the youth make...
This person's a demon.
After that...
Hanabi and I slowly became more sexual...
And we then delved deeper
To the ends of what we can call as pleasure...
No, not there...
Where would that be...
It's getting more stretched.
S-Somebody will see us...
Why does it feel this good...
Someone might show up...
W-We can't do this while at work.
We already did it this morning, right?
For me to masturbate this way...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
H-Hanabi!
R-Release it!
Inside me!
I want all of your cum inside me!
How many times did we have sex this week?
I stopped counting after 20.
It's 32 times.
You're just too lively to even stop doing it.
And you're also just starting to want it yourself.
Th-That's... Idiot...
But I never thought we'd really be like this...
I wanted to tell my past self about it.
Oh, yeah.
On our next day off, I want to go somewhere.
This place hasn’t really changed.
Why did you want to come here?
At that time, things might have become weird for us, but...
This is still an important place for you and me.
Hey, Kaito.
Could we try doing it again?
Just like that time.
If we start dating, things will become a lot more fun, right?
Hanabi, please go out with me.
I've been waiting for you to tell me that.
It should have been this way from the start.
Were you also planning to do this before?
I wonder...
Kaito...
We'll be together, forever.
Of course.
Let's go home... to our Aloha.
www.SubDESU-H.net