Milky news
Hello everyone.
It's me! Pure hearted Nanase Akira again!
Milky way, a café and my house which boast it's cheerfulness and enjoyment.
But there was a big incident that happened in our store.
I’m reporting the incident from Milky Way.
This is my stupid bro Nanase Kenji.
Of all things, he is accused of sexual assault, that he raped a waitress of Milky Way!
I’m innocent here!
Just give up!
Let's stomp on him.
Stop!
According to my sister notebook,
this my stupid bro, with his stimulating play,
he made Yuuki Rin-san, who she is his childhood friend, owner, producer, waitress
and a beauty when she takes off her glasses, feel more than the usual.
Is this true Rin-san!?
Oh uhm... how should I say this...
Did it flow a lot more than usual?
I can’t say that!
Well, we have a witness in this incident.
The waitress from Milky Way.
It's Mikage Sakuya-san and Toujou Remi-san.
Why am I after her?
And please call me Remi~~
I’m sorry, I’m sorry.
I didn’t intend to watch.
Ahahaa.
Don’t lie.
You got excited like the whore with the chain.
I’m not a whore.
Oh? You’re talking back to me?
Ouch!
Here, here.
You’re a whore.
You’re a dirty whore.
Go and moan in the backyard.
The witnesses are not only them.
Takanashi Chihiro-san.
She’s stupid bro’s ex-gf.
Waitress of Milky Way.
She passed by the store by coincidence.
As stupid bro found out about this,
he brought Chihiro-onee chan into his room and raped her to shut her mouth.
It’s a lie!
I was sleeping at my room and...
Uhm.. there's a bit of a mistake...
You mean it's almost correct if you say there's a bit of a mistake!?
No... it's uhm...
Don’t hide it Onee-chan!
Beside, me and my friend Ayumi were at the site and watched it.
Weren't we Ayu?
It’s a misunderstanding.
There’s a reason for this.
What kind of reason do you have?
Say something Ayu.
Onii-chan you dummy!
I was splashed in the face.
Let's stomp him!
Rawr!
Anyway,
It'll be a big problem if we let this idiot free.
And it's dangerous for female workers!
Isn’t it?
From the left,
Kousaka Mayu-san.
Kusumoto Yura-san.
Toujou Haruka-san.
Uhm...
Oh...
I don’t know?
Owwww.
I think there a problem at their sides.
It’s a problem especially for Onee-sama.
She’s the eldest and got new interest.
It’s embarrassing for me.
Remi!
Come with me.
What?
As a teacher, let me teach you a lesson.
I have a work to do Onee-sama.
This one must be prioritized!
Oh my...
Anyway,
Lust, jealousy and expectation.
There’s a lot of complications in Milky Way but right now,
Rainbow parfait,
Kankin pudding,
and Ohoukyou Aradomo.
These three dishes are recommended.
So take a look.
That’s all.
The end of milky news~
This is worse than before.
Hey!
SubDESU-H
presents
Episode 2
I can't stop my feelings
I want you to do what you want.
Ugh, still sleepy.
Ugh...  it's Summer...
Are you not going to swim, Ayu?
Oh... yes...
Later...
Are you depressed?
About stupid bro?
N-No!
Just leave that cheater.
Argh! How annoying!
Why do Rin-san and Chihiro-san love that fool?
But...
Huh?
I understand how Chihiro-san feels.
You can’t stop your own feelings.
Ayu...
But I can do that.
Ayu is Onii-chan’s sister.
Uhm... his sister is me though.
I’m like his sister.
Ugh...
Let's swim.
Please come to Kokoro library.
Niko Niko Rin.
*wooow*
You’ll sink.
Let's burst with Sensei.
There’s new one today.
Why me too?
Excuse me, can you look here?
Smile Remi.
All the books were sold again today, the Cosplay power upped!
But why are you so silent Rin-san?
Do you have any problems?
If you don’t mind, you can you tell me?
I’ll die to be able to help you.
Who are you?
I’m sorry for calling you out.
Oh there’s no problem.
I’m sorry too.
Letting you see something this crazy.
No... uhm...
I learned something...
Huh?
Not in that way...
First of all, me and Remi-san watched that happening.
Don’t mind about it.
It was a good trigger though.
A trigger?
Yep.
I've always loved Kenji.
I love him.
I've always kept that feeling for him.
And the feeling got bigger until I couldn't bear it.
I wasn’t able to stop it.
But.. the store manager has owner...
I know.
But it’s a lie if you hide your feels.
It’s a lie between Kenji and me.
I don’t like myself in that way so...
I decided to be honest to myself and face him naked.
Chihiro-san.
I don’t have any regrets.
You wanted to hear that right?
I don't regret what I did.
I said all the things I kept a secret.
I did some embarrassing things but,
Kenji accepted it all.
It's summer.
So I think it's alright for something like this to happen.
Store manager, let me help you.
Sakuya-chan, what's up?
The store will open tomorrow so...
I think I need to clean the store.
You too right?
Yeah, I have nothing to do that’s why.
But I think it's bad for you even if it’s the last day of the break.
It's alright.
I’m the one who wants to do it.
I’m sorry about yesterday.
No problem.
I washed my face properly.
Store manager.
Does that thing feel good?
Sa-Sakuya-chan?
Is the thing which feels good also good into your body?
Huh?
Like inside the store, inside your room, do you get excited in different places?
Sakuya-chan?
I... it's...
I watched it twice.
So... uhm... I think I got problems with my feelings.
Store manager!
Yes?
Yes??
I’m sorry.
Eh?
I did my best to remember the script.
I used my courage.
But my mind is all white right now.
Sakuya-chan, your face.
Noo!!
What’s funny store manager?
Oh, I thought that it's just like you.
You’re cruel.
I know that I’m like this.
Sorry.
Store manager, I have a lot of memories in this store.
Yeah.
So something dirty is...
Yeah, I won’t do that again.
Can you forgive me?
When I work in the store.
I’ll surely remember about you and owner.
No way...
Then make me remember something else!
Uhm?
Do that dirty thing to me too.
Noo, I wanted to say that more romantically.
Uhm, but...
Rin...
Sure.
I believe in you.
Store manager...
Store manager... your eyes...
My eyes?
Your eyes are perverted.
Sorry for that.
I’m a pervert anyway.
But...
I don't hate the perverted store manager.
I will do my best to do the perverted thing tonight.
S-Store manager?
Please turn off the lights.
No!
Why?
Cuz I will watch the perverted Sakuya-chan.
No!
Do you best.
Bear with it.
This and that is..
It tastes like coffee.
I drank it a while ago.
It’s a taste of an adult.
Not my breasts yet...
I’m not yet prepared.
Do it later.
It's too late if I do it later.
No...
What’s the matter?
Store manager, why are you always touching there?
Because I like it.
Don’t take it off.
Remi always do that.
She was just mischievous.
This is also a perverted mischief.
It’s sexual harassment.
It's embarrassing.
We haven’t started yet.
Don’t suck it...
Don’t pinch it.
Store manager...
Don’t always touch the nipples.
I understand.
Then...
I’ll touch the more perverted part.
Eh?
How’s the feeling?
I don’t know?
Store manager?
I’m going to take it off.
No, no you can’t.
Rejected.
Noo!
You meanie~
How irresponsible.
I’m a composition of kindness.
For proof, I will clean Sakuya-chan.
Store manager, that part is...
It's wet...
Don’t be so mean.
Store manager... I’m... spilling it...
I think it’s ready.
Wait.
In this position first...
Here I come.
Ok.
Relax.
Yes.
You’re a meanie store manager.
But, I don’t hate being teased by store manager.
I’m going to move.
Ok.
Sakuya-chan.
Store manager...
It's full of store manager.
I’m being teased by store manager.
What should I do?
This shouldn’t be like this.
I...
It's good.
I can’t stop the feeling of loving you.
Store... manager.
Kenji-san.
Please.
Please tease Sakuya.
Until the end...
Tease me until the end.
Store manager, we need to clean up again.
Let's celebrate for continuous sold of the magazines!
Today again was a success.
Was I not ugly that time?
I’m still a newbie so did I make some trouble?
You don’t have to be so modest.
Onee-sama was popular being a middle aged woman.
Who are you referring to as a middle aged woman!?
Wait you!
You’re not lively Rin-chan.
Forgive me sister
No I’m not.
You can go home if you’re feeling lonely.
Why me?
My... my...
I know everything about Hana-chan.
Thank you.
Sorry, just go home when you like to.
Owner?
Where are you going?
I have something to ask about this winter's coming even.
I recommend you to do something which can retain your age in the winter.
What did you say!?
What exactly I’m doing?
Even though I have Rin...
With Chihiro, Sakuya-chan.
You can have an affair.
What am I to her.
And what is her to me?
Is it Akira?
I’m still taking a bath.
Is it Chihiro?
Is it Rin?
Are you done with the party?
It’s a good timing, I have something to ask.
What do you mean by I can have an affair?
Really, I did it with Chihiro.
To tell the truth I did it with Sakuya-chan today.
Uhm, it's my fault.
But you also said that,
so I don’t understand exactly what you mean...
Hey Ayu!?
Sorry but I’m not Rin-san.
What’s the matter?
I’m all sweaty so I thought of taking a bath.
Go take it in your house.
I don’t have any Onii-chan at my house.
What do you mean by that?
Let's take a bath together Onii-chan.
We’re already taking it.
It's a bit confined.
Please hug me Onii-chan.
Hey wait.
This is bad.
Why?
We always took baths together when we were young.
But we were young at that time so...
I think it's obvious.
If we can’t take a bath together.
It's ok for Ayu not to get big.
It's impossible.
Yes.
We all get big right?
We all get big and many things change.
But you know...
My important thing won’t change.
I love Onii-chan.
Even if my boobs get big, even if my height increases, even if my hips get bigger.
I'll still love Onii-chan.
All of me loves you Onii-chan.
Ayu...
I want you to know that.
Please eat Ayu’s pudding Onii-chan.
You.
When did you become like an adult character?
What?
I got surprised for a bit.
Do we need to stop it?
No.
Please continue.
Onii-chan is only touching the perverted place.
No I’m not.
It's my turn.
Your turn?
Lie down.
Ayu?
How do you know this?
Where did you learn this?
From the magazines in Onii-chan’s room.
Ohh.
Akira-chan was so mad.
Rin-san, Chihiro-san and Sakuya-san.
They love you right?
But Ayu has also been in love with Onii-chan for a long time now.
I love you more than choco pudding and strawberry pudding.
You won’t say only Ayu can’t, right?
Ayu...
Where did you...
From the video in onii-chan’s room.
Onii-chan is cool, strong and tall.
But this part is so cute.
What’s the meaning of that?
It's because...
When I do this...
It trembles.
You’re too adult.
I’ll counter attack.
Noo.
Onii-chan you pervert.
Are you sure?
It's because it's onii-chan.
Does it hurt?
Yes but,... I will bear with it.
It's because it's Onii-chan...
Ayu...
Please come here Onii-chan.
Onii-chan is...
Onii-chan is coming inside me!
Ayu’s inside is full of Onii-chan.
It's full of Onii-chan!
Ayu...
Onii-chan...
Your pudding is delicious.
It’s the best.
The pudding is sloppy.
Its going to be sloppy.
Ayu... Ayu...
Onii-chan...
You fool, close the window.
Ayu...
I’m almost...
I love you!
I love you Onii-chan!
Forever... I'll love you forever!
I love you more than anything!
I love you!
I’m going crazy!
Ayu-
Onii-chan-
What are you doing!?
Have you still not learned your lesson?
Stop!
Stupid!
Akira-chan!
Stop!
I’ll cut off your penis you pervert big bro!
Stop!!
Oh!
Uhm... hey!
Are you cheating?
Eh?
It's no problem if you're just having an affair.
I know it’s a method of releasing stress.
I don’t want to isolate you either.
But reserve the last for me.
Oh...
Hey.
How to do you feel about me?
Of course, I love you.
Don’t let me say that! You fool!
Welcome!!!
Red Lanter
We’re
Closed
Fool~
It's hard to become a part of society.
I know.
I understand!
Once more!
Let's go home onee-sama~
Bye bye.