www.SubDESU-H.net
It's quality... assorted quality sushi!
And of course, it's Mom's treat!
Is Mom coming home this evening?
She said she is busy this evening, so it's impossible.
But tomorrow she'll surely come home and see you.
I see!
Well then.
Without delay, let's eat!
Thank you for the food.
So, Yuki-chan.
It has been a while... right?
Yes... I-It's been a while.
Seiichi and Yuki.
Both embarrassingly shy.
They avoid talking to each other
ever since their first meeting at the station.
Even meeting in the corridor of the apartment building
would only end with them silently brushing past each other.
How far were you able to explain our relationship to Yuki-chan?
Let's see, "This is big sister's boyfriend, and the person who will soon be your brother-in-law." That's it.
Anyway, nice to meet you, Yuki-chan.
Ah, yes. N-Nice to meet you, too.
Misono Yuki
A girl that looks like a younger version of Maki.
No doubt, the beautiful daughter of a mother who used to be a model.
She's three years younger than Maki.
In contrast to her sister's loud and vibrant personality,
she's quite an introvert and has a quiet atmosphere around her.
Maki also used the surname Misono
before their parents divorced.
Now, she is using her mother's maiden name.
And with that Seiichi-san,
I'll be leaving Yuki with you this evening.
Ah, okay.
Are you going somewhere, Onee-chan?
After this, I need to go to school for a bit.
I'll be gone until then.
W
Maki-chan
to Nau
Original Animation Disc
～ The Pure and Untainted Angel Misono Yuki Chapter ～
So, I'll be going now.
Be careful.
I'm off then!
S-See you later...
You don't have to be so nervous.
Ah, okay.
I'll do my best.
Maki-chan rarely stays at her place and is mostly here everyday.
I-Is that so?
Indeed, it is so.
Umm...
Can I wash the dirty dishes we used earlier?
Dishes?
Oh, the sushi ones?
I want to do it as thanks for taking care of my sister.
I see. I'll leave it to you then.
So she's a bit active even though she looks quite timid.
Could it be that you are good at doing household chores, Yuki-chan?
Rather than "good", I'd say "love".
Onee-chan never does them anyway.
It's probably more accurate to say that she can't be entrusted with those tasks.
Excellent points in looks, elegance and academics.
She's even good in sports,
but she is quite clumsy with household tasks.
If she's made to do such chores,
it always ends up in disaster.
That's one of her defining qualities.
Umm... is there something else that I can do?
Ah no, no. It’s okay, Yuki-chan.
But I still need to do something to make up for Onee-chan's stay here.
But I'm also being taken cared of by her.
Especially when it comes to sexual activities.
She's always taking care of me.
Doing this, and even doing that...
By the way, Yuki-chan. I heard that you like anime and manga?
Yes, I like them.
Come in.
This is amazing!
Feels like heaven.
That's an exaggeration.
My father forbade me to watch anime or read manga since it's bad for me and won't do me any good.
He never allows me to.
I see.
But he said that books are good for knowledge.
So he lets me read light novels.
Is that so? Then...
Have you read this already?
Academy Report
Calamity
Yes, I've read up to volume 3.
Did you find it interesting?
I don't remember the story well.
I-I see...
Are you a fan of this book's author?
That's not it. Well...
The author of that light novel is...
me.
Amazing!
Amazing amazing!
Onii-chan is a real light novel author?
Yeah, but my works don’t really sell that well.
However,
I'm also doing scriptwriting work for H-games.
It's not something I can let Yuki-chan find out.
Unlike Maki-chan,
this girl isn't really that comfortable with such topics.
If she finds out, disdain would immediately replace the momentary admiration.
I see.
Someone this amazing is Onee-chan's boyfriend.
Just read whatever you like here, okay?
It's my dream to read manga volumes in their complete sets.
Thank you, Onii-chan!
T-Take your time.
Onii-chan, huh?
Yuki!
Could it be that you've been reading manga all day long?
Welcome home, Onee-chan.
Onii-chan's room is really amazing.
It’s a mountain of treasures.
Onii-chan?
How do you feel being called "Onii-chan"?
Well, it's not that bad, I think.
Is it really okay for me to borrow this, Onii-chan?
Of course.
If you need to borrow anything else,
just call me through the window at the open veranda.
Take whatever you like with you.
That's right. Although, I don't really know where I live anymore.
You're just so free and unrestrained, you know.
Onee-chan and Onii-chan are really close.
That's right. Are you envious, Yuki?
I'm not envious of it.
Don’t you have a boy that you like?
I don't have one!
There's no way I'd have one!
That's quite suspicious...
Oh well, I suppose it is so.
In your case, you'll have to find a way to get past your ultimate hurdle of being shy first.
I know that already.
It's morni... No, it's noon already.
Wake up, Onii-chan!
There it is. There it is!
His thing is getting bigger. Amazing!
Wai— no, no!
Only perverts get awestruck by a sight like this!
What's this? I thought Maki-chan has come up with yet another sexual play, but...
You're sleeping too much, Onii-chan.
You’re eyelids will get stuck if you don't wake up.
So wake up already!
Onii-chan!
Oniichan?
Wake up!
Yuki-chan?
So you're finally awake, Onii-chan.
Good morning!
Good morning, too.
Why are you here?
Onee-chan went to school early for a meeting this morning.
I was asked to wake you up in her stead.
Thank you.
Even so, she looks really great with that apron on.
It's quite cute.
What's wrong, Yuki-chan?
Umm...
Anyway, I'm glad that you woke me up.
Breakfast, err no, lunch is already prepared so freshen up quickly, Onii-chan.
Y-Yuki-chan? That getup...
Yuki-chan... What's up with that attire...?
Onee-chan taught me to wear this whenever I come to wake you up.
Maki-chan did?
Y-Yes.
Is that so.
It's okay if you’re the one to see me like this.
The kitchen also felt too hot,
and this outfit feels quite cool.
So I was like "Oh well, it's no big deal".
I-I see.
Also Onee-chan said that
since you are a bum, wearing something like this everyday,
I won't have to worry about other people.
I don't understand what that really means though.
But is that right, Onii-chan?
Well, she's right, I guess?
Anyway, it looks great on you.
The apron also looks very cute.
Really? That's good.
I also like this apron.
You made everything by yourself?
I hope Onii-chan will like it.
Thank you for the food.
This is good!
You're such a flatterer, Onii-chan.
What are you doing, Onii-chan?
Are you okay, Onii-chan?
I was just a bit flustered.
Hey, Onii-chan. Can I watch you work today?
Of course.
Really? Thank you, Onii-chan!
For the moment, I'm nothing but a simple light novel author for her.
The fact that I'm writing scripts for erotic scenes with beautiful girls in a 2D game
is definitely something I have to keep hidden from her.
I'm gonna write these scenes as casually and calm as possible.
With this, it's done. Now for the next scene—
Is that...
the product of what you and Onee-chan were doing that time?
No, it isn't that.
Onii-chan...
Yes?
Want to eat some snacks?
Maki-chan and Now.
Okay, done.
The nude form, of course, is splendid.
However, the obvious nakedness can be plain and boring.
If only the important parts of a girl are covered,
where she is almost naked but not really so...
Such is the true essence of a naked apron.
It is elegance and obscenity intertwined.
A simple symbol of sexual modesty.
It really looks great on you, Yuki-chan.
Really? I'm glad.
Onii-chan? W-Were you looking at me while I was changing?
Was I not supposed to?
Of course not.
That's why I said I'll call you after I'm done preparing.
The naked apron form is okay,
but exposing yourself while changing is not.
This is a girl-thing that Seiichi didn't really understand.
I made hotcakes.
It looks delicious.
That’s great.
I'll be preparing ice coffee then, Onii-chan.
Watch out!
Ugh
Ahh
Seiichi fell with his back on the floor
while Yuki falls in such a manner that she ends up bent over as if mounting him.
Moreover, the apron slipped a little bit to the side,
revealing one of her breasts.
It's not... big...
I'm sorry.
A-Are you alright, Onii-chan?
How about you? You aren't hurt anywhere?
No, you held me back so...
Thank you, Onii-chan.
If I let someone precious like you get hurt anywhere,
Maki-chan would surely get mad at me.
Seiichi's eyes were looking straight at her breasts.
It was comparatively smaller than Maki's large breasts.
The skin around her breasts looks shiny, and does not have a single stain or spot.
Her small mounds bring up sexual delusions.
Yuki-chan?
What is it, Onii-chan?
Your breasts are...
They're in plain sight, right?
Should I cover them?
For me, I would be happier if you didn't.
But hey, Yuki-chan's nipples are getting hard.
Could she be...
If this keeps up, I won't be able to control my fantasies.
My sanity, my sanity!
Onii-chan, I am aware of the boy-girl  relationship that both you and Onee-chan share.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
When we met at the station, I saw you two doing it.
That was a "train molester" play, right?
So you know about it...
The face of my sister as the train doors opened showed happiness and pleasure.
At that time, my heartbeat went really fast.
I was totally envious of my sister.
I also wanted Onii-chan to make me feel good like that.
Yuki-chan?
Wait, wait. Isn’t this situation moving to a really weird direction?
After that, I talked with Onee-chan and asked what I should do about it.
You talked about it?
Onee-chan said that I should try seducing you with erotic getups.
And if you become willing to it,
then I can do whatever I want afterwards.
That's why Onii-chan, please do the things you’re doing to Onee-chan wth me, too.
Teach me things about sex.
That would mean giving your virginity to me, you know.
I know.
It's because I like you, Onii-chan.
I don’t want to do it if it’s not you, Onii-chan.
Well, that's Maki-chan's sister for you.
No, no, no.
Or does that mean that you won't do if it's not Onee-chan?
That's not really the case,
but do you really understand what sex is?
No, I don’t really know,
but I am curious.
I want you to teach me about it.
You don't say.
However, a woman's hole is called a vagina, right?
I know that you are supposed to insert your cock in there.
Onee-chan showed me a few videos so...
W-Wai... Yuki-chan!?
So this is Onii-chan's cock.
All that's left to do is to insert this, right?
Yeah, but...
I'll try it right away then.
Hey, doing it already is reckless.
It hurts.
Doing it without proper foreplay is next to impossible.
You have to make the vagina wet enough first.
Foreplay? Wet vagina?
The wild arousal is already starting to get out of hand
since Seiichi is slowly losing control over his hip area.
Anyway, why don't you try getting off me first?
Alright, sit here, Yuki-chan.
Okay, spread your legs out.
Yes, but it feels embarrassing, Onii-chan.
That feeling of embarrassment converting into enjoyment is what sex is, Yuki-chan.
Is... that so?
You’re cute, Yuki-chan.
Onii-chan, is this okay?
Yeah, that's fine.
I can see your embarrassing part completely.
It really is embarrassing for me to be looked at in such a way, Onii-chan.
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan, you can't lick that part!
Why can't I?
B-Because that part is drenched in sweat and is dirty.
It smells great over here.
Besides, we can't have sex if I don’t make your pussy wet like this.
Making my pussy wet?
Does that mean wetting it with saliva?
It's not saliva.
I'll make your pussy wet on its own.
Is that so? But I still don't understand.
That's the hole from where I pee!
Oh yeah, so?
But... It really is quite dirty!
If you lick me there...
It also feels very embarrassing.
Do you know what this little thing is?
I don't know...
But I have been feeling a bit hot there for a while now.
My mind can no longer calm down.
This is called the "clitoris".
In short, Cli-chan.
No, Onii-chan, I feel weird.
My Cli-chan feels weird!
I think I'm going to lose it!
Look Yuki-chan, your love juice is flowing.
That's what it feels like to cum, Yuki-chan.
I didn't know about this.
This is my first time...
I'm going to go crazy!
My mind still feels like its floating.
It felt really good, Onii-chan.
So Onee-chan always does this kind of pleasurable act with Onii-chan?
Sex feels better and is even more intense, Yuki-chan.
Feels better?
It might be painful at first.
Are you really okay with this?
I'll endure it.
Then, let's begin.
It's okay. Come inside me, Onii-chan.
Try to relax a bit more.
Relax yourself.
Relax.
I'll try my best.
It hurts!
Look, Yuki-chan.
Onii-chan's cock is entering my hole.
Wait, there's blood coming out?
Is my period starting already?
I'll push a bit farther in, okay?
Can you still endure it?
Yes. I'm alright, Onii-chan.
I believe in you.
Please do what you will.
Does it hurt?
It hurts, but I can still endure this.
Besides, I'm really happy right now.
Happy?
Because I'm becoming one with my beloved, Onii-chan.
I'm also happy to be one with you.
Is it okay if I move?
Umm... move?
It means my cock will keep rubbing inside the vagina back and forth.
That way the pleasure of having a cock will start to rise
before it finally ejaculates.
That's what sex is.
So that's how it is.
Okay. I'll endure it even if it hurts.
Use my pussy to feel good, Onii-chan.
I'll move now, Yuki-chan.
Onii-chan is moving wildly inside me.
Your boobs seem to be aroused too, Yuki-chan.
It's embarrassing for my breasts to be touched like that.
Your breasts are really cute.
Onii-chan, if you keep on fondling my breasts like that... I will definitely lose it and go crazy.
When a woman's breasts are fondled sexually, it gets aroused, and the sensitive nipples harden up.
It's true. My nipples are really getting hard.
Then, if I try to massage it like this...
No... If you tease my nipples like that then my breasts feel tingly all over.
Onii-chan, my pussy...
Something hot is happening in there!
Is the pain gone?
My pussy is in pain, and yet it feels kind of good.
It's the first time I've felt like this.
Do you feel like cumming?
I'm cumming.
But it feels a bit different from what I felt with Cli-chan.
My vagina feels so hot as if...
some thing's filling it in—
Do you want to cum?
I want to cum.
I want to cum with my pussy!
Then I'll make you cum.
Onii-chan's hard and hot cock keeps on hitting deep inside.
More! I want you to hit me deeper!
Yuki-chan's pussy is starting to get really soft.
My pussy really feels good.
Onii-chan it hurts, but I feel it inside me.
Yeah, it feels very good for me too, Yuki-chan.
I'm so happy.
Please use me more and make yourself feel good. Okay, Onii-chan?
It's both erotic and lewdly cute when she's getting all wriggly like that.
Onii-chan, I really feel something is coming and my pussy is going crazy.
Yuki-chan, I'm also at my limit!
Let's cum together!
Yes! Cum, Onii-chan!
Cum together... Cum together with me.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My pussy is about to burst!
Onii-chan, your cock released something white and sticky.
That's called semen, Yuki-chan.
So this is Onii-chan's semen.
So if this gets inside the womb, the woman gets pregnant.
For today you can try tasting it if you're interested, Yuki-chan.
Is it okay if I taste it?
Maki-chan loves and drinks it pleasurably.
Really?
Then I'll try a bit.
How is it?
It's not even a bit delicious, Onii-chan.
Looking at each other silently,
Seiichi's lips drew closer to Yuki's face.
Onii-chan...
Seiichi's tongue twists and turns inside.
His left hand gently caresses her breasts.
Seiichi looks straight at Yuki's face.
Yuki's face shines with passion, looking back at Seiichi's face.
Hey Onii-chan, did you know? That was my first kiss.
With the two charmed by each other,
Seiichi holds Yuuki's left hand gently,
and escorts her out of the bathroom.
And they started their journey towards sexual pleasure.
Maki-chan, you've been noisy for a while now.
Geez, you two seemed to be doing it with such intense pleasure for some time.
My pussy just wasn't able to wait any longer.
Geez, Onee-chan. I just wanted to have sex a little bit more.
Sorry about that.
Then, let's all do it right now.
Go to that wonderful paradise!
Everyone!
Thank you for watching until the very end!
Please look out for Collaboration Works next month!
www.SubDESU-H.net