Good morning.
Good morning!
Her name is Takashima Shigure-senpai.
She's got a beautiful figure, is the student council president,
and is the athletic ace of the swimming team as well.
But...
S-So what happened yesterday was real?
You've got to be kidding, right?
For a person like Takashima-senpai to be doing that...
I came across an unthinkable sight!
For me to be fully naked inside the classroom, and touching my pussy...
If someone were to see me...
If they saw me...
I'm watching! I'm a person watching!
Noo!
I'm going to cum, I'm gonna cum!
Eh?! Is someone there?
I-I'm sorry!
Are you alright?
Ouch... Yes, I'm fine...
Your nose is bleeding...
Umm, Senpai?
I promise not to tell anyone.
Really?
So close-!
Y-Yes, I won't tell any-
Ah~! You're so good!
Huh? W-Wait!
If I don't do this, you won't trust me, will you?
If you're going to be silent, it'll be give and take!
For your information, that kiss we just had was my first!
You've been getting hard haven't you? Show me! There!
Whoa! A real penis! This is my first time seeing such a thing!
This isn't something a girl should smell, is it?
If a girl does smell this...
They turn as horny as a dog in heat!
It's sour-
So this is what a penis tastes like...
It tastes funny, but it's good!
I-I'm about to-!
It's fine, let it out!
Amazing! It's so thick and jelly-like!
Ah! My pussy is quivering!
I'm going to eat your penis with my pussy!
It's okay, right?
Even if you disagree, I'll do it anyway...
W-Wait, senpai!
I'm going to let you have my first time, okay?
F-First time?!
Are you happy? Isn't this your first time, too?
Let's give each other our virginity!
The tip went in!
Oh my, my pussy is quivering already!
It's clinging on to me, it feels like it's sucking me in!
It's only halfway in!
Even so, it feels great!
Even my fingers haven't been from here on in!
I wonder what will happen if it goes all the way in?
But since this is the first time for both of us, enjoy it much as you ca-!
It's kissing my uterus!
With a smooch!
S-Senpai?
S-Sex is... Great! It feels so good!
Your cock is expanding inside of me!
This is incredible! It's totally different than masturbating!
Please thrust up more!
Noo~! I love your cock!
Your cock~!
I feel electrocuted when your cock kisses my uterus!
I feel as if I'm floating!
I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum again!
This is tiring, I've already came 5 times!
I don't think I can live without your cock!
Let it out! Let out your milk inside me!
Hey, I know this is kinda late...
But what's your name?
I-I'm Kita Komatsu.
You know, it's hard work living up to everyone’s expectations.
If I'm good for the whole time, my other half says to me,
"Look look! This is the real me!"
But I'm glad...
I'm glad you were the one who saw me.
See you tomorrow!
Eh?
From then on, my sexual relationship with senpai began...
Your insides are clinging to me, senpai...
You can tell? I'm feeling really aroused.
I-It's throbbing on its own!
I can't bear it!
Please let me cum!
Let it out with your tip against my uterus!
Senpai-!
I might end up moaning loudly, so kiss me!
I'm cumming~!!
You're being rougher than usual!
Your penis is dancing around inside me!
Are you getting aroused from being outside?
I am too!
Please thrust inside me more!
Push against my deep sensitive spot more!
No~! This position is embarrassing!
If someone sees us, they'll see my pussy!
No~! No more~!
It's coming out... Your semen is filling me-!
I wet myself lots, too!
Swimming contest...
Spelling bee...
Preparation for the cultural festival...
Various departmental budget meetings...
All sorts of file gathering...
Volunteer work...
What's all this unimportant business?
I haven't had sex in a month!
I wanna do it, I wanna do it, I wanna do it!
I've unconsciously come to this memorable classroom.
It's been a month since that day.
I haven't met her, I haven't even seen her, and of course we haven't had sex!
That means it's over, doesn’t it!
This desk... She was masturbating on it that time...
S-Senpai?!
Senpai!!
I've...
I've reached my limit!
Be obedient!
Bon appétit!
It tastes so good! The tip is like jelly in my mouth!
I can't get married now!
I-I'm cumming!
You came so energetically that I choked!
Something amazing is happening to my pussy as well!
How is it?
Since I'm feeling super aroused, I bet you can detect my womanly scent!
T-The smell of senpai's pussy is amazing-!
My juices are flowing out!
It's wanting something to fill it!
Noo~!
My body is getting pushed apart!
It's coming in!
This is it... This is what I wanted!
No~! I might get teary!
I can't stop! It's thrusting so deeply, the kisses from your penis!
I-If you do it so much, my dick will melt!
No~! My pussy is so happy that I can't stop!
I-I feel like I'm flying!
I-It feels so good!
Give it to me-!
Give me your thick white love.
Full up my uterus with it!
It's coming!!
That's your third load!
That's the fifth time!
Seventh time!
Tenth time!
I'm so full! I'm satisfied...
I-It's over...
It felt good, but... I could see the flower meadow...
So then! How about we go for dessert?
B-But! Didn't you say you were satisfied?
TL note= In Japan, it is said that the main course and dessert in cuisine are processed in different stomachs, so that even if you're full, you can always eat dessert!
That's the other stomach!
N-No more!!
Don't say that!
SubDesu-H