Where am I? Why am I being...
So, you're awake.
Brother?
No... You're the traitor, Hie!
I see... I was captured by you, and...
Why didn't you kill me?
I thought I could use you.
You underestimate me... I won't let you use me!
I will have even you help me find the manjidanyuu's ninja technique.
I won't let you talk back to me!
Don't make a fool of me, who will...
How was it?
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you, and all the Sakuyas!
Do you still have the gall to talk back?
I want you to bear this for a while.
I think I need to make you understand the situation you're in!
It's still too early to sleep, Hoden!
You have to endure this...
I don't want you to die yet, you know!
Brother... Please, stop this!
You're not like Sakuya, you'll break.
Translated by SubDESU-H
A rotten kunoichi, filled with sperm.
You're late today.
Were you waiting for the lesson?
No, I wasn't!
I... I just thought that something might have happened to you.
What nonsense.
Yes, you're right.
You look better now.
What are you...?!
I think the results of the lessons are starting to show.
No, that's not...
You're already wet...
No, I'm not...
I'm not feeling it touching my pussy...
No...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
My pussy is cumming!
You're already making a woman's face, Sakuya!
Please... Don't do this anymore!
I... I....
No... Don't look at me!
No...
It's great... You're rubbing my pussy!
Please... Stop it!
You still won't be obedient?
No... Stop it!
I'm going to break!
Your dick feels too good, I'll break!
No... You should stop this!
Stop!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
You wanted me to cum inside you like always, right?
No... Not inside!
No... You can't cum inside!
If you cum inside, I'll feel good,
and you'll make me pregnant!
No...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Cum... I'll stay inside and cum!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out inside...
So much of my brother's cum is spilling out inside me!
No... My pussy is at its limit!
It's good... So good!
My pussy is being torn apart!
So intense... I... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I love my brother's dick!
It's so intense, I...
I'll cum again!
Please... Please give it to me again!
I'm cumming!
I think I'll work on Sakuya a little more.
What should I do next?
I'm coming in.
What is it?
It seems Sakuya's lessons are going well.
But there's still one more kunoichi you need to take care of.
I would like it if the next one had more of a twist, don't you think?
Do you have anything planned?
I do have an interesting plan.
I can tell you, but before that...
Please let me taste your dick too!
Your dick is great!
It's so firm...
Delicious...
It's so delicious!
Please, be gentle...
I understand.
Good... Deeper... Lick the clitoris too!
Please.... Not with your tongue; let me cum with your dick!
Alright...
Your dick is great!
Good...
Deeper inside my pussy...
Please cum a lot!
Good...
Your dick makes my pussy feel so good!
I'm going to cum now!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
My pussy is cumming!
About the lesson with Sakuya...
I thought I would join you next time.
Oh.
There's one more kunoichi you captured, right?
Let her join too.
Use the other ninja's as well.
I think this'll be fun!
I'm going to use that plan.
Yes, go ahead.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
But...
We should have some fun today too.
I've prepared a special guest for you!
Ho... Hotaru!
Sakuya!
Hotaru... I didn't think you'd been captured too!
I came here to kill you and that traitor over there!
Hotaru...
Brother... Don't tell me you did those horrible things to Hotaru too?
Let's start.
Ok...
It's pointless to do this kind of thing...
Is it so unusual for you to see this?
As I expected from a virgin, such a good reaction!
It'll be a bit painful, but please bear it...
I can't hold it anymore!
Who told you to scream?
Stop! Let her go!
Keep quiet!
Do you want me to tie you up?
Hotaru...
A kunoichi from Nagiri village is just a woman when she becomes like this!
Suck it properly!
Stop! Let Hotaru go!
Wha... Don't come near me!
You want some dick too, right?
You lecherous woman!
No, I'm not... Stop it!
You really are a noisy girl!
Just shut up and suck this!
Hey, you two, serve them properly!
It's such fun to make a strong kunoichi cry!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming too!
Hey! Don't let Sakuya spit it out!
Ok!
Here, don't let it spill.
If you can spit it with this then try it
I'm cumming...
I'm going next!
Hey I haven't cum yet!
What are you saying, it's me
Shut up!
Please, forgive me...
Stop...
If you keep going I'll...
I'm cumming...
I can't...
Help me!
Good... Good... Good!
It's so good!
There's a dick in both my holes and they're rubbing together inside!
Good... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Dicks...
There are so many dicks...
No... If I continue this...
I'm cumming!
It hurts!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
There's a lot coming out...
It's coming out here too!
Here comes the next batch!
It's my turn next!
We can't do it anymore!
No... Stop!
What a dirty voice!
I'll let you cum again!
I'm going to break!
No...
No... I can't keep going!
I'm cumming!
My ass and my pussy will cum!
Please stop it!
I don't want this!
Don't cum inside my pussy!
Hey, you two, don't lie down yet!
There are still a lot of ninja's you haven't satisfied!
You should make them cum, one by one!
No... No!
Please forgive us!
My pussy is at its limit!
No!
So good... My pussy feels so good!
Please give me more of your dick!
Put that in too!
Yeah, you perverted kunoichi!
Good... Rub it more!
Good... Faster... Faster!
Cum in my pussy!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Not yet! Hold it!
No... You can't put in two dicks at once!
It can't... It can't!
So good...
No...
No... Take it out!
I'm going to die!
Dicks...
The hot sperm is coming out...
So good... Those two girls' voices are good too!
It's so delicious!
So good...
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm cumming!
Cum inside... Cum a lot inside!
This is perfect...
It's over...
Yeah.