There... that’s good…
Don't...
You like it here.
Getting close…
Good... boy…
Good… it feels good…Seiichi-san
Hehehe…Your clitoris is sensitive,
isn’t it? Sorry about that.
I’m close! I’m–I’m cumming!
Try to keep your voice down. It probably
carried all the way to the kid's rooms.
S-Sorry, It's been a while since I've had sex.
This time, make me feel good.
Okay.
You’ve become quite the little
cock-tease, haven’t you?
I’m not teasing you. I’m just licking
it because it’s delicious.
Hanae-san…
What? You’re putting it in already?
Yes, since your penis is so wonderful, I can't help myself.
I haven’t had it in a while, so it's fine if i put it in, right?
I guess it can’t be helped. You do the
moving and make me feel good.
I can feel your penis moving inside of me.
Yes, yes…
Yes, so good… I’ve missed your cock…
Seiichi-san’s cock… So good…
So good...
Yes, your cock…
No...
My clitoris feels so good…
I'm gonna cum.
Yes, your cock… So good… My clitoris
feels so good… So good…
Hanae-san… Why are you moving your hips like that?
Why do you look like it makes you feel so good?
You're hitting my womb.
So good.
I’m cumming! I'm cumming!
I’m cumming…
I’m cumming! Cumming! Cumming!
What? You came before me?
Crap!
It’s my turn to cum now.
Yes, please give a lot of it to me.
Amazing! It’s all the way in me!
So good... So incredibly good...
Fuck me harder, Seiichi-san!
It feels so good there...
More... Fuck me harder further inside!
It feels so good...
Yes! I’m cumming! I’m cumming, Seiichi-san!
So good...
I love you, I love you, Seiichi-san!
More...
Crap. He probably saw me.
Good! I'm about to cum! I feel like I'm about to cum!!
No...
Noo...
There now. Without making me cum again, lick it clean.
Yes…
First                 Volume
SubDESU-H Presents
Haha Sange
Mom! You seem pretty cheerful.
Do I really?
Did something good happen yesterday?
Not really, nothing at all.
Ooh...?
You should hurry up. You’ll be late for school.
Good morning Tomonori-san.
Good morning Onii-chan
Uh, yeah.
Don’t you have a proper greeting
for your mother and little sister?
He’s probably stayed up all night doing
homework and now he’s tired, right?
Yeah. Hanae-san, I don’t feel well,
so I won’t need breakfast.
Are you ok?
I’m fine.
Don’t worry about me.
I'll be on my way.
Ah, Onii-chan!
Hm?
Do you have some free time tonight?
Hm? At night?
I was hoping you could help me with my homework.
I don’t really know anything
about your homework…
Don’t worry, you've got good grades!
So, tonight, right? Thanks a lot!
Marie, you’d better hurry up too.
Okay.
Onii-chan, can I come in?
Come in.
What? Are you coming in or not?
Tada! Does it suit me?
Well? You’re surprised, right? Isn’t it just perfect on me?
It’s super cute, right? Onii-chan, what do you think?
Is it sexy? Is it cute?
Which of them is it?
Hey, did you come here to show me your cosplay?
What about your homework?
This isn’t a cosplay.
I’ve been picked to be a regular.
I-If you say such things ...
Hey, it’s fine. I only wanted to show it to you first.
Oh, sorry. It suits you. And it's amazing that
you have been selected to be a regular.
It makes me happy seeing you going to practice every
morning and knowing you're doing your best.
Really? Heheheh... Thank you...
Yay, Onii-chan praised me!
Uh… What’s wrong, Onii-chan?
Well, your skirt is too short. Your panties are showing.
That’s okay. During practice we wear shorts over the panties.
That’s not it. I can see your panties right now.
You’re not just seeing them. I’m showing them to just you.
Eh?
Come over here, Onii-chan ...
So, when you saw my panties, did you feel excited?
D-desire for my little sister?!
Even though I’m your sister, we're not related by blood,
and I want to get married, and make a baby too ...
Well, technically yes, but...
Onii-chan, your heart is pounding so fast.
My heart is pounding, right?
Her breasts are soft…
I love you. I can’t hide it anymore.
But…
Onii-chan… How do you feel about me?
Well, as my little sister, I think you’re cute, but…
But?
I do...
You like mother, so you can’t love me, right?
What!
Why do you think I like Hanae-san…
It’s obvious. Every day you look at her.
The way you look at her is different.
I like Hanae-san, but... She's the one who drove
my mother away from this house, away from me!
Yes, so good… More… More… Cum…
You’re moving in me so much I can’t stand it. It feels so good.
I’m about to cum. I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
There’s no way!
Marie-chan will be Onii-chan's...
I'll be only your woman, Onii-chan.
I’m different from mother.
I love you, Onii-chan.
Her lips are soft. They feel so good.
It's ok. If it's Onii-chan...
I'll give you my virginity.
You can't...
So wet…
Good.
Yes… Onii-chan, there feels good!
Hey, is it okay if I lick you?
Yeah. You’ll lick gently, right?
There... Onii-chan, Onii-chan, there…
I'll cum... I'm cumming!!
Hehe… Your cock is so hard!
Fellatio feels... So good.
I’m close. I’m coming. That’s enough… Sto–
You swallowed it? Are you okay?
It was a little bitter, but since it's Onii-chan's,
so it was delicious.
Is it really okay to do this?
Yes. I've always wanted to do this with Onii-chan...
I've always wanted us to become one.
Yes, please put it in me.
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
It hurts a bit, but I’m okay. I can handle it.
How does it feel inside me?
It's very warm and feel very good.
I'm so glad, that you'd be happy.
I'll be ok, so please start moving.
Make yourself feel good. Ok?
It's starting to gradually feel better ..
Onii-chan's penis... It's good...
Onii-chan! Onii-chan! So good! Put it deeper in... Onii-chan!
So close! I’m cumming! I’m about to cum!
Today was a safe day, so it was ok to release it inside...
Onii-chan... Let's do this again, ok?
Oh, Tomonori-san.
Oh, I just had some things i needed to research on
the Internet. Dad’s computer is faster than mine, so...
When you're done, make sure to tidy up after yourself.
Seiichi-san is strict, you know.
Yeah, I understand. Hey, dad left on a business trip today, didn’t he?
Yes, for a week.
Why do you ask?
No reason. It’s just that I haven’t spoken to him recently.
Well, that won’t do. Closeness is important in families.
Yes. Sorry.
What?
It's been a while since I last saw you smile.
R-Really?
Did something good happen?
Well, um, yeah, more or less.
Your expression was glum for a while. I was a bit worried about you.
If something bothers you again, please tell me about it, okay?
O-okay, when that time comes.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Looks like she doesn’t know about Marie. Nor about dad cheating on her...
Hanae is beautiful and stylish. It’s too bad.
Hm?
What? I’ve never seen this folder before.
Is dad planning another adulterous meeting?
No! Please, Tomonori-san!
Nooo… !!
S-stop, why would you do this to me, Tomonori-san?
Are you gonna make a fuss? If you scream,
you’ll wake Marie, and the neighbors will hear.
If i did that, this house, our family would be over.
This house? What are you playing family for?
You cockroach! You crawled into this
house and threw my mother out.
What? We’re a family, aren't we? Calm down, ok?
If family is so important, come sink yourself onto your son.
If I use my mouth on you, things will be back to normal
tomorrow right? You'll stop this? You promise?
Hey. You said you’d use your mouth.
I’m sorry.
Stop. That’s enough.
So, we’re good now?
I won't be satisfied with just this.
No… !!
Stop it... Stop this!
Please... We're mother and son...
We can't do this! We can't!
Don't put it that far inside...!
Stop! Forgive me!
You can't! You can't cum inside! Release it outside!!
To be continued.