I want to be with you, Onii-chan...
Kaede! This is not the time-!
O-Onii-chan!
Please look at me down here!
I-I'm so wet already!
See? Please look at my most private parts!
Oh no, this feels too good!
No-! Oh no!
M-My finger-!
It's so embarrassing, but-!
I-It's overflowing!
M-My lewd juices are dribbling out-!
T-This is too good-!
It's like I'm dreaming!
I-I'm being watched by Onii-chan while I'm masturbating...!
T-This is amazing!
SubDESU-H Presents
Kagirohi - Shaku Kei
Onii-chan...
Let's become one...
Why...
Why are you making such a sad face?
If you'll be satisfied with it, then...
I'm really just being a burden to you, aren't I, Senpai?
Kaede...
I'm sorry!
But Senpai-!
Please let us go until the end!
Please listen to my selfishness this last time!
Alright...
I'm so happy, Senpai...
Senpai... Please give it to me...
Senpai-! This is embarrassing!
P-Please don't tease me...
It's going in-!
Y-Your hard and big thing is entering me-!
It's all the way in...
I'm so happy... It's all the way inside me...
Senpai, don't mind me. Thrust all you want.
Okay.
Thank you, Senpai...
Senpai's thing is thrusting inside me-!
I-It's mixing up my insides-!
No!
D-Don't-!
My breasts feel too good!
A-Amazing-!
Onii-chan's thing is knocking against the end-!
It might start to swell!
It's reaching my deepest spots!
I'm going crazy!
It's so good! Your cock is mixing up my insides-!
T-This is incredible-!
S-So good-! This feels too good! I'm-!
I'm gonna lose it soon!
I can hear the lewd sounds!
I can't help it!
No more! I'm-!
Kaede-!
I-I'm nearly cumming as well!
Y-You sure filled me up, didn't you?
Senpai...
Are you serious about Ajisai?
Yes. You won't stop me.
You love her very much, don't you...
But...
Kaede...
As an underclassman, I cannot let Senpai go through such danger again.
I will take care of Ajisai.
I will end...
this crazed tale for you.
Where do you think you're going?
Sumire-sama?
Oh my, if it isn't Kaede-chan.
Are you perhaps betraying us?
T-This is a promise to Senpai, so...!
That man?
Maybe you require harsh punishment, Kaede-chan.
Eh? A-Ajisai-?
Impossible! This cannot be...
Why?!
W-Why is Izanami-sama...?!
T-This is...?! Ajisai!
W-What did you do-?!
I won't forgive you two.
No!
Kaede? Where are you?
Don't tell me...?!
Damn it!
No!
No!!
This feels disgusting! Let me go!
No! Senpai!!
Help us!
L-Let us go!
Now, let me hear your cries.
Entertain me.
D-Don't-!
T-That's too big-!
N-Not my ass-!
That's it... suffer more...
It's going inside me-!
N-No-!
It's too deep-!
Don't push it in so much!
No...!
I-It's going wild inside me-!
I-It's too big! N-Not there-!
Stop it-!
I'm gonna die, I'm really gonna die!
You'll break my butt-!
N-No...
I-If two go inside me, I'll-!
So deep-!
I-It's going in so deep-!
T-This is too much-!
D-Don't spread my butt like that-!
D-Don't-!
N-No-! I-It's too big-!
No-!
I'll turn into a loose woman-!
I-I can't hold my voice!
I don't want it, but...!
I-I'm gonna cum-!
P-Please stop it-!
I-It's entering me so deeply-!
My butt, it's-!
Don't lick my insides!
D-Don't-! T-That's my-!
D-Don't push it in so deep!
I-I'm going crazy from this!
Stop!
No!
I can't breathe!
More...
No more!
No, I'm gonna cum!
F-From these two-!
I'm... I-I'm gonna cum!
I won't let this end.
You two need more...
Ajisai!
Aoi...?
Stop this already, Ajisai!
I've already become Izanami.
My consciousness and Izanami have already merged.
I won't stop until I've destroyed this village.
Ajisai wouldn't do such a thing!
I can.
If you're going to get in my way, then...
The Ajisai that I love wouldn't do such a thing!
Forget about me!
Aoi...
The light...
I-Izanami is disappearing...
So beautiful...
Hey, do you remember?
This classroom is where we first met.
Yeah, a lot of things have happened since then.
Hey...
H-Hey...
I want to do it here, the place where we first met.
We can't?
Fine, then.
I'll do it to you.
You've already gotten so hard from just kissing.
Is it painful?
I'll let it out now.
I-It's gotten so big already!
It smells so dirty...
It's so hard and hot...
I can feel it throbbing...
Hey, how is it?
Does my hand feel good?
I'll make you feel even better...
Y-You're overflowing already...
Y-You're gonna cum?
Go on, you can let it out anytime.
Let it out!
Amazing...
Come here.
Oh no...
N-No...
So good...
T-That's...
Your finger is going inside me!
D-Don't do that so much!
Otherwise-!
C-Can we do it now?
Hurry up...
P-Put it in, please...
It's rubbing against me...
Put it in, put it in-!
D-Don't tease me...
It's going in!
It's so hard and hot!
So big-!
It feels like I'm melting!
No!
I can't hold my voice!
No, I'm gonna cum!
T-This is amazing!
P-Please do it harder!
No! I-I'm overflowing so much!
It's making such lewd sounds! It's embarrassing!
No, I-I'm overflowing so much!
M-My deepest spots...!
Y-Your cock is rubbing against my deepest spots!
If you do that, I'll-!
No! If you do it so hard, I'll-!
N-No!
Something is coming!
Your cock is throbbing inside me!
Are you gonna cum?
Go on, cum inside me!
Let out lots of your hot semen!
N-No!
I'm-! N-No!
N-No! I'm gonna-!
D-Donft, I'm gonna cum-!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming-!
I-It's coming out... So much is coming out...
I love you...