W
~ Angels’ Private Lessons ~
MegaPile
Air Mix
Here’s Your Meal
Miyazawa-san’s Rape Experience Confessional
Ami?
Huh?
Hime-chan, where’s Miyazawa-san?
Not sure.
K-Kanda-kun?
If you stay quiet, I’ll be gentle.
In that case, Hime-chan, you should ask him out.
Ask Ka-n-da-ku-n.
Don’t!
Kanda-kun...
Hime-chan... has a crush on you...
Don’t.
I’ll scream.
Miyazawa... I’ve always wanted you.
No... No! Don’t take off my clothes!
Wh-What?
What is this thing?
It... It’s so big...
Is that going to fit in me?
It won’t!
I’ll break apart!
Wait... Don’t put something so big in me!
But I can’t hold back anymore.
Wait... I understand.
Can we... can we just do foreplay?
It’s touching my pussy... slipping by it.
My clitoris... it’s hitting it...
It’s getting hard...
Wh-Why do I feel it getting bigger?
It’s coming!
It’s like a water gun!
I’ll wipe it off... okay?
Did everything come out, Kanda-kun?
Wh-Why?
It’s even bigger than before...
Miyazawa!
Well then, see you later.
Okay, good work.
So tight... it’s too big!
It feels like it’s going to reach up to my mouth!
Don’t go in so deep...
Or my insides...
My insides... will be ripped apart!
Hime-chan, let’s go home.
Sure...
Maybe I was just hearing things.
It’s coming.
This feels great, Miyazawa.
It’s not over yet.
Kanda-kun... please, stop it.
I’ve still got more.
Wait a minute!
I forgot my soda!
I’m cumming!
Miyazawa, your insides are so wet, they feel great.
Whoa, they’re tightening.
It feels good for you too, doesn’t it?
Can I see your face?
Wow, so pretty.
And I’m fucking this pretty girl right now.
It’s been a year – let me have my fun.
Wow, so tight.
If he cums any more in me, I’ll probably get pregnant.
I’m cumming!
No... spray my face instead!
Miyazawa is covered in my sticky semen!
Open your mouth more or it won’t go in.
Miyazawa, your tongue is so warm and soft.
It feels great!
It’s coming out!
It’s like I’m cumming deep into your pussy.
Hey, Miyazawa, stay behind in the classroom after school tomorrow.
Wow, she smells great.
No... stop it!
I said I’d only blow you.
Oh... Too bad.
Don’t! Something that big won’t fit in!
You’ll be fine. It fit fine yesterday.
Look, even the base went in.
I’m such a horny bastard.
And you’re really tight.
You’re pissing yourself, Miyazawa.
I’m cumming soon too.
Please, not inside!
Then, swallow it.
My... uterus... is ripping apart.
Sex With Mikura-san
Don’t... don’t lick it.
Don’t... my pussy is dirty...
N-No!
W-Wait, wait a minute.
D-Don’t... don’t...
It’s coming out. It’s coming out!
Mikura-san, are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I’m fine.
S-Sorry!
My sex juices made your face all sticky.
I’ll clean it now.
Mikura-san, that tickles.
Endo-kun... come to me.
Mikura-san, your insides are all sticky.
Is it because of the fever?
I seem more sensitive than usual.
It’s hitting... hitting so deep inside of me.
Well then, this one, too.
If you move your fingers so much... I’ll cum again.
Mikura-san, did you cum?
Y-Yes.
Sorry.
I came alone... you need to cum too.
You can cum inside of me today.
Endo-kun, your dick is so hot! It’s throbbing inside me!
Mikura-san... I’m almost...
It’s okay. Cum inside me.
Fill me full of semen – it’s okay.
It’s coming in.
Hot stuff... is pulsating inside me.
So hot...
I got all sweaty again.
You don’t need to push yourself.
I’m fine.
I get to relax.
You can be the one to move.
You get what I mean?
Mi-Mikura-san...
N-No!
Oh, you just came.
And you’re already hard again.
Mikura-san, you just... feel so good to me...
It’s okay.
Endo-kun, fuck me as much as you want.
Wow... You came again.
My insides are all full now.
Are you putting it away already?
Um... well, I...
You don’t need to hold back.
Cum lots more if you want.
B-But I...
Do it fast or it’ll spill out.
Mikura-san...
Wow... my body is so hot...
I think it’s all I can feel anymore.
W-Wait...
You’re sloshing the semen inside me.
What naughty noises.
I’m losing my mind.
Mikura-san... I’m... again...
It’s okay.
Me too.
I’m gonna cum again too.
Please, together!
Wait, don’t pull it out.
Please stay like this for a while longer.
W-Will you really do it?
This and that with Miyazawa-san.
I’ll borrow this one, please.
S-Sure!
It’s due a week from now.
Huh? Okay.
Ah... wh...
Uh, nothing.
Bye...
Are you embarrassed?
Wanna see my tits too?
Miyazawa-san!
Take a good look.
Oh dear.
So much spunk.
Does it feel good?
Mi-Miyazawa-san!
We’re in the library. We need to be quiet.
I’m sorry.
I’ll try harder to be quiet.
Well?
My boobs are small so I can’t do this very well.
But I’ll cover them in drool.
Yes... my nipples... are rubbing... and I’m starting to get turned on.
This is a Subdesu-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Mi-Miyazawa-san... I’m...
Miyazawa-san... I wanna see... your pussy.
P-Please.
If I see your pussy, I’m sure I’ll...
You’re only seeing it, okay?
Just don’t... stare too long at it.
W-Wow.
Miyazawa-san, you’re soaked through right here.
Oh... no!
Don’t say such embarrassing things.
Miyazawa-san.
I’m cumming!
Wait, you can’t do that!
I told you, just a look!
Don’t touch...
D-Don’t do it. Don’t put it in!
But I can’t hold back.
But...
Just the tip, okay?
“Just the tip”... did I hear that right?
It’s all the way inside!
W-Wow.
Miyazawa-san... I’m in... your pussy...
I can see it.
N-No!
Stop it!
But... but I’m... almost there...
N-Not inside!
B-But... Kanda told me... that I could cum... inside of you.
N-No Way!
No...
Don’t!
I’ll cum...
I’m gonna cum...
I’m cumming... cumming... cumming...
I’m cumming!
So... so much came... out...
N-No...
You’re soaked through.
You were turned on.
No. That’s not... true.
Then let’s test out that theory.
See? It went in with just one push.
You’re soaked through.
Please... don’t be rough so suddenly like that.
I’ll break apart!
I can’t take anymore...
Why am I fucked every day... by these gross guys?
Oh, shit. I’m gonna cum!
D-Don’t!
No... today is not a good day for that!
Seriously... I’ll get pregnant...!
Oh, really?
Even though he already came in you in the library?
You need to let me cum in you too.
Please... not inside... not inside... please stop!
There...?
You can’t get pregnant from this hole, right?
No... don't...!
Kanda-kun, you’re too big... it won’t fit...
You'll never know unless you try.
See? It fit.
It hurts...
Miyazawa, your asshole... it’s fucking tight!
My... my insides... are being stirred up...
Wow!
The base of my dick is being squeezed so tight.
T-Time to cum.
Please... hurry... just get it over with.
Or I’ll break apart.
I’ll...
How much longer... how much longer will this... continue?
I’ve become... tainted...
Masturbating With Kirishima-san.
What's this?
My body got hot all of a sudden.
My pussy...
Kirishima-san, what’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
My pussy...
Kirishima-san, are you okay?
Kirishima-san?
Why?
Why so sudden...
I want to... fuck someone...
Asaoka-sensei!
Kirishima needs...
A-Asaoka-sensei... what are you doing?
N-Nothing!
Close the door, fast!
Put her on the bed here.
Okay.
Next, unbutton her blouse and expose her chest.
Hurry!
Okay.
What a big chest.
Oh, her nipples are erect.
You’ve been holding back a lot, the both of you.
Take it off, both of you!
Hurry! Take off your pants!
Maybe it’s about time now?
Oh no!
Okay, wait for me, Asaoka-sensei!
You like it, don’t you?
Oh, well.
Are you a mother, Kirishima-san?
Oh, you’re hard too.
I'll suck out your semen with these huge tits.
Kirishima’s tits are so warm.
Your hard-on is soaking wet in breast milk.
See?
You need to take it in.
Wow, it was so thick.
But you can still cum much more.
You always fantasize about these tits when you masturbate, right?
This is a Subdesu-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
It’s cumming!
You’re all soaked.
Oh, shit!
I wanna join in!
Just a bit...
What? Are you gonna cum? Are you gonna cum?
Are you almost there?
Then cum.
It’s okay, please cum.
Now, we’re all ready.
This time, I’ll suck it out of you with this hole.
Okay, come on, okay, come on, okay!
Okay, I’ll put it in.
You both wanted it, didn't you?
Now, suck his semen all the way out.
You need to move more, it feels better that way.
When you want to cum, don’t hold back.
Cum inside, okay?
Show me how thick and heavy your semen is.
Mizuho-senpai’s Masturbation Experience Confessional
Mizuho-senpai.
It’s about this problem.
I don’t know how to solve it.
Ah, you need to divide it up first.
Oh, thanks, Senpai.
Thanks for staying behind after school for me.
It’s okay. I enjoy teaching.
S-Senpai... this is bad.
But... the atmosphere of an upperclassman sure is different.
Really?
Mizuho-senpai, is your seat right there?
Yes, it is.
Why?
Uh, no reason.
S-Senpai... Seriously... I’m almost...
Oh no.
S-Senpai...
Oh, dear. You wake up fast.
Or, maybe you were awake this whole time.
Does my tongue feel good?
Yes.
Your tongue is... soft.
I’ll stick it in your hole, too.
S-Senpai...
Your tongue... it’s inside...
See?
You had so much stored up.
I can’t wait to see how much more is in you.
Inside... The pasta and... your tongue are tangled...
Senpai?
I spilled it.
Oh yes.
My pussy... it’s so soaked.
Senpai... your pussy... it feels good.
Did that hurt?
It hurts... but it feels good.
Oh... then...
Wow! Wow!
I feel it throbbing inside of me.
S-Senpai...
We need... to move more...
No, we don’t. Just be patient.
That’s right.
This time, get on top.
Yes...
Oh!
Senpai... I’m... almost...
All of it... in my mouth, please.
It’s coming...
Wow... I thought you’d get me pregnant through the mouth.
Just look at how much there was.
Sorry... it’s been a while.
www.Subdesu-H.net