Please wake up,
Master.
Good morning, Master.
Good morning.
Wait, that outfit is...!
Do you like it?
Yeah, especially around the boob area!
– Boobs!
– Master!
Soft and tender boobs!
So you're finally awake, eh?
My worthless and stupid master.
What do you want at this hour, Kiriha?
Also...
What's with that outfit?
It's a maid uniform.
So not only your personality, but your eyes are rotten as well?
H-Hey, what are you planning on doing?
I'm going to prick those rotten eyes.
Anything but that, Kiriha-sama!
I'll forgive you then.
Part 01
I'll discipline my master
My Cranky Maid Is Very Horny
I'm waiting for an explanation for this.
Is that your order as a master?
Yeah, that's right.
I was asked by Aunt,
to take care of a worthless stupid bug who can't even take care of himself.
So I'm a bug now?
I'm sorry. I guess a bug is not conscious of its own self worth.
What a waste.
Aside from that foul mouth, you are the very definition of "beauty"...
Maybe I was attracted to that cute side of hers?
Also, that clear white skin,
and the deep valley formed by those two big mountains!
What an atrocious!
What was that for?
It's punishment for blabbering about your
slimy desires this early in the morning.
Eh, was I saying it out loud?
It may be okay in here,
but please refrain from exposing your perverted
sexual desires to other people outside.
I am very sorry.
These clothes were left to me by your mom
to control that infinite libido of yours.
You can't defy me when I'm in these clothes, can you?
No fair!
Using my maid fetish like that...
I had to reluctantly accept her request as your childhood friend.
Being thanked for it is one thing, but I won't
stand for you complaining about it.
It's just all a ruse to extract vengeance for loosing that game to me, isn't it?
I know!
That maid outfit was meant to vent your anger on me, right?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Your maid... One week...
What are we going to play next?
Keep... Your maid... One week...
This activity helps me take care of you
while perfectly managing your libido.
So the total points that are written at the back of three command
cards will decide the outcome of the contest.
A maximum of 10 points will be alloted for each card.
If the total points are more than 15, then you lose.
This is interesting. Let's get started already!
The subject is related to a maid's "household chores",
and they start with either sa, shi, su, se or so.
I-If I try to let out my maid fetish desires here,
my chance of losing would be greater.
However, I can't defy the game's penalty rules.
Come on, horny maid!
On Card: Keep your maid cosplay on for one week
For me to be the recipient of that great libido...
You sure look really refreshed.
Would there be any meaning to this card
if I try to win it without going for a horny maid outfit?
Then as commanded, I will take care of you for one week in these clothes.
Rejoice now,
because here you've got a cute girl who's going to serve you in this outfit.
Let out your tears of joy and be grateful to me.
That won't seem to happen even if I win or not though...
Well then, master.
See you tomorrow.
Damn that Kiriha...
She put away all of my porn material!
Kiriha...
you're going to serve me completely.
You're going to serve your master!
Put it between those big boobs!
I'm going to cum, Kiriha.
Drink all of it!
Here you go, master.
Oh, thanks!
Oh, so master has this weird hobby of using
maids as porn material while jacking off.
Seems my imaginary version has done lots of things...
...to serve you, eh?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I won't do it anymore,
so please just forget about it!
I'm not asking for an apology, you know?
What should I do...?
You are my master right now.
Why don't you think about it for yourself?
You're not angry?
Ever so timid...
Stupid, perverted and worthless master!
Hey, your eyes look scary.
Just stay still.
I'm going to serve my pitiful and pathetic master.
Getting all twitchy just by it being held like this...
How unsightly.
Master, are you happy that a maid is currently giving you a handjob?
I'll stop doing it.
It absolutely feels good!
Is that all?
Aren't you happy?
Of course, I am!
I'm being done by the girl that I've liked for so long.
C-Confessing in this situation...
How much more deplorable of a master do you plan to be?
Then in that case...
Serve your master's cock until the very end!
If that's your order, then it can't be helped.
Be grateful, my perverted master.
Please say it when you are about to cum, master.
If you don't, I'll crush your balls.
I'm cumming. It's coming out!
Hey, stop!
It's very sensitive right now!
No way.
I'm going to tease it until it gets squeezed dry.
It doesn't taste good, but it might be okay in my mind if I get used to it.
Why are you okay with this?
Aren't you ashamed even for a bit?
I'll be the one to determine that.
Is the handjob of a pure and beautiful maiden not enough for you?
My manliness will go down if I keep getting pushed over.
This is an order!
Take responsibility for this and appease me!
I'll do it then if that's your command.
I wonder what kind of indecent and vulgar order
will this lazy and virginal master give me?
Give me a titty-fuck with those overly grown breasts!
Okay, then.
He did not even ask for a kiss or sex.
How much more disappointing of a man can he get?
Your boobs are the best!
Are you just going to ogle at it?
Are you getting aroused because you're about to be my first titty-fuck?
You're just too sharp.
I know because you're my master.
So, what should I do then?
Move it up and down.
Move it to the sides.
And lick the tip while you're at it.
I don't want to.
We haven't even kissed yet...
Did you say something else?
I did not!
Here, this is how you want it, right?
How does it feel to be serviced by a maid's boobs?
If course it's the best feeling!
It's hot and stiff.
My master's cock is twitching.
Cumming already?
Are you about to cum while your cock is being done by my boobs?
I'm going to cum now, Kiriha.
This is my special service.
Kiriha...!
S-Sorry...
The maid game had a rough start,
and while Kiriha pushed me around throughout that time,
one week had already passed by.
You already know what will happen if you move it, right?
Are you for real?
It's the "Maid will discipline the master sexually" card.
Prepare yourself.
I'm going to wetly discipline you.
It's really getting wet here.
Do you feel really good when a maid plays with it?
It'd get absolutely stiff if it's teased while your panties are exposed.
Blunthead!
I'm deliberately showing it off, you know!
If it's embarrassing for you, then don't do it.
Shut up!
You don't even have the guts to do it with a maid or two!
But you'd get angry if I do that!
Of course!
But...
I wouldn't resist.
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is a pussy!
A woman's... Mine...!
Don't stare at it too much.
S-Say something.
It feels uncomfortable,
If you don't... do something...
Well... It's erotic, Kiriha.
Is that the only thing you can say to a woman in this situation?
But, that erotic you...
It's what I like!
It's a confession fit for a worthless master such as you, I see.
If you want me to discipline you with my body,
then say "woof".
Woof, woof!
My master is willing to throw away his pride for his sexual desires.
It's so wonderful that it gives me the chills.
This is equal exchange between your precious and absolutely pure virginity,
and my own world-worthy and valuable virginity.
I-It hurts!
Kiriha!
I'm okay now.
You're not convincing me with those tears and strong act.
Hey, just continue with it already.
Do you want the maid that just lost her virginity to take the lead?
Are you happy that you're the one who got my first kiss?
This is part of your disciplining.
Convey it through words.
I'm happy!
I'm so happy that I'm about to die!
Do it more gently.
No, if you suck it strongly like that...
Now, I'll be the one to discipline you!
His cock is kissing my pussy deeply.
I feel like I'm the one going to be disciplined...
Yes, there...
Kiriha, I'm cumming...!
No, this is part of your disciplining.
This sex is meant for you to cum inside.
Because I've already decided to be penetrated
all the way into my womb by you.
Master has the right to impregnate his maid.
Yes, yes!
That face...
It arouses me!
I was still a virgin a while earlier, and now my pussy's really shaking hard.
Drill all the way into me with your sex already!
Pour your seed into my womb!
It's coming out!
It's coming out...
Lots of it is coming out!
I'm completely impregnated...
Kiriha!
I wasn't able to sleep...
Good morning, master.
Tsk.
So you're already awake.
It's all because of you
that I feel refreshed now!
*stare*
So the parts that make up my master are...
...libido, lust, and carnal desires, eh?
This is...!
Master, what are you going to do today?