That’s enough!
Please leave me alone!
Now isn’t the time...
Now is the best time!
Because I...
I’m telling you, you’re bothering me!
Bothering you?
And here I was holding back for you.
You ungrateful...
Nee-san...
Yukito
Let’s go.
Hey!
Why?
Why is this happening?
Why is Kotomi...
Nee-san, you should lie down for a bit.
I’m sorry, Yukito.
Is she okay? I heard her crying.
Oh, sorry for worrying you.
You sure are silly. I’m not worried.
Yukito...
- One day earlier -
Yukito-kun, are you mad?
No, not at all.
I was able to bring both my sisters along.
What a relief.
Since you kept looking out the window,
I was worried that maybe you’d felt obligated to take me.
It's so high in the mountains.
And the bridges were amazing.
That’s for sure.
That was kind of scary.
You used to be very scared of heights before.
You're a little chicken.
T-That’s not true!
Jeez. You only remember the embarrassing things.
Wow!
Otoha, your family has a summer home too, right?
We do, but it’s not that big.
Yukito-kun, do you remember the promise we made when we were kids?
Sorry. Forget about it.
It’s nothing.
Hurry, let’s go.
Otoha... What happened before we parted ways...
How could I ever forget it?
Why? Kotomi!
We have a special news bulletin.
Today, at around 18:45,
stabbing victims were discovered by the Buryou-cho train station.
The suspects were spotted yesterday at Morino-cho by the woods.
Suzuki-san, Matsui-san, Kuroki-san - three convicted violent criminals
They are currently on the run, violating their parole.
The police are...
The murderers... they’re on the move.
They were probably the ones who broke the glass.
I saw no one else around the property...
Only, I noticed that the footbridge leading here was destroyed.
Does that mean we’re trapped in here?
Isn’t there something we can do?
What are the police doing?
Let’s leave things outside to Nigel and his team.
We should all return to our rooms.
W
Endless...
Blue dyed in black
Original Video Animation
~ Gazing Shame ~
Reiya-san, are you okay?
What’s wrong, Reiya?!
Nothing... I’m okay.
Have you slept at all?
I’m sorry.
I’ll be fine if I take a nap.
Um... I’ll call Honaka-san.
No, don't.
I don’t want Honaka to have any more trouble.
I need to be strong.
The murderers were caught, right?
You don’t need to beat yourself up over it.
That may be so...
But I’m the one responsible here.
I need to make sure you all make it home safely.
I understand.
I’ll look after Reiya-sama.
Yukito-kun, you should rest too.
Otoha... can you take care of him alone?
I’m not that incompetent!
Stop teasing me, Yukito-kun.
I'll come see you later, Yukito-kun.
Good idea.
Okay. You can take care of things here.
See you later.
How sneaky of you...
I said I would examine you.
F-Fine, I get it.
“I understand”, you mean.
I understand.
This girl’s fancy...
Wh-What are you doing?!
If you do any more, I’ll scream!
So you don’t mind if anyone else sees your diary?
Better that than to be molested by you!
You’ve done enough, haven’t you?
So give me my diary back!
You accuse me of molestation?
Choose your words more carefully!
Hey... wait!
Yukito...
What’s wrong, Nee-san?
Doctor Takamine looked like he was in a hurry.
Did something happen again?
N-Nothing.
I’m okay.
You weren’t in your room so I was wondering what was wrong.
Thanks. I’m okay now.
Okay.
I’ll be in my room. If something happens, call me.
This is bad... not him...
Yukito-kun?
Can I come in?
Otoha... Is Reiya okay?
Yes. He was exhausted. He fell asleep right away.
Reiya feels very guilty about everything.
We should try to keep him calm.
That’s true.
He wishes he hadn’t organized the trip.
I see... I hope he doesn’t feel responsible.
That’s true. I’ll take care of him tomorrow, so I’ll try to tell him that.
You’ll take care of him tomorrow too?
He looks so strained. And I just want to be useful.
Oh, well, I didn’t mean...
Then, Yukito-kun, I’ll be going back to my room.
Don’t push yourself too hard. You’ll get sick.
I’ll be fine.
I can’t rest when everyone else is working so hard.
He’s trying to work himself hard again?
I need to tell him to be careful.
I don’t think you should walk around too much alone.
I need the others to respect me.
But still...
No one thinks I’m doing a good job.
That’s not true!
Please care more about your own health.
But if I don’t do something, I feel like I’ll lose my mind.
It’s all my fault!
Reiya-san, please don’t blame yourself like that.
Would you... let me cry... for a bit?
Reiya-san?
Otoha. I want...
What was that?
My beloved girl is with another man?
Um... Reiya-san?
I'm so sorry!
I think I'm losing my mind.
Me too! I’m sorry.
It was sudden so I was surprised...
So would you have been okay with it if it hadn’t been sudden?
Well...
We’re only engaged as far as our parents are concerned.
You don’t need to humor them.
Reiya-san...
But, I want to be with you more.
I want to know you, Otoha.
I don’t think it’s because you’ve been nice to me,
but I think I do have feelings for you.
I know you love someone else.
Reiya-san...
Sorry.
I just... wanted you to know how I felt.
Yes...
Thank you.
I really am honored that you feel that way.
But, like you said, I love someone else.
So I cannot return your feelings.
I know that.
So that’s why I plan to wait for you.
But...
Or maybe there’s no possibility at all?
No... I’m not sure...
You don’t need to look so guilty.
Whether or not I wait for you is my own choice.
Okay.
What I want you to remember is that I’m grateful to you.
So thank you, Otoha.
Okay.
I think it’s almost dinner time.
That’s right.
To still be hungry at a time like this... humans sure are ridiculous creatures.
But it’s because it’s a time like this that we need to keep strong.
Otoha, you sure are strong.
When we met, you were so weak. I thought you were always about to cry.
Oh, please, Reiya-san!
Reiya loves Otoha?
Yukito-kun...
Do you remember the promise we made as kids?
But I also love Otoha...
No...
Wh-What did you say?
I can’t do that!
Then maybe I’ll show this to everyone.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Then not only will you lose face, but so will your darling little brother.
For having a slut for a sister.
You’re insane.
No...
Everyone, please listen.
The footbridge is almost repaired.
We’ll be able to leave here soon.
What a relief, Yukito-kun.
Yukito-kun?
Is something wrong?
No... It’s nothing.
I’m sorry.
If you’ll excuse me for a moment.
I think the stress is finally catching up to me.
I’ll go check on her. That’s what I’m here for, after all.
Oh no.
Not so...
What’s wrong? Are you okay?
Stop creeping me out.
I’m just concerned about you.
What’s with that attitude?
You must be soaking wet.
You may act strong, but you’re just a woman after all.
No.
No... not like this...
You know yourself better now, don’t you?
We can’t have you cumming out here.
Go to my room.
What the hell...
What the hell d’you mean what the hell?
Are you in a position to talk to me like that?
Jeez.
Oh, so it’s your little brother.
Were you worried about her?
Yeah.
She’s okay. It’s just anemia.
Right?
Y-Yes.
I’ll be fine.
Yukito...
Okay. Then I’ll go back to dinner.
What a gullible little brother you have.
If you don’t want him to find out, do as I say.
Come in.
Let’s start the examination.
Strip off.
Your underwear and everything.
Wha...
Hurry it up. You want them to find out?
Fine, I get it.
Now, masturbate on my bed.
H-Huh?
N-No way!
I won’t...
Stop joking around.
Is this your first time seeing a dick?
What a cute reaction.
If you can’t masturbate, I’ll have you suck me off.
Fine, I’ll do it.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
You’re stupider than you look.
You pig!
And what does that make you? Falling for this pig’s trap?
I’ll give you your diary back.
But whether or not this picture stays private is up to you.
Just do it yourself.
Stick out your tongue.
Lick it.
It stinks.
No way.
Do I really have to lick it?
Are you playing me for a fool?
Lick it!
Why am I sucking his...?
If you don’t keep it up, things will get even worse.
Hey, fine, I get it!
Get the shaft too.
I-It’s so dirty. This is so gross!
Is this enough?
Next, bury it.
Eh?!
Bury it in those huge tits of yours!
You don’t even know how to titty fuck?
You certainly have the equipment.
So big.
Very good. Move it like that.
Was the toy not enough for you?
Maybe you’re all wet from my dick.
What’re you saying? No way is that tr-
Keep sucking. I like being sucked while titty-fucking.
I can’t breathe. I can’t breathe!
Very good. You know how to suck my dick now.
Very nice.
I can’t breathe. This is so gross.
No... no...
Yukito...
Reiya-san, you need to rest.
I don’t want you to faint.
Sorry. I'm just a bit shaky.
It’s really nothing.
But it is something.
If you faint, then Honoka-san’s hard work will have been in vain.
I see.
You’re right.
Sorry.
Otoha, you’re right.
Otoha...
What?
What are you doing?
No!
Ew, gross.
Please, stop it.
I won’t stop it.
You’re gonna keep this up.
No way, no way!
No. I don’t want to!
Stay still!
No, no!
It’s going in.
Hey, it’s going in.
Stop it!
It will only go in if you move.
No. I would never... I can’t...
It’s just a line.
Say it quick.
“Your dick rubbing against my pussy feels so good”.
“When I feel your dick push against my pussy’s entrance my pussy tingles”.
I know women like this sort of thing.
“Your hard cock is rubbing against my pussy"...
“Making it a slippery wet pussy”.
“My pussy is throbbing”.
“Your dick is touching my clit”.
"No".
“It feels so good”.
Suzuka’s... dirty pussy... is about to cum.
No way. No!
My body is hot.
“Please, sir"...
“Bury your... big cock in my... pussy, please”.
I got all of that on tape, too, Suzuka!
Look over there.
Oh no!
You wouldn’t want the others to see that.
Please, please stop filming!
Please!
Just give up.
A virgin is in no position to bargain.
No! I’m begging you... I’m begging you!
Then I guess it’s time to go.
That hurts!
Too big for a virgin, eh?
Well, you’ll get used to it.
That hurts... that hurts!
That hurts... stop it.
So this is your uterus?
I’m already all the way inside?
You’re small.
No... that hurts... I’ll die!
Stop... it.
No, no!
Be quiet.
Do you want the others to find out?
Shall I cum inside the first time, Suzuka?
No, no, not that!
I don’t want a baby!
No! No! No!
No!
Please, please, I’m begging you.
I’ll let you have your way every other time, Suzuka.
No... no...
No...
No!
No way!
I ended up cumming inside.
This means you belong to me now.
You're my slave.
Don’t forget it, Suzuka.
Nee-san was... treated like that?
I... I wanted Nee-san to...
I wanted Nee-san to get fucked even harder.
What the hell is wrong with me?
No, Reiya-san.
Reiya-san, I’m embarrassed.
No, it really suits you, Otoha.
Don’t say that...
I think that sort of swimsuit is most suitable on a girl like you.
Oh, Reiya-san.
Please stop saying such embarrassing things.
Maybe it’s a bit much to say now that you know I love you.
And I've noticed you’ve changed the way you speak to me.
Maybe it’s a sign that we’ve grown closer.
Reiya-san...
That’s the second time we’ve kissed.
Second time?
It can’t be.
When did they...
I...
What?
What did I just think?
Did I want to see it?
Did I want to see the girl I love kiss someone else?
What’s wrong with me?
What am I... What am I...
No... Reiya-san...
No...
Reiya-san... oh...