I want Daisuke...
It's like there's a whirlpool inside my body.
Kiriya Hakushakuke no
Roku Shimai
The Six Sisters of the Noble Kiriya Family
What is this… what?
Well then, let us conduct the ceremony.
Go… you really are good.
Even with your brains fucked, and your emotions sucked out,
you're still alive.
From now on, you'll stay with our family and work for us.
Now, let me have your blood.
What a nice flavor.
I feel it flowing through my body.
Now, continue.
Kurenai Onee-sama.
Blood…
Delicious.
Shino Onee-chan.
Your dick is so hard.
I'll put your dick in now.
This feels great… how's it for you?
My pussy feels great… too…
Your dick is throbbing inside me.
Onee-chan?
Do you wish to ejaculate?
Then you may.
Ejaculate lots.
Daisuke-kun, you don’t need to do any of the work.
Don’t move.
Just feel pleasure.
What a troublesome human you are.
This hardness is nice.
I feel… so good.
It’s so hard.
His precum is leaking out.
Let me lick it too.
What the? What the?
Good morning, Daisuke.
What are you two doing?
What are we doing? We were thinking we’d receive your first offering of the morning.
Sorry for scaring you yesterday.
So yesterday… wasn’t a dream?
Let's continue this conversation while having fun.
More… drink my juice more.
Daisuke, your perverted dick is mine!
It’s spreading my insides apart!
It’s so thick and hot!
But you girls seduce men and then suck their blood.
It’s almost like you’re…
Almost like we’re…
Vampires, right?
Yes!
Yes, Kiriya is an ancient family of vampires.
Harder… Suck harder!
But when you first met me…
I am special.
It’s rubbing inside of me!
I don’t participate in all the family ceremonies with the tekigosha.
The “tekigosha”?
That’s you, Daisuke.
I’m cumming... cumming!
Now, suck us!
But which one first?
Either is fine, just hurry!
We vampires can’t suck just anyone’s blood.
If we drink incompatible blood, we die.
But a man who has blood that suits us and semen that will grant us with great descendants...
We call these men “tekigosha”.
My nipples are rubbing…
So Go was…
My nipples!
That man was only good enough for his blood.
So… Daisuke… you are the tekigosha that is worthy to fuck us.
Give me some too.
It’s going in. Daisuke’s dick is going so deep!
Who the hell are you?
I am a member of a certain organization.
We have been spying on vampires.
Is that all?
Isn’t there something different about you two?
I have a man overseas.
Doesn’t he look a little like Daisuke?
You’re probably right.
So… Daisuke… I’m almost...
Me too.
Then cum!
Cum in my pussy.
I’m cumming!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I’m so happy. Hurry.
Yes…
I’m cumming… cumming… I’m cumming!
Before a tekigosha can take a Kiriya female as his bride, there is one more ceremony he must pass.
The contract ceremony.
Contract?
The man who becomes a vampire’s husband must drink from the woman and then she drinks from him.
Although, the one who is sucked becomes weaker.
Well, it feels good. So it can’t be helped.
Is the maid making the bed right now?
Daisuke-san! Won’t you notice me?
That's why I am doing this indecent thing.
I know this is wrong, but it feels good.
Daisuke-san!
Daisuke-san… your semen… please let me have it.
I want your baby.
Daisuke-san, I’m cumming!
I’m cumming… cum…
I’m cumming in Daisuke-san’s room!
Daisuke-san…
Daisuke-san...
Um...
Daisuke-san… I…
I…
Sumire-chan, you are also a daughter of Kiriya… correct?
Yes.
Not so…
Don’t lick so much… please…
Sumire-chan, I’m going in.
Okay.
Please do.
This is my first time. I’ll give you my virginity.
Daisuke-san!
Are you okay, Sumire-chan?
Yes.
Please… move, Daisuke-san.
Are you sure?
Yes.
My pussy wants to make you happy.
Daisuke-san, your dick is so hard… so thick, you’re ripping my pussy apart.
So deep… it’s thrusting so deep.
Daisuke-san, your dick is dancing around… dancing around so deep in my pussy.
Daisuke-san… harder…
Fuck me harder and feel even better.
Then I will.
I’m… okay… with it.
Daisuke-san.
I… I’m floating…
Daiuske-san, Daisuke-san, Daisuke-san.
Then I’m… about to cum…
Daisuke-san, your cum, please let me have it.
Hurry, it’s coming faster.
I’m cumming, Sumire-chan.
My insides are hot.
The heat from your semen – I can feel it.
Daisuke-san…
I…
I’m happy you were my first.
Sumire-chan.
Daisuke-san…
Hey, Kurenai!
What are you doing?
You want sunlight? You must be losing your mind!
Shut up. Leave me alone!
You think I can?
Aren’t you prepared to be a vampire?
Daisuke… how do you know?
Botan and Ryudan told me.
I saw yesterday, too.
You can’t keep it a secret.
Let me see your arm.
I’ll get some medicine from Aya.
Wait. I already have medicine.
I’ll do it myself.
Fine. Jeez, you’re a crazy girl.
Dropping a vase on me out of nowhere.
Well, Daisuke, you were drooling over Ryuda.
No I wasn’t.
Yes you were!
No I wasn’t!
Ryuda only gave me advice about vampires.
She was helping me.
Daisuke, aren’t you scared of me?
Yesterday, I’ll admit I was.
But I also thought you were beautiful.
Strange, isn’t it?
But it’s true.
I’m attracted to you vampire-girls.
Especially to you, Kurenai.
What’re you saying?
I’m a monster!
The prettiest rose has thorns.
So it wouldn’t be unusual for a beautiful woman to have fangs.
You and your sweet talk…
We talked before, right?
About when you were here for only one night.
Yeah.
While I was playing with Sumire,
you went to bed with Fujino Nee-sama.
The next day, you were taken away to the orphanage.
Sumire and I quietly watched you leave.
That day, you noticed us and you smiled and waved.
Seeing you smiling in the sunlight, waving,
I still remember your face then.
So even after you went far away, I’ve been wanting to be in the sun like you.
Even if mother and Aya scold me, I go out into the sun – I’ve built up a tolerance for it.
But you see…
The truth is, I want to be under the even brighter sun, walking by your side.
I want to walk beneath the sun with you, my beloved Daisuke!
Kurenai.
Daisuke.
Don’t look… at me like that.
You’re pretty, Kurenai.
Idiot.
Kurenai, it’s you, Kurenai.
No!
You’re so pretty.
I’m embarrassed.
Not my boobs.
Daisuke… don’t squeeze my boobs so hard.
Why?
They’re so sensitive!
My nipples…
Sucking…
Your fingers… your fingers are…
Undress me.
Okay.
I feel… embarrassed.
You’re very pretty, Kurenai.
Really?
Yes, really.
I’m so happy.
Kurenai… I… I’m almost…
I… will do anything for you, Daisuke.
So… please?
Come.
Daisuke.
I want to give my first time to you.
Then here we go.
It’s inside.
Just a bit more...
Moving…
Daisuke… let me go!
Kurenai… I can’t stop it.
It’s okay. Keep going.
I won’t stop you.
Kurenai!
Daisuke, does it feel good?
Yes. your pussy feels great.
I’m so happy. Stay inside… and cum inside, okay?
Please? Make me pregnant?
Yeah. Kurenai, I’ll fill you up with plenty of my cum.
This feels so great.
Fill me up.
Make me feel good.
I… I… Are you ready?
Almost there.
Then cum lots.
I want your cum!
I want to watch your face as we finish.
It’s rubbing.
You’re moving inside and echoing…
I’m cumming, Kurenai!
Such hot stuff is coming out.
Inside of me, your cum is spilling out, filling me up.
I can feel it.
Inside of me… your baby seed… so much… so much is inside.
Even after you know everything, you still want to participate?
Yeah.
There’s no turning back.
I know.
But it’s my decision.
I think you can change the fate of the Kiriya family.
Hey, Daisuke…
You really want to have sex here?
Yes.
You pervert.
Kurenai.
Come. Make the contract with me.
Wait!
Why?
Kurenai.
Make the contract with me.
I’ll be fine.
Don’t hold back.
No. I refuse!
If I do that, you’ll no longer be my Daisuke.
And I can’t have that!
Kurenai.
I want you, Daisuke.
Just merging with you won’t satisfy me.
My fangs and my throat are throbbing.
Because I love you, Daisuke!
But if I bite you, you won’t be yourself anymore.
So I don’t want to carry out the contract!
If you join our clan you’ll be of the dark – there will be no turning back.
You’ll never be the Daisuke who waved to me in the sun.
My dreams, your sparkle, everything will disappear.
There must be some other way.
Botan can move outside in the sunlight without losing her vampire powers.
But it’s because Botan-nee-sama is special.
That is why.
There must be some reason behind that.
And once we find it, you’ll be able to walk in the sun too.
Daisuke.
You can leave the Kiriya family as well.
Leave the Kiriya family… I’d never even considered it.
I’ll take care of you.
Daisuke.
No…
Stop… not…
Kurenai, your pussy is all wet.
That’s because your fingers feel too good.
This time I’ll make you feel good
Kurenai…
I know.
Daisuke, you like this, don’t you?
Feel even better, okay?
Kurenai...
This feels too good.
Daisuke, please…
I can’t hold back anymore.
Then let’s go.
It’s inside.
Move, Daisuke.
Roughly, okay?
Yeah.
It’s going all the way inside!
It’s hitting me so deep, my pussy is being spread apart by your dick!
My nipples...
I can’t stop… I’m sorry… sorry, Sumire!
Yes…
Daisuke, your dick.
Harder, harder.
Yeah, I’ll cum plenty into your naughty pussy.
So tight!
Kurenai… I’m almost…
Daisuke, you’re about to cum, right?
Your dick is getting bigger inside of me.
You’re gonna cum, right?
Daisuke, cum with me.
Kurenai!
It’s coming out.
Daisuke’s cum. So much is coming out.
I’m cumming. Cumming!
Let’s look for it together.
A way for you to walk beneath the sun.