W
~ Conclusion ~
Okay, it's reward time.
Now, take it!
Hello.
Dostoevsky?
Looks like difficult reading.
When I was a university student, I also challenged myself with that one.
But I got lost in the middle.
Russian literature has so many names that appear again and again-
-that I had such a difficult time keeping everyone separate.
That's the first smile I've seen from you.
You’re a rather pretty girl.
Oh, no... I'm not...
But you are.
I’ll bet your boyfriend loves to boast about you.
No... I don’t have one...
You're kidding! When you're this pretty?
If that's true, then the boys at this school really have poor taste.
But somewhere in this school there should be a boy you like, right?
There is! Tell me, what kind of person is he?
It's probably someone who likes books, right?
I see.
Well, I won't force you to speak,
but you can come talk to me anytime.
You're the type to find true romantic love,
so I'll give you some advice.
This time it's fine.
It's going into the p*ssy you love so much.
It feels so good!
I can also feel it in my p*ssy.
This...
is not much of a punishment.
I can't believe how much she can take!
This is the largest size and we got three in!
Now, birth them.
Eat it.
Do you happen to know what happened?
The secretary, Hiraishi-san, was the last person here last night.
We checked all the classrooms many times.
One man.
Whereas the women were all different people.
The more I think about it,
it has to be a student.
As the victims are all members of the school,
no one else could do this.
Moreover, as I pick at this case...
So pitiful... can't come out of depression... how could the criminal...
You haven't been coming to the library lately.
Did something happen?
I'm just busy with my after-school job.
What's your name?
Your name?
It's Midaigawa Shion.
Oh! From the well-known family.
What are you reading?
Crime and Punishment
I read it in middle school, but it was difficult.
I'm re-reading it right now.
I read that about six months ago.
It's a very deep and wonderful book, isn't it?
I liked the old you.
Bye, then.
But now you’re obsessed with getting attention and adoration from everyone…
Does it really make you that happy?
Master... and that girl!
Don't lay a hand on useless women.
Crime and Punishment
I was asked my name... What should I do?
I...
I want him.
A bibliomaniac student?
Exactly. It would be great if you could remember a name...
All right.
Strange.
Apart from the people the librarian told me about,
there's this name stamped here.
Mutsuki Jouji.
Sister, I heard there was something you want to tell me. What was it?
The student congress president, Shiina Mizuho-san,
wants you to become one of our group.
To make our Master the ruler of this school, you can help.
Yes!
Next stage.
This is the best! I want more!
More, please be rougher!
I beg you!
Stop pestering me.
Have you forgotten that you are my slave?
I'm sorry, Master.
It was my fault. I was impertinent.
The people I hate most are those who try to score points.
To change that kind of attitude,
we have to purify the body.
Put it in.
This is one part of a larger ceremony.
You must surmount this or else.
No!
No, you say?
No, I mean, thank you very much.
Push it all out.
Don't look!
Here, your reward.
Who will be the next sacrifice?
Such a lovely smile...
He can't possibly be related to the incidents.
I wonder if he's looking at the same starry sky?
I wish that I could have the same conversation with him about books,
That I had with Ichijou-sensei.
Why am I such an idiot?
What do you plan to do with me?
Do you honestly think you’ll get away with this?
Sensei, you're the one at fault.
You were sniffing around me.
You're behind all of this!
I thought you had the power of a magic circle, but that was a lie.
You and everyone are merely under someone else’s hypnosis!
Midaigawa.
The reason why everyone adores you now-
-is because they finally came to see how wonderful you are.
It's the true power that was sleeping inside of you.