W
Love Bitch.
Chisato-san is my senior in the university.
She's kind and everyone adores her.
Sato-kun.
I really love Chisato-san.
But I can't seem to reveal my true feelings to Chisato-san.
Quickly go inside, Chisato. Don't take too long.
Yes.
Chisato.
I really want to fuck you now.
Anyways, why don't you strip?
Eh!?
I just told you, strip. I want you to.
B-But...
Didn't you hear what I said? Strip.
Yes.
Heh?!
Come now, open your hole wider!
B-But, in this kind of place...
You're such a noisy bitch!
Hey, hey. You said you didn't want it, but your pussy's
already drenched.
Your pussy sucks my penis too easily without foreplay.
Chisato-san, what are you...
No, you can't!
You're getting excited in such a place.
You're a pervert, after all.
Someone might find us here having sex like this.
No way!
But I'm sure you wouldn't mind having everyone in school see you like this.
I want everyone to know their lovely Chisato Senpai is
a perverted, penis loving woman.
No!
You can't.
You can't!
I can't believe that... That Chisato-san is...
No...
Did Chisato-san just look at me?
It feels good.
More...
More!
Oh?
With your vulgar body, you're trying to grab every man's attention!
If... If you're doing it that hard...
When I look at you, I just want to thrust in and out, ya know?
Cumming...
No!
I'm cumming!
With you in this kind of state, I'll head back first.
Chisato-san.
But I've got something to deal with first.
I know you're in there, Sato.
I know you've been hiding in there this whole time.
You feel strongly for Chisato, right?
I've noticed you're always staring at Chisato.
That's make me sick, ya know?!
Well... I'll forgive you this one time, since your presence
made Chisato and I excited.
But let me tell you; after I get myself drunk, I'm going to fuck Chisato all night.
You can go and imagine that tonight while you masturbate.
Well, you know Chisato is my woman, after all,
so it's up to me to satisfy her.
I feel sorry for you, Sato.
Sato-kun.
Heh!?
I'm sorry.
You perverted woman. You dare look at someone other than me!?
Although I'm screwing you everyday, is a perverted woman like you still not getting enough attention!?
I-It's not like that!
You were excited while Sato was watching earlier, right?
N-No!
N-No...
I wasn't excited...
I doubt that! I mean, with breasts like these...
How much attention do you need from other men?
Please don't do it so hard.
Huh!? But it won't be enough if I don't do it this hard, right?
I-It's not...
Or is it just that you want to attract attention from other men with this pussy?
No!
You, you can't!
You're drolling and screaming at the same time.
But I'm sure you really want it since your pussy's
getting tighter and tighter around my dick.
M-My body's doing that by itself...
Hm?
Yo.
No.
Chisato is the kind of woman who'll do whatever I ask.
Tonight, I asked some friends to come and fuck Chisato.
Chisato, you're such a perverted woman!
She's having sex with other men...
It excites me to hear her voice resound like this within the hotel room.
Chisato, is it possible you feel me even without my penis throbbing inside of you?
I-It's not like that!
Stop.
Chisato is a lot like a bitch who can't stop waiving its tail for its master.
This can no longer be a joke.
Chisato-san, you get excited every time I draw on your body.
Should I draw something even more perverted than before?
P-Please... Don't draw anything more.
I-I can't...
No... I'm going to cum again.
I'm cumming inside Chisato-san's tight pussy.
T-There's...
...so much...
...hot juice inside me.
I just remembered something good, Chisato!
Taking pictures!
No!
I'll let Sato stare at this, rather than stare upfront.
I'm sure he'll be ecstatic over these.
That he can masturbate to these pictures.
Sato-kun would do that?
You're also happy about that, right?
T-That's not true!
Your pussy's become sloppier than usual.
Geez... You're such a slutty woman!
You're such...!
Chisato-san is making an unsatisfied face.
If you want more from us, why don't ask for more?
This woman...
...is a boring slut who'll listen to everything I say.
~One Month Later~
It appears I've been dumped.
S-Sato-kun?
Though I probably shouldn't let you see this...
Huh!?
This is what he really thinks of you.
You can see Chisato's ass being fucked from the rear!
Today I've sent you a picture of cum spilling out of her.
I'll let you have this woman, Sato. I've gotten pretty tired of her anyways.
He's so cruel to you, Chisato-san.
It makes me mad that you're always in pain because of his demands.
Sorry.
Eh?
I-I'm...
I'm the one who's at fault.
Ch-Chisato-san?
I'm a boring woman. Everyone gets tired of me eventually.
It's not that man's fault.
W-What are you saying, Chisato-san?
There's a limit to your kindness.
He can't help it, s-since it's my fault after all.
What are you saying?
Eh?
I don't understand that at all!
L-Long ago, I was just like you!
But, there's always someone by your side.
That painful... Painful! Painful!
Sato-kun!?
I'm sorry.
I just...
What should I do then?
Eh?
What should I do to fix everything?
I'm scum to make Chisato-san do something like this.
No... Don't think that. I actually feel happy about this.
If I can relieve your pain with my slutty body...
You can use it as much as you like.
And then... Sato-kun.
Have you masturbated to me?
Eh?
You've seen me doing it before.
And you also saw my perverted body in those photographs.
That's why, Sato-kun...
I was... I was wondering if you've masturbated to the thought of me.
That day.
You saw me being screwed at Izayaka-san's place.
You know, I've thought of you while being screwed before.
I don't know why I become so excited from such thoughts.
Sato-kun, have you masturbated to me?
I have!
I've masturbated to you over a hundred times!
I'm sure everyone has.
Though... I've liked you even before.
But I couldn't do anything about it.
I can't go on doing this myself!
It was too hard not masturbating to those pictures
since I knew they'd still be there regardless.
I'm so sorry, Sato-kun.
I didn't know you had those feelings.
I'm sure you're still hurting because of me, right?
I'm sorry.
That's why...
That's right. It's all Chisato-san's fault.
You've hurt me!
Chisato-san.
T-That place.
You can't!
You can't lick something like that.
If you do that... I'm going to...
Cum— I'm cumming!
S-Sato-kun, everything's my fault.
That's why I want you to punish me more.
I should atone for all your woes.
P-Please... Sato-kun.
Make me... Make me cum!
Sato-kun!
I'll make you take responsibility for everything!
I'm so sorry!
Good...
It's so hard!
With this hole.
With this hole!
I-I'm sorry, Sato-kun.
It ended up happening like this.
Let's forget about that other man.
Eh?
From now on, I'll take any kindness Chisato has to offer.
That's alright with you, isn't it?
Y-Yes.
I've found another.