SubDESU-H.net
What?
L-Let's go back home now, okay?
W
It's going to be summer soon.
Eh?!
W-What is it?
W-Well...
Is it really okay?
I don't really mind...
It's wet...
Are you are really okay with this?
It's going to dry up...
Is it really okay?
Ow... Ouch!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
I'd like to kiss you.
What is it?
It... It's nothing.
Such a beautiful sunset.
Her name is Aoba Chinatsu.
We're currently boyfriend-girlfriend.
Hi, I'll be sitting next to you. I'm Sahara Satoshi.
Let's get on well together!
Sure.
Did I do anything to upset her?
My first impression was a disaster.
Hey, Aoba-san.
Even though...
I tried talking to her to get closer to her.
Excuse me... could you please show me your textbook?
Thanks.
I eventually got used to it.
What did you just say?
I said...
Will you go out with me?
So what is it?
Do you not want to?
N-No, it's not that.
One day, she suddenly asked ME out.
Aoba-san...
She's gotten so good at kissing.
What is it?
It... It's nothing.
It's so wet...
Um...
If you don't want to, then...
Don't you like it?
No, I'm really happy!
Then it's fine, isn't it?
Oh, crap...
Are you okay?
I'm putting it in now, okay?
Aoba-san...
I... I love you.
It's been a little while since we started dating, but...
I have yet to see her smiling face.
In actual fact...
She kinda...
...seems to be looking more and more pissed off lately.
N-No, it's nothing...
Even though she normally doesn't look very upbeat...
But if she makes that kind of face then I'm obviously going to get worried.
Does she really like me?
What if our relationship isn't what she thought it would be like,
but she thinks that since she asked me out that she can't break up with me?
What if it's something like that?
This is bad...
That really seems like a possibility...
Hey... Hey...!
Wh-What?
We're already at my house...
Ah, I see. I'll see you tomorrow then.
Hey...
Do you wanna come in?
Um, was it Chiyaki-chan?
What's the matter?
So you're the reason why Onee-chan is so happy these days.
Does your sister smile at home?
Nope. But you know how she makes an angry face and her forehead wrinkles up?
These subs were done by SubDESU-H.net. These ungrateful assholes just stole our subs.
That's because she's trying to keep herself from laughing or looking happy.
Actually, the happier she is, the angrier she looks.
Onee-san gets embarrassed really easily.
So that's what it is...
So she was happy those times...
Yup!
By the way, did your sister go out?
She had a doctor's appointment today.
I see.
So she really was happy.
But... looking angrier the happier she gets...?
There's limit to how shy you can get...
Wh-What are you staring at?
So that means...
Up until now she just seemed mad, but in reality she was happy?
Is it true?
What are you doing all of a sudden?
I thought I would continue where we left off...
Did you not want to?
I don't really care...
She isn't actually angry now, right? Probably not...
Your boobs look so beautiful.
They're just... too big...
She's happy now, right?
No... it's not just the size, I think the shape is good too.
Is it okay to keep going?
Besides... they're heavy and... fluffy and... warm and...
No... stop...
This feeling of it just being stuck to my hand... is the best!
I really like them!
Ah!
Her face looks a bit more relaxed now...
Nope. But you know how she makes an angry face and her forehead wrinkles up?
That's because she's trying to keep herself from laughing or looking happy.
Actually, the happier she is, the angrier she looks.
Onee-chan gets embarrassed really easily.
I didn't really notice it up until now, but come to think of it...
N-No...
Your horny face looks really cute, Chinatsu...
No...
Don't say weird things!
You idiot!
Y-You shouldn't hide it...
By weird... does she mean "cute"?
No... don't!
Even so
You idiot...
Wow. I want to see this expression more.
W-Wait...
Why like this?
Don't worry and just do it.
Did she return to her usual self?
No!
That expression is so cute...
Your boobs feel so good...
Don't just play with other people's breasts...
You look so cute right now...
Her face started to relax...
Look how hard your nipples are.
Your sexy moan is really cute as well.
Aoba-san...
Your mouth... feels so good!
Aoba-san!
I-I'm cumming!
Aoba-san, you look super cute.
You idiot.
I was surprised since you started sucking it so suddenly.
I thought you would be happy if I did that...
It's soaking wet...
Don't say it!
Awesome... It looks molten...
Don't stare at it!
You got this wet from giving a titjob, huh?
Shut up, idiot!
You're so cute.
Aoba-san, I'm putting it in.
Are you okay?
I might have just cum a bit.
You made such a cute face just now...
No... don't...
I-Idiot!
I'm not lying...
You're so cute...
Not that again...
No...
It's so embarrassing for you to see my face like this...
Don't say such things.
Your horny face looks super cute.
It's not weird?
R-Really?
Yeah.
I love you.
I love you even when your face is twisted in lust. I love you.
Show me more of your cute face...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I love you...