Why has it come to something like this...
But, I won't give up!
I won't give up until this place is overhauled and complete with utter discipline!
Incompetent teachers... disorderly students...
And the stupid parents who push their children here!
Strict discipline is required to preserve this prestigious school!
They're here...
I will not permit anyone who will interfere with this overhaul!
D-Don't resist!
Throw down your weapon!
To think that you brought such toys onto school grounds...
I will be confiscating them!
Shoot, shoot!
C'mon, c'mon!
Oh, now you've done it!
But it's no use!
I won't allow disorderly conduct!
Shoot, shoot!
SubDESU
-H
Presents
Kurutta
Kyoutou
What's this?!
Just be quiet and watch.
This uniform, it's-!
That's right, it's the uniform from this place, Kousei academy.
W-Why is this...?
It's too early to be surprised, Noumori-kun.
Look at this.
Principal Kasagi!
That's right.
It's Kasagi-kun, the principal of Kousei academy.
Well, ex-principal.
S-So then...
He came here before you did, and we got him to quit.
So that means that you, the vice-principal, will take his spot.
R-Right...
It's not all right!
Don't tell me that you're happy!?
O-Of course not!
This is the first pinch we've had in our academy.
If this incident leaks, it would be the end of this academy!
Do you understand?
I-I am very sorry!
Noumori-kun,
you want to do the best you can until you retire, yes?
O-Of course I do!
If there are any more deplorable incidents, your head will be next.
You will be discharged, and your retirement funds will be lost.
N-No way...
Ojii-sama! What are you shouting about?
Touko is tired of waiting.
Sorry, I forgot!
Oh, if it isn't the vice-principal.
C'mon, let's go.
Over here, hurry!
Yahoo!
Eh? You actually did it?
I can't stop him when he's like that!
Congratulations! We should celebrate!
Hey, hey! Did it feel good?
Not really.
I think it just hurt.
Ehh?!
I was so busy thinking about him that I can't really remember.
Hey, let's talk later.
It would be troublesome if a teacher were to find out.
It's fine, don't worry!
Hey! Natsuko!
Do you have a sanitary napkin?
Sorry! I use tampons! Is that okay?
It's fine! Throw it here!
Here!
Sorry, I missed!
Jeez, hitting such a thing... It's too dirty to use!
It's still in the packaging!
TL note: "Ei!" (‚¦‚¢!) is a word used to emphasize an action, similar to shouting "one, two!" during training.
Ei! Ei! Ei!
Put more power into it!
It's too early to be getting tired!
Show me some spirit!
Yes!
Ten more!
I mustn't give up.
There are students like this, after all.
I know! I should try it! I haven't done it in a while.
Animals will die if you don't feed them.
Don't the students even know that?
Oh?
Y-You're...?
I'm Sasaragi, Sasaragi Misao.
T-That's right.
Isn't this the beautiful daughter of the boss of that construction company?
Oh, I need to be polite with her...
Were you part of the animal care committee, Sasaragi-kun?
N-No, I'm not in the animal care committee,
but the food box was empty, so...
Oh! I'm impressed!
Go on in, the rabbits are waiting!
Yes!
Even though she's the daughter of a high-class family,
she's completely different from the board chairman's granddaughter!
However!
Even though Misao-kun is a good student,
the length of that short skirt is against the rules!
I suspect she's breaking other rules as well!
I must thoroughly inspect and punish her for her acts!
Sensei! I won't do it anymore!
Please, let me out of here!
Looks like you finally understand.
That's good! I'll get on with your punishment, then!
Eh?
That hurts, Sensei-!
T-That hurts!
That hurts!
I'm sorry!!
Looks like you're not yet resentful!
Then I'll...
No-!
No!!
I'll train you thoroughly!
Vice-principal...
Sensei!
Usatarou is scared since you've been too kind to him!
You're right! I'll leave you to it, then!
No! This can't go on!
It's not like I'm jealous of ex-principal Kasagi or anything!
There's no way I would want to rape my students!
This feeling...
I had forgotten it...
Even if I'm not as fit as I used to be, I should be still able to-!
Banish the evil!
You may have heard already, but principal Kasagi has resigned.
It was because he had a scandalous affair with some students.
It's an incident that may be big enough to put the school's reputation on the line!
So, we must be more strict about rules and snap some discipline into our students!
I agree!
So do I!
If we don't address this issue, it will just get worse.
For starters, we're going to do a belongings check every morning.
Unless they're cleared, they won't be allowed into the school.
But I don't think the other teachers will take this seriously...
That is why I called these three to help me out!
We will begin tomorrow!
Yes!
Good morning.
What-?! What's happening?!
I'm checking your belongings!
Didn't we announce that we'd do it?
W-Where do you think you're touching?!
Stop struggling.
If you're still, it'll end quicker.
T-That's-!
Don't move! Stay still!
You're suspicious...
You're carrying something prohibited, aren't you?
No-! I don't have anything-!
No! Give it back!
I knew you were carrying something by the way you were acting!
Cell phones are prohibited!
Hey you, what's with that bag?
That's not a school issue one!
Stay behind.
I said that I don't have anything!
No! Chinatsu-chan, give it back!
Why are you using that honorific for a teacher?
Your skirt is too short as well!
It's a breach of the rules! Stay behind!
E-Eh?!
Hitomi-sensei, this is too much!
What happened?
We have to strictly check belongings now.
Today was sudden, so I guess it can't be helped.
Be more careful in the future.
Yes...
Jeez, this is going to get annoying...
No-! Stop it!
Why are you touching me there-?!
You could be hiding something here! Eh?
No-!
Your nipples are getting hard, and you're getting wet here!
You must be-!
No way! Stop it!
You're suspicious! Stay behind!
I'll thoroughly check you later!
Next!
What's all this?
Why is this happening all of a sudden?
It's too cruel... I'm scared, Akane-chan!
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
Oh! You're coming over here!
Don't moan so seductively!
I-I wasn't-!
What are you-?! No-!
You're suspicious... You're too sensitive to be a virgin.
Stay behind!
No way-!
So, I was like...
Huh? Yeah!
I know! I get sick of it!
You mustn't ignore it!
You must go through the inspection!
Hey, vice principal! I'll tell Touko-sama! Now get out of my way!
Trying to blackmail me...
I can't allow such a delinquent student in!
Cell phone! Piercing! Manicure! Make-up!
They're all breaches of the rules!!
Why are you so bitchy all of a sudden today?
I know!
Vice principal, you autocrat!
T-This isn't good...
Be quiet!
What's with that short skirt?!
If you like them so short, then you're better off not even wearing them!
Take them off!
Ehh?!
I'm not convinced!
Why is it just me?
Hey! That girl over there is wearing them even shorter!
Make her take them off first!
That's right, that's right!
Autocrat! Autocrat! Autocrat!
This isn't good, I must do something...
Otherwise everything will go down the drain!
No!!
I won't allow disorderly conduct!
Has he gone crazy?
You're the crazy ones that are breaking the rules!!
W-What are you doing-?!
You were wearing banned underwear as well, I see.
V-Vice principal! You had better remember this!
I will remember, however...
I won't allow any disorderly conduct!
Take these off too!
It's Kiruuji-san!
It's Touko-sama!
Touko-sama will do something about this!
We're saved!
It's the board chairman's grandchild...
Touko-sama! Please teach the vice-principal a lesson!
You're up to something interesting, it seems.
Vice-principal, what's the meaning of this?
It's a belongings inspection.
I already explained it during morning assembly.
That seems to have been a while ago.
Also, you've never cared for me, so I wonder how it's going to go today?
My head will be on the line if I anger the board chairman...
B-But... I must go through with it!
That's right! I'm not doing anything wrong!
I won't allow disorderly conduct!
T-There will be no exceptions!
Oh? Then vice-principal, will you be the one checking me?
T-That will be so.
How disgraceful!
I can't wait to see her grandfather's reaction!
All seems well. Go on through.
There are some areas which you haven't checked.
Hm?
My underwear might be breaking the regulations.
Are you going to check?
Go on!
What should I do?
If I anger the board chairman, what will happen?!
Is it okay like this?
Go on!
I can't go back!
I couldn't go back, even if I wanted to!
I-I won't allow disorderly conduct!
C'mon!
I'm not the same as I was!!
Nice, clean white underwear, very good!
You pass!
I will turn a blind eye to the length of your skirt this time.
Touko-sama!
Oh! You haven't gone through inspection yet!
Eh?
We must go after Touko-sama!
I will be the one checking you two as well!
Get back over there!
What are you people doing?!
Get on with the inspection!!
The first time is the most important!
We mustn't let anyone through who's breaking the rules!
Yeah!
G-Give it back! That's Touko-sama's cell phone!
Oh? Then there's no way I can let you have it!
I must inspect the contents thoroughly...
Stop it!
Moreover...
How's this?!
No!
I knew it! This bra isn't allowed!
Now you're not breaking the rules.
Where are you off to?
Please, let me go! I'll follow the rules!
Looks like you're finally willing to follow the rules.
I'm impressed!
However, you haven't gone through inspection yet!
I won't! I won't try to escape next time!
Looks like you're finally being honest!
I should have done this from the beginning!
How's this?!
How about this?
This is a breach of the rules as well!
I won't allow disorderly conduct!
It's very upsetting to see that so many of you didn't obey the rules!
We enforce strict rules so that you can all grow up to be a responsible part of society!
For the hopes of your parents, and for the future of you, the students...
we're being strict for your own benefit!
Shut up!
Do you think you'll be let off if you cry?!
I cannot allow students to learn who is in breach of the rules!
Rip off their piercings!
Stomp on their cell phones!
And strip off their short skirts!
B-But-!
Isn't that too extreme?
No!!
Just do it!
We must re-attain our respect as teachers!
Yeah!
No, no!!
Stop! I said don't-!
Looks like you've all awoken to the true nature of teaching!
Okay! Now get them into groups and punish them accordingly!
Show no sympathy!
Yeah!
You lot have clearly breached the rule
stating that your skirt can be no more than 20cm above your knees!
Those caught breaking this rule aren't worthy of wearing skirts!
As punishment, you're going to clean this gymnasium, dressed as you are now!
Ehh?
For the people who don't do a good job, they'll do it completely naked!
Ehhh?!
I'm completely serious!
Now, who wants to get stripped naked first?
Get on with the cleaning!
The vice principal has really lost it!
I should have followed the rules!
What are you doing?!
Do it properly!
C'mon! Use both of your hands! Raise your butt a little higher!
Ouch!
Do what the vice-principal says!
Otherwise, you'll be stripped naked!
C'mon, you lot! Use both hands and do it properly!
Raise your butts!
Do you want to be stripped naked?!
Right, you've all got towels, haven't you?
You knew very well that you weren't allowed to bring in cell phones!
But, the reason you brought them in
is because you supposedly want to keep in touch with your friends!
We're going to train you to purge such naive thoughts from your head!
One! Two! One! Two!
Put more strength into it!
The ones who don't do it properly will regret it!
One! Two! One! Two!
You there!
What do you want?
Do it properly!
I am!
It doesn't look like it.
Right, take off your bloomers.
What did you say?!
I have to demonstrate what happens to delinquents like you.
What's wrong? Do you want me to pull them off instead?
You've broken the rules and you wore something like those T-back panties.
That's why you're exposed like this now!
See? Use this.
Wha-?
The knots are quite effective.
It might get interesting with those T-back panties of yours too!
Okay, start over!
One! Two! One! Two! One! Two!
Put more strength into it!
More!
Like this!
One! Two! One! Two!
This happens to the ones who don't do it properly!
Who's going next?!
C'mon! One! Two! One! Two! One! Two!
Now then, you lot, the ones who severely disobeyed the rules,
are not worthy of being taught at this school!
I won't allow disorderly conduct!
We will strictly reproach you, so that you won't even think of disobeying the rules next time!
Stop crying and shut up!
First, we're going to check whether you're virgins or not!
If you are, then you can go back to class.
For the ones who are not, we'll make sure that you regret disobeying the rules!
Teachers!
Yes!
To closely inspect each individual student,
I asked the male staff to carry out the inspection!
The female staff will assist!
Yeah!
The ones who're not virgins will be required to do "volunteer" work for us!
First, the male staff will instruct you in "private" tutoring!
You delinquents! Stand on the chairs!
Kneel down!
Now for the next position. Open your legs!
You were Misao-kun, weren't you?
Now, let's have a look!
This is embarrassing! Please don't!
I beg of you, please!
No!
No-! Stop it!
Now, let's see...
Of course, you'll insist that you're a virgin.
However, this is for the academy, so I still need to check.
W-What's this?!
The daughter of the Sasaragi family isn't a virgin?!
I'm surprised that you can come to terms with yourself with such shame!
I am a virgin!
I haven't done anything indecent!
Shut your mouth!
Ouch-!
You could just be acting! I need to check you thoroughly...
We start with here!
No!
You taste good...
Please, don't!
Not there, not-!
That's-!
It hurts!
There's no way that it hurts!
If you were a real virgin, this is what would be painful!
It hurts!!
It hurts, it hurts!
It hurts! Please, take it out!
Stop with the cheap act!
You shouldn't scream like a virgin when I'm being this gentle!
I'd rather have it done to my butt-!
Oh really? Then...
W-What are you-?
I'll send you to heaven, just as you wanted!
With my cock!
No!
Looks like everyone has finally awoken to the true nature of teaching!
All is well.
We will restore the shine of this prestigious Kousei academy!
The legend of the crazy vice-principal of Kousei academy had just started.
This is only the beginning.
The new fear, no, the new way of teaching had just begun.