Sae!
Your panties are showing!
No!!
Geez, Emito. You gave me a fright-!
It's not like this is your first act of clumsiness.
Anyway... We have a perpetrator nearby, hurry up and transform!
What?! Here?!
Of course! Hurry up!
Do I use the catch phrase and turn into that?
If you don't hurry, I'll spread your embarrassing secret!
I've made us invisible, so transform away!
S-Sure...
Twinkle Starlight!
Warm up!
SubDESU-H presents
Mahou Shoujo Sae
My, this is embarrassing every time!
Gosh! Don't cause such a nuisance to a high-ranking fairy!
Geez, rude as usual.
What did you say?!
Anyway, we gotta get going!
Wait up, Emito!
There it is!
It seems quite strong...
I don't sense very strong magical power from it, so you'll probably be fine...
Probably?!
It noticed us?
Well, I guess it will notice you since you're the bearer of a strong consciousness.
Umm, can I go home now?
What're you gonna accomplish by going home?!
You're the magical girl, aren't you?!
Get yourself together!
But it's scary...
Don't be scared!
I'm sure you'll win-!
Oh, it's coming this way!
No~! What's this?!
No~! Not this way!
Oh no! My skirt and panties melted!
Don't worry! The crack between your crotch looks goo!
That means I'm completely visible!
Not really...
Sae! Use fire!
That's right! It's a pseudo-slime type, so it should be weak to fire!
Got it!
Grenade Launcher!
What a non-magical girl type weapon...
Slime-san! Prepare yourself!
Huh?
Oh yeah, did Shouko say that I needed grenades?
Then hurry up and make some!
Hurry up, dammit!
But I've never seen a grenade before...
Then what're you gonna do?!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Then what about this?
Oh geez, anything to get rid of it...
Slime-san, I'm sorry!
Oh, that's good. The consciousness that it took is returning...
But couldn't you have done it in a more...
It all worked out, right Emito?
I wonder if I'm still tired from yesterday...
Sae-san!
You seem sleepy, did you stay up late?
Yeah, a little...
If you're troubled, talk to me anytime!
I, Nishijima Shouko, will do anything for you!
Yeah, thanks.
In the parallel universe of Eetel land, the world of magicians was separate from ours.
However, a number of magicians came to this world to suck the consciousness from humans and use it as power.
The magicians of Eetel Land
considered those who crossed the boundaries to be trespassers.
To destroy them, some were chosen to possess magical powers
to fight as magicians against the enemies.
So I, Kusunoki Sae, became the 13th magician to fight, but...
I'm not good at studying or sports, so no matter how I look at it, it seems like I'm not a suitable person...
But I have to try my best for the people who lost their consciousness!
By the way, how's your dad doing?
As usual, he's not regaining consciousness.
The cause still hasn't been determined either...
Really... I guess the magician who took Shouko's dad's consciousness has yet to be defeated...
S-Shouko! I-!
Sa-Sae-san?
Ouch~!
Sae-san! You're trying to cheering me up, right?
Eh? Um, not really-!
I'm so touched! I'm full of energy now!
So many people!
Where did they all germinate?
What are they, plants?
Even though there's an innocent girl who fights trespassers from another world right here...
Emito!
If they get all lovey dovey, I think I'll get frustrated! -By Kusunoki Sae.
Is that supposed to be my conscience talking?
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
Those girls sure are going at it!
Sa-Sae?!
S-Stop, you-!
What are you doing?!
That was my precious first kiss...
Sae?! Are you okay?
Y-You're Ruran?!
Huh?
It's been a while, Emito. Still can't use magic detection?
You're still a useless fairy, aren't you?
Do you know her?
She's one of the evil magicians.
She likes taking lewd consciousness,
and on top of that, she's a pervert who likes bullying cute girls.
Sae! Transform now!
What?! Right here?!
Hurry up and transform! I'll make sure to bully you lots!
Umm, how about we do this another day?
I'll clear everyone’s memories later!
Or do you want me to tell everyone your secret?!
Fine! Twinkle starlight warm up!
Amazing! What was that? Special effects!?
I can't believe there's some basis of which I can't understand...
Show us how you change again, slowly!
What's with this?! I'm fighting for you guys~!
Ruran-san, brace yourself!
W-What's this...?
No, my nipples are getting hard-! Down there too-!
Sae! What's wrong? Are you okay?
Hey! What did you do?!
As well as sucking her consciousness,
I used some magic that will make her nipples and clitoris throb.
Forgive me... I might overflow!
Sae...!
You perverted woman! Turn Sae back to normal!
What a noisy fly.
Emito?!
Hey! Lemme out, lemme out! Can't you hear me?! Lemme out!
Everyone! We're filming a special adult video here.
What?
And here is our main actor, Kusunoki Sae, a real maiden!
Wha-!
A virgin!
Hey~!
Also, the more people watch her,
and the more extreme the clothes she wears, the more she gets turned on like an outdoors fetishistic masochist!
No-! I'm not such a lewd girl-!
That's it, cosplay-neechan!
Take it off and show us!
Oh? She's so cute, but she's a masochist?
Filming in such places, she really must have an outdoor fetish.
So then Sae-chan, lets show these eager people your cute breasts!
W-What?!
Oh, playing dumb? What a cute fetishistic girl!
D-Don't fool around!
Oh, are you sure you can say such things?
Eh?
No!!
Emito!
No, no! Lemme go!
Emito~!
Let me go you perverted woman! Cut it out already!
Geez, you sure are a bad-mouthed fairy! For such a mouth...
What are you doin-!
It needs punishment!
Emito?!
Please! Don't do bad things to Emito!
That's up to you, Sae-chan.
Huh?
No-! Stop-!
N-No way...
Emito!!
No-!
Huh, w-what? No!
No! Stop!
No!!
How is it, Emito? That semen has some arousal benefits.
No! stop-!
No, stop!
No-! No! No-!
Oh? Looks like it's working.
Stop it! Stop it-!
No!
I'm gonna cum!
No-!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
E-Emito! Emito!
She's taking my consciousness again?!
Mmm! You're consciousness certainly is delicious!
Now, if you don't want me to play with Emito further, stand up.
Okay then, just don't do anything more to Emito...
What's this?!
It's a force shield, since it wouldn't be good if we were interrupted. Here I can bully you all I want!
Everyone! Thanks for waiting!
Now, with Kusunoki Sae, the outdoors fetishist and masochist, I shall display for you our lesbian show!
She's here!
Now then, Sae-chan...
Sae-chan! Hurry up and show us your cute breasts!
Hurry, hurry!
If you don't hurry up, Emito's gonna...
I-I understand! I understand!
It's so embarrassing~!
I knew you weren't wearing a bra! Also, your nipples are so erect!
Is being watched turning you on?
N-No! Don't say such things!
Then pull up your skirt next.
What?!
Didn't you hear me?
Pull up your skirt!
W-What are you-
Stop it-!
What's this? You're soaking already!
Stop! Don't rub me so firmly!
You're such a naughty girl to get turned on by your friend being violated.
There's no point in wearing those panties, is there? Take them off.
Take them off, Sae-chan! Show us your naughty pussy!
Take them off, Sae-chan~!
Take them off! Take them off! Take them off!
No! I don't want to! Everyone stop!
C'mon, hurry!
C'mon, Sae-chan! We can't keep the customers waiting!
No more-!
We can't see anything like that!
Pull up your skirt! Open your legs!
No way!
Oh? You're not gonna do what I say? Then...
I will! I will...
More.
More!
Thrust out your hips!
I can see it! I can see it!
Sae-chan... Your legs are so slender!
No-! Don't say such embarrassing things!
Oh~? You're this wet?
Whoa! You're so beautiful! Let's show everyone else!
Amazing! Her pink color really is beautiful!
Show Sae-chan's pussy over here too!
Stop it, no! Don't do such-!
N-Not there, don't do it like that! Don't loosen me like that!
Oh really? Then what about here?
No, no, no! No! I'll feel good...
You can't cum yet, I just thought of something good.
What?!
I'll put a spell on you so that peeing yields the same sensation as a guy ejaculating.
N-No!
Oh? You're not happy? Don't hold back and take it!
No! Stop it!!
Ru-Ruran-san, please, please let me go pee!
Oh? You're about to wet yourself already? How immodest, Sae-chan.
I-I can't hold it in! Please allow me to go p-pee! Let me pee, please!
Sure, then announce to everyone here:
I, Kusunoki Sae, am going to pee. Everyone, please watch me!
N-No way! I can't say something like that-!
Oh, then you can't.
You're so mean...
So then Sae-chan, say it!
N-No!! Forgive me!
Then say it!
I-I, Kusunoki Sae am going to pee! Everyone, please watch me!
I-It feels so good! This feeling, it's my first time, it's my first!
No... No-!
Hey, you're not done yet!
No, I can't stop!
I'll-! I'll feel funny!
C'mon Sae-chan, say you're cumming.
I-I'm c-cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!!
Sae-chan, you're such a pervert! Even with such a cute expression...
No, you're wrong! This is because of Ruran-san's magic...
Wake up! Are you fine with us starting our next show with you asleep?
Starting our next show with me asleep?
It's pretty bold of you to fall unconscious after peeing like that.
No! Forgive me!
D-Don't tell me-!
Okay then, Sae-chan! Let's all have plenty of fun together!
N-No!
N-No! I'm gonna be violated!
No!!
I found it! Your hymen is so cute!
It's gleaming inside your pussy like a diamond!
No! Don't look!
No! His cock is entering my mouth! No way! It's awful!
No!!
His cock is moving inside my mouth!
No-! Don't move it!
I might break! Don't poke me so much!
Sae-chan...
Show me, show me more of your lewd face! C'mon! Do it more!
No! How immodest! Don't stare at me with such an aroused gaze!
He's about to cum! Make sure you drink it!
It's sour and bitter!
Now Sae-chan, we're getting to the main event!
No!!
Not that-! Stop it!
Please, Ruran-san! Anything but that!
I want to keep it for someone I love...
Sae-chan! You're so cute! I'm getting more turned on!
No way!
No, stop! Don't put it inside me!
Not my first, no!
No!!
It hurts, it hurts!
No! Stop it, stop it!
No, pull it out! It hurts-! Pull it out-!
I'm being violated! I'm being raped for my first time!
Don't move-!
No!
Sae-chan, we're about to cum!
No, don't let it out! At least don't let it out inside!
I'm gonna cum, Sae-chan!
No!
No... I'll get pregnant...
No more...
I want to die...!
Sae...
Sae!
Emito?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
Moreover, I put a magical spell on you that activates if your consciousness is about to be sucked.
A magical spell?
Yes! Whenever someone takes consciousness from others, their own consciousness is exposed.
So when she's about to suck yours, you're gonna suck Ruran's instead!
Will it work?
This is our last chance.
Understood, I'll try it!
Ruran-san-!
Ru...ran-san-!
What is it, Sae-chan?
Ow!
Please... Please suck out my consciousness!
Oh, why is that?
If... If you suck it out while I cum,
I think it'll... feel really good!
Okay then, I'll make sure to suck out a lot if that is your request.
Now then, everyone! Please make Sae-chan more aroused!
Okay, Sae-chan! Cum all you want!
I-I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Now, Sae-chan! Take it out!
Bon appétit!
E-Emito! You tricked me...
Ruran-san, I won't go easy on you!
H-Hey wait! What's that strange weapon you have?
Get out of the human realm! Go back to Eetel Land!
But didn't you enjoy it too, Sae-chan?
Shall we go home?
Yep.
Maybe I won't be able to bound back...
Sae-san!
Good morning!
Good morning! Did something good happen?
Yes! My father regained consciousness!
Really?!
The doctors say that he'll be fine now!
I'm glad!
This is because of your doing, Sae!
Huh?
Since you beat Ruran, her dad's consciousness returned to him!
Oh! So my work really isn't in vain!
Sae-san... Where did you get such a flying creature?
Sh-Shouko! Can you see her?!
Yes.
She can see you?
That means... Perhaps...
That Shouko is...
Yes?
A magical girl?!