…
Anime, comics
Front desk
I came here again.
Today, I wanted to check to if something was true.
Excuse me, may I rent this?
Welcome, sir!
Thank you for being a regular customer, sir.
Would you like to take it home?
No, today… I’m just…
I’d like to watch it here.
Please pardon me.
So you'd like to use it within the shop?
Understood, sir.
In that case, I would like to suggest a maid for you.
Okay…
At this time of day, these girls are available.
Who do you prefer?
You choose this girl? I see.
Maid Box
~Private lesson of the angels~
Will this room suffice?
Y-yes.
Then please step inside.
I will call for the maid.
Until the maid comes, please wait in the room.
Master.
Th-thanks.
Wow, I didn’t know the rooms looked like this.
“Ooh-hoo-hoo-Service”…
Come in.
Welcome. Thank you for using our shop.
H-hello.
S-so you really came here.
Master.
“Master”?
Umm…
I’m a maid.
I want to address my master in the proper manner.
O-okay…
So, which service-course would you like today?
The V… V… VIP course!
I apologize, Master.
I was only hired here for outercourse and the drinks course.
Oh… really…?
But, Master…
You like maids, don’t you.
Well, I…
Maybe just a little…
Granting Master’s wishes is a maid’s job.
What happens in our shop stays in our shop.
Shibuya-san.
Special service.
Eat me for dinner, please.
Sh-Shibuya-san… You’re already wet down there…
Yes, well, Master, if you stare at me so, my heart pounds.
Master, you’re so big!
What an amazing member.
Can you see it? My slutty place.
It’s already dripping.
So amazingly rough!
I’m starting to feel strange.
Master!
Lots of nasty juices are flowing out!
Master, please look.
I actually am very naughty.
Shibuya-san… Your n-nipples…
Yes. My nipples are… just like your cock… they’re hard.
I’m sorry for being such a naughty maid.
Don’t say that!
Shibuya-san!
Master, please watch!
Being watched while I masturbate… really turns me on!
Maybe I’m… really perverted.
Oh shit! I’m about to cum.
Yes, you may.
When you want to cum, Master, let a lot of it out.
I will receive it all.
Amazing!
You had so much stored up inside.
And your cock still looks alive and well.
Then as a special service, I will finish it off.
Awesome… This feels great!
Master, what other fantasies do you have?
W-well, I…
Getting me naked, licking me all over, making me all wet…
Or forcing me into a slutty pose…
Or sucking on my nipples?
In your fantasies, I’ve probably been fucked many times.
In my mouth, my pussy, my butt…
Shibuya-san… Th-this feels great!
Really… Master?
Master, you’ve gotten thicker and hotter again.
Master, the tip of your cock is oozing with naughty juices.
N-not so rough!
I’ll c-cum again.
Master, please hold on just a bit more.
Master… perhaps it’s time to test which is better… masturbation, or the real thing?
B-but…
Please do it.
The real thing.
Master, treat me as you wish.
Master, you’ve gotten so thick!
Please, put it in.
Sh… Shibuya-san.
M-Master… does this feel good?
Between masturbation and sex, which do you prefer?
Sh-Shibuya-san… your pussy… is so tight… and wet…
If you tell me that… I’ll also get… turned on.
So awesome… so rough… Master…
Deeper… you’re hitting so deep.
All the way to my… my uterus!
I’m sorry! I can’t stop it.
Don’t worry.
I’m fine.
Ha-harder.
Fill me up more!
Master!
Today it’s special service.
Sh-Shibuya-san?
Do more to me… do whatever you want!
Harder…
Feel more ecstasy.
Your cock… fill my pussy… fill me so much! Let me give you a pussy-hug!
Squeeze my tits harder!
Shibuya-san, you’re so tight.
The intensity is making me lose my mind.
Oh, Master, you’re so…
Shibuya-san!
I… I’m almost…
Then cum.
Today it’s special… service… so inside… fill me with lots, please!
Umm… here…
I’d like to ring this up.
Yes.
Thank you for your service.
Are you finished for today?
Y-yes.
By the way, Master, try to actually watch the DVD next time.
Maid Box
One afternoon I had off,
Mizuno-senpai asked me out to the park.
S-Senpai!
Tomohisa-kun.
Did you wait long?
No, not really.
What a huge bag!
Are you going out somewhere?
I’m already going out.
I got in a fight with dad and ran away.
Wanna go?
Yeah, I’ll carry that.
Thanks.
Tomohisa-kun, you sure are sweet.
Don’t say that.
Why did you fight with your dad this time?
Our car is dying so the subject of buying a new one came up.
And then, dad said…
That this type of car was what he wanted.
He just wants to go camping with me.
Tent-dad
Barbecue-dad
Fishing-dad
I love you, Dad!
But going on a trip with dad at my age?
If it were my choice…
I’d TOTALLY choose this one.
I want to get a license and drive it, too.
Um… so… is that why you ran away?
That’s right.
My dad just doesn’t listen to me or consider my feelings.
I’d say the same about you…
Anyway.
I won’t go home today.
So Tomohisa-kun, spend lots of time with me.
Senpai.
What are we doing here?
A business district on a day off is kind of like a ghost town.
It feels very alluring, don’t you think?
S-Senpai!
This is it!
This is what I want!
Isn’t it cool?
The insides are also really pretty!
Maybe dad wouldn’t go this far for me…
I wouldn’t call it “pretty” exactly…
Sexy… maybe.
Tomohisa-kun.
Where were you looking when you said that?
Er! Well…
Very well. Come here.
You really want to do it here?
You’ve been thinking about naughty things this whole time, haven’t you?
So big.
It’s stiff as a board.
Senpai… don't go so far…
I haven’t showered yet…
I don’t mind.
I actually like this smell.
It makes me feel naughty.
S… Senpai…
I’m… almost…
Tomohisa-kun, are you in serious-mode?
Tomohisa-kun, you’re still so thick.
Let’s make sure no one notices us.
Doing it outside… makes me wonder if we’re gonna be seen… and it gets me off.
Today I feel so…
Hey, Tomohisa-kun, put it in.
I want your cock.
Senpai!
Awesome!
I… I feel like I’m going crazy!
No…
This feels too good!
It feels like your dick is slashing my soul!
Hey… Tomohisa-kun… don’t stop.
B-But…
I get more aroused this way.
Please, keep going.
Senpai!
I can’t shout out…
Guess I’m hearing things.
Tomohisa-kun… that’s not fair…
There's still more coming out?
But it… feels good.
Weekends really are deserted.
Feels like a little ghost town.
A great place for doing various things.
“Various things”?
Let’s go this way!
This turns me on… My pussy is throbbing…
Your cum is still spilling out.
Senpai, your pussy is so wet.
I can’t hold out.
Tomohisa-kun, put it in.
Tomohisa-kun, your dick is so hot.
Yes… do as you wish.
Fill me deep full of cum.
Senpai… don’t yell… people will hear you.
Easy for you to say…
But… I can’t help but to shout out…
It’s so rough!
A train is approaching on track 2.
Oh no!
They’ll see us!
You… I can’t stop…
They can see… The people on the train can see!
I… I’m almost… gonna cum…
Inside… You can cum inside.
So hurry… hurry!
Cum lots!
S… Senpai.
What are you going to do about sleeping tonight?
Good question.
Should I take you home?
Could you take me to a hotel instead?
Eh… H-Hotel?
I’d like to be with you more.
Today felt really good.
T… Tomohisa-kun… I…
Dad already got a hotel reserved for work.
And it’s close to school.
Th-that’s an unusual “running away from home.”
Tomohisa-kun!
Senpai?
Until dad gives in, I’m not coming home.
So Tomohisa-kun, prepare yourself.
For starters, let’s keep up the pace.