www.SubDESU-H.net
If this continues
D-Don't come near me.
Don't come near me!
Dammit!!
Thanks for your hard work, Efanatica.
Aku
no
Onna
Kan
bu
W
Chapter One
「Half Naked Drawn Sheep」
It's time for your punishment, Efanatica.
It's punishment to those who failed their missions.
This is the established rule in the Great Lunarium kingdom, right?
Put your arms above your head.
There, are you satisfied now?
As expected.
You have the shape that can only be rivaled by the executive, Diana.
Isn’t that a nice pair of breasts?
Enjoying the humiliation of a woman...
You scum!
Shut up!
It seems that you still don't know your place here.
Remove this dirty underwear of yours.
Do you know who you're talking to?
Pull down... your underwear.
I understand...
What a nice view, Efanatica.
Next, try widening that hole of yours.
Damn...
You've already humiliated me this much.
I-Isn't this enough?
Stop punishing me already.
I'm not asking for your opinion.
No way. Are you...?
You lewd sow!
You really inserted it.
Do you understand the consequences of what you just did?
I don't care at all about that.
Anyway, this is quite a nice pussy.
At least, it can be used well for sexual gratification.
Don’t make a fool out of me...
Who would ever want to be like that...?
The pussy of the demon general
is gripping me nicely here.
If it wasn't for the punishment,
the likes of you wouldn't be able to do...
You failed your mission and humiliated yourself.
What are you blabbering about when you returned miserably beaten?
It’s thick!
If you can't even become a human toilet,
then you're nothing but a bug.
Despite being a bug, you've got some interesting moans there.
Learn some shame!
D-Don’t say that...
I never intended to be like that...
You're suddenly too intense!
You're a feeble sex doll.
Just brace yourself for it.
If you do it roughly like that, I'll...
No!
Don't push in further.
Don't give me orders, you blue skinned pig girl!
It's rubbing inside me.
It's deep inside!
You should be ashamed that you get aroused by having your ass seen!
No, don't say that!
Don't thrust too deeply...
I'll be pouring my seed into your vile pussy!
Don't...
Don’t release it inside!
I'm going to be impregnated.
No, not inside...
Emblem steal!
It's flowing in me.
I got impregnated by...
... someone like Kazuma!
I-I'm going to be...
... the mother of Kazuma's child?
Yo-You've got to be kidding me...
Hey, you.
You've really done it this time, huh?
This is the first time that I've been made a fool of by someone.
You're nothing but a...
How dare you...
I would like to have that rude attitude of yours removed from now on.
I already outrank you.
Th-That crest!
I stole your Moon crest while you were still stupefied earlier.
Th-That can't be...
Then it means, the reason I failed my mission...
You betrayed me, didn't you?
You beast!
What are you talking about?
I'll tell you one thing.
You will never be able to disobey a single word from me.
Calling me out here again...
You've already toyed with my body lots of times since then.
Are you still not satisfied?
You scum!
Wh-What in the world... is this?
There's nothing to be surprised about, right?
This is your clone on Earth.
It's Efa Granada, right?
Kazuma-san!
My butt and my insides are...
Stop that!
What kind of evil taste do you have for wanting to have sex and pleasure from my fake self?
It's an almost perfect replica of you that was built based on your personal data.
A copy of myself?
Wait, I guess in terms of being docile, this one is better.
That savage woman with an unsightly skin color can't possibly be me.
The pitiful pig that derives pleasure from getting her butt raped is the real me.
What did you say?
More.
Do me roughly...
More intensely!
Stop.
I don't want anything like that!
Don't compare me to this slut who loves anal sex.
I am the same as you.
N-No...
You're not me...
You're lying.
You even love to have your weak female part dominated by men.
Why won't you accept it?
Shut up! Shut up, shut up!
I am elegant.
Prideful
a-and powerful...
But you actually hate it, right?
That unsightly bluish skin and ugly horns that you got
in exchange for obtaining great magic powers.
That's not it...
Both of us have bluish skin...
I wonder which of us is the real Efanatica...
Now, let yourself go,
Efanatica.
Now, come over here.
Amazing...
Th-This is...
Mess me up more!
For me to rape my own self...
This is crazy...
Yes!
I'm being raped by my own self.
Rape me more!
It's intense.
My two holes are going to burst!
Oh, no!
M-My hips won't stop.
I love you, Efanatica!
You... You love me?
I love myself.
Play with me more naughtily!
Why am I...?
You are me,
and I am you,
Efanatica.
The two of us are one and the same.
That's right. Once in every month we'll have sex with each other.
Is this the real me?
I'm being defiled by my very own secretions!
I'm...
I'm being peed on by my own self.
It's coming out!
You are me...
I am you...
Oh, no!
I'm cumming
in front of my subordinates
and enemies...!
Efa-sama has...
... gone crazy!
I don't want this anymore...
I'm going to thoroughly play with those explosive breasts, Diana.
No, don't look!
Even without covers, it still looks very big, Diana.
No...
Th-That part's sensitive,
so don't do it so roughly!
Aside from your breasts, your nipples are also quite large.
It's bordering on the grotesque.
Kazuma-chan, you’re terrible!
And I thought you genuinely cared for me...
Shut up. Don't cry.
From now on, you're going to be my titty fuck machine.
Titty fuck machine?
What are you planning to do?
No... Don’t!
No...
No!
Don't rub on my breasts with that!
Eww, this feels gross...
Pull it out quickly!
Stop!
Don't play with my breasts any more.
This is terrible!
Diana isn't an object or a machine!
What?
You failed your mission, so what are you saying?
Even so, this is just too terrible!
If you continue, it'll break.
My breasts aren't made to be treated like this.
Stop fooling around, release my breasts quickly now.
Being treated like this by Kazuma-chan...
This is frustrating.
I don't want it, but I instinctively moan...
Let me go already.
The punishment doesn't stop there, Diana.
This getup is...?
Don't play dumb.
Isn't that your attire from before when you were still on Earth?
What in the world are you planning?
The Diana that loves flashy things...
Was actually this plain before.
Diana-chan is Diana-chan.
I already threw my old self away a long time ago.
No!
No, no!
Please, I beg of you. Stop this already!
I'll do anything other than this.
No.
No...
This is embarrassing!
It hurts!
It hurts!!
Could this be your first time?!
Yes, what's wrong with that?
I was afraid of men when I was still on Earth.
I was able to create a new identity when I arrived on Great Lunarium, but...
... in the end, I was still afraid of them.
I gave up and thought that I'd be a virgin forever.
That's why,
even if it's only because of my punishment,
even if my partner is you,
I'm a bit glad.
I know that this is punishment, but...
But if possible, please do it more gently...
I'll try to endure the pain.
It's okay, so continue.
I've already come this far,
so let's finish this.
My insides feel like they're being ripped.
I have become a real woman now, haven't I?
Wait, don't move so roughly.
There, I think it feels good there!
I was a virgin just a few moments ago,
but I can't stop moaning...
This is sex...
And Kazuma-chan is stirring up my insides!
This is weird.
Having sex actually feels very different.
It's still a bit painful,
but my insides are getting hot and twitchy.
No...
I'm going to cum on my first time having sex.
I'll be releasing all of it in you.
Inside? No, you can't!
I'm not safe today.
No...
B-But I can’t stop...
My mind's going blank...
Emblem steal!
Wow, Kazuma-chan's semen is flowing inside.
It's hot...
If I get pregnant during my first time...
I can’t tell this to anyone...
You can't tell what happened earlier to anyone!
You have no right to tell me that.
Oh?
The punishment's over already.
I stole your crest while you were in ecstasy.
That's not possible...
From now on, you'll have to follow me, Diana.
Kazuma-chan, you idiot!
Give me back my purity!
www.SubDESU-H.net
Kazuma-chan, are you going to do lewd things to me again?
Kazuma-chan, I feel embarrassed in this position.
What are you saying now?
Your pussy's already been exposed many times before.
But it still feels embarrassing to be seen.
Besides, my butthole is also exposed...
So this is Diana's butthole...
What are you doing?
No, let me go!
I'll take care of your "back-hole" today.
Eh? That's...
It's dirty...
I-I'll let you do the front,
so let's just forget the butt, okay?
Stop that!
It's dirty to lick that part!
No!
Kazuma-chan, you pervert!
Please, let me be already.
S-Something's entering my butthole...
Don’t insert your finger inside me.
No...
My butthole will widen.
Just think of the size of the things that come out from here usually.
A finger can't even compare, right?
Kazuma-chan, you idiot!
Why are you saying such vulgar things?!
No...!
It can't go in...
It can't go in any further!
Don't!
My butthole will become full!
This is embarrassing.
Get this over with already.
This feels gross!
You're the one who first saw my naked body,
and now you've seen that...
So I'm your first time for everything?
Then, I'll also be the first to take your anal virginity!
Something thick is entering...!
It's really too big after all.
It's going to break.
My butthole will break apart!
It's rubbing and pushing my insides upward!
No...
It hurts!
Pull it out quickly
You've had enough already, right?
My butt will break if this continues!
Why are you doing this to my butthole?
Because it feels good, that's why!
You don’t hate my butthole?
If I did, then I wouldn't have licked it, would I?
Oh, is that so?
No, it's suddenly deep in me!
No way...
My womb is being pushed from the back.
I think this is great.
So this is anal sex.
I think it feels good.
Maybe it's okay if it gets a little more intense.
If I get used to this...
No...
This can't be...
My moaning won't stop.
My pussy's insides are moving with the cock's movements.
I might just release it all.
But it still feels good!
My butt's moving on its own,
and it won't stay in one place.
P-Please...
I want plenty of your hot stuff inside me!
And now, even my butthole is taken.
While everyone is looking at me lactating and peeing...
I'm cumming!!
Kazuma-chan, are you there?
Eh? Efa-sama?!
Kazuma...
Put this big one in me already.
Efa-sama...
Why is she...
D-Don’t tease me.
I'm already doing this.
I-It...
It feels...
... really great!
Kazuma-chan, you couldn't have...
not taken only mine, but also Efa-sama's crest as well?
Let's enjoy this together, Diana.
Efa-sama's breasts and pussy are beautiful.
Kazuma, there...
That Efa-sama is now...
What's with that Kazuma?
Sucking my breasts like a baby...
No...
My body...
It's coming.
Efa-sama's breasts taste good.
Suck my breasts more!
In here, too.
Rape me more intensely...
Get inside more deeply!
Efa-sama...
There, do it more...
Diana?
W-Why?
No!
Don’t look!!
It must've felt so good that you didn’t notice, Efanatica.
Stop... Stop this already.
As the ones who lost their crests, why don't you two just enjoy yourselves?
No way. Diana lost hers, too?
How much of a scum do you plan to be?
Something's coming...
It’s coming.
Don't continue any further...
I'll really fall down...
This is how a cock really tastes...
This feeling...
Give me more of this feeling!
If you stir me up like that...
Diana's really feeling it.
Efa-sama is watching how I'm being violated.
Oh, no.
I might get used to this...
For Diana to be like this when being raped by Kazuma...
It's all because Kazuma-chan's cock feels really great!
Wow!
This feels good!
It’s thick!
Wait.
I'm about to cum.
No...
My hips won't stop.
This thick thing is...
My breasts and pussy feels great.
Kazuma-chan, thrust your cock into me more!
My body's becoming white because of Diana's giant breasts...
Now, swear loyalty to me.
As sex slaves from now on.
Yes.
Master...
www.SubDESU-H.net
Hey, you two...
It’s okay for you to release it on my breasts...
Release that hot thing with our breasts...
Efa-sama.
Yours is rubbing with mine,
and it makes a really erotic sound.
Once you get a whiff of this smell,
You won't be able to resist...
I'm at my limit already.
Oh, no.
A-Any more and...
What are you saying?
Master.
That's right...
I'll be sure to entertain you more than Efa-sama.
I shall teach you that my breasts are far greater than yours.
Master, oh my...
These idiotic girls!
Having failed with your missions altogether...
Now, I'll have to retrain you all.
It's time for the Hell Training Camp.
Training Camp?
And where would you be heading, your Highness?
That's obvious already.
If it's about training camps...
... then it's got to be the sea!