Where am I?
I got in an accident and...
A girl... in green?
Please rape me
I'm going to touch these characters...
My consciousness...
There's an electrical current flowing to my brain...
The characters in the space...
The reality in the past...
Or is this my dream?
Hallucination?
I'm going crazy.
There's something in this hospital.
Midori-san... Aoi... and Kurumi-chan...
Yanagi-sensei.... Director...
And Agisa who's already gone.
And Hinoki-chan and me...
There's someone raping Hinoki-chan.
Is it Director or me?
What's with this hospital!?
Translated by SubDesu-H
The Forbidden Ward
Mom...?
No... a doll?
Good morning.
Eh?
I'm nurse Kasuga Midori, Ogi Takumi-sama.
Uhm... How do you feel?
Where... am I?
We're in the hospital.
Hospital!?
I see.
I got in an accident...
Uhm... Who's that girl?
It's Hinoki-san.
She's also a patient receiving medical treatment in this hospital.
Uhm... Why is she in my room?
It's an order from the Director...
You're Ogi Takumi right?
Or am I mistaken?
Yes I am...
She's the family doctor, Yanagi Hiroko.
Your hearing seems stable.
As I checked the chart,
there's no need for me to examine you.
Then why am I... here?
Seems you don't have the subjective symptoms.
Sense, attentiveness - deviated, and language.
Seems he has some injuries on those.
Uhm...
Introverted and fear from self-assertion.
Weak will and split quality is defensive.
Mild case of anxiety.
This is the symptom from first check.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Takumi-sama, she is...
I'm Aoi, Orihara Aoi.
Oh... ok...
Where are you looking at?
What color is this?
It's yellow.
How many is this?
Two...
Do you feel something weird?
Why...?
Look at this...
It's not even an inborn disease.
This disorder may be a serious one.
That's why I'm hospitalized here...
That's just one of the trivial symptoms.
That's all for the diagnosis.
Midori, bring Hinoki.
Yes.
How long are you gonna lay there?
I'm going to clean up so get out of the bed!
I understand... ouch!
Will it rain?
Kurumi doesn't like rain.
The fairies in the forest will become happy when it rains.
Can I see them?
The fairies?
You use your eyes to see the voice of the fairies.
Can I see them with my eyes?
Oh! It's the new comer, onii-chan!
Hello, I'm Ogi Takumi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kurumi.
He's sensei.
Nice to meet you.
Wow, you really have different colors of eyes.
Do you have poor eyesight?
It seems not.
Hey onii-chan, can you see the voices of the fairies?
Eh?
Please come play in my room later.
It's a promise!
Room of the Director
You can't satisfy right?
You've been hospitalized in this hospital without even knowing the reason.
But we want you to receive medical treatment for a while.
But it's too sudden and I...
Does Takumi-kun see and hear the things which can't be seen or heard?
You need medical treatment for your mental state.
Yes...
I'll prescribe you a medicine if you can't sleep.
It's alright...
By the way, I want to call...
If you find the piece of the puzzle, let me know.
The piece?
Yes? Who is it?
Oh damn... so you finally came.
I promised her.
Onee-chan, who is it?
It's Takumi-oniichan.
Eh? Really? Come in!
Don't do weird things.
I wanted an Onii-chan...
What kind of Onii-chan do you like?
Uhm... Onii-chan who plays with me... eats with me...
and... and...
uhm... uhm...
Kurumi-chan? Kurumi-chan?
Shhh... Just leave her like that.
She suddenly falls unconscious and sleeps.
Will she be alright?
She'll forget it when she wakes up.
I'm full.
I can't eat anymore.
Aoi is like a mother.
That's a beautiful brooch you got there.
When I first met her, she gave me this saying be my Onee-chan.
We're siblings and matched.
We're matched so we're siblings...
It's good that you've made an Onii-chan.
You're a good girl so you can be happy, right?
We don't accept interviews.
You're hiding something right?
I said we're not doing such kind of things.
If there's nothing which makes you guilty then let me do the interview.
We don't have anything to say.
I'm not asking of you.
It's the Director.
If you make trouble here, the patients will get worried.
Do you mean that boy over there?
Takumi-sama?
Midori-san, what happened?
Amano Aki, I'm a reporter.
I'm here to do an interview about the illegal medical treatments.
Eh?
Do you know of the patient named Shiori?
What's going on here?
There's nothing you can do an interview about.
Director...
Please leave here for today.
Hm?
This is... the Director and... Midori-san...
The other girl is...
Takumi-sama, what's the matter?
Oh... this...
This is a picture of my mom remarried with my dad.
She looks like Hinoki-chan.
My mother's name was also Hinoki.
But she was weak and after all she...
That's why the director was so caring about Hinoki-chan...
Yes...
Hinoki-san, Takumi-san will scrub your hair for today.
Can I leave it to you?
Hinoki-chan, uhm...
Please get along more with Hinoki-san.
His Dad also said that.
Eh? Ok...
Hinoki-chan, I'm going to touch you...
Hinoki-chan, do you feel good?
Do you feel it?
What's the matter?
I need to go.
Oh, yes... it's about Hinoki-chan...
Hinoki-kun is dead.
If she's the Hinoki-kun you recognize,then...
She's alive.
I'm referring to the Hinoki-chan who Midori-san took care of.
Which Midori-kun are you referring to?
Ah!?
You dreamed about sex?
Yes...
It's not rare for your age.
The nervous system confirmed the recovery of your body.
Your sexual desire also recovered.
Well that's for now.
But.. Hinoki-chan who I haven't met yet appeared and...
And it was...
Are you sure that was Hinoki?
You're not the one raping her and you look at it as you're the third person?
No... I mean.
It's like I'm possessing the man who's doing that.
Do you know that person?
I don't know.
But he was like Director.
Did he recognize that it was Hinoki he was raping?
About that, it was weird...
He was calling her in another name, he said... Midori.
The story is too good to be true.
Was it really your first time meeting with Hinoki?
Yes.
I have an interest in your mental shape.
Like the rage and the sexual desire,
the powerful electric current flows into the brain...
and it will be recorded in space.
According to science this information gathered will be
regenerated and analysed to be played back.
So it was you.
If he asks something, suit the conversation with him,
but don't argue with him.
What is he doing?
He's writing a thesis.
As it regenerates in the brain.
Recognizing the vision and considering one's self.
With these kind of ability...
It's Ogi Takumi is the one who has this ability.
Eh? Me?
Ohhh Takumi-kun.
I was waiting for a patient like you.
But you must be careful.
If you regenerate that much...
If you over regenerate , because of the circuit, your brain will deteriorate.
Oh ok, I'll be careful.
Let him talk as he wants to.
It's a new patient.
Welcome to my hospital.
Amano-san... why are you here?
Hello boy.
I came for a little business.
By the way, who's this?
Uhm...
I'm a doctor.
Oh what good timing.
It means I'm welcome for a 2nd time?
Then can I interview you?
Of course.
Let me announce my research.
Research?
Let me hear it briefly.
That's enough.
Mom...
An interview?
You're the person from that trouble a while ago right?
The roads are shut off because of this storm.
The car also had an engine stall.
I'm in trouble you know.
I see.
That's interesting.
Ok then, I'll be the one to talk to Director.
You're easy to deal with.
Hey! You're late.
Amano-san...
I thought of letting you suck my boobs.
You're cute...
I want to really rape you.
What's your business?
Help me with my work.
Work?
Investigating this hospital.
I want to investigate about what they're doing underground.
Why me?
I like fresh boys.
Don't tell me it was your first time?
It smells of smoke.
You say it.
I'm counting on you.
I can't sleep.
Director...
He's not around...
What? A presence...!?
A body temperature and... a smell.
You're a good girl Midori,
you're really a good girl...
Love me father
This is...
You're a good girl Midori,
you're really a good girl
Midori... You'll begin to live as Midori from now on...
If you want to be by my side.
Yes...
Please rape me.
Please gouge me...
I'm about to cum Midori...
Call me, please call me more.
Midori, I'm going to release a lot of my sperm inside you.
More and more...
I will taint you more.
Was it Midori-san now?
No way...
I dreamed about Hinoki-chan this morning and now...
It's Midori-san's...
What's really happening to me?
I need to take some medicine and sleep.
Yanagi-sensei, excuse me...
He's not here, maybe he's not around.
He's not in his bedroom too.
Where did he go?
If I remember it right, this is sensei's room.
What's this...?
This sends me chills.
Midori-san, are you here?
I can't sleep.
Is she still working?
This warm feeling is...
The effect of this medicine...
is unstable..
This girl is a virgin
The effect of this medicine...
is unstable..
The medicine is taking its effect.
It's the same as always.
Then let's start the diagnosis.
Aoi-kun.
Yes Director... Please do it.
Because of the effect of the medicine, she's unstable.
We must hurry up for the disposition.
Ok then.
The sensitiveness of the clitoris is stable.
It's so sensitive.
Maybe it's because of the medicine.
There's a lot of changes if we compared it to our first diagnosis.
Do you feel it?
It's slimy.
Into my pleat, into my pleat.
Did I want to do something like that to Aoi?
I don't know if this is an illusion or hallucination.
If this continues...
I'm really going to go crazy.
She's cute.
My breath... I can't stay here.
Midori-san.
Are you here?
Hinoki-chan?
She's wearing the same clothes at noon?
This feeling...
It's hot and vivid...
It's not only the voice...
and heart being lost.
Ugh...
uahh, arghhhh
It's not only the voice...
and heart being lost.
The thing lost from Midori is
not only her voice and heart.
The smell of her body...
The smell of her sweat...
Did she really became a doll?
Midori, Midori! Answer me!
Let me hear your voice again.
Midori, do you feel it?
Do you know it?
Then please move.
Please scream.
Midori!
You knew me for a moment, right?
Midori, Midori!!!
Midori?
Hinoki-chan... what do you mean by Midori?
This thing... I must not see them again.
I'll never see them again.
Sorry, Hinoki-chan.
Aoi!?
What?
What happened to you?
Are you half-asleep?
Do you know me?
Hm? Takumi? Oh it's Takumi.
Aoi?
Uhm... Hey...
It's Takumi.
You're useless.
Where are you going?
This wasn't put in the noon.
Is this the underground Amano-san talked about?
But, is it really the thing Amano-san said exists?
Why is this so old?
Is Aoi here also?
What's this smell?
It's like hair being burned.
What are they burning?
I feel something bad.
Is someone there?
Aoi? Are you there?
My head aches...
I feel sick.
No... I don't want to stay near this room.
What's this underground?
Smell of blood...
Smell of human's oil...
I don't like this, it's gross.
I want to vomit.
Again... It appeared again...
The smell of sweat, urine,
sperm and love juice
white breast,
white skin and soft meat
with her hot
body, she gulped
as I cumshot into her body
white breast, white skin
and soft meat
I think she gradually feels it
She still has her ego and consciousness.
I think she needs a treatment.
NO... no...
I'm going crazy.
The lights...