Maybe I won't be able to bound back...
Sae-san!
Good morning!
Good morning! Did something good happen?
Yes! My father regained consciousness!
Really?!
The doctors say that he'll be fine now!
I'm glad!
This is because of your doing, Sae!
Huh?
Since you beat Ruran, her dad's consciousness returned to him!
Oh! So my work really isn't in vain!
Sae-san... Where did you get such a flying creature?
Sh-Shouko! Can you see her?!
Yes.
She can see you?
That means... Perhaps...
That Shouko is...
Yes?
A magical girl?!
SubDESU-H presents
Mahou Shoujo Sae
Um, let me introduce you.
This is my friend, Nishijima Shouko.
She's from an extraordinarily rich family...
However, she has lots of... hobbies.
Yes! I am Nishijima Shouko, Sae-san's friend!
TL note = Bonsai is a Japanese art form using miniature trees grown in containers
My hobbies are: anime, military affairs, and I also started doing bonsai and fortune telling!
If you're going to throw away scrap metal, please talk to me first!
Oh, sure, nice to meet you.
Are the weapons you produce because of...
Yep! Shouko told me about them!
Thanks to her, it's saving us a lot of hassle, isn't it?
So it's because of her influence?!
Sae-san, who is this?
Oh, sorry. This is Emito.
She's a fairy from Eetel land, here to fight off the evil magicians...
Emito?
Although it's not as strong as yours Sae, her potential to use magic is pretty strong.
Oh, of course!
Magic, you say?
Do you want to be a magical girl too?
Do I want to become a magical girl?
Emito! Don't say it so casually...
Don't worry, like you, she looks like a good girl.
However, her hobbies are a bit odd, but...
It shouldn't be a problem!
But... It'll be bad if something happens to Shouko like what happened to me...
Well? It'll help Sae and I a lot if you would join.
Yes! Let me become one!
It has been my dream to become a magical girl since I was little.
Yes, yes! That should be the response of a normal girl!
Y-You can't, Shouko!
I can't let Shouko get involved in these things!
"These things"?
I wasn't going to talk about this, but...
I...
was raped.
Under the spell of the evil magician Ruran-san,
I was forced to masturbate in front of lots of people...
And I thought that was the end,
but the people under her spell came at me and forced me to suck their cocks...
It was my first time...
Even though I said that I didn't want it, they put it in...
Sae-san! That's enough!
Shouko?
I'll become a magical girl!
For me to not be aware that you were going through such hardships...
I can't forgive... I can't forgive myself!
Shouko...
I never knew anything...
You even saved my father!
I couldn't do anything for you!
So, so-!
So I shall become a magical girl and protect you, Sae-san!
B-But-!
I will help you, Sae-san!
I've already decided this!
Shouko, thank you...
Then it's decided.
So then, lets make it so that you can use magic.
Shouko, that's amazing.
That's so cool!
What's wrong, Emito?
This is bad. A perpetrator is coming this way.
Huh? Really? W-What should we do...?
We don't have a choice! We're gonna fight here!
But what about Shouko?
Shouko.
What's happening?
Shouko, listen carefully.
In a little while, a perpetrator will appear. They seem pretty strong.
You're not ready to fight yet, so I'll put an invisible spell on you and you can hide.
N-No way! I can fight too!
Shouko! I'm sorry, I don't think you're ready yet, so...
That's right! This will be a cake walk, so watch us!
Sae-san... Understood.
This time I'll just watch. However, if I feel that you're in danger, I'm gonna fight too!
Oh, they're here!
Kaki!!
So you were here, Emito?
Along with that young magical girl.
Baldoi! This could be bad...
From just the look of him, he seems like a pervert.
That's not all, his preference is bad behavior.
That's right! I love messing with innocent young girls!
I'm gonna have fun with you soon!
I won't lose again!
Prepare yourself, Demon-san!
I'm not a demon! Call me a magician!
Twinkle starlight! Warm up!
Take down!
Too easy!
Tsk, he's quick!
Sae! You're getting into it!
Huh? Not really...
Not bad, Kusunoki Sae.
Huh? How do you know my name?
I was watching in the sky while you were with Ruran!
Although it seems that you guys were too busy to notice me...
I must thank Ruran... Thanks to her, I got lots of material!
Sweat, tears, fluids... And virgin love juice!
Urine, red blood, and only one of them, but pubic hair as well!
He really is a pervert...
T-This isn't good... Sae, lets run.
W-Why?
If he has all that material, you're gonna easily fall for his spell!
It's too late!!
N-No way! This can't be-!
That's right! This is an anti-magic barrier specifically for Kusunoki Sae!
Now she's under my control!
Sae!
Emito! Even if it's just you, run!
Huh?
Sae!
Emito...
Now let's have plenty of fun!
They're underneath...
Wait for me!
Emito?!
W-What?
Baldoi-san, that's mean...!
It certainly is a delicately flavored consciousness! It's wonderful that you're this shameful!
P-Please, stop this...
Now, I'll have you become more shameful to deepen the taste of your consciousness!
Let's start with you playing with yourself...
Eh? Playing with myself? Do you mean masturbation?
Yes! And also-!
Everyone!
You guys, this young girl is going to play with herself!
Make sure you get a close look!
It's Sae-chan's masturbation show!
Whoa, such a stern look, you sure are bold!
H-Huh? What's up with everyone?
The guys here have had their memories altered,
so they think that you got everyone here to show yourself masturbating!
N-No way!
Hurry up and start!
You're the one who rounded us up, right?
That's right! Show us yourself masturbating!
Masturbate! Masturbate! Masturbate!
So mean...
If you don't hurry, they will be ones who can't hold back!
Since I've also weakened their senses...
Not from over your clothes!
Yeah! Show us your tits!
It's too embarrassing! No more!
It can't be helped... Looks like I have to help you.
W-What?!
How is it? Don't you feel like doing it now?
Baldoi-san, what kind of spell is it?
Stop right there!
Shouko? D-Don't come!
Huh? There was another magical girl?
You did something horrible to Sae-san, didn't you? Prepare yourself!
No! Run away, hurry!
Sae-san! Close your eyes!
Sae-san, I'm sorry.
But that should...
Oh? So you were just bluffing.
Huh?
No way! It didn't do anything?!
How foolish, attacks without magic aren't effective against magicians!
Huh?
Even if it is a bright flash, so... What shall I do?
How about you guys show me some lesbian action between magical girls?
Huh?
S-Sae-san?
Sorry Shouko, I can't hold back anymore!
Shouko...
Your breasts are great, Shouko!
No-!
Sae-san! Get ahold of yourself!
Sae-san, don't!
Shouko! Do it to me, too!
S-Sae-san, you can't-!
Please, make me feel good too! It's too much-!
What's wrong? You're not going to?
I refuse! Why would I do such a thing in front of you?!
Oh, then it can't be helped... Now...
What?!
I'll have to cheer her up with my cock...
S-Stop it!
It can't be helped! You're not going to do it!
Now then Kusunoki Sae, I'm gonna do you!
Baldoi-san... Hurry!
I'm gonna lose it-!
S-Sae-san!
Here-!
Amazing! It's so big!
N-No way-!
That's it! It's great! It's entering me! It's filling me up!
You like my cock?
Yes, yes! Your cock is great, Baldoi-san!
It's reaching my deepest spots!
N-No way!
C'mon Shouko, let's feel good together!
Sae-san-! N-Not there-!
Your cock is great! Fill me up more!
Stop it already, Sae-san! Get ahold of yourself!
It's no use!
If you do it so roughly, I'll break!
No, Sae-san! If you do that any more, I'll-!
L-Look at me, Shouko! It's amazing! This thick cock is penetrating me!
No-!
It's rubbing against me! It's reaching my uterus!
I can't hold back-!
Sae-san, stop it already, or I'll-! No!!
No, it feels so good that I might die!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum! Watch me Shouko, watch me cum!
I can't hold it in-! I'm gonna cum! No! I don't want to!
I'm gonna cum, I-I'm gonna cum-!
No, no!
I can't hold it back!!
It's filling me up in my deepest spot...
Baldoi-!
What's this? You had this much power?
Too bad it's not strong enough to defeat me,
although it seems like you took some of my magic away...
Sh-Shouko?
Sae-san, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. What happened?
You don't remember?!
Um, well, nothing after you came and something shone brightly...
It's fine if you don't remember.
More importantly, we have to defeat that guy.
Hmph! Looks like you broke my spell.
Well that's alright. While I regain my strength, play with these guys!
We can do you now, right?
We can do anything we want, right Sae-chan?
I didn't say such a thing!
Shouko-chan too?
Just once in my life I wanted her to rub me with those tits!
You guys! Cut it out-!
Looks like they're waiting on us! Let's get started!
No! Stop it everyone!
Stop this! Don't think you can get away with such-
What?! You're the ones who invited us!
C'mon? You said so!
Do you like it rough?
Oh! So that's how it is! Then I don't need to hold back-!
Stop it! Shouko!
S-Sae-san!
N-No! Don't touch me there!
Oh?! You're wet already!
I can put it in then!
N-No! Don't-!
No-! Don't put it in!
Oh?! It went in so easily!
So then you're not a virgin, Sae-chan!
You're used to it, even with your innocent looks?
N-No-! That's not-!
You're such a lewd girl, so you're seducing me, right?!
No...
No, I don't want to touch that thing-!
N-No! Don't bring it so close-!
Sae-san!
Let's have fun over here, too!
You guys...!
Not my breasts-!
Oh! You're moist already!
S-Stop it! If you continue, I'll-!
Baldoi!
Now, what shall I have you do?
How about you suck me?
Suck you?! I won't do such a thing!
Hmph! Then are you fine with me putting another spell on that other girl again?
W-What should I do?
Is it your first time with a guy?
T-That doesn't matter! Hurry up and tell me what to do!
I'll have you lick the end then put it in your mouth!
You can't do it? Here! Move your head, like this!
Amazing! Look at the size of the thing she's holding!
Are you serious about it being her first time?
Sae-san! What should I do?!
Shouko, Shouko!
Emito? Where?
I'm here, inside the birdcage.
Thank god, finally I got through.
Emito, what should I do?!
Shouko, could you create something?
Create?
Due to Baldoi's spell, Sae can't use magic. Although you should be able to!
But I'm not at that level-!
There isn't much time!
If Baldoi sucks Sae's consciousness again, she'll be fully under his command!
She'll forever be his toy!
H-His toy?
That's right! You have to help Sae!
I have to help Sae-san...?
Isn't that why you became a magical girl?
Okay, I'll try it!
N-No!!
S-Sae-san!
Hey! Quit stalling!
No! Don't touch that place! No, not there, don't fiddle with it!
Oh Sae-chan! Is this your first time doing it in the butt?
Let's try putting into her ass too! I hear that doubles are great!
Don't you mean triples?
No-! It feels unpleasant! Please don't!
I'm gonna take Sae-chan's other virginity!
I-It hurts, it hurts! Pull it out, please! Pull out your cock!
This is great!! Her ass is squeezing me!
It's painful, it feels unpleasant! No! Your whole cock is entering me!
No... Don't move...
You guys are hitting each other inside me...
Now it's triple penetration!
Hey, don't use her mouth too much! I can't hear her lustful moans!
That's not true!
No more of such a... No more!
Sae-san!
Over here!
Not there!
I'm not allowed to put it in, am I, Shouko-chan?
Then your ass is fine, right?
Of course it's not! Take your hands off of me!
That's good, we'll leave the fun of ripping her hymen for the end.
For the time being, have fun with her ass!
Alright then! Let's try putting two in!
There's no way that'll-!
How interesting! I think I'll help!
W-What's this? My ass feels tingly...
I did some preparations for your ass, now two should fit in!
Also, I made it more sensitive...
W-Why would you?!
S-Stop it! My ass isn't...!
Hey, don't you think she's ready?
Yeah, lets try it!
A-Are you guys serious?
You're actually gonna put it in?
What a rare occasion! The first insertion being with two cocks!
Ready and-!
It's in, it's in!
This is great! She's holding two at the same time!
It's painful!
I can't breathe!
I'm getting aroused from my ass!
It's tingly! It's tingling!
Looks like you're getting aroused! How about we finish up here?
Even though it's painful, my ass is getting aroused! Is it because of the spell?
My ass is-! My ass is-!
Not my ass, no, it's too arousing! I'm getting aroused!
That's it! Thrust inside me, thrust more!
Shouko, Shouko!
My ass, it's too stimulating! No!
Shouko! Get ahold of yourself! You're our only hope!
Emito...! That's right!
Create something... Create something...!
Hurry up and cum!
I'll break!
Okay I'm cumming!
I can't... No more...
I'm cumming too!
I'm gonna pour it into your intestines!
I'm cumming!!
What the?!
Take this!
What was-?!
A Claymore mine. It's been modified, so I'm sure it's effective.
Damn! You brat!
Baldoi-san, end of the road!
What?! What about the barrier-?
There is no such thing anymore!
Give up already, Baldoi!
You two, give him your best shot!
Yes!
How dare you do those things to us! This is our revenge!
Baldoi-san! Please return to Eetel Land!
Sae-san, sorry to make you wait.
Sae-san... I'll... I'll become stronger!
Thanks, Shouko.
I'll become stronger too, so I can protect you.
Sae-san...
I'll become stronger...