Takaaki...
Takaaki!
Where's the alarm?
Good morning, Koumei.
Eh, why did you have such a weird reaction?
If you're waking up beside this girl who had an indecent body...
Why didn't you get surprised, and are you feeling the maximum this morning?
Now it doesn't matter to look at your naked body.
Shocking Pink!
Part 2
W
Chouhi's Battle
What an indelicate person!
We jwust hawd twhree twimes bwefore...
If you decide to stay angry and don't eat
it will be bad for your health.
Don't you think you should put on some clothes first...?
Please tell me, what shouldn't I do?
I don't think you should stay closed within his private room...
Why don't you try to change the place and situation then?
You're a bunch of virgins, don't try to lecture me!!
What should I do to make Koumei look at me?
How to make Strategist-dono look at big sister.
You suddenly made me follow you
just how far are we gonna go?
You'll know soon enough.
This girl doesn't have any amiability within her.
Um...hey...are the three of you really sisters?
We're not related in blood, but you can call us step sisters.
Aside from that, me and Chouhi don't have any parents or siblings
we were just simply abandoned by the heavens.
Eh..I wonder if it would be a problem when I ask it?
Big sister is like a stray dog who picked us up and called us little sisters.
So big sister is kind of like someone who saved our lives
and someone we called family within ourselves.
Hm..something like that really happened...
We've arrived at our destination.
Kan..Kan'u-san...here is...
Don't you know about it? It's what we call a love hotel.
I've never stepped inside this place too, but...
Big sister is a beatiful person, but it doesn't matter how beautiful you are
If someone likes her and gets easily bored with the ordinary,
That's where I step in, and let you taste a different kind of woman.
If you're to compare it with cooking, I'm the chef who's got skill and good talent.
That's what you call a full course menu in cooking.
You can't compare it with big sister's appeal.
Strategist-dono is a really shy person!
No way, let me go!
Hey, stop it!
Just behave yourself, I'll let you have this beautiful Onee-san's virginity.
I said that I don't want to have it!
Why're you yelling like a kid in here?
You don't seem like a kid down here.
Stand still, It won't do you any better if you're like that!
How is it, does it feel good?
I just try to pretend like it's big sister, so I don't know exactly how I have to go for it.
You can try to move it, rubbing it a little...
Did you peek on us?!
Don't worry, we're sisters in mind and in body.
I worried about that!
I remember big sister putting it between her breats.
What is it, there's some fluid coming out from the tip of it.
That's right, It's like this.
It's slowly getting excited from it.
You...
Eh?
You seem a bit serious in many ways,
but you're getting turned on when it comes to this.
Even your ears are turning red, I find it very cute.
I hope you understand that I'm holding your key point down here,
I'm sure you don't want to forget that.
That's enough, I'll put it inside!
He...hey...don't put it in so roughly...
I...I'm fine...I'm used to pain.
Are...are you okay?
You're the third person who's given my body a wound.
Even though you said something like that...
I'm gonna move it.
Did you get used to the pain?
This kind of pain is nothing to me!
Then it won't matter if I do it more intensely.
What? Wait a minute!
Does it still hurt?
It hurts but...
It feels...
Somewhat strange!
Is that so, I guess Kan'u is getting excited with pain?
It's not like that.
If you're doing it that intense, then the door of my womb will be open!!
Kan'u, here I come!
Wa...wait...don't pull it out yet.
I want to be like this a little bit.
When we're connected like this...
It's something I never felt before in all of my life...
Never felt it?
It's what I call happiness.
It's peacefull...
Maybe it's because Ryuubi and Kan'u are going somewhere today.
Oh, It's you Chouhi. Don't startle me like that.
I'm sorry, but I've been told by my older sisters to look after you today.
Look after me?
You don't have to do that.
Then...Strategist-sama, It looks like my sisters give you trouble, night after night...
That's why, let me take this chance to help you with your daily life for the rest of today.
She's a good girl...
The truth is...can you stop calling me like Strategist-sama...?
Then you're not allowed to used any polite words to me,
didn't we already have like a family in here?
Thank you, Koumei Onii-chan.
Onii-chan...Onii-chan...Onii-chan...Onii-chan...Onii-chan...
So I finally became Onii-chan, maybe this is how it feels to have a little sister...
Onii-chan?
Ye...Yes?
How's the water feel?
It's..It just feels good.
Then, I'll let my self get inside as well...
Eh?
Eh? What is it?
Let me scrub your back, alright?
It's fine, I'm not kid anymore...
Here...quickly sit in here, Onii-chan.
Wait...I'll wash the front side myself.
Onii-chan's penis is getting big, isn't it?
I'm sorry...sorry...sorry...
She's my little sister...but someone like me...
Um...It's okay...
Eh?
I'll give my first time to Onii-chan.
No...No...I couldn't do that, you're like a little sister to me.
Let me give birth to a lot of Onii-chan's kids...
Moral
Moe
Is it your first kiss?
The truth is, my first time is with Ryuu-nee...
That unfaithfull woman...
But other than that, it's my first time doing it with Onii-chan...
No, you can't! If you're doing that in there, the,
It's gonna come out! It's surely gonna come out!
We're in the bathroom, so it's good to go.
Chouhi, are you okay?
Hmph...I just can't stand over you again.
Chouhi, what're you doing suddenly?
No...no...I'm Yokutoku, I'm another Chouhi inside her body.
No...another personality has come out...
It's because Chouhi has been through many kinds of problems when she was a little girl,
so it didn't matter if one or two personalities comes out at that time.
The other personality rarely came out when I started to live with my sisters...
It's because Onii-chan is being a pervert, so I had to come out.
There's only one result when I come out, I'll make you die instantly!
Why's that?!
That's because your penis is getting big from the touch of your little sister,
so that would make you a useless weirdo.
There's no way I would let you live, isn't that right?
I don't have any comeback words for that...
Is it that you really want it?
You want to taste the virginity of this little girl, and let the sperm inside of it?
No way, It's not that I want to do that anyway...
You're not really honest, are you?
Then how 'bout this?
If you make my virginity come out, the I'll let you release it.
So I don't have much choice in here...
Or somehow, you don't have any confidence with your penis?
You're being arrogant, my little sister!
If you're not going to make me come out, I'm gonna kill you, okay?
It's coming inside!!
It...It hurts...Onii-chan...
Eh, It's not Youkutoku?!
Eh?! It's coming inside! Onii-chan's penis coming inside!!
Onii-chan, did I just lose consciousness?
Yokutoku, you're pulling out in the time like this?!
Sorry, I'm gonna pull it out right now.
No...don't do that...I'm okay with it...
Please continue like this 'till the end of it.
Please...Onii-chan...
Chouhi...
Onii-chan...
It's amazing!
Onii-chan, even though it's my first time...
It feels...so good...
I'm sorry for being a perverted little girl.
Please don't hate me, Onii-chan!
There's no way I would hate my cute and perverted little sister for being like this.
You're unbelievable, Onii-chan.
Yo..Yokutoku?!
You're cumming inside for the first time of this virgin.
Should I just let you die?
What should I do then?
I'm back!
What is this? The enemy attack or is that some kind of play?
Please...help...me...
I like you...Onii-chan...
Hm...is Yokutoku coming out?
Do you know about that girl?
Somehow, It comes out when the battle starts as well.
Like the battle when we met the first time.
Even though my combat power is higher than her, Yokutoku is a skilled assassin.
Just when I saw her satisfied sleeping face.
She's really take a liking with you, Strategist-dono.