Now I will explain the rules.
The goal of this game is to open the locked doors with these keys to escape.
The players each have their own key that they must defend.
The keys that are to be used in the keyholes are hidden in boxes.
The "Opener" must choose their keys, choose the keyholes, and open the correct doors.
The correct doors chosen will give either an X or Y answer.
Those with an XX answer will unlock.
Those boys who wish to get keys from the boxes must go to the female players…
From the mouth, vagina, breasts, and buttocks.
Please use these four venues.
If you refuse to play this game or go against the rules,
The game will be over.
This isn’t funny!
Death… “Game over”
Ten minutes earlier
I will now check the players.
Lock Kankei Academy, Class 2-B.
Tadato Keisuke
Also from Class 2-B: Ando Miyako
Class 2-D, Hokari Kanae
Also from Class 2-B, Manaka Nemu.
Byakuya Rinne from Class 2-A.
Makiwa Rika from Class 1-D.
What? Oh no, I’m scared.
Makiwa-san, you don’t need to be scared.
Aoi Natsuki, teacher.
Those are all seven members of group 1 in this game.
I don’t want to play!
If you try to leave or if you break the rules, the game will be over.
This isn’t funny!
The lights…
She’s gone?
Ando-san?
This is… our student council president.
What a stench… I feel like vomiting.
The rope… it hurts.
Kei-chan…
Kanae…
Who’s there!
No…
My butt… down there… it’s sucking up my panties…
This is so embarrassing…
This is more embarrassing than being naked.
I’d rather just… please… take it all off.
That hurts.
Wh-why?
Why are you spanking me?
That hurts…
That hurts… That hurts.
My butt… time after time… it’s swelling… and feels good.
W-wait.
Kei-chan…
That hurts.
My… virginity…
Ow…
Are you… going to cum?
Kei… Kei-chan…
Why?
This is… so cruel…
What is it?
No, who is it?
Kanae? No… Makiwa?
Manaka-san?
Manaka Nemu, my classmate…
Rumored to have the blood of a Westerner in her…
Her face is thinner, and more dignified than a Japanese girl’s.
Her proportions are also perfect.
Distant from others, cold-hearted and independent.
A high-priced flower, feared and adored by all.
Those words are well suited to her.
And that Manaka-san is embracing me.
And at this sort of inappropriate timing
What are you doing in a place like this?
Hey, won’t you answer me?
Darling…
Hmmm?
So you get hard this easily?
She found out!
Manaka-san understands perfectly.
She knows the reason why a certain part of my body is this stiff.
Watching that destroyed shell of a body… you’re turned on from it, aren’t you.
I’m surprised you’re involved in this terrifying game.
I wonder what the others would think of you if they knew?
Well, they…
I’ll keep it a secret for you.
So do as I say.
That’s right.
How about three wishes total?
What’s your answer?
If she asks me that…
I will.
… that’s the only answer I can give.
Good boy.
Well. Then the first one…
Manaka-san, I’m…
Call me “Nemu”
Nemu…-san.
Just Ne-mu.
Nemu…
Then the first one.
Kiss me.
R-right here?
Is this your first kiss?
Yeah.
Really? Me too.
You start it.
Bad boy.
Kanae?!
Oh?
Um… so… I…
Kanae… this wasn’t…
It WAS what you think.
Kanae!
Kanae.
Hey… Kei-chan, look at this.
Welcome to the main room.
Now scanning.
6 players total.
"Keyholes": five.
"Door Opener": one
The way to open the first door is to give the key to the Door Opener,
Fit each key in its appropriate hole
to open the doors
and fit each key in its appropriate hole to open the doors.
It is the Door Opener’s judgment that decides which doors are opened,
As that is decided, doors will open one by one.
There are five doors total.
Now we will begin the game.
Within the next ten seconds, please assemble at the lit door.
Line up on the line on the floor.
Ten… nine… eight…
We have no choice but to obey.
Everyone, assemble on this line.
I wonder if this is the right line?
two… one… zero.
Now scanning.
What a sadistic computer.
I have successfully located all players in front of the door.
The Door Opener must now walk ten paces forward and turn around.
Now setting the position…
The “Keyholes”…
That was referring the girls standing in front of me.
The keyholes will now be determined by the Door Opener.
We will give you thirty seconds.
The Door Opener must choose one Keyhole in the allotted time.
If you reject the keyhole, the game will be over.
The same applies to the Keyhole.
Game over?
That means everyone dies, I suppose.
Be quiet.
Explanations over.
Turn 1. Choosing Phase
All players must be quiet.
I must choose someone… or everyone will die.
Nemu…
Let’s… do… more… please…
I have to decide.
Manaka Nemu.
Keyhole chosen.
The Keyhole and Door Opener must now relocate beyond the door.
The door will open.
Unlocked.
Beginning countdown.
Ten… nine… eight… seven… six… five… four… three… two… one…
The Door Opener and Keyhole are now in the room.
Moving on to Phase Two.
Deciding on the door opening method.
The Door Opener will decide on the type of key.
If the Door Opener fails to decide, he will fail the game.
The key and method of unlocking will be a physical and mental challenge to both the door opener and the keyhole.
Physical and mental? How is that tested?
From these chokers?
Now scanning…
Scanning complete.
We will present the Door Opener with a key.
We will give everyone in the small room the “Terms of Opening”.
The Door Opener must open the box.
The actions in the small room will be broadcast live in real time to everyone in the main room.
But the sound and audio from the main room will not be broadcast.
Look.
That is the “Terms of Opening.”
Keyhole: vagina
Times to ejaculate: twice
Method: hard
The Terms of Opening for the Keyhole and Door Opener are written above
Please review the Terms of Opening.
Apparently trickery doesn’t work.
So that is the key?
Yeah…
You need to use that to fuck me, right?
Yeah.
What an awesome costume.
I suppose they’re making me your hardcore sex slave.
The "Keyhole" is her vagina.
Ejaculation: twice.
Method: hard.
Hard, they say.
So they want you to rape me. Can you do that?
Of course I can.
Let’s skip the formalities. Just thrust it in. To my pussy, that is…
You don’t need to tell me twice… I’ll do that.
So this is… Nemu’s pussy…
Hymen?
She’s still a virgin?
My… virginity…
My virginity…
That’s right.
I know it hurts.
Losing your virginity to an unusually big dick.
How satisfying.
You… are you turned on… by being raped by me…?
I thought she was just a sadist… Maybe she was also a masochist.
What a slut you are.
Yes, that’s right.
I’m a slut.
A slut who loves being raped by you… is that what you wanted to hear?
You ripped my hymen… Isn’t a girl in pain a nice thing?
That’s what your face is saying.
My pussy’s insides… are filled with a cock.
You think it’s rape?
It’s so hard, swirling around inside me.
You’re being too gentle.
I’m losing my mind!
Did my virgin pussy turn you on?
Fuck me more violently, please.
You’re a weird girl…
You don’t need to tell me to be rough!
Pussy… ripping… it’s breaking!
She’s still well enough to talk?
Then she needs more!
It’s… cumming!
Inside… there’s semen… dick milk… in my pussy…
It’s so smelly… and hot… so much…
Did she… just… squeeze my… dick?
Are you stopping?
You can’t.
You’re supposed to do my pussy twice.
Think of it like you’re planting a seed.
Do you have any idea what you’re saying?
Keyhole: Vagina
Times to ejaculate: Twice
Method: Hard
Now we’re even.
My nipples!
They’re being squeezed!
My nipples…
You're squeezing them with your nails!
If you pull on them that hard, they’ll fall off!
They’ll be twisted off
does it hurt?
Nemu, does it hurt?
Yes, it hurts!
My nipples are hot… and your cock…
Your hard cock… is messing up my pussy!
That’s right.
Your pussy is getting messed up. I’m fucking it to shreds.
I’ll give you plenty.
Inside…
I'll fill you with my semen.
The cock in my pussy… is getting bigger again!
It’s coming.
You’re going to cum soon.
Even though I’ll be ovulating soon.
I might get p… pregnant from this!
So hot… hothothot!
The boiling dick milk is… in my pussy!
Such hot dick milk… yummy…
On my face, my skin…
I have a semen-mask.
Is…
With just a faint “is…” as her final word,
All I could hear from Nemu’s mouth was scattered breathing.
While listening to Nemu’s voice,
Opening complete
I opened my first door.
I've fulfilled my first duty as the Opener.
Euphoria ~ The Game From Hell Begins~
W