Don't!
A-Awesome!
Putting it into my womb...
...feels so good!
So good!
That was close.
I win again.
Master's utter defeat!
There!
No way...
O-One more round?
Huh? What?
D-Don't!
That's... no...
Don't... It's so good.
I'm cumming.
I-I-I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
That didn't count!
As a penalty...
...I'm gonna give you head once.
I really know the taste of your spit now, so...
Your cum is delicious.
Right after we went on summer vacation...
...Grandpa died.
And, as specified in his will...
...I became a butler during summer vacation at the home of the Tsuburateras.
And that's where I met the lady of the house.
It was her, Tsuburatera Kotoha.
What's with all this?
Oh yes...
Yes...
And what's with the size of this mansion?
Heavy...
Madam, your luggage arrived.
What the-
Oops.
Wha...?
Shit...
You saw me, didn't you?
Well, no.
You're Katsuragi's grandchild, aren't you?
Come here.
Let's talk!
Okay.
This mansion's huge, isn't it?
We have so much stuff, it gets annoying.
It was then when I learned to masturbate.
I got so addicted then, I couldn't stop.
"It's even okay to get caught", is what I thought.
Is it okay to talk to a housekeeper about this?
Well, you're the one who just got here and saw me.
I wasn't looking, you know.
Then what's this?
That's-
I don't like to be the only one seen.
What are you-
I'm still horny because I didn't cum before.
You're also excited, so...
...you've got quite the lance here.
Lance?!
Madam, what are you-
Oh, you don't know?
You want to do it too, don't you?
But...!
I won't do it with you, if you don't beg.
How is it?
Feels good?
Lady Kotoha!
W-What?
I've never seen someone cum so quickly.
But you're still hard.
Oh no, madam!
Huh?
Although you just came...
...it's getting harder and harder.
I might like this scent.
I'm about to cum.
Madam...
...you're really skilled.
What?
What did you just say?
Did you think I was a bitch?
All right, take a good look.
There's nothing embarrassing about being watched.
How's that?
Does it look like I do it a lot?
I admit that I'm naughty.
But-
If you think I'd do it with just anyone, you're hugely mistaken.
Here.
Have a lick.
See for yourself what it tastes like.
You're also...
...pretty skilled.
Treating me like I'd be the only naughty one here.
You're also...
...good.
Good.
Please excuse me.
But it's my first time.
Would you be my first?
What? Really?
O-Oh my...
...I was jumping to conclusions.
I would, but...
...would you be my personal butler then?
Of course.
This is a penis?
Incredible.
It's my first time, too.
This feels extremely good.
Hurry up and put it in!
Okay.
So good!
Awesome!
Amazing!
It feels too good. I'll go crazy!
This is how it feels inside a girl's pussy...
It's wrapping so nicely around me.
H-Harder!
Katsuragi, do my breasts too!
Sure!
This is great!
Squeeze my tits!
My pussy's tightening up, too!
Do it harder!
I-I'm cumming!
Cumming!
I'm cumming!
We're not done yet.
It's hitting deep!
K-Katsuragi!
I-Inside!
Cum inside!
That's not a good idea!
Just do it.
Do it inside!
I said no!
Sheesh...
...laying your hands on me before even doing your duties.
Oh please...
Hey...
...let's see who's better at making the other cum.
First one who reaches ten times wins.
What?
T-Ten times?
I'm weak against cowgirl position!
All right! One more time!
After that...
...we changed time and place...
...and had sex.
The happy times continued.
Just...
...it was Lady Kotoha who won the challenge outright.
If you master the utmost squeezing technique...
...it feels like the day has begun.
Well then, Katsuragi...
...get ready please.
You and me will be going to the same school from now on.
What? Me too?
As expected of a place where the Tsuburateras would go...
...to be precise, they founded the school.
They practically piss money!
At school, Lady Kotoha is in the student council and very popular.
A prim and proper girl, and an honor student.
A big contrast to how she is at home.
But...
Madam!
I can't get enough of this scent.
I can't hold it in any longer.
Because of how stressed she is it ends up like this.
Madam, I'm about to-
Wait, not so fast.
I made it rock hard, so-
-put it in...
...right here!
Will that be all right?
Here I go.
Madam, you're very tight.
I love dick, after all.
Don't speak so loud!
Seal my lips then!
Don't move your hips so much...
I can't hold back when I think of you, who I'm always having sex with.
Your penis is so hard...
...and hitting my womb!
It's a mess there!
Lady Kotoha...
...I-I'm about to...
Not-
-yet!
Screw me from behind!
Understood!
My pussy's full of you.
Feels so good!
Oh no, it's better than usual!
Give me your hot stuff!
Here I go. I'll pump you full of it!
You're all mine, so-
I like you, I love you!
I'm... I'm cumming!
That was refreshing!
What I meant back there wasn't about you, it was the sex that I love.
Huh, what did you just say?
Nothing, it's fine.
By the way, clean this place up, please.
What?
No way...
The sexual encounters with her continued.
Anywhere, anytime.
But I...
...thought that this relationship wouldn't last long.
Butler and lady.
For that was our relationship.
So nice! I want to do it too!
Katsuragi-san!
Yes?
Excuse me.
Could you help me with the school festival preparations when you're done?
Wh-What monster tits!
Was there someone like her in my class?
Ah, o-okay!
What?
Did you notice?
Y-You're...
Why are you doing this?
Remembering...
T-To be honest, I want to ask you a favor.
What?
W-Wait! Hold on!
This is yours...
Although I said wait-
Soft...
...is not what I should be thinking about!
Wow. It's gotten bigger!
What the fuck is happening?
Is this a confession?
Does she love me?
Is this all right?
Lady Kotoha and I are...
...nothing more than butler and lady, so...
A fitting man for her...
would be among the rich ones.
That's right. I'm free. Free, right?
Y-Yeah.
I'm free.
I'm...
Katsuragi!
Katsuragi~!
Would you be my personal butler?
K-Kotoha...
I-I'm sorry!
I'm in love with someone.
What?
H-He's in love with someone?
That's enough!
L-Lady Kotoha?!