Dolce for Vanpire
Ever since I started dating Setagaya Mari,
there is just one main question that bothers me.
The issue of her fidelity as a succubus.
So she really does it with someone else other than me?
This is amazing.
You can keep going even after cumming so many times!
This feels great.
It's a lot bigger than Kanzaki-kun's!
My pussy is being stretched by it!
That's good.
Your dick is pushing into the deepest parts of my pussy.
I think I'm going to get the hang of being
fucked by this big thing every day.
With this thick cum, I won't be satisfied
with Kanzaki-kun's anymore.
I won't be satisfied...
– That just has to be it!
– I won't be...
Kanzaki-kun.
Hey, Kanzaki-kun!
What's wrong? Everyone's left already, you know.
Hey Setagaya,
I don't think I can keep on dating you anymore.
I mean, we are currently dating,
but in the end, I'm just your meal anyway, so...
It just makes me feel sad.
Then that means you want to break up with me?!
Wait, I didn't mean...
How terrible of you, Kanzaki-kun.
True, my powers as a succubus are still basic, but...
Hey, listen to what I have to...
My breasts are quite lacking too, so you're
probably dissatisfied with them.
Oh, so you're conscious about it.
But that doesn't mean we have to break up, right?!
I always do it like you want me to!
– Here, like this...
– Hey what are you doing?!
Listen, what I wanted to say was that...
So that's how it is, huh?
So you're fed up with me already?
In that case...
You don't plan on listening to me, do you?
I can make it stiff using this rich and plump body.
It feels soft!
Here, it's starting to get harder.
Of course, because it feels great...
Wait, that's not it!
Still not good enough?
Well then, how about this?
You're free to fuck this little pussy like a wild beast.
Th-That's not fair... I think...
My aroused pussy is being completely filled...
As long as you want to,
even if it's a cat, a rabbit, any animal, or any kind of girl even...
I can become one for you.
That's not what I was trying to say!
I'm asking whether you're really okay with me.
What? Of course I want you!
The one I love and the one I want to have sex with,
is none other than you, Kanzaki-kun!
Ma-Mari!
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum...
Me too, I'm going to cum.
It's overflowing!
I love you.
I really do.
Hey, do you want to drop by our place later?
Would it be okay?
Yep!
I want to introduce you to Mom.
Wait, you said before that she's a succubus, right?
That's right.
Am I going to be okay there?
Don't worry.
She's not going to lay a hand on her daughter's boyfriend.
I think.
Oh, you think, eh?
Kanzaki-kun, you just thought of something naughty, didn't you?!
You're one to talk!