Does it taste good?
Yes, it's delicious!
So good...
Cum! Please let it out!
P-Please pour your hot semen into my mouth!
Nicely done. I'll give you a reward. Here.
Don't spill any of it. Drink every last drop.
Did you drink it all?
It was very delicious.
Then I'll give your other mouth some...
Shake your hips more! You're getting slower!
E-Even if you say that, I can't-!
Then I'll help you!
I-If you do that, I'll break!
It'll feel too good!
I can't sit straight!
Does it feel so good that you can't hold yourself up?
Even if you say that...!
No...!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Go on, cum!
I'll pour it into you!
Thank you very much!
I still haven't finished for today.
Yes... Use me as you wish...
Why am I doing something like this?
Onee-sama...!
Elf no Futago Hime
Willan to Ursula
By SubDESU-H
I'm surprised that you were hiding such a thing...
Kill me already!
Interesting...
Teaching them isn't any fun unless they're a little feisty.
I won't forgive you for this...
I'd rather commit suicide than be defiled by you!
Oh? That's very brave of you.
I'm serious!
No matter. It just means that we're going to do your older sister instead.
Onee-sama?!
You princesses are identical twins.
It doesn't matter to me which one is made into my slave.
N-No way...!
Not Onee-sama...
I can't let her become a s-sex slave for this man...
I'll leave the dagger here for you.
You can kill yourself whenever you want.
W-Wait-!
I-I understand...
I'll do it, so...
I'll do anything in her stead, so please leave Onee-sama be!
Oh? Anything?
That's right! Just do whatever you want to me!
Then, to prove your loyalty to me, you can...
Now shift your bra so that I can see your breasts.
Oh? They're quite nicely-shaped despite the fact that they're in armor all the time.
Y-You pervert!
C'mon, we're nearly there.
Quickly, take it off.
I know that already!
I took it off.
What are you hiding yourself for?
Put your arms behind your head and show me everything.
When will you have embarrassed me enough?
If you don't want to do it, then that's fine.
We'll just get your sister to do it instead.
Y-You coward!
I can't see too well. Spread your legs wider!
H-Have you had enough?
Alright then, how about you dance around naked?
D-Dance naked?
Move your hips and gyrate your body!
Do it like you're showing yourself off down there.
N-No way...!
Would you rather not?
F-Fine! I'll do it!
If I... If I just bear with this humiliation, Onee-sama will be...
What's wrong? Move your hips more!
I-Is this enough?
I won't lose! I can't lose!
I'll bear with any humiliating things he does to me!
J-Just look all you want!
That's good.
You're already this wet.
Were you feeling aroused before I touched you?
No way, you're lying!
That's not possible! I-I can't possibly be feeling aroused!
O-Ouch! Stop it!
Stop it at once!
Very well. I'll teach you personally.
P-Putting a woman in a position like this...
You should be ashamed of yourself!
You're going to show me more, aren't you?
I-Is this all right?
If you're going to rape me, hurry up!
That's not right. Say it like I told you to.
P-Please, I...
Willan's... virgin...
You're too quiet!
Please mess up Willan's virgin pussy with your cock!
Fine, then. I'll do as you wish.
No, stop it!
I-It hurts!
Stop it! Stop it!
That's something I can't do.
No, stop it!
Not so rough!
How's this? You can see better now, can't you?
N-No!
N-No, it's going inside me!
That thing is going deep inside me!
Stop that! Not my ears-!
I see, so it's true that high elves' ears are sensitive!
Stop it! No more!
It's getting bigger inside of me!
No!!
H-Haven't you had enough? Please go away!
Had enough? Don't be silly.
I can keep going.
N-No way, it isn't over?!
I won't lose...
To protect Onee-sama, I'll...!
I... I'll...!
I'm surprised that you can still say such a thing when you're this aroused.
No! N-Not so rough!
I-I'm gonna cum!
No!!
P-Please, l-let me go!
Frerdenia's princess is pleading to the enemy?
You've fallen quite low.
N-No-!
I'm the p-proud Princess of Frerdenia!
P-Please... Please let me rest a bit-!
I-It's starting to hurt!
Then I shall cum inside you this time.
No, don't!
Anything but that!
Just leave it to me. I'll make you cum.
I'm gonna cum!
You mustn't!
I'll feel too good!
That's probably enough for now.
It would be boring if you were broken any further.
You're doing it harder than usual, May.
Is something wrong?
You're busy, so I shouldn't fawn on you too much, should I?
Are you worried about my body?
I thought that you might be tired, Darsh.
Hey, Darsh...
Yeah?
Do you play with those girls because they're high elves?
Sorry, Darsh! I'll try my best!
Darsh!
It tastes good...
May, your mouth feels great.
It's so hot and slippery...
Yes! Please let my mouth make you feel good!
The twin elf princesses.
You've gotten pretty tame.
What happened to your feisty self from before?
Haven't you humiliated me enough?
Don't be mistaken.
There was someone that I wanted you to meet tonight.
Wi-Willan?
Onee-sama?!
I'm sorry, Willan. I'm sorry that I made you go through such things...
Yes...
It's not fair that only the younger one is naked.
O-Onee-sama?!
W-Why...?!
No way...!
How is it? How is the twins' heartwarming reunion?
What does this mean?
This isn't what you promised!
You said that i-if I took her place, you wouldn't do anything to Onee-sama!
Don't be mistaken. Ursula herself suggested this.
Onee-sama did...?
She said that she couldn't bear for only her sister to go through such pains.
What a beautiful relationship!
N-No way...
Now then, Ursula, shall we get started?
Y-Yes...
Don't worry, Willan. I won't let him do anything humiliating to you again.
Onee-sama?! What are you...?!
Okay, get started.
I, Ursula, the first Princess of Frerdenia,
a-am going to show myself masturbating...
Stop it! Don't make Onee-sama do such a thing!
I'll take her place!
If you want to rape her, do me instead!
It's fine, Willan. I asked for this myself.
O-Onee-sama...!
Ursula, fondle yourself with both hands.
Play with your nipples as well.
Y-Yes...
T-To think that I'd be doing such lewd things...
I-It's so indecent!
To think that my elegant and modest Onee-sama is d-doing such a thing...!
I bet that you want to play with yourself...
Y-Yes... I want to...
So embarrassing...!
You're too gentle.
Onee-sama...!
C'mon, mix it up like this!
No! Don't! I'll do it, I'll do it myself!
Okay then, go ahead.
Yes...
You're that wet already?
Such a loose Princess.
No, that's not true!
Please don't say such things!
Say what you're doing right now.
I'm relieving myself and it's making such an indecent sound...
And... m-my body is throbbing, h-hot, and it feels paralyzed...!
Alright then, I'll let you taste my thing now.
That's...
Please stop this!
Don't defile Onee-sama any further!
What a loud Princess.
May, you take care of her.
Onee-sama...!
Stop it...!
Please stop this!
You promised that you'd leave my sister alone if I did what you said!
Then you'll have to satisfy me.
If it's not good enough, I'm going to do your sister instead!
I-I understand...
I'll do anything, so please leave Willan alone!
O-Onee-sama...
Raise your butt a bit higher, and plead for it.
Understood... Please watch me...
Please look at my lewd...
p-puss...
I-I'm sorry!
Continue.
C-Can you see my pussy?
Please use your cock on it if you wish!
As you say.
No! I-it's twisting up my insides!
How is it, Ursula? Does it feel good?
No way, can it...?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Y-Yes...
I-It feels good...
T-This position is...!
You like this position, eh?
Yes, I-I like it!
It feels amazing!
Don't look away!
Burn the image of your sister being raped in your place into your mind!
No!!
No more!
Are you going to resist?
I don't mind doing both of you.
Wi-Willan, look at me!
What?
O-Onee-sama...!?
L-Look, Willan!
Please look at my pussy lewdly sucking his cock in!
Wi-Wi-Willan!
Willan! My pussy feels amazing!
It feels incredible! I love his cock!
Onee-sama, please stop it!
I-It's fine, Willan!
I'm doing this because I want to!
I-It's because I'm a s-sex slave that likes to be fucked!
Onee-sama... Onee-sama...
Onee-sama... Onee-sama!
It's hitting me!
H-His big thing is hitting my deepest spots!
No-! Y-You mustn't! If you do that now, I'll-!
Oh? Do you want me to stop?
S-So good-!
I-It already feels so good just from my pussy,
but you're playing with my breasts too! I-I'm so happy!
Yes, that's good.
Onee-sama, Onee-sama...!
Onee-sama!
You shouldn't keep staring! You should feel good, too!
W-What are you...?
I'll make you feel better...
Not there!
Here I go!
Oh my, that must have felt good.
I'll do you a bit more.
This is great! You're tightening around me!
I-It's so big!
You're getting bigger inside of me!
I'm gonna cum soon!
Yes, I understand!
Please cover me with your s-semen!
No-! Wi-Willan!
I-I'm gonna-!
I'm cumming, I'm gonna cum!
Willan, look at me...
I'm covered in white... I-It's beautiful...
Onee-sama!
N-No!
You should cum too!
No!!
You came so much! How dirty.
Onee-sama, I'm sorry...!
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
This is getting interesting...
Just you wait, high elves!
Not only will I desecrate your bodies, I'll corrupt your very souls!