Wanna stay out a bit longer?
Eh? Uh... Yeah.
Senpai... Where should we go?
Someplace fun.
Like karaoke?
That’s right, Tomohisa-kun, we haven’t been in a while.
Yeah... Let’s go there.
S-Senpai, I’m sorry.
I’m okay.
But, Tomohisa-kun, your hands...
Eh?
Whoa! Yeah, that’s right!
Everyone’s looking at my panties, Tomohisa-kun.
I’m sorry!
Don’t worry.
Let’s go to karaoke.
Okay!
W
~Private Lessons from Angels~
Sign: Karaoke
Senpai... in here...
Is it okay?
It’s dark and loud, so no matter what we do, we’ll be fine.
No matter what?
Are you sure?
You certain there are no cameras...?
S-Senpai... that’s too strong...
Tomohisa-kun, does this feel good?
I love deep throating.
It hurts and fills me up and throbs.
You can do it rougher if you want.
S-Senpai!
Deep in your throat... I’m...
S-Senpai...
Wow... you’re sucking so hard... I’m gonna cum!
Tomohisa-kun, I drank yours.
It’s still hard.
Eh... Ah... Well...
I want to feel good too.
Because...
Senpai.
No! Too embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
You don’t understand a woman’s feelings, Tomohisa-kun?
N-No...
A woman feels like this...
I can’t hold back anymore.
Tomohisa-kun, your hard cock... it’s rubbing against me!
Wow... It feels so good.
My boob feels great too.
Senpai, your voice is getting picked up by the mic.
I know that, but I still can't stop.
Welcome in.
Hey, what do you want to sing?
I’ll have to see the list first.
T-Tomohisa-kun... your dick is... touching my skin.
Wow... it’s so hard... and throbbing.
Senpai... I...
Me too...
Look...
Get me more aroused.
Senpai.
I feel embarrassed if you stare at me like that.
Yes!
Oh, I feel it!
Senpai’s... smell is so... nasty!
Don’t say that. It’s embarrassing!
Put it in already!
Thrust it in hard!
Just like before, deep inside.
Please.
Hurry!
Okay.
I’m going in.
Okay!
Hello?
Oh, r-really?
I understand.
Yes... Yes.
Our time is up.
I-It can't be helped.
Thanks for coming.
Be sure to come again.
Senpai, what should we do now?
Tomohisa-kun, I’ll go wherever you want.
Maybe a love hotel?
Oh no!
Ah, that’s right.
Maybe over there.
W-Where?
Step on in.
Eh?
It’s my mom’s car.
But she sometimes parks it here.
This car looks like the one my dad wants to buy.
Wow, it’s pretty spacious.
Though it's a bit dark.
Are you cold?
No. I’m fine.
I can’t turn on the heater without the engine on.
But... now we can finish what we started.
That’s not exactly why I...
Oh, really?  But I wouldn’t mind sleeping with you here.
Um, well, I guess I was just lonely...
I’m already so wet.
Please... fuck me.
The inside of a car really gets me off.
Yeah, people could totally see us... it makes my heart throb.
Oh no. I’m so aroused.
I’ve been holding back so much...
Me too.
I’ve always... wanted to fuck you...
That’s okay. Fuck me as much as you want.
Harder!
Yes. Oh yes... I’m getting fucked up!
S-Senpai... I’m almost there...
Let me cum with you.
I’m cumming...
I’m cumming, cumming!
I’m cumming, cumming, cumming!
I’m cumming!
Senpai!
Good morning, Tomohisa-kun.
Good morning.
Listen...
I... want to go home.
Eh?
With the argument you had with your dad about the car, you sure?
Yeah...
Why did you change your mind about the car?
Well, I found out that minivans have their perks.
And I figured I’d talk to dad again about the car he wants to buy.
Tomohisa-kun, thanks.
Eh?
I love you, Tomohisa-kun.
S-Senpai... your undies?
Huh?
Oh no ! I left them on the stick shift!
I’m sorry!
No... by now my mom has left for work in her car already.
Let’s give up.
Will you be okay?
I-I think so...
More importantly, we need to smooth things over with your dad.
Um... This is a new car, isn't it?
Yeah... This is the car I said I wanted.
Oh, mercy! Please give me guidance!
Mizuho!
Mizuho, I bought the car you wanted!
I bought your favorite food!
And I’ll be nicer, I promise...
Mizuho! Please come home!
Mizuho!
Looks like you still got trials ahead of you.
Dad’s always like this.
He’ll be fine when I'm back home.
I’m back, Dad.
Mizuho!
You want to model for the Photography Club, Mikura-san?
Modeling Portfolio
Photography Club
Yes.
They want me to model the uniforms for the various clubs for their club pamphlets.
And you accepted?
They were so desperate I couldn’t resist.
Please help us!
And wearing the uniforms of the other clubs also sounded like fun.
But... that just sounds suspicious.
I never heard that they were making pamphlets.
But they are.
So, we’re shooting tomorrow after school.
And I want you to help, Endo-kun.
Eh?
Will you help me?
Shooting
Developing
Can you look over here a bit more?
Okay!
Mikura-san, you sure are pretty.
Wow... Very nice. Yes, yes.
Now, push your boobs together and lean forward a bit.
Um... Is this okay?
Yes, yes. That’s perfect.
Very nice.
Next, turn around.
Yes, yes.
And then, the same pose as before.
Okay!
Is this okay?
Mikura-san, you rock!
Now, let’s take a break.
Mikura-san, change into the next uniform.
Okay, I’m on it.
Excuse me.
Endo-kun, good job.
How was my modeling?
Mikura-san, I think this is weird.
Shh! Don’t talk too loud, they’ll notice you’re here.
But you’re not a glamor model.
If it looks like they’re gonna rape me, you come rescue me, okay?
W-Wait... Eh?!
You can watch for a bit.
Endo-kun, I need to make it worth your while.
M-Mikura-san...
You really got big quickly.
This is bad! You need to get dressed fast!
Ah, but you like it when you can see my boobs!
That’s not what I mean...
Endo-kun, you’re so hard.
And the tip is wet.
Watching my photo shoot must’ve turned you on.
Wow, you’re getting wetter.
Shall I lick it clean?
M-Mikura-san...
It tastes a bit sexy.
Endo-kun, you naughty boy.
H-Hey...
Mikura-san, don’t suck so hard...
Mikura-san... that’s too rough. I’ll cum.
Mikura-san? Have you finished changing?
J-Just a bit more...
Is there a problem?
Um, no! T-There’s no problem!
B-But I have a HUGE problem...
Um... I’ll thank you properly later.
So don’t cum yet - wait for me.
U-Um... this swimsuit... isn’t it a bit too small?
Oh, I’m sorry.
That was the only size we had.
But it looks very good on you.
Very nice.
Yes, yes, how nice.
Oh yes, wonderful.
That’s perfect!
Is this pose really okay?
Good point. Can you wedge the swimsuit in your ass crack more?
Eh?
We can get your body lines better that way.
Is this okay?
Very nice!
What will happen to Mikura-san if this keeps going?
I’ll thank you properly later.
So don’t cum yet - wait for me.
Mikura-san.
Since we’re at it, can we see a bit of your boobs?
Eh?
Don’t worry, just cover them with your hands.
B-But...
It’s often done in glamor shots.
Yes, but...
Are they going to make...
Mikura-san go nude?
Hi... Sorry.
So the pamphlet was all a lie?
Yeah, the Photo Club didn’t even know about it.
Did you erase all the photos they took?
It felt like a waste, but I did.
Ah, and I was starting to have fun. I felt like a real model.
But if you’d let things go any further, you might have ended up nude.
Were you looking forward to it? My nude photo shoot.
That’s not the case!
But you didn’t cum and you waited for me.
Oopsie!
So you can take pictures of me in my swimsuit.
Mikura-san!
You saved me, after all.
So it’s a thank you service.
Thank you service?
Mikura-san, you’re so cute!
Mikura-san, are you sure that’s okay?
It’s okay. I want you to snap ALL of me.
M-Mikura-san... Your pussy looks wet.
That’s because you’re watching me be slutty!
W-Well, I’m...
And knowing that you can see everything
makes my heart pound and makes my pussy wetter.
Mikura-san... I... can’t hold back anymore.
Okay.
That's alright, I’ll give you your reward.
It’s inside.
I’m gonna cum quickly.
Wow! I feel it hitting my uterus.
Mikura-san...
Eh?!
Oh no...
It’s slipping! Sliding so easily.
Wow!
Mikura-san, I’m gonna... again...
Alright, you can cum inside.
Your dick is so wonderful.
Wow!
You’re pounding me so hard inside, Endo-kun, it’s amazing!
Watching you get your photos taken in such sexy poses...
Again...
This feels great.
M-My insides are all being stirred up.
Wow...
A-Again... I’m cumming again.
It’s okay... Inside... Cum inside a lot!
M-Mikura-san...
I’m almost... there...
I’m cumming. I’m cumming!
Oh no!
Yes...
I’m cumming... I'm cumming!
That felt really good.
What about you?
Of course, it did for me as well.
Let’s take pictures of us fucking next time.
Just kidding.
The reason I fucked you so hard...
...was as a thank you service.