SubDESU-H.net
To celebrate graduating high school,
we went to Wani Land in Tokyo.
Starting in the spring, we’ll be in a long distance relationship.
Since our colleges will be separate.
But... I had no idea that would happen. No idea at all.
W
SubDESU-H Presents
「Heart Pounding Pollinic Girl Land」
The Pollinic Girls Attack! The Animation.
Heart Pounding Pollinic Girl Land
I... I had heard that Tokyo was severely infested with Pollinic Girls...
But I had no idea it was this extreme...
W-What should we do, Ami-chan?
Wanna just go home?
No. I’m okay.
We came all this way.
So let’s make some fun memories here.
Ok. I got it.
Let’s go!
I think we’ll be okay if we ride on something...
What?!
Oh? You want to get off already?
We were hoping you would get off to our fun Pollinic Play.
S-Sorry!
Would you care to join us?
Ah, um, we...
We’d rather ride the merry-go-round!
What cute people.
The merry-go-round should be okay...
So deep... it’s hitting me so deep.
I’ve never felt this!
It’s rubbing around in my pussy so tightly!
I love this merry-go-round!
I-I think we should call this one quits too...
H-Hey, Ken-kun, how about a roller coaster?
Eh?
You know, since it goes at a high speed, the pollen probably flies off.
Good idea!
Sign: Please form a line behind here. Estimated waiting time: 2 HOURS.
Oh no! Don’t!
If you’re so rough with me, I’ll cum in front of everyone!
I’ll go crazy!
Th-This looks a bit...
Yeah...
S-Sorry, Ami-chan...
In the end it turned out this way.
Oh well. We can’t help it. We’re both allergic to pollen.
Oh no... it’s starting to feel good.
Was I really this susceptible to it?
S-Stop it.
I don’t want Ken-kun... to see everything.
Ken-kun’s penis... it’s getting so big.
I didn’t realize boys got like that.
A-Ami-chan, I’ll try not to watch you.
No... no...
N-Not there. Don’t tweak it!
Don’t make me hornier...
I’ve never heard Ami-chan moan like this.
And her nipples are rock-hard.
Her crotch is soaking wet...
So this is what a girl is.
Ken-kun and I haven’t ever done this.
D-Don’t moan so sexily like that!
Ami-chan, I’m sorry, but... I...
I’m at my limit...
So hot.
Ken-kun’s semen... there’s so much.
It smells foul...
No...
N-Not so rough... I’ll cum... you’ll make me cum...
I can’t hold out...
Please, Ken-kun, don’t watch.
Are you okay, Ami-chan?
Can you walk?
Ami-chan?
Are you okay?
I... I... no!
Ami-chan!
Sigh... And here I have this wonderful day off...
But thanks to the Pollinic Girls, I can’t go out anywhere.
"Clunk"?
What the hell is this?
What are you?
N-No!
Don’t spread it...
S-Stop...
N-No... no, no!
My clitoris... it’s throbbing...
No way!
It’s broad daylight... out here...
Not so... rough...
So hot.
Don’t squirt strange things on me.
Ew.
I’m getting all sticky.
No...
Not my asshole...
N-No...
Oh... please let me go!
I-If you make me cum here, I’ll... pee...
I’m cumming... cum...
No!
It’s gonna come out... it’s coming out...
I peed... I peed so much... all over...
D-Darling?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Snack time.
Horrible things happened to me!
When did you put that thing in the bathroom?
Jeez, you really are a pervert.
Well, lately you’ve been taking lots of time in the toilet, Mami.
I was hoping you’d pee faster.
W-Well, I can’t help it!
The only thing I can do to kill time at home is read magazines.
Looks like you have a very unusual collection.
Pleasure
Oh, I've already read all of those.
You can tie them up if you want.
T-Tie them up?
W-What is it?
H-Hey! No... Stop it!
Just stay still!
What is this room?
A-And, why am I the one tied up?!
Well, I figured I should practice before I tie up the magazines.
That’s a lie and you know it.
If you struggle, you really might get hurt.
D-Don’t pull so hard...
It’s going in my crack...
But... Doesn't this actually feel good to you?
O-Of course it doesn’t!
It just hurts, that’s all.
That’s what you say, but, your boobs...
Are getting very hot.
That's...
Well, that’s because they’re tied up...
Don’t!
Don't... Please... stop this.
It’s still daylight... so don’t...
That’s what you say, but your nipples are so hard.
Oh no... if he tweaks my nipples so hard... it’ll feel too good.
Jeez! Why did you set up this room?!
I figured something like this might happen, so I remodeled it.
Well then.
No... not there!
Not there... Not so rough... or I’ll...
If you make me cum first, I’ll stop.
Okay. I understand.
I accept your challenge.
You really wanted this, didn’t you?
No, I didn’t. I’m not a pervert like you.
But, Mami, you’re much wetter than usual.
W-What about you? You smell so sexy.
Wow... His dick... it’s so hot and it’s throbbing.
He’s excited.
He can stare at my pussy... at my wet, soaking... naughty pussy...
Mami, I’m gonna move.
O-Oh no, now it’s like my mouth is a pussy.
Wow... This feels great...
Mami, you feel good too... with all this.
Yes, I do. Pull stronger!
I’m about to cum.
That's alright. Cum lots in my "pussy-mouth".
I’m gonna cum lots too!
I’m cumming!
So hot... so sticky... so hot...
Looks like your switch has been completely flipped, Mami-chan.
Hey, darling, please, squirt your semen into this "mouth" too...
Hm... What should I do?
If I cum too much, I’ll get tired.
Oh, please don’t change the subject.
Please, put your dick in.
I’ll do anything you want.
You don’t have to cry.
See?
Inside in one thrust.
It’s a bit too soon to be too happy.
A-Awesome! So deep... all the way deep inside!
Wow! So fast!
It’s rough... it’s too rough...
Then, do you want me to stop?
No don't stop, please, fuck me harder!
My pussy wants to be fucked up!
Then I won’t hold back.
Mami-chan, looks like you’ve gotten more sensitive.
Yes, I have... I’ve gotten much sluttier...
Because you do perverted things to me all the time.
But you don’t hate it, do you?
I don't. I love it. I love it!
I love having naughty things done to me.
Your dick is getting so thick.
I... I’m cumming!
Th-This makes me... feel strange...
Oh... I can’t...
Doesn’t it feel good moving so much?
But... but no!
If you thrust into me so much, I’ll lose my mind.
No... I can’t stop... I’m gonna fly forward!
Don’t worry. I’ve got you firmly tied up.
You can just relax.
I’ll cum... I’m gonna cum again!
I’m so hot!
And with you so tight... me too...
No! Not yet!
Please, can we cum... cum together this time?
I'm... I’m cumming...
So hot. So much hot stuff.
Oops.
This way, all the semen will spill out of you.
It’s coming inside.
Semen is spurting into my uterus.
With this, I’m sure we’ll have a baby.
- Many days later -
Um... Mami-chan...
What are you doing this for?
Well, I guess I’m really into it now.
Whoa!
Well?
Did I do a good job?
You were perfect!
From now on, be sure to help me tie things up.
Darling.
Ami-chan... I wonder where she went.
Um, may I interrupt for a second?
Yes?
You're looking for your girlfriend, right?
Do you know something?
Yes. I’m sure she’s waiting for you.
Is Ami-chan here?
Ami-chan...?
My tits... and my pussy are soaked...
Oh no...
Ami-chan!
Ami-chan?
K-Ken-kun...
Ken-kun... Ken-kun...
I finally found you.
It’s so hot and lonely... let me handle it.
W-Wait a...
I’ve never done this before...
So I might not be any good at it, but...
Don’t say...
This is Ken-kun’s penis.
So this is how a man’s thing feels.
Wow...
It’s so hot... and it’s throbbing.
All I’m doing is sucking it, but I’m gradually feeling more and more naughty.
These subs were made by SubDESU-H. Visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
A-Ami-chan...
Hey, Ken-kun, I have a request...
Will you listen?
Yeah...
They’ve done lots of naughty things to the rest of my body, but...
I’m still a virgin here.
So please... Ken-kun... Please be my first.
H-Here I go, Ami-chan.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
I’m fine.
It hurts a little, but... I think it also feels good.
Ken-kun, you can move.
Let’s feel good together.
Ami-chan!
Wow!
Your penis is... moving inside of me...
Oh no... don’t... not so rough... not my clitoris...
So this is sex.
I’m actually having sex right now.
Wow, right there... it’s making naughty squishing noises...
Ami-chan, your pussy is so tight.
I-It’s feeling so good.
Even though it’s my first time... that’s strange...
It feels so good.
I-I’m sorry, Ken-kun.
I’m sorry I’m such a slut.
You can tease me plenty for that.
Ami-chan... I... I love you!
I’m so happy. I love you too, Ken-kun!
I love you!
Sorry for the wait, ladies and gentlemen.
We will start the Galactic Parade now.
Wait...
No, Ken-kun.
Don’t stop.
I can’t hold back.
B-But...
Come on, hurry... be rougher.
Please, Ken-kun.
Oh, whatever!
So now, ladies and gentlemen, please greet them.
Those of you having fun, behold the Galactic Parade.
Please, be sure to get a good look.
Today, we used a sweet cake as our motif.
Wow! There are so many Pollinic Girls around me!
Not so...
N-Not so deep... oh no...
Yes... more, more!
Suck harder... I like it...
Yes!
It’s turning me on... too much!
Oh... no...
I’m losing my mind.
Oh, yes!
Fuck me more!
Fuck me hard!
I’m cumming... cumming!
It’s so hot... throbbing, hot stuff is flowing into me...
Yes...
Oh, so marvelous...
It’s so deep... so deep...
My nipples... my nipples are so firm.
Wow, I’m really turned on.
I’m cumming again... I'm cumming now!
I feel it... I feel the hot stuff coming.
So much, hitting me strong.
The Pollinic Girls... you're all so beautiful.
My mind is... going blank.
Yes... I love this...
It feels so wonderful.
Oh... yes... yes...
I already came so many times...
My nipples... my nipples are rubbing yours. Oh yes!
Mine feel good too. I love the feel of mine against yours.
I’m being fucked so violently, but it feels so good!
Deeper, deeper!
Come all the way inside!
Your dick - yes, I love it!
Oh, your dick, it feels so good.
I’m gonna cum again.
I’m cumming... cumming... I’m cumming again...
I feel it too.
Oh, I’m almost...
I’m cumming, cumming...
I’m so hot... so very hot.
And sticky...
Yes... we came too much...
I don’t know what’s up and what's down...
Oh...
We can’t go... anymore...
And at the top of our float, exchanging their love,
are today’s special Prince and Princess.
They’re all watching us... they’re watching us.
Our first sexual experience... they’re all watching.
Ami-chan, I’m sorry, but I can’t stop anymore.
It’s okay, Ken-kun. Do whatever you want with me.
I... feel so good.
Having people watch me gets me off... so...
Ami-chan!
So deep... Ken-kun's big dick is hitting me so deep...
You can be rougher if you want...
I want to do sluttier things.
I’m cumming...
Then cum!
Please, inside... please cum inside of me.
I want to be filled with you.
Your hard, thick, hot cock is rubbing so hard...
Wow! Your cock is throbbing and getting bigger.
I’m cumming. Cumming! While being watched...
There's more!
I can’t stop.
It’s so hot... and sticky... overflowing from me.
So hot... oh no... oh no...
I really had no idea this would happen.
I never could have imagined it.
But... I want to come back with him someday.
To The Heart Pounding Pollinic Girls Land.
SubDESU-H.net