No!!
Shizuru-san.
Are you alright?
Sakura-chan...
Y-Yes, I'm fine. Did I frighten you?
N-No. Um, here is your meal.
Thanks.
U-Um, I know it's hard, but please stay strong!
It wasn't a dream...
I heard that Father was seriously injured...
I was taken captive in front of the school, then...
After that, they did it to me over and over...
I wonder how many days have passed.
That Sakura-chan...
I wonder if she was kidnapped as well...
...You're still a criminal.
You're going to pay amends for your offenses here.
This isn't right! I must do something!
But what should I do?
Toriko Hime
2nd Episode
Presented by SubDESU-H
Father... Himeno... Onee-sama...
Gone missing?!
Se-Senpai! Not so loud!
S-Sorry, and...?
Shizuru's father was attacked and he was seriously injured.
Yes, I heard that on the news.
I didn't want to contact her when it happened, but I thought that we might be able to help.
We think alike.
However, I can't get through to Shizuru's cell phone no matter how many times I try.
Same here.
That's why I asked my father to contact the hospital.
Your father is the boss of that major electronics company, isn't he?
I usually don't rely on Father's influence. However, desperate times call for desperate measures.
And?
Apparently Shizuru hasn't gone to the hospital.
Seriously? But that day, she...
She hasn't gone to the hospital, and they can't get in contact with her, either.
But since her father's in such a state, no one has the time to look for Shizuru!
It's been a week since her birthday!
Shizuru, where on Earth are you?
Maybe something happened between her and her father's attackers?
Let's look for her.
Senpai?
Let's look for her together, Himeno.
Senpai...
Yes!
Um, you're...?
This is the first time we've met, isn't it?
I'm Rena, the second in command.
And I will be the giving you orders.
Rena-san?
Now, please change your clothes and follow me.
C'mon, hurry up!
Are you alright?
Don't be so rough.
Y-Yes...
U-Um, thank you very much.
You know where we're going today, right?
Yes.
Then take care of the rest.
Roger.
Do your best today as well.
I-It's going to happen to me again...
How's she doing?
She's been great entertainment for everyone.
And? Has she figured out anything?
It doesn't look like she has.
However, what's happening to her father?
They're being quite stubborn, but we must have him transferred to the Tsuruma Group's hospital...
It'll be troubling if you didn't.
It is very important that he spills out the information he holds.
It's a good thing he's the only one who knows that secret.
On top of all, we've got his daughter, too.
What shall we do with her once we deal with her father?
Let's have her work here, like Rena.
You're going to lie and say that it's for her father or something,
but you're actually going to kill him, aren't you?
You're such a villain!
I'm gonna get to the point. What did you do with Shizuru?
What are you talking about?
I haven't met Shizuru these past few days.
You know that shefs missing, don't you?
We do.
It's not like I can help it.
Or did you come up with something just to meet me?
T-That's not funny!
The last time you met Shizuru was over a week ago, wasn't it?
Why did you say "these past few days"?
I wonder if perhaps you've actually met her these past few days?
You really want to twist my words and make it look like I kidnapped Shizuru, don't you?
No.
Then I'll let you meet her.
However, my condition is that you two come alone.
Also, don't tell anyone else about where we're going.
That's...
Senpai, let's go.
Himeno?
I don't want to put you in danger, but Shizuru's...
I don't want to put you in danger, either!
Senpai, I'll be fine.
Okay then, let's both go.
Shizuru, please be safe!
What's up, Rena-san?
Please let us stay like this for a bit...
Uh, sure.
I wonder what happened. This is the first time...
Sana, Grandfather, Father, Mother...
I've...
Thank you, some of Shizuru's acquaintances are coming. Please take care of them.
Eh? Shizuru-san's...?
Um, are they going to be...
Please.
She's the kindest person here.
She said that I was needed.
I want to help her...
There's something I want to show you first.
Rena.
Yes.
W-What is this?!
W-What are you trying to do by showing me this?
This voice... I-Is it Shizuru?
Eh?
Shizuru-! W-Why?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Actually, Shizuru has committed a crime.
No, Shizuru-! No, stop it, stop it!
Himeno! Himeno, calm down!
I don't wanna hear it, I don't wanna hear it!
No, stop it! Stop it!
Himeno!
Hurry up and make it stop!
Also, Shizuru committed a crime? What did she do?
Shizuru tried to kill her father.
She's already been convicted.
Impossible!
Also, you two are believed to have assisted in the murder.
In other words, you're suspected accomplices.
Murder? Accomplices?
That's how it is, so you're going to stay here for a bit.
Rena.
I'll take you two to your rooms. Give her to me.
I'm fine, I'll take her.
I see.
Himeno and Ayane, too! I'm looking forward to this!
Himeno?
Senpai...
Senpai, where are we? W-Where's Shizuru?
I don't know anything yet.
I don't know where we are, or why that sort of thing is happening to Shizuru.
Shizuru...
Eh?!
Are you perhaps Sautome Sakura?
Yes, um, how are you two feeling?
Never mind that, why are you here?
Rena-san...
Can I have a moment? I want to ask you two something.
Something you want to ask?
Yes.
The camera and microphones have been turned off, so speak freely.
What is it?
What is there between you and Shizuru?
Eh? What do you mean?
What is Shizuru, as a person, to you?
Is she someone you have to look for, even if it puts you in danger?
Shizuru is my rival, and also my friend!
So why does that matter?
She's like a sister to me!
A friend... A sister...
That's right! That's why we came to look for her!
It's obvious, since we're friends!
Isn't it normal for the eldest to worry about her siblings?!
Yes, you're right.
And what are you going to do with that information?
I was just asking.
W-What do you mean?
M-Moreover, where is Shizuru? Let us meet her!
Alright.
If you swear to take her place, then we can let you meet her.
Rena-san!
Take Shizuru's...
Place?
You heard me.
Then I'll...
W-Wait, I-I'll...
You mustn't!
Senpai...
You can't, I'll do it.
W-What are you saying?
I can't let you do that!
I can't let something like that happen to you!
You're like my younger sister!
Se-Senpai...
I don't want to see my siblings hurt anymore!
Neither do I!
Why?
You're not related! How can you even consider taking her place?
It's obviously because we're friends!
Is that all...
Do we need another reason?
I see, then I'll see to it.
You'll take care of the other prisoners...
Rena-san!
These people aren't... I'll do it instead!
Thanks, but it's something that we have to do, isnft it?
If we can bear it, will you let us meet Shizuru?
I promise.
Then let's get started.
Eh? Right now?
Won't it be better to do so before you change your mind?
It means that we can meet Shizuru sooner, doesn't it?
Rena-san, what are you trying to do?
Are you ready?
Y-Yes.
I'm fine.
Do your best.
More prey...
It's fresh prey!
Then we'll be taking you!
Come over here!
Himeno!
Senpai!
Noo!
You've got nice breasts! I bet that you have more expensive meals than normal folks!
N-No...
Please be good to my little guy!
N-No, don't do that to my breasts!
No, not there-! Don't touch me there!
Let's play with this!
It looks like this is your first time, but there are more of us waiting!
Please, stop this!
No-!
It smells! No-!
I'm gonna cum!
Eh?
No!
A-All over my face...
C'mon, put it in your mouth!
Um-!
This is irritating... Do it like this!
I can't breathe-!
Stop it, already!
I'm gonna cum! Make sure you drink it all!
My mouth's all sticky! It's disgusting!
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts, Senpai! Senpai!
It hurts...It's splitting me!
Does Shizuru go through this too?
It's like I'm being hammered by a hot stake!
This is horrible!
It hurts, it hurts-!
Hurry, hurry up and make this end!
D-Don't...
No way...
P-Please do it slower!
She's squeezing me so much! I'm gonna cum!
C-Cum? Please, not inside me! Not inside!
I'm gonna cum soon!
Don't! Not inside!
I'm gonna cum!
Don't, don't! No-!
Please don't! You can't!
This is too much...
Please stop it already-!
Himeno, Himeno!
You're in no position to be worrying about others!
This is suffocating!
I'm sure they won't be bored for a while.
Don't be too harsh on them.
They're our precious tools.
This solves the matter of the new prisoners.
It's unfortunate that we can't be there...
Rena, I'll leave that day in your hands.
Yes...
Shizuru-san, please come quietly.
Here you go.
Shizuru...
Shizuru!
Shizuru. You did well.
Onee-sama, Himeno!
I'm sorry to disturb your precious reunion, but can we talk?
I'll let you out of here.
Eh?
If you believe me, there's something I have to ask you.
I'll believe you. I can, right?
Well, you did keep your promise.
I can't trust you completely.
However, if there is a chance...
Thank you.
Sakura, how about you?
Eh? Me too?
That's right. Don't you want to get out of here?
Of course I do, but...
That's only if you come as well, Rena-san.
Sakura...
Rena-san.
Now then, what are we supposed to do?
There are going to be new prisoners coming in tomorrow.
New prisoners? So is this really a prison?
This is the new drug research facility owned by the Tsuruma Group.
The prisoners are the test subjects for a new drug.
N-No way! Then all that about the crime I committed was...?
They were all false accusations.
You and Sakura were brought here as prey to calm the prisoners down.
The chief and the others from the Tsuruma Group won't be here due to business elsewhere.
I'm going to be in charge of everything here.
This is our best chance.
We need assign people to certain jobs.
A person who'll setup the trap here tomorrow,
and someone who'll attend the prisoners' admission.
Attend the admission?
It's exactly what you think.
We'll need two people for that, minimum.
I'll do it!
Shizuru?
I can do it.
Then I'll be the other...
I'll do it!
Sakura-chan?
I'm used to it, so I'll be fine.
B-But-!
Yes, I think it's best if it's someone who's experienced.
Himeno, let's leave it to them.
Senpai...
Now then, I'll explain what happens tomorrow.
This is Rena, the second in command. We're going to commence the admission.
The cell doors are going to be opened randomly. After that, just enjoy yourselves.
I won't permit any fighting, that is all.
We get to go first?
It's like a show! Talk about being lucky!
You two look good!
The school uniform is such a turn on! I'm getting hard already!
Now then, let's have some fun!
I'll take this one!
No...
Don't touch me-!
I can't get enough!
No-!
Take it deeper!
There are people waiting! Stop hogging it!
You're right. I'll take the front, so can you take the back?
I don't mind which hole I get!
No-!
It's too big-!
If I do my best, everyone will be saved!
Himeno...! Onee-sama!
After this, I can go outside! Together with Rena-san...
I'm nearly done.
I'm glad you're here. I would probably mess it up.
No, no. If it were just me, I wouldn't have made it this far.
I see, let's end this quickly.
Yes.
I'm gonna cum soon! Others are waiting!
Me too-!
I'm gonna cum!
Me too!
No!!
They keep...
cumming inside!
N-No way...
No!!
We're done.
Is it going well?
It's fine.
I'm going to release the gas, as I explained earlier.
It should only affect the males, but just in case...
We know.
Let's go, Senpai.
What's this?
Shizuru? Sakura-chan?
T-This is horrible!
Himeno? Onee-sama!
Himeno, you take Shizuru.
Let's hurry up and get out of here.
I'll be okay.
I can get out myself...
But I'm dirty, and...
I don't care about that. C'mon.
I-I'm sorry.
C'mon Shizuru, you too.
Thanks...
Looks like you guys got up to some interesting things while we were gone.
Rena... you bastard...
You!
Tsuruma, you broke our promise.
Promise?
I heard that my grandfather, father, mother, and my little sister Sana are all dead.
H-How did you know?
If they had lived out their lives, then I wouldn't mind. However...
C-Calm down, Rena!
T-That Nasukawa told me to! I had no choice!
I see. I understand.
You do?
Goodbye.
Have you forgotten about me?
Rena, I thank you.
Now the Tsuruma Group is mine.
How is it? Have you changed your mind?
Well, I presume that you're not stupid enough to come at me like this.
Don't... Don't call me by my given name!
We don't know each other that well!
Rena-san!
You lot, hurry up and go!
If you spend too much time here, the prisoners will wake up!
How about you?
I have other things to take care of.
Rena-san, your wound...
I'll be fine, just hurry and leave.
You promised that youfd come too!
You somewhat look like my sister.
Your sister?
Sakura-chan?
She's just asleep. Please take her, too.
A month later, we were hospitalized. However, we recovered enough to go to school again.
My father also regained consciousness, and everything was peaceful again.
The incident didn't make the headlines.
However, the Tsurama family has gone missing, and the company seems to be going down.
Sakura-chan is working back at her studio, and we don't know what happened to Rena-san after that.
What's wrong, Shizuru?
You seem to be spacing out. Something bothering you?
No, it's nothing. I was just thinking about something.
Thinking about something?
Jeez!
You fawn on her too much!
You guys are so radiant!