The salon which is popular among beauties.
Its reputation spreads by word of mouth.
Young and beautiful women will gather.
The store where you can't get a reservation easily.
The popularity of the store always goes up.
There was a man named...
Dokushima Nero, who is a rapist, looked into the store.
He is...
sorting all the customers who made reservations.
And placed a fang on them...
Translated by SubDESU-H
Yubisaki Annainin Shirudaku Settai Okawari Sanbai-me
指先案内人 汁だく接待 おかわり三杯目
The woman he caught right now is
The famous female lawyer known as man hater
In order to make that kind of arrogant woman obedient,
she's been locked up in the underground of the salon
and has started taking his lessons...
Good..
More... more..
Please, do it more..
Hey... please..
Please move..
My, this part..
Please pound my pussy..
Please pound it..
Please..
I want you to pound it deeper and more intensely..
You're noisy...
If you want to cum then, move on your own.
N...no way..
Try to make me more excited.
Do that, I will pound you all you want.
Yes..
I understand..
How is my pussy..?
It's so hot and wet..
If you're the one...
You can do anything you want to my pussy and anus
I want you to ruin it..
My body is so hot and..
My nipples are erected too..
It's so hard..
Please..
Don't tease me!
I want it.. I want that dick..
Hey... you can do it already right?
My clitoris is erect and is this hard too.
I want it..
Pound me... please pound me...
Do you want to be fucked that badly?
Y.. yes..
P... please..
p.. please... I want to cum, let me cum... let me cum..
I'll do anything you want!
L....locking me up in this kind of place..
You added to your sin again..
It's a big mistake if you think I'll prostrate myself!
You must worry a lot..
About what you did to me here.
I'll remember it all!
I'll testify to it all in court!
You always have a retort, don't you?
(I mean here she always answers/talkback)
I...if you don't want that then... release me immediately!
I knew it!
You haven't tried to kill the women you raped right?
You know how heavy the sin of killing someone is..?
So what..?
Someday, when the time comes that you release me,
that day will be your last day!
The ones you raped up to now
I'll make guilty for them all!!
Release you?
I will release you when you become a whore!
If you want to rape me then
Just rape me all you want.
You're so noisy..
I'm cumming soon!
Take it in your womb!
No...
Even if you rape me
I'll be fine..
My heart...
will never fall!!
Really.. she's an annoying one..
Even though I embarrassed her this much,
She still won't fall
Hmmm for me, if you got this nice prey
I'm satisfied with it!
This one too will be marketable!
Damn..
Well then, I'll just have to do anything just to make her submit
Then..
I have something nice in mind for you!
Ah?
It's the journal that led her to be a famous lawyer
美しすぎる最強弁護士 Beautiful powerful lawyer
Because the officer of the big company sexually harassed his secretary,
He was found guilty for that.
南の楽園で休暇を楽しむ最強弁護士 The powerful lawyer who enjoys her vacation in the southern island
パーフェクトボディ perfect body
女性 woman
Oh..
I know this about the journal too.
So what's with this?
To tell the truth
This officer and the secretary
After the court trial
They got into an interesting situation.
連続 continuous　連泊 staying (at hotel) for a few nights  //Editor: They contiunued staying at the hotel for a few nights. (Not sure if this is what the transaltion is getting at)
Few days later...
To make her totally submit,
The last lesson
has started..
How long... I have been in here..?
A small amount of water..
and sperm is only given to me..
The situation is being repeated everyday.
My power and energy..
it's already at the limit
It's like... I'm really going to die..
You're messed up already!
If I just think of this as a diet
there's nothing to worry about.
Is that so?
Well, don't say that.
I'll give you some food today again.
Hey pretty woman, it's time for your meal.
Oh.. you must drink it properly
or else you'll get hungry.
Next, please suck my dick.
That dirty thing of yours
I can't lick that!
My dick smells good right?
Can you put it inside your small mouth?
Don't make a fool of me... you stink...
Hey sis, if you move it that much..
Don't spit it out, drink it all!
Ohhh you spit it.. what a waste..!
Who's the one that's going to drink this..?
How long can you say those strong words..?
If you really don't want to suck it with the upper mouth
Then I will use the bottom mouth!
Eh?!
S...stop that..!
There's no use in refusing!
If you're being fucked everyday
You'll start to feel horny right?
A...are you fool!?
That's impossible!
Well then,
What's with this wet pussy?
W..what are you saying?
It's impossible that I'll get horny from you guys!
Is that so?
Then I will make you feel it!
It came in..
T... take... take it out!!!
I...it's dirty..
No...
It's so tight..
Your dick is so big..
I'm going to release it soon, Ms. lawyer!
Hey, don't give up with just this!
For today, this will be the real one.
J... just do whatever you want.
Even though you embarrass me..
I will never feel it!
I'm glad that you're fine.
But.. you know rape..
not only assaults your body
Eh?
What!?
No.. way... why..?
Long time no see... Nikaido-sensei..
It looks like sensei is having fun, so can you let us join in?
W...why are you with him...?
What's the matter?
For you..
Aren't they close to you?
This is your fault sensei..
Eh?!
Tell sensei what happened to you after that trial.
If sensei won the trial
You said the sexual harassment will be gone
I... more terrible things were being done to me by different men..
N.. no way..
For reporting the superior
I'm being harassed because I betrayed the company.
Even I wanted to transfer because I'm being harassed but
I was disliked by people because I am the troublesome woman from the sexual harassment trial
H...hey.. stop it alrea....
I have no choice but to become his sexual slave..
I... I just did to you..
What sensei did to me
Nothing can be helped about it..
Sensei is just saying this is a woman's right but you're just feeling good by yourself!
N..no... no it's not!
Women can't win again men!
So you're just acting like you're going to protect the woman
I just wanted to placate yourself right!?
I... I just...
It's good to talk about the past but
Don't forget about this one too
H..hey.. wait... ah
Don't move..
We.. are having a talk..
Now you understand right?
You're just a forger
N.. no way..
No... no I'm not..
That's...
It seems sensei feels good by doing dirty things!
Hey... show your dirty looks to sensei too
Y.. yes... I understand..
Se..sensei.. look at this..
This is my dirty appearance..
No... no way..
You're already..
Doing that thing..
That thick..
dick is moving inside my pussy
Good, it's so good...
Sensei... can you see it?
My, that part..
The big dick.... it's so big... so big..
S...stop... stop it.. stop it!!
Don't rape her anymore!!!
Here, here, here!!!
Squeeze your pussy more!
Y... yes..
Sorry... sorry for having a wide open pussy..
I'll squeeze it more so.. please thrust the dick more..
Ohhh.... go on..
Good.. moan.... moan more!
Now you understand
All the things you've done... is just to satisfy yourself!
No.... stop... stop it..
Don't say it anymore!
This is all a lie!
Why don't you imitate that woman and moan like her?
Don't make a fool of me... Isn't this all your fault!?
It's that man's fault that woman became like this!
I'm not the one who's wrong!
I'm not!
I will never forgive you... I will never forgive you!!!
She's so hot... I can't hold this..
Let me use this too
Eh?
That... that part is my ass!
I can't hold it anymore!
What a noisy mouth!
I will shut it using mine!
Here you go!
Ok then, I'm going to pound your ass!
N...no... stop..
Stop it..
My ass.. they're doing it together...
If you.. if you thrust any more..
I want this sis to suck mine too
Please fuck my throat using your penis..
Ohhh
Your pussy is squeezing!
It seems you're cumming right?
No.. I'm not... I will not cum becuase of these kinds of things...
I will not.. cum..
I'm not feeling it good..
I don't want... I don't want this!!
Sensei.. even  though you're acting strong.. you're still feeling it..
I know it..
You know, we're already in trouble..
Your embarrassment... your pussy..
Please show me all!
I will.. I will cum together with you..
No... this is bad..
I don't want this guy to cum in me!
Why.. why..? Why did she become like this??
Here..
We're ready here now..
Hey, hey!
Try cumin together with that woman!
Y... yes... master...
I'll cum... I'm going to cum..
Release it inside..
Please give me the sperm deep inside!
N...no...
If they release more inside..
N..no...
I won't lose... I will never lose!
Yes..
I wanted to see that face of yours..
Faster..
I need to find another target..
By that I..
I will not be left by that man..
He will fuck me agian..
I'm now..
I can't go back anymore..
From now on..
The one that he'll put a fang..
I must find them...
I found it..
Then come to the massage room..