W
My name is Daiginjou Makoto.
I’m just an ordinary girl who fell in love.
This guy is my lover Takerus penis.
Takeru said to call it a dick.
But I can’t say it you know.
Letting a girl say dick.
I love Takeru and Takeru’s penis but...
I haven’t tried having sex.
Even saying that…
Hey Takeru… let’s do it…
Ok…
Ok then… here I come.
Ok.
Come.
Takeru...
Faster...
Here I come...
Takeru...
Faster.
Ok…
Here I come.
Makoto, there’s a bus hijacking incident.
Emer-
gency.
It’s the doing of the evil organization nu~gu.
Kogerion, prepare for action!
Roger!
Sorry Takeru, I need to go.
Again~~?
Change!
Kogerion!
Well I say that,
I’m Kogerion, a super beauty who fights for justice.
Ok then Takeru, I’m going.
Makoto.
I’ll be right back soon.
So let's continue it later.
Oh, hey! Makoto!
She’s always like this.
Hey Makoto!  Your panties!
Can’t help it.
Nu~gu, the evil who disturbs the peace.
I won’t forgive those bad ones!
Beauty fighter.
Kogerion!
You finally appeared Kogerion!
Release the hostages.
Or it seems you need a punishment for this week again.
Hey you! You’re not wearing a panties!
No more discussions!
Kogerion kick!
Ei!
Yaaa!
Taryaaa!
Oh my, it's started.
My my, she spread it widely.
Grrr go! loser Robot no.25!
Naïve naïve, you can’t beat Kogerion by size alone.
Tou!
You did it loser Robot no. 25!
*do your best* ß- children cheering.
I’ve been waiting for this day.
The last day for Kogerion!
This period will be put in our disgusting history!
Shut up!
Kogerion, I’m sorry to say good bye, you know it right?
With this button,
Here, explode.
What!?
It's sure effective.
I did it!
Makoto!
Takeru...
Why is Takeru in a place like this?
It's dangerous out here.
Ah, why is my body.
Lying out there?
Takeru?
Takeru says something.
What? Takeru, I can’t hear it.
Sorry Takeru...
If I knew things would turn out like this,
I would have had sex with you.
I’m... going to die...
Takeru...
I don’t want to.
I don’t want to die.
I don’t want to die Takeru!
Makoto!
Makoto!!
Professor!
Professor Daiginjou!
Daiginjou Laboratory
Prof! Makoto is...
Makoto is...
Hey, Soutou Shigoku-sama.
Please give me a great reward quickly.
It's true the Assassination of Kogerion was successful right?
How negative you are.
I cut off the head of Kogerion.
Good job Sasurina.
Here’s your reward.
Ahhhh here it comes.
Here it comes.
It's great.
That’s why I can’t stop this job.
Good.
It's great!
It's so good!
Good!
It's great!
Shigooku-sama’s great dick is thrusting inside me!
Good!
Thrust me!
Thrust me deeper!
Release it!
Shigooku-sama’s hot and sticky milk!
Inject a lot inside me!
Ryou… Makoto can’t be saved anymore.
Makato is dead.
Makoto…
The time has come, Yamane-kun.
Switch…
On!
Occupied
Makoto-chan.
Yes!?
Makoto?
Makoto.
Makoto!
Makoto!!
Makoto!!!
Makoto!!!!
Makoto!!!!!
Takeru?
Hey wait Makoto!
My my...
Yamane-kun, you hold the location of Makoto right?
Takeru, Takeru!
Oh?
What?
Takeru! 5x
Sasurina-sama!
Hm? What?
I’m at a good part.
That’s... uhm...
What is it? Say it.
Uhm… there was a response just like Kogerion’s appeared again.
What!?
Takeru?
You….
I wanted to see you.
Takeru!
Takeru! 3x
Who are you?
Don’t make fun of me.
Takeru?
What are you saying Takeru?
It is me.
Makoto!
Makoto is dead.
And what’s with that appearance?
What you say? It's the same as always…
ah? I’m naked!
Hey! It's flat!
What should I do Takeru?
My boobs are gone?
It's shiny!
Nooo Takeru…
Such a weird kid…
The behavior is the same as Makoto but…
Don’t tell me...
Nooo Takeru...
Don’t tell me this kid…
It's just a kid.
You are…
Sasurina!
How dare you shouldn’t have killed me!
I’ll repay this.
Don’t tell me.
Don’t tell me you’re really a Kogerion?
Are you Makoto?
Are you really Makoto?
Kogerion punch!
You!!!!
Eat this!!!
Rawrrr!! :D
Yaaaaa!
What’s this? You’re too weak.
I don’t know why but you’re naked.
Nice timing,
You guys surround her.
Roger!
Don’t lay a hand on Makoto.
Stop it Takeru.
Takeru..
It's impossible to handle them Takeru!
I know.
Police officer!
The Hentai Cosplay group is attacking the woman!
What?
Hey! What are you doing!
This is bad, retreat!
Remember this you two!
Wait!
Makoto…
Takeru...
I wanted to see you.
Me too.
I’m really Makoto.
I know.
Are we no longer lovers?
It won’t be.
But…
I’m already this tiny.
Dummy.
I can’t fight with this.
Makoto, come with me.
It's only us who can do this right?
Maybe?
What are you suddenly?
It's because…
It's because...
Why are you so kind?
With this body, I can’t have sex with you.
I didn’t go out with you to have sex.
Takeru...
Besides, I think I like this one better.
You dummy.
Pervert!
I’m already with this body.
This is real.
Yes it's real.
You’re cute Makoto.
Really?
Are you sure you want to be with me?
Then, then, is this cute?
Yes it's cute.
Hey hey, Takeru.
Hey Takeru, let try it.
Try what?
You perverted kid...
Or do you want it in the ass?
Makoto…
Takeru…
Touch it.
I’ll wash Onii-chan’s too.
Takeru…
Your finger…
Put your finger in...
Makoto...
Touch it...
Takeru...
More...
Make more sounds...
I’m at my limit...
No...
I want to see it.
I want to see.
The part where Takeru ejaculates.
A lot came out.
No….
No…
No… the pee is coming out.
Makoto?
I... again...
I want to do it too Makoto.
I can’t hold it.
Sure.
Let's do it.
Lets put Takeru’s in.
Yeay.
Bath with Onii-chan.
We’re going to put it in right?
Yeah.
Let's take a bath together.
Hey Makoto, spread your legs.
It seems Takeru’s penis is bigger than before.
It just you got smaller.
Ahh I see.
Hm?
I feel I’m special.
Because Takeru’s penis got big.
And I love big penises.
Makoto…
I love Takeru’s thick dick.
Takeru you… got big again.
Can’t help it you know.
Makoto...
Let's put it in.
This big one… it won’t fit in…
It's coming in…
Makoto…
Does it hurt?
It's alright.
Let's move it little by little.
Ok...
It came in.
In front of everyone.
Takeru, today is the greatest day.
Yeah it is Makoto.
But Takeru’s is really thick.
Takeru’s what?
Takeru’s dick…
This won’t fit in to my mouth.
Mouth?
Do it in your mouth too.
Takeru you really...
Don’t move that much.
It’ll come out.
It's because it’s too good and I can’t stop it.
No...
I’m cumming!
Oops...
I released it inside.
Makoto!?
Wait! Makoto, shhh!
Hey Makoto, don’t scream inside the bath.
Your answer?
Yes…
Ok, you’re good Makoto.
Ohh, I was surprised.
That voice was so bad.
Yeah...
How did that feel awhile ago?
Some part of my stomach suddenly got hot and
I felt some power inside me.
Does that mean my body reacted on the 1st try?
No way...
xSauna
Makoto.
Change your clothes faster.
xSauna
Oh... ok.
The power huh...
Onii-chan.
I love to peel the skin of the penis.
Ma... Makoto... you...
It's punishment for making it painful.
Just joking.
It’s a reward for making me happy.
Stop... it.
I’m a perverted girl anyway.
Release it Takeru...
We need to take a bath again.
Nooo!
It’s a failure again.
Ok ok, go home.
Go home already.
Don’t hang around on the way.
My my...
Where is that Okotamite anyway?
Shigooku-sama wants some weird things again.
What’s with him? Saying Okotama Okotama.
We’re risking our self for finding those things you want.
Hm?
That’s...
That’s Kogarion!
How dare you make a fool of me earlier!
Kogerion!
Be prepared!
I will make you scream with these pist fats’s punch!
Why~~~~?
What’s with that power?
Maybe Takeru gave this to me.
What’s that?
It’s the power of love.
Damn you Kogerion!
Remember this next time!
What?
Makoto activated?
I see.
Those two got some nerves.
Hm?
There’s some killing presence.
I think it's just my imagination.