We've finally found you.
No, stay away...
Someone help me...
Are you sure a little girl like this is qualified?
Yes, there's no doubt.
She's the next in line of Princess Kukkuri, a blood relative.
Father, Mother...
We didn't have to keep the others alive, did we?
Do it before her very eyes.
Detachment is usually evoked through despair.
No... Father, Mother... No, stop...
It's alright.
We won't kill you.
You're going to go through hardships worse than death,
and as the sacrifice, we have to awaken you.
Well then, let's get going.
Now to fulfill the tale from 120 years ago.
SubDESU-H Presents
Kagirohi - Shaku Kei
I see, so you're Izanami the god.
When I was born with these eyes, my family was...
S-Stop!
N-No-!
N-No, no!
T-That place is...!
D-Don't! No!
Was I born into this world to become a sacrifice like this?
I shouldn't have hoped for anything...
This is so painful...
I don't want this!
Help me, Aoi!
Senpai...
I overheard the villagers talking about the human sacrifice.
There's no way something as ridiculous as that is real, right?
Senpai...
Please don't get involved with her any further.
It's something that she wished for herself.
Impossible!
Kaede, where are the Ajisai?
We must go save her-!
I won't tell you.
And I can't let you go any further.
Kaede!
Everyone, capture this man!
Damn it, I'm surrounded!
What's happening?
After him!
We mustn't let him escape!
Catch him at all costs!
Did they give up?
Wakoudo! I've come to help you!
Kusano! Where have you been all this time?
That was the power of these "magical" glasses!
Aren't they amazing?
Ah, so the disturbance earlier was you.
You saved me, Kusano.
It's good to see that you're safe.
Yeah, but...
Ajisai was taken away, Wakoudo.
I couldn't stop them...
T-That's right; Kusano, where is Ajisai?
What would you do if you knew?
Ajisai is a very precious person to me.
I must save her!
She's deep inside the cave, in an area called the 'Shiniki'
Ajisai went to hold back the god Izanami who had turned evil.
S-Stop!
N-Not there-!
It won't fit! N-No!
Not my first time! I want to give that to him!
P-Please-!
No-! It's entering me!
Don't push it in me!
It's so hot...!
It's so big, and so hot-!
No-!
I wanted to give him my first...
No! It's going in so deep-!
It's hot-! Please pull it out!
No-!
It's reaching my deepest spots!
My uterus is being struck by this disgusting thing!
It's really inside me...!
What's up? Calling me out to such a place...
You...
You're always staring at me, aren't you?
Eh?
Do you want to play a game?
It's easy, all you have to do is walk over to me.
Isn't it simple?
Y-Yeah...
C'mon... Let's get started...
No...
This is disgusting!
P-Please stop it!
It's all hot...
It's like I'm going to get burned!
P-Please stop this!
No...
T-That's my sensitive spot-!
Not my clitoris-!
I-I'll cum if it does that-!
N-Not so rough-! No-!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum-!
I'm gonna cum-!
I-I'm gonna cum!
It came... It sprayed its hot semen all over me...
That thing came inside me!
It took my virginity...
I wanted to give it to Aoi...
I'm sorry...
This game is to test whether you can change my family traditions,
and whether you have the power to change the destiny that is before me.
W-What on Earth is this?!
I knew it, he can't get close to my soul...
My destiny can't be changed...
Why... How can he move forward?
Maybe if it's him...
He might be able to change my destiny...
Ajisai!
Together with him... Even if my destiny didn't change, I...
Now that I think about it, I felt that he was different the first time I saw him.
I was drawn towards him...
And... it was my first love...
S-Stop this already!
N-Not that one-!
Please! Stop it-!
I-It's piercing my butt...
The tentacle is rubbing my insides!
My mouth, my butt, and my pussy...
I'm being penetrated on three sides! It'll break me!
It's painful, and I can't breathe...!
It's going deep down my throat...
This raw smell makes me want to throw up...
B-But...!
I-It feels good...
My mind is going blank...
I can forget all the misery...
M-My butt feels good...
M-My pussy feels like it's going to melt!
It really feels good...
Do it to me more!
More, give me more!
Give it to me!
So good!
I wonder whom I was thinking about just a few moments ago...
It was a very precious person, but my mind is going blank and I can't remember!
I-I'm gonna cum-!
It came inside me...
It's gushing into me...
It's still coming out...
I-It's like I'm the one cumming...
It hasn't calmed down yet...
I wonder how long this is going to happen to me?
So good-!
More! Give me more!
Okay then, you go ahead like we planned.
I'm leaving Ajisai up to you.
Okay! Roger that!
Then do your best in securing my and Ajisai's escape route, Wakoudo.
We're relying on you!
I wonder if Ajisai is behind these gates.
I knew you would sneak in here and try to get her out.
Did you really think I wouldn't notice?
How pitiful.
H-How did you...?
Your job is to protect Ajisai-san, isn't it?
You shouldn't be authorized to interrupt this ceremony.
I'm so close...
Wakoudo... Ajisai...
Ajisai...
That's right... I came to love Ajisai...
That's why my assignment doesn't matter...
You wanted to rescue Kukkuri-hime despite Yoshino's orders?
You sure do some capricious things...
Like you would understand my feelings!
I wouldn't, as I'm a human.
Why would I understand the feelings of a demon?
You say some strange things...
You wicked woman!
If you weren't here, then...
I could easily spot you.
Oh yeah, how could you see me?
How were you able to...
Oh my, you don't know? It wasn't very smart of you to consider rescuing Ajisai-san.
How humorous.
T-Those eyes... You're of the same origin as Ajisai?!
This would make a good entrée for the main act...
With this little girl, we shall begin the "Yomotsu Hegui" ceremony.
S-Stop!
Damn you! Don't touch me with those dirty hands-!
You idiot-!
Oh yeah.
Are you aware that since ancient times,
intercourse between a man and a woman
has taken place on this altar to appease Izanami-sama?
If you do your best, Ajisai-san just might be saved.
I bet that's a lie!
But if what she says is true, then...
Don't you want to save Ajisai-san?
T-That's-!
I-If you put your finger in, I'll-!
N-No!
Stop it-!
Don't!
Not that thing-!
Don't struggle!
You deserve it.
Now then, please drill your meat stick inside this little girl.
D-Don't rub it against me!
You're pretty tight...
It's piercing so deep inside me...
Even though it's my first time, he's forcefully drilling his cock into me...
Stop moving!
No-!
D-Don't-!
I-If you do it that much, I'll-!
T-This feels strange!
It overflows every time he thrusts!
N-No!
I-It's making lewd sounds!
N-No-! Not so hard!
S-Something is coming!
It's coming out-!
S-So much is coming out inside me!
No time to rest!
Next, you have to repent with your ass!
Ajisai...
C'mon! Hurry up!
I-It's going into my butt-!
It really went in!
It'll stretch too much!
Don't move so suddenly-!
It's so hot-!
My butt is getting hot!
You're gonna tear my butt!
I-It's rubbing against my insides-!
S-So deep! It's going in so deep-!
I don't want to feel good from my butt, but-!
N-No way!
D-Don't-! I-I'm gonna cum! No!
I don't want to cum from this!
M-My butt...
Oh my!
However, we're not done yet!
P-Please! Stop this!
No-! Help me!
Right, now I just have to go in and...
Senpai...
Do you love Ajisai that much?
Do you?!
Kaede! Please help me!
Otherwise-
Onii-chan, I loved you before anyone else.
It's not right that you chase after that girl.
Ka-Kaede-! Stop!
Please just think about me...
If it's me, then I can do anything you want, Onii-chan...
Onii-chan... Please become one with me...
I'm gonna cum again-!
I-I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I don't want to cum again, but I can't help it!