“After school” or after school is over.
“After School”
How should I put it?
It’s like a time for women to be free.
Some girls take off their bloomers right
after school. What are they thinking?
It’s time to compete, so I can’t say I’m
embarrassed because of panty-shots.
“Cute and pretty strawberry print panties are the regular panties of Moriyou Gakuen Women’s School for panty-shots♡ One of the most popular brands is Strawberry Angel, which is unique to the ‘Panty Club (aka P Kura)’ shop at Funny Plaza. Those panties are Moriyou girls’ secret pride♪”
The chime for the end of school
is like a signal to start a battle.
I hope our school will adopt gym shorts soon.
You say something like that, but you still
checked yourself out carefully in a mirror.
I don’t like mesh bloomers,
and my bloomers are size S.
Say, if we’re to go on to some school anyway,
don’t you wanna go on to Moriyou Gakuen?
But it has a reputation that there
are many cute school girls...
Anyway, why don’t we go to P Kura?
Do you wanna go to Sylvian?
I’ll pass ‘cause I’m on a diet.
Well, I should say it’s too high a level for me.
You're not confident about your figure?
The school uniform is pretty and
I'd love to wear it, but the skirt...
Mari-nacchi’s skirt doesn’t fit her big butt.
“I guess one in two girls wear bloomers even during class. By Anna”
Arisubara school’s specified bloomers are in size S.
Teachers will boycott classes if they find
white panties under a student’s skirt.
“Wakatsuki Anna. Bloomers are best suited for her adolescent body.” By Kotarou
During puberty, sweat and other
body odors get stronger.
Bloomers are best to wear, especially in summer
when you get even sweatier than usual.
Ahhh!
“Kawai Hinako. DOB July 7th. Cancer. Blood Type B.”
Onee-chan, are you okay?
If Kotarou doesn’t look after me,
I’ll be blown about by the wind.
Hey, look at that couple. He's super cute!
He's the kind of a boy who
encourages motherly instinct.
He looked over here.
Oh, his face turned red.
Mari-nacchi’s butt must have seduced him.
No, it’s because Yayoi’s bloomers are sexy.
Yours too!
No, yours!
Onee-chan, stop it. Everybody is watching us.
But it’s normal for a brother
and a sister to be close. Right?
Kotarou is my brother.
“Body measurement will take place today. Please go to the Nurse's Office.”
“Girls are required to wear bloomers.”
I think when choosing underwear
became my secret pleasure...
...I started to live with Kotarou.
I am NOT fat.
I've got a touch of constipation now.
My father told me that he is a son of my
father’s friend, who was killed in an accident.
It’s morning, onee-chan.
Good morning, Kotarou.
Oh... Well...
W-W-Why are they here?
You're the one who said to me that if I dried
my panties outside, they could be stolen.
No, I mean, why is my underwear here with yours?
I found your underwear in the laundry
hamper and washed it with my clothes.
Did I do something I shouldn’t have done?
S-Sorry.
What did you apologize for?
I don’t mind being watched by you...
...because we are a brother and a sister.
“But I’ve discovered Kotarou’s secret.”
Anna’s Moriyou Town Map
Hey, Hinako-oneechan, one more time.
Let’s take a picture again.
“Wakatuki Anna. DOB August 1st. Leo. Blood Type A.”
“New Product Now In Stock”
“Please stand in line.”
This time, Anna-chan, you can
choose a background pattern.
Love Kiss, a new instant photo sticker machine,
has been installed recently at P Kura,
and it's becoming a popular date spot.
Which should I pick?
There are so many patterns
that I can't decide what to pick.
They are polka dot... And check, too.
Wow, this lace pattern is super pretty!
Anna-chan looks good with a floral pattern.
What? You think?
Oh no.
Did you see it?
Mama said she had finished washing all my clothes.
Do I still need to wear bloomers?
I don't think this is a good thing...
I feel sorry for the girls having
voyeur photos taken of them.
It’s a shock to see these photos.
You like to take pictures, but the reason why
you won’t show me any pictures is this...
It’s all right because you're special.
I don’t mind taking pictures of you taking a crap.
C-Crap!?
I know you like that kind of thing.
If you like, shall I take pictures
of you in front of everybody?
I can make you feel so good.
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
You know I don’t like dirty talk, don’t you?
What’s with you?
I know Kotarou is not the kind of a boy
who secretly takes pictures of panties.
I’m gonna hate you.
Amazing.
Look at you. It’s true that when a masochist
is picked on, her face glows.
M-Masochist?
Well, we don’t wear them to be shown.
That’s right. Arisubara Gakuen’s school rule is insulting.
Anyway, we gotta wear frumpy things until we graduate.
Boys flip up my skirt.
It is said that, for boys, flipping skirts is one
of the ways to express their first love.
“What do you think about love?”
Love should be a serious business. Right?
I think to each her own.
The start of a new love is almost like an accident.
It starts one day, all of a sudden.
So, the way to meet a boy or start a new
relationship should be friendlier.
That’s the motto of our club.
Our Love Club’s main activities
are to find love and nurture it.
Well, um...
Love is a difficult and important thing, but I
guess it’s not a bad idea to work on it casually.
So, that’s what the After-School Love Club is all about.
“’After-School Mania Club’ I want something thick. The Animation”
SubDESU-H Presents
“Collection 1 Hinako, Rinko and M Lesson”
We use Starry Sky as a clubroom for our Love Club.
The Moriyou city-based café plans to expand it throughout all of Japan.
I wonder if waitresses are alright with
wearing a uniform that embarrassing?
Gee, do I look so much like a trendy girl?
“Nitou Kanami. DOB October 8th. Libra. Blood Type B.”
To tell the truth, somewhat I want to be like that.
I can’t stand wearing the school
uniform until the end of school.
I go straight to the station restroom
after school to change my clothes.
I wanna express my femininity.
I wanna have a photo of a boy
and me as a couple soon.
“Wakatsuki Anna. DOB August 1st. Leo. Blood Type A.
Hobby/Special Skills: Nobody can beat me in beat ‘em up games!
My favorite food:”
I need to sell my sex appeal a little more.
Give me a cherry, Anna-chan.
When I am with you, I feel like I am a grown-up.
I like it because it’s pretty and sweet.
“Kawai Hinako"
Well, my membership number of the Love
Club is 4 and my name is Kawai Hinako.
My birthday is July 7th and my sign
is Cancer, and my blood type is B.
I have a bust measuring 85, waist measuring 58 and hip measuring 88.
But, why do you ask about my measurements?
Because I wanna check in advance.
It’s for a boy who may be my boyfriend.
Did you join this club to fall in love?
I really don’t know about love, but just
getting together makes me excited.
Oh? Won't you try on a bikini?
I was going to, but... How can I put it...
I look thinner in clothes and I’d be embarrassed
if my breasts hung out of a bikini top.
You just ridiculed me as childish!
No, I didn’t!
I'm jealous of you because there is a rumor that
many boys masturbate while thinking of you.
“You know, I am not a good imaginary bedmate (・・;)”
One in five men...
One in five men looks over at Hinako-san.
He did it, too.
Did you see it?
If I were you, I’d get nervous.
“Horikawa Mutsumi. DOB May 10th. Taurus. Blood Type A.
I’m reluctant to wear my summer clothes.
I’m worried about men’s eyes.
You gave me a look saying I’m overly self-conscious.
N-No.
Your brother told me a terrible thing.
He said being overly self-consciousness is
an indication of a masochist’s exhibitionism.
This is a shopping mall, Will. It’s very popular among the
girls of Moriyou Gakuen and convenient as a meeting place.
There is a forbidden garden for boys on the fourth floor.
Is it surprising to know that I care so much about underwear?
Huh?
Nanase said... Oh, She is my little sister.
My sister laughs at me by saying that I’m an honor
student but I'm stubborn about something so strange.
But I have no intention to show my underwear
to anybody except my significant other.
So, I want to wear something beautiful.
Do you think that's weird?
A-Are you gonna show it?
Well, am I saying something unreasonable?
Your brother may have had a point
with what he said to me.
“A girl’s feelings are complicated.”
Speaking of which, don’t you think toilets of this building are very interesting?
I don't think it's a good idea that one of the toilets is a Japanese style toilet.
To Ayumi, it’s nasty.
It may be good for a girl called Anna.
Ahhh, it seriously pisses me off.
That's disgusting and awful!
I feel hesitant to come out of the toilet.
Just because it’s the rainy season, and...
...too humid...
...makes my hair too dry...
...and I can’t have a boyfriend!
Come to think of it, I think Reiichi-senpai is handsome.
That’s not my point.
My unruly hair is my big problem during this time of year.
I feel like I’m eavesdropping. Is it shameful of me?
It is said that a masochist is aroused by watching someone
on the toilet or showing themself on the toilet.
I’m fed up with blow-drying my hair every day.
N-No. My pulse isn't racing because I’m a masochist or something.
“Have you ever imagined something naughty by hearing the clear sound from a toilet next to you?”
“I believe that browsing in the bookstore is a culture for school girls. By Kazumi”
I heard that boys get horny just by hearing
the sound of toilet paper rolling.
You won’t be infected by germs even if you
don’t wipe after you do your business.
A girl browsing is an easy prey for upskirt shots.
Please be careful about a wedgie.
A cheap stopper is no good.
But a better one is too expensive.
What are you talking about in the restroom?
It’s a secret.
It’s not my day.
Only a Japanese-style toilet is available.
Do I get sexually aroused by watching her peeing?
“Do you know your hidden real self?”
What should I do if I am a masochist?
Oh! Don’t look at me!
I may be a masochist.
May I sit down here?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I joined this club, but I feel like everybody avoids me.
At this rate, I’m gonna be in a bad mood.
Well, my membership number of the
Love Club is 8 and my name is Yusa Rinko.
“I’m at work.”
“Make me cute.”
“What is my next dress?”
“I’m at work.”
“My funny face.”
“I’m working, ahem.”
“Good night.”
These are my three body measurements.
I have a bust measuring 83...
...waist measuring 58...
...and hip measuring 86.
Please don’t tell my mother that
I told you about my measurements.
Your mother is a writer, isn’t she?
Everybody at school calls you an “idol”.
That’s why everybody is reluctant to say hello.
That’s true.
They call me an idol, but what makes them say that I’m an idol?
Does it really look that way?
My mom has never praised me before.
The theme of her writings is about women’s
independence but she's strict with me.
She doesn't approve of me.
Does even the idol go to the restroom...
...for a pee or a crap?
And she decides which panties I wear every day!
I respect her, but at the same time
I feel a bit fed up with her.
So I want to be an independent
woman and give her a surprise.
I’m pretty sure she'll be pleased.
She wrote in her book that a woman’s
independence would begin with love.
Yusa Rinko
“Yusa”
I'm home, Purupuru-chan.
Look, look.
They said if I liked these outfits they would
give them to me. That’s how I got them.
I’d be in big trouble if my mom found out about it.
She said she'd be home late tonight
because of a publisher’s party.
I think it's okay to enjoy myself
a little while my mom is away.
By the way, the park wasn't
a good place to visit.
The bench was hard and the restroom was terrible.
It was the first time I used a Japanese-style toilet.
I need to squat to pee.
It’s disgusting because it looks like being exposed.
I can’t say if I feel embarrassed or good or guilty.
I had a strange feeling.
Speaking of strange, Kotarou-senpai
said to me something strange.
Rinko-chan, you have the makings of a queen.
I have no interest in picking on someone.
It’s more like, my mom's always
bullying me, and yet I respect her.
It’s your fault, mom.
Mom, you're too strict, it just makes me
want to do what I'm not supposed to.
It feels better and better.
“Don’t ask me what to do to feel best because I don’t have an answer.”
My anus is very sensitive. That’s why I touch here like this.
Don’t stare at me like that.
You pervert!
Purupuru-chan, this is a secret between you and me.
If I become a queen, can I feel better?
Boycott?
I skipped a violin lesson today.
I feel like becoming a shut-in.
Are you gonna be a shut-in?
I have a more important lesson to become
independent from my mom.
Lesson?
No, I can’t do it.
I think you need to take responsibility
for what you’ve done to me.
Because your brother is the one who
aroused my masochistic sexuality.
Senpai?
Don’t let me do it alone.
B-But, I don’t want to do it here.
You have a better idea than me.
N-No, that’s not it.
Actually, I have a secret item.
This is it. Ta-dah.
Rinko-chan, stop it.
If you raise your voice, someone will come here.
No, no.
I’m getting excited.
Kotarou-sanpai may be right.
Hinako-senpai, you have it in you
to become a masochist’s slave.
And I have it in me to become...
...a masochistic queen.
My mom said that I can ignore the school rule
because bloomers are a symbol of sexism.
I don’t care about it. I’m confident in bloomers.
But I don’t feel like wearing them today.
I weighed myself yesterday and I was
shocked to find that I put on some weight.
If I’m on my period, it would make sense.
But that’s not the case.
I gotta check my mesh bloomers.
It’s disgusting to be watched by the PE teacher, Miyazawa.
He stares at my butt and breasts and calls me a fat virgin
As I recall, he called me that, too.
If you want to go on a diet,...
Are you really sure about that?
Enema diet?
It’s said that it works more than expected.
Have you tried it?
Actually, I haven’t.
I got this information from Nanase.
“Horikawa Nanase. DOB April 11th . Aries. Blood Type B.”
She looks like a naughty girl.
The sisters have hard bowel movements so they have a lot of enema equipment and know a lot about them.
Give me your sperm, to the last drop.
I’ll swallow all of it.
Nitou-san’s information was useful for unexpected situations.
Don’t forget about the slave agreement with me.
I’ll do anything you say from now on,
so please let me take a crap.
Senpai.
I am the one who wiped your crap.
There are some people who
are vulnerable to sexual attack.
Hinako-san is one of them.
But they are sensitive to other people’s eyes.
For example, you take a trip to
the hot spring with your friends.
A girl, who is reluctant to take off her panties in front of
her friends, tends not to take much care of her public hair.
Fat virgin.
Automatic reaction is a scary thing.
By being watched, the body automatically reacts.
If so, you have a sexy body.
It's cute that you worry about your sexy body
and you are bashful about it.
No!
Oh, for you information, I just repeated
what Kotarou-senpai said.
Kotarou?
No, no.
What is that?
This? This is...
Ah! Kotarou.
I don’t want to give you to anybody,
but I can’t go against the queen.
So, I’ve decided to give your anus to her.
What?
No!
Do I really need to do this?
Do you wanna be the queen?
N-No! Stop!
I’m gonna insert it.
Noooo!
Rinko-chan, move it!
Yes.
No.
The fun after school has only started.
Tanshii koto jamerarenai
I can’t stop doing something fun.
boku wa sukoshi oshiete ageru, afurereru egao no himitsu, koko ni aru kara
I’ll tell you a little about the secret of my bright smile, because it's right here.
tsuragi wa otou, fuue agetou
When I feel down, and feel uneasy
kigaeshitara, hajimeyou
We'll get started after I change my clothes
mail wo okuri, denwa de warattari, to
With sending emails and laughing over the phone,
kore kara ga isogashii
From now on it'll be busy
tomare ni natta ni naranai you ni ne
Make sure nobody will stop us.
ai mo omoi ni deteru. Inochikare de itai, watashi tacheru kisetsu, motto mankitsu shiraii
In the city where I picture myself as
falling in love, our season is shining.
Daremo waramitenai
Don’t you wanna enjoy yourselves more?
okiniri no rouge
No one's seen my favorite rouge yet.
soutto kagami ni mukatte, egao wo nagekakeru
I gently smile at the mirror.
Yume miru koto jamerarenai
I can’t stop dreaming.
nee, isshoni eegai kekirai
Don’t you wanna draw together?
oosaro ni, nanairo no niji, kagayaki tachitta
A seven-colored rainbow shone brightly in the sky.
Yume miru koto jamerarenai
I can't stop dreaming
nee, isshoni eegai kekirai
Don’t you wanna draw together?
oosaro ni, nanairo no niji, kagayaki tachitta
A seven-colored rainbow shone brightly in the sky.
“’After-School Mania Club’ I want something thick. The Animation”
Ri-Rinko-chan ... Aren't we really not supposed to do this?
That's right. Didn't I tell you? A girl's independence is the start-line of her love
“Release in this fall!”
Please look forward to After-School Mania Club:
I want love, second collection, ok~?
“Don’t miss it!”