This voice?
Don't tell me that...?
What should we do?
If we don't get a move on, she's gonna steal Kouta from us.
I want to do something about it.
But Kou-chan doesn't really look at us.
Did we tease him too much before that teacher came here?
But it's not like Kouta-kun hated what we did before.
Don't you think that we should join them?
Eh?
W
Kouta-chan, move your hips more!
Yes!
That's it? How disappointing.
That's right, that's how to do it.
Hey, should I squeeze your balls too?
Oh, what a strange voice.
Kouta-chan's dick,
its size and hardness is perfect.
You're hitting the right spot, it feels really good.
Hey, do you also feel good?
Yes—
Then, I want you to say that Hikaru Sensei's pussy
feels really good!
Hikaru... sensei's pussy feels good.
Don't be such a baby.
Guess this is how you deal with an idiot.
Your penis is getting hard!
It feels good.
Don't you think that it feels good too?
My pussy is dripping wet.
Hey!
Kouta-chan, that's too fast!
You came with all your strength, right?
That's because you suddenly moved!
That shouldn't be a problem.
There's more time, you can cum outside next time.
Hikaru-sensei.
I'm surprised that you're actually back in this village.
That's because it's my hometown after all.
But you leave your class for them to study on their own all the time.
You always leave everything to a substitute teacher.
Why do you even come to school anyway?
Isn't it obvious?
I came here to do stuff like this.
But it's a school with three girls,
and only one boy.
Don't you think it's time for us to stop this?
It's gonna be ok!
Don't those girls also do stuff like this with you?
That's... true.
Don't you want to try something besides those girls?
So you won't get bored.
The first thing that we need to look at is Rui's breasts, right?
If you're titfucked by those breasts,
I'm sure you'll cum over and over.
Well... I can't deny that.
Hitomi is the 'loli' type, right?
Almost like a forbidden fruit.
How is it? Did you feel something about that?
It's... not like I'm doing something bad with her.
What do you think about Aiko?
She doesn't talk that much, but isn't she too forward?
Well... the first one who approached me
was Ai...
Good, keep licking it like that.
Hey, Kouta-chan.
Do you also lick those girls' feet?
Yes.
They also made you do something like that?
What good childhood friends you have there.
What are you going to do?
Don't you want to put it in?
Hey, don't break the rules!
It's payback!
I can't hold back from anal.
Hey, Kouta! If you do something like that, I'm gonna—
No!
My asshole is spreading like that...!
You can't do something like this.
Didn't I tell you... not to tease... my asshole?
Put your finger in deeper.
Kouta-chan, I want you to push it in hard.
My asshole feels so good!
Push it in more, make me cum!
What should we do?
Do you want to join in?
I don't want to.
If we do that... then...
How about we just blend with them?
Hitomi-chan, I think 'mixed' would be a better way to say it.
Kou-chan, I'm worried about his weakness.
Can he overcome it with something like that?
Good work with your class, Enchou-sensei.
Good work today!
Well... I'm not going to be able
to take you for gym class today.
Isn't that what you're always doing?
What are you busy with anyway?
I'm sure you can find something to do, like self study, cleaning
or something else useful around here, ok?
Heh!
Well, I'll leave you to it.
I'll—
I'll eat my lunch outside!
I can't eat my lunch in peace with that kind of pressure back there.
It's a nice day today.
Hi-Hitomi?
What are you doing?!
I've caught the criminal!
Damn, how do you know this place?
And how did you get here so quickly?
I just tracked you up here.
On our ranch, we're always tracking missing foals.
F-Foals?
Nevermind that, Kouta!
You're having sex with Sensei, right?
No—
No, that's not...
It's not like that...
Why's that?
Why don't you want to do it with us?
When Hikaru-sensei came here,  I didn't notice that she was taking you away from us.
I really want to do it, but why are you always running away?!
That's because...
It's not that I hate Hitomi-chan, but the timing wasn't—
You hate me, right? That's because I was born without meat like this.
M-Meat?
That's okay.
I'll forgive you, if you do that with me.
Th-That's—
No excuse!
Why don't you lick it?
Kouta-kun's tongue is—
The first time, I was the one who licked you.
I was surprised when your penis got big from my licking.
Kouta-chan's tongue is touching my clit-chan.
I want you to lick it really hard.
Kouta, you're getting better at this.
You're licking that part...
Inside...
That place—
I'm dripping wet from the way you're licking down there.
My pervert juice is—
It's coming out from it!
Having my pussy licked in broad daylight like this—
My clitoris is being teased—
Cumming!
I'm going to cum from Kouta-chan's tongue!
Next, I want Kouta-chan to do it with your penis.
It's my chance!
Kouta?
Sorry, Hitomi! But I want to eat my lunch!
There's no one... coming back here.
Damn, I just want to eat my lunch in peace!
This is... Isn't this a poster of the idol who's debuting in adult video?
Lucky!
There's more.
Was Enchou-sensei the one who dropped these?
Found it.
Hm... In here.
The next one—
Wow, sexy!
Welcome, Kouta-kun.
Damn it, it's a trap?!
I knew you'd fall for something like that.
Is it okay for you to keep running away from us?
I know that sometimes we pester you, or tease you too much.
I have to admit that.
But,
when Hikaru-sensei stole you from us,
it really irritated me!
M-Mature woman—
No, because she's older than me...?
Do you really want to do it with Sensei that much?
If that's so, then you could have a foursome with us.
I... I still want to live a bit longer.
I'm sure you'll be fine, Kouta-kun.
As I thought, this guy is really healthy.
Good afternoon.
It's been a while, Kouta-kun's penis.
Then—
It's still a—
If I just—
This... This is bad.
Doing something like this.
I really love the texture of this penis.
It's something that a girl's body doesn't have...
How should I put it?
It's pretty strange to us.
I don't know much about it.
I've been doing my research about it.
I want you to feel really good.
There, it's already this hard.
I can feel it getting big.
You can feel my touch, right?
Kouta-kun's penis is really pretty.
It's beautiful.
R-Really?
Let me taste it a bit.
Kouta-kun, you're so sensitive!
It's tasty.
I want you to feel good from my tits, ok?
R-Rui?
Is she dead?
My head hurts... Can I have some medicine—
Wait, Rui?
What's the matter?
Kouta-kun, more... I want more of it!
I'm sorry.
But, you looked like you were having a good time in there.
Well... that's ok.
It's been a while since the two of us have been together like this, right?
R-Really?
That because, Kou-chan,
you've been avoiding us lately.
That thing is—
I want to do it
with Kou-chan right now.
Isn't—
Isn't it almost time to go home and study?
Didn't you say that you always studied at night?
Well... I have to prepare dinner or get the bath ready.
That's your father's responsibility, right?
Your family doesn't want to burden you with something like that at home.
Isn't that what your family always do?
But... Rui might come here soon.
She's still sleeping in the infirmary.
There's a chance that Hitomi might come in to the library!
That shouldn't be a problem.
Hitomi-chan is allergic to old books.
Then, what should I do right now?
I want you to mess with my body again.
I can't wait any longer.
It might seem perverted,
but you always take your time when doing it.
I think that this part is important after all.
That's ok, you can do whatever you like.
Hey, bite it... I want you to bite on my nipples.
Kou-chan is teasing my breasts.
You're such a pervert!
My pussy is...
already dripping wet, right?
It's your fault, you know?
That I'm drenched this way.
No—
You're touching my perverted thing.
That place... will be drenched a lot.
Don't—
Next,
I'll do it... for you.
I feel so dirty right now.
It's your pussy after all,
of course it would be dirty.
No way... That can't be... It's ordinary.
Am I... really addicted to something like this?
I'm dripping wet like this...
That's because you never masturbate.
Of course I masturbate by myself.
That's because you're not there for me, so I do it by myself.
Then, why's your pussy so wet now?
That's...
That's because you're extremely perverted, aren't you?
I'm perverted, but this is normal!
Your penis is getting big.
I'm also feeling hot.
Cumming... I'm cumming!
Even though she said that no one's home so we could do this,
I'm surprised you said that.
That's because I get worried when doing it in school.
There... in there... I want you to stir it up.
Make me dirtier!
It's hot... Kou-chan's penis is hot!
Even your pussy is—
My pussy... feels... so good!
Tease my breasts too,
I want you to squash them.
Though they're not as big as Rui's breasts—
I don't care about that!
Kou-chan's penis feels good!
Push it in... more... more!
More—
It feels really good!
Your penis is penetrating me!
You're coming deep inside me!
I want you to move more inside me.
No—
Your penis inside me—
Kou-chan, you're getting big again.
You're... getting big again.
It's hot, my pussy is burning.
It's gonna break apart!
A-Ai, inside... Can I cum inside you today?
It's ok... inside me... if it's Kou-chan.
Inside is good!
It's out... It came out!
Inside me... that hot, sticky stuff...
Self
Study
Sniff... sniff.
Hitomi-chan, didn't you say that you did not like the library?
It's like... the scent.
The scent of what?
There's a scent that I don't like mixing with the scent I like the most.
Eh?
That's true.
I can smell a living thing within those scents, right?
Hm... hm.