Sign: Only 14 more days until this year’s **
A little more to the right.
Think a little more about balance!
The School Festival is the crowning jewel of our school activities.
I will not have slacking off!
I have been waiting a long time for this big event.
I think it's time to have some fun.
W
Hypnosis
Humiliation School
Episode Three
Group
Hypnosis
Yes? What is it?
I have something from the faculty lounge.
May I hand it over?
No, you may not.
Don't enter without my permission.
Here you go.
Actually, from our side...
From Shirogane-san...
She came to discuss you.
She did?
She came to discuss ME?
She was concerned that you were overloaded with stress, and wanted me to have a talk with you.
Shirogane-san really trusts you as her secretary.
She... trusts me?
You need to open up your heart, for her sake.
Open... my heart...
So think of me as Shirogane-san, and talk to me.
You are... the president...
That's right.
I'm Shirogane Reika.
To you, that is.
You're the president...You're Shirogane Reika...
Thanks to you, the student council will be fine.
I thank you for that.
Don't say that... The pleasure is all mine in helping you, President.
Arinime, I had no idea you liked me that much.
Why did I kiss you?
We're both girls...
Because it's you, Arinime, I can speak of even my deepest secrets.
Your secrets?
Yes.
Don't be shocked.
But to be honest...
I've got one of these.
Is that... a man's...
Isn't it gross? I'm a girl.
Th-that's not it at all...!
So you see, I want it to be our secret.
Our... secret?
I'm scared.
It's thick...and tastes strange.
Arinime, you're pretty good at that.
Well, come to me.
Ichiru.
Your fingers... are... inside me...
Ichiru, I had no idea you were such a slut.
No...I'm not a slut...
Arinime Ichiru loves cocks.
And wants her pussy to feel good as well.
Am I not right?
I want to... feel good... with you, President.
That makes me happy, Ichiru.
Then let's go a bit further.
I wish I could do this while looking at your face.
Well... it's too embarrassing.
That hurts.
Since this is your first time... can I take your virginity?
Yes.
If it... pleases you.
Then, I'll take it.
What... that hurts...
Shirogane Reika's cock is now within Ichiru's pussy.
Your cock is... inside...
Your cock... it hurts so much...
That's because it's your first time.
Do you want me to stop?
Please, don't stop.
President, your cock is hitting me so deep.
Yes, I feel it too, Ichiru.
You’re just so... big...
That feels great!
Does it hurt?
It does, but...
Ichiru, your body... I want it to feel better.
That makes me so happy, Reika-sama!
President, I'm so hot.
That makes two of us.
Ah, that's right.
Yes, yes.
About the School Festival.
Yes?
All of the other clubs were being so greedy about their own wants...
School Festival Meeting minutes
It wasn't much of a "meeting"!
I think that bickering over the rules...can't be avoided.
Umm, President...
About last month's Counseling plan.
You mean the advice sessions?
Yes.
Fujimi-sensei says that if it's part of the School Festival, he'll help us out.
Oh.
And so...he had a request.
What?
He wanted you to observe him at work.
Observe... you say?
Good point.
If I can get a more solid idea of what he does, then perhaps I can give permission.
Please do this, President.
I'm supposed to do it?
To be visited by the president herself.
This makes me a bit nervous.
It’s not that I doubt you, Sensei.
It's just that in order to approve of your plan, I need official school permission.
I get it.
And experiencing a counseling session firsthand is the best way to be certain.
I have no problems, however. Am I still an acceptable subject?
I think I've told you this before, but there are such things as problems we are unaware of.
Drawing out these subconscious anxieties is my job.
That tea has relaxing properties. And it's not bad tasting either, I'd say.
Yes... you're... right...
Now then, let us begin.
Shirogane-san, I know that you disapprove of me.
I think you see that your strong point is that you are a good leader.
However, part of your job was stolen by me.
That's how you feel, right?
Yes.
But if that's the case, then you must set an example for everyone else by at least taking a counseling session with me.
Listen to me and do as I say.
Do you understand?
Yes.
First, you must accept me as your councilor.
"Accept"?
You must openly do as I say.
Without prejudice.
Openly?
Yes.
Take down the walls around your heart.
And be yourself.
Umm... why are you...
In counseling, it's important for the hearts to communicate.
And this is the fastest way to establish that connection.
But... I don't think this is...
This is just a massage.
So relax.
And just let the good feelings flow.
I do feel it... I'll give you that much...
Good, good. Empty your mind of unnecessary thoughts.
No! ...Not my breasts...
Reika, your tits... they're so big and soft.
Is this something... you do to everyone else?
I can't tell you that. Patient confidentiality and all.
But that's...
No!
What are you doing now?
Wh...where do you think you're...?!
You're pretty wet.
Don't... it's so dirty...
I've never even touched it.
You've never masturbated?
I could never... be so naughty...
But the student president has to set an example for all students.
You must at least masturbate.
Now. Let's practice masturbating.
I don't want to... do... no, I don't...
Doesn't it feel good?
But I shouldn't!
Masturbating makes you wet down here.
With the next step, you'll feel even more pleasure.
This thing I'm holding up, you know what it is, right?
Yes, I do.
It's... a penis...
Yes, we'll use it to make you feel even better.
Umm... but I'm... not ready...
Don't worry. I won't go THAT far.
It's so... so very hot...
I mustn't do this. It's wrong.
It's not wrong
Didn't I tell you at the start?
Tell me what?
That you needed to be open, and listen to everything I say.
But this is disgusting.
Passing judgment is not a good thing.
Calling it "disgusting" – that's the sort of prejudice I was talking about.
But...
This is too...
Just open your heart... and make certain.
Make... certain?
No... this feels too good!
Until our next counseling session, I'm assigning you some homework.
Home... work?
Yes. Use the Internet or whatever you wish to do a little research.
Where does this go?
Ahhh, I'm wiped.
Sign: School Festival
Oh, this way!
That's right.
Ahhh, secure that side good and tight.
Presently, those working on decorations are doing well.
Everyone has been working hard since early this morning.
It's nice that the school is decorated and all, but what's most important are the club booths.
I wonder what's wrong with them?
Um, President, that reminds me, how was counseling?
Fujimi-sensei talked to you, right?
I think... it'll be okay
You "think"?
W-well, I think I wasn't focused enough.
I fell asleep a bit...
Oh, really?
I have things to do. Make sure no one is late to class.
Why?
Why does it consume my mind so much?
I must... go to the counseling room quickly.
Hi, Shirogane-san.
Good... morning.
Um, am I bothering you?
Not at all.
As you can see, I'm free.
The weather is so nice today.
Let's go have our session on the roof.
Well then, did you do your homework?
I did... my research.
So you typed it into a search engine?
The word "fellatio".
Y-yes.
Very good.
Then why don't you show me what you've learned?
Oh, did you really research it?
Or did you read a little, then get embarrassed and close the browser?
I'm sorry.
I did as you said and looked it up,
But when I saw the pictures, I...
Never mind.
I'll take the time to teach you.
Well, you may call me Toshikazu.
Toshikazu-san?
Yes. That's the way, Reika.
Does it turn you on? If so, you can touch yourself.
Move your tongue faster.
Yes, sir.
What's wrong? I think you've gotten good.
Your penis... is throbbing... and it's turning me on
I'm impressed. Very good for a first time, Reika.
Reika, your fellatio is perfect
Thank you... sir.
Reika, that's enough.
Toshikazu-san, your penis is so hot and hard.
That's because your tits feel so good.
That makes it hot and hard.
I make it feel good?
That's right.
Has anyone ever told you that?
No. I've never done this before.
I can tell you're starting to feel it too.
Your nipples are so hard.
My... nipples...
Just like a man, if you feel good, they get hard.
Not there...
See? You;re getting hard here, too.
No... not there...
Don't touch it so much!
Does it feel good?
But you mustn't forget what your tits are doing.
Yes, Toshikazu-san, I want you to be turned on.
I'm impressed. Reika, you're a natural.
Stop it. Don't touch it so much.
Reika, your pussy is drenched with naughty juice.
Well, it just feels too good!
Don't! Don't take them off.
No... don't look at it.
Reika, lots of juice is flowing from your pussy.
No. Please, don't touch it. It's dirty!
It's not dirty at all.
Your pussy and butthole are pink, and very pretty.
No!
Hey, Reika, I want your virginity.
Is that okay?
My virginity?
Now, hold your legs out.
Toshikazu-san... will take my virginity?
My cock can't hold back anymore.
It's touching my pussy.
You're plenty wet enough.
I'm coming in.
No... ouch, that hurts!
Does it? Should I stop?
I'll... be... okay.
I can take it.
Shirogane Reika...
Reika offers you her virginity.
Good.
So hot!
It's so...
It's so deep.
This is... Toshikazu-san's...
Amazing. You're so tight.
Hold on just a bit more.
That hurts!
I'll break apart!
Your insides are so hot.  My cock is going to melt off.
I'm so hot... you're rubbing me... I'm burning!
This means that you and I are one now, Reika.
But it hurts... so much...
My head is... blacking out...
Reika, I want to cum inside.
I'm cumming inside.
Inside?
Your semen?
It will turn you on.
Turn me on! Turn me on more!
It's so hot...so much hot stuff is flowing inside me.
Hi, I've been waiting for you.
Arinime!
President.
I contacted her a little while ago.
Your beloved President, I'm going to show her a good time.
Come to the roof after we're finished.
Ever since you took my virginity, President my body won't dry off.
And I've been studying sex in hopes of pleasing you.
Your virginity? What are you talking about?
Arimine...
You see, you took her virginity.
I'm sure you don't believe it, though.
But I never... not with Arimine...
Toshikazu-san, you must have done something.
Maybe I did, maybe I didn't.
But as long as we're up here, let's have a good time as a threesome.
Since I received the student president's approval, I've earned the trust of the entire student body.
Students and teachers alike are coming to my conference room with more problems.
My preparations are sufficient.
Let's push this event forward.
Good morning!
What's that noise?
What?
Releasing cries of lust... that is a sound from the Heavens.
While you're in this school, your heart and body are free.
Student council office
You're a class officer! Why are you dressed like that?
My father likes it...
What are you talking about?
President, for the success of the School Festival, I think it's a bad idea to have officers like this walking around.
But she looks cute. I think it's acceptable.
We must not bind ourselves down – we must release ourselves.
Wouldn't you like to try it too?
Try what?
Yes... I would.
Sis... don't call me so suddenly...
But all the girls have been called to the baseball club.
Me too. I'm supposed to be at the calligraphy club.
I'm sorry. I promised these guys I'd see them.
Do a good job, will ya? My little sisters are here!
Why did you stop suddenly?
That was my first kiss.
Really?
That was your first?
I'm disappointed because the counseling session plan didn't go through.
But I'd still like to help out at the School Festival.
I'm so pleased.
Everyone else will be so happy.
Do you think that we could use the candle I mentioned earlier?
I've distributed them throughout the entire school.
Classrooms lit intimately with sweet scents – how wonderful!
Toshikazu-san!
Since you're letting me participate, I’m going to do as much as I can.
School Festival
Reception
Oh, what a nice smell.
You're right.
I wonder what scent that is.
If you wish to take the tour, please start at that room.
Patrons of today’s Festival, we have only just begun with the festivities.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Fortune telling house
Sign: Hit a bull’s eye and win SEX
What a thick cock.
Aim here!
Harder...
Oh! Not so... rough...
Aim here
My pussy...
Yes!
Good. Right on target.
So you get another go at her!
You mustn't. I'm sorry.
Menu: Coffee, tea, hot sandwich, sausage wrapped in tits, fellatio
Master, how does the inside of my pussy feel?
Master, your dick is so hard and delicious.
My tits... are insufficient.
But I hope they please you, Master.
Looks like a big success.
At this rate, the Main Event will also be...
Sign: School Festival Live Presentations
What a wonderful scene!
Aphrodesiac is merely a stepping stone.
A human's basic feeling is sexual lust.
My experiment was a big success.
Toshikazu-san!
This feels great!
How is it, Reika?
Do you like being aroused by all these people?
I'm so grateful.
Everyone gets to watch you fuck me!
Isn't it perfect?
This is what a heart-to-heart connection is.
Yes!
Sensei, go deeper!
Not my butt...
I'll help you cum.
I need to practice more for her.
Oh, Dad, that hurts! Be more gentle!
My hypnosis is quite something!
Everyone is just an animal.
Even the snooty rich girls have become horny sows.
This is the best School Festival ever.
I hope you all enjoy it!