Well...
Sakuma-san, could you clean
this up with your mouth?
Why should I do that?
Isn't it because of Sakuma-san
that my dick became like this?
What are you saying? Isn't that because of yourself?
Ah.. Being told off like that,
I want to release it out again.
Just hold it in, If you're a good adult.
I'm sorry.
Yamamoto-san, you can't do that.
Yes, I want to with Sakuma-san-
You want to release it together, right?
Not only yourself, but you want Sakuma-san to release it too. That's a wonderful.
This is totally strange!
Yes, It's strange.
Sakuma-san, Isn't that why you came here, to release
all of your pain from your daily life?
Eh? Yes, It is.
Then why don't you let Yamamoto-san
help you out with that-
You're embarrassed aren't you, Sakuma-san?
To conquer your embarrassment,
you need to release it all out.
I understand.
If I help this person to release,
then I'll help myself to release it too, right?
Yes, that's it.
Can you do that?
I can do that.
What a disgusting man he is,
Hasn't he ever taken a bath?
I can't believe it.
But if I don't do it, then I'll be forced to have sex again.
It.. It tastes horrible.
Wha.. What?
Sakuma-san's asshole-
No-!
Don't lick at that place.
If you're this wet,
Then it's okay, right?
Wa.. Wait-
No, you can't!
Please!
Please let me go!
I don't want to pose like this.
I don't want it!
With men like them-
being like this-
for sex.
How beautiful...
Yes, It's truly...
to release, Isn't it?
You have to endure it, Riko.
It's for helping Anna.
Anna...
W
I'm sorry mother, to have use my name
in place like this.
But being a sister for Anna is a difficult task.
So, forgive me.
It's for helping Anna.
Ah, I found it!
It's still only a little space on this, though...
It's just the beginning from now on Anna.
That's true, You're finally starting a job as a Gravure Idol.
So I need to stand behind you, Right?
Thank you. Even though for now I am just the little sister of Ichinose Riko, Ex Top Model.
Even for me, I'm just a person from the past.
No,
Onee-chan will always be the legendary top model.
But, someday I'll surpass you.
That's the spirit, you can't go on without that
in entertainment life.
Yes, then I'll go now.
Be careful.
Anna hasn't come back home for a week.
Anna never does anything like this.
She's not at her friends or relatives houses.
Where did you go, Anna?
Anna as a Gravure Idol not wanted for big jobs,
It's difficult for her.
That's when those people came.
Self-Enlightement Seminar, BELIEVES LABORATORY.
The chairman, Majima Zenko.
Rank A for Upper Class,
Boarding Course.
Anna is in there.
Morning, Sakuma-san.
I can't resist your thrilling face.
Oh.. Your angry face is good as well.
Today in this course room,
You'll receive your lesson.
This is Sakuma Sachiko-san
who'll join us in the middle class.
She's having difficulty controlling her sexual desire.
Please to meet you.
Well everyone, please take off your clothes.
Wha.. What're you people doing?
What is it, release isn't it?
That's why all of you took off your clothes?
Sakuma-san, In the lower class we do a lot of counseling.
But, in this middle class we experienced the real thing.
How is that related with being naked like this?
With just being sit down down in chair,
How you could possibly ease your worries of it?
Here.
Would you stop that!
Eh, If your sexual desire is that strong,
Wouldn't you be happy to see a cock?
I understand you, Sakuma-san.
It's difficult to live with strong sexual desire like that.
You're ashamed and you had no one to talk to,
Then you're suffered from it.
It must have been hard.
Ye.. Yes.
But now, Sakuma-san...
You don't have to be ashamed anymore.
Eh?
When you're in the middle class,
you can let it all out.
What do you mean by that?
From middle class on,
It will be real practice on releasing it.
Eh?
In this middle class, If you're together in the conquest of your sexual desires,
It will be easier for you to release it.
I.. I can't do something like that.
Then would you go back to the lower class?
It seems for Sakuma-san it's still
too early for real practice.
It look's like our judgement
was wrong about her.
I'm sorry for that.
I understand.
Can you do it?
I.. I'll do it.
Should we leave it at this for now?
No, I'll keep going.
Is this okay?
Please put down your hand.
You can't release it by hiding it.
Sa..Sakaki Sensei, I can't hold it anymore.
I understand.
Takeda-san, please release with all that you have.
It's ok to release it when it comes.
Ye..Yes.
Yes, release it out for today.
What are you doing?!
Let's us release together, right?
Stop it!
Please don't rub your thing like that.
It's make me dirty!
Sa..Sakuma-san, you wouldn't say that
if your sexual desire was that strong.
What are you talking about?
Sakuma-san's sexual desire makes
me want to release it out.
Don't say want you want.
Sakuma-san, do you really have
strong sexual desire?
Then why you're resisting like this?
Is it because of me?
It's not something like that.
I..I understand.
It's disgusting, I can't let this thing inside my mouth.
Sakuma-san, please let Yamamoto-san release it out.
While we're at it-
Is it over, right?
What are you doing?!
Wait, what are you doing?
No, stop it!
Please don't just watch it.
Stop this person!
No, put it out!
Put it out!
Yamamoto-san, let your heart break free.
Well, let it release now.
Yes.
No~!
Good afternoon, everyone.
Everyone who's having difficulty with desire is already in the middle class,
That's why from now on you need to decide,
your own sexual desire releases.
Anna is in upper class which already
entering the boarding course.
I need quickly get to a higher rank...
Then, why not Sakuma-san show us women's fluid.
Eh?!
Wh..Why's that?
If you expose something by yourself,
It would make your release a lot better.
Something indecent like that, I can't do that.
I think it's better for you to return to the lower class.
I..understand.
Sakuma-san, please change your clothes to this.
I can..put it on?
Sato-san isn't that familiar with
a women's naked body.
Wh..Why should I have to dress like this?
You're beautiful, Sakuma-san.
You're like figurine.
Don't put people on the same level with a doll.
Well Sakuma-san, would you sit
down and open your legs.
Yes.
In front of these disgusting men,
I have to pose like this...
Would you like to go home?
Well then, Open your bloomers
and release your pussy fluid.
I can't do something like that.
It's really troublesome, Sakuma-san isn't willing
to release her heart.
Sakuma-san, we're here only to help you release it-
But, being able to release and being made a higher rank
It will be your decision.
That's right, I need to rank-up
and catch up with Anna.
I'll do it.
Why don't you release it more?
No~!
No, stop that!
I'll help you release with that.
Please stop that!
Hey..hey..your sexual desire is strong, right?
Yes..
With strong sexual desire like that,
wouldn't she want more than that?
Huh?
St..Stop it.
If you keep resisting like that,
You can't release anything.
That's the way it is.
Then let me release it too.
It's impossible for a big thing like that.
It's nothing, it's only hard the first time.
No~ It's gonna rip it!
Stop moving it!
I can't hold it!
I'll release it!
Wait!
The..The next one is my turn.
It..It's not getting in, that's why the real one...
You're still gonna continue?
Please let me go.
Sato-san, right now you can touch
a woman's body...
It's okay, you can do it.
What are you doing?
Thank you so much.
I don't want it, why with this man-
What an emotional situation...
Stop it, please!
Eh, It's coming out again?
I don't want it anymore...
It's coming in again.
Then, If you would like to move it first.
Why don't you lower your hips by yourself.
I can't do something like that.
That's a shame, If Sakuma-san could release it by herself,
She could continue to the special course.
Eh, special course?
To meet..to meet with Anna.
I'll do it.
That's a great release, isn't it?
I'll release it too.
Me..me too.
Not anymore...
No~!!
With this...
I could go to the special course, right.
Anna, did you go through the
same experience as I did?
Tomorrow is quick photo session, isn't it?
Why you don't go to your room and get some sleep?
But today, I want to sleep with Onee-chan.
I still need to dry my hair, so it may take a lot of time.
Yes, I'll wait here.
If you're waiting then you're not sleeping, right?
I want to look at Onee-chan.
What is it Anna? You're acting strange.
Eh?
Did you got fever? Why don't you take a cold pill
and quickly get some sleep.
Tha..That's right, maybe...
I'll take a pill.
On the way, you should go to your own room.
Okay.
Onee-chan...
What is it?
No, It's nothing.
Good night.
That time, Anna was worried about something
and she wanted to share it with me.
If I just listened to her that time...
Anna...
My one and only sweetest little sister
in the world.
Finally It's special course,
If I'll just rank-up in here-
I'll go to Anna's place.
As I expected of a special course.
Between these people, how many
will go to the upper class?
Good morning, everyone.
Finally today, in this seminar, you'll receive special lesson from our chairman,
Majima Zenko.
Majima Zenko, If I could make an impression in front of him
I definitely could rank-up myself.
Then, Zenko Sensei's appearance.
Zenko-sama's voice.
Where is he?
It's Zenko-sama!!
Zenko-sama is right here.
It's a blessed..a blessed.
Wha..What is this?
BELIEVE!
It's totally strange with this group of people.
That ugly and disgusting man up there.
He pretending to be a saint or something like that.
What you're doing always failed or
the first time never did anything.
Do any of you think like that?
That's because inside yourself,
you build a limit within yourself.
My BELIEVES LABORATORY,
Will help you take down that limit within you.
Then..Let's all release together!
Now way, that man is really using hypnotism.
Release!!
What's gonna happen right now?
Is this the truth of these people?
This is the truth of release.
Majima Zenko.
You need to release it too, Sakuma Sachiko-san.
No, It's Ichinose Riko-san.
Wh..Why do you know my name?
There's nothing I don't know about anything.
I could say that you're looking for someone.
Did you know that I was looking for someone?
If you want to know, release it out.
Re..lease...
That's right, then...
In front of this man like who's like a water rag,
I have to get naked.
But, this man is this groups leader.
If I can do it with this man,
I'll go to Anna's place.
Then, let's start with swallowing my cock.
Ye..Yes.
The energy which come out from my cock,
will give everything that you want.
Soon you're gonna understand it too.
Then, let's release it!
You need to drink it, from that you will receive
a way that leads you to your release.
Is it okay with this?
Well, let's continue to the next release!
Wait a minute!
Now let's begin!
No, That big thing won't fit.
It's coming in.
My cock is much larger than the average cock out there,
enjoy your time thoroughly with it.
I don't want it again,
It will be the last time.
Look, It's all the way in.
Here you go, release with all your mighty.
It hurts!
My grateful cock will rip out your lovely pussy.
That's because I want to enter upper class.
With this powerful hips like this,
my cock is soon gonna explode.
That's...
Let's release it, accept all of it!
Release!!
N..No..Stop it...
Stop it!!!
Finally, next would be the boarding course.
It's gonna be fun.
There will be more release on it.