Ow ow ow!
Nurakoshi, what the hell are you doing?
Nothing suspicious-! Rather, I'm not doing anything!
You were peeping at the female student passing by!
No, it's not just her. You're peeping at all the female students in the class!
There's no way I would...
S-She's spot on!
Listen here, I just don't want any problems.
I don't want you messing up my schedules, so I can't have delinquents like you roaming about!
Y-You're gonna pull it off! It's gonna rip!
Don't come out of the classroom! Don't even leave your seat!
But I might have to go to the toilet...
Just go where you're sitting, and clean it up afterward!
N-No way, that's crazy-!
Ow! Please don't pull!
This is my final advice: don't talk back to me!
I'll get you back...
Gitai Saimin Zenpen
Episode 01
You have to stretch properly...
Whoa, this sure is nice...
Do you want to get in the pool that much?
Well, of course I do! Then I can brush past some girls and...
I can't believe someone like her can be a teacher! Geez...
But if I can keep looking at girls like this...
I can't help but imagine things!
Study period
Hey, Na-chan.
Hmm?
Isn't it strange that Kasuga-sensei is issuing study periods so suddenly?
Oh, according to rumors, she's not getting along with her husband too well...
Huh?
Hitomi-chan? Are you fantasizing about something lewd?
N-No! I was just wondering if we're getting enough lessons for the tests...!
Nurakoshi-kun is a bit disgusting, but this...
It's a bit mean.
Darn it! Why do I have to be so irritated about all of this?!
Reina-san, are you awake?
Reina-san~?
What do you want?
Would you mind if I come over to your bed?
Huh? Don't say things like that unless you're sleep talking... Wha-?
What are you-? Hey, stop it!
Wait-! S-Stop it!
Y-You're annoying!
Why am I annoying?
T-That's because...
Reina-san, I love you.
N-No, we can't-!
But it looks like you want me to play with you.
Even before I began touching you.
I-I said that we can't!
No, no, no, no!!
Your love juices smell great Reina-san.
A-Aren't you satisfied? Why don't you go the bed?
You're the only one who's satisfied...
Oh, maybe you're not satisfied either.
N-No! I said that we can't! W-Why won't you stop?
I can't cum, I mustn't cum!
Darling-!
Huh?
Do you want me to keep going, Reina-san?
What are you saying?!
Then do you want me to stop?
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
You came for the first time.
If you keep doing this-!
I'm putting it in, then.
D-Don't!
Why not?
That's because...
Is today dangerous? That can't be, can it? It's not the end of the month yet...
Y-You idiot!
Then why can't we?
T-That's because...
I just came, and it would feel too good...
That's why I want to.
Your cock, your cock feels so good!
Reina-san! I love you! I really do, Reina-san!
This is amazing!
T-This is too good-! I'm going to lose it!
If you keep going, I'll lose it! I really will!
Now we're a real couple, Reina-san!
It's-! It's so good!
This feels too good!
It's amazingly good!
Really? I'm glad!
Souichirou-san, d-don't move so much!
I'm happy that you like it!
Your cock feels so great when it rubs me deep inside!
This... This feels so good! It really does!
H-How about this?
Sure thing.
Reina-san, I love you.
I-I-It can't be so. It can't be, it can't be, it can't be!
What happened?
Who knows.
Haruka, what's wrong?
It's nothing...
A-Akari, you're nearly visible as well.
Huh? What do you mean?
U-Um, your swimsuit...
What?!
What happened?
Na-chan, I wonder what that was all about...
I'm sorry that this is so sudden, but... Hitomi-chan, um...
N-No, it's not like I don't want to do this. I was just surprised because it's so sudden...
U-Um, I've always liked you, Hitomi-chan...
Hitomi-chan, are you free after school?
Yes, after my club activities...
Then-! I'll be in the library.
Hey...
Huh?
I can believe that you'll accept my feelings... Right?
Yes...
Na-chan...
Hitomi-chan...
Your breasts are so soft, Hitomi-chan. They feel so good...
Na-chan, please don't get so feisty...
I can't?
It's not that...
But I want to do other amazing things with you, Hitomi-chan...
O-Other amazing things?!
Yes, other things...
Na-Na-chan, don't!
I-It feels too good there!
Your breasts are so wonderful, Hitomi-chan!
Let's move on to other amazing places!
O-Other amazing places?
Yes, other amazing places...
Na-Na-chan, it's dirty down there! I had P.E today, too...
It smells and tastes like it too!
Na-chan, stop it!
I won't stop, because I know you like it.
Whoa, your clitoris is swollen!
You're putting on an innocent face, but look at how indecent you are!
T-That's because-!
Maybe you masturbate using your clitoris too much?
I've never done that!
Masturbating using your clitoris... It's like a shining star, a star that's as beautiful as you!
Hey, Hitomi-chan... There's no need to hide it... Don't hide it from me.
I don't mind how much you like masturbating, or how large your clitoris has become from it...
I love everything about you!
What...
What?!
I can feel your warmth. Hitomi-chan...
Na-chan's thing is hitting mine...
We're both so lewd and wet...
Hitomi-chan, I don't think getting aroused is something to be ashamed of.
The reason you're so aroused is because you like me, isn't it?
Huh?
Was I wrong?
Ah, no...
Hitomi-chan...
I think you're right...
Hitomi-chan, that felt really good...
Na-chan... It felt good for me, too...
Hey guys, I went to the cake buffet restaurant from that magazine the other day...
That's so cool! You went there already?
Apparently the Monte Blanco cake is really good!
Then how about we go together next time?
Sounds good!
You'll need to camouflage your semen or they'll see it.
Oh yeah, thanks for looking out for me.
I don't mind. Your responsibility is mine.
The day I was abducted by aliens, my cock was transformed into this.
And this is my observer.
W-W-What the hell?!
W-Who are you guys?
Earthling, want to see, reproduction.
Huh?
Earthling, want to see, impregnate.
You, woman, impregnate, impregnate, impregnate.
Hey, hey!
Understood?
I get it. I get it, but...
Problem?
Yes, I do have a problem.
I want to impregnate women too, but I don't have the means to do so.
No genitals?
Huh?
What a strange dream...
What the hell?!
Genitals, power up.
Are you retarded?! What am I supposed to do with this?!
Change it back!
Power, will not work, immediately.
You, woman, impregnate.
I can't walk like this!
Cannot, difficult problem.
That's your problem!
Camouflage hypnosis.
Huh?
I've tried changing into a human body, since I can't talk well in my normal form.
Basically, your genitals have gotten a power up.
I randomly chose a person out of your memory. How is it?
Although this is just a human body made from the consumption of proteins,
However, I look like Akari to you.
So you'll help me...
Yes, I guess I'm going to.
Do it with girls?
Yes, will you not impregnate them for us?
My dream has come true! I shall impregnate them!
That feels good, Reina-san.
O-Of course it feels good, since I'm the one doing it.
I-It's amazing, Reina-san!
Reina-san, Reina-san!
Re-Reina-san-! I-I-I'm cumming-!
Hey, I bet you still want to cum from doing it in other places, don't you?
H-How's this? You better be grateful.
I'm very happy.
I don't mind doing this every day.
I would very much like you to.
B-But in return, you have to entertain me.
Of course, Reina-san.
I-I'm not just talking about every night...
I want you to take me out to dinner at least once a month, and we have to make seasonal trips too! A-And...
And?
O-On our anniversary, I want a present from you...
Yes, sure thing.
Since it's your request, Reina-san.
What a greedy and luscious woman!
She's hits me if she's not pleased at school, and on top of that, her demands are sky-high!
I really wouldn't want to marry such a woman!
Oh well, the one who's going to have a hard time is Souichirou.
Besides, this pig's unreasonably successful, so he probably won't have any trouble meeting demands.
Souichirou-san...
Do we have to keep going-?
I can't cum anymore...
Student Council Briefing Room
Reina-san, I made your lunch.
W-Well, I guess I'll take it, since you're at least good at cooking.
Reina-san, I poured you some coffee.
Y-You're being pretty thoughtful for such a guy! I guess I'll drink it for you, then.
Here you go, Reina-san.
Huh?
Isn't today your birthday?
He's not that attractive, and at first I honestly thought that I shouldn't marry him...
However, he's thoughtful, kind, good at cooking, and...
He's even good at sex! He does it so strongly!
Oh no! What should I do~?
Hey, we did it so many times last night.
Yes, I was watching.
She's got such a sex drive.
How's her impregnation coming along?
Unfortunately, it looks like she isn't pregnant yet.
This can't keep going!
What's wrong now?
Everything's wrong!
Even though I'm being so nice to her, all the credit goes to her husband!
That can't be helped...
Although it looked like you were having fun...
That was only at the beginning!
If she does it so much, it's like torture!
No matter how happy I make her, the credit goes to her pig-like husband!
You sure are agnostic about this...
Shut up, shut up! I need one who'll only appreciate me!
Hey Alien.
My name is Hikari...
Shut it, calling you Alien is good enough.
Anyhow, I've decided on my next target.
Sheesh, so forceful...