No... way...
Doutaro... the protagonist... went to Germany to study...
He is crying in the old church in Carosdel.
How did it become like this?
SubDESU-H
Machi Gurumi no Wana
Good morning!
Onee-chan!
Yui!
Hm?
While we're at school, you have to call me Sensei, remember?
Oh yeah, Takagi-sensei.
That sure was a strong gust of wind!
If you're not careful, the male students will see something!
I doubt that.
But there isn't a male student here who isn't interested in seeing your panties, Takagi-sensei!
When I was having a hard time getting jobs as a tutor,
I was introduced as a teacher to this Nansui Academy by my father’s friend.
My father is a clerk, and with Yui as a student, we go to this school.
I'll go ahead to my classroom, then!
G-Good morning!
She's an S huh?
An "S"? I wonder what he means...
Good morning to you, headmaster.
It seems you're doing well, Takagi-sensei.
Yes.
Since the students have entrance exams coming up,
please make sure they can concentrate.
Yes.
Do your best so that we don't have any students losing focus.
Understood.
What is this...?
Who did this?! Who pulled such a prank?
See ya!
Onee-chan!
Yui. You're on your way home?
Yep!
Anyway, there were some peeping photos on the board today, weren't there?
Yes, the staff room was in an uproar over who did it.
Isn't it obvious?
The culprit must be Murayama Kenji.
That can't be true!
Onee-chan, why are you defending him?
Is it because he's the son of the headmaster?
T-That is...
Yes, it's because Kenji-kun is the headmaster's son.
We can't say bad things about him.
Is it because you believe in him?
I... want to believe in him.
If onee-chan says that, then I won't keep bugging you.
Thanks for understanding, Yui.
I heard some interesting rumor about those photos...
It seems that Kenji is under suspicion.
Kenji says that it's hurt his feelings,
and he says that he doesn't have the will to study.
No way...
All of this is your fault, Takagi-sensei.
U-Umm...
If you don't mend his feelings,
I'll fire you and your whole family.
I-I understand, I'll fix it, so please just don't fire us.
Remember that everything is up to you.
I must do something,
I can't be a burden to Dad and Yui.
Kenji-kun!
So this is where you were.
What do you want?
Can I sit next to you?
Huh?
You didn't come to class, is my lesson...
that boring?
You suspect me of taking those photos, right?
No way! I'm always on your side.
I believe that you didn't take those photos.
Then show me some proof.
Proof?
The proof that shows that you're on my side.
W-What? How do I prove it?
It's easy!
W-What are you doing?!
If you make me cum with your hands, I'll believe you.
You're on my side, right?
Or was that a lie?
I-It wasn't a lie! I am on your side!
Then you'll do it, right?
It stinks...
For me to touch such a thing...
Sensei, hurry up!
F-Fine then.
It's.. getting hotter and bigger...
Rub my balls too, sensei.
N-No... Such an indecent shape...
Hurry, please... Hurry up and cum!
W-What are doing?
I'm going to splash your face with my semen, sensei!
No! Anything but that!
It stinks...
This is semen...?
Onee-chan? Why are you stopping?
Yui...
Did something happen?
Is someone bullying you?
No, it's nothing. I was just lost in my thoughts.
If so, then it's fine...
However, if there is someone bullying you, tell me okay?
I'll teach them.
Thanks, Yui.
I'm going ahead then!
I can't worry Yui or Dad,
since we can live as a family if I bear with this.
I'm not supposed to be sighing, but I feel kinda down.
Text = Newly received mail 1 article
No way!
There was someone watching?!
Who? Who would take such-?!
No-! W-Why?!
Text = If you don't follow the instructions, that photo will be leaked across the school campus.
Is the sender Kenji-kun?
No way, a teacher can't blame their students...
But... Who did such-
Atsuko.
D-Dad?
What's up?
You look pale.
I-It's nothing.
Oh really? Well, don't overexert yourself.
Yeah, sure.
No, I can't consult my dad...
I don't want him to worry about me further...
Why do I have to put on such clothes?
Text = Wear the costume that's inside the second drawer of the desk, don't wear a bra.
Y-You may start your test.
Is obeying the texts all I can do?
For me to lure Kenji-kun...
Sensei... You want me to touch them?
I-It hurts If you grab me so roughly-!
Even though I don't want this...
If I fight back, everyone will see those photos...
No!!
I-I'm sorry, I-!
You said that you were on my side.
Wait! Kenji-kun!
From that day on, Kenji-kun stopped coming to school.
I heard that you flung Kenji off of his chair during class.
T-That's because... Um...
What's your reason?!
Kenji says he shocked, and he refuses to come out of his room.
No way...
Normally, I would have fired you already.
Please! Don't do that!
I'll give you one last chance.
Get Kenji out of his room.
If you can do that, I might reconsider.
I understand...
Kenji-kun, I was wrong, so please forgive me.
Hmph.
What should I do for you to forgive me?
Isn't that obvious?
This...
Suck this, then I'll forgive you.
No way...
If you won't, then leave. I won't go to school.
We can't be pushed out of this town for my sake!
What are you doing to do then?
F-Fine then. I'll do what you say...
No... It stinks...
Amazing... This feels great...
This feels disgusting, I feel queasy... I don't want this!
I'm going to cum in your mouth, sensei...
N-No! Really, no!
No, no! Don't look!
You want me to forgive you... don't you?
I don't want to feel good, but my legs are paralyzed!
What's happening to me?
I can't hold back...
What?!
N-No...!
Stop! Stop it! Don't!
Dammit-
No way! Kenji-kun's penis is entering me!
I-It hurts! Please! Pull it out!
It hurts, but it's not only that, something inside me is-!
I'm cumming!
No! Don't! Don't release it inside!
Please, not inside!
I... have been defiled...
I want to go home!
Text = Stay with Kenji until morning.
Oh? You're not leaving?
Then, we can do it again, can't we?
Wait!
No-!
How long... is this going to go on?
All night... I was played with by Kenji-kun...
No!
Pervert!
No, your penis is filling me!
No, Kenji-kun! No more! If you keep going, I'll-!
Onee-chan, where were you?
Sorry, I had a ton of extra work, so I stayed over at school.
Oh... Is that so?
Yui? Are you feeling sick?
Huh? N-No! It's nothing! I'm fine!
If you're well...
Then that's good.
The blackmail kept coming.
Ones that said I had to let Kenji-kun molest me on the bus...
No! It's entering me!
It's going deep inside me!
No-!
Stop!
Everyone is watching!
W-Wait!
N-Not here!
N-No... Letting out so much...
Other ones that said I had to invite him for private tutoring at my house.
Hello there, Takagi-sensei.
Kenji-kun, you're here early...
Yeah, since you sent me a text...
Y-Yeah, I guess so.
L-Let's go to my room.
Atsuko?
D-Dad!
U-Umm... This is...
Oh? If it isn't Kenji-kun, the headmaster's son!
Sensei said she'd give me private tutoring...
Oh really?
How diligent.
S-So then, let's study.
By studying... You mean this, right?
Wha? That's...
Hey sensei... I have a request...
Huh?
I want to do you in this...
N-No! I can't!
You're the one who invited me.
A-Ah, f-fine.
In such places...
If Dad sees us...
So this is what a titfuck is like...
Lick the end!
My head is going blank!
Open your mouth, sensei...
His hot penis is entering my mouth!
This feels great!
Atsuko! I brought some tea...
Dad! No! Don't come in!
He can't see me like this!
Sensei... He's calling you...
Thanks Dad, but we're fine without tea for the time being...
What are you doing, Kenji-kun?!
What am I doing? I'm putting it in since you're overflowing, of course.
No! Don't put it in!
What's wrong, Atsuko?
Atsuko? Is something wrong? Talk to me!
We'll have tea when we finish studying...
So just leave it outside the door, please!
O-Okay, got it.
It's coming in-!
It's rubbing against my insides, so hot...
No! Don't! Don't mess up my insides!
Your insides feel great when you squeeze me!
I'm gonna cum soon, okay?
No! If you cum inside me, I'll feel funny!
No, don't cum! If you pour it inside me, I'll-!
What... is going to happen to me?
This can't go on, but who is sending me the texts?
What?
Text = If you don't follow the instructions, I will leak the photos across the school campus.
I wonder what it's about... Maybe the sender will be there?
I-Is anyone there?
I-I came alone, like the text said.
W-Who is it?
What?
Dad?
W-Why are you here?
Atsuko?
What does this mean?
Why is Dad here?
What's wrong?
Um, well...
It's odd for someone to be at school at this hour,
did you forget something?
Y-Yes! That's right, I suddenly remembered something important...
This is Dad... right?
Something important... like these photos?
No way!
Why does Dad have them?
Did you come here because you wanted to feel good?
You look more and more like your mother, Atsuko.
Dad?
The voice I heard from your room, it was just like your mother's.
No way! That's a lie!
Can you let Dad hear your voice again?
No way... No way!
N-No!
What are you doing Dad!? Stop it!
You don't need to be worried, Atsuko.
Just leave it to Dad.
N-No!
No! Please Dad!
Dad, no, don't!
Atsuko, does this feel good? Atsuko...
N-No!
Dad's penis is getting hot, it's hitting me...
No! Dad! Please stop this!
Atsuko, you're overflowing already!
No, no! That's not true!
Dad, stop this...
I shouldn't be doing such things with my father...
But I can't apply any strength to fight back!
Dad-!
Why? Why do I feel good when Dad licks me?
Not ther-!
I came... Dad made me feel too good...
No-!
Atsuko, will you make Dad feel good too?
No... No Dad!
I'm your daughter! I'm not mom!
We shouldn't be doing this!
It's entering me!
Dad's penis is entering my deepest spots...
Your penis feels good. Doing such things with Dad inside the classroom...
I'll fail as a teacher, we'll fail as a family!
My pussy is quivering from your thrusting, Dad!
No Dad, if you thrust into me further, I'll feel funny-!
Dad, oh no! Someone is coming!
Huh? Yui...?
Onee-chan... Dad...?
No Yui... Dad don't!
Atsuko, Atsuko!
Y-Yui, this isn't what you think!
No, even though Yui is looking, my pussy won't stop!
You can't look, I'm about to cum, I'm going to cum!
My mind is going blank!
Yui, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!!!