As the train runs through the city,
you're hemmed in by a crowd of strangers.
A bunch of people you don't want to be touched by.
Even cute girls are shoving you...
You must not touch the skin of those maidens.
Hirata Megumi
Occupation: Second-year college student
Blood Type: AB
Hobby: Collecting stuffed toys
In this enclosed space within society,
This lonely city makes your son grieve.
Katou Youko
Occupation: Part-timer
Blood Type: O
Hobby: Seeing her favorite band live
You're damned if you touch,
and you're damned if you don't.
Kashiwagi Reiko
* squad of * Railroad Company
Blood Type: A
Hobbies: Reading books,
listening to music
If you don't listen to me, "the finger" will attack you.
molester group
Chikan Juunintai
Ten
At that time,
I didn't know anything.
I didn't know what was going to happen.
I just believed in my own sense of justice.
The
scar
of
the
hunter
W
Anti-molesting Office
Nothing wrong on the eighth car.
Nothing wrong on the third car.
Nothing wrong on the fifth car.
Ninth car...
What happened to the ninth car?
Car nine!
Oh... excuse me.
Please let me pass.
Excuse me...
I found a suspicious person.
I'm going to check it out now.
N-no...
Please stop...
A little bit more...
Excuse me... let me pass...
Don't ask for the impossible. It's crowded, you know.
But...
What should I do?
No!
Stop!
Even though you saw the molester, you couldn't stop him?
What are you doing!?
I'm sorry.
Tomorrow... I'll definitely catch them tomorrow!
The eradication of molesters is...
My duty!
However, the next day...
I...
No...no...
No... no!
Please stop...
Again... I...
couldn't do anything...
All I did was watch...
What are you doing?
I'm really sorry.
You've seriously blundered.
You let the suspect escape, even though you saw the molestation take place.
I'm sorry.
It's already the second time this has happened.
Are you taking this seriously?
I'm not going to make any excuses.
It's just...
Huh? What is it?
Those vivid methods...
The 10,000 yen the suspect grabbed.
I think this is the work of Chikan Juunintai.
Chikan Juunintai?
Oh, that group of ten that surround the molester and his victim?
Those are just rumors!
But...
Those methods match the ones I saw.
There is no mistake, I think they are the ones behind this.
Just thinking it isn't enough!
It's all right if you're doing your best,
but there is a limit.
You can only work with what they give you.
Why does she strain herself over these molesters?
Back then...
I was...
Desecrate.
Dessert.
Reserve.
Re...
Help me...
No...
Stop... please...
No way... not on the train...
No... no...
Please stop...
Stop it, already...
No... I can't... someone...
Someone help me...
Someone...
Someone please notice me...
Someone please...
Just watch...
I won't let you escape.
Chikan Juunintai... I will surely catch you.
Chikan Junnintai... If they act exactly as the rumors say,
they will target the woman that the client requested.
It's probably too dangerous for them to be walking around freely, so
they will stay in the area near the ticket examiner.
Ah! That man...
Don't ask for the impossible. It's crowded, you know.
That guy...!
There's no mistake.
I've found them!
That means the client is that man.
His clothes are expensive, and in good taste.
He's not the type to frequent the railway.
His attitude seems egotistical and arrogant.
He seems like the president of a company, able to buy anything he wants.
There's a subdued side to him, too.
He's not the type to own a high ranking business.
Analyzing his attitude should help me determine the target.
The woman whose name appears in his secret list...
She will be intelligent and very beautiful.
Even though he likes that type of woman,
he is too afraid of scandals.
He's a timid guy who can't do anything.
A little longer... please wait a little longer...
Yes, yes it is...
Yes, it will start at six o'clock.
There will be six people coming.
Yes, the president will be present for the introduction,
but then he needs to leave for Osaka on other business.
Yes, OK. I understand.
I will return to the office later.
Oh, sorry.
Hey, we can sit here.
Bear it...  I must be sure that it's them.
Just bear it...
If I can record the molesting in a video...
I can arrest them all.
A little bit more...
This occurrence must be recorded.
W-What?!
No...
No way...
Don't tell me... no...
I couldn't do anything.
Really, I...
Don't make a fool out of me!
It recorded!
The evidence of the event was recorded!
What!? What's this?
I got molested and I felt it?
I...
After that event, something inside me had changed.
I don't know what exactly what.
But I think the answer is on that train.
So I'm always riding in the front car.
And today, again...