Staring at me like that makes me embarrassed.
After all, my boobs are smaller than Rio-chan’s.
Jeez, Aniki sure is a pervert!
This is the only time we’re doing something like this, alright?
Aya! This is awesome!
Just like in those erotic video games you love so much, you can cum as much as you want.
We’re cosplaying your favorite anime characters as it is.
Cum lots on my face!
No! Cum on my costume instead!
Squirt it all over my face!
Amazing, there’s so much on my face.
I’m cumming!
Then cum!
Feed me with your semen!
Nii-san, that was so much semen.
But you’re still so hard.
You’re still so big.
Your dick really is horny.
Punishment time.
Don’t plow into me so deep!
I’ll cum right away!
I’m sorry I’m such a slut, Nii-san!
I’m a perverted bitch!
The most perverted cosplay bitch of all!
Punish me! Harder!
Punish me harder! Deeper!
Rio, you’re such a pervert.
Dressed like this, turned on so much.
No, Aniki, you’re the pervert!
No! Not so deep!
I’ll fall apart!
That naughty dick. Give it to Aya, please!
I want your semen inside!
I’m cumming! I’m cumming!
Punish me like the bad girl I am!
I’m cumming!
Huh?
That was a good dream.
W
Imouto Paradise!
~ Onii-chan, watashi to shiyou yo!~
Little Sister Paradise!
~ Onii-chan, fuck me first!~
Aya! Breakfast time!
Coming!
Based on the original “Imouto Paradise!” by Moonstone
I see... I did get really into this before I fell asleep.
N-Now I get it.
Wow, wow! This must be love!
Nii-san, I’m coming in.
Wa—
Good morning, Nii-san.
Breakfast is ready downstairs. Everyone’s waiting for you.
A-Aya... Um, okay.
I’m c-coming right away.
Just w-wait a minute.
Come as quickly as you can.
Fine, I will.
Stupid Nii-san.
Let’s see...
Onee-chan!
Kogori-chan, watch your manners!
Michiko-chan, you too.
Our parents went away on business trips this summer vacation.
So it's just us five sisters and our big brother.
It’s barely even started, and...
Hey, hey, Onii-chan.
Hmm?
Listen.
What’s "masturbating?"
Should I not have asked that?
W-Well...
Masturbating itself isn't bad.
In fact, it means to pleasure yourself.
Pleasure?
W-Why are you asking this all of a sudden?
Onee-chan...
Because! We figured you would be an expert on masturbating.
Stupid!
I only know what it's like for boys.
But, um, as for girls...
I-Is it different for boys than girls?
The sensations may or may not be different, but the technique has to be.
How you do it depends on what you have to work with.
Onii, aren’t you gonna answer your little sis’s question?
W-Well, let’s see...
Masturbating is...
I-Is?
T-To become an adult... It’s an important step in becoming an adult.
A ceremony.
That's not a lie.
Adult, huh...
Come now. You should eat your breakfast before it gets cold.
As you can see, despite being relatives we're quite varied in personalities and looks.
But if there’s one trait we share, it must be how we all feel about our brother.
I think we all love him.
Aya?
Is this wrong?
Nii-san! This is embarrassing!
We can’t have sex since we’re related, but this should be okay.
Don’t, Nii-san!
No, Nii-san!
It’s dirty there!
I don’t care how we do it, I just want to have you!
Or maybe you’d prefer this instead.
So big! Onii-san is inside my butt.
I can’t hold back anymore.
Nii-san, it’s okay.
Keep it up.
I want you to feel good.
Aya!
Oh no!
Is your butt turning you on?
No, you’re turning me on.
What a slutty body you have.
Oh no! I want it so bad, but it hurts!
Nii-san... For you, Nii-san, I’d do...
Aya, you have a heavenly body.
No, Nii-san!
I’m about to cum!
I’m cumming inside.
Don’t, Nii-san! Not inside!
I’m cumming! Cumming!
Oh no!
A-Awesome.
It’s no good, Aya, I can’t stop.
It’s your fault, Aya!
Nii-san, Nii-san!
Your body is so slutty!
No!
You little whore!
I’m cumming! Cumming again!
Aya! Take it!
Nii-san... No.
My butt will fall apart!
Oh no, I’m cumming! I'm cumming too!
From the feeling... In my butt.
I’m cumming too... I’m cumming too.
Aya! I’m cumming!
Oh no!
I-I did it.
S-Something so...
So lewd.
Nii-san?
Er, well, I didn’t...
If you’re busy, I can talk to you later.
N-No way.
Did he just see me doing that?
Seeing that makes me need to get it out of my system too.
"Oh, don’t. Just the smell of your semen makes me wanna cum, Nii-chan."
Ko-Koharu!
Onii-chan, what were ya doing?
Wh-Why are you in my room, Koharu?
I knocked on the door, but you never answered.
And besides... When you say that with your dick that hard...
...your words just have no authority when you’re like that.
If your dick is already that hard anyway...
This thing feels nicer, doesn’t it?
What’s this thing?
I made it to please you, Nii-chan.
It’s called "virgin jelly."
Awesome. You’re so hard.
This must really turn you on.
Onii, your dick...
Your big dick...
Yes, yes...
It’s your dick’s fault, Onii.
You’re making me so slutty.
Your slutty dick needs to be emptied by me.
It’s made me so slutty with all that pre-cum...
Your dick is like a magic wand.
Look, look.
Oh, no!
I slosh it around and gently bite it.
It’s okay, Onii.
You can squirt out all your dick milk if you want.
Let me drink it.
Let me have all your dick milk!
Splash your cum all over my face. I don’t mind.
Your semen... I want it all over me.
Yes.
Inside my mouth... Onii’s dick milk... So much.
Amazing! I’m all sticky from your cum.
I told you to cum on my face, but you came in my mouth.
So I can’t see it.
As punishment you need one more go at it.
Yes.
You just came and you’re still so hard.
On my... On my face again.
Splash it all on my face.
This dirty dick of yours... I need to suck it dry of semen.
Come closer, Onii.
On my face.
Splash it on—
This time, I’m cumming with you.
Cum all over my face!
I’m cumming!
Onii...
Your semen is making me cum.
All over my face... So much... Onii’s sperm.
I’m... I’m also very happy, Onii.
A-Aya?
Nii-san...
Nii-san, you saw, didn’t you.
Yeah.
It’s gross, isn’t it?
Even though I’m your sister, I thought of you while masturbating.
You did?
I’m sorry.
But I love you.
I know it’s wrong, but...
But... I want to fuck you, Nii-san.
Aya.
You’re soaking wet already...
...Aya.
No... It’s embarrassing.
Don’t! Not down there... I’ll cum right away!
You’re so big and thick.
So this is a man’s...
Nii-san’s dick...
If it’s inside my pussy...
Aya!
I don’t care what anyone says.
I don’t care. As long as I can have sex with Nii-san.
I’ll accept anything.
Aya.
I can’t hold back.
It’s okay, Nii-san.
Put your dick inside.
Nii-san’s coming inside.
Are you okay, Aya?
I’m okay.
It hurts a little, but...
Move more, Nii-san.
You can move more.
I’ll be okay.
I want to feel all of you inside me.
You’re all the way inside.
This is the first time for you, yet you like it hitting your cervix?
I don’t know, but it feels good.
Aya...
What a slutty body you have.
Nii-san, you meanie!
Nii-san, you’re so rough. Swirling around inside me.
Aya... For a first-timer, you’re sure into this!
Don’t say that! You’re embarrassing me.
Aya, you’re such a slutty little sister... Such a bad girl!
I’m sorry, Nii-san!
I’m gonna cum, Aya!
Inside... I’m cumming inside!
Don’t, Nii-san!
I’m cumming.
It’s my first time, but I’m cumming!
I'm cumming!
I’ll get pregnant!
So much...
So much semen...
I love you, Nii-san.
I love you, too.
You’re all my precious sisters.
S-Sisters?
What’s that?
So late at night...
Who—
H-Hiyori? What are you doing?
It’s not what you think!
I just woke up and wanted to go pee, but I tripped and fell and...
And you peed yourself?
Yes.
I’m sorry.
I promise I’ll wash it off.
Never mind that.
Are you mad?
Are you going to punish Hiyori?
No...
Hiyori is such a bad girl.
Always causing so much trouble for Nii-chan.
Punishment, eh?
Come on, you can’t pee yourself.
I’m sorry, Nii-chan!
Never pee yourself again.
Yes.. I promise I won’t...
You need to say it properly.
Hiyori will never pee herself again.
Then are we finished?
But I might pee myself again.
I’m not a good girl yet.
I want Nii-chan to punish me more.
I can’t turn down a request.
Then here we go.
Take that! And that!
Does this feel good?
No... Not at all!
B-But Hiyori, you’re wet.
And when does juice come out of your pussy, Hiyori?
It’s when... It’s when Hiyori thinks of slutty things.
Not there... Onii-chan!
Does your butt feel that good?
I don’t know! I feel like I’m going to pee.
I’m going to pee myself again!
I won’t get mad this time, so go ahead and pee.
It’s coming. I’m peeing!
Pee...
You’re such a bad girl, Hiyori.
I’ll clean it up, so you go to bed.
Koharu seems different than usual.
And Hiyori too.
Hiyori went right to sleep and didn’t even wake up from the alarm clock.
R-Really?
Say, Onii, wanna have fun with me again today?
S-Stupid!
You’re blushing!
The devil made me do it!
Nii-san...
I wonder if he did it with Koharu-chan and Hiyori-chan too?
I guess it can’t be helped.
He loves all of us.
What the hell!
You horny brother!
B-But it’s chicks with a bust over 90 centimeters and huge nipples!
But only the ones you’re looking at now have big nipples!
No, no, I saw all of them and they’re all huge.
Unlike me.
Is what you may say...
Fine, I’ll let you see them.
Really?
S-Sure, I will.
But if my nipples aren’t big...
Fine, I’ll apologize, I promise!
Why?
Why is this happening?
Well?
My nipples aren’t that big, right?
No. They’re light pink, and so cute!
Wait! I said I’d only show you!
No, don’t suck them!
Wh-Where are you licking me now?
It smells and tastes good.
Stupid!
Aniki, you pervert! That tickles!
I can’t hold back anymore!
Aniki, your dick... It’s in my armpit.
It's gross, it’s all wet.
Awesome. This feels great!
Not only your tits, your armpits are also slutty.
It’s not my fault!
Are you turned on?
No!
I’m not a slut!
It’s just because your dick is so gross.
You were showing me a slutty face.
No, it's gross.
I’m cumming!
Don’t... So much...
A lot came out.
I see, well then.
I guess once won’t do it for you.
Rio...
Just today.
I’ll humor your perversion for today.
Does this feel good?
Doesn’t it hurt?
No. Your glasses and the sensation is so...
So wet... What a pervert.
Awesome. You’re such a slut, Rio!
It’s your fault. You got my body all dirty and sticky.
It’s turning you on too, isn’t it, Rio?
It’s all your fault, Aniki.
You’re making me gross too.
Oh no!
I feel so hot inside.
Awesome! You’re so slutty, Rio!
If this keeps up...
Oh no!
Not so rough.
It’s no good.
I’m cumming! I'm cumming right on your face.
I’m cumming!
It’s all over my face.
Aniki, I also can’t hold back.
I want to fuck you, Aniki.
Come in.
Ow...
Aniki’s dick is inside.
All the way in my pussy!
I want you to feel good, Aniki.
Your slippery pussy is filled with my dick. I can see it.
Stupid! Stop saying gross things.
But it makes you excited, Rio.
No!
Why? It’s my first time, but my brother’s dick is turning me on so much.
It’s because you’re a slutty little sister, Rio.
No! I’m not!
This isn’t me.
It’s because your dick... It's so perverted.
Rio! Your boobs are bouncing everywhere. What a whore!
I can’t help it.
I can’t help it if my boobs bounce!
No... Not rougher... I’ll break...
Oh, I don’t care. My pussy can break.
I can’t... Rio, I can’t hold back.
It’s so intense!
I’m cumming.
Oh no!
Aniki!
I can’t...
I’m cumming!
I’ll break!
Rio’s pussy will break!
I’m cumming!
No! Not so deep.
Oh no! I’m cumming...
Cumming...
Your dick is all the way inside.
Aniki!
Oh no... I’m cumming.
Aniki, it’s your fault, I got semen on my face again...
I wouldn’t have minded if you came inside me...
Oh no... Rio-chan too?
Don’t, Nii-san.
I really can't... I can’t take it!
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, love me more, Onii-chan
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, motto suki shite, Onii-chan.
Uchuu ichi no ai o sodatete
Let’s create the biggest love in the universe.
Futari no paradise
Into our paradise.
Kisu kisu shite (chu!)
Kiss me, kiss me (smooch!)
Asa wa ohayou kou to yutte
I tell you good morning when you wake up.
Okocchau no nee ii deshou?
Why are you mad? I don’t see anything wrong with that.
(Nee, okite!)
(Wake up, sweetie!)
Kyou wa futari de dekakeyou yo
Let’s go out together today.
Te o tsunaide arukitai no
I want to hold hands while we walk.
(Hayaku! Hayaku!)
(Hurry! Hurry!)
Ano ne, sono ne, kore de yasashiku
But listen, well, you’re still sweet to me.
Atama o nadete kureru
When you pat my head.
Itsumo sore ga ureshiin da yo
That always makes me happy.
Kyou mo asu mo saki mo zutto hanasanai yo
Today and tomorrow and always, don’t ever let me go.
(Issho!)
(Together!)
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, motto suki shite Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, love me more, Onii-chan.
Kitto mitsume atta nara
I’m sure that if you look into my eyes,
Mou koko wa paradise
I’ll be in paradise.
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, ooki na ai de, Onii-chan
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, with your big love, Onii-chan,
Mou konna sekai no mannaka de
I know the world we’re in is awful,
Futari no paradise.
But we have our own paradise.
Kisu kisu shiyou (chu)
Let’s kiss, let’s kiss (smooch)