Ijou Chitai Jikken Dorei
No…
Come now. You shouldn't be resting, Landlord-san.
M-Moriyama-san!
Please stop this.
Stop what?
What do you mean "what?"
Could you mean this thing?
W
Ijou Chitai Jikken Dorei 1 (Special Sexuation Experimental Slave)
My name is Konna Azusa.
When my parents passed away, they left me this apartment.
And I’ve taken care of it until now.
Stop it, Moriyama-san!
Moriyama-san, I’ll do anything you want.
So please don’t leave this apartment.
It hurts! It hurts!
If the last remaining tenant, Moriyama-san, left...
Then all the memories from this apartment would also leave.
That’s why I don’t mind becoming a slutty sex slave.
I can’t help it.
Please... Can I take it out?
Take what out?
The vibrator.
Then maybe I should move out.
Unless you want me to tease you more with the vibrator.
Please…
You’re too quiet. I couldn't quite hear that.
Say it.
Use the vibrator... Use the vibrator to tease me more.
As you wish.
Oh no!
Not there. Not my butt.
No...
Don’t put your fingers...
Don’t put your fingers in there!
Not in there.
Don’t put them in my butt!
Do the sensations in your butt turn you on?
They don't.
It... It didn't!
Don’t!
Not your fingers.
St-Stop!
Don’t!
Moriyama-san, what are you...
Why are you...
It’s in my butt!
Does it feel good?
Of course not!
Really?
Inside...
Moriyama-san is inside!
You’re so hot. So tight. So tender.
You feel unbelievably good.
No!
Don’t say things like that!
Putting it in my butt... No!
It hurts!
Moriyama-san’s dick is in my butt!
My butt is falling apart.
Stop it!
It’s starting to feel good, isn't it?
That’s not true!
Really?
But what I’m using is a special invention made from a professor at my college.
It doesn’t feel good...
It should make you feel good.
This was a perfect chance to test it.
Don’t! Don’t!
Don’t do me in my butt!
If you feel me with your fingers, I'll... Oh!
Stop!
Please, no more! I’ll...
I’ll...
You’ll what?
Nothing... Nothing will happen!
I'm going crazy! Going crazy!
Don’t!
I can’t take it!
I’m cumming!
From being fucked in the ass!
Moriyama-san’s dick is inside me... It's throbbing!
Ew. Feels like something is still inside.
What’s wrong?
Ahh, looks like I got you good.
What do you want?
Just for a test, take these.
It’s not poison, is it?
Of course not. They're vitamins.
I exhausted you, so I thought I’d apologize.
You don’t trust me? That hurts.
Very well.
Then I'll leave this apartment.
Wait! Please don’t go!
But...
I’ll take them.
I’ll take them, so please don’t leave!
How do you feel?
Feel?
W-What?
My pussy feels...
Feels hot, so very hot.
Looks like I've revived you.
I didn’t get revived.
Yes, you did.
Look at how revived your clitoris is.
My clitoris is so big.
Do you like it?
Of course I don’t!
Really?
Landlord-san, don't you enjoy having your clitoris played with?
I don’t... I don't like it!
That’s strange.
It seems you do like it.
That’s not...
Stop it!
It’s turning bright red!
My clit...
I’ll cum! I’ll cum!
Oh, you already came?
Then let's have some more fun.
Don’t. Don’t do anymore, please...
It’s inside.
Moriyama-san’s dick is inside!
No! Deep... It's so deep!
Don’t!
No!
Don’t... Stop!
Not the toothbrush!
You’re already all the way inside, so if you stimulate my clitoris like this...
I’ll cum!
I’ll cum... I'll cum again.
Does it feel that good?
It feels... It feels...
Moriyama-san’s dick is thrashing my pussy... Teasing it...
Landlord-san, you sure are slutty.
But I’m... I'm not!
I’m cumming!
Cumming!
The entire way home my clit's been sore.
I’m at my limit.
I’m home, Landlord-san.
W-Welcome...
Wow, she’s super cute!
Her tits are so big.
You should be pleased.
These boys are underclassmen of mine.
They would like to rent in this apartment complex.
What?
Moriyama-san, what is this?
I figured they should get to know their landlord first.
Wait, stop it!
So soft.
Stop it!
Really!? She’s got such a huge clitoris!
Moriyama-san, make them stop!
Isn’t this nice of them?
Looks like they both like you.
Don't...
Stop it!
No!
Don’t!
Not there!
I’ll cum right away!
Landlord-san, does it feel good?
Yes... It does.
How so?
So deep... My pussy... The dick is so deep... It's making my pussy so happy.
How can we make you feel even better?
My clit…
My clitoris…
Tease it like you always do.
I want to cum from my clit...
Harder!
Please, my clit... Squeeze it harder!
I’ll cum!
There's a dick in both my ass and pussy.
My ass and pussy are filled with throbbing dicks.
They’re scraping my insides!
My clit!
I’m cumming!
I’m cumming again!
I’m throbbing!
From the dicks inside me.
They're both throbbing too!