Ryuubi Gentoku's ambition is to conquer the world.
It's tasty...
You still can do it, right?
Today, I decided to eat all of this thing
until I'm satisfied.
It's..inside...
You dare put it inside my private part...
Bad penis, you should be punished.
Ryuubi..cumming..Ryuubi..gonna cum.
Inside..It's..bigger inside of me...
Kan'u.
It's your turn, Chouhi.
Onii-chan's penis!
Onii-chan~!
You're cumming..inside my pussy.
Just when I let my guard down..It's unfair!
I'm your sister, so It's okay.
These girls purpose should be to conquer the world...
Shocking Pink!
Part 1
Peach's Vow
W
It's really noisy...
Okay..okay...
Who is it?
Shoukatsu Koumei-dono.
It's really sudden, but I want you to be my strategist.
In here, we don't accept any offer
for any salary raise.
Eh? Koumei-dono~!
Shoukatsu Koumei Sensei~!
Hey neighbor, It's noisy!
I got it, just go inside for details!
Here is..truly a place of knowledge.
Well, who are you exactly?
I'm sorry for the late introduction,
my name is Ryuubi Gentoku.
Huh?
You mean..Ryuubi from the Three Kingdoms?
Yes, first generation ruler of the Central Kingdom.
Sorry, even I don't know the circumstances.
Why would people like Ryuubi-sama want to meet me?
That's of course to meet you, Shoukatsu Koumei-dono.
It's Morokuzu Takaaki.
It's because we have similar names,
It's really hard with my own life.
Always being compared to each other,
in the end,
even someone like you is here...
No, you're really Shoukatsu Koumei-dono.
No matter what people say.
It's not what those people say!
The real person said that it's different!
Anyway, you're someone important to me!
Even if you say something like that,
No is NO!
Even though I look like this, I'm a busy person.
From morning 'till evening, I've got part-time jobs to do.
Even if it's my turn to get a day off.
Doing something strange like this...
She's got a good appearance though...
I beg you, please be my strategist!
If you need money, I'll pay you...
Would you cut it out! I don't have time to
play with rich girls like-
Wait- what are you...?
Certainly..If I let you join me with money,
that would be unacceptable.
I don't even have to use the money,
I'll make it with seducing you.
Wait-
With only a kiss, you've already...
It's an amazing scent.
Yes, It's over.
Eh, why's that? Just a bit more...
That's right, isn't it? Half way in is no good, right?
Then, why don't you do it with me?
With that, there's gonna be more good things...
Besides your mouth, you can do it with the other thing.
Wha..what are you saying...
Who exactly are you?
Who am I?
What an imprudence thing.
I'm a king among kings, ruler of the center
Ryuubi Gentoku.
Shoukatsu Koumei would you take a vow with me?
Just say that you like me!
Like..like you...
Like..like..like..kiss..kiss..kiss...
This girl is truly a king,
Even she's a king, a king of tyrants!
Wa..wait a minute!
No way, I can't wait any longer...
It's inside..inside... Koumei's thick penis.
It's inside...
Koumei's penis...
Inside of me..It's like a dream...
You..Is it your first time?
That's for sure...
Because I had decided, that I was gonna give
my virginity to you.
Did you know what's the word of the fellowship
of those two?
Ryuubi and Koumei relationship is expressed with something,
Like the life of fish and the water.
I admire those words...
Me and Koumei-dono too, the time our bodies
meet each other like this...
It feels like a good thing...
I want to do it all...
I don't think this is like that pink situation.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Yes...
It hurts, but I feel happy and I don't know how to think...
Why this girl going as far as this?
I don't get it all...
I feel regret, but this girl...
Is really cute...
Ko..Koumei...
Koumei, It's amazing...
No...
I can't...
It's okay..you can let it out..just like that.
Inside of me.
That's something bad, isn't it?
Koumei is Ryuubi's thing, you should be obedient to my order...
I'll put out your head!
Put..put out my head?!
Hey, are you okay?
Koumei too, you're still okay right?
Eh?
Did you like something like this?
I won't say I like it, but I don't hate it all.
Your penis is throbbing, It's really cute...
Koumei, you want to come?
It's gonna be bad...
No way~ you should hold it back.
I said you can't..but you came out like this...
Next time I want you to put it inside of this.
I'll put it in.
Doing it from behind is...
Like riding a horse, right?
Surely like a strategist, isn't it?
So deep..amazing...
Though I've just cum..I'm gonna...
Gonna cum~
Me too, I'm gonna...
Let it out..let the sperm out!!
The sperm is hot and drenched a lot...
You're awful, Koumei-dono.
Even though that's my first time...
You're doing it hard and you even thrust in
to cum inside...
Wha-
Of course, you're gonna take responsibility right?
You set me up?
Ah, you're the one who set me up.
Argh..I get it, resemble or gonna do it-
Do as you please!
It's good!
If we're settled on it, let me introduce you to my little sisters.
Your little sisters?!
The two of you, come in!
I'm Kan'u Unchou.
I'm Chou..Chouhi Ekitoku.
The three of us.
Even though we were born in different places,
we're sisters in this life.
This time,  I'll make sure you take care of all of us
from now and forever.
Right, Koumei?
Then, what should I do from now?
Yes?
Job..I'm talking about the job!
Even you said that I'm gonna be a strategist,
It's not like we're gonna go to war, right?
We don't have any plan for doing that right now...
The first is how 'bout we build the base course
of our kingdom...
I want someone to be by my side,
always listen and do what I order...
That is your job.
Hey, wait a minute. What do you mean
build a kingdom?
I'll listen to you just in case, what is your purpose?
That's of course, right?
To conquer the world.
If your hearing is bad, let me explain it to you.
I hope you don't ask about that...
That's right, I have important job and fit
for you to do?
I hope it wasn't something like breaking the law-
Making children.
You say children?!
That's an important job after the job as king...
For the time being, I want children, as many as one platoon.
44 children?!
That's a lot...
That's of course we divide that amount
with rotation between the three of us.
Eh~?!
What are you saying, Chouhi?!
We're both one heart and one body as sisters, right?!
If in death we're together, then we should be
together when we bear a child!
Bu..bu..bu..but...
I don't have any experience, it's my first time,
and my heart isn't ready!
If your body is ready, then your heart will come after it.
No~ please stop it, Onee-sama!!
You've got yourself in trouble, Strategist-dono.
If you feel like that, why don't you do something with that?
Don't worry about it, I'm a virgin too.
Are you three idiots?!
We're ready here~!
Err..please take it easy on me...
Thus, now I'm...
I'm being forced to be Shoukatsu Koumei.