Again...
Hello, Saki.
You were cute again today.
But, the lower left part of your skirt was frayed.
Since that day, the stalker is always messaging me.
He follows my daily routine.
And lastly, he confessed that he loves me.
He even knows my weak spot!
I can't even seek help from my brother.
I was always wondering what I should do.
At one time, I thought of this thing...
That day...
What was that thing that satisfied my body...
like that...
N... No...
I... received another mail this morning.
What is the relationship between you and Saki?
Why won't Saki say anything?
What in the world is happening to her?
I need to protect Saki no matter what!
My cute sister
and my precious girlfriend.
But I...
SubDESU-H Presents
The girl raped by the
Sinister
NERD
Molesting lesson
Saki.
Nii-san... what's the matter?
Do you have time after school??
I want you to come with me to buy some goods.
For today... I'm...
I have an appointment for a group study at my friend's house...
I see.
I understand.
I'll head home first and wait for you.
I'll prepare dinner.
Sorry...
I placed a wiretap in Saki's clothes.
I'm telling myself to protect Saki...
I have no confidence if that is my true intention...
Don't look away from the screen...
N... no...
Stop... please stop...
Moaning like that...
You feel good being touched by your boobs right?
No, I don't...
No... forgive me...
Saki's boobs are really perverted.
Even though it's soft, it's still elastic...
No...
Stop touching my boobs...
I'm not feeling it...
It's just gross!
This...
Hey...
I want to see Saki's naked boobs!
It's alright, right?
Ahhh, it's white and big...
Really, Saki's boobs are amazing...
No...
Don't speak that loudly...
They will notice us...
They will see me showing my boobs...
You feel it, right?
Your nipples are getting erect...
No...
No, they're not...
No... don't look...
It looks like a dick...
The nipples are getting bigger!
Saki is really a lecherous one.
No...
No I'm not...
I'm not lecherous!
Don't look...
If you pull it that hard...
It's great.
Saki's boobs stretch this much!
No... stop...
Don't play with my nipples!
No...
Stop...
N... no...
I'll moan...
How about doing this with your dick-like nipples...
Sorry...
My nipples...
Don't squeeze it that much...
Does your dick-like nipples feel good?
No... my nipples... it's getting numb...
Stop...
Feeling it by being teased...
Saki is a lecherous, perverted, filthy masochist
No... no I'm not...
No...
No way...
The love juices are flowing out and it's wet...
S... stop...
That... stop that...
Since Saki is a lecherous, perverted, filthy masochist you like being teased like this right?
Hey, it feels good right?
It feels so good...
Am I cumming...?
It's so good...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I must not...
I must not cum...
N... no!!!
I'm home...
Welcome home!
Sorry for coming home late.
Saki...
Uhm... is there something you're hiding from me?
Eh?
Uhm... no...
Sorry... I think I'm just tired...
I'll go back to my room.
Why... why did you remain silent Saki?
Saki... if you don't hurry, you'll be late!
Yes, sorry nii-san...
What's the matter?
N... no...
nothing...
Is that so... well then...
Nii-san...
He's right there...
I think I'll glad if he's a bit away...
As for my order, you're putting the vibrator in your pussy...
Good girl... Saki...
Sa... saki...
What's the matter?
Saki's legs feels good...
It's chubby and slippery...
N... no...
Saki's pussy is already hot...
It's seems like it's getting excited with the vibrator...
No...
But the vibration is so weak...
You must make it stronger...
N... no...
T... take it out...
This is intense... so intense...
T... this...
I can't stand...
You're trembling...
It seems you feel it a lot...
Even in a place like this...
N... no...
I don't want this anymore...
I can't stand this one...
What will happen if I do it like this...
No!...
S... stop...
It's coming in...
The fingers...
It's going deeper...
Saki's pussy is getting so wet...
The perverted juices are flowing out...
N... no...
My panties are already wet...
It's wet and sticking to my pussy...
From deep inside...
The love juice is flowing out...
If you do it that hard...
It's hot... the love juices will stain...
Hey... look at this...
N... no...
D... don't show me that...
It's gross to wear wet underwear right?
Sorry for not noticing it...
I will take it off now...
Eh!? No!!!
Ah... Saki's pussy is so wet the vibrator fell out...
No...
No... don't look at it... you can clearly see the embarrassing part...
Don't move... don't even step...
This thing... they will notice this...
They will see it... my pussy... they will see it...
Saki's pussy is really dirty...
I'm not touching it but the love juice is still flowing...
No...
No... no way...
It's shameful to flow this much...
I'll put a cap on it...
No...
They will notice you if you scream...
You must bear with it...
He's rubbing it...
My pussy is making a dirty sound...
It's so embarrassing...
It's flowing out...
As I get embarrassed... the juices continue flowing out...
This one got big too!
That one is...
As I thought, you liked it here...
You're always touching this one when you masturbate, right?
Masturbation...
No...
You're always touching that part...
Even I can't...
I'll moan...
Saki's clitoris got bigger again...
Look, touching it like this...
No...
If you squeeze my clitoris like that...
Don't touch my clitoris...
It's so intense...
Shaking your body like that... you're going to cum right?
I can't cum...
Am I cumming with my clitoris?
You're squeezing it too hard...
You can cum now...
I... I can't cum... my clitoris...
Here!
I'm cumming!!!
You came so loudly!
They will notice you if you moan like that.
N... no...
It's so embarrassing... don't look...
Oh? Your pussy started twitching again...
Really, Saki is a lecherous masochist who likes to be watched, right?
N... no, I'm not...
It's because... look!
This part is really twitching...
No... that part.
Saki's ass..
It's shining with the love juice and so dirty...
No... don't look at my asshole...
This is really embarrassing...
W... why...
Your finger is bursting inside my ass...
You're feeling it so much...
The love juice is flowing out a lot from your pussy.
No... the juice flowing out is touching my ass...
I feel it in that part too!!!
I will make you feel better!
Stop that...
If you twist that hard... the dirty sound will...
It's getting wet...
Well then...
My ass...
Two fingers are coming inside...
Hey, hey... stand properly...
You're pushing it...
Don't push my ass...
It's already ruined the inside of my ass...
My ass is being picked...
It's getting hot...
Don't do it...
Moaning, having your ass touched...
I must punish the lecherous, perverted girl...
My asshole...
More...
The dick...
Even in my ass...
He's even putting his dick in my ass!
My ass and the dick...
Stand up properly Saki!
I can't...
I can't stand up...
It's going deeper...
The ass isn't even a hole for sex...
Saki's lecherous pussy ass is squeezing so tightly.
How greedy is this...
My ass is being fucked and it's so embarrassing...
It's so embarrassing...
Don't... don't do that...
It's spreading...
My pussy ass is spreading more with your dick...
B... but...
It's rubbing...
My pussy ass is spreading...
I'm enjoying it...
If you stretch my asshole with your dick...
My ass will remain stretched...
Saki's pussy ass is so good and...
I'm already at my limit...
Good... my ass... my asshole...
My pussy ass...
It's shaking...
My ass is being ripped apart with the dick...
It's breaking... my ass is breaking with his dick...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!!!!!!
If you squeeze that hard...
The sperm is coming out...
It's being released inside my ass...
It was fun... Saki...
My ass... the sperm...
It's flowing out...
N... no way...
It's him... It's his fault!