Onii-chan...
It's okay if it's you,
Onii-chan.
S-Since onni-chan has a big breast fetish,
I might do something extreme!
I might do things like lick your areolae...
Or suck on them whole, like this!
And while I'm sucking on your breasts,
I might thrust inside your soft pussy too!
Onii-chan-!
You're already doing that!
You're already doing what you said!
I wonder what would happen if your mom and dad saw us?
Who would've known that something like this would happen
while your parents were away?
Do you regret it?
Nope! Not one bit! I've always wanted to do this with you, Onii-chan.
So-!
Konami!
Konami, I can't stop myself if you say such things!
No-! Onii-chan!
I'll get you pregnant!
I'll make sure that you get pregnant tonight!
Yes! Konami will be your bride!
I'm gonna cum in your deepest spots, okay?
Do it, please!
Cum all you want inside me!
Konami!
I'm gonna cum-!
Konami...!
Konami! Konami...
Konami!
SubDESU-H
Konami...
You called, Onii-chan?
N-No! It's nothing!
I was just disoriented...
Were you perhaps dreaming about me?
N-No! I wasn't!
I'm gonna go to the bathroom-!
Since Konami’s parents live next door and mine are away,
she came over to make dinner for us.
Could you put that over there?
Here?
Let's eat, Onii-chan!
Yeah, it looks good!
We've known each other for a long time.
I used to think of her as my little sister...
But... she sure has grown!
Especially...
a certain part of her...
No, I mustn't!
Her breasts are-! They're like dessert!
N-No, I mustn't...
But...
she's fast asleep...
Sorry, Konami!
Let me feel them just this once-!
I can't get enough!
Oh no, I can't stop myself!
I bet they'd feel even better if I touched them directly!
T-They're inverted!?
What a nice surprise!
Konami is embarrassed about these things, isn't she?
Hold on! I'll help you out of there!
Ko-Konami, you were awake?!
T-This, um, you see...
They feel so good that I can't let go!
Konami, why aren't you saying anything?
Konami, are you feeling aroused?
Ko-Konami!
N-No... Don't-!
H-Huh?
Konami-?
W-Whoa-! Her pussy is so hot!
It's in all the way, Konami!
Your insides are sticking to me!
Do you want me to take it out?
You like it when I pull it out, don't you?
No-! That's not true!
Your supple butt is shaking every time I thrust!
You're so warm, Konami!
It feels so good to hug you!
Onii-chan will make your pussy his!
I can smell her scent every time I thrust!
I'm gonna lose my mind-! Konami!
O-Onii-chan-!
I love you, Onii-chan!
Konami!
I really can't stop now-! You're too cute!
I-I'm gonna cum inside you!
No~!
I'm starting to feel good!
I-I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum inside you!
I'm cumming-!
Onii-chan...
I-I love you!
Konami...
What?
Another dream?
How obsessed am I?
I-It was real?
Yeah...
I didn't know you were so perverted, Onii-chan.
Geez, I'm all sticky...
Onii-chan, can I use your bath?
Ko-Konami!
Since this is reality, can we do it again? Please?
O-Onii-chan!
It feels great between your breasts too!
O-Onii-chan... This is embarrassing...
Aren't you feeling aroused too?
That's not true!
It feels too good for me and-!
I can't hold back-!
I'm still fine even after cumming so much!
You just said that we would only do it once!
Don't worry about the small details!
Your pussy is shaping around my cock again!
I can feel you, Onii-chan-!
It's so tight inside you, Konami!
It feels as though my cock is going to bend!
No-! I want to be shaped by you, Onii-chan!
I want to be shaped exclusively for you!
Konami-!
I can't believe it!
Being so rough and cumming inside me on my first time like that...
What will we do if I get pregnant?
S-Sorry... I'll take responsibility!
That's a promise,
Onii-chan.
Y-Yeah...
How about we do it again before we go to sleep?
Geez, Onii-chan!