www.SubDESU-H.net
Hey, Kaito,
I love you.
Will you go out with me?
Hey, wait up!
Kaito will go out with me.
No. Kaito-sama will marry me.
I-I also love you Kaito.
I sincerely came here for Kaito.
Kaito.
Kaito-sama.
Kaito-san.
Kaito-kun.
Who are you going to choose?
The cake, pudding, cream puffs, donuts and parfait
all taste great!
How much dessert are you going to eat?
I'm already having heartburn simply by looking at it.
You’re going all-out today? That's great.
Don't you just feel like eating a lot whenever something good happens?
What do you mean?
Kaito-san and I have just started dating each other.
Eh?!
Coming!
Fallen in love with breasts?
About 30 percent.
That's actually 99.9999% in reality.
I'm still bound to grow,
so please give up already, everyone!
I love Kaito-san far more than I do cheesecakes!
Tropical Kiss
W
Original Animation Disc
~Slippery Wet Diet?! The warrior that has to eat Matsuri Chapter ~
Kaito-san!
I want to do something about my body.
A "trippy" body...
Weren't you just stumbling on your legs?
Oh, I get it now.
She can't see her feet because her breasts are in the way.
And if they're as big as Matsuri's breasts, they'll surely cause shoulder pain.
That's so true.
I wonder why they became this big...
Rikka, stop!
How about we color the pool red?
This is bad.
In that case,
Tokoro Ten!
Read this aloud!
What?
Live big breasts.
Die small breasts.
You're the one who needs to die!
I stopped the disaster with minimal loss...
What happened?
Male Bath
Female Bath
Hey, hey, Onii-chan!
The bath's really big, right?
Yep.
Are you okay?
This is nothing compared to Hanabi's blows...
What are you doing?
Natane said that she wanted to see the Great Bathhouse.
With you?
This isn't a mixed bath, you know!
What would happen if shampoo entered her eyes,
or someone attempted to kidnap her because of her cuteness?!
You really are different when it concerns Natane...
I thought of something.
Lend me your ear a bit.
Quite a great idea from such a fool.
I'm in.
Hey, are you really sure about this?
If you don’t do anything, nothing will change.
Ladies and gentlemen,
has everyone already noticed?
The reason there's a gap between the male and female workers at Aloha is simple:
the men are coming from a perverted perspective.
Even if they try to hide it, the desire is still there.
No. Because that desire is only partially hidden, it's causing problems.
Why don't we just let it all explode?!
I don't understand what he's talking about.
That's why we will hold a battle here between the men and women!
The girl's swimsuits will dissolve if they come in contact with water,
and the men will be armed with water guns.
Of course, the women will also be equipped with paint ball guns.
If the men are hit 150 times once the game begins,
bombs between their legs will be set to explode.
Also, if they get aroused by the females' outfits,
I'm
also
partici-
pating?
I
didn't
know
this!
they will be out of the game immediately.
I
just
said
it
now!
This means that any guy that looks at the women erotically will explode.
By the way, I'm not participating.
As I already know who'll win.
Well, he's only interested in 2-D women...
This is how strong the bombs are...
Oh, this is a Sengoku Otome Musou's limited figure!
It was made wonderfully.
Isn't he almost dead already?!
It's okay as long as you don’t increase your heart rate!
There!
I'm not going to lose here!
Too lame!
So they're unstoppable when they work together?
In that case...
We-we did it...
Something's wrong...
They're here!
They found us, Izumi!
Go!
The enemy's open and surrounded!
My weapon will be...
these fists!
Izumi-chan's a master of Minazuki-style martial arts,
and she's also good at Aikido.
Just how good is her Aikido or martial art skills?
Izumi-chan, if you're going to do it, do it until the end.
You're dark.
You're dark, Hotaru-chan!
Winner declared! No one can beat...
Izumi-chan...
If it's come to this,
I'll have to use the Minazuki-style arts technique...
This is what I can really do!
Izumi-chan...
Prepare yourself, Nagi-san!
We'll take out, Nagi-san.
Oh no...
It sure is safe around you, Nagi-san.
Don’t use me as a shield!
We'll die in honor!
Let's make them strip!
In this case...
Super technique:
Fuurin barrier!
H-Hey!
What did you just do?!
Just settling an old score.
Don't think it'll
simply end like this!
No!
Matsuri, you'll be shot at!
I was separated from everyone.
Push through!
We won’t lose!
It’s dangerous here.
Yeah.
You tripped at such a dangerous time?
If she falls...
I didn’t mean to hold this!
I know...
Sorry, my hands will...
I'll fall if you release them!
This is bad.
I have to calm my heart down.
Can you pull me back?
Okay...
Her breasts feel so  good....
I have to at least save her...
Kaito-san!
And here, I was able to protect Matsuri
with my life as collateral...
It was really hell back there.
But there was someone who won at the end.
And that's....
Natane-chan!
Yay!
It's a victory for the girls' team.
Do your best in cleaning things up, boys!
Can we even finish this today?
C'mon now, guys.
You'll only cause trouble for us
if you sit there all depressed.
Here, let's finish this quickly.
You’re going to help?
Thank you. What a relief!
I can’t believe this.
It’s because they've exposed and learned about each other.
All is well that ends well.
Is everything really  fine?
Defeated in the end
We ran and sweat a lot back there!
Let's freshen ourselves up.
Of course, you can't do that.
Now then, tomorrow's a day off...
Um, it's also my day off tomorrow...
So, if it's possible, let's...
What?
There's a nearby all-you-can-eat cake shop.
So, umm...
Let's go together, then.
Is it really okay?
Thank you very much!
You really like sweet things, don't you?
Searching for challengers!
Home-made wedding cake
Time limit 60 minutes
Prize 20,000 yen
What the heck is this?!
I'm digging in!
This is really good!
We'll have to pay 20,000 yen if you can't eat it all, though...
Thanks for the food!
In just 30 minutes...
Well, then, Kaito-san...
Oh, let's go now.
Our next stop is the all-you-can-eat shop, okay?
She went to an all-you-can-eat shop after eating the wedding cake?
Big eating challenges are completely out of reach for me.
That brings back memories.
We used to go around those places.
Grand steak, Hamburgers, Yakiniku, Churrasco, Jingisukan
and the last one was Dotekins, right?
Is that why they have big breasts?
Everyone,
I made cheesecake, so if it's okay with all of you...
Oh, thanks!
We’re still going to eat?
Natame-chan, I made some chocolate cake!
Wow. Thanks!
I made some Mont Blanc.
My, it looks wonderful.
That's amazing.
It’s short cake today.
As always, it tastes great.
Have you gotten better?
Bath! Bath!
It's good that we get to use the Great Bathhouse, right?
Big baths are the best!
Hello, everyone!
That's something normal.
There's nothing wrong with a little breast groping.
That's exactly what we don't want.
And she doesn't choose her targets...
Eh? Even Rikka too?
What's with that surprised look?
Rikka has substantial tenderness.
The size isn't enough, though.
Nagi really is the best here,
but she's had her guard up the past few days.
Of course I would!
Hanabi and Izumi would instantly strike back.
Hotaru is quite tender, but she's lacking.
I thought you were a groper?
It's my normal mode of defense.
Not sure if I should be happy or not...
In that case...
I'll be looking forward to our fun in ten years.
I guess that's really impossible, right?
That's right.
So for now...
Has Kaito fondled these already?
Not yet...
I see. I see.
Then before it's too late...
Matsuri...
Have your tits grown bigger again?
Now that you mention it...
T-They don't just grow whenever...
You've put on some weight?
My weight's increased by two pounds!
Only two pounds from all of that stuffing?!
Inversely, isn't that amazing?
Is this what you call "eventual weight gain"?
Kaito will now hate me...
It’s all right.
You're cute when you're a little chubby.
It feels good and squishy.
It really is! Squishy. Squishy!
I...
will go on a diet!
www.SubDESU-H.net
Tropical KISS!
Matsuri-chan, that's...
It's a plan to keep my head in the game.
So you had one...
Keep this a secret from Kaito-san.
Good morning! I'll give you my pudding.
Really? Thank you very much!
Kaito-san, you idiot!
Are going to be full with just that?
I won't! No. I mean I will!
It won’t mean anything if you get sick.
It also makes it hard for us to eat.
Please don't mind me.
I'll overcome my weakness.
Matsuri.
This is the cheesecake that came from that popular shop.
I don't need it!
I have some cake here...
I won't eat it
Let's go by the sea on our next day off.
I won't go!
How about the pool?
I won’t go!
This popsicle is delicious!
Don’t eat in front of me!
Matsuri.
Are we really going out?
Oh, a sauna?
That sounds good.
Heated-
Swimming
Pool
Can I come along?
Sauna Room
Heated-
Swimming
Pool
Okay!
Sauna Room
Heated-
Swimming
Pool
Why are you eating dried shiitake?
There was a boxer in a manga that was using this to lose weight.
It releases more moisture,
and it can make you feel full.
I think there's a difference between dieting and losing weight...
R-Ruiku.
Similar phrase
Kurote Tenaga-zaru.
Nomascus
Rufu.
Circulation
Firipin Megane-zaru.
Philippine Tarsier
Ruiji.
Analogous
Jentoru Kitsune-zaru.
Hapalemur
I give up already!
It's fundamental to use the "Ru," offense strategy!
Ru-seme
Ru or some other word that doesn't end in zaru wa...
Wao Kitsune-zaru.
Ring-tailed lemur
I'm not going to win this...
It's already turning back into regular shiitake.
I'm already at my limit.
I can still continue.
Don’t push yourself too  much, okay?
Dried shiitake...
Are you awake now?
This place is...
I thought I should clean the sauna...
And then...
No matter how much you want to go on a diet...
How did you know that?
I carried you along with Fuurin.
They ended up spilling the beans.
B-But...
Matsuri, would you hate me if I got fat?
Of course not!
That goes for me as well.
You don’t have to push yourself.
I love the you that always smiles and likes to eat cakes all the time.
This klutz and stupid me...
Are you really okay with that me?
Of course.
Then, will you kiss me?
Is that okay?
Yes.
Kaito-san...
Matsuri...
Your breasts are amazing...
Wait a minute.
Um...
It's not okay?
Not that...
I just went inside the sauna, so I'm sweaty...
That's not true.
But...
It's my first time...
I'd like to take a shower....
Then why don’t we take one together?
Okay...
What is that?
You're going to
use that later?
Pretty much, yeah.
Matsuri!
No way...
There's just no way.
The length is perfectly just fine,
but it's not thick enough.
It won't fit your mouth if it's anything bigger than that.
Matsuri-sama is a real glutton!
This won't do...
Thanks for the meal.
You're great with regular meals too.
There are still lots for me to learn,
but what I've made today is filled with love!
Sorry, I couldn't hold it anymore!
No way...
Don't you want to do it?
That's not it.
I also want to...
have sex with you...
Still afraid?
I already prepared myself.
It's in, Matsuri
Fu...
"Fu"?
It hurts!
It really hurts!
This can’t be!
I'm going to die!
It's hell!
The depths of hades!
I might be dead already!
I'll pull it out quickly.
Good morning.
Painkiller
Sakai clinic
Suppository
I was prepared for death.
Actually, if I took it before bed, I'd easily gain more weight.
I already told you that you don’t need to.
Oh, but in the future, I might be the one who'll get fat.
No, I don't think they’re really that delicious.
But I'm going to eat your cooking from now on,
right?
Yes.
Umm, Kaito.
How many children would you like?
Children, eh?
Two, I guess...
Me too...
If it’s a girl, I bet she'd be as cute as you.
I'm not really...
I wonder when that'll happen...
But I want them as soon as possible:
our children.
Then why don’t we practice?
What kind?
Copulation!
I thought so!
Does it feel good yet?
It feels...
Eh?
It feels good..
It got wet...
Then are you okay with this?
Yes.
I'll endure it this time.
This is amazing.
The feeling of something inside me...
I'll move now.
What? What's wrong?
Did you strain your back?
It's easier to strain your back when carrying heavy things, right?
I really have to diet after all!
Several days after
Oh, so you've recovered already?
That was fast.
Many things happened...
Man, I really want to get catty with a 2-D girl!
2-D girls are really great.
And you can do your day's worth of exercise by doing it!
It would be the best if you could even diet along the way.
Kaito-kun,
can I leave the water quality tests to you?
Okay, let's finish this quickly.
Matsuri, what are you...
This is called a "titty fuck," right?
I saw an image on your computer.
Since when did you...
How is it?
Your thing is so hot it seems like it's burning.
Are you about to cum?
We're still far from being through.
Matsuri...
You released a lot.
So this is Kaito-san's....
funny flavor!
Sorry, it felt too  good...
But why?
Let's go back now.
We're not finished.
But you just had...
Wait a second...
I said wait...
Well?
It still hurts a bit,
but it's already used to it.
I'll move now.
Kaito-san's big and thick...
Wow...
Not deep inside...
It feels weird...
I can't take it anymore...
About to cum already?
That's because
your thing feels so  good.
Me too, Matsuri...
Just release it anytime you want to.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Kaito-san released lots inside me...
Kaito-san...
Matsuri...
I did it!
I lost some weight!
So that's why...
Matsuri, your breasts are...
I'm doing it on purpose.
Matsuri and Onii-chan really are close.
Yes, we're very close.
Here, say "ah."
U-Um...
"Ah."
Is it delicious?
I don't really know.
Hey, somebody kick these two idiot lovebirds out of here.
We're not idiots!
Not a single shred of awareness.
Their condition's already serious, eh?
Kaito-san! Kaito-san!
That really made me tired...
See you later...
Please give me a goodbye kiss.
Don't put it in, okay?
I won't.
You liar...
I did it. I lost weight again!
Good morning!
Matsuri's full of energy.
Maybe it's being sucked out of me...
Part-time job's done.
And I also finished bathing and cleaning.
There's only one thing to do, right?
That would be sleep...
It starts with the letter "s."
Hey, it’s the idiot lovebirds.
Yes, what is it?
So you're no longer denying it, eh?
Yay! I'm back to my normal weight again!
You really have energy for that stuff.
Matsuri, here it comes!
There!
Hiya!
Am I heavy?
You've done your diet routines already.
So it's okay now.
Kaito-san's thing is too thick, and goes deep in me.
It feels too  good.
Release it...
Release it inside me.
Okay.
Something hot is flowing inside me...
It's amazing...
Kaito-san...
Matsuri-chan...
I-I'm Aoi Matsuri, nice to meet you.
I'm so sorry!
I'm glad.
I'm a klutz, so I thought you hated me for giving you a hard time.
I love you, Kaito-san.
She's currently defenseless...
Shall I attack you?
Just kidding!
I wonder if he'll attack me?
Maybe she wants a kiss or something...
Won't he give me a kiss or something?
No. No. Purge yourself of these dirty thoughts.
Do something already!
I finally found the path that I want to take.
I'll aim to become a Food Coordinator.
Don't cheat on me
for the next two years.
Kaito-san.
What's wrong? Are you really longing for my breasts?
Yep. One year and nine months have just passed.
For me not to be able to hold it for three more months...
Being all good with just breasts...
Are you sexually frustrated?
That's not it.
It's lonely not having Matsuri with me.
Then you are sexually frustrated?
No way...
There's still...
I did my best,
so I was able to come back early.
That's...
Why didn’t you tell me?
I wanted to surprise you.
I still feel like this is a dream.
Then did you feel this?
Well?
I didn't insert my tongue this time.
So you've finally remembered how to do a normal kiss?
I kept worrying about it, though.
We've met here again.
We didn't even promise to get together like this,
and it's even on the same day.
I'm sure there's nothing that'll
ever separate us!
www.SubDESU-H.net