www.SubDESU-H.net
One seat diagonally away from me,
is the seat of Shiiba-san.
She's silent, mysterious,
and she emanates an aura that tells you not to speak to her.
But I know...
What she's really like.
Sensei, my eraser fell and I'm going to pick it up.
Oh, okay.
S-She's close.
This is the first time I've seen Shiiba-san this close.
After school, in the unused room at the end of the building.
Come.
The True Face of Shiiba-san
Little Sister Lip
Why?
Could she have noticed that I was checking her out?
Do you have a girlfriend?
N-None.
Then, do you like somebody in particular?
N-No.
I see, that's good.
Want to do it with me?
Wh-What?
Sex.
What's going on?
Am I hallucinating?
Have my delusions driven me crazy?
H-Hey, wait...
This is...
Are you doing this to make money?
Or do you plan to tell this to everyone to humiliate me?
I don't do those things.
Now I've planted a kiss mark on you.
I'll be taking this off.
Okay.
Wow.
It's totally bent upwards.
I think this will be different from what I usually do.
Oh, so this peels off.
I find it fascinating.
The spot at the end of my sheath is sensitive.
It's just too arousing.
Shiiba-san.
No holding.
Put your hands behind your back.
O-Okay...
Sh-Shiiba-san, no...
Just a little more...
No, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming.
You want to cum, eh?
You see, I want you to cum inside me.
In-Inside...?
Yep.
So, lay down.
Is this your first time?
Y-Y-Yeah.
Then I'll be taking 'it', okay?
Oh, it looks like it's going to burst.
I'm sorry.
No, it's your first time anyway.
And you were about to cum earlier.
It couldn't be helped.
But, I still came inside.
I...
It's okay.
I already took a contraceptive.
Oh, I see.
She did say something about how it's okay to cum inside.
It's still stiff.
Does this mean that I can cum inside her all I want?
I-It's overflowing...
Hey...
It's okay,
you can touch them.
It's gotten a lot bigger than earlier.
Why is she doing this?
There are a lot of things I wanted to ask,
but I've put them aside already.
No, my nipples...
Shiiba-san, the girl whom I could never reach.
I never thought I'd do this with her.
Wow, it's twitching inside me.
Just cum anytime you want to.
It's not that I've developed feelings for her.
I think this weird girl may be too much for me to handle.
U-Umm, we can do this again, right?
This isn't the last time, right?
I... I won't mention this to anyone, so...
See you.
I see...
Until next time then.
Like a venom,
Shiiba-san started to contaminate me inside.
The True Face of Shiiba-san
Can you hurry up and introduce me to your little sister already?
Later.
Hey!
Everyone is envious of the bond I have with my cute little sister.
Miku.
There are actually times when I really want to touch her,
but she is my little sister, so...
W-What? From my room?
I... I think I recognize this...
This is amazing...
Please give me your cum.
Pour it all into my mouth!
Spray it all over me!
Miku!
Oh crap, why did you have to see all of this?
I came here to find and get the DVD you borrowed.
A lot of this lewd stuff just came out.
I thought of how you liked these lewd things, so I just...
I get it already.
Oh jeez.
Don't tell Mom about this, okay?
Onii-chan, do you like these things?
You know, getting a blowjob...
Th-That's none of your concern!
I just couldn't stop watching the DVD once it started.
T-The next thing I knew I was drooling.
Wh-What are you saying?
I want to try it.
Little Sister Lip
H-Hey... Wa-wait!
If you like this, then I...
What’s this?
Did a switch flip in her brain after watching that porn video?
Well...
I... I need to shower first!
Oh crap.
I got really aroused from that.
It's true that Miku's quite cute, but...
My little sister... she's my little sister!
Onii-chan?
I already got undressed in your room.
You...
D-Don't just come in without asking!
Wow.
So it really does get like this.
H-Hey...
It's hot and stiff.
Oh, some stuff is leaking from the tip.
Can I lick your dick?
Oh crap.
I'm getting turned on by all of this.
Miku, y-you're cute.
T-That's...!
Mi-Miku!
Oni-chan's dick feels hot.
It's also twitching inside my mouth.
I can't breathe!
It hurts a bit, but my heart won't stop pounding!
Mi-Miku!
I'm getting more and more aroused!
I'm about to cum!
I... I'm cumming!
That felt really good.
I just sprayed my cum all over my cute little sister.
Onii-chan, this is amazing.
Do you normally cum a lot like this?
Yeah.
Let's take a bath together now.
Forget the bath!
Onii-chan, put some clothes on before coming out!
Huh? Didn't Miku go in earlier?
Onii-chan, you're such a...
Hey now...
What are you doing first thing in the morning?
Onii-chan, you usually do it once in the morning, right?
From now on I'll do it for you.
Yeah.
Mi-Miku!
This feels amazing.
The top of her mouth and tongue are rubbing smoothly against it.
It's getting sucked inside her tender mouth.
I came in and saw your dick like this, so I just couldn't resist.
Onii-chan, your dick is twitching already.
Just cum whenever you want to, okay?
Hey, you're really good at this!
I studied a lot on the internet last night.
Everyone seemed to be feeling great from having sex,
so I thought of giving pleasure to you too.
This time, I'm going to make you cum inside my throat.
The tip is hitting her throat.
Just a little more...
Miku, I came again...
Miku's sucking on my entire dick,
and it's dripping wet with her saliva.
Her mouth pussy is just too erotic!
I... I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
W-Wait, drink it all...
That felt good.
Thank goodness.
I thought that being step-siblings and doing this would get us in trouble,
but I guess it's okay if it's just a blowjob.
I think it's the same as masturbating.
Onii-chan, you idiot!
Little Sister Lip
One day after school, I happened to see Shiba-san.
She was with a man who seemed to be in his thirties.
Her expression was far different from the one she usually has at school.
I really thought that she was a different person.
Of course I was really surprised,
but knowing her secret also made me excited.
I wanted to see more of the Shiiba-san I never knew.
Before I realized it, I was already tailing her.
The place they'd come to was probably her home.
All of my anxiety washed away.
They were actually a close father and daughter pair.
Dad.
Hey, let's go inside first.
Sorry Dad, I just can't wait anymore.
My oh my, what a troublesome daughter.
Oh, you're so wet already.
Dad, the curtains are open.
It's okay, nobody's coming this way.
I simply wasn't able to turn back at this point.
I wanted to see her secret.
Her father was playing with her pussy.
I had already anticipated something like this the moment they did that in front of the house,
but to see it actually happening in front of me...
Amazing, your clitoris is so stiff before I even touched it.
Dad, you're hitting my sensitive spots already!
So this is what Shiba-san looks like at home.
Oh no...
I'm going to cum quickly like this.
No...!
You just cum too quickly.
Why don't you hold it in as Daddy tells you to?
What? No way...
No, I can't do it...
Th-Th-The more I hold it, the closer I come to cumming!
Oh no, I'm cumming!
I'm sorry!
I'm cumming!
I... I'm cumming!
Oh yeah, I haven't heard her moan like that yet.
It felt like a sweet, soft and tender moan.
Shouko, make me cum as well.
Oh wow, your dick is already stiff and big.
Dad, your dick's fluids are already coming out.
Your thing is just too big Dad, my mouth gets tired easily.
Shouko, how lewd you are, masturbating like that while doing this.
Dad, are you about to cum?
I...
Huh?
This is a scene you only see in porn videos.
The inside of Shiiba-san's pretty mouth.
He's forcibly pushing and rubbing it in.
Shouko, I'm about to cum.
I can see it clearly even from here,
the huge amount of sexual fluids flowing out from her...
The cum that poured inside her mouth,
makes Shiiba-san remember the taste of her father very clearly.
Dad, please put it inside the lower hole too.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Please drill your erotic log inside me.
Shouko, it’s making indecent, sloppy sounds.
Dad you're mean.
Here, here.
Have a good taste.
It's big...
It's inside me!
I-It's pushing up to my womb!
Shiiba-san is popular with boys at school.
But everyone knows that they are not good enough for her.
No one would dare confess to her.
Everyone just fantasized about her,
and that includes myself.
I masturbated uncontrollably,
while I tried to imprint the sight of Shiiba-san into my brain.
It's completely penetrating my womb!
I know, you've been twitching inside for a while already.
You're a good girl, so I'm going to pour it all into your womb.
It's totally exposed, as if they're actually trying to show me.
Oh no...
Oh no...!
If you play with my clit like that, I'm going to cum again!
Dad, your cum is about to pour inside my womb!
,We've continued doing the same routine for several days already.
I feel like getting really into this habit now.
Shiiba-san, Shiiba-san, I'm about to...!
Your dick is twitching, you're about to cum already?
I'm going to cum inside!
Amazing, lots of it is being poured inside.
It's starting to overflow.
Shiiba-san, you're ready to answer me now, right?
The reason why you wanted to have sex with me.
I think I may have expected too much.
To think that she might actually have feelings for me...
I just asked her straight without bracing myself.
You looked like the loneliest one in class.
So I thought you'd never mention this to anyone.
F-For some reason, I already understood...
That's all?
Oh good, it's all thanks to my unpopularity, huh?
I became this beauty's sex friend because of it.
This is too intense, it just hurts!
Why? Why am I feeling this hesitant...
Just wait...
You're thrusting too deep!
I know it, your womb is your sensitive spot after all, eh?
What do you mean?
No, not there!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming deep inside!
I'm starting to feel weak.
Please...
Your insides are twitching wildly.
Shiiba-san, you're going to cum again?
I'm going to let you cum with your womb again!
Here I go!
Cum Shiiba-san!
Cum while I'm cumming inside your womb!
I'm cumming!
Damn, why is she crying?
Why did it not turn into the smile that I saw before?
Huh? Are you okay?
Why did you cry?
Oh, I get it.
I understand now.
You wanted to become my special someone.
Am I wrong?
Umm... I...
I see, I did something wrong.
There, there.
I became enamored with her.
Oh yeah, I haven't asked of your name yet.
www.SubDESU-H.net