www.SubDESU-H.net
Part 1
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Part 1
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
W
Hey! It's your classmate, Igawa.
Hey, Yano. If you're there, please come out!
Hey, Yano!
You need something?
Yo, I'm here to give you your printout since you were absent from school...
If that's all, you can put it inside the mailbox out there.
Well, I need to tell you about the subject for next week's test as well.
I personally came here for that one.
I'm sorry if I'm bothering you, but can you let me in for a moment?
Wait a minute!
Come in.
Look at you, you look restored!
Isn't it about time you come back to school?
Sensei and everyone are worried about you.
Is that so...
I sense a "Go home!" aura all around her...
As usual, an unsociable girl...
Mathematics lessons would be from this page up to...
She's a quiet and obedient person, but never gets along with her friends...
...and that's it for French Modern History.
Is that so?
If she were just more open, she'd be even cuter...
If it was possible, I wanted to talk a bit more with her, but...
Sorry for taking so much of your time, I'll go home now.
Before that, can you let me use your toilet?
In here?
That room isn't...
This is...
What... what is all this?!
Err... it's not what you think.
Amazing! You've got all the DVD sets of the Taiga series?
Oh, the Green Bell figure? And even better, it's the limited edition!
Um... Igawa-kun, you're into these kind of things?
If you're talking about Anime and Manga, I'm a huge fan.
In fact, did you see Taiga's suit yesterday?
I watched that, it was amazing!
Yesterday, Hoshino's body suit didn't look like a good design...
but his battle suit was totally...
Yano is truly excited...
The revelation that the main character, Shin Hiyama, and his rival Akai Hoshino are in fact siblings...
That scene really stands out!
I don't know what more I can say except this new series is really awesome!
So, this is the real Yano.
Sorry, I got caught up in talking and forget you were here.
I'm so embarrassed!
Not at all, I honestly hadn't caught that myself!
If you don't mind, please tell me more.
It turns out that she's cute after all.
Oh, it's this late already?
I'm sorry, it's nightfall and I took a lot of your time.
Err... if it's okay with you, can talk for a little longer?
I don't mind, but don't you need some rest?
I'm okay with me.
Then I'll pour us some more tea...
Yes, thank you.
It has been bugging me for a while, but isn't that a sketch book?
Does she draw pictures or something?
It would be bad to look inside it, but...
But, a peek wouldn't hurt...
You mustn't!
Men doing it with men? Isn't this what they call "Yaoi" ?
Don't look at it!
Oh, is he gonna put it inside him?
Are they gonna do it to each other?
By the way, where is he putting that?
In the butt hole...
He saw it! I'm definitely gonna get laughed at...
It's amazing, Yano!
No, I'm really impressed with this!
Even though I like Anime, I can't draw anything this well.
I really admire someone who can actually draw.
That's a lie! I'm always playing hooky to draw things like this...
You must think I'm a disgusting Otaku, right?
No, not at all.
But sorry for looking at your things
without permission. I'm really sorry.
However, it's not really something you need to hide.
Everyone thinks about those things.
It'd be strange to not think about that.
You know that most boys like me think about perverted things all the time.
Even if you're drawing something erotic or yaoi
it's nothing to be ashamed of, instead, you should be proud of it.
It's still talent, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Wait a minute, you took an absence to draw this stuff?
You're not sick after all?!
The truth is...
I can't stop drawing when I get focused on it.
Even so, you still need to attend class.
And of course control your perverted thoughts, okay?
Although, looking at it again, this really makes me laugh.
It's really degenerate, isn't it?
That's not it! Something about the shape is off...
Shape?
Look here, at the shape of this man's thing.
Real ones aren't shaped like that. This really wouldn't fit together at all.
That's because I haven't seen a real one before, so I drew it from my imagination.
Hey, hey,Yano-kun, do you take absences to think about penises?
Geez... you're teasing me, Igawa-kun!
If that's so, would you like to see mine for reference?
Just joking, of course.
That's not something you just say to anyone... Eh?! What's with those sparkling eyes?!
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
You don't just go around showing it to others, you know?
Besides, Yano, you wouldn't show yours off either, right?
Actually, yeah! Let's see each others!
Yano?
Hey, wa-wait...
Well?
Whad'ya mean "well"?! Put your clothes back on!
I've taken off most of my clothes. I'm almost naked myself.
I don't have anything to be afraid of.
Moreover, who's the one that peeked at my sketch book?
I hate an Otaku who can't be honest with himself.
Look... there, that's pretty different from what you're drawing, right?
Amazing, It's getting bigger and it looks like it's alive.
I am alive, you know?!
Looks delicious, like it has a strong power within.
But the tip has a pink color, so it's kind of cute.
How should I say this, it's something I want.
Yano, st-stop it...
Yano, stop...
Here it comes!
I swallowed it.
Igawa-kun's sperm...
Yano, why?
What is it, Yano?
Are you okay?
No, don't touch me!
Hey, is it possible you came?
No, that can't be...
Would you spread your legs?
No, you can't do it right now!
You can't do this after teasing me.
No, you can't!
Yano, you're totally drenched here.
Amazing...
No, you can't touch...
It's dirty...
No, it's beautiful.
That's not...
I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
Em, Yano, I don't want to kill the moment for you, but...
They've gotten totally soaked!
That's really awful, Igawa-kun!
Awful? Isn't that your doing?
That's not true. It's a common thing to drink it, right?
No, I'm not gonna do something weird like that.
I drank Igawa-kun's sperm, didn't I?
Well, it's okay.
In exchange, if you'll go all the way with me... then I'll forgive you.
You really are dirty you know.
That's...
It's going all the way in.
Yano, putting it in like this...
You are taking this too far.
If you like this, you're more than just erotic.
You're perverted.
No...
Per... vert... girl...
No, that's not true!
I'm sure that while you were absent, you masturbated, right?
I don't do that...
If you lie, I'll stop doing this.
No, you can't...
I do it every day...
I look at Doujinshi's and touch my clitoris while thinking of penises.
You really like penises, right?
Penises... I like penises!
Yano, I can't...
Let it out...
Please let it out!
Inside the deepest part of my pussy!
Do it! Do it!
Here it comes!
The sperm is inside...
As I thought, you are mean.
You're saying that I'm erotic, lewd, even perverted.
Yet you're the same as me.
The same...
You're a total sadist, for god's sake.
But if you say that, then you're like a super masochist who likes perverted things.
That may be true, but I'm not denying it.
You're not gonna deny it?
But, thanks to Igawa-kun...
Because of you... I can...
From now I can...
I can draw a realistic penis!
That's it?!
www.SubDESU-H.net