Playing-around romance makes me into a wicked woman.
True romance... turns me into a coward.
So, what do you think of this room?
I had it made specially for you.
You know I'm quick at getting things done, right?
Hey, don't you want to do it with me?
I-Is that really okay?
That's what you called me over for in the first place.
You too, really want to do it so badly you can't help yourself, right?
Not really.
What's this? You're not wearing any panties.
A media creator who goes commando?
What's with that? Panty lines show, and I don't like it.
Amazing. It's already wet, and your nipples are already this hard!
Yeah, I'm all wet, and my nipples are getting excited.
All of that... Can't you tell by just looking?
Don't say any unnecessary things.
More... Do me more, okay?
Immoral Wife
Numashiri Rieka's Perverted Inclinations Come to Light
W
Here, look closely.
You want to put it inside here, right?
Look, it's already like this... Come on...
Hurry up!
This is dangerous... it's squeezing so tight around me i can't hold back.
It's fine. You can do me a little roughly!
Thrust into me as much as you want!
Just like that!
Harder!
More!
Go all the way in!
How is it? It's hitting you all the way inside, right? It's good, right?
Whatever!
I'm... about to come!
Good!
Inside... inside me... come inside... come inside me!
If I come inside, we'll create a child, won't we?
Go on... that... it's doesn't matter...
All of it! Inside me! Inside, inside me! Come inside me!
Good! Come! Release it! It's fantastic! It feels so good!
Release it! Release it!
It's begun, hasn't it? The two-colored solar eclipse.
For us, a two-colored one is special.
I wanted to go to Amami this year too, but...
It's fine, isn't it?
As long as you write and sell another song?
I don't like that song.
It sounds like standard J-pop.
I don't get why it went to number one.
Everyone's strange!
Now, now...
Ah, we've finally found you.
You've got guts.
W-What are you guys doing?
That's no way to say hello.
Don't you know whose woman that is?
Um, yes?
He's...
Who? I can't be made fun of this way.
Go to his house and tie him up!
She belongs to the president of our company!
That's can't be true!
Rieka! Why didn't you tell me something so important?
Whatever.
And you Nee-san is the way you are too! Why did you betray the president?
Did the president have problems with your company or something?
Not particularly.
Well, that's a nice attitude.
We have instructions from the president to punish you.
I... never... planned... to create... a reality... like... this...
I realize now that I have utterly betrayed you.
As an actress, as a pro, as things I never became, and as a person, I realize that I am still inexperienced.
For every kind of trouble that has come from this event, I plan to take full responsibility!
That's good, you've got guts.
First, I'll have you service me with your mouth.
Hey, now, take it further in!
You were plotting against the company president, weren't you?
This is mortifying! I can't breathe...
What's this? Your pussy is all dirty inside.
Look up here.
Yes, yes, that's it!
When im looked up at like that,
I can't get enough of it.
It's lonely with just your mouth, isn't it?
Don't get so flustered.
I'll give it to you now.
This one... She's feeling it even though she's getting raped.
Her pussy's seriously tightening!
A bitch like this... Now that I think of it, I guess I'll come inside.
She's in so good shape. I can't stand it!
I'm being violated... both in my mouth... my pussy...
By such dirty men!
I'm being raped...
She's totally feeling it.
This is such a good pussy!
It's a first for me.
Don't, no! I'm gonna cum, I'm going to cum!
I can't get enough this squeezing...
Same here...
Im going to shoot a load!
Now, now, I can still cum!
The fun... starts here!
How is it? You can completely see my dick filling your pussy, right?
No, I can see it ...
It's thrusting deep into me.
Yeah, that's good.
This is a nice display.
No! My the insides of my pussy and my ass are rubbing against eachother...
To think we've can even completely explore your ass.
As to be expected from the president's woman.
A-Amazing! Their dicks, their dicks are...
My pussy is being torn apart... My pussy is tearing!
You liar.
The truth is that you feel good like this too, right?
No, not at all...
Look at that. Both her ass and pussy are covered in semen.
Well, I guess she's been totally messed up by this.
She's probably repented by now.
Hey...
A-Are you... already done?
Huh?
I'm not satisfied yet.
Let me cum more and more.
Hey, I said cut it out! Nothing more is gonna come out!
Im all out of sperm!
Don't say that. Your penis is already wet with semen, and it'll start to feel good soon.
You're kidding, right?
We already fucked you that much!
The office said I had to apologize, but I've always refused to.
I didn't want to do it. I said that it was my way of doing things.
Huh? You... What are you saying?
I gave in in the end, but that was a mistake.
I said cut it out already!
If you do it so roughly... I said it hurts!
It felt like, "Go ahead, bash me!"
There are many different values in the world,
so I think it's impossible to be recognized by everyone.
What are you talking about?
I enjoyed it just a little bit when they first talked about me.
But when too much was said, I was shaken off.
Y-You... There really is something wrong with you!
Your penis is throbbing.
It's hot!
Me too... I'm...
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!!
That's enough, isn't it?
My heart rate is already at 100%.
No way. The fun starts here, doesn't it?
To make up for getting in the way of the two-colored lunar eclipse,
you have to make me feel good now.
Eh-... I'll get cumming problems!
Playing with romance makes me a wicked woman.
True romance... turns me into a coward.
Numashiri Company
So, what were your impressions of men other than me?
Swamp Buttocks
I'm not divorced... yet
They weren't good memories.
Swamp Buttocks
I'm not divorced... yet
It was really awful, like a nightmare.
Like I thought... no one other than me... can be your partner.
Japanese movies are so boring. I want to change Japanese movies!
That's it, that's it!
I totally don't understand what you're saying,
but that kind of thing is just like you.
Ah! P-President! Your cock is so good!
More, more! Fuck my pussy more!
Looks like you've finally gotten in the mood.
Our younglings weren't enough.
Yes. My pussy, my erotic pussy...
It's getting so sloppy wet... I can't hold it any longer!
Okay, I'm going to do the moving, so make it tighter!
Yes, I'm tightening! Im pussy is properly tight, so...
Go deep, all the way in...
I-It's rubbing...
It's so good!
Right there! It feels really ... good!
How about it? You can feel it here, right? Seems I'm the one who knows the most about your body.
Not really... it's not...
Oh? Cheeky, aren't you?  I'll go stronger then till the end!
Not really... Not really...
No, no...
I'm... not really...
not really...
Im about to cum...
No...
It's not really...
not really...
not really, not really...
not...
not really...
Good!
What, have you given up already?
When it comes to sex, I'm your senpai. I can still keep on going.
What's the matter?
Not really.
What's with that? That's all you say!