Training... I see...
Starting next week it will be for about 3 months.
I see.
I'll be lonely.
After I come back from training.
I'm thinking of telling the principal about us.
Then you can finally wear that ring.
Eiji-san...
Mi...yuki-san.
No...
You can’t...
From this point...
No... Sorry...
I’m happy but...
I want to do this after we get married.
Sorry, I just got too excited.
Eiji-san, are you mad?
No I’m not.
This is who miyuki-san is.
I feel more in love with you.
Thank you Eiji-san.
W
Mesu Kyoushi
Injoku no Kyoushitsu
Part 1
I’m  messed up...
Wow!
In the ass...
Its hard!
The carrot!
The carrot is....
The carrot...
Carrot carrot, you’re so noisy.
Are you not satisfied with just one?
H...hey wait...
It's hard...
The two of them are rubbing.
No… forgive me.
Putting them together…
No… the hard thing is rubbing inside.
Don’t twist it...
My ass is spreading!
Misawa-kun and Hasekure-sensei.
What are they doing?
It's big...
I want it.
Misawa-kun’s…
That’s...
More…
Deeper...
It's inside…
The hard thing is sticking inside me!
It's hard!
It's too hard!
It's thrusting my ass!
It's hot...
It's getting hot...
It's rubbing inside.
It's hot....
It's flowing out.
No…
No...
Not the boobs!
You’re so hot.
Inside this…
What’s inside this, huh?
That’s… milk.
Its full of milk...
My boobs...
I feel it.
If you… thrust that… deep...
My boobs.
It's good.
It's good...
I’m cumming!
Misawa-kun…
Why did he do that to Hasekura-sensei?
But Hasekura-sensei seemed happy about it.
What’s the meaning of this?
Miyuki-sensei.
Yes?
Sorry for disturbing you but can I borrow your ruler?
I lost mine.
Sure you can.
Is something wrong?
No... nothing.
Thank you very much.
After school,
at the same place.
I think I need to talk about Misawa-kun to Eiji-san.
Did you tell her as what I ordered you, sensei?
Yes...
I see.
For your reward I’ll release a lot into your throat.
Well then I’ll be going.
Did you wait long?
Misawa-kun.
Why are you here?
Of course because I’m the one who called you.
Eh?
Or… Were you expecting Sanada-sensei to come?
How did you know that?
I don’t know.
I just wanted to talk to sensei.
W… wait...
Why here...?
What…
Are you going to tell me?
You don’t have to be scared.
No…
Nooo!
Stop it!
Stop it please!
That's some sexy underwear you're wearing.
No… not there...
No...
No…
Forgive me...
You really can’t...
Even though you say that...
I know that you feel it.
That’s a lie...
That’s a lie…
That’s impossible!
Please…
Let go of me.
Stop it please.
Noooo!
Stop!
It's all wet.
Nooo!
S-Stop...
I’m going to put it in now.
You want it right?
No... stop…
Help me!
Someone... help me!
No!
Hey… spread your legs more.
No...
I’m going to move.
It hurts!
Don’t move!
Please take it out.
It's squeezing.
It's tight.
Please…
Stop it...
No...
Help me… Eiji-san...
It hurts…
Please...
Help me...
Your pussy is getting sticky with this juice of yours.
You’re feeling it even though you’re being raped by student.
Ah...
No…
No...
I’ll be releasing.
A lot of semen inside your pussy.
No!
You mustn't do that!
No no no no!
Please don’t do it!
Please forgive me. Please don't do it!
I beg you!
No!
You can’t release it inside.
Pull it out.
It hurts.
Don’t release it.
Its coming in...
Inside…
Sanada-sensei.
Makiyama-sensei...
Lets go for dinner.
Sorry... I can’t...
I felt lonely when I heard that Sanada-sensei won't be around because of his training.
I felt I wanted to be with you.
S...sorry...
Makiyama-sensei...
Y-Yes?
Do you know where Toudou-sensei went?
No I don't.
Maybe she went home already?
Is that so...
Well then...
Sanada-sensei...
Eiji-san...
The picture...
Got messy...
Hey...
Don’t you think today’s Miyuki-sensei is weird?
She’s so dark...
Did something happen to her?
Miyuki!
Miyuki what happened to you?
You’re so absent minded.
Makoto...
The students are worried that Miyuki-sensei is feeling down.
I’m sorry.
It's just…
I’m not feeling well.
If you feel that bad...
You should leave early.
It's alright.
Hey Makoto.
It's about Misawa-kun in my class...
Misawa… Did something happen to him?
No… Not really.
Miyuki…
But…
I didn’t think that I’d be called here by Makoto-sensei.
Misawa...
Don’t tell me you also laid a hand on Miyuki?
Huh?
What are you talking about.
Don’t pretend you don’t know.
Don’t lay a hand on Miyuki.
Wasn't that enough?
Don’t misunderstand.
Are you in a place where you can oppose me?
Please…
Please don’t lay a hand on Miyuki anymore.
In exchange...
I’ll do anything for you.
Oh… anything?
You can do anything you like.
What’s this?
Are you telling me to wear this?
You’re too intelligent to be a sports minded p.e. teacher.
Now, wear it.
O-OK...
It suits you.
Making me wear this…
Are you going to do some hentai play again?
You like it right?
Didn’t you feel it last time?
I...
Didn’t feel it.
Don’t blab around and suck it.
I’ll just have to suck it right?
Not like that.
Suck it like this.
It's getting nice and wet.
Squeeze it with your big boobs next.
Y…yes...
Like this...
Suck the tip.
Like this…
You're feeling it while you’re sucking it right?
No I’m not...
How is it?
Are you satisfied?
Turn around.
You’re a masochist whore.
It suits you.
I’m not a masochist whore.
It's all wet.
You whore, you want my dick right?
I won’t put it in if you won’t say “I want it”!
Yes...
I want it...
Huh? I can’t hear you.
I want it!
I want your dick!
Put it inside this whore's pussy!
Let the visitor watch you.
Mi…
Miyuki…?
No... it's so sudden...
Miyuki is watching me.
No...
No... pull it out!
Miyuki this is a mistake.
This is...
This is a mistake.
You’re revealing to Miyuki-sensei that you're masochist perverted whore.
Its too embarrassing.
Here, whore!
Let her watch you properly.
It's so deep...
If you stir that much...
My boobs will...
It hurts...
Its coming out!
You’re squeezing it too much.
You’re such a dirty whore.
Don’t say that.
Its numb...
Its getting numb...
You should be happy.
I’ll be releasing a lot inside your pussy again today.
Its so good...
I’m cumming! I'm cumming!
Why…?
It means you’re pregnant.
No... way...
Okay then...
I’ll be going...
Take care of your self.
Is something wrong?
You look pale.
No...
I’m fine.
Do your best in your training.
I’ll be waiting.
Okay, I’m going now.
I’m sorry Eiji-san...
I'm... already messed up...