A-Ai...
Can you lick around it a little more?
Like this?
Yeah, right there.
It feels good...
You're getting really hard.
Are you going to cum?
I'm nearly-!
In that case...
Go ahead, you don't need to hold back!
Relax yourself using my mouth, Sei-chan...
Se-Sei-chan...
A-Ai...
I-I'm gonna cum!
Amazing!
I'm sorry, Ai...
SubDESU-H
You've already revived...
In that case, I'll put it in.
Se-Sei-chan...
S-So deep...
It's warm inside of you, Ai...
H-How is it...?
Does it feel good?
Sei-chan, are you feeling aroused?
Y-Yes...
Your hips are moving so intimately.
I'm getting aroused just by looking at it...
Pervert...
Don't look.
Don't move so suddenly...!
It's bad for your foot.
I'm fine!
N-No, I’ll cum-!
It feels too good! I can't stay still!
No, no-!
It's too intense...!
I-It feels good!
Se-Sei-chan!
I love you, Ai!
I'm glad! Please feel more aroused!
Feel more aroused because of me!
Ai-!
N-No...! I'm going to cum-!
M-Me too-!
Cum, cum! Release all your milk inside Ai!
Ai-! Ai!
Se-Sei-chan!
I-It's coming out...
It's coming out...!
S-Sorry for cumming inside you, Ai...
No, it's alright since it's yours, Sei-chan.
Ai...
This girl is Fujisawa Ai.
She's my girlfriend that I got acquainted with at my part-time job.
Since I got hospitalized after a motorcycle accident,
she has, in between her university studies and part-time job,
come to visit me every day.
Your neighbor will be back soon, right?
And...
This long hospitalization will bring us closer.
Eventually, we had come to where we even began to make love in the hospital room.
Sei-chan, umm...
If you get backed up again, don't hesitate to tell me.
Ai...
I thought that times like these would last forever.
That won't happen, Shouko-san!
Nakamura-san, as soon as the X-ray room is free, we're going for your check-up.
So please be ready.
I'm going to open up the curtains.
Yes.
A c-check-up?
Nakamura-san, please don't leave the curtains closed.
I-I'm sorry.
What? Ai-chan! You were visiting again.
Shibuya-san...
You're pretty as always.
H-Hello.
Soon I won't be able to meet you either.
I'll soon be discharged from the hospital, you see...
So, in celebration, won't you accompany me to dinner?
What?
H-Hey...!
It's a joke! Just a joke!
Seiji-san's so short tempered!
Right, right, don't be jealous.
You shouldn't overdo it either, Nakamura-san.
You have to get better quickly,
otherwise it's a pity for your cute girlfriend.
Well then, please get ready.
Okay...
And Shibuya-san, you should also be quieter.
Then won't you date me instead?
Idiot.
To be honest...
there was something about that nurse that I was hiding from Ai...
That's no good, Seiji.
If you don't act more natural, then she'll find out.
What are you doing?
We've already broken up.
But your cock is already this hard...
T-That's because you're doing that-!
Fine then, if you're going to say something like that...
Should I tell that girl, Ai, about me being your ex-girlfriend?
W-What? Y-You idiot, don't do that!
How scary...
Night shift is sexually frustrating, you know...
Hey! Wait...!
I'll keep it a secret from her, so...
Only once, okay?
Sho-Shouko...!
Hey, hey... Can you tell...?
My pussy's so wet...
This is great, your cock's getting harder and harder...
It's not that you dislike me, is it Seiji?
You came to this hospital because I was here, didn't you?
N-No, it's just a coincidence!
When I was carried here by the ambulance, it was by pure coincidence...!
Really...?
I was waiting...
Waiting for Seiji's cock.
Sho-Shouko...
How is it?
Is it painful?
Do you want to put it in?
I'll put you at ease now...
Amazing!
It's coming deep inside me...
This rubbing sensation is...
I-It's irresistible-!
When we do this, I remember the first time I had sex with you.
You had a rather difficult time finding the entrance.
Back then as well, I went ahead and put it in.
That was a long time ago!
Seiji's getting bigger again!
You're feeling aroused thanks to my pussy, right?
Y-You've got amazing vitality...
Even though you already did it with Ai-chan during the day...
What?!
I know that you have sex with Ai-chan in the hospital room...
T-That's... Y-You see...
I'll shut up.
So make me shut up with your cock.
Se-Seiji...
L-Like that... so intense...
Here, right?
It feels good here, right?
S-So good...
Your cock... your cock, it's-! It's churning up my insides!
Se-Seiji...
That's it, thrust more. Thrust more!
Your cock, it's-!
My pussy is being shaped by your cock!
Sho-Shouko!
Se-Seiji, you're feeling good too, right?
Your cock is twitching...!
It feels good-!
My pussy feels so good!
Idiot! Shut up!
Y-You're gonna cum, right!?
You're going to cum inside me, aren't you!
I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum from Seiji's cock...
Seiji...
Say...
Is there a chance that you like me even in the slightest?
Stop it.
You already know that it's over.
I already have Ai.
Seiji, you idiot!
You could have played along for a bit...
T-Thanks...!
I'm going to be late for my job!
T-That's right...
A girl like that is not fit for Seiji...
That time...
If I had been a bit nicer to Shouko...
Me and Ai's fate might have been different.
I'm a bit late today. I wonder if Sei-chan is waiting?
Yo, Ai-chan!
Oh, Shibuya-san!
Do you have a moment?
Huh?
Um, what is it that you want to talk to me about, Sei-chan?
Geez, why are you being silent?
Nevermind, I need to get going. Sei-chan is waiting.
Well, I was just lost for words when I saw this picture of you...
W-What?!
W-What is this?!
...So please take this for today.
Ai... You're pretty late today...
Did she have to work overtime at her job?
Hey! Are you listening?
Y-Yeah.
Geez! I was saying that you're going to take a different medicine today!
S-Sorry.
Here you go, take it before you sleep.
Got it, I will.
So many medicines... I'm not used to taking so many...
At least you're getting them.
You need to hurry up and get better.
Otherwise it wouldn't be nice for Ai-chan, would it?
I can't do such a thing!
What?
Then what should I do with this picture?
Should I show your family?
How about I put it on the Internet?
No! Don't take such photos! Please delete them all!
Then do what I ask!
No!
C'mon!
All you have to do is suck me with that cute mouth of yours...
If you resist, it's just going to be harder on you!
It'll be easier for you if you suck it properly!
Hey! Don't you understand your situation?!
Do what I say.
You're quite good, aren't you?
Se-Sei-chan... I'm sorry!
This feel good...
It was worth holding back just so I could do it with you!
Ai-chan, that a good expression. I'm getting more aroused!
Mine is bigger than Seiji-san's, so isn't it better?
Oh? You want to suck on me some more?
H-How's this?
P-Please hurry. Hurry up and finish so I can go!
That good! Yes, that's it-!
I can't hold back! I'm gonna cum!
Drink it all up!
Oh no, you're all dirty now.
Looks like I have to teach you again.
What? Umm...!
What is it?
Do you think I'll be satisfied by cumming only once?
N-No way... You promised... Please delete those photos...
Not knowing what was happening to Ai,
I was in a deep sleep from the medicine Shouko gave me...
I didn't know about the tragedy that was coming next, either.
You're awake?
It's time, Seiji.
Sho-Shouko!
What is this?!
Seiji, something interesting is about to begin!
It's fine!
Seiji-san is asleep from the medicine, so he won't hear us!
Hey, you know what's happening beside us, don't you?
Stop it!
A-Ai?
No!!
Ai!
Don't look!
P-Please don't look!
Ai-!
Yo, Seiji-san! You're awake!
I thought that the first time I did Ai-chan should be in front of you.
No! Don't undress me!
Why is this happening to Ai?!
Stop it!
We can't do that.
Seiji-san was so enthusiastic when I told him about this...
Shouko-! You-!
You're the bad one, since you didn't pay attention to a woman's feelings...
...No, don't!
Oh really? You're already soaking down here!
No, no!
P-Please, I beg you! N-Not sex, anything but sex!
I-I'll do anything else, so please-!
P-Please!
No way.
No, no!
You'll soon start craving my cock!
Here you go, Shouko-san...
W-What?!
Oh my, what a beautiful pussy...
You have to become used to men, Ai-chan.
W-What did you put in me?!
No! I'm getting hot down there!
N-No!
M-My body, it's getting so hot!
This medicine?
It's a strong aphrodisiac. It makes even virgin girls want cocks!
I bet she can't help herself from wanting it either!
No!
M-My insides are-!
Hey, say: "Please give me your cock" in front or your boyfriend!
You'll be thrilled!
No, no!
No! Sei-chan! Sei-chan, help me! Please help me!
Shut up!
Now then, how about we show your boyfriend you getting fucked?
It'll feel really good!
S-Stop it-!
Stop urging me on. Don't worry, I will.
Bon Appétit, Seiji-san!
No!!
It went all the way in!
P-Pull it out! Hurry up and pull it out!
It feels great inside you!
It's sucking me in so much that I can't pull it out!
Ai!
N-No! Don't thrust like that!
Don't lie, your insides are clinging on to me!
Don't move! I-I'm gonna-!
Ai-chan, you're the best!
What's this, Seiji?
You've got an erection from watching Ai-chan get raped?
I'll be the one playing with you...
Here I go.
How is it? Does my cock feel good?
No! Don't move it!
Hey! If it feels good, just say so!
There's no way that it feels good!
Ai!!!
Once that medicine is used, all you can do is cum like crazy.
I'm cumming again-!
I-It feels so good-!
Looks like you're being honest now!
Where does it feel good? Say it in a louder voice!
My pussy feels good!
I can't get enough!
No!
Then I'll keep doing it!
No-!
No more!
I'll start feeling good again!
Then I have to do it harder!
No! I said you couldn't!
I'm gonna cum, even though I don't want to!
I-I'm gonna cum again!
No, no!!
Stop it...
How can I stop?
I have to cum and relieve myself, too!
That's it, Seiji. Cum inside me!
C'mon, show Ai-chan how it's done!
Ai...!
No... No-!
I-It's churning me up!
No more, pull it out!
Pull it out, please!
I-I'm gonna cum!
For it to be fulfilling sex, you have to cum inside, don't you?
No! Please, please don't-!
I'm, I'm gonna cum!
No-!
Thanks for the meal!
Shibuya and Shouko raped Ai and I until dawn.
As quickly as they had come, they were gone.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Sei-chan...
Ai kept apologizing to me with those unfocused eyes...
I did such perverted things, didn't I...?
Ai!