What's a sophisticated-looking girl like you doing in this shop?
No!
Hey! stop it!
Rikurou, she's your customer, do something about this!
If you think you can do better, be my guest!
Calm down.
Aren't you...
Otonashi Miki?
I would like you to find my lost brother.
Although I started out by myself, I can't do it alone.
But a great detective like Annerose...
... will definitely find him.
Or so I was told by a brown skinned lady.
Brown?
Oh, you mean Aishya-san.
I'm surprised you came alone...
... to a terrifying town like this.
Amidahara, one of the worst of the destroyed cities in Japan.
Some call it “the Dark Neighborhood”.
In a slum where humans mix with beings from the underworld,
criminals and murderers have disputes every day.
It’s a lawless land.
Rikurou-san?
Tachibana Rikurou-san?
Are you listening to me?
Yes, of course, Miki-chan.
Is there something on my chest?
N-no! It’s just been so long since I last saw a human girl... I let my happiness distract me.
Leave it to me.
I will definitely find your brother.
Th... thank yo-
Why are you acting so lovestruck, you stupid human!
Ouch!
What the fuck are you doing, Michiko?!
Hmph! I finished my shopping so I am leaving!
I will ask Annerose-san about it.
Let’s meet here again tomorrow.
Hurry up! Stupid human!
Witch of Steel
Annerose
What the hell was that?
Who do you think you are?
I am Michiko-sama, that a problem for you?
You're just Annerose-sama's maid.
Do not order me around!
You have a real demon in front of you.
A mere human shouldn't talk back!
Jeez.
You have a cute face but the worst personality.
Just to let you know...
What?
Although you seem to have an interest in Annerose,
she is mine.
You're a hindrance.
So it’s best that you die here.
Wai... Michiko-san?
Stupid human, I'll just say that you were eaten by a mad demon dog.
Th... that's not a very funny joke.
I'm serious.
Die! Stupid human!
Here we are, little doggies! It’s dinner time!
Thank you for saving me!
Let’s get o-
I like you.
You're mine.
You're now my undead slave.
You're awake.
Although this was already awake.
Aishya-san!
I... when did I...?
When did you get a boner, you ask?
No that’s not what I...
It’s so hard.
It stood up nice and tall as soon as your body repaired itself well enough.
I'd expect no less of a dick Anne chose.
By the way, that girl called Miki?
You were the one who introduced her to me, right?
Ah, that Machine Gun Girl?
I am glad you met her.
Aisha-san, why are you doing this?
I've been interested in you for a while,
or at least interested in this.
You are a bit cute,
but other than that,
why did Anne take on a useless student like you?
Please tell me that secret.
There isn't any secret...
Keep this quiet from your master.
Look how much pre cum there is.
I am sorry!
I like licking this pre cum.
Aisya-san!
I love smelly and thick pre cum! I love it so much!
You've got nice eyes.
I am going to peek in to your future.
Future?
First time getting a blow job?
Y..yes, it is.
Yes! Ram it, slam it!
Take my mouth and throat!
C'mon, deeper!
Deeper?
Shove it deeper into my throat!
Rape my mouth pussy!
Harder! Harder! Fuck my mouth pussy!
Aisis... Aisis!
More! Do it harder!
Rape my mouth pussy!
Aishya-san!
Make Anne do the same to you!
Make her use her mouth and tongue on your dick!
Swear you will!
Annerose-san?
Amazing!
It’s so thick and delicious.
What is this?
This is a world of your own.
I touched some power within you.
You are amazing!
I nearly died of your semen.
What do you mean by the power within me?
You're an immortal whose soul was stolen by a witch.
But not everyone can be like that.
It’s because of the unbelievable power within you.
Me?
Even if you're her dead knight...
... Michiko went too far.
I will help you punish that demon.
Use this.
This?
Play it near her when she is sleeping.
I'm back... I’ve returned.
Riku?
Where the hell were you playing, slave?
Annerose-san...
Because you came late...
I had to make dinner.
Michiko butchered me into pieces.
Again?
Well, then in that case, aren't you a bit earlier than expected?
It’s because Aishya-san picked me up.
Aisha did?
I've known her since we were kids.
She is a sadist who enjoys watching people in trouble.
Don't get involved with her.
Understood.
I am going to bed.
And it’s your fault.
I drank too much.
Then I am going to sleep, too.
Foolish human, you'd better clean everything up.
Or else you’ll be punished.
Shut up!
Annerose-san told me not to, but...
I won’t forgive Michiko!
What was that?!
What the hell is this! I can’t move at all
This is Aishya's magic power.
Is it you? Are you the one who did this to me!?
That's a good posture you've got there,
Michiko.
Shut Up!
Hurry up and undo it!
No, I won’t.
Try and remember how much I've suffered because of you.
Well, um...
Beheading you on the road, drugging food to paralyze you... and...
and what else?
Today you cut me into pieces with your axe.
That's right!
I even put dog food on you so they would eat you!
You're a stubborn one. Idiot human!
So you...
...don't want to...
repent your misdeeds?
What are you doing?!
Don't move. It’s dangerous.
It’s cold!
Stop that!
Why are you cutting as you please?!
Stop it!
There we are!
Don't say that!
And don't look, stupid human!
Don't pretend to be tough,
Michiko.
Stop!
Don't... don’t touch me there.
I can't believe it’s twitching so violently.
Michiko could it be that...
you frig yourself!
You perverted demon!
No I don't...
Stop.
If you won’t confess, then...
take this!
I don't frig! I don’t...
You're still not telling the truth.
How about this?
No stop!
You're soaking wet.
You're so wet! Take a look! Take this!
No, no!
I will... cum if you do that!
I will cum from an idiot human's hand!
Go on! Cum with your tingling clit!
I’m cumming! cumming, cumming, cumming...
Michiko...
Something is gushing out from your pussy.
Don't look!
I am wetting myself!
Don’t watch!
Your pussy looks molten.
You look so cute right now.
I'm not going to forgive you for saying that!
Have a look.
Y... you're going to rape me... with that?
Yeah, Michiko, I am going to fuck your brains out with this.
This is your punishment.
I'm putting it in.
Look...
Michiko, your pussy is full of my dick!
You're a virgin?
I won’t forgive you!
That's alright, I'll happily be guilty of popping your virgin pussy with my dick!
Here, lick my fingers.
Awesome, you're making such perverted noises.
You're getting aroused so much from my dick!
Good... it feels so good!
Just for now...
Let’s make up for now.
Your womb... It will belong only to me!
Don't thrust it too hard!
You're going to crush it!
If you keep doing that I will become your idiot woman!
I am cumming! I am cumming in your pussy!
No! I don't want to be your woman, you stupid human, so don't!
No! Even though I am a demon, a human made me cum!
Very satisfying! Michiko, was it good for you?
I will kill you!
Heh heh! Seems like you're not yet ready to make yourself my girl.
We've only got a truce.
Okay...
Can I punish you again?
D-Do whatever you want....
I will punish you some more and make you a complete whore!
Eh? Morning already?
Annerose-san!
Gotta wake her up!
As usual. What a vulnerable sleeping position!
Who'd believe this is the Steel Witch Annerose,
who shook the whole of Amidahara.
Even though I endure this every day,
I can't hold it back today!
B... but if she wakes up...
Said of someone who wakes up very slowly.
Anne Rose-san has very low blood pressure.
It will be fine.
Be brave, Tachibana Rikurou!
You're a man!
Awesome!
It’s so soft!
You cock tease a naive boy like me every day! It's all your fault.
She is feeling it!
I am glad to be alive!
T... this is her.... what I’d only dreamed of until today...
I can't take it!
I am going to do it!
Could it be?
Is she awake?
Could it be that she is awake and accepting me?!
Her nipples are so hard.
My dick is arousing her!
Awesome! Her tits are so soft and hot!
It’s coming! it’s coming!
Awesome.
I came all over her face.
Here, Anne Rose-san, drink all my jizz.
Still not satisfied?
I understand.
Your cunt's aroused, Anne Rose-san?
Then I'll do this.
I will make you cum with my finger, Annerose-san.
Annerose-san, go on! Cum! Make that pussy twitch!
I knew it! My fingers aren't enough! I won’t be able to satisfy her with my fingers alone.
I am putting it in, Annerose-san.
My... my dick is inside her pussy... my dick... my dick...
... will slam in so hard it will hit your womb!
What? Riku!
Annerose-san, you're dreaming.
Sleep a little longer.
A dream?
No way, she's a virgin too?
Awesome!
I can't believe I am her first man!
I will make you feel more!
Riku!
What...?!
Annerose-san!
Annerose-san!!
It’s no use. I can’t hold back anymore.
I am cumming!
I am going to release my hot jizz into you!
I'll cum inside. I can cum inside, right?
Annerose!!!
Awesome.
Shit, I came so much, what do I do?!
Tissue!
Riku, you're heavy.
This is, um...
You...
What have you done?!
A slave raping his master!
I hope you're ready for what’s coming!
Um... well...
Well... that was an obvious punishment.
Annerose-san...
I've found you,
Anne Rose.
Nasu beki mono to toki to sadame
What must be done is time and fate...
Sameru made no yume to kodoku
And the dreams and loneliness that are present until sleep ends.
Nasu beki mono wa migi-te ni ari
What must be done is in my right hand...
Sore dake ga shinjitsu
That and only that is the truth.
Sashi nobeta hidari-te ga ima
My outstretched left hand is now...
Mata chi ni somaru
...Once again stained in blood.
Kono sekai wa kodoku dakara
Because this world is lonely,
Mata dareka no na o yobu
I will once again call someone’s name.
Kikoeru no wa uso ni naru etakae dake na no ni
Even though all who can hear are painful lies.
Takaneta no wa migi-te ni aru iroasenu fufui yume
That fluffy dream in which I hold a rose in my right hand is still vivid.
Sore wa yagate ienu kotae o sakebu
And in time, they will scream out a wordless answer.