www.SubDESU-H.net
Futa-Club!
SubDESU-H
Part two
Please don't.
Don't drip here  now.
Huh?
It's locked?
W-Where's Akane-san?
I wonder which one they usually use?
Do they stand up? Or sit down?
I can't bother her while she's cleaning.
No, I don't think so...
It's quite easily to scrub off,
so it's quite easy to clean, right Aya-chan?
Well, it does have everybody's smell in it.
Huh?
Oh, but it is kind of aromatic actually.
We also have lots of lubricants around here.
The smell can even be quite distinct, depending on the person.
As punishment for that, I'm the one who's going to tease you from now on.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
Just put up with it.
Hey...!
Wait... Stop that!
I'm the one offended this time.
I don't get to do this very often you know.
Here I go.
There, there...
I get it already.
Let's hurry up and do something nice shall we?
Your thing down there is all mine for today, got it?
How did it turn out like this?
Oh well.
But just today okay?
Yep, I understand.
Sorry, you don't get to work this time. Too bad.
Hey, don't talk to it like that!
Aya-chan you're cute.
Hey sit down.
Then spread your legs.
You look embarrassed!
That expression is ill-suited with your large dick here.
Shut up.
Hurry and just do it already.
Alright, alright.
Now then...
Here I go.
Your pussy... The entrance feels tight, but it feels really great.
Now we're really getting it on.
This small but delectable pussy...
It's kind of shaped to be my personal hole, right?
And it's so tight, that I feel like cumming already.
I'm about to cum!
I'm about... I'm about to cum lots!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
This feels great, Aya-chan!
Cumming inside is the best!
My cum won't stop flowing!
Ai!
You came lots as always.
Hey, the cum I poured inside is overflowing.
But that's okay I guess,
because I'm about to cum a lot more.
I'm going to fill your insides with cum until your tummy bulges.
B-Bulges?
Just wait a bit.
Ow!
What are you trying to do?
This is payback for always teasing me during club activities.
Now, how about we get a taste of this hole then?
Hey, that's...!
I know that you just love being fucked anally.
Stop, don't...
It's wrapping me just as tight as your pussy.
And your asshole is squeezing me as it twitches.
I know, I'm sensitive down there.
Also, please get this off my dick.
Oh well, here you go then.
Your ass...
I can release it all inside, right?
Are you stupid? I can't take any more of that inside me.
It's okay, I know you can take it all.
It's still coming out!
Whew, that felt really satisfying.
I haven't felt that relieved in a long time.
You did well.
I think we just went over a liter.
Well, ain't that good for you now?
Being able to cum all you want like that.
Looks like we have to clean again.
You went overboard!
You understand what'll happen later right?
Nessie!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Stop thrusting that into me!
Here comes Nessie!
Stop saying that!
Silence, save your complaints for later!
We'll settle this with our bodies!
Scream out loud!
Where's the president?
Whew, primary emergency procedure complete.
It's a good thing the prep room was open.
But at this rate...
Was it okay for you to have used our brand new sex toy?
Akane-chan?
It's not good for you to sneak around doing things like that.
But, I just felt an irresistible urge during class.
I was about to get a boner.
I can't get a boner in front of other people.
I had no choice but to head for the club room, but it was locked so...
I'm sorry president.
I see that...
The medicine you drank yesterday finally worked.
Medicine?
Did that have to do with my sudden arousal?
Yes.
I thought a little prank like this wouldn't hurt.
That's terrible of you Sumika-san!
Well, it's not all that bad is it?
You were always with Akane these past few days anyway.
Well that's...
This is our long awaited opportunity to do it by ourselves...
Sumika-san.
I've prepared something different for this today.
I think it feels a bit too tight.
Now, Mao-chan.
Spread your legs a bit more.
Sumika-san, your eyes scare me a bit.
Of course I'll get really horny, seeing that I can thrust myself inside president's pussy like this.
It's normally like this, so it's pretty hard to hide.
Just stay as the cute president you are for today okay?
Was it always this big?
For you to give me a straight blowjob like that...
Your small mouth feels great.
Oh no, please wait.
I haven't cum in three days and I've decided to release it all inside you.
Here I go, president.
It'll go straight through your womb if I try to push it in all the way.
So I'm going to start enjoying it this deep.
Don't twist your dick inside me.
My insides feel tingly all the way to the end.
Your insides feel really good, and I'm going to cum inside.
Is that okay?
This feels good but, my dick feels very tight.
It wants to get hard and stiff.
I'm going to cum president.
The cum that I built up for three days is all coming out
All coming out inside your small womb...
President, please put it all the way inside next time, okay?
That definitely won't fit.
It's okay,
futanaris usually have their female sex organs made to fit their own male sex organs.
R-Really?
It's going in... It's going in...
It's in, all the way to my womb.
Sumika-san, please hurry up and set my dick free already.
But, this...
Feels quite good actually.
I'm not fainting yet...
It feels great, but it hurts a bit.
You have to endure it president.
Because your dainty pussy also feels great for me.
Both of us feel good in a different way.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Asakura Mao, boner at 100%.
Vice-president Sumika-san.
I'm going to have to insert this too.
Oh wow, so this is president's monstrous beast.
I understand president.
I'm going to let you cum inside me.
No...
If this continues, I'll lose consciousness...
Why?
Why am I tied up like this?
It's dangerous for you to go wild with your 100% boner, president.
Here I go.
Are you ready?
Hurry up and wrap around my dick already.
Here comes her hot pussy!
You really did it now president.
Hurry up and move already, I can't hold myself anymore.
It's going in,
and it's trying to widen my insides.
Here, have some please.
It's tight, but it feels great.
It feels like the insides of my womb are about to bulge out.
Your insides feel good.
Hey, Akane-san, join us here too.
Yes!
It got even bigger inside.
Take this president.
This is the president's cum...
Sumika-san!
Actually,
I've already prepared my pussy to be able to take your dick inside.
No wonder my dick entered it so easily.
So, how's my pussy?
It's wet, slippery, wraps me well, anyway it generally feels great.
I'm glad that you liked it.
I'm envious.
I think I want a dick too.
Huh?
Jeez, please don't laugh.
There is a somewhat familiar stinky smell.
What the heck is this?!
And we've just finished cleaning the bathroom!
Jeez, I don't want to do this anymore!
www.SubDESU-H.net