www.SubDESU-H.net
Catch!
Okay, here!
Written on swimsuit: Hitomi
Let’s see, this way this time!
What are you getting stimulated over during class?
Understand?
We’re swimming in the ocean today, so safety comes first.
If you rough around too much, your feet might slip.
Or if you get a bloody nose, you might attract sharks.
If you act foolishly, you very well might put your lives in danger.
Um... Hikaru-sensei?
What is it?
...The headmaster is in trouble.
Well then, since I’m taking the headmaster to the hospital,
you'll have the afternoon off!
Eh?! No way.
Go home on the bus by yourselves.
How horrible!
It’s just crabs.
You’re a teacher, teach, damn it.
Then I will begin my time off.
Bye-bye!
Kou-chan!
We don’t know how to swim.
W
I did manage to run away... but what’ll I do now?
Let’s fuck!
Wh-when did you follow me?
I thought I could get away safely alone since the three of you can’t swim.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Listen, today Mr. Alligator helped me.
You came prepared...
Hey, do you like my school swimsuit?
Well... I do think it’s cute...
That makes me happy!
I wanted to please you, so I went out of my way to buy it on the Internet.
...You don’t have to go that far for me.
But, Kouta, you like this, don’t you?
Well, well, maybe... I don’t dislike it...
Come on.
Look this way, too.
Pet me.
You’ve fucked Ai-chan.
I know about that.
How do you know?
Shit!
Okay, fine.
You got away last time, but... you’re gonna do it properly today.
My pussy juice is already flowing.
Don’t call it a pussy.
But it is a pussy.
Touch my tits too.
Oh, what naughty hands.
Wait a sec...
Kouta, your fingers... they’re so manly...
They’re big...and so warm...
K... Kouta...
Oh, you pervert...
You really do love school swimsuits...
That’s not... exactly... it...
Hitomi, I do like the way you look in that swimsuit.
So sexy, I can’t stand it.
Oh, now you’ve said it.
Don’t rub me so hard or I’ll...
Inside... touch me inside too.
Okay...
Kouta, your sexy fingers are driving me mad.
Put them in... put them inside, please.
Your sexy fingers... they’re making me feel so good.
My pussy is melting...
Pussy... My pussy... it’s getting wetter.
Wetter and stickier.
Oh, yes, there! That feels great.
Kouta... you made me cum again.
Now I’ll suck you off.
Hi, Mr. Dick.
How’re ya doing?
Ahh! You’re turned on.
You’re so cute, Kouta.
Not even in the slightest.
Oh, really? Then maybe...
Your juices are a bit salty.
Aren’t they tasty?
I guess they are.
I’ll suck it clean.
Mr. Dick... you taste so good.
Kouta, lick me too.
The anal feels so good, but... please be gentle.
This one, too...
I’m gonna lick your balls.
Oh, but I’m so... sensitive there...
It’s okay to let loose, Kouta.
Squirt your semen on my face.
Your semen!
Kouta’s dick milk!
Kouta’s flavor...
More! I want more on me!
Hey... next use your dick here.
What?
Since you bothered to wear a school swimsuit, I want my dick to experience that.
Does it feel good, Kouta?
Yeah. It feels excellent!
Yes, but I think it would feel better inside.
Really?
Yes, but... this also feels good... your dick rubbing against me feels good.
Kouta... rub harder.
Rub my clit hard!
Hurry, put it in or the tide will get us...please?
Okay, fine.
Your dick is coming in.
Kouta’s dick... it’s been a while.
So hot...
My pussy is getting hotter... by your dick.
Hitomi’s pussy... it’s getting hotter!
Yes!
Your dick is so deep in!
Harder!
Fuck me harder!
Awesome!
My pussy is being rubbed so hard!
Kouta... oh...
You’re in too deep... in too deep...
Hitomi’s pussy... will break apart!
Yes!
Kouta’s dick... I love it!
Hitomi’s pussy is throbbing!
Harder!
I want more of your dick!
I want your semen!
Hitomi’s pussy wants... Kouta’s semen! Please!
So hot...
Hitomi, where were you?
I was off playing with a sea cucumber.
Sea cucumber?
Huh? Rui, you already got dressed?
The bus is about to arrive,
and the shower is a bit far away.
Hurrying is for the best.
I agree.
Then... Hitomi, let’s go.
Okay.
Wh... what is this??
Kick ass! Over there too.
Panties... mine!
Kouta-kun, nice work.
Well, let us go home now.
Wait up, you two!
What are you gonna do with my panties?!
Give them back!
Finally... we’re alone.
Wasn’t that a bit forced?
It’s your fault I’m losing my mind.
With you nearby, I’m always so aroused.
You were the one who opened that door inside of me.
You need to take responsibility for your actions.
In such a place...
Kouta-kun, you’re too bold.
We are now entering the freeway.
Rui... you’re soaked through.
I told you... I’m always soaked around you.
Your penis... I want to lick it.
Rui-chan, you bitch...
She’ll fucking pay for this!
She didn’t have to take our wallets with her.
Kouta-kun.
Please, put it in quickly.
Rui’s pussy wants it.
Hurry.
Spread your legs more.
Kouta-kun, your penis... your penis...
Your dick... you don’t need to hurry.
Why not?
Because we’ve just barely started.
Were you always that sensitive?
Sensitive? No, I’m still fine.
So please, mess up my pussy more.
Oh no.
Harder, harder.
Rub my tits too.
Please rub my tits, right?
Please... rub my tits...
Kouta-kun...You can cum inside of me today.
Okay... then inside...
Kouta-kun, your penis... your dick, it’s making amazing noises.
You’re cumming!
So much semen is coming inside!
Kouta-kun...
You’re being too rough.
My pussy... it’s flooding!
Ai-chan... are we still walking?
We have no choice. No cars are passing by.
But I’m tired. And I’m hungry.
Shut up and walk.
This time, use this hole.
I want it anal next.
I’m at the age... where I want to experiment.
K..Kouta-kun!
Please, just a bit more gentle.
My butthole feels so...
Kouta-kun, your dick is so hard.
It’s throbbing inside my anus.
It’s your fault for having such a sexy body.
That’s what makes it throb.
Make me turned on by my asshole.
Make me even sluttier!
Kouta-kun... kiss... I want a kiss...
My anus is hot...
It feels so good!
Me too...
I’m almost there...
You can pull on my tits. it feels so good.
Your dick is going all the way inside... all the way inside my butt.
Touch my pussy more.
Fuck it up more.
Front and back... both feel so good!
My butthole, my pussy, my butthole... both are so good!
Oh no!
Kouta-kun, your semen, shoot it all inside.
I’m cumming!
Kouta-kun...
Won’t you break up with Hikaru-sensei?
Break up? But we’re not even dating.
Kouta-kun, if you keep fucking us this way, we’ll lose our minds.
That’s easier said than done...
But I suppose one good thing came from all of this.
One good thing?
Kouta-kun, you’ve gotten better than before.
But if we lose our minds any more over you...
Then what?
Then I think we’ll punish you without restraint.
Rui...
Brace yourself for a tri-pussy attack!
Ai-chan, how much further?
Maybe an hour?
Could it be... you’re lost?
Th... That’s not it at all!
I wanna go home.
It’s breezy... and my pussy is getting cold.
See? So are you.
I guess even this experience
will go down as one of the most memorable moments of the summer.
Kouta-chan, do you love your sensei?
Wh-why do you ask?
Well, because it used to be that just a little stimulation would
give you a full hard-on.
Well, I guess I just got used to it.
“Used to it”? Meaning, you’re cheating on me?
Cheating? I’d never...
Hey...did you think I wouldn't find out?
Well...
Don’t misunderstand, I’m not giving you the typical girly, “OMG,
he cheated on me?! Waaah!” reaction.
It’s just that...
I’m pissed that you’re not getting hard from this and I want to know why.
Sorry, ma’am.
Or is it maybe that Hikaru-sensei’s pussy doesn’t get you off anymore?
I assure you, it’s not that!
And here I thought that at least in the dick department, you were a grown-up...
These subtitles were made by SubDESU-H, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
What shall I do?
What’s this for?
You girls!
Sensei, you misunderstand.
Kouta...it’s not his fault he’s not hard.
We can make him perfectly hard.
Sensei, we think perhaps your womanly wiles are insufficient.
What the fuck are you saying!
Compared to you little girls, I am far more...
But, just see for yourself.
We know how to handle men.
So, Sensei, we’re going to borrow Kouta-kun for a while.
Hey! Wait up! Where are you going!
Come back here!
What’s going to happen to me?
Hey!
Fun times are waiting for you.
Right.
Tonight, all night.
And plenty of it.
www.SubDESU-H.net