SubDESU-H.net
Why do I... have to be... the demons' meat?
Stop it already... you scum...
If... If you do that...
...I'll... cum again...
...even though I... don't want to cum.
Ariya... Ariya!
I'm so sorry.
This is... all my fault.
Stop it, please!
I don't care what you do with me.
But... But don't hurt the baby.
No!
Don't! If you do it so hard...
...it'll come out... it's coming out!
Don't...
There are babies inside of them...
I-If you want to violate somebody... violate me instead!
I-I'll do anything!
Milady!
We were ordered by the war god Odin...
...to fight to protect Midgard... as war maidens.
But...
...we got caught in the foul trap of the demon king's forces...
...and were captured and held as prisoners.
The demon king and his troops stole our purity... our virginity...
...and soiled our bodies over and over again.
Being raped by ugly beings...
...getting humiliated in front of humans...
...this humiliation was just for the sake of the demon king and his troops' satisfaction.
Not just our pussies...
...also our mouths... our asses... all of our bodies got sticky with sperm.
And now, even having been made to bear their demonic children...
...the days of rape weren't over.
W
War Maiden
Valkyrie
「Master, please forgive me for being naughty...」
Episode Three 「Shameless Sexual Repentance」
After being captured by the demon king's troops, the most shocking thing for me was that...
...among them were Freya, the goddess, and...
...Skuld, the war maiden in training.
They, who became the demon king's pleasure slaves...
...betrayed Odin, the war god, and all of us.
While Ariya and Reia were about to give birth to the demonic children...
...Skuld and Freya toyed with me as if I were their plaything.
P-Please... let me go to the toilet.
No we won't, Lady Hild.
We haven't even started yet.
No...
Don't put any more in me!
You see? There's a lot going in.
S-Stop it...
My stomach... will break.
How many bottles does this make?
You can fill her up quite a lot.
No...
...don't push!
I-It's leaking...
If you want to go to the toilet, you have to make me cum, Lady Hild.
F-Freya-sama...
...this penis is...
This cock's nice, isn't it?
It grew courtesy of the demon king's powers.
The demon king's?
Come on.
You will make this cock cum with your mouth and your hands.
This...
...this is embarrassing. I can't do this.
Oh? You're rebelling against us?
You might need some punishment.
Right away.
D-Don't!
Please spare me from this!
Well, isn't your ass-pussy getting hot?
N-N-N-N-N-No!
No!
If you don't do as we say, I'll inject more into you.
I understand.
I'll do it. I'll do it, so...
No... more... enemas.
Here, hurry up.
Y-Yes...
How is it? Isn't cock delicious?
Cock's... delicious.
Oh my. She admitted it just like that.
Lady Hild is unexpectedly lewd.
B-But I can't change it.
If I disobey, it'll mean more enemas.
You love to suck cock, don't you?
Try saying it loud and clear.
Yes... I love... sucking... cock.
A... war maiden... who loves cock...
Okay, I'll give you a reward then.
Hm? Your pussy's already dripping wet.
You were turned on by sucking cock, huh?
Th-That's not true... not true...
As if I'd get turned on from that...
S-Stop it!
It's leaking... I'm gonna leak.
Oh my... your mouth's empty.
Lady Hild is so perverted.
You're twitching inside and squeezing the vibrator.
You're such a slut.
You're good with your mouth, too.
Lady Hild, I feel it with my cock.
The best mouth pussy ever.
No!
I'm... I'm just being forced to.
Feeling good when being forced like this...
...Lady Hild, you really are a masochistic pervert.
N-No!
I'm not a pervert!
There's no way I should be feeling good from this.
Why? Why does my body react like this?
I'm about to cum!
Lady Hild...
I'll cum in your mouth!
Your sperm-stained face is beautiful, too.
Please... hurry... hurry and let me go to the toilet.
I-I'm at my limit!
Are you stupid?
We're not letting you go now we've come this far.
N-No way!
B-But you promised!
Lady Hild...
...please show us all of you.
No... it's coming out...
...coming out...
...oh no...
Wow, it's like a water fountain.
No... don't look... don't look.
Don't look!
Cumming while shitting...
...it's only a matter of time until you fall, too.
Exactly.
My body and mind at that time were already...
War Maiden Valkyrie 2
It's all my fault.
Because I got captured by the demon king first...
...Ariya and Lady Hild were also...
After they took the humans hostage, I did what they told me to...
...and they violated me until they eventually became worn out.
"I'd rather die"!
...is what I thought over and over again.
But as I was thinking about my friends and comrades, I tried to endure everything.
I was desperately trying not to give in, but in the end...
...the demon king and his troops were planning to break my heart rather than my body.
What's going on?
Why is Lady Reia...?
Are we really going to do it here?
Of course.
If you don't like it....
...I can also kill all the humans assembled here.
No way!
Well, could you start then?
Just as I explained earlier.
Understood.
...is she going to...?
Everybody... everybody's watching...
Me being naked... everybody's...
Hey, don't just strip...
...you should say something as well.
Yes.
Everybody...
...now, I...
...war maiden Reia...
...will be...
...masturbating...
...in front of you.
Please take a good look at my dirty masturbation...
...my breasts and my pussy... Get a good long look!
It's okay, everybody. Don't hesitate.
Come closer and watch.
I'll show you all of me.
Please don't look at me with those eyes.
It's not what you think.
I don't have a choice since I'm doing this to protect everyone's lives here.
Reia, you have to spread your legs open wider or else not everyone will be able to see.
Yes.
More... spread them more.
Show them the inside of your pussy.
Is this all right?
Yes, like that.
Keep going in that position.
You have to beg for everyone's attention.
Understood.
I beg you, please, look at me more.
I'm diddling my pussy in front of you!
Embarrassing... it's so embarrassing...
...but I have to do it.
Look, it's my pussy...
...my perverted pussy.
It's dripping wet.
You should be able to hear the dirty sounds.
My nipples are standing erect, too.
These subs were done by SubDESU-H.net. These ungrateful assholes just stole our subs.
I get turned on while being watched. This makes me feel good.
I guess it's about time.
No...
No!
Lady Reia!
Lady Valkyrie!
I can't hide anything in this position.
All of me can be seen clearly.
Don't make such a fuss, you guys.
She wanted this herself.
Isn't that right, Reia?
Yes, it's true.
I want to show you my naughty self...
...getting violated by tentacles.
Please...
...look at me.
Now I'll be fucked by tentacles...
...fucked by tentacle cocks... in my pussy.
Look.
It's amazing.
My pussy is being penetrated by tentacle cocks.
My clitoris is also...
...incredibly stiff. So dirty.
Enough already.
What are you doing?
Oh gods.
They're talking about me.
The perverted war maiden... I...
How is it, Reia?
Doesn't it turn you on to be watched by everybody?
Yes.
It feels good.
It feels great!
My body feels hot, and it's like everyone's eyes are violating me.
W-Why?
Even though I'm being forced to do dirty things, I'm starting to feel good.
Who would've thought that a war maiden would be such a loose woman?
Everybody is probably disappointed.
Everybody, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I'm showing you all my shameful spots in this tied up position.
Wow!
It's rubbing in my ass, too.
They're making me... feel funny...
This is a special service.
You feel it in your ass, don't you?
Yes.
Ass...
My ass-pussy...
...ass-pussy...
...if you do it that hard, I'll feel good.
Good, just like that. Show everybody your shameful self.
Wow.
Harder, do it harder!
Screw my pussy... my mouth...
...and my ass.
Screw me hard!
You're about to cum, aren't you, Reia?
I'm cumming...
My pussy is so hot and twitching... it'll melt!
Watch me!
I'm about to cum!
Look... look at me! Watch me!
You were begging for real there, weren't you?
N-No...
I wasn't.
It was for the sake... of the people...
In fact, she was right.
I was feeling good while begging for perverted things.
War Maiden Valkyrie 2
After I was captured by the demon lord and his henchmen...
...I was disgraced so much...
...but I desperately struggled not to lose my honor as a war maiden.
But Duke, the leader of the demonic army...
...was enjoying my resistance...
...and tortured me even more... even more violently...
Yes, that was a short while before they made me bear this demonic child.
Duke and his henchmen made me a laughing stock that night.
Endure it... however cruel and shameful it may be... I'll show you that I'll endure it.
For I am Lord Odin's war maiden!
What's up, Ariya? Do you feel like obeying the demonic forces?
Fuck you!
Who would obey such fiends?
Seems I have no choice.
I don't want to lose to these... men... who try to enslave by force.
I won't lose at all costs.
A woman in pain and suffering is quite beautiful.
How's that?
Should I just rip out your nipples like this?
You... heretic!
Do what you want.
Do you really think that torturing me whenever you want is acceptable?
Just hurting you is quite pitiful, isn't it?
Let's change our approach.
What?
What... what is this?
Stop it...
How's the taste of this current?
If you're the war maiden I expected you to be, you should be able to enjoy this stimulation.
Don't be ridiculous.
There's no way this could feel good.
I like your expression.
No!
No, don't! Don't look!
What's going on? Did it feel so great you had to pee yourself?
Duke, it's useless whatever you do.
Even if I'm barely alive like this, I won't give in.
I don't care.
If I can't use you, I'll just use the other two.
The sister you hold so dear.
I wonder if Hildegard could endure this much.
S-Stop it! Don't lay your hands on her!
Then you should know what to do, right?
You scum.
If your body won't bend with pain, I'll just embarrass you completely.
I'll toss you into pleasure.
Make all these orcs here cum.
All of them?
I'll have the ones you couldn't make cum use Hildegard afterwards.
I got it.
I'll take them on... all of them.
If you want to rape, rape me then.
...As much as you want.
Endurance.
I'll show him that I'll endure it.
If I don't endure this, Lady Hild will... And the others too...
They've used my mouth...
...my breasts, and down there too...
...and even my ass, so much that it's sticky everywhere.
But it isn't over yet?
Their meat poles are still getting hot and hard.
Isn't it...
...enough already?
This time, I will personally stain your body.
This won't happen.
No... if you put something that big inside my body... it'll...
Wow, your pussy feels like it's falling apart.
That's all these guys' fault!
But still, you're squeezing my dick so hard.
You feel good, right?
Liar. I wouldn't feel good from this.
Don't lie. You should know best.
No, this is... this is...
Don't... if you do it so hard... I'll...
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Your pussy is twitching.
It's no use.
I've been raped so much down there, it's like electric shocks.
I can't hold it any longer.
I'll strike the final blow with my sperm!
Stop!
If you make me cum again, I'll...
No...
Thinking about that now...
...I might have already fallen at that moment.
Just like Lady Hild and Reia.
War Maiden Valkyrie 2
One Year Later
At this time... for us...
...war maidens...
...the demonic forces...
...and everything else...
...became unimportant.
Just to strip off all our clothes...
...get naked...
...and wish to get raped by hard and fat cocks.
That's all we were thinking about.
After we gave birth to these abominations... the demonic children...
...we became slaves of the demonic forces...
...no...
...slaves of pleasure.
We might not be able to go back ever again.
Sister...
...I'm sorry.
I'm... cumming... again...
I'm about to cum!
I feel so good, even though I shouldn't...
...even though I shouldn't... my body feels so good, I just can't stop!
It's alright. It's alright to become perverted.
Let's all... together...
I'm cumming!
No!
SubDESU-H.net