Hello guys, long time no see.
Do you remember us?
Sign: Disappearing pill
Oh, you forgot?
Then for your sake, let me tell you last time's plot.
One day, a dull part-timer, Mie Naito-kun accidentally acquired a pill that makes you disappear.
From then on, he was doing this thing, that thing and such thing every day.
But, those days didn't last long.
And at last he was found out about what he had done and was punished badly.
The pill was kept in a safe box and the matter was settled, but...
BB Store
SubDESU-H Presents
The Invisible Stud Returns
Part One
cigarette
delicious lunch
Tadaaaa!
Wow, is that the bag you bought last time?
I got it through a bargain, but many people wanted it so it was hard acquiring it.
Tsk. Why are women like that?
Mie-kun, did you say something?
No, I did not.
Welcome...
Hello!
Oh, long time no see.
Come in.
Long time no see.
Oh, it's just loli, thin and fat one.
I’m not a loli.
Who the heck is thin?
Don't say such things to a customer.
I’m sorry.
How are you then?
I've been fine since you took the pill.
Tsk. What a boring youth.
Did you say something?
No, I did not...
I’ll bring you some tea so feel at home.
Ok.
Give me meat bun and bean bun.
I must settle things with this one soon.
Hey look, right now this is called jire.
Eh? But my grandma said it's a vest.
Vest? It’s my first time hearing that.
Really?!
Which one should I choose?
Suzu wants pink, right?
Hmm, I think so.
What have you been looking at for such long time?
I'm imagining the thing which I can't see.
You still haven't changed Mie-san.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Oh, you still can make it, if you want to be a lolicon character or a thin one.
You're still saying it.
I’m not a loli.
Uhm... I'm here for the interview for the job.
Oh, you're Yurigaoka-san, right?
Come this way.
So let's start with cleaning up the mess outside.
Ok.
Many people throw their trash everywhere so pay attention when dividing them.
Ah, you’re right.
Sheesh, it's a shame that many people have low morals.
Ohhh! I can see everything.
Hey, hello?
Ugh, it's all messy!
I hope there's no panty.
But I think it's all the same.
Really there are a lot of people who don't have any morals.
Yeah, really disgusting.
Mie-kun.
Eh?
First, you must get rid of your moral!
If I’m to do this, then I can also...
Just watch...
Get bigger, get bigger...
It can't be...
There's no way it could be, right?
Hoop
Sheesh, why did the bra disappear?
Ugh, the wind is passing through.
I hope no one notices...
Hey, look at that!
Natsuna-chan's dvd is on sale!
Wow, amazing!
I'm tired.
But the weather today is nice, it's warm and...
The sunshine tickles me and...
Maybe I'm a pervert for feeling good at such a place.
Ahh... It feels so good.
Why does it feel so good?
Why?
This is so weird...
Don't... At such a place...
Mie!!!
W-What are you doing so suddenly?!
You still haven't learned your lesson?
What are you talking about?
You undressed Suzu-chan and made her cum in front of so many people.
Who else will do that?
What?! You say I made that loli cum in front of many people?
It's too much that you made her cum in front of many people.
Stop the non-sense, I didn't make her cum!
Please don't say cum, cum.
Yes, and besides at that time Mie-san and I...
And I?
Umm...
You mean you were with him?
Y-Yes...
Hmm? If that's so, then...
Wait a minute, before continuing don't you have something to say to me?
Yeah...
Damn, I’ll make you pay for this.
Beside, you're the one who is holding onto that pill.
Maybe it's stolen?
Anyway let's check it.
For now, the safe box is here.
Mie-kun, look away whilst I enter the code.
Ok, ok.
Different place... Different place...
Ok, I'll open it now.
Hm?
Where are you looking at?!
I’m sorry.
It's here.
Then this means...
This means there's a another pill and another invisible man.
W-What?!
I sensed someone just now.
Really?!
Maybe it was just my imagination.
Don't surprise me like that.
Anyway, we're hopeless right now.
Everyone be careful when you're going home.
Ok.
Go home, go home.
Another pill and another invisible man.
Ooops, ouch.
Eh?
Huh?
What's this?!
You're the invisible man, right?!
Who exactly are you anyway?
Hey, stop it.
Stop it I said.
Hey, I'll not forgive you if you go any further.
Are you listening?
Stop... it...
You!!!
If you do it again, it won't end just like this.
Don't...
No!!
Stop it, please.
Stop it please, I beg you.
At such a place...
Stop it, please...
I said don't...