It's been a while since I came here.
Isn't it quite a nice place?
My ass is numb from all the shaking around on the path coming here.
Although, that was nothing compared to the fun that we're going to have here.
Shu-Shuji-kun, I can't hold back...
We're really allowed to have sex with those two, right?
Hey, you don't seem to understand that you're an extra here.
I'm going to tell you my intentions right now.
My wish is for them to have the utmost discipline.
For that reason, we can't just use them, we have to train them.
So then, lets start Kurata Ibuki and Miyauchi Akira's training, shall we?
A week at a summer resort! I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah! I've never won a prize before.
Looks like this summer is going to be great!
I agree.
Say, Ibuki...
Huh? What is it, Akira?
Ibuki!
Akira... we're here already?
Shuji-kun?
Ibuki...
Hey, hey. What's with the attitude?
I'm a sensitive person; you'll hurt my feelings.
Why is Shuji-kun here? Where are we?
I also want to ask where we are!
Yakushima!  Why did you kidnap us?
You don't have to shout, I can hear you.
As for the first question...
This place is something like my summer resort.
And the reason we brought you guys here is...
"We"?
We're here to use and train you along the obedient path.
Be serious! You kidnapped us for such a reason?
Shuji-kun...
Yakushima, I bet you feel that you've won. However, you're wrong.
Right, Ibuki?
Yes! Our families know that we're on a holiday.
If we don't arrive at the inn, our families will be notified.
That's right! What you guys are trying to do will be found out in no time!
Quit being assholes and let us go!
Should we tell them the news, Kazuma?
The vacation contest isn't real. In fact, I made it all up.
In other words, the whole vacation is a setup.
W-What? That means-!
That's right! That week of vacation is actually with us.
Why does it have to be us?
You probably won't have trouble getting girls, right?
It's probably those eyes...
Eyes?
I told you to move! Yakushima Shuji!
Are you listening to us, Shiji-kun?
You two are the only ones who despise me at school.
Forcefully doing those with sharp glances...
It's my favorite activity!
Right then, which one should we start with?
For an entire week...
You want me to be your playmate, right?
Ibuki?
It looks like it.
Then... I'll be the one!
So don't touch Akira!
Hey, Ibuki!
I'm the one who entered the contest,
which means I was your target from the beginning, right?
Please release Akira.
W-Wait up! I'm the one who despises Yakishima the most.
I'll be your playmate,
so don't touch Ibuki!
Akira...
I said I'm training you both.
If you don't touch Akira, I'll be your playmate without quarrel.
However, if you even put a finger on Akira, I'll never forgive you!
Hey, Ibuki... I said that I'm going to do it...
Fine, then.
In respect of your beautiful relationship, we shall only train one.
Shuji!
Then I will.
Ibuki, I said that I will!
Hm. Akira, I shall train you.
Shuji-kun?
Since you did suddenly punch me when you woke up...
We shall teach you manners as well.
Hmph, what's wrong with hitting the bastard who kidnapped you?
Isn't this great, Ibuki?
So, let's begin.
Wait, no Shuji-kun!
Akira...
Akira!
I'll have you keep your promise.
Akira~! No!
Oumori, sorry to keep you waiting...
This is your cue.
Akira hates you the most,
so you can start off.
W-What?!
Didn't you hear my order?
I'll definitely be killed...
Shes good at Karate, right?
It's fine, she agreed beforehand
that she'll keep her promise.
Don't tell me that just because you don't want to,
you're going to let this 'thing' have a go at your friend?
This 'thing'?
R-Right. I'll keep my promise.
So you better keep it, too.
Akira...
She said it's fine.
Oumuri, what do you want her to do first?
G-Give me fellatio.
What's a fella-tio?
Fellatio is when a girl sucks a guy's dick with her mouth.
Don't tell me you don't know that at your age.
O-Of course I know that!
I just have to lick it, right?
It stinks.
It's sour!
Akira...
P-Put it in your mouth...
D-Didn't you say just to lick it?
I-I'll teach you real fellatio!
I'm c-cumming!
N-No...
Okay, now for the real thing.
R-Real thing? But I just...
You don't think that this was alright?
I guess you're not the type to enjoy it rough, however, bare with it, okay?
And if you don't agree...
Fine, then.
Very good! Now I'll have you first.
Huh? You don't want me to?
Then Oumori, will you do it?
R-Really?
W-Wait! Anybody but him!
Geez, which are you going to choose, Akira?
T-That's...
You don't have to choose.
Well, it just means that we'll take Ibuki's virginity instead.
Hmm?
Yakushima is fine...
You sure are hated, Oumori.
N-No way...
Well, that's what she wants.
No! No...
No~!
Your underwear is wet.
Did holding Oumori's penis in your mouth make you wet?
No, it's sweat! It's because I got sweaty!
Is that so?
Ouch!
Stop it!
Stop it! It hurts!
It can't be helped.
Then, here I'll...
No, not there!
No~!
It's too stimulating!
No, really! It's too much...
No! I'm-
Since you're this wet, you want me, right?
That's not true!
W-What are you doing?
Why of course,
I'm putting it in.
N-No!
It hurts!
Nooo~!!
So you were a virgin.
Well? How does it feel to be a woman?
No...
Pull it out, pull it out!
Hey, if you fidget that much, I might cum inside you.
No!!
D-Don't you move-!
I told you not to move!
S-Stop it!
So deep-!
Don't do such lewd things!
It feels good taking your virginity.
How about I cum inside you?
No, don't do it!
No, don't! Not inside! Absolutely not inside!
No! I don't want it!
Put it out, pull it out!
No~!
N-No! It's coming out! Lots of it...
No! Noo!!
No! It's filling me inside, I'll become pregnant...
Well then, the curtains have now been raised.
Akira, now we're getting to the main act.
Stay away, stay away!
Please stop it!
Akira! Akira~!
Did you sleep well?
There's no way I could sleep.
Moreover, what do you want?
I have a suggestion.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
No, please stop it already. I'm feeling funny-!
How does it feel to lose both front and rear virginities in one day?
It just hurts!
How tough-minded.
Oumori, how did it feel to have Akira take your virginity?
It felt so good!
It feels like I can cum as much as I want!
Not inside, please!
Use your tongue properly! Don't slack off.
Over here too, please.
I'm going to cum soon...
Nwwooo!
That's right Akira, fight back! Don't fall into acceptance!
Please stop it!
I'll break!
Haven't you had enough? Please stop it now...
Don't be silly,
none of us are satisfied.
How could I forget?!
Moreover, stop this idiocy and release us at once!
About Akira's training...
A-After doing all that to her yesterday, are you going to continue today as well?!
Well, I'm not such a bad man. I bet she'll be tired after doing all that yesterday.
Then-!
But the training isn't over yet. We can't quit now.
So then, do you want to train instead of having it done to Akira?
Oh, and of course we'll keep Akira's promise.
We won't take your virginity, so how about it?
If I take the training, it would be easier on Akira. That's what you mean, right?
Exactly.
Alright then. However, you have to promise me that you won't do anything more to Akira-
I know, I'll keep my promise.
Akagi, I'm leaving it to you.
I'm not really interested in shy ones that don't fight back, but if you insist...
N-No!
No! Not a pose like this!
Please don't!
No, don't lick there! It's dirty!
No~!
No! Please don't lick me there!
You getting wet now?
Then...
What is... that?
You don't know?
This tool is called a rotor, and it's used to please lonely women.
Like this.
No, not in such a place-!
S-Stop it~!
I guess I'll shove it in you.
No... No more...
Don't toy with me down there!
Noo!!
Don't lick such a dirty place!
Please! I beg of you!
Your voice is getting more lewd.
Does it feel good?
For me to feel good in such places...
There's no way-
You are being quite rough.
Akagi, give her the final push.
N-Not my butt!
Noo...
You did good, now Akira has it easier.
Let me praise you,
even if you have turned into a horny bitch who cums from anal.
Shuji-kun, h-how does this look on her?
It suits her well.
So does this mean that you're Akira's master?
T-That's right! I'm teaching the maid who wet herself.
That's no good, Akira-chan! You have to swallow all of it!
What? No way...
I-I'm sorry.
Do you deserve punishment?
Punishment?
Lift your ass.
I'm feeling flushed again...
Nii-sama...
Why didn't you choose me?
You're the only one, I don't need anything apart from you.
Oh, and about that,
I'll definitely join in.
I will be the one breaking the minds of Kurata Ibuki and Miyauchi Akira.
No, don't~!
It should be me, Karen, who Nii-sama should love!
No-one would pay me any attention since I was the daughter of father's mistress...
However, Nii-sama was different!
He, he would watch over me.
For me to be doing such things...
He wouldn't like such a lewd girl, would he?
But when I think about Nii-sama, I get so turned on-
I won't give Nii-sama away. Nii-sama belongs to me!
I should hate it, but my body becomes aroused and I nearly get washed away with pleasure.
Even though I'm here instead of Ibuki,
I've gotten used to this absurd treatment...
I need to find a way to escape...
Who is it? I've already-
Y-You're-
Yakushima's little sister?
Are you here to save me?
Why do you continue to despise Nii-sama?
W-What?
I think that this feeling I'm getting is called "annoyance"
This feeling of being readily shown something that I've really wanted for a long time.
You...
What kinds of words did you use to seduce Nii-sama? You whore!
I-I didnt...
Akira?
Ibuki?
What's happening?
Akira tried to escape, even if you were trapped here.
By manipulating my sister.
Yakushima, you bastard! Stop with the bullshit!
Trying to run away is true, though.
T-That's because your little sister...
So, Ibuki, I think you know what I'm wanting to say...
If I take Akira's punishment, then you will forgive her, correct?
No! Don't do it, Ibuki!
It's fine. It pains me more to see you suffer than me being defiled.
Please understand, Akira.
Looks like it's settled.
As for you, we will have to punish you for breaking the promise.
So what are we going to do, Shuji?
Should we take turns pounding Ibuki in front of her?
Or should we do some extra tough training?
Hmm, let's take turns doing Ibuki then.
Her good friend became a woman before her,
Ibuki also needs to become one.
If you don't want to look, that's fine. However, she is the finale.
Please bear with the pain if it hurts.
Since it's to make up for your friends mistake...
I understand, so why don't you hurry up?
Okay, lets have fun then, Ibuki.
Stop it, Yakishima!
No! Stop!
No!
It hurts! Not so sudden!
I can feel your hymen against my fingers.
See? It's right here!
No way... No way such a large thing will fit in me!
Noo~!!
It hurts!!
Please don't move!
I'll break!
No! Not inside! Please, anything but cumming inside!
Oh, really? So you're going to betray your friend?
No, that's not it! If you cum inside me, I'll-
I'm cumming, my dear Ibuki!
No!! It's coming out! It's filling me up!
You came so much...
Ibuki...!
Next, Akagi, it's your go.
Anywhere you want...
H-Hey...
S-Stop it!!
You're splitting me!
Stop it!
No! My butt is being split open!
This feels great!
Doing this from behind is exhilarating!
Kurata!
You're probably a high class miss elsewhere, but now you're just a horny bitch!
Get ready, I'm going to fill your asshole with semen!
No, don't! Do do such-!
Don't fill my butt with-!
No!
It's... It's coming out inside my butt...
Ibuki!
We're done with foreplay.
Now let's start with the real punishment.
Her being in such a hazy state isn't so bad.
No more! I don't want to cum anymore...
I-It's hitting me. It's hitting my deepest parts!
Are you about to cum, Ibuki?
I'm about to! My mind is blank...
With my insides being pounded...
Don't cum inside me anymore!
No more, I'll become pregnant! No more sperm, please-!
I'll end up having a baby...
She's still aroused even after this?
Maybe it's that girls have a longer sex drive.
Don't you think so, Akira?
It's no good, Shuji-kun!
She's been like this since we started doing Ibuki-chan.
Seems like she's abandoned her friend...
I dug your asshole out with this.
Better clean it throughly, eh?
This is all your fault, Akira.
It's because of you that this is happening.
Well, I guess you don't need to take responsibility,
since you willingly gave yourself for Ibuki's protection.
It seems as though it has deepened your relationship.
So hot...
From now on, why don't you get Ibuki to take over?
Don't you dare defile Ibuki any further!
I'll take the training.
So please-!
Ah, that's the spirit!
Even though she's unconscious, I'm sure she would be delighted to hear that.
I'll take it all... So-!