The third war maiden. She was surprisingly short-lived.
You may call her the daughter of Odin...
...but she's just a brat that doesn't even know anything about men.
Making her fall won't be any trouble.
What are you going to do to that girl?
Just leave her there having fallen?
That'd be very boring.
I'll let her help me tame Ariya.
Ariya?
W
War Maiden
Valkyrie
「Master, please forgive me for being naughty...」
Episode Two   「The treacherous female slave」
Why I am being treated like this?
You should stop lying to yourself.
You'll start to enjoy it as soon as you do.
Why you as well, Freya-sama...?
Start enjoying it...
Hardly.
You're saying I should just accept this disgrace?
I can't do this.
Here, there's a very important lady waiting for you.
Don't!
What's... that... supposed... to... mean?
Why is Lady Hilda here?
Don't!
Ariya...
I'm so glad you're okay.
You fiends! What did you do to her?
Don't make false accusations.
She wanted this.
What?
In your place, she has been...
...violated by dozens of soldiers.
"If you suffer and become tainted, I'll share your pain by tainting myself".
I would've loved for you to see that.
Losing her chastity...
...and getting raped in every single hole. That view...
Oh no...
Milady...
Sister...
Don't worry about me.
If you're safe then I'm fine.
But isn't it sad just to talk about being violated?
T-That's-
If I put this seed in you...
...you can become one with your beloved sister.
...with Sister...
S-Stop it!
I don't care what you do with me.
But don't lay your hands on her!
Milady!
S-Something is... c-coming out...
I have a penis.
How do you like it?
You want to stick it inside a pussy, don't you?
Y-Yes...
...my penis is hot...
...and I want a pussy.
Milady...
What are you... please stop it... no.
Sister, let's feel good together.
Don't do it, Milady.
Anything but that... you must not put it-
Your pussy feels... great!
No...
Please pull it out, Milady!
My, my...
Who would've thought that the daughter of War God Odin would be this lewd?
She doesn't even care that we're watching.
You bet.
To have such a hard penis...
...It's so dirty.
D-Don't watch!
Don't watch Milady in such a disgraceful state!
Sister, you must not look away.
Oh god... no... don't!
If you do it so hard...
Seems like Ariya is starting to feel it too.
Her nipples are so hard.
I'm connected to Milady down there.
Your pussy is squeezing my penis...
...I'm so happy... that you feel good.
No!
This is wrong!
I want to ejaculate inside you!
I want to pump you full of sperm!
M-Milady... anywhere but inside!
M-My penis is...
It's no good. It's coming.
Both came.
Even Hildegard, the highest war maiden, becomes a normal girl...
...if you strip her of her powers, eh?
I'm sorry... I love you, but I did this...
It's all right.
Because being violated by you felt good.
Sister...
...I'm so sorry...
...I became sullied.
It's only a matter of time until these children fall too.
I wonder if Master will like this.
Reia, how does it feel?
I'm transforming another of your comrades.
Master...
...please don't talk about that now.
Please just enjoy this "pussy" between my tits.
Your shamelessly large breasts are the best.
It makes me happy to hear that.
Please enjoy them more.
I'm doing you with my tits.
Alright, should I cum soon?
Yes! Cum!
Cum from my breasts! Cum inside this slippery "pussy"!
This "pussy" covered in your penis-milk!
Wow, it's almost as if I could get pregnant from you fucking my tits.
It's not over yet.
You can't satisfy me just by doing that.
Master, please punish this lewd Reia with your amazing dick.
It's already soaking wet down there.
Ah, I'm yearning for your dick, you see?
My pussy is drooling in expectation.
Truly, this goddess desires to breed!
I love this position!
Getting violated from behind like a beast.
Hey, you're moving your hips by yourself.
But...
...I love it... when it hits deep inside.
I really love your beastly cock.
No...
...oh wow...
I'm becoming a beast myself by getting violated by this beastly cock.
Good! I'll stain your backside with sperm this time!
Okay!
Shoot your cum all over my ass!
Coat it with your semen!
Here I go.
Wow!
Down there... my pussy's about to explode!
I'm about to cum, I'm almost there!
I'm cumming!
Wow...
...I'm covered in so much hot sperm...
The moon will be hidden completely, soon.
That will be the time when...
Ariya, war maiden of the early morning moon, will fall.
Shoot your hot stuff all over me today, too, okay?
Oh no, it's leaking. Just when I got cum inside.
At last, this day has arrived, Ariya.
W-What do you want?
You should know what I want when I visit you in this room.
I-I'm not feeling well today.
Please spare me today.
Y-You really must not do it today.
If it's tomorrow...
...if it's tomorrow, it'll be okay.
Is it because today is the day of the eclipse?
You fiend...
...how did you know that?
The power bestowed on you by the holy world... comes from the light of the moon.
These subs were done by SubDESU-H.net. These ungrateful assholes just stole our subs.
Thus, when the moon is eclipsed and its light is darkened...
...your war maiden power gets even weaker.
That includes the power to defend your womb from the evil bodily fluids of a man.
If I cum inside of you today...
...you will doubtlessly become pregnant.
You foul brute...
Should you say things like that?
Everything depends on my mood, you know?
Curse you.
Come on.
Try begging properly.
P-Please don't do it today.
Anything else...
...I'll do anything.
You'll do anything, eh?
Interesting.
Lick my feet then.
Your feet?
You'll do anything, right?
Or do you want me to make you pregnant?
You coward!
It reeks of sweat.
Are you saying I should put this dirty foot into my mouth?
What's wrong? Hurry up and lick it.
Who said that licking it once would be enough?
Continue until I say to stop.
Clean my whole toe.
Reia, prepare "that".
Yes, master.
What are you up to?
S-Stop it, Reia.
Don't tell me you're going to... in my ass...
N-No!
There's no way all of that will fit inside me!
Sorry, but Master's orders are absolute.
No! No!
It's pouring in...
Do you like it? Reia made this especially for you.
If you can bear this until the end, I might not fuck you today.
No way...
...stop it already...
No, please!
This is the limit! No more!
I'll burst!
I... can't take...
...any more...
At your limit already?
You can let it out then.
It's coming out.
At this rate...
Just let it out and feel better.
Don't look!
No!
Don't...
Amazing, it's spraying so high.
The proud Ariya has been reduced to this...
...how wonderful.
So, as promised...
...I'll impregnate you now.
No, stop it!
Your breasts are telling me you want to be pregnant.
Why...
...does this feel so good?
It's like that on ovulation day.
Just surrender to it,
and  bear my child.
If you put that in, I'll surely become pregnant!
No!
A pussy on an ovulation day is exceptional, right?
Pull it out! Please, hurry and pull it out!
Today's no good!
No way!
How deep are you pushing it in?
It's hitting my womb!
No!
My thing is itching to make you pregnant!
No, at this rate I'll...
...become pregnant!
Ah, Ariya crying, what a scene.
It's about time for me to fill you up with my sperm.
No!
Stop it, stop it!
Please, let me go!
I'll really become pregnant!
No, no, no... NO!
It'll combine inside...!
Eight months later
Please... you'll hurt it.
It's spreading.
It's so good!
This item Reia created is quite nice.
I like it.
Tentacles make you feel good?
Your pussy is all messed up.
Please stop it!
If you play with my pussy now I'll...
Hey, can I do it now?
Skuld wants to put her penis in her.
Oh, yes, yes. Ladies first.
No, I don't want this!
I don't want to be raped by a girl!
Huh? But you fucked Hirata and Ariya too.
But that was...
Let's feel good together.
Lady Hilda, your pussy is amazing...
...it's so hot and tight.
No...
Fenrir, how about screwing her ass at the same time?
No!
Sister, please help me!
You assholes! If you want to rape so bad...
...rape me, then!
I admire your spirit, but I'll be your partner.
Y-You traitor!
W-Why do you have something like that?
Let me tell you this. It's not made of magic.
I've always had this body.
So I'm neither god nor devil, neither man nor woman.
This is an incomplete body.
It's all in.
Perhaps I'll go fishing with this dick in your womb.
W-Wait!
P-Please let me bear this child safely, at least.
I beg you!
That all depends on you.
I'll reconsider if you please me.
Fine.
I'll make you feel good.
How brave.
I can't quite believe that I'm seeing a war maiden moving her hips by herself.
Shut up!
Hurry up and cum!
Can't you make me feel good like Ariya did?
Stop it!
Don't squeeze my tits so hard.
Milk will come out!
So you became very sensitive while being pregnant.
How about here?
Don't! There's a baby inside!
Don't worry. It's a child with demonic blood.
It shouldn't be that weak.
No, please...
...don't do it so hard!
You'll hurt the baby!
Is a demonic child that important?
I don't care what happens to me, so long as the baby is-
Good... it feels good.
My pussy feels great.
I can't anymore... this fat thing is stirring me up inside...
...it'll burst!
Oh no, no...
I'm about to cum!
Cumming, cumming, cumming...
...I'm cumming!
Duke, how much do you have to play with us until you're satisfied?
Actually I was just killing time with the likes of you.
Speaking of which, I'm getting bored by fucking you war maidens all the time.
I shall give you a replacement for me.
Duke...
...is this the future you wish for?
This is the end you've chosen, right?
No.
No...
Ah!
I felt it moving!