SubDESU-H.net
How did this happen?
Moriyama-san... didn’t used to be like that.
Even so, he made me look so embarrassing.
And he messed up my body.
But…
It felt so good.
N-No!
What am I thinking about? Jeez!
Oh no.
My pussy... My clitoris is erect. I’m wet.
Why?
Is it from my weird fantasies?
Because I remembered all that stuff?
My body is reacting to it.
SubDESU
-H
Presents
Ijou Chitai Jikken Dorei 2
This feels great.
It feels so good.
I’m not supposed to do this.
I’m really not supposed to do this.
Two boys fucked my pussy and asshole.
Moriyama-san had my clit... my clitoris...
Like this… and like this…
My clit… my clitoris feels so good.
No more...
I’m gonna cum.
I’m going to cum!
Landlord. I’m home.
Hello!
M-Moriyama-san!
What is it?
Well, I feel bad about giving you those weird drugs earlier.
Here. Take it.
Please, swallow it.
Will this get my body back to normal?
Not back to normal, but it'll give you your balance back.
Really?
I see.
I understand my landlord’s feelings.
Do you mean...?
Take care.
I feel bad that this apartment will be torn down.
W-Wait!
I’ll take it.
I’ll take the drug, so please don't leave!
If only you’d said so at the start.
What’s going on?
My head is all foggy.
My body is all hot.
My boobs...
They’re throbbing.
What? What’s going on?
The drugs have taken effect.
B-But those drugs were...
After making your clitoris bigger and more sensitive, I thought it was time for your boobs.
So I got some drugs from the college research lab.
You're a bit more "balanced" now, right?
That’s...
Irrational!
You’ve only made things worse!
Well, Landlord. You've become quite slutty.
I’m not slutty!
No!
My nipples, not so hard!
My nipples... don’t tweak them anymore!
What happens if I tweak them?
W-Well, they...
I-I can’t stop...
It feels too good!
Oh no!
My tits are making me feel weird.
No, I’ll go crazy.
I’ll cum from my tits!
No!
It’s cumming out!
Milk is...!
Breast milk is...!
No!
It’s cumming again.
Boob-cum!
I can’t stop it!
Every time I cum out of my boobs, I cum!
I'm cumming!
It feels so good!
It feels so very good!
I’m cumming!
M-Moriyama-san, your cock is...
Sliding against my boobs.
And my boobs... feel so good...
I’m cumming.
My boobs, my boobs are too sensitive!
I suppose it’s unfair to ignore your lower half.
No!
S-Stop it!
My boobs are... my boobs are...
Your boobs are what?
They feel good!
Sliding against the sheets, I’m losing my mind!
So your boobs feel best, eh?
My pussy too. My pussy feels good too!
Your cock... It's filling me up so much.
Your cock's thrusting in and out and up and down, it feels so good.
No!
It feels too good.
My clit… my clitoris… ohhh, so good!
Oh no!
You can’t play with me like that.
I’ll cum again!
I’ll cum. I’ll cum too much!
It’s coming out again!
I can’t stop it!
My cum, my milk, I can’t stop them!
I’ll break, I’ll break!
Oh no, I’m cumming!
Cumming too much... I’ll dry up!
I’m losing my mind!
I’ll cum again? I’ll cum again?
I can’t anymore!
I can’t!
Every time your cock slides in, I cum!
My boobs are cumming!
I can’t stop myself from cumming!
Oh no!
If you do any more to me, I’ll want more!
Oh? You’ll want what?
Y-Your... cock, Moriyama-san.
Landlord, you sure are slutty.
Yes. I'm slutty.
Moriyama’s cock… is making my pussy… all broken up.
Please break it!
I’m cumming! Cumming!
More! I want your cock more!
I want your cock more!
Will you listen to my request?
Y-Yes.
I’ll listen to anything you say.
So please take care of my pussy.
With your cock!
At my college, we’re doing an experiment.
Would you help me?
Yes! I'll help! Please let me cum!
Let me cum with your cock!
Fuck me harder!
Moriyama-san, I want your cock to destroy my pussy!
Moriyama... grab my boobs...
Y-Yes!
I love this!
I’m cumming!
Wh-What is this thing?
Why am I...?
Where am I?
What’s going to happen to me?
Don’t worry, Landlord.
You’ll be fine.
Please stop it.
Please, let me go home.
Landlord, we want to see you being embarrassed a lot.
N-No.
We’re starting.
No! It’s feeling good!
It’s starting to feel good – no!
I’ll cum! I’ll cum! I’ll cum!
No...
I’ll cum. I’ll cum again!
No!
Don't...
I’ll cum again!
I’ll cum... I’ll cum!
I’ll cum. I’ll cum again!
Landlord, let’s do the vibrator next.
No... No way...
I’ve already cum so many times.
If you do that to me... I’ll break.
I'll... I’ll...
I’ll be broken.
No!
S-Stop it.
No...
Don’t...
Wow.
This feels too good!
No...
I can’t cum anymore!
Not there!
I’ll break... You’ll break me!
My butt? No, that will feel too good!
No, you can’t!
My boobs, my pussy...
And my asshole – everything feels good!
Everything feels too good!
I’ll cum.
I’ll cum again!
No! No more!
I’ll lose my mind again!
Cock...
Cock... I want a cock...
Moriyama-san, your cock...
Please, I want it in my pussy!
Please!