While returning home from his work at the rental video shop,
Hosaka Ippei frequently takes a walk around this park.
Not because he wants to relax after a long day...
Yes...
More...
Not another couple again...
Yes, I love RAPE!
However, his experience in rape is non-existent...
And he has never came across a rape scene before...
I am tired of the lovey-dovey couples...
No, let me go!
This way?
Woah!!!
Please help me!
Didn't I tell you to shut up?!
All right...
Good girl. I will give it to you right away...
Ippei, who is peeking from the bush,
as usual, starts to fantasize that he is the rapist...
This big one is going to enter you now!
Take this!
Yeah, I can't get enough of that expression.
I will cum a ton in you!
Your nipples are starting to get hard.
And your pussy is drenched.
All right, I am going to spurt it in soon!
I.. It’s going in!
It’s still... cumming!
How's that? I came a lot in you!
Holding his rock hard cock,
he enviously looks at the rape scene...
T-This is it! This is what I want!
W-Who is there?!
Oh shit!
Goodbye!
I wanna do it too.
Could it be?
I thought I heard a woman's voice just now.
Woah!!!
Come on, is this for real?
Hey...
Is she alive?
I can see her panties.
Panties... A girl’s panties!
Alright...
I will...
rape this girl!
It will be a pain if she starts screaming...
You are not gonna wake up now, are you?
Her lips look so soft.
I want to put mine in her mouth...
Take it out just before I cum...
And spurt it all over her cute face.
And then, I will forcefully put my dick in her pussy.
I will cum thrice in her pussy and twice in her mouth!
I will sodomize her and cum all over it!
Just a little more...
I am cumming!
Where should I cum?
On her thighs?
Her breast?
Or her face...
Hold it... Wait!!
Oh no, I can't stop!
It’s still cumming!
This isn't what it seems, this is...
What isn't what it seems?
W
Original Animation Video.
Please rape me!
~Chidori’s ***** gets ***ed by a ******?!~
Here is my room.
It looks like a sexual ceremonial room... it reeks of lust.
Reeks of lust?
Is this your meal of choice?
“Slutty Teacher,  by Hazuki”
Don't touch it without my permission.
All you have are rape genres...
You sex maniac..
That's none of your business!
I am hungry.
Eh?
Can't you hear me?
I said I am hungry.
Hurry up and prepare some food.
Blue balls
Calm down...This is all for free sex...
Y-You're going to stay in my room?
Yes, I keep telling you that.
Wa.. Wait a minute! You...
Call me Sari-sama.
Umm... Sari-sama, how can I live with a woman I just met...
Then can I go to the police and tell them what you did to a woman 'you just met'?
That's...
Could it be that she ran away from home?
Don't jump to conclusions.
Just let me stay with you.
No... Wait a minute...
I recently read a blog about
a guy who let a girl who ran away from her home live in his house
and as a reward she allowed him to have sex with her.
This is...
A chance to have sex for free!
So what do you think? Should I go to the police or...
P-Please, you are welcome to my home, Seri-sama.
Well that's ok...
If you are insisting so much.
Where is the bathroom?
Through that door.
Prepare some food while I take a shower.
Do you understand?
Yes ma’am.
Endure it for free sex! You can do it!
So I fell asleep, huh?
This girl...
Popular Idol, Kujyou Sakura, new maxi-single on sale!
Oh, that's Kujyou Sakura.
Do you like this kind of music?
This woman has a rape fetish.
Um.. You got some medicine?
Please do take it after you are done eating.
You are such a...
Ok, fine...
I will tell you what it is...
I can sense women who want to get raped.
I can fuck myself! Just a little rape diary.
This woman definitely has a rape fetish.
She wants to get raped.
A “rape fetish”?
W-Welcome.
It's smaller than I thought.
Excuse me, customer...
I am not a customer.
Don't worry about me.
Ok...
Oh, that’s the adult corner so kids shouldn't...
Who did you call a kid?
I am very sorry, manager.
Oh Ippei-kun.
Hey, why are you here?
Ippei-kun, do you know her?
Don't tell me... Is she your girlfriend?
Not at all! She is my... Well... um...
Hey, manager.
Y-Yes!
You have quite a good collection here.
You have some maniac video collection. Not bad...
Oh... You can tell?
Of course.
You have some minor ones and some from outside the country.
And you even have some domestic ones that aren’t yet on sale.
Did you choose them?
Y-Yes.
You have some good taste. I'll praise you for that.
T-Thank you very much!
Hey...
Do you know what you are talking about?
Of course.
By the way, how do you know Ippei-kun?
You want to know?
Yes.
I was lying unconscious in the park,
and then this guy came in and...
S-She is my cousin.
Cousin?
Yes, that's it.
She is a farmer’s daughter who just came here yesterday.
You think I could pass for a farmer AND your cousin?
Shhhh...
Leave this to me...
Ok? Ok?
Well, that's fine..
Come on, introduce yourself to the manager.
I am his cousin, Sari.
Sari-chan, huh? What a cute name.
M..moe! Just kidding...
Moe!
Hey, is this guy alright?
Shhhhh...
I work as a manager here. I am Iwao Kojiro.
Nice to meet you, Sari-chan.
I certainly hope it’s “nice”.
Why are you so rude?!
Well then, I will be at the back.
I will leave the rest to you, Ippei-kun
Roger, sir.
Sari-chan, take your time.
She is so cute...
I see...
So this is what they mean by “birds of a feather flock together”
I am not a pedophile!
But there’s no mistaking that you both fall under the category of “pervert”.
Pervert?
You're welcome!
I want to be a member here.
Ok.
T-Then fill in some details in this form.
Put your name, phone number and address, please.
Ok.
Hm?
She looks like her...
Hey!
Is something wrong with that woman?
Idiot! You're too loud.
She looks like someone I knew.
Whom does she resemble?
An old classmate.
Oh?
Excuse...
Yes!
Forgive me if I am wrong, but..
We used to be in the same class in high school...
Eh?
Are you not Hosaka Ippei-kun?
Chidori-san?
Yeah! So you remembered!
I am so glad.
Yeah, I remember you...
Of course...
What a coincidence.
It kinda feels like destiny, doesn't it?
Y-Yeah.
Sorry, I am meeting a friend now, so I've got to go.
Ok...
Can I introduce my friend to this shop?
Of course...
Thanks. I will come again.
Ok...
Wait... Take this.
Your membership card.
Thank you.
If it’s ok with you let’s have lunch together next time.
Eh?
You can call me anytime. C’ya.
C’ya...
Isn't it a chance?
No, she just said it to be polite.
That's not what I mean.
I am telling you that it's a chance to rape the woman you had a crush on.
Huh? Could it be...
Yes.
She wants to be raped by a man.
Someone who used be an idol in our class... Her?
I will tell you one more interesting thing...
That woman...
Is a virgin.
What’s the matter?
Hey, what do you call this snack?
It’s an ummaibo.
Ummaibo, you say?
It’s a snack I used to eat as a kid.
It's delicious, right?
Yes, this is delicious.
It’s cheap and has a lot of flavors.
There are more flavors?
Well yeah, you like it?
I like it.
From now on I declare that my dinner is pudding and this ummaibo.
No, eat normal food for dinner.
Welcome!
Hi, Hosaka-kun
Chidori, welcome.
Like I promised, I brought my friend..
Eh? Promise?
Didn't I tell you that I would introduce my friend to this shop?
Oh! So you really did introduce her.
Of course
Not only that, I brought a really hi-quality customer.
Hi!
Welcome!
Did you notice?
Woah!!!
Shhh. you are too loud.
Ku..Kujou Sakura?!
That’s right.
I will introduce you.
This beauty is as you know it...
the top record selling idol...
Kujyou Sakura.
I am Kujyou Sakura.
Nice to meet you.
Is this a dream?
What’s the matter?
She is the second one.
Eh?
Like I told you before...
That idol has a rape fetish.
H-Hey, what are you...
Do you want to know?
I.. I will pass on that.
I see.
I don't care about who Sari is at the moment.
Besides, I have something I must do!
My old high school crush, Chidori Yuuma!
And then...
Someone you wouldn't know normally, a popular idol...
Kujyou Sakura!
I have to choose who I should rape for my first experience.
They don't show it on the outside...
But they truly desire to be raped.
She wants to get violated by men...
They want to be raped!
I will fulfill their wishes!
I will make them say...
Background Text: Come on in
Please rape me!
Thanks for waiting, Chidori.
You're late!
Sorry, I had some things to take care of.
since you are late, it’s your treat today, okay?
of course
Just kidding
But...
I am the one who called you here.
So it will be my treat, ok?
Well, ok.
Good. Then let's go.
And then because she fell, Rit’suko scattered all the water in the bucket,
but below was Maeda sensei, so he said 'who is there! I will be right there so stay put!'
I’ve been the only one speaking since we came.
Sorry I just got nervous
Eh?
You were beautiful and really popular in class so...
You are too kind... Are you drunk already?
My phone is ringing, excuse me.
I will be right back.
Ok.
Alright, this is my chance!
Will this much do?
Maybe a little more...
Oh shit! Is this going to be alright?
I hope I don't get caught.
After she drinks this all I have to do is wait for her to go to the toilet,
wear my mask,
and break in to her cubical!
I will rip her clothes off as she is desperately trying to stop me!
I will slam her and cum a ton inside her!
Then we will leave the shop as a couple.
A perfect plan!
I am a born genius.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ok then, let’s make a toast.
Yeah.
Cheers!
Please rape me!
Now drink!
Drink the wine with lactose in.
And then after you go to the toilet, you will be raped by me, Chidori Yuuma!
Hosaka kun.
Why? Why didn't she go to the toilet even once?!
Hosaka kun!
H-Huh?
Are you okay? Can you make it home alone?
Y-Yeah! What about you?
I know that she lives alone...
If that's the case then I will go to her room, then...
S-Should I drop you at your house?
No, I can go home alone so don't worry.
But it's dangerous for a woman to walk alone.
But it feels like it’s even more dangerous staying with you, Hosaka kun.
Wai... S-She found out...
Just kidding. I'm only joking.
I’ll call you later.
Huh? Are you serious?
Don't joke with me!
Is she going to take a taxi?
Could it be that she...
This park doesn't have any lights, so it’s very dark.
Even if it's a short cut,
this isn't a place where a woman by herself can pass through alone.
Yes, another chance!
All right! I'm going in!
Phew, right on time. I think I drank too much wine.
W-What was that noise just noise!
A molester?
No, you're wrong... This is...
No!!!
This is bad.
Huh?
Hey, Chido...
Wait, I shouldn't call out her name...
Hey, are you okay?
We’re in a public bathroom alone,
and she’s lying face down on the ground with her pussy sticking up at me.
I've got to do it!
This is the...
virgin pussy of Chidori Yuuma!
W-What is this?
So you woke up.
What is this?
Someone come and help!
Someone-
Shut up!
Please help!
I said shut up!
Do you want to get hurt?
Who are you?
Well I am a... Umm...
As soon as you put that mask on, you are the mysterious rape man!
The demon of rape,
a child sent from heaven to rape...
The name is...
Masked Rapist!
I am the mysterious rape man, Masked Rapist!
So basically, you are a pervert.
Shut up... Don't call me a pervert.
You are obviously a pervert if you enter the girls toilet in that outfit!
I- I know it...
I know that you have a rape fetish.
R-Rape-fetish?
That's impossible...
This is Chidori Yuuma's pussy...
Could it be that you...
So this is how she tastes!
Wait, I beg you, please wait!
I can't get enough of this taste!
It’s salty...
What?
No... Well that's because I just took a pee...
So please stop...
Well then, shall I have you suck mine?
Are you stupid?
Don't bring such a vulgar thing in front of me.
Open your mouth.
No... don’t!
If you don't listen to me, then I don't know what will happen to your friend.
Isn't she Kujyou, the idol?
Why do you know... Sakura has nothing to do with this.
Don't you dare touch her.
Well that depends on you.
You coward, just let me go if I use my mouth.
I don't want my body to be stained... So please...
Only if you can satisfy me with your mouth.
What’s the matter?
Hurry up and start!
I-I understand.
This feels good!
What's this?!
As I thought, this is the best!
Ouch! please stop!
Eh?!
Please stop!
what!? I can't understand what you are saying!
Wrapped around by hot mucus, this is the best!
Oh no, this is bad...
It seems like your stomach is full of my semen now.
Are you mad?
Umm...
As you promised, you’ll release me now.
Hm?
What?
Hey, this is...
Eh?
So you felt that good huh? I knew it.
T-That’s...
S-Stop...
Please stop!
If you want to be raped then just say it.
Don't joke with me. who'd...
want to get raped by you!
No!
Well then, as you wish I will forcefully shove it in.
Eh? W-What’s the matter?
What’s that? It’s bigger than before...
That's going to go in?
Yes.
If I get raped by that, I will...
Eh?
N-Nothing...
W-Wait, that won't...
Be glad...
Your virginity...
How do you know that I am a virgin?
...I will take it!
What... I can't take anymore of that...
I-It hurts!
So you really were a virgin.
Just as Sari said.
Isn't this what you wished for?
I don't want this! I didn't wish for it!
Well that's weird...
Does she really have a rape fetish?
Just wait until I ejaculate.
Hurry up... Hurry up and ejaculate!
Shall I then?
Eh?
It might hurt even more...
What do you want?
Do as you wish!
Well then, I will!
Are you done? Aren't you done yet?
I can’t... No more...
Hurry up and finish... Hurry!
If you want it so fast then...
I will spurt it in you!
Huh? No, not inside...
Please not inside...
It’s already too late...
Not inside!!
I beg you... Please do it outside!
It's inside...
It’s hot inside my stomach...
Not done yet!
It’s cumming, it’s filling inside my stomach!
Wait... you...
So cruel...
Chidori, I never imagined you’d cry...
You just said Chidori...
Oops...
I said something unnecessary again!
Didn't I say I saw your student card earlier?
You haven't said anything about it, idiot!
Could it be...
I am the mysterious rape man.
Masked Rapist!
I will come and rape you again.
So until then, adieu!
Adieu = French for farewell
I made such a big mistake...
Ignoring me...
Idiot! Idiot, idiot. Idiot!
I will rape her someday!
Rape! Rape! Rape! Rape! Rape... Rape...
What's this strange, intense feeling on my crotch?
Umm...
W-Why is she holding my dick?!
She has the worst attitude when she wakes up...
If I wake her up now, I won't live!
I just noticed, but I can see her tits!
Tits... Sai's tits!
This is like...
I will rub your dick while you look at my tits, ok?
saying that!
Give it back to me you idiot...
What? What should I return?
My... Umaibo... Roasted sausage flavor...
What’s with you all a sudden?
It doesn't open...
This isn't ummaibo, that is my meat rod!
It’s open...
Even though you are sleeping... You weirdo...
Itadakimas!
Don't pull it!
It hurts, but it feels good!
I can't take any more...
Here Sari, bring your face closer...
You want it don't you? Then just a little more...
Ummaibo...
I want it.
Oh no! This feels too good. I might cum before she puts it in her mouth.
Sari, bring your face closer and open your mouth.
I can't anymore!
I’m cumming!
Umaibo... it’s hot...
That felt good...
Well then, before she wakes up...
Umm... Huh?
Hey!
Ye... Yes?
What is the meaning of this? Explain yourself.
well, this is a result based on complicated actions and coincidence and, well...
Basically...
Basically what?
basically... well...
I will die.
Permission granted. Die at once.
Yes, sir!
Good bye, life.
On that day, somewhere near Hosaka Ippei's apartment, a man's scream was heard.
No don't... Don't put ummaibo in my ass!!