Thinking about it again,
it was actually a terrible chance encounter.
The very first person who sent me a love letter,
was a cute girl from a class section not far from ours.
Kanzaki-kun I'll be at the gym storage room affer school, so come.
Setagaya Mari
I, who's currently at the peak of puberty,
naturally expected something good to happen.
And indeed there was something good.
However,
I think it wasn't worth a strong and painful kick in the face.
Gotcha! Semen
Dinner for Vanpire
Hey, what do you think you're doing you bitch!
H-Huh? I can usually knock someone out unconscious with that.
You're tough.
Stop joking around.
You just kicked someone you've just met you know.
Please calm down Kanzaki-kun!
I-I'm sorry,
I think I need a little blood...
What? You need blood?
I think you meant brains.
No, I need blood.
More so as I look in your vibrant and lively face.
It makes me really hungry.
Excuse me...
Munch
She really bit me.
Suck~
Hey.
I-I'm sorry.
I'm not really used to drinking raw things.
So...?
I'm a vampire and yet I'm not used to blood.
Talk
Actually, I can live as long as I can absorb
any life force, even if it's not blood.
Hey.
I was able to live up to now with just sweat and saliva.
Hey!
Though I admit that blood is by far the most effective.
Hey listen you psycho!
– My, my, I don't want to be called that.
– Shut up, I don't have time to deal with your delusions!
Delusions?
Oh, you don't believe what I said?
Then...
I think you'll believe me once you see this.
Are those real?
U-Umm, so do you believe me now?
I'm really hungry right now.
Even sweat will do, so can you give me some please?
I don't care if it's just a bit.
Please, I beg of you.
A-Any type of secretion will do, huh?
So you're going to give me some?
Yep, you bet I will.
However,
not sweat, but semen.
S-Semen?
I... I see, it'd be a bit weird,
but I heard it's quite nutritious.
Okay then.
– I'm going to squeeze it all out!
– Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Huh? It's not coming out.
Are you nuts?!
You don't do it that way!
It's not some cow's tit.
It won't come out if you don't lick it or do something good to it.
L-Licking, huh...
So, like this...?
How should I put it?
She really "sucks" at this.
Does this really feel good for him?
You don't just lick one side.
You take it in your mouth and suck on it as well.
Okay, I got it.
Eh? H-Hey...
What's this?
I never said anything to her and yet she
suddenly became really good at it.
Oh well.
She seems to be a dunce,
but it looks like she can understand signs pretty well.
– If her boobs were just a bit bigger,
– Delicious.
– then I could enjoy a good tit-fuck.
– Then I could enjoy a good tit-fuck.
No, no, as the stud I mustn't be too greedy.
My breasts suddenly got heavier.
What?
K-Kanzaki-kun, what's the meaning of this?
H-How the hell should I know?
But this is great!
Really great!
Huh, it is?
I'm going to borrow this for a bit,
and use it like this.
No...
Wow, I really wanted to experience this once.
J-Just wait...
Oh, sorry, did it hurt?
No, t-that's not what I mean.
It's starting to feel good.
My breasts go rub rub.
You can hear it night? Those lewd sounds.
My breasts are all wet.
This is amazing!
I'm very happy!
Hurry up and give it to me.
I want to drink all of your cum, Kanzaki-kun.
O-Oh no, I'm about to...!
Your cum...!
It's really thick.
It feels like your life force is going to seep into me.
O-Oh really.
It looks like it's been built up for quite a while.
Is this your first time to experience this?
That doesn't matter!
That's good. Great even.
Now, I'll be taking your virgin cock with my hole.
H-Hey...!
I'll be the one to move, so just stay right there.
W-W-What is this?
It's really gripping me tight.
So this is how it feels inside a girl?
Your thing is big and stiff.
It feels great.
My insides are being pierced.
Hey, your personality just flipped around!
That's because you prefer this type of woman.
I understand everything like it's in the palm of my hand.
Here, how about moving up and down like this?
You wanted to be pushed by these big, tender breasts, right?
This girl... even the way she speaks is different now.
Is this the power of a vampire too?
Anyway,
don't get too cocky you dunce!
No...!
Oh, so your wings are sensitive?
Then...
I'm going to touch them more!
Wait, don't...
What's wrong?
Your pussy is gripping me even tighter now.
Why?
My... pussy.
Oh no...
It feels so good that I'm...
What? Are you about to cum?
I'm going to cum.
Your dick is bulging up inside me.
P-Please cum.
Let my pussy remember the taste of your cum.
The hot stuff is pouring in!
My pussy is getting filled with the sticky stuff.
You know, I stopped being a virgin yesterday.
Another day
Kanzaki-kun!
Thanks for last time.
I came here to tell you something.
She's back to normal.
Her breasts too...
I told my mom about the other day,
and she told me that I am actually half-succubus, half-vampire.
She hid that fact to keep my sex education in check.
I think I've been enlightened thanks to our compatibility.
Talk
She also told me that's the reason
why my breasts temporarily grew.
I see.
So, from now on, please let me have your cum as my meal.
After you do something about that bird brain of yours!
Full-course dinner for Vanpire
It's lunchtime Kanzaki-kun!
My meal! I'm very hungry already!
– Kanzaki-kun...
– They're at it again.
– Hey...
– They're always so annoying.
Come on, let's go.
I can eat? I can eat now?
Music Room
Hey, I'd like you to stop kissing and jumping
on me inside the classroom.
Huh? But I'm hungry already.
Can't you think of anything other than that?
This girl, which was actually the offspring
of a succubus and vampire,
now lives off of human semen.
She said something about being attracted to my dense energy,
and every day during lunch and after school,
she comes to me to fill herself up.
In other words, there is no romantic connection whatsoever.
No, I'm not really depressed by it.
Even so, she still "sucks" at it even though she does it every day.
Suck it more erotically for heaven's sake!
And do something about that washboard chest as well.
My oh my, they're getting big again?
That's really straightforward of you.
Kanzaki-kun, you pervert.
But, why does her personality change too?
Is it really because I like it?
For a breast maniac like you Kanzaki-kun...
Shall I take care of you dick with this?
The feeling of her breasts squeezing me is very nice.
It's getting all twitchy.
How cute.
She seems to be drooling a lot now,
and it feels great when combined with her warm mouth.
It's sucking my thing in pretty strongly.
It's still too early, but I think I'm about to cum already.
Oh crap, somebody's there!
And them of all people?!
Oh, it's you Kanzaki.
You always disappear during lunch,
so here's where you do it, huh?
You're quite conceited for someone who is plain-looking.
Just stop before our disciplinary code gets broken.
What's wrong Kanzaki-kun? Let's continue.
What the hell are you saying in the middle of this situation?
And you, why did you choose him?
He's bad at sports and academics,
he's never ever stood out,
he's got nothing for you, you know.
We're a lot better than him.
What are you saying?
None of you can replace him.
I've got no business with the weak life forces that you two have.
Yours doesn't even compare to the rich
and dense cum Kanzaki-kun has.
H-Hey, just stop right there already.
You're bothering my meal, so just get out please.
What did you just...?
– Ow, ow, ow!
– This crazy girl calls us weak?!
What's with you?
How terrible of you to interrupt me during my meal!
Stop that, let go of Setagaya!
Now, now, you're not needed here so...
Hey, let me go!
What the heck is this?
Just sit still and watch.
Damn!
K-Kanzaki-kun!
Woah!
Huh? I think it was bigger earlier.
Was it just my imagination?
Hey, I said stop!
So who's the weak one now?
I at least wanted to have em' D-cups though...
Her breasts aren't getting bigger?
She's not using her ability?
Hey, you're used to giving blowjobs, right?
You're doing it to Kanzaki everyday.
Compare his to ours.
I don't want that.
Compared to Kanzaki-kun's your cum is bland and weak.
How would you know if you haven't even tasted it?
What? This girl has no technique at all.
You should have taught her better.
Stop! Can't you see she doesn't want to do it?
Hey, give me a handjob too.
What are you doing? Letting these guys push you around like that.
Where's your normal arrogant self?
Stop giving me that wear look!
You're just giving them pleasure with that!
Huh? What happened?
She just used her teeth!
I did it on purpose.
Oh, but don't worry,
we'll do it all the way till the end.
What?
I'll definitely, absolutely make you cum.
What is she saying?
Okay, let's see...
The masochist spirit seems to be strong in you.
It looks like you enjoy it when it hurts.
Do you feel good being stroked in both directions?
And you...
You want me to play with this mostly, right?
She's suddenly...
See? You two really are no better.
Oh crap, I'm about to...
Me too, I'm about to cum.
These masochist dicks are cumming already?
Okay, let's give it a taste.
Oh? It's not as bad as I thought.
Did my thoughts just reach her earlier?
But their words didn't affect her at all.
Your dick is already stiff Kanzaki-kun.
Hey you!
I think yours is the best after all.
Stop that!
I don't plan on putting on a live show!
Oh, I forgot.
You like doing it with my breasts enlarged right?
No! You're completely missing my point!
What's with those wings?!
Are you a youkai or something?
Hmm, I think I don't like the sound of that.
I'm a half-succubus, half-vampire.
Please remember that.
No way...!
The only one that can really make me full inside,
is none other than you Kanzaki-kun!
Y-You idiot, this is no place for you to say that!
Anyway, untie me first!
I don't wanna.
It feels more exciting this way.
Even you got aroused when I was being violated earlier right?
You just shut up.
How cute of you Kanzaki-kun.
Did I just hear a gulp? You two sure
are getting really aroused there.
W-Who are you talking to?
I see... and here I was thinking of rewarding
somebody more honest with this.
What are you feeling cocky about huh?!
Okay then, I'll be sure to make you squeal this time.
Wait, no way...
I-It feels too tight...
Wow, I can feel the movement from inside
her pussy, making it feel even better.
Oh... Oh no...
– Don't move...
– Huh? Something's not right.
Where's the arrogant girl now?
Hey, don't tell me...
It's my first time having anal sex...
Don't try to do something that you can't do!
But...
I just can't give my pussy to someone my heart didn't choose!
Eh?
Don't forget about me now.
In any case, things are going to get worse if this continues.
If there was just a way to give more pleasure to them...
What's this?
Her butt suddenly swelled and got twitchy.
This feels too good.
I'm losing my mind.
Something big is coming.
I just came, but I'm already about to cum again...
Me too, I'm about to...
I-I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Here it comes!
I got too greedy and had too much.
That's why I can't take in anything except Kanzaki-kun's.
I see...
I came twice because of this weird girl.
Oh yeah, you can make your body transform,
but why weren't you affected by what they said?
Oh, you're quite sharp to have noticed that.
I'm not a complete succubus,
and my body doesn't seem to listen to anyone but you.
What?
Now I'm 100% sure, I love you Kanzaki-kun!
Please go out with me!
W-What? For real?
Uh-huh.
You don't just want me because you need someone to "eat"?
It's true, I really do love you.
The way she said it just doesn't make it seem convincing enough.
Next Day.
Kanzaki-kun, it's lunchtime!
– It's time to eat, I'm hungry already!
– I knew that you're just treating me as your meal after all.