Gakuen 3 Kareinaru Etsujoku
Ridim Arses
Oh?
Then?
Last time's summary
What's the business for calling me out here?
The medicine..
Please give me another medicine to subside this throbbing...
Do you mean about this?
Yes... that one..
Did you really want it that badly?
Since the effect of that medicine ran out..
the throbbing keeps increasing...
I can't even sleep on night
This has my sperm diluted in it and can
temporarily  subdue the withdrawal symptoms.
But in return, the more she uses this medicine,
the more she'll became enslaved by my sperm.
Hey hey, what are you going to do? Princess?
Just like what I did last time,
I will do this with my mouth in exchange for the medicine.
I can smell the sperm from the tip...
Hurry.....
Use my mouth.....
have your way....
And give me the medicine...
I can't believe this is being done
by a so called virtuous woman.
Don't say that..
This can't be helped..
Like that...
The medicine.... please...
What are you saying?
Obviously having the same thing
done twice won't satisfy me...
You had "No way" but it doesn't really fit the character
But...
No rest for the wicked...
Next, I will let you pay with this mouth here.
Eh!?
In the ass it's vulgar!
Figures... you like it here too, don't you?
Stop...
A modest virtuous lady, putting a dick inside the ass is improp...
Virtuous lady my ass!
You're clearly enjoying the thrusting in your ass!
That's... impossible...
I'm losing my senses from being thrusted
by that big dick in my dirty hole...
If this goes on... I'll have my ass ruined...
I'm going crazy with this embarrassing situation!
Here!
Cum with your first anal sex!
No!!!!!!
Here's your prize!!
He's coming again inside me... and so much....!!
Are you Kagetora-sama?
I was told you are a clown who came from Japan?
Yes I am.. Princess Ridim..
Your highness...
There's no need for you to talk with the likes of this clown...
Why?
I've loved clowns since I was a child.
Say, Kagetora-sama
What sort of act do you perform?
Act?
I acted stupid and set myself as a clown to hide my identity...
But I don't have any acts...
My princess,
Apparently this clown can drink wine trough his nose...
My!
I want to see it Kagetora-sama!
I understand...
Wow, that's amazing Kagetora-sama...
Thanks Kagetora-sama
You are the only one who will speak to me
with such familiarity.
Not at all!
I'm the one who's humbled for having the Princess'
accompany a clown such as myself.
Well... Kagetora-sama..
If it's not too much to ask of you...
Would you like to befriend me?
Why gladly...
The tea Kagetora-sama prepared tastes so refined.
I'm honored it is to your highness' liking..
Then.. what's the continuation of that fairytale?
What will happen to the princess and the young man?
Yes..
The young man felt love at first sight for the princess
and both fell in love each other.
However their status were far too different.
So the young man
decided to use a certain spell.
A... spell..?
Yes... a spell..
The young man cast such evil spell on the princess..
He wanted to have a mutual love.
Yes..
Just like this...
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
Gakuen 3
~Karei Naru Etsujoku~
Translated by SubDESU-H
As for the requested investigation of Ridim-sama's trend
Ridim-sama seems to swim in the pool to cool down her body alone after she's done with her dance practice
Really,
She's already been trough all that, and still ever the careless princess.
Well, it works to my advantage, though...
Why is my body this hot?
It won't cool down even if I swim in the pool
Besides why does this feel so good if it's not even sex?
I'm just rubbing that part...
There's a sticky liquid coming out from down there...
It's so good I'm...
I'm going to pee...
It'll be a while more until she's at her limit and craves for me...
I'm wearing a swimsuit today too...
So I'll take good care of her here where no one comes...
Meylin? What's the matter?
It seems Ridim-sama collapsed in the middle of her practice.
She's currently resting at the infirmary.
What!?!!
Why...
Why won't this throbbing inside me stop?
Didn't I told you?
Kagetora-sama!?
You're already affected by this clown's magic.
No...
Why do you run away?
You can't hold your craving for my sperm since that day right?
No...
No...no...
I'm losing my strength....
What a big clitoris
I can tell it even with your bloomers on.
My clitoris...
It wasn't this weird before...
This is your fault too!
Is this because of my sperm?
I think it happened before...
I had sex with many girls before but this is my first time to see one this big.
Stop it, please...
If you touch me there...
You'll feel good right?
You should know...
Since you're touching it with yourself...
How did you know?
Oh, so you really touched it.
You fooled me!
No... you can't....
Don't touch me there...
I'll pee... I'm going to pee...
No... please spare me...
What a shameless princess...
This comes next...
You can't have sex with me.
I'm a princess.
I need to protect my purity until I get married, for my country...
But you wanted this right?
No...
Your throbbing won't stop unless you
enjoy yourself with this one.
If you ignore this, you'll wet yourself even just from being touched.
But
the sex is...
If you keep quiet no one will know.
A man can't tell the difference between a virgin
or someone one who experienced it only once...
Is that true?
Yes...
Now, say "please stick your dick in my pussy".
Say it and you'll suffer no longer.
Please stick your dick in my pussy.
inside my pussy!..
Well, I can't help it if you keep pestering me.
I finally took the royal virginity!
This is the greatest prey!
So..? How's the feeling being thrusted by a man for the first time?
How...??
It hurts!
It only hurts?
Even your clitoris getting bigger...
You're enjoying yourself, aren't you?
Well then, I'm going to cum inside that princess pussy with that embarrassing clitoris!
Not inside..
I'll impregnate if you come inside!
Exactly. I'll have you bear my child!
No... They'll find out!
They'll find out I had sex!
I can't...
I can't get pregnant!
No!!!
I know it's wrong...
But it feels good coming inside...
I'm cumming...!
What...?
It won't stop...
He won't stop coming inside...
If he comes that much, it'll feel too good...
I'll break...
The princes not only has big clit, but squirts as well?
No..
Might as well take the occasion and hit a
second load to make sure you impregnate.
No...
Stop it already...
I can't..
I'm going crazy...
It's so good I'm going crazy...
It's coming.. .
It's still coming...
It's coming out.. He's really coming again.
Why? It feels good dripping it from my pussy...
No...
I don't want this as a first kiss.
My head...
I'm going insane...
It's so good I'm going insane...
He just released it a while ago and he's releasing it again inside!
It's coming out...
It's so good... I'm going to die...
How was it Your Highness?
The throbbing in your body is gone right?
Ah... she can't hear...
Well then, I'll leave the cleanup to Meylin.
I'll let you enjoy it again, Your Highness...
Why...
I just raped yesterday...
He even came inside...
Why is my body throbbing again?
Why do I want more sex?
I apologize for the delay, Your Highness.
Here...
I'll stop that throbbing of yours.
You're going to rape me again right?
Nope.
If you don't want it, you can do it with your mouth alone.
Eh?
So... what's wrong?
You want the sperm right?
Squeeze it out already.
No...
If you don't want it...
I'll just use this on Yukino again...
Please, wait...
Oh...
Would Princess Ridim prefer to have sex...?
I don't want to have sex but...
It's just to protect that girl...
Besides a man can't tell the difference between a virgin
or someone one who experienced it only once, right?
Yeah.
Then, I don't want it but...
But I prefer to have sex.
Doing it with the mouth is worse...
Do it already.
Yes.
What? Did you cum with just one thrust?
You were really holding it right? You perverted princess....
I didn't cum...
I haven't cum yet...
No...
If you do it that hard... I'll...
As a clown, I must make you enjoy yourself!
No..
Please... slower...
I'm cumming....
I'm going to cum...
Well then...
I'm going to thrust you until you cum!
No... I'm dead... I'm already gone...
Don't thrust....
I'm cumming now...
It's coming out...
The cum...
The sperm...
He's ejaculating so much... I'm breaking...
It feels so good... I'm breaking...