www.SubDESU-H.net
Come on, let's get started.
Hey, don't be like that.
Let's just enjoy this, okay?
This is great.
They feel really soft and tender.
Wow, that's such a horny expression!
Don't...!
No... Please don't!
You sure you want us to stop?
If you resist, then our agreement will be cancelled.
Then I...
Then you just need to stay put.
Yes...
Your pubic hair sure is thin.
The pussy is totally exposed.
Stop, please don't say that.
Lick~
It'll be tougher on you if you keep resisting like that.
Hey look, her thing is perfectly pink.
Make sure to take a good shot of this.
Please don't look.
It really is. That looks really horny!
It looks very different from slut pussies.
We went through a lot of trouble for this, so just enjoy the moment.
Just let yourself loose and moan however you like.
Nagatsuki, have you tried fondling this part?
Like this...?
Don't do that.
Sticky fluids are starting to leak out.
Anyway, these boobs sure are big.
Did you fondle them yourself to get them this big?
Stop this already.
Don't lick me there.
It has a very horny taste.
We can't just stop now, can we?
No!
And your nipples are already getting this hard anyway.
What did you...
Stop it already.
Oh, feeling horny now?
Your sensitive areas sure love it.
You really are a slutty girl, Nagatsuki.
Oh no, something's... coming out...!
Oh wow, she just climaxed!
No...
This is embarrassing...
Amazing!
But, I have to endure this...
Make that expression hornier, would you?
Can't stand anymore because it feels too good?
How about this?
No...!
That's a wonderfully sloppy expression for this shot, Nagatsuki Kasumi-chan.
They're filming me....
My breasts, my pussy...
It's so embarrassing that I'm about to lose it.
We're not through yet.
But... I have to endure this.
If I don't, Takemura-kun will...
W
Obscenity Missile
Oh no, it came again
Seasonal Retribution
Are you underestimating us, punk?
Speak up!
Hey Takemura, what's wrong?
Hey, there's a...
Umm...
What do you want?
Who the hell is she?
Nagatsuki-san.
I think I've seen her in our class.
Please stop this.
What?!
Hmph, ah forget it, I don't feel like doing this anymore.
How annoying.
Takemura-kun, are you okay?
I refused to listen to them, and got it.
Thank you, Nagatsuki-san.
That's nothing.
But if now they do something to you instead...
And what about you? They might come back for you again.
Nagatsuki-san.
You don't need to worry about me.
It's risky to do so.
But, I'm worried about you.
What, me?
Yup, if you take the place of Takemura and do as we say.
That's... Why?
You can refuse if you want to.
We'll just continue playing with Takemura.
Like giving him orders and such?
Yep, you got it.
Of course, if you refuse though, we'll be pissed and go all out on Takemura.
If I take his place, will you really not harm him anymore?
Of course! That'll be our agreement.
That is, if you properly follow what we say.
So what will it be?
I understand.
I'm going to do as you say.
Okay, then let's have you do something right away.
I can't do that!
I can't say it!
Fine, if you don't want to.
The agreement's cancelled then.
Takemura-kun.
Please caress my big boobs and slutty pussy.
Please do.
Oh, you want something horny to be done to you?
Some real pervert we have here.
Huh? I didn't... That's not what I...!
Okay, we'll do it for you then.
Please, let me off already.
You want a cock inside already, don't you?
No... put me down...
Here, come over here.
I'm going to properly insert it in as I put you down.
Now, combination is in progress.
No... no...
It all went in instantly.
It hurts.
It hurts...
Woah, that looks pretty tight.
Virgin pussies are great!
No, please don't move me.
Please, pull it out.
My insides are being violated by this cock.
It hurts.
It's my first time.
It hurts!
Stop!
The feeling of it touching and pressing me is really great.
Don't...!
Pull it out!
Ouch...
Let me do it too.
Wait for your turn.
I won't be able to resist this first-timer, you know?
What's that?
Let me use this hole too.
What, you can't...!
Stop, don't touch me in there!
There? Where exactly is "there"?
Don't open my asshole wide.
This is embarrassing.
Stop this!
I already told you to keep quiet!
I'll kill you if you sink your teeth into it.
I'm going to film your blowjob as well.
I think it's good already.
Here, try to relax.
Hey, if you don't try to relax, it'll hurt.
What's this? What's happening now?
It's wrapping me really tight.
Just how great is this horny slut?
The way her butthole squeezes is really great.
No, no I'm not!
I'm not a horny slut!
Stop this.
Please don't mess up my body anymore!
There are cocks in my mouth, my pussy, and even in my butt!
I don't want this anymore.
I don't want it, and yet...
Their cocks are rubbing inside me, and I'm starting to lose my mind.
This is suffocating...
Use your tongue properly.
My nipples are being constantly pinched.
It's getting more and more intense.
I'm going to break.
My butt, my pussy.
They're going to break...
What a great horny expression.
I'm going to cum too.
What? They're going to do it now?
Their cocks are getting hotter and twitchier.
I'm about to cum too.
What? Would...would they be releasing semen?
Then let's all cum together!
Please don't!
No!
Not inside!
Don't!
Please!
Make sure to drink it all up.
It has a... gross taste...
Wow, it's overflowing.
You just came too much.
I've cum a lot more than that before.
We're going home now.
So clean this up properly, okay?
No wearing of bras and panties tomorrow!
If you don't do it, we'll just go back to Takemura.
Oh, and the video we recorded will be uploaded on the web too.
Since then, every day after-school hours,
they'd call me, and order me to have sex with them.
As I said, you're going to be porn material for these virgins.
So you really did see Nagatsuki's insides, huh?
Mine's been stiff since yesterday.
Now show us your thing and play with it.
Wow, she's not wearing panties.
There's just one line and nothing else.
Looks really sexy.
Kasumi-chan's really cute.
Nagatsuki's breasts look very tender.
My breasts and pussy... are exposed to everyone.
Open your legs wider so that everyone can see clearly.
Yes.
Okay everyone, have a closer look at it.
Is it okay?
This is really embarrassing.
For everyone to clearly see my...
Make sure it's seen clearly!
Okay.
Show your face and boobs too!
Wow, I can really see her do it!
For real? Kasumi-chan really is a slutty girl!
I can’t hold on anymore.
Her nipples are getting stiff.
Hey, you have something to say, right?
Something for the virgins here.
Please look, look at my stiff nipples.
My pussy is also getting very wet now.
This is embarrassing.
But, as they look, I seem to feel more horny...
I can’t hold it in anymore...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Lots of hot stuff is being squirted on me!
Nagatsuki Kasumi!
Today, your seat will be this one.
The seat in front of us.
Okay.
Today you're having classes here.
What is this?
Something else is on it.
Sit down 'properly' okay?
I'm going to sit here?
You already know the drill, right?
Sit.
Pull your skirt up so we can see.
What a slutty girl.
Even though this is the classroom...
And everyone's here.
I'm doing this obscene thing.
If you don’t sit down quickly,
somebody will notice.
It's big, and it's reaching deep inside me.
Wow, she's really inserting that dildo in the classroom.
Kasumi-chan's a real pervert.
Wow, it's so big that it's already touching my womb.
This is something.
It's also wiggling inside me.
I'm going to moan.
Oh no, if it vibrates like this I'll...
Everyone will notice.
I'm going to moan.
This is embarrassing.
I'm cumming...!
Oh look, it's already very wet down there.
Pervert Kasumi-chan.
Getting wet like that, you're an exhibitionist, aren’t you?
No, I'm not.
I'm not a pervert.
How about this?
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Takemura-kun will notice that I've been having sex with these guys.
After that, I was constantly called to conduct different 'experiments'.
It fits quite well.
No...
I don't want this, I'm scared!
My nipples are going to break.
Kasumi-chan is getting really wet now.
Power on!
Wow, so pervert Kasumi-chan's insides look like this.
No... please don’t look.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to insert something bigger.
How about this?
It won’t fit in!
No!
Kasumi-chan's a pervert so I bet you can endure it all the way.
No, I can't!
Oh, the electric shock seems to be working.
Kasumi-chan's, it's going all the way in.
It'd be dangerous to move.
I'm going to break.
Slutty Kasumi-chan's pussy is getting a really clear shot.
Woah, it's going off the scale!
I'm cumming!
I'm a sex tool, made to fulfill your sexual desires.
Use me as you please.
Here I go!
Does it feel good to cum inside?
Please come again.
I can use this hole too right?
And this one too right?
It's hot!
Nagatsuki Kasumi's really something!
She literally came within seconds!
She agreed to become a slave for Takemura's sake, right?
That's one hell of a fondness she holds!
Nagatsuki-san.
Though she's now really soiled and dirty because of that.
Next cock please.
Nagatsuki-san!
Takemura-kun!
Why are you here?
No, please don't look at me!
Calm down.
It's okay now.
I'm going to protect you from now on.
I will protect you no matter what!
Yes.
Takemura may have said that yesterday, but...
Wouldn't it be bad if I disobey them?
I'm really sorry!
Please forgive us!
If our regular deals and transactions with TK Enterprise ends, it'll be the end of Dad's business!
TK Industries also sent us a warning that they'll end their business with us.
What's the meaning of this, Takemura-kun?
Have you heard of the Takemura Group of Companies?
Yes, the famous business...
The president of that conglomerate is my Grandfather.
In the end, I had to rely on my Grandfather.
Sorry if that was too pathetic of me.
No, that's not true.
I'm grateful that you did this for me.
Umm...
Kasumi-san, you can wear panties again from now on.
Eh? Oh no, don't look!
This is...
I'm going to do my best, so that next time I can protect you on my own.
Yes!
www.SubDESU-H.net
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Hey, look at this!
Not there.
Here!
Now we finally have one as well!
Our own milk supply cow-girl!
This is amazing!
Now I can drink fresh milk every day!
You love milk right, Yuugo?
It's really good for you.
Good morning Mom.
Oh, milking her already?
Just wait a bit for your milk, okay?
I'm not used to it yet, so I can't milk her properly.
Squeezing right from the tits, eh?
Won't it just come all out in one squirt?
Oh, it's starting to squirt well now!
That looks kind of sexy, Mom.
What are you saying?
I'm milking her!
Here's your milk.
Wow, it's really tasty!
Thanks Mom!
I'm off to work then.
Okay.
Still...
Being alone with this cute thing...
And because she's a cow-girl, her breasts are huge.
She really looks cute, but she's a cow-girl.
And her breasts are made to produce milk...
It'd be boring to just squeeze milk out of her everyday anyway.
She also has that really horny expression.
Could she be... aroused?
It's getting wet?
What is it?
You want me to take it off?
Wow, it's gotten really wet.
Do you... want me to do it?
Woah, it's opening really wide.
It'd be bad if we go all the way with this, though.
Can't we just leave the situation as it is?
I can't resist her anymore!
It's really tight!
Could it be her first time?
It's wrapping me tightly.
You like getting milked, right?
It's squirting really far!
Oh crap, if you keep squeezing me like that I'll...
I can't take it anymore.
I'm cumming.
As thanks for your milk, I'm going to give you my own 'milk'.
I'm going to pour it all inside.
S-She looks really cute!
I think I may have fallen in love with a cow-girl.
So I'm a pervert now?
Since then, I've been having sex with the cow-girl,
whenever Mom goes out to work.
I also completely forgot about the milk supply thing,
and just continued doing it with her.
Really tasty as always.
But she sure is capable of producing a whole lot more in a single day.
Huh? Look at her belly!
She's pregnant!
What, for real?
Could she have done it with our neighbor's cow-boy?
That can't be...
She then gave birth to a male cow-baby.
About the issue of the baby's father,
I managed to make up some story about it,
and it was decided that the baby would stay and be raised in our home.
I have more work and jobs to do now because of him.
Even now, the baby that bears my resemblance is drinking his milk peacefully.
www.SubDESU-H.net