(credits)
Have a nice day at work.
Thanks, Nanami.
About tonight’s anniversary plans...
We’re meeting up at the hotel at 7 pm, right?
Yeah.
I’m looking forward to it!
I’m dressing up.
Well... I’ll be off.
Have a nice day, darling.
Now the fun really starts.
Her dirty pussy is trembling.
This is the proper housewife, Honda Nanami-san.
To think that such a good girl pisses like the rest of us.
This pained face really gets me off!
And her erotic-pussy is wide open for the looking.
She’s pissing with such naughty noises.
Awesome expression!
Excuse me, it’s Honda.
Kamata-san, hello.
Sorry it took me so long.
I had something to take care of...
Don’t worry about it.
It’s not healthy to hold it in.
I’ve been waiting for you.
S-Sorry.
Umm... You said you had something from the Renters' Committee to talk about?
Something smells salty...
Y-You don’t mean...
Well, please come inside.
Let’s have some tea while we chat.
Come on in.
Wh-What are you doing?
There’s something I want to show you, Nanami-san.
W
Sore Demo Tsuma o Aishiteru
Even So, I Love My Wife
Episode 1:          The Wife’s Secret She Can’t Tell Her Husband.
What are you going to do?
Just look at this, please.
As the apartment caretaker...
Oh no!
Observing the tenants’ behavior for their safety is a very important part of my job.
You can’t... What?
S-Stop it!
It’s taken so beautifully, isn’t it?
No! Stop it!
Oh, but it’s getting to the best part.
Please, stop it!
No!
What a cute little voice you have.
I’ve been watching you for a very long time.
No! No!
I have recordings of EVERY embarrassing thing you’ve done.
Let me go!
I’m begging you!
It’s your fault, Nanami-san.
I was okay with just watching over you.
No!
But now I can’t hold back.
I want to be one with you.
That’s why I bothered to rent this extra room.
No way... You can’t... Don’t!
That belongs to my husband.
Please... Stop it!
Ow... S-So big.
It hurts!
I did it!
I’m one body with Nanami-san.
A man who’s not my Shuuichi is inside of me...
Help me, Shuuichi-san!
You feel even better than I thought!
Nanami-san, your pussy is squeezing me so tight.
Please, take it out!
I’ll... I’ll break!
I won’t tell... Anyone.
I’ll pretend... This didn’t happen.
This sex is also being recorded.
So just be a good girl and do as I say.
No... you can’t... No!
In that position... You’re even tighter!
Nanami-san, you haven’t had kids yet, right?
I’ll help you with that!
No!
Don’t... Don’t do it!
Don’t cum inside!
You can’t!
I’ll do whatever you say.
So please... Not inside!
No excuses!
Today is our anniversary... So I was going to hurry home.
Put on some makeup...
Meet up with Shuuichi-san...
And together, we were going to celebrate.
I’m so happy to celebrate our wedding anniversary today, Nanami.
Not so loud... I’m embarrassed.
Don’t worry.
The room next door won’t hear us.
That’s not it.
I’m embarrassed that you might think you have a whore for a wife.
I’d never think that.
You’re my sweet wife.
You can’t...
Nanami, you’re rougher than usual tonight.
Don’t... Don’t say that.
It embarr-... It embarrasses me.
It’s hitting... Hitting deep.
All the way inside...
Since this is our third year, do you want kids?
No... Don’t say that.
It’s embarrassing.
Nanami-san. You haven’t had kids yet.
I can help you with that!
Just as I thought.
You feel so good!
Nanami-san, your pussy squeezes me so tightly.
Nanami-san! That’s perfect!
Here it goes!
Cum inside.
I love you. I love you...
Then I’ll cum... Inside of you!
Please cum inside!
I want all of your seed in me.
Please!
It’s coming... It’s coming...
The juice... Inside... Flowing wide...
I love you, Nanami.
Me too.
I love you.
Today is the anniversary of the first time we made love.
Let’s love each other plenty every day from now on.
Don’t worry.
I’ll keep this a secret from your man.
Nanami?
You actually came on time to our appointment... You must really miss my cock, eh?
No... That’s not true.
You took a drive with your man in this car today, didn’t you.
Suck up my dick while thinking back to the good times you had with your man in this car.
This is too cruel...
Hurry... Please finish!
Help... Help me...
This is... Too cruel!
I can’t...
What a sweet voice you have!
Do you love my cock now?
That’s not...
I’m sorry... Shuuichi-san...
I’m so sorry!
Please... Please...
Even with my cock buried inside of you, you were still thinking about your husband?
Stop it... I’ll break... I’ll break!
By the way, how does it feel to be fucked by your husband, then sneak out, and be fucked by another man?
No!
Darling...
I’m sorry!
I’m so sorry!
Darling...
Very nice.
I’m excited again.
I’ll cum inside you again!
No... Please cum outside.
But I’ve already filled your womb with my seed so many times so far.
Don’t!
I really don’t want to get pregnant!
Stop!
If you make sure to fuck your husband every day, he won’t realize it isn’t his baby!
Nanami... I have to be at work early tomorrow. Can’t we...
Sorry.
I’ll do the work for you.
So please...
I just want to be with you as much as possible.
Why, Nanami?
You’ve been acting weird lately.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry!
I’ll do the work... I’ll do the work for you.
I just want... More... More of you!
Darling... I love how you feel.
I want... I want you inside of me.
I want your semen... Cum inside of me!
This way, this way!
Hurry!
I can’t...
I can’t do this in front of you...
What’re you talking about?
Then there was no reason for me to bring the camera.
I’m ready when you are.
Let it all out whenever you’re ready.
No...
I can’t...
I won’t...
Then let me help you.
No...
What a pretty little face, and yet you let out so much smelly stuff.
Why... Why are you being so cruel...
I got some wonderful shots out of that.
Well, now that you’ve relieved yourself, let’s go at it full force.
No way!
No... Not right after I went...
Raise your ass, baby. It’s sex, sex!
Stop it... Stop it... No... No!
A raw dick inside of your pussy just after I filmed it. This is fucking awesome!
No, no, no!
Please!
Let me wipe my butt!
But having sex with you while smelling your stinky butt? Even better!
No...
I’m sorry, Shuuichi-san... I’m sorry...
Oh my?
Looks like more is coming out of your butt.
Are you shitting yourself while you have a dick in you?
What a gross woman you are.
No... I’m not...
Nanami-san, you’re a poop-fetish pervert, aren’t ya?
No...
Nooo...
Darling... Help me!
While smelling your own shit, take a look!
Come on, come on, come on!
It’s coming, coming..
Take up all my semen!
Oh no!
Not inside!
Thank god.
I’m not pregnant.
I’m sorry... Shuuichi-san.
Come on.
Nanami-san, you pissed yourself again?
It’s not a dream...
How long have I been doing this?
I’ve been losing my memory halfway through.
Not so much... Oh no... Don’t cum right away...
Nanami-san, did you cum again?
I guess you love my dick!
What is Shuuichi-san doing right now?
Nanami-san, you’ve got a call.
Who is it?
Hello?
Hello, Nanami? It’s me.
Oh... Darling...
I just got back to the hotel from my business trip.
I hope you had a successful trip...
Yes. I’ll be back tomorrow evening.
I can’t wait...
Hey, Nanami, what’s wrong?
Don’t worry... It’s nothing...
Nanami? Nanami?
I’m just... A little sick...
Don’t worry.
Are you really okay?
Yes. I’m really okay.
Work hard, okay?
And don’t worry about me.
Tomorrow... I’ll be... Waiting at home.
Okay. I’ll come back as early as I can.
Don’t push yourself too hard, okay?
I can’t wait.
I love you, darling.
Me too. I love you, Nanami.
Darling... Sorry! I’m so sorry!
How pathetic you are, Nanami-san.
Darling... Please...
Your pussy feels much better after you’ve talked to your husband.
Wh-What?
What did you feed me?
Drugs that will make you feel much, MUCH better.
Until your husband comes back tomorrow, let’s make a shitload of love tonight.
Okay, Nanami-san?
No....
Sorry... Feels... Good...
What feels good?
It does... My body shivers... And it... Feels good...
What feels that good, madam?
Your cock.
Your cock feels so good.
Nanami-san, you’re a filthy whore of a wife who loves getting fucked!
My body is... My body is...
I can’t stop... I can’t stop it....
Fuck yeah!
Oh no... I’m losing...my mind...
Oh no... I can’t stop it...
Hey, Shuuichi-san...
I want to be your wife forever.
But I can’t undo what I’ve done.
Please... Shuuichi-san...
Will you still love me, even so?