Even if the training camp is over for us,
summer break training still goes on.
Ai, here I come!
Next!
More speed!
Mio!
Mio, keep up the pace!
I can't go on, It's too hot to be moving around.
That's why, after today's training
we can use pool like I told you.
Why don't you keep it up!
Se..Senpai, but we would like to dive
in the pool as soon as possible.
That's right! I'm even already wearing a swimsuit inside.
Mio, you're really...
That's because, It's too bothersome for me.
Err..Senpai...
The truth, I'm too...
Eh?
I'm sorry, I'm already wearing it.
Huh..Yes-yes, I understand.
Let's finished up for today.
Hurray!!
Oh, there's another one who already prepared for it.
Hey, everyone! Let's go to the pool together!
Se..Sensei, you've already change into your swimsuit?
He..He..That's because I bought a new swimsuit,
what do you think of it?
What I think..is that...
Hey, Mio!
Shuu-chan, are you okay?
What are you doing,
blushing like that?!
Stupid brother!
Hey..hey..don't swing the racket that way.
Actually, this is the beginning of something.
...Really Love
Are you awake, Shuu-chan?
I..I'm...
How is it, do you still feel dizzy?
Or does your head still hurt?
It's already fine.
Don't get up so quickly, just wait for a moment.
No, but...
Shuu-chan, It's getting big!
I'm sorry.
Why don't you let me look at it?
That's because your pants are stretching out like that,
I think it would be hard for you.
Is it okay with Sugiyama-kun?
That stupid brother, just leave him alone!
Sensei is with him, so I think it will be just fine.
Mio, could you please take a look at them?
Eh..?
It's your fault to begin with and it would be bad
to leave it with Sensei.
Huh, stupid brother! Leaves me no choice at all!
I'll go to!
Those two, they were looking for a reason to go anyway.
Shuu-chan, is this okay?
It doesn't hurt right?
Ye..Yes.
Amazing, It's not just big but it's also hot
and still getting bigger.
Sensei, It feels good.
Really? Does it feels good when I rub like this on your penis?
Shuu-chan!
It makes me feel bad to feel this good all alone.
No, you can't! You can't touch my breast like that!
Sensei's breasts are truly amazing.
You can't touch my breast,
I'm really weak there.
Sensei, do you feel it?
It feels good, but..but..If this continues
I'm gonna go crazy.
Please touch on mine too.
The fluid keeps coming out at the tip.
Sensei's getting wet already.
Sensei, how do you feel?
My breast's gonna melt,
my nipples feel good.
Shuu-chan, please give me more!
Sensei, you're gonna come right?
Coming? Is that what this is?
Inside of my body feels hot and my head is whirling around.
Me too, together...
Being abused like this, I can't...
No, I can't hold it!
Is this sperm, It's really hot.
Sorry for splashing on you like that.
Shuu-chan, you're still not
satisfied right?
That's because your penis is still big like this.
Wow, it's amazing.
Sugiyama-kun and Sensei look so erotic.
Hey..Did she take advantage of my stupid brother?
No, It doesn't look that way.
This time, I'll make you feel good with my pussy.
Se..Sensei.
Just do it quick, It's embarrassing to be
posed like this.
Yes.
Slowly, okay?
Sensei, was this your first time?
It's okay, please go all the way.
But,
It's fine, I'm an adult.
I can take Shuu-chan.
I understand.
It hurts..It hurts!
Sensei, It's all inside.
Shuu-chan, It's okay to move a little.
Sensei, but...
It's okay, move however you like.
Don't worry about me.
If you can't take, please say so.
Shuu-chan..Shuu-chan!
Sensei, It's hitting your deepest parts.
You can't let it out inside, okay?
That's an important place to make babies.
No, you can't! If you keep doing that,
I'm gonna go crazy.
But, your pussy is hot and totally drenched.
You're mean, I can't-
It's my first time...
It's my first time but I.
You're gonna cum, Sensei?
Shuu-chan, you're gonna cum too?
Would you do it together with me?
Yes. Together.
Shuu-chan, together with me.
No, cum..cumming.
I'm gonna cum.
I'm cumming!!
He let it out! It's cumming out!
Sugiyama-kun released it inside of Sensei's thing.
It could be bad, I wouldn't think
that Sensei could be a rival.
Rival is it?
That's right! Ai-san please come to my house
when we're finished today.
I want to talk about something with you.
Ye..Yes.
After that, we pretended we didn't see anything and returned to the pool.
Just a moment later, Sensei and Sugiyama-kun returned too...
But, they don't seem to feel awkward at all.
In the end, I don't ask anything about it.
-Sugiyama-
Mio-san, what do you think you're doing?!
Ai-san, take off your clothes too. Right now we need to think about
how we can be more erotic.
Hey, look at this!
Is that a porn magazine?
Yes, It was hidden inside Shuu-niichan's room.
Shuu-niichan loves this kind of stuff.
Do...Do you mean we have to do the things that are in this magazine?
That's right, If not we're gonna lose against Sensei.
Is that alright with you?
That's something I don't want,
but what If Sugiyama-kun comes back?
It's alright, I called Shuu-niichan to do some shopping with Kei.
Come on, quickly!
Okay, I'll take off my clothes too.
Ah..amazing, It's see-through...
It's more embarrassing to put on a suit like that
than to be naked isn't it?
Wha-What is this? Being done by a lot of people,
No way, the sperm is all over the body.
In here, there's a big thing going inside of it.
But, this person looks like she enjoyed it.
This one, they're doing it outdoors.
Sugiyama-kun is totally pervert, having this kind of book,
it's really indecent.
This is what they called adult toys, isn't it?
Did Shuu-niichan want to try these too?
It's embarrassing.
Mio-san, suddenly I'm staring to feel weird.
Ye..Yes, me too.
Err..If you don't mind, how 'bout we try some of it?
Eh?!
I think, If we only read the book then
we won't know how to really do it.
That's..that's right isn't it...
We're all women here, so we don't have to feel ashamed.
We even take baths together when we're in training camp...
But If we look at each other like this,
It's really embarrassing.
Hey, can I touch it a little?
Yes, It's okay.
Amazing, your skin is so smooth.
Mio-san's touch feels really soft,
It's different compared to a man's touch.
No, wait!!
Your nipples get hard when your turned on right?
I'm sensitive to this kind of thing,
it's embarrassing.
Me..me too, doing something like this
it's make me very sensitive.
I really feel it.
Mi..Mio-san, the next thing..why we don't do it in the bed?
We're actually perverts aren't we?
Masturbation with another women and getting drenched like this.
I feel bad for Sugiyama-kun,
since we're doing this by our selfs.
Ai-san..I'll put my finger inside, okay?
It's okay, me too..let me do it too.
Hey..Ai-san, do you ever masturbate by yourself?
Yes, about two or three times a week.
When I masturbate, I always think of
being touched by Shuu-niichan.
Me too, I always think back to when we're having sex in the past.
But still I want to do it with Shuu-niichan,
I want his penis inside of me.
Yes, I want his penis thrusting in me like this
and doing it much more.
If Sugiyama-kun likes it, I would let him do it
like the ones in the porno magazine.
Mio too, I'll be more erotic than ever.
I'll keep doing embarrassing things.
No, I can't hold it anymore.
It's coming..coming out.
Ai-san, me too..me too..I'm gonna cum..it's coming out.
I'm Cumming!!
It's three days after Mio-san and me
experienced doing something like that.
Eh, where'd they go?
They called me out here.
Shuu-niichan.
Mio, you're here?
Eh?!
How is it Shuu-niichan?
Do we look good at these suits?
Mio, what are you doing with that?
Even Saeki-san doing that.
I thought Sugiyama-kun would like cosplay like this.
Eh?!
We'd already decided it, today we're gonna do
every erotic thing we've never done before.
Even if we're ashamed of it, we're gonna try our best!
He..Hey, what is really going on?!
Saeki-san, wait a minute!
I'm sorry, I can't wait any longer.
Sugiyama-kun too, it's already big like this.
It's not good, If you're continue doing that
I'm gonna feel like doing it.
It's okay, I'll do whatever Sugiyama-kun's likes.
Because today, I'll be an erotic woman.
Saeki-san.
Please, Sugiyama-kun. Please tease me there...
on my embarrassing part.
Then I'll...
It's good..It's okay to be harder with it.
Saeki-san's pussy is already this wet.
No! I'm sorry, I'm going to cum already.
I'm getting turned on playing with your dick.
Can you tell?  I'm using my breasts.
My breasts are already this hot and I'm already horny.
No way, she even said that it's embarassing
Ai-san's really doing all that.
Me too, I'm already feeling weird.
Don't lick me where I'm drenched!
Saeki-san, should I stop?
No, I'm sorry. My thing..please lick my pussy!
Saeki-san, you're saying something indecent.
Yes, I said it.
If it's gonna make Sugiyama-kun happy, I'll say whatever it is.
Then, please say it more.
I really love penis and being tease like this,
make me feel it in my pussy.
Saeki-san, you're really perverted.
Why is it so embarrassing but it feels so good?
I can't hold it.
Me too..I'm gonna cum too.
Please..please squirt me with your sperm.
Please punish me for my indecent ways.
It's amazing, the sperm..it's coming
a lot is comming.
But, Shuu-niichan's penis is still as hard as ever.
Hey Mio, stop it! I just came!
No way! Today I'll make Shuu-niichan come all out.
Look, my nipples are getting hard.
Even though it's smaller than Sensei and Ai-san, It feel's good right?
Shuu-niichan's turned on face is really cute.
It make me want to tease you more.
Saeki-san?!
Mio-san, I'm cumming.
It..It's okay, Mio's pussy is already drenched enough.
It's in..inside all of it!
Mio..Saeki-san?
Shuu-niichan, look at us!
Please look at us while we're doing this indecent act!
Shuu-niichan's penis is really tasty and it makes me more horny.
Mio-san, I can't stop my hips.
It's feels too good!
Me too, I'm feeling you inside of me.
This penis is so good to me.
Mio, I can't...
Shuu-niichan, please give..give Mio..give Mio
all of your sperm, I'll take it all.
No, I can't hold it anymore!
Mio too..Mio too..I'm gonna cumming soon!
Please make a mess of my pussy.
It's hot..Shuu-niichan's sperm is hot
and feels sticky on me.
Mio, sorry.
Don't say that, now let me taste your sperm in my pussy.
Eh?!
With a pose like this, you can do it with the two of us.
Please, Sugiyama-kun, We can't hold it anymore.
If you're using pose like that, I'm gonna...
Yes, If it's for Sugiyama-kun we're gonna do...
gonna do anything...
Anything perverted for you.
I'll put it in, okay?
Shuu-niichan!!
It's great, Sugiyama-kun's penis is scrubbing against our pussies.
Your both so hot inside.
No, don't say that.  It's all your fault!
For awhile now..we've..we've really wanted your penis inside of us.
Doing things like this with all of you feels strange and
it's feels indecent of me.
Mio-san! Your nipples are getting hard
and ramming on mine.
Ai-san too, your breasts feels so hot.
You're really a pervert, Ai-san!
I can't hold it anymore.
Shuu-niichan, don't hold it in. Please fill our pussies with your sperm!
It's okay..to let it out wherever you like.
Please make us..make us dirty with it!
Mio too, I'm gonna cum again!
My erotic fluid is gonna come out again!
Me too, I'm gonna cum too!
My pussy..my pussy is beating around,
Together..together with everyone.
Let it out..let it out!
Amazing, It still yearns for your thing.
It's my first time doing something like this.
All of you, would you stop that already!
Eh?!
Senpai, why you're...?
If you're talking so loud,
there's no way someones not gonna notice it.
-Womens Bath!-
You intentionally invite him, what do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry for that, but after we saw Sugiyama-kun and Sensei doing that...
We thought we couldn't lose after that...
No way, you're watching all of it?
That's embarrassing!
By the way, It's all Shuu-nichan's fault!
He's doing it with everyone like a playboy.
Is that so? But that's what I like about Shuuichi.
Eh?! Why?!
Me too, I think that kind of behavior fits with Sugiyama-kun.
Shuu-chan's good side is okay with me.
Wa..Wait a minute, how did we start talking about this kind of thing?
It's true.
In the end, we don't have a choice but to notice everything about Sugiyama-kun.
I can't help but really love Sugiyama-kun.