www.SubDESU-H.net
Are you concentrating properly there?
O-Of course!
This guy here tells a different story though.
Ki-Kiriha...
Do my toes feel good to you?
If you plead to be taught gently,
by a gorgeous and style-perfect goddess maid like me,
then I'll be happy to let your cock inside me.
My Cranky Maid
Is Very Horny
Part 02
My maid is tamed from her butt
Bathtime Horniness!
The master will wash the maid's body.
Praise the Lord!
I don't understand you.
You've touched and licked my body a lot.
I can't believe you'd still be aroused by this.
It's because it's the girl that I love!
Even the way you wash is lame.
Because it hasn't taken effect yet.
Hey, that's...!
Hey!
Are you going to clean it or tease me?
I love you Kiriha!
I want you and I to be together forever.
That's unfair.
That's... stop...
It's just fine.
This is your master's order.
Idiot, idiot!
I don't want to say it while drowning in my sexual pleasures.
I'll say it already so stop!
Master...
So?
I love you.
Face me and say it!
I absolutely won't show you my face as I confess.
I love you too, Eishun.
Is that true?
You wanted me to say it, right?
Sorry, don't take it back.
Violating me right after confessing...
You really are a beast, huh?
Before you do that, vow to me and say this first,
"I'm sorry for being born into this world. I am going to be your slave."
I'm sorry for being born into this world.
There are still some words left to say.
Even if you don't want it, I'm going to be by your side forever.
I'm cumming.
I'm already cumming~!
He proposed as he inserted his cock...
... and my womb is accepting it!
Kiriha, I love you!
Wait idiot, I'm still...
He's rubbing spots that haven't been touched before.
No, let me rest for a bit...
No escaping.
I'm going to make you cum properly, Kiriha.
Please...
You're my only maid!
I'm going to leave my mark on this horny body!
Don't open it wide while you're inside me.
I'm going to be impregnated.
I'm going to break.
If you keep this up, I'm going to...
I'm going to cum from both my pussy and my butt~!
I'm still cumming~!
Multiple orgasms confirmed...
Aren't we getting out yet?
We've not yet finished.
It's still dripping no matter how much I rub it.
The way you clean it is lame.
I'm not about to let my beloved be this weak.
I love you, Eishun.
I will always stay by your side.
Punishment Sex!!
You just placed a collar on your cute maid.
What a sexy butt.
My lewd pussy is exposed!
This cock-teaser play is a bit embarrassing, but it feels wonderful.
Are you asking me for it?
What a dirty maid you are!
Don't make those ecstatic sounds!
This is your punishment, you know?
I'm sorry Master.
It's best for you to reflect on your actions!
Your maid gets aroused by getting slapped on the butt.
Please punish her more!
Oh no...
Don't play with it...
So you're getting horny from my punishment, eh?
You sex maniac maid!
My butt is sucking his fingers in!
Master~!
This is punishment for the perverted maid.
Master's cock is entering my butt!
Please don't move.
Master...
What is this?
Don't rub it inside my butt hole!
Don't... don't...
My butt is going to break...
It feels good Master...
I'm cumming from my butt~!
My insides feel like they're going to melt.
The way you look now is really, really cute!
And there he goes looking at my stupefied face.
He's such a brute.
How long are you just going to stare?
Until you plead for me to do it.
Do it more please!
You want to be violated by this cock, right?
Please punish my pussy with your cock Master!
This cock is wonderful!
Your insides are wrapping me!
No kissing!
Master...
Show me your face.
No, I don't want to.
Not there!
I like you.
I love you.
Master~.
I love you too.
Don't tease my cumming pussy any further!
I just can't stop cumming!
Here it comes again!
This is so brutal, master.
But, I like it.
I love him.
Don't touch me there.
No, no!
Not there!
I'm going to cum inside Kiriha.
Do whatever you please.
Please impregnate my masochist pussy.
Kiriha!
Here comes my impregnation orgasm~!
Being a maid is wonderful.
Please punish me some more...
...Master.
Eishun, I've brought you some souvenirs!
Good morning, Mom!
I understand that you're really 'invigorated' in the morning,
but wear some clothes, you're going to catch a cold.
It's early and you're already this noisy.
Oh, Kiriha-chan?
Good morning Auntie.
Kiriha-chan, I leave this idiot to you, okay?
Leave it to me.
I'll take on the responsibility of properly taming him.
What should I do?!
We have your mom's approval, so no problem, right?
I love you, Eishun.
So this is a mutual thing, huh?
Does this mean you're going to be lovey dovey with me from now on?
Now, it's time for our punishment game.
Huh?
Huh?!
I'm going to have to confiscate your base allowance,
but I'll be giving you a few choices,
and I'm already being pretty merciful, so be grateful.
Steal her purity
as a woman,
totally violate her
body and soul,
and then throw
her away like
an old rag.
You're going
to be the
maid, and
I'm going to
be the master.
Take
responsibility
and accept me
as
your
maid
forever.
I don't know if she's being honest or just plain rebellious.
You're going
to be the
maid, and
I'm going to
be the master.
Take
responsibility
and accept me
as
your
maid
forever.
Okay, Master.
Thank you, Shuu.
The punishment game won't end until one of us gives up.
I hate losing, you know?
I remember you do, Master.
Achoo!
www.SubDESU-H.net
The End