No...
We, the female teachers from Sawashiro academy...
Were under the control of Misawa-kun.
We are always being raped through unreasonable training.
At first, I can't help it and I didn't like it but,
As we were being raped...
Our bodies started getting numb...
And I noticed that we've already become his dirty whores.
W
Mesu Kyoushi
Injoku no Kyoushitsu
Part 3
I'm lucky...
I....
Did my best to bear it and waited for you.
My fiance, Eiji-san should be coming back to school soon...
I'm waiting for the day he comes back...
Infirmary
No...
Your dick seems happy.
Between my boobs.
Your dick is getting bigger.
My my...
You're really a perverted teacher, Rihoko-sensei.
How nice of you.
What will the others think?
To be able to have sex with other teachers?
When they find out that there's a teacher who is cooperating with me,
How do you think they'll react?
You should be thankful.
To be able to feel the sensation of cum through titfucking.
I told you.
Yeah, you're right.
H...Hey...
My boobs... don't thrust it...
Even if I ejaculate,
It'll become erect again right after.
The pills you gave is really effective.
You... how impudent...
How is it?
How's the feeling of your big dick being rubbed by erected nipples?
It's good right?
Sensei's erect nipples...
It's pumping and...
It's hot!!
Your dick...
I'm getting weird...
I'm getting more horny!!
You can...
With your sticky sperm...
You can spray it all over my boobs...
Release it all over my milk filled breasts!
My boobs... are coming!
I'm cumming too!
The milk!
I'm stained with milk and semen...
It's so thick...
It's already a lump...
Hey...
Are you going to deal with Miyuki-sensei after class?
Yeah, this thing I got from Rihoko will be useful.
What kind face will Miyuki-sensei make?
But are you sure about that Rihoko?
You're not kidding about your feelings towards that man right?
It's alright.
You know...
I got all excited when...
I saw a nice man like him in trouble.
If you do that hard...
I'm going to break!
Miyuki-sensei is wearing a nude apron and servicing to me.
It'll be a loss if I don't have fun with it.
Please...
Next week... that man...
Eiji-san will come back.
It's alright.
Show your fiance as you are right now.
How cruel...
Isn't he your...
No... stop...
My boobs... No...
Don't touch them...
Hey hey, are you going to cum from your boobs again?
How many times will this make it?
No... I feel it...
No...
The milk will flow out...
It's so good.
No... The milk will flow out...
My boobs will cum...
It came out again...
My boobs...
Hey, I didn't cum yet.
Please... let me take a break...
Just give up... You'll be more comfortable if you'll accept that you're a slut.
Just like the other female teachers.
But... I will not give up.
When that man... When Eiji-san comes back... Then maybe...
Even if you stop now,
Your virginity and the boobs that spray milk will never be the same as before.
And... are you the only one who's betraying your partner?
Eh? What do yo mean by that?
Look at this.
He's been deceiving you and,
Has already laid hands on other woman.
No way...
Why... why...
Eiji-san...
It can't be helped,
It's because you didn't let him do anything to you.
No way...
You can't...
You can't go far with this...
No!
Sorry, I'm happy but...
This thing...
I want to do this after we get married...
Sorry...
I just got carried away...
I... I...
Is this my fault...?
Yes.
You're already messed up with my dick right now.
No...
Why am I...
Why is my body getting hot in this situation?
You don't have to think of him anymore.
You can be more... honest with yourself.
It's so intense...
The penis is thrusting inside.
Don't do it so hard.
Yes, yes, keep going.
You should feel it.
Just like what he did.
The penis...
The penis is so good.
Even though it's not Eiji-san's.
I feel it.
I'm feeling it a lot...
Hey hey, are you touching your boobs by yourself?
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop this.
It's so good.
Hey... If you ask for it... I can make you feel even better.
Please thrust me more...
Please thrust your penis even more...
Please make me more good.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Sanada-sensei, good job on your 3 months training.
Oh, thank you very much.
Oh, uhm... Makiyama-sensei?
Miyuki... no... How's Toudou-sensei?
Are you worried about her?
It seems that the other teachers aren't around either.
You'll find out later.
Sanada-sensei... Hey sensei...
Sanada-sensei...
You're finally awake.
Takamine-sensei!?
What are you doing?
I feel it...
Look.
Stop it...
Why are you doing this?
This... Sanada-sensei.
Are you watching...?
Are you properly watching me masturbate?
My boobs too...
Watch them.
Tankamine-sensei...
It's so good!
The erotic milk is flowing out from feeling it too much.
Milk!?
No... I'm cumming...
My boobs and pussy are cumming together...
Look at it.
Watch the moment when I cum.
Stop! Stop it!
No! I'll cum...
I can't hold it!
It will come out!
Sensei...
Takamine-sensei...
Sanada-sensei.
Look at her too.
Ka... Kasai-sensei...
Makiyama-sensei too...
Sanada-sensei...
Look at my perverted part...
Look at me!
My my... Kasai-sensei is totaly a filthy masochist whore.
Makiyama-sensei... stop it already!
Oh my...
Do you think I'm doing this by force?
My ass is getting numb... Please spank me more.
The rope is breaking into my pussy...
Do you understand?
She's a perverted woman.
Ouch!
It hurts!
Kasai-sensei, do you hate pain?
I don't hate it...
I never thought that you would be like this within 3 months.
Was your master's training that good?
Master...?
It's me, Sanada-sensei.
The penis...
It's so good.
You! What are you doing to Hasekura-sensei?!
As you can see, this.
I'm being watched by Sanada-sensei...
My my.. you really can't be helped.
Are you that horny from being watched by sensei?
Yes I am.
I got horny...
I got horny from being watched.
Misawa, what are you thinking?
Stop it!
Hey! Hey! Wait...
This is all what they want.
Master... please.
My anus... deeper...
With master's dick.
Please thrust it deeper.
No way...
Well, I think this is my revenge.
Nii-san...
A little more...
The thick dick is going in deeper...
Don't stop... Keep thrusting...
Please... give me master's sperm!
Release a lot of it inside my ass...
S...Stop!
Stop it!
Master... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!!
Misawa...
Why are you...
Because I'm the lover's son...
From the main family.
I've been ignored by them and from you too.
I've been waiting for this moment.
When I can pull you down.
Don't tell me...
Where's Toudou-sensei?? Where's Miyuki-san!?
Welcome back Eiji-san...
Good job on your training.
Miyuki-san, your outfit...
Hey, let him watch it.
Okay.
Look at my pussy.
I've been fondled by my master.
No way...
If you touch so hard...
My nipples will get hard...
Your penis is getting hot.
My boobs... My nipples are hard and it will come out...
Good, show him your bosom...
Eiji-san...
The milk will gush... the breast milk will gush!!!
Look at it...
Look at it!!!
I think it's over...
The penis is coming in...
No... I'm too sensitive...
If you thrust that hard...
So much will come out!
Hey hey... if you go too insane, you're fiance will get bored.
I'm sorry.
I can't hold it...
I'm already this perverted...
I can't do it anymore if it's not you master...
This hot, thick and big dick is what I want.
I'm feeling my master's kiss so much.
My body is so hot...
Master, it's so intense...
My... My pussy is cumming...
I'll release it inside in front of your fiance.
Go on and cum.
Cum inside of me!
Release it... release it inside!
It's hot...
Master..
I...
I want more of your dick.
Please do it more...
Please rape me more...