Centering.
Okay.
Nice keeper!
Offside Girl
You shouldn't miss that one!
Defender, you musn't lower your guard!
Raise your voice to check on that!
Coach!!
What're you doing in here?!
How rude of you, didn't the coach say he would watch your training?
No..no..that's not what I mean,
but what were you doing up 'till now?
That..would be...
I'm trying to change myself.
What is she saying...
Is that person our team coach?
Right, she's our coach after all.
There's been a problem lately.
She hasn't shown up to our training before,
so we're thinking of her.
Listen to me, Nanami.
Careful with that person, okay?
Why's that?
Just be careful with her!
That's what Akira-chan said, but...
Why should I be careful with this person?
She's doesn't look like a weird person to me...
What is it? Is there something on my face, Nanami-chan?
No..It's nothing.
I can call you Nanami-chan, right?
Yes..you can.
Um..coach..Azuma-san, why are you coaching the soccer team?
Is it weird for a woman to be coaching a soccer team?
No..It's unusual for a woman though...
That may be true..you can call it my hobby for doing such a thing.
What is it, Nanami?
No...
The truth is...
Can I go over there?
She's joking of course...
Don't say anything foolish, tomorrow we have morning practice.
You should go to sleep early today.
It should be more busy for us from now on.
Wait, Akira-chan!
Hmph..what his problem?!
Akira-chan is an idiot!
But, it's like Akira-chan said.
The tournament is closer, so soccer teams should be fighting over it.
Hey, manager!
Yes!
Can you take this as well?
I can't..more than this..I can't carry it.
A mountain of laundry...
It doesn't get any drier...
I don't get soccer rules at all...
Manager should work hard everyday...
Even at school, I rarely meet Akira-chan.
He..I can't do this anymore..I'm gonna die..!
It's already been one week since that and I haven't
had any sex with Akira-chan.
I know that he's tired from the training, but we're live in the same neighborhood after all...
I want to have sex..have sex..have sex..have sex...
Want to have sex!!
I want to have sex with Akira-chan!
Nanami-chan, If you have time, could you help me in here?
Yes, it's okay!
Okay, let's take a little break!
Akira, I don't see the coach.
If you're looking for coach, she just entered the club's room with the manager.
What?!?!
That's dangerous!!
No..you can't...
Please stop it..coach...
We're all woman in here...
I'm sorry Nanami-chan, but I can't hold it any longer...
I can't hold myself back anymore after I've seen you
look after everyone in here.
Nanami-chan is already a good manager for them.
What does that mean..It's not...
What big breats you have...
Did you feel it?
No..you can't..If you're rubbing on it...
No..!
It's gonna come out!!
I let someone make it come out besides Akira-chan...
It's unbelievable..you could let the milk out?
What indecent breasts, right?
What is it Nanami-chan? Did the milk over here also come out?
You can't..If you touch there right now...
You can't...
I want to have sex so badly with Akira-chan,
so my body is already this sensitive...
Come out!
It's gonna come out from my pussy!
No..come out..It's coming out!!
That's it, coach!
I just thought of something like this.
When you're not here, we made an extra key for this room.
I'll take Nanami right now.
Co..a..ch...
I've told you about it since that time,
looks like you need more intense punishment.
What..wait..Kawakami?
I'll have anal sex with my lovely penis in here.
It should be tight, right?
No way..wait..stop it...
No..!
No~!!
Look at this, the two of you.
It's all the way inside of her.
This woman's asshole is really amazing.
No..
No...
No,
don't look at it...
What're you doing, Nanami?
It's Akira-chan's fault.
I wanted to have sex with you all this time.
You're not letting me do it.
Idiot, that's not...
I masturbate by myself, when I remember this.
I can't stop it, cause of your delicious penis.
Even me too...
I want to have sex with you!
The tournament is close, so I should think more of soccer.
This..this...
If I thrust my penis in this pussy everyday...
I couldn't think of anything else, you know?
No...
Akira-chan..Akira-chan!!
It's rubbing in..Akira-chan's penis...
It's rubbing inside my pussy!
Akira-chan, do you feel good?
Is it good inside my pussy?
Sure, it really feels good!
Nanami-chan's doing it...
What is it, did her asshole get loose right now?
Here Nanami-chan, lick coach's pussy.
Please Nanami-chan, please lick my pussy.
I want you to lick my clitoris.
It's good...
Nanami-chan's tounge is really good!
Kawakami, spread my asshole and break it!
Akira-chan..Akira-chan!
Break it..make my pussy break apart!!
Kawakami, I can feel your hot thrust in my stomach.
I' cum..cumming..cumming...
Akira-chan..I'm gonna cum..!
Cum..cumming...
It's cumming~!
Cumming!!!
What?! Manager fetish?!
That's her purpose all this time and though
we're the only ones who knew about it.
She doesn't even care who the manager is,
even it's a boy or a girl.
That's why she told you about her hobby before.
The last manager left abruptly after being teased by her.
She transferred into the other school after that, you idiot!
But, she's lurking in her room all the time.
Nanami-chan should remember the last manager.
The last manager is Miyajima.
Miyajima-san...
Captain.
Miyajima.
It's been a long time.