I wonder what's wrong with Tomoe-chan.
Tomoe-chan and Hachiya-san.
He's sexually harassing someone again.
Now you re hitting on students?
I know how to deal with him,
but I can't let him continue like this.
Hachiya-san, Tomoe-chan, is something wrong?
Why if it isn't Atsuko-chan.
Hachiya-san.
I'm sorry, but I need to go now.
Tomoe-chan?
Tomoe-chan...
Well, you're here now so it's okay.
I have to finish my grocery shopping.
Hey!
Oops, I thought your ass was one of my fresh watermelons.
It's been a week since I moved in to this town.
There are still some students in my class that I'm unfamiliar with.
Tomoe-chan though, doesn't seem to be like the others.
Something else also feels different about her.
She's being sexually harassed, right?
Then why is she...
Was she trying to apologize to Hachiya-san?
Welcome home.
Yui, what's wrong?
I'm home. Well, Asuma injured himself again earlier.
Jeez, and he's not that healthy to begin with.
He's from our neighbor's place, right?
Chikako's brother.
He's always making me worry.
My my, you really care about him, huh?
What are you saying?
That's not it!
It's not like that at all!
Anyway, let's take a bath already.
Eh?
Me too?
This feels nice.
Dad really got a nice place for us.
Just like our late mother, I decided to become a teacher.
After I became one, I got a request from Nasui
town's mayor to teach at their academy.
They arrange to official documents and even
moved me and my family to their town.
I was surprised by the intensive background check
the town had, but everyone seemed welcoming.
Most of the monthly expenses in this town are covered.
In exchange, the town compensates for the
fees with their volunteer work programs.
One month has passed since I became a volunteer.
My volunteer work has become a part of my normal routine.
Everyday occurrences have also become
normal for the students as well.
I don't think that was just some prank...
...but Tomoe-chan was...
Jeez, Onee-chan.
You're going to get wrinkles if you keep looking all serious.
Oh Yui...
That's right
I need to talk to her first.
The town-entrenched trap
Bodies stained in white
Good morning, Kenji-kun.
He's one of my students and is the son of the school principal.
I'll see you off sensei.
You-You're not wearing Angel Ribbon's virgin clothing!
Change now!
I'll be able to teach better with this?
Though he's a NEET, it's something the principal wants you to do.
You just have to follow his orders.
Th-That was just for the day before.
I was simply told to wear it.
Those clothes are already...
K-Kenji-kun?
Just for the day before?
So that "virginity" was just for the day before...?
S-Sensei you tricked me!
I'm not interested in a non-virgin Angel Ribbon!
Wha-What was that?
Staff Room
Is that true?
Why?
Kenji-kun won't be able to attend class for
awhile because he is being hospitalized?
He was acting a little weird this morning.
I suddenly have a lot of free time,
maybe I should make something delicious.
Oh, Tomoe-chan!
This is good, maybe we could shop together.
Tomoe-chan's shoplifting?
Hey you!
Come with me for a second.
Well, it seems that she doesn't want to accept Kenji's situation.
Can't you do something?
You're too soft on your son.
She is quite popular though, so I think it should be okay.
Thank you very much.
I'll repay you for this someday.
You again?
You never learn do you?
I'm tired of getting angry over you.
I'll just have to teach your body a lesson.
No...
Don't!
You don't get to say that!
Man, you sure have a sexy body.
Are you inviting me to do it?
I'm not...
These sure are big.
Hey, work on this too.
Hey, it's still too early for that.
I can't hold myself back any longer.
Do it already.
I'm pretty sure this was where Tomoe-chan was led to.
It's open.
Wait, I think I can hear voices.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
You keep on shoplifting in our store.
Were you looking forward to this?
Forgive me, I'm sorry.
Forgive me...
Are you getting wet from this?
No, I'm not!
Your nipples are getting stiff.
Seems like your body still hasn't learned its lesson.
No, please...
This is...
You're sucking on my thing quite well.
I'm just about to cum.
It's delicious...
I'm going to cum a lot inside you.
Not inside!
You're not supposed to shoplift!
Reflect on your actions!
T-Tomoe-chan...
It's coming out.
Your stinky cum is pouring inside.
Forgive me...
It's my turn now, hurry up.
I'm taking her now.
Oh no, I need to stop them.
St-Stop that!
Who are you?
I'm her class adviser!
Th-This is a crime!
Sensei...
Didn't you ask for another round?
I added another as a service.
Then we'll have to enjoy this one as well.
She regularly shoplifts at our store.
How many things do you think she's stolen already?
Even so, doing this is...
It's better than handing her over to the police.
Or maybe you plan to tell the police yourself?
Th-That's...
If I go to the police, Tomoe-chan's life will...
Would you be willing to take her punishment instead?
Th-That's...
Then get out of here.
We're really busy punishing her.
Wait! Please wait!
What should I do?
I can't just leave her here.
No way.
I... I understand.
I'll take her place.
So, please forgive her.
Oh, really eh?
Then to start, why don't you give me a tit fuck?
H-He's telling me to put that huge thing between my breasts?
Here, do it already.
Wh-What should I do?
Hey don't let go of your hands.
Th-This is, his dick?
Rub it already.
Ru-Rub it?
S-So, what am I supposed to do?
You don't know how to give a tit fuck?
Or are you just acting innocent?
A man's dick is between my breasts.
This is...
This is for Tomoe-chan!
For Tomoe-chan's sake.
Sensei, make me feel good with that cute mouth of yours.
Mouth?
No way using my mouth?
A dick is inside my mouth.
It feels gross.
Good sensei.
You're sacrificing yourself for your student.
His dick is rubbing inside my mouth.
I don't want to, yet my tongue is holding it in.
Is-Isn't this enough?
You want it that bad?
What a shameless teacher.
This won't do as a punishment.
It... It's coming out.
From his dick, into my mouth...
Don't spit it out.
Drink it all.
Oh no, he's choking me with his dick!
He just made me drink his stuff.
I don't want this anymore, forgive me.
Hey, we're not done yet.
It's my turn now.
Sorry, I'm going home now.
Wha-What, finished already?
That was unexpectedly short.
See ya sensei.
We'll be counting on you next time.
Tomoe-chan, wait.
Even if you did shoplift,
they did something that can't be forgiven.
So you have to talk to your guardian and report
the incident to the supermarket's...
Hey, wait!
You don't understand a thing, sensei.
Wha-What do you mean?
You'll understand eventually.
You'll soon understand.
Tomoe-chan!
Hachiya-san, don't startle me like that!
You’re working as a volunteer, Atsuko-chan?
Then it was right for me to wait.
Volunteer, you mean... ?
So this is the volunteer work?
It starts in three days?
Volunteer Work Participation Details
I didn't think it would start so soon.
Leave of absence
There's still that issue with Tomoe-chan.
But she's too reserved, so...
Onee-chan!
Wh-What should I do?
Asuma is...
What should I do?
What do I...?
Asuma is...
Asuma is...!
Yui, calm down.
Asuma was working at his part-time job, when he
made a mistake and caused property damage.
How about Chikako-san?
He never told her about it.
He's not allowed to have a part-time job, but he
wanted to help his sister in any way he could.
So he decided to take responsibility
and do something to help out.
I understand.
In the meantime, tell me everything that happened.
And about Asuma-kun as well.
Onee-chan, thankyou.
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
What? Are you his older sister too?
I-I'm his older sister's friend, Takagi Atsuko.
I'm a teacher at Nansui Academy.
Chi-Chikako-san won't be able to come,
so I came instead to hear the whole story.
I don't think this is a good idea.
Yo-You're right.
We can't allow you to interfere.
We need his older sister.
Ma-May I ask why? I don't see why it's a problem
for me to hear the details of the incident.
Besides, I will tell Chikako-san about it later.
Even if you say that...
When will his sister be able to come?
Umm, I can't contact her until the day after
tomorrow since I have volunteer work.
Volunteer work, huh?
So you're saying you will be away from school?
Yes.
But it will only be temporary.
I have an idea.
The boy and the girl can go home.
We'll just need to talk to you and everything will be okay.
Okay, Asuma...
Onee-chan, thank you!
10 million?
It was a specialized equipment.
So I understand that he can't pay us for the damages.
That's right.
10 million yen is just...
If Chikako-san hears about this...
So...
I think you may be able to pay for it
if you agree to come work for us.
Here...?
If I can reduce the amount that way...
But, Chikako-san is also working, so I do not
think the issue could be resolved soon.
If you need assistance though, I think
I can do something about it.
Even if just a little...
Really? Then that would really be helpful.
I want you to start right away.
It will only be for three days, but I hope I can be of some use.
This is for the best.
That will be enough.
Everyone will surely be satisfied by then.
Well, have we got ourselves a deal?
Yeah, she said she'll do it right away.
That sure went smoothly.
Umm, then what will I do?
Don't worry, it's easy.
You just need to provide a little service using your body.
That can't be...
I can't do that.
Please let me go.
What are you saying?
Maybe we should let his sweet older sister do it instead?
No way, you can't do that.
You can't do that!
Too late now.
You have to keep your word.
No!
Stop, this is gross.
Please stop!
She has the sweet scent of a virgin.
No, please don't do that!
Stop.
Please let me go!
No way...
No, I'm in this sort situation again...
I want you to pleasure this dick with your boobs.
I can't... breathe.
I'm sucking a dick again.
No, stop.
Hey, this won't end if you don't use your tongue more.
It smells and tastes worse than the dicks from before.
Oh no, the sour smell is creeping inside.
It also feels weird in my mouth.
This feels good.
I haven't washed my dick for quite a while.
Clean it well, okay?
No, why is this happening?
Your clitoris is getting hard.
No, not there!
Don't play with it.
Are you getting horny even though
you're being forced to do this?
You sex pig!
No...
That's not true.
No way.
I can't be feeling good from this.
I'm about to cum.
No!
She's really sucking it.
She's going to squeeze it all.
Oh no, I have cum in my mouth again.
It's still coming out.
I can't drink this much cum!
It stinks.
I can't believe something this stinky is...
We're just getting started.
Hey, suck it with your mouth properly.
It feels like his dick is completely filling my mouth.
This is amazing.
I've never experienced a fellatio like this before.
She's learning well.
So, she's finally going to... to...
Hey, you guys started already?
We were quick to start.
This woman feels amazing.
No, there's another one?
It's really looking good now, I think it's time to stick it in.
No!
Anything but that!
It's my first time!
Is that so?
Well, you did say you were going to do it.
So here's your second dick!
It hurts!
It's inside me...
Her mouth pussy's squeezing me tight.
It feels really good!
Hey, that's blood!
What?
You really were a virgin!
The one appointed to you hasn't fucked you yet?
What...?
That's not good.
It’ll be bad if they find out.
This is the Ooguro construction firm.
If boss says it's okay, then there's probably no problem with it.
We're going to change plans a bit.
I'm going to go harder on you now.
It hurts!
It’s going deep inside me.
No!
No, don't record me in this position!
If you move like that I won't be able to hold myself back!
No, stop!
Don't move!
Your dick will be molded into my pussy.
My insides feel like it's going to burst from this pain.
It's entering even deeper!
No...
Oh, you get even more aroused When I hit you deep?
Then...
It-It's still going deeper inside!
No, my body will break!
I will go crazy!
I can't get enough of this squeezing sensation!
I'm going to cum inside, okay?
No, anything but that!
I'm going to get pregnant.
I don't want to get pregnant!
If you say that, I might want to impregnate you even more!
No, stop.
Please.
No... No... Don't!
No!
It's coming out.
Pull it out!
No, I beg of you...
I don't want to get pregnant.
Stop pouring it inside me.
Pull it out.
I'm going to get pregnant...
Seems like we can still use these.
What big tits you got here.
How long does he plan on doing this?
Your nipples have become pretty hard.
You're quite horny, huh?
Don't pinch my nipples.
No...
Even if you say that, you're still feeling aroused, aren't you?
You're feeling happy that you're covered in cum.
No, my body feels all tingly.
I'm going to squirt it all over you.
Ooguru-sama will be happy with her as well.
So from now on we can fuck this woman, right?
No, she's just here for three days.
After that we will deal with the boy's older sister.
So it's come to that, huh?
Looks like we'll be able to work well for a few days.
You bet.
I'm home.
Onee-chan, welcome home.
What happened?
Yui, so you're still awake.
It's okay now.
So sleep well.
Thank goodness.
Thank you.
I have to tell Asuma tomorrow.
Well then, good night.
Good night.
I have to go back there tomorrow.
What should I say to Chikako-san?
If you keep pushing it in lake that,
I'll feel all tingly.
It's like you weren't a virgin yesterday.
This dick has made you crazy.
It's going deep inside me again.
Don’t go so deep inside me!
Don't push it against my womb.
Then make it feel better for me so I won't have to go so deep.
He's being so rough, yet it doesn't feel as painful as yesterday.
I'm going to cum inside you again.
He's going to cum inside again.
I'm going to get impregnated.
What's going to happen to me?
Hey, there's someone on the phone for you.
Yes? Right, yes...
What? Well... Is that so?
Yes, I understand.
Hey, you can go home now.
You don't need to come tomorrow, okay?
Huh?
Seems we're done with the boy's case.
We don't have any business with his sister anymore either.
Just go home, an prepare for tomorrow or somethimg.
If this continued things would probably go awry.
Okay, I'm going back to work.
Why?
What just happened?
Also, I wonder what he meant.
Are they doing it here?
This is a requirement for living in this town,
and I don't want to impose on my father any longer.
We've been waiting for you.
Now, please come inside.
Mayor Ooguro!
I haven't seen you in a long time.
I am pleased to work here starting today.
General counseling?
I haven't done something like that before.
It's okay, it's not that hard.
They said you have what it takes.
Who said that?
Oh yes, Tomoe-san from your class has also
been doing a good job these past few days.
Tomoe-chan?
She's the one doing the counseling? Not the other way around?
Okay, you can observe her from here.
Here.
It's deep!
It's rubbing deep inside me.
T-Tomoe-chan...?
Father...?