www.SubDESU-H.net
Now then, lick my pussy.
Make me feel good, okay?
Insert your tongue in the hole.
Oh, that's good.
You're doing great.
Keep that up.
Don't just lick the pussy, lick my asshole too.
That's right, suck and lick it.
Play around it with your tongue.
There, good.
Don't forget the clit.
W
Masochist Men Devouring
Oh no, it's already time for the last order.
You're closing shop already?
It's still a few minutes before ten.
Still too early.
Can't be helped.
Why don't we start again somewhere else?
Get the bill already then.
This will be your total.
What, you're trying to rip us off?!
It's because you women came here alone.
How foolish of you two.
If you can't pay up, then you'd best be prepared.
I know a few places where you can instantly earn some cash if you want to.
You scum...
Stop fucking with us.
If you don't want to be hurt,
then just pay up already.
Hurt, you say?
Makin' real fun of us, eh?
What?
You don't know what'll happen when we get really angry!
I'll kill you all on the spot!
Now she's gone loose.
You...!
Don't you dare underestimate us!
We've already beaten up countless thugs just like you.
W-wait...
Who the hell are you gals?
Just the leader and the right hand of a brawl gang in Tokyo.
Well, former-leader and right hand though.
Oh? You look quite the pretty boy when looked up close.
It'd be a waste to just smash your face.
Our trip here was quite devoid of a man's presence anyway.
I was thinking of really letting loose on our last night here at least.
Wow, quite something you've got here.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Stop... hey!
I'm going to let you have a taste of mine so get it stiff already.
Hey, something wrong?
Here, take this!
Rina's specialty, her reverse-rape has now begun.
Stop, he's my boyfriend!
Please!
Stop it!
Oh, so you two are related in that way.
Erika...
I guess it's just natural for the girlfriend to not want to see his guy do it with another girl.
Then do it with that guy.
That's a great idea.
I think that would be interesting.
Cuz adultery is only good when you yourself commit it, not when your partner does it.
Now that it's settled,
take off your pants already.
Wow, the guy's really into it.
T-Tamura, what is your cock getting stiff for?!
Shut your mouth!
It'd be really easy to crush your throat just like this, you know?
You all,
You'd better stop taking it easy with us!
Come on, take off your panties and show us your butt already.
Your boyfriend will get it if you don't.
Hey, the name's Tamura, right?
She's already askin' for it.
Just drive it in and make her feel good.
Erika-san...
Kenji-san...
I'm sorry!
No...
Stop...
I don't want...
No, don't....
Huh? You got a boner by watching your girlfriend have sex with someone?
What a real pervert you are!
Well, I've got quite a taste for perverts though.
We'll do it our own way here.
Let's just have fun.
No!
Stop!
Get away from Kenji!
Please!
It went all the way in.
It's really big and stiff.
No...
I don't want this...
Kenji!
Hey, I'm the only one left out here!
Now then, lick my pussy.
Make me feel good, okay?
Insert your tongue in the hole.
Oh, that's good.
You're doing great.
Keep that up.
Stop!
Get away from Kenji already!
Please!
Don't just lick the pussy, lick my asshole too.
That's right, suck and lick it.
Play around it with your tongue.
There, good.
Don't forget the clit.
There, there!
Feels great, right?
Here, have some more!
There!
Wow, that's amazing.
I can totally see how his cock enters your pussy.
Here, in and out.
In and out.
His cock's already twitching.
There, there!
There!
Hey, Tamura-kun, stop this already.
Kenji is...
Kenji is...!
Please, stop this!
No....
Hey woman.
Take a look at this.
This man's moving his hips by himself.
This means that mine feels a whole lot better than your loose one.
Kenji...?
Take this, take this!
Feels good, right?
Don't you cum just yet.
Make me fully enjoy this.
There, there!
It's getting stiffer and stiffer!
Here!
More, more!
Take this!
That's great.
You’re doing well.
Put more energy in your licking.
Stir it up inside the hole.
There.
Do it like you're digging into the flesh.
And don't forget the clit.
There.
More,
Do it more intensely...!
There,
There!
Do you feel the twitching inside?
It means that my pussy feels good with your cock inside.
Sync your movement with mine and thrust it in more.
There...
That's great.
Stop this already.
Yes.
Suck, then lick.
Your tongue...
Oh yeah, try getting deep inside me and suck it.
Intensely draw your tongue in and out.
Good.
Keep that up.
There, that feels good, right?
Can't stop shaking your hips, eh?
Does it really feel good inside me?
Your cock's already twitching.
Don’t cum yet.
Take this, take this!
There!
Take this!
Man, this guy just came inside me.
No way.
This isn't real, right Kenji?
Hey woman, suck his semen out.
If you don't, I'll get pregnant with his child.
Drink it all up, and don’t leave a single drop of your boyfriend's semen.
Hey, the guy named Tamura.
You've been at it since earlier.
You really like this woman, huh?
I was cummed inside so
you can cum inside her too.
Stop, stop.
Stop, Tamura-kun.
I'm begging you.
Stop this.
No, no!
Oh no.
No way...
Don't...
Stop...
Don't!
No!
It's... It's bursting inside...
Semen's flowing inside me.
No...
I'm going to get pregnant.
I already told you to stop.
No...
No!
What, are you getting boned again after your girlfriend got cummed inside?
You really are a pervert!
Now that it's stiff again,
I'll let you insert that in me.
Make me feel really good, okay?
Wow, it's quite bigger than I thought.
My insides now feel really tight.
Here.
There now.
Here,
Here!
My pussy feels great, right?
Make me enjoy all of this.
Now, make me feel good with your tongue.
It's full of your girl's saliva so you should be happy.
Hey now, lick it already.
Use your tongue well.
There might still be drops of your semen left,
I want you to suck all of it.
Wow, Rina, your asshole's throbbing.
You're a real pervert and masochist.
Now I like you.
Your cock's huge, and you eat pussies well.
Just keep that up and make me cum.
Now that's a good thrusting.
You're really getting into it, eh?
That feels great.
Thrust it into me more.
That's right.
Yes.
That's good.
That feels good.
This guy's tongue is really great.
Oh crap, it feels really good!
Wow!
Yes!
This is great!
His cock is getting even stiffer.
Yes.
Oh no, this is really intense, Rina.
I think I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I wonder what happened to them.
I bet they're now all messed up beyond repair.
Guess you're right.
We've crushed yet another shop now.
Let's go.
Okay.
How about having a drink again somewhere else?
That's a good idea.
We're going all out now?
Of course!
www.SubDESU-H.net