SubDESU-H Presents
Honor and cash will be given to the winner.
And the loser will be devastated.
This is the rule of the underground fighting competition.
The dry mat is waiting for the winner and loser for today.
Kureha.
Her name is Shien.
She is the descendant of a ninja.
And she infiltrated a certain organization by the request from the police.
But her sister became the hostage of the organization.
So she also became a captive.
The condition made by the organization to release her and her sister is..
To enter the underground fighting competition administered by the organization.
And to win.
Just wait Kureha.
Your sis will win and save you immediately.
I got you!
I didn’t think that my special technique: elbow blow won’t work.
If big attacks won’t work then how about this!
My body is hot.
That part aches.
Finally it show its effect.
What?
What are you doing!?
You’re descendant of ninja and you didn’t touch the food last night.
But you haven’t managed to avoid the sleeping gas flowing all over the room.
What!? You say.
How long can the tough ninja can bear with the erotic feeling?
No kidding, I have no time to feel good right now.
Why , why that part getting so hot!?
What will happen if that part is touched when you’re in this state?
It’s wet!
It’s a very sensitive body
No it’s not.
How mortifying, but I feel it.
Wow I see.
Let me go!
Do you have any plans to reverse the situation?
Where are the gorgeous moves you’ve done a while ago?
My head dizzies as my weakest parts are touched.
And I can’t do anything!
Don’t get drunk with pleasure and try to resist.
The audience is expecting a strong woman to be raped.
Why I am being raped by a guy like him?
But my body won’t listen.
Why does it feel so good!?
You’re very weak when you’re touched in this part.
I’m not.
How mortifying, my body aches and that part is hot.
I can’t counter attack.
I can’t breathe.
It feels so good.
What’s this?
No I don’t want to die here.
I’m going to cum!
How dirty you are!
You cum once, and undressed, being tied.
But your heart is still not broken.
How is it? You can’t speak because you feel so good?
But I’m being to enjoy this pleasure.
I must save my sister.
I can’t collapse in a place like this.
I can’t resist because it feels so good.
Hey want to cum again?
My body feels on its on.
The serious part will be from here.
No.
That big thing won't enter.
That big one.
It entered me and it reached the cervix.
Amazing.
It's coming through!
It became bigger. No.
I-I’m cumming!
Sorry, your sis cummed.
Please forgive me.
How mortifying.
But it feels so good.
Kureha!
kureha!
Kureha, you’re fine!
Are you ok? You didn’t feel anything?
It felt so good sis right?
Kureha, what are you saying?
I’ve been taught many good things from them.
It felt so good.
What did they do to you, Kureha?
Kureha.
As I said sis.
Don’t oppose to the organization.
Kureha, don’t say such foolish things.
No... I just came and still my body is sensitive.
I didn’t think that i would feel it as I was kissed by my sister.
You’re cute when you are being raped in the ring sis.
Shows us the cute side of you more.
Us you said?
Touji-san!?
Touji-san, why are you here?
Touji-niichan continued the mission failed by Shien–neechan.
But he got deceived by me and became like this.
And came investigate the organization.
Touji-san.
Shien.
Touji-niichan, the one Shien-neechan inspired, looked after you where ever you went.
You’ll be raped by Touji-niichan next.
Watch him properly, isn’t he your inspiration?
It’s already like this from the tip.
Stop it.
Don’t worry.
We are the ones to deal with you.
Even though you said no, the bottom part of yours is honest.
How is it?
No.. in front of Touji-san.
Your nipples are so erecting in front of the man you like.
Next, lets show it to the man named Touji, the embarrassing appearance of you.
No.. stop.
No. .I don’t want to show him this appearance and that dirty part.
But I got more excited.
There is more flowing out.
You can release it oniichan.
Here I come.
Next, Release it inside that dirty hole.
No I don’t want it form the kind-hearted Touji-san.
Noooooo.
As I think of the big dick of Touji-san, It inspired long time stir inside me,
I wanted it to get it in deeper.
Lastly, I’ll release a lot of it in the bottom.
Touji-san.
I can’t  I can’t!
Sis is crafty.
I want to feel good too.
Oniichan please make Kureha feel good too.
Please lick it.
Good lick it more.
I can’t!
I can’t hold it any longer.
I’m going to cum!
Why...
Why does it...
Why does it feel so good?