Zoldo's mass sexual assault has begun!
I have to save everyone!
No!
Don't try to stop me!
It's impossible for you alone.
There's just too many of them!
You have no choice but to head for the moon.
You must defeat Zoldo!
But, I don't think I can reach the
moon with my current powers.
If I pour out all of my magic into you,
that would be enough to get you there.
Wouldn't doing something like
that mortally endanger you?
It's true that if I use up all my magic power,
there's a possibility of me dying.
But...
we need to save everyone,
and Emil.
Obi...
Don't hesitate now.
The fate of your family...
No,
the fate of the entire world,
is in your hands, Elena.
Elena...
That's why you must go now while you can.
Even if I disappear,
I don't want you to look back.
Elena,
I'm glad that I met you.
Obi...
Magicalgirl ERENA! 03
Lands on... Elena blasts out!
Dad...
Dad!
This place is...
Obi?
Obi!
Obi, you expended all of your magic, didn't you...?
I'm going now...
to the moon.
I can't let you do that... Onee-chan.
Emil!
What a nice pose there, onee-chan.
Emil, let me go!
Let's talk about this again!
Onee-chan, what are you talking about?
We're at war.
It's a battle of life or death between Zoldo and Humans.
You and I are now enemies.
But what hasn't changed, is the fact that we are sisters.
That's why...
I will share the humiliation, pain and misery,
that I suffered at the hands of Zoldo.
My butt hole!
It's suddenly being widened from the inside out!
No...!
My insides are getting twisted around.
It's really lively inside there, isn't it?
I'll stir it in more for you.
I'm going to break.
My stomach...!
Seems like onee-chan's raw flesh is enjoying this!
My intestines are going to burst out!
But,
I'm going to make you mine,
teasing you thoroughly.
I'm going to die...
Oh, so you want it there too?
I never thought that the day would come,
when I would see onee-chan like this.
It's like a dream.
That humiliated face...
is something that you'd only show to me.
I'm so horny...
The tentacles connected together!
What a sight!
Your inards don't even look human anymore.
Or maybe...
You want your pussy to be teased too?
Then I will make sure to pleasure your pussy intensely!
Do it!
Do you feel it?
You feel numb now,
and your womb is getting really filled up.
Now, it's time for onee-chan's
body to be totally twisted!
Don't worry.
This thing puts a plug in your wounds to prevent
blood as well as secretions from overflowing.
Sloppily, though.
No need to struggle against it.
Every touch from Zoldo bring nothing but pleasure.
Amazing, amazing!
You are taking all of it in.
It feels good right?
Feel it more.
Feel it more and more!
Lose yourself over it!
Onee-chan...
It's time now.
Do you feel it, onee-chan?
These tentacles are really excited, bulging.
Expanding your butt hole more.
You realize what's about to happen, right?
The tentacles are filled to the brim with semen
and that in turn is expanding your throat and guts.
These tentacles are about to squeeze
every last bit of cum inside you!
I love you onee-chan!
I love you very much!
You're my everything!
I was in love with you long before
I became a part of Zoldo.
That's why, I'm going to break you.
I will break you.
Forever, and ever, and ever...
Be at my side!
I'm the only one who can break onee-chan.
I'm the only one,
who can violate onee-chan.
I...
won't lose!
Emil!
Onee-chan...!
Even Emil too...
Emil...
Stop this already!
I can't...
I can't afford to lose!
I can't, I can't, I can't!
I also won't lose!
In order to save you from Zoldo...
Nothing but lies. You just want
to feel better about yourself,
by looking down and feeling pity on me!
No!
I'm doing this for your sake!
You only care for me,
so that you can distract yourself
from your own loneliness.
That's terrible!
You're the one who's terrible onee-chan!
Because you're like that,
because you're that kind...
That's why I can never get separated from you!
My insides, my insides are...!
I'll never,
I'll never let you reach the moon!
What are you protecting on the moon?!
Shut up.
Shut up, shut up!
You're simply mine!
There's no need for you to meet that person!
Emil, who is that...
Shut up!
I won't lose!
So this is your strength?!
Emil, open your eyes!
The Emil that I know isn't that stubborn!
You don't know anything.
Not even,
not even a single bit of my feelings...
I understand all of it!
All your feelings.
Because,
we've been together all our lives.
Your feelings are reaching me!
Even now,
I love you very much!
Nothing's going to change that!
Onee-chan...
It's overflowing and it won't stop...!
Stop it onee-chan!
Stop it!
Both our magic powers are getting out of control!
I can't!
It won't stop!
I'm going to die!
– I'm dying!
– My insides,
are getting wildly stirred by the tentacles going wild,
– and they won't stop!
– I'm cumming.
It won't stop.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
I feel it.
I feel you in me!
Are you going to cum?
You're also going to cum.
Let's cum together!
Emil,
if this continues we're both going to die...!
I'm cumming!
No!
Onee-chan!
Cumming!
Emil,
you drew Zoldo out at the last moment, didn't you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
And I even promised to protect you...
Don't apologize.
There is no need for the both of us to die.
As long as you are safe, I am happy.
I don't care for the consequences anymore.
Emil...
Onee-chan...
Emil, get a hold of yourself!
I love you.
Onee-chan...
Emil. Emil!
I'm going now.
Mom...
Obi...
Emil...
and for the sake of everyone on Earth!
It's Dad's shuttle!
What in...?
Why is mom...?
Onee-chan.
I warned you not to go to the moon, didn't I?
We are finally together, all of us.
We can live together once again.
Could this be,
Zoldo's den?
No, onee-chan.
Look more closely, Elena.
No way, Dad is...
It's not a lie.
I promised you all.
That we would surely meet again.
I've been waiting for this day...
Elena!
No!
Let me go!
This position...
Dad!
You mustn't let your mind get corrupted like this!
Elena...
You have been raised well.
Your pussy has matured beautifully,
and your breasts incredibly large.
I'm happy.
Dad, get back to your senses!
Dad would never do something like this!
You must fight Zoldo's grasp!
Dad's finger is...!
No!
I don't want to feel aroused from Dad's touch!
Don't...!
No need to be ashamed, onee-chan.
It's Zoldo who's playing with you.
So getting horny is completely understandable.
It feels good...!
So it feels good, huh?
Then allow me to take this up a notch.
No way...
It's thick!
This is...!
Why are you doing this...?
It's to check how much you have grown up.
To see if you are capable of hosting
Zoldo's essence or not.
Zoldo's essence?
Zoldo becomes stronger by being reborn
from someone who is blood-related.
In order for Dad to have children,
he needs either my or your womb for it.
And yours Elena, is the most suitably developed.
That's why I didn't want you to come to the moon.
Because my precious onee-chan
will be taken by Dad.
I will make you bear Zoldo!
Don't twist around inside of me.
Just watching Elena makes me want it too.
I want some...
I also it!
Mom!
Emil!
Then I'll give it to you both as well.
No...!
It's in me!
This feeling is great!
It's forcing into my womb...
It's going to melt and fuse with your cock!
It's hot...
I'll melt!
I want this...
I don't care about anything anymore.
We're all together as a family!
My butthole feels the best!
I want that sensation of semen
bursting and leaking out of it!
More,
I want it more, more, more!
Love me more!
Our familial holes are getting violated by Dad!
Now I can feel it too...
How onee-chan feels.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
No!
We must climax together as a family!
Let's all cum together.
Give it to me, please!
Give me all that semen pumping
in inside those tentacles!
Pour it all inside of me!
Cock!
Cock!!
Cock!!!
Something is coming.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming hard!
Give it to my pussy!
I'm cumming.
We're cumming!
Elena.
Elena!
Obi?
So this means, that I died?
This is the realm of your heart.
It seems that a little of my magic power is still in you.
Then, I'm still alive, aren't I?
Can I ask you one thing, Elena?
What?
What will you choose?
Your family or the Earth?
I...
This light is...
Onee-chan...?
What is this light?!
Blessed by the divine mother of the Universe.
Magical Girl Elena!
Now lifting off with the Rune Empress!
What is this light?
This bright and warm light...!
Stop!
My body!
You two...
What are you doing?
Emil?
Mom!
You regained your senses, right?
Yes, thanks to that light you radiated.
Listen carefully, Elena!
You have to defeat Zoldo right now!
But if I fired right now, then Mom and Emil will also...
Elena!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and do it!
But...!
Hurry onee-chan!
I can't shoot.
Why do I have to shoot?
Elena...
You really have grown into suth a kind girl.
Don't worry about us.
We have no regrets.
I already told you how much I love you.
I met my daughters, who I never
thought I would meet again.
So do it, okay?
Shoot now Elena!
Shoot it!
Rune Empress of Serenity!
Mom...
Emil...
Dad...
Thank you, Elena.
I'm glad.
I'm home, Elena.
Everyone, it's time to eat.
Dad, welcome home.
Emil, you're still half asleep.
Oh yeah.
We have a special present for you two.
It's something you've been wanting for a while.
This one is now part of the family too!
Huh?
That's an interestingly peculiar
necklace he is wearing, isn't it?