Ah, no.
Why are you saying “No”?
No, don’t touch me anymore.
Why are that bastard and my sister having…
N-No.
I’m gonna go crazy.
“Yumi Takanashi. She’ll get horny in the school gymnasium and then she’ll be molested.”
How come my body feels strange?
SubDESU-H
Presents
“Corrupt Family, Promiscuity Begins!”
Yumi-chan, are you okay?
Sensei, why are you doing this to me?
Of course, It’s because it feels good.
Yumi-chan’s body is so sensitive and it’s fun to play with you.
Don’t say such a thing.
Don’t put your fingers that deep inside.
No…
No, please stop it!
Yumi-chan, It’s not nice to tell a lie.
I see your hard erect nipples.
That’s not true.
Sensei, stop it!
You don't mean that, do you?
N-No.
Don’t touch my tits.
We’re not supposed to do this and we’re doing it in such a place as this.
That feels good.
What are you doing?
Sensei, no!
Don’t say “No”.
No...
Yumi-chan’s pussy is all wet.
It’s a lie. Don’t put your fingers in there.
No, I’m gonna feel good if you finger me so hard.
No...
Please don’t touch my pussy like that.
I’m aroused at school even when someone may come here.
My pussy feels so good!
Oh yes, my pussy feels good!
My clit feels so good that I'm going to cum soon.
I’m gonna cum!
Yumi-chan, what do you want me to do next?
I want S-Sensei’s…
You want my…?
I want your dick.
Where do you want my dick?
I want your dick in my pussy.
It’s in me. Sensei's dick is in me.
It's amazing! Sensei's dick is so amazing!
Your dick feels good in my pussy.
So good…
Give me more and more.
Sensei, I can't take it anymore.
Shoot your cum inside me!
I’m cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming!
Cumming!
W-Why is my sister having sex with such a bastard?
Huh?
Shit.
“Shiori Takanashi. She will sneak into Yumi’s school and she will be molested with her sister.”
My body feels weird.
Very hot.
It feels hot down there and it feels like I’m gonna cum any second.
I need to go back there. I gotta go back.
Sis.
It's about time you came.
Well, let’s get started.
W-What?
What the hell am I doing here?
What is it? How come my body won’t move?
Yumi-chan, restrain her hands.
What are you saying?
Ah, sis!
What’re you doing? Knock it off!
No.
You pervert, I won’t forgive you.
I don’t care. I’ll give you a lot of pleasure.
Hey, don’t move.
No.
Your pussy is all wet. How can you say no?
You two play like lesbians.
What?
What you are talking about?
Shiori.
Stop, sis.
Why do you listen to him?
Shiori, please obey him.
Sis.
Amazing.
Why does it feel so good?
Yes, yes, it feels good.
My “down there” feels a tingling sensation.
Good, yes, it's amazingly good.
I can’t hold it any longer.
I’m cumming too!
Don’t just give pleasure to each other. Give me some, too.
D-Don’t put your dick close to me.
Sensei. Shiori.
I want Yumi to do it, too.
No, sis. Why can’t I stop it?
I don’t want it, but…
No.
You're not good at all.
You gotta gain a lot of experience.
I’m burning up.
What’s wrong with me?
Don’t stop it.
You're no good, Shiori.
Hey Yumi, show her how to do it.
She's got to do this because you weren't good enough, Shiori.
Sis, I’m sorry.
As I expected, Yumi is better than you.
Shiori, look carefully.
Please, it’s my fault. Please forgive her.
Now, you’re talking.
Are you okay, sis?
The best is yet to come.
What?
N-No, I don’t like this pose. Please forgive me.
How can you say that?
I’m about to give you both pleasure.
Your pussies are so wet.
You're not satisfied yet, right?
No, that’s just not true.
Alright, I’ll take real good care of you two now.
It’s hot. Your hot dick is penetrating me.
No, don’t move.
Why, why does my down there feel good?
Our tits are rubbing together.
Don’t look at me, sis.
I don’t want you to look at me.
If only Shiori gets pleasure, I feel sorry for Yumi.
Yes, your dick is so good.
I can feel your dick reaching all the way into my pussy.
It feels good.
I'm about to cum!
I’m almost cumming.
Which pussy should I give my cum?
I-Inside of me!
Sensei, Sensei please.
Please give me your sperm.
Please fill my pussy with it.
Please. Give me your hot stuff!
I-I want it, too.
I see. Both of you want it.
That’s right. Treating you differently is not nice.
Here it comes.
Your hot man juice is coming out of your dick.
Yes!  I’m cumming, cumming. My pussy feels good!
Darling, I’m a little embarrassed because it’s been a while.
Misako, that is some very naughty lingerie you're wearing.
“Misako Takanashi. She will believe her daughter’s tutor to be her husband and have sex with him in the bedroom. And then…”
Because .. It’s been a while since I last spent time with you.
Misako, I’m happy.
Darling.
Misako, please me now.
Yes, darling.
Misako, it’s good. You’re good at this.
I’m glad you like it.
Right there. Very good.
Misako, use your tits.
Yes, darling.
Misako, I’m cumming.
Misako, open your mouth.
Swallow everything.
I've been lonely for so long.
This is the first time in a while and I can’t wait any longer.
Misako, your pussy is burning.
Now, you may put my dick in you.
Yes, darling.
I can feel your hard, hot cock coming into my pussy.
I feel good.
I can’t get enough of it.
I’m happy because my pussy is filled with your great cock.
Misako, you’re good.
Darling, did you say my pussy is good?
That’s nice to hear.
I jacked off a lot earlier, but I can still get hard.
Oh yeah, give it to me a lot.
Cumming, cumming, cumming…
Cumming, I’m cumming…
I'm about to cum.
My pussy feels so good.
I want you to fill my pussy with your sperm.
Misako, tell me who is the man in front of you.
Huh? You are not my husband.
Why? What’s going on?
You moaned many times, swallowed my sperm and had cream pie sex. How do you like it?
Oh, no.
Don’t you feel good?  Go ahead and cum, you sow!
No, that’s not right.
What is not right?
Aren’t you happy that you were trapped and your pussy got creamed?
Don’t say that.
Then tell me what you wanted me to do. Tell me!
I can’t. Why is this happening to me?
Tell me. Say it!
It hurts.
Say it.
Please fill my pussy with your sperm.
Alright. I’ll give you a plenty of it.
Darling…
It’s hot. You’re ejaculating inside of me.
I’m cumming.
I’m so happy my pussy is filled with sperm.
I’m sorry, darling.
Ha ha ha, you can do it without foreplay.
Do you want to do it here?
Yeah, that’s right.
You are that Yumi-chan? Seriously?
What?
Are you sure we can fuck her?
W-What’s going on?
Never mind.
It’s okay to fuck her ‘cause she’s a huge pervert.
W-What are you saying?
Well then.
We’ll do it without hesitation.
“Yumi Takanashi. She will be treated like a whore by two guys in a park toilet at night.”
To think I get to have sex with such a cute girl.
I can’t believe she has a gentle face but still loves this kind of stuff.
Ah, it’s coming out.
I’m cumming, cumming!
My pussy feels good.
You perverted girl, does your pussy feel that good?
Yes, my pussy does feel so good.
Fuck my perverted pussy harder and harder.
Are you happy to be sandwiched between us and fucked?
I can feel your hard dicks moving inside of me. I’m gonna go crazy.
Yes, I’m cumming.
It’s very tight. This girl is really good.
I’m cumming again.
Your dicks are good. I’m not satisfied yet.
Give it to me more! Fuck me!
You’re not satisfied yet? Then I’ll give it to you more!
My stomach is gonna start hurting.
Great! I feel in heaven.
My dick is still hard even though I've ejaculated a lot.
Her pussy is great and it’s still so tight.
Your dicks are rubbing against the insides of my pussy and ass. It feels great!
I’m gonna cum, again.
Give it to me. I want your cum in both my pussy and my ass again!
Okay.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming, cumming!
My pussy's about to cum!
Let’s cum together.
I’m cumming.
I feel your hot stuff coming out inside of me.
Why? Why have I done such a thing?
I’m going to get tired of this soon...
Why? There is something wrong with my body.
It's so good. I can’t stop my hands.
Why am I masturbating here?
Why? I shouldn't do it.
I’m so horny. I’m masturbating at school to feel good.
I’m cumming, cumming, cumming!
Oh yeah, I’m cumming.
“Shiori Takanashi. She will get horny at the rooftop of the school and begin to masturbate. Two school boys will see her masturbating and fuck her.”
Thank you for letting us watch something good.
Takanashi, I didn’t know how frustrated you were!
No.
Don’t run away. I don’t think that only masturbation could have satisfied you.
No, stop it!
Let me go! No!
Amazing...You are this wet at school.
No, no, cut it out.
I didn’t know you were such a pervert.
Stop it.
Wait, don’t. I can’t take this.
Don't move around.
Takanashi’s pussy is very nice.
Her ass is tight and good.
No, my pussy and ass are being used by these guys.
Stop it. Don’t do me that violently.
I can’t. I can’t take it anymore.
Me, too.
I-I’m cumming.
D-Don’t ejaculate inside of my pussy and ass.
I feel hot. My stomach feels wrong.
My pussy is so sticky with cum.
I really hate you guys.
No, what’s happening to my body?
Misako-san.
Huh? Don’t get close to me.
I thought you wanted me to come here for something.
Me? It can’t be.
Are you sure?
I…
Misako-san, is there something you want me to do for you?
No, there isn’t.
Alright then, I’m going home.
W-Wait! My…
My body is hungry for sex. Please fuck me.
Well, shall we all do it together?
“Misako Takanashi. She will get horny while cooking. Everybody will get together and have sex.”
It’s not fair that only mom gets some.
Master, please give me your dick now.
I can’t take it anymore.
My pussy wants your dick so bad.
You are hopeless daughters.
Don’t make life difficult for our master.
But...
Misako’s right.
Be good girls and wait.
Master…
Thank you for your cum.
It's good, your dick is so good!
Master…
I...Can't wait anymore!
Yumi, now is Shiori’s turn.
Just wait.
I'm cumming, master, I’m cumming.
Please fill my uterus with your cum.
Oh yeah, I’m cumming. Yes, I’m cumming.
I’m cumming. My pussy feels good.
Alright, everybody, cum now!
Yes, master, Yumi’s pussy is having an orgasm.
I’m cumming, too.
Darling, I’m sorry.
Dad, how are you doing?
We're fucking our master.
We’re so happy that we received plenty of his cum.
We’ll conceive healthy babies.
Dad, don’t worry about us.
Because we're really happy.
See you soon, dad.