An accident on the first day of a field trip?
Where did everyone else go?
What on Earth happened?
SubDESU-H
Kansen2
Inzai
Toshi
Did everyone else die?
It's that maid cafe I went to with Hiroshi and the others!
Hiroshi...
No reception, though...
Stop it, scumbags!
Stop, stop it already!
Senpai's high class pussy feels so good!
C'mon, try harder!
I-I'm about to cum again!
You just came, you sure are a quick shot!
Yes!
It's fine. If you can't hold it in,
just cum all you want inside of me!
Mizaho-san! What are you saying?!
You sure are feisty!
I like strong-minded girls.
Let me go, scum!
Whoa! Your pussy just squeezed me!
You should enjoy it too, Chihiro-oneesama!
You're feeling good from an unfamiliar cock being pushed inside you, no?
Let's all have fun!
That's right, Chihiro-oneesama!
Not Satsue-san too!
It looks like this is the end.
W-Wata-kun! Yamamoto-kun! Yokoyama-kun! What are you doing?!
Who is that?
I've never seen such a cute girl...
Oh, hey Alice! You wanna do it too?
No!
Don't!
Alice-san! Let's run!
This should be far enough...
Thank you!
Um, is it alright to leave those people behind?
They can't be helped now.
Huh?
They've already been defiled...
But you haven't yet...
What's up?
No, it's nothing.
Alice-san, are you going to find your friend you were talking about earlier?
Yes, but where should I start...
Those twin towers over there are an emergency shelter.
Your friend might be there too.
Let's go together.
Really? Thanks, Nagasaki-san!
I knew it, this girl sure is cute...
Your pussy tastes great...
More-!
Nagasaki-san, these people...
They're probably all under the influence of a drug...
Let's enter from the back so we won't be noticed.
Be careful!
Those guys we saw earlier might be in here.
Yeah...
Hiroshi!
Hello? Is it really you?
Thank goodness you're safe!
I'm glad, where are you now?
I'm on the third floor of a place called Ground City.
Yuu is here too.
What about you?
Is Yuuki there too? That's great!
I'm on the first floor of Ground City!
Oh, so you are here.
You should come up too!
We've got some snacks,
and we can wait for the rescue team here in peace.
Okay! I'll be on my way!
Lets go, Nagasaki-san!
S-Sure...
Nagasaki-san! Hurry up!
Alice-san, why are you so happy to meet these guys?
Hayami...
Hurry up...
We'll be waiting, Alice...
Let me introduce you.
This is Oukura Hiroshi-kun and Kobayashi Yuuki-kun from my class.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
And this is...
Nagasaki Chihiro, 3rd year, Seiha Academy.
Oh? You're from that high-class academy?
Aren't you hungry? Let's eat!
Thanks.
We've already had ours, so go ahead.
We don't mind if you have it all.
Geez! There's no way we can eat that much!
Now that I'm full, I'm getting sleepy...
So am I.
Go sleep in one of the beds.
Yeah... We'll do that.
Hey! What's this?!
What are you trying to do?!
Let's have lots of fun, Hayami...
Just like those people over there.
What?
Satsue-san?!
Mizaho-san?!
C'mon, Hayami...
W-Wait! Hiro-!
Oukura-kun! Stop it at once!
Nagasaki-san, you shouldn't interfere.
What?
H-Hey!
Kobayashi-kun, let me go!
No-!
Amazing...
I-It hurts! Don't rub them so roughly!
Then, how about I suck on them?
No, don't!
I'll start to feel good!
I'll make you feel better, Hayami.
No, no!
Don't look! Don't look!
You're already soaking wet, Hayami.
Your juices keep flooding out.
It's because...
your tongue feels too good!
I'll have you make me feel good too!
That's great, Hayami...
Hiroshi-! No more...
I don't want this!
I'm going to cum, so swallow it!
Oh c'mon, I said to swallow it!
I-It's bitter...
Now then, how about we get to the main act?
N-No...
No! No~!
Wait, Hiroshi! Please!
I can't wait.
No, not like this, not like this! No, don't! Stop it!
You're squeezing me! Is this your first time?
It is! It's my first...
This is... horrible!
Yay! I took Hayami's virginity!
Hey Yuu. How are you doing?
How is it, Nagasaki-san?
Does it feel good?
How can I feel good with a guy sucking on me?
However...
Looks like you're getting turned on.
N-No! That's...!
Please look at me, Alice-san. I'm this wet...
I'll make you even more wet.
No!
Not there!
Would you rather I lick your clitoris?
Hey, I can't hold back, so I'm putting it in.
What-?
No! I don't want to feel good from a guy's filthy cock!
No-!
Hiroshi! Please stop it already!
Alice-san...
So cute...
Hey, can you untie my hands?
I'll be on top now.
Sure thing.
This suits you.
No way...
Your cock is quivering already...
I-If you do that, I'll cum too quickly!
That's good, let it out.
I-I'm cumming!
Hmph! Once a guy cums, they've had it.
It's not stopping...
Alice-san! We're getting out of here!
Okay!
Why did Hiroshi and Yuuki do such...?
Don't cry, I'll protect you...
I keep getting saved by you, Nagasaki-san...
Need to pee?
Yeah...
Then go for it.
But... you're in here...
Yes, I'll watch you from here.
B-But...
If you don't hurry, those freaks might find us.
But...
C'mon...
I-It's coming out!
Let it out already.
No~!
Don't look...
Don't look!
The government has started an investigation into the disaster
and is currently doing all they can to find any valuable information.
Any news shall be reported as soon as possible.
I repeat.
About nine hours ago, on the sixth of August at 8:15 PM,
an unknown explosion destroyed much of Sendai City.
Maybe it was because of the explosion that the bus...
Also, from 10 PM and onward,
a new virus has been rapidly spreading in the areas of Sendai City, Suzuka, and Sakatashi.
Sakata too?
The connection between the explosion and the spread of the virus is yet unclear.
An explosion and a new virus?
What a horrible combination.
The Ministry of Health and Welfare has tentatively named
this new widespread virus Unknown Level 4.
Unknown Level 4...
The specified symptoms of this virus are:
loss of ethics, extreme euphoria, an increase in sexual desire, mood swings,
blurred memory, loss of physical strength, and a speech impediment,
making the virus infectious and very deadly.
Then Hiroshi and Yuuki were...
The means of infection currently identified are:
Sexual transmission, oral transmission and blood transmission.
The time needed for the virus to take effect form infection is still unclear...
Huh? What the-?!
N-No! Stop!
I-Is this Unknown Level 4?!
Hiroshi and Yuuki have gone...
I bet they're elsewhere having sex with other girls.
No!
You liked Oukura-kun, didn't you?
I'll make you forget him.
Nagasaki-san?
What large breasts...
It's... embarrassing...
They're cute.
It's warm inside you, Alice-san...
N-Nagasaki-san! I just went for a pee before!
Then I'll clean you up.
Alice-san, your juices are tasty...
It feels so good!
Let's feel much better.
I-I'm scared...
Don't worry, I'm with you.
okay, we're ready to go.
Nagasaki-san, you look great...
I'm putting it in, okay?
Y-Yeah...
It's thick!
It's in, now I'm going to turn it on.
This is... amazing!
I-I can't stop moving my hips!
Alice-san, you're drooling! What a lewd girl...
It's because-!
I'm losing my mind!
It's hard to believe you were a virgin until just before...
It's so deep!
Doesn't this feel better than a man?
Girl on girl feels much better!
Nagasaki-san! I'm gonna...
You're going to cum? You're gonna cum, right?
No! Don't stop!
You're not allowed to cum yet.
I'll lose it if I don't finish!
Describe to me what you want me to do.
P-Please make me cum...
Say it properly.
Make me cum from your electric...
What is it? I can't hear you.
You can't say it?
Then how about we call it quits?
N-No!
Make me cum from your electric two-ended strap-on!
Very good.
This is your reward...
Open your legs. You want it, right?
More.
I-I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
No-!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
So cute.
Hiroshi...
I'm so happy, now we're one...
She still likes guys more?
Satsue-san and Mizuho-san have already become addicted to cocks, huh?
Over here! Hiroshi!
Alice-san?!
Hey, Hayami!
Let's continue where we left off!
Sure!
Alice-san...
Everyone...
You've left me behind, haven't you?
Don't tell me...
Even though I'm infected with this virus...
How can I want a man's cock this much?
Why would I want to give myself to such a filthy thing?
It's impossible!
If that's gonna happen, I'd rather...!
Oh! It's Nagasaki-san!
Let's all feel good together!
Nagasaki-san!
Come quickly!