Even a simple act like sitting in front of the PC...
is enough...
to push my pussy over the edge.
And it itches uncontrollably for pleasure.
Hey there! You came again, Ryou-kun.
I'm glad.
Well, I just somehow...
I'm glad whatever the reason may be.
Hey, while talking to you,
I became horny.
I'll start immediately now, okay?
This is something that I've been hooked into lately.
It's called Internet sex.
Mutual Love by the Window
~ Pure Love Mellow ~
It's getting wet.
It's not an act,
I really am getting aroused.
Hey, Ryou-kun,
can you see my pussy?
I can see it.
I can see Miku-san's pussy.
Hey, can you tell me how my pussy looks like?
Tell me quickly...!
It's wet...
Very wet.
I see.
When I think of you,
my womb constricts and it get all wet.
That's right, this isn't an act.
Hey, take off your pants and show me your cock already.
It's embarrassing to be the only one doing it by myself.
Hurry up!
Hey, Ryou-kun.
Yes?
My boobs have gotten bigger again, you know.
Is that so?
It's all your fault,
because we're doing this together everyday.
I'll have you take responsibility for this tonight.
It's gotten hot recently and I end up with
a lot of sweat below my boobs you see.
My nipples have somehow...
Hey, can you see my nipples getting stiff?
Yeah, I see it.
Hey, suck it, please suck them...
Yes, more...
Suck them harder!
Ryou-kun, stop!
Don't be in such a hurry!
Look, my breasts are so soft you know.
Do it gently, gently, okay?
Ryou-kun, don't push so hard into me
while you take me from behind!
Hey, show more... of your pussy...
Ryou-kun, can you see it?
Can you see my pussy?
Ryou-kun, look.
Me too...
I'm starting to feel good too.
Look...
Look here...
My clitoris is also getting big.
It feels like bursting out.
I'm already...!
I'm also about to...
Please, lets do this together!
Please!
I'm going to...!
No, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming...
Thank you.
It felt really great today, wouldn't you say?
I-Indeed, I agree.
That's great.
Let's do it again, okay?
Yeah.
I am careful never to expose my face,
so he probably doesn't know who I am.
Well then, goodnight.
Okay, goodnight.
But I know who he is.
I'll be going!
Hey there!
Good morning.
He's Aida Ryou, my childhood friend. Also the same
person who was masturbating with me last night.
Well, he's supposed to be, but...
I am not really sure if he is a thick
head or something else...
What's wrong?
He can't even recognize the person he was
busy masturbating with the other night,
even if she was standing right in front of him.
In fact, this guy has been masturbating every night
with a woman he doesn't even know or recognize.
W-What's with you?
Nothing.
Seriously! What's with you?
From this, we can evaluate the direction of the electric current by...
Oh, he has P.E. today.
Recently, I always feel irritated whenever I see Ryou.
Ryou and I go way back,
and since we were very close neighbors.
We often used to play together.
That continued until middle school,
where we suddenly found ourselves
estranged with each other.
It was by chance when I found Ryou on the Internet.
Nkype Name:   Aida Ryou
Location:     Tokyo, Japan
Language:        Japanese
I found his name on the chat website
that I frequently used to visit.
Initially I thought it was just someone
with the same name,
but he had actually used his real photo
on the profile like an honest idiot.
I found it strange that he didn't recognize
me during our first meeting
white I was pretending to by a different person,
so I decided to tease him a little.
By the way,
do you know anything about, Internet sex?
Eh? Yeah.
I planned on stopping it immediately at first,
but I got engrossed at the idea
of seeing Ryou's other side.
And at the thought of possibly getting caught.
The situation slowly escalated out of hand and...
Before I knew,
I was already having Internet sex every night.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm also about to cum!
What have I been doing?
And why do it with someone like Ryou?
He's not really that special to me...
He doesn't even know how I feel...
What the heck is going on with me?!
Why do I get so irritated at the thought of Ryou?
Ah, just stop thinking about it!
I'm just doing it because it feels good!
I'm home.
I bought it!
It's way too skimpy!
The slit is also very lewd!
He said he liked dresses like these, didn't he?!
Oh no, oh no.
I'm about to think of something weird again.
That was close.
He's here.
I wonder how he's going to react...
Hello!
Good evening!
What's with that outfit?
I purchased it on the fly!
Well, does it suit me?
Yeah, it suits you very well.
I see.
I knew Ryou-kun would say something like that.
Thanks!
Well then, let's get started...
Umm, for today...
What is it?
To tell you the truth, a childhood female
friend of mine lives nearby.
Oh...
She seems to be acting quite cold recently.
To put it directly, she's somehow avoiding me.
I see...
Yeah, it wasn't like that until recently...
And so,
about girls, you see...
A-About...
About that girl...
Do you like her?
What am I saying?
I don't really have any feelings for him...!
Yeah, I think so.
I probably like her.
I've never been conscious about it till now,
because we were childhood friends, but...
I don't have,
any feelings, for him...
Hey, open your window for a bit.
Open it.
Why?
Just do it!
The moon is beautiful.
But even if I open it, I won't see the moon...
It's already opened.
Asuka?!
Why?
Can I...
Can I come over there?
O-Okay.
Ryou, you said earlier that you liked me, right?
Me too...
I think I like you too.
Because, whenever I think of you...
mine gets wet like this.
Hey...
let's lick each other together.
Asuka...!
You are way too intense!
Ryou's cock, which I was only able
to see behind a screen before...
Your penis is so stiff.
It's stiff, hot and twitchy.
Wait...
Wait a sec...
I'm going to quickly cum if it continues like this...
I want to lick it more!
Ryou's tongue is entering me.
No... don't...
That feels good...
It feels good to have my pussy licked by Ryou!
Drive it in more!
No, Asuka...
I'm about to cum!
I want it.
I want Ryou's semen.
Not just in front of the monitor,
but right into my mouth!
So this is Ryou's real semen.
There's lots of it...
It's hot...
and bitter.
Wow!
Ryou's cock is still this stiff...
Can I put it in?
It's okay to put it in, right?
It's alright to drive it in my pussy, right?
I want to put it in.
I want to put Ryou's cock in!
It's in!
Wow, my hips won't stop!
Sex feels great!
Hey, Asuka...
That's fast...
That's too fast!
Like this, I'm going to...!
But it just feels so good!
It feels so good that it cannot even compare to masturbating!
My hips are moving on their own...
I can't stop it!
Asuka.
Ryou...
This is amazing...
I can clearly see Ryou entering me!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Don't...
Don't suck on my nipple now!
I just came, so it's very sensitive.
No...!
I'm still in the middle of my orgasm...
Oh no, I'm going to cum again!
No, I can't stop...
I can't stop my orgasm...!
I'm also about to cum...
Asuka's wrapping me...
I'm cumming!
Wow,
I can't stand up...
I never thought that real sex could feel this good.
It's overflowing...
This is Ryou's.
It's still stiff...
Hey, Ryou...
Here.
Put it in here too...
There...?
Yep.
In my butthole.
But...
You said before during out chat that
you wanted to try anal, right?
Besides, I want you to violate every part of me.
I want you to insert your cock in my butthole...
Wow, he's getting really aroused...
You're absolutely sure, right?
I'm really going to put it in.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's not as painful as I thought, so...
I see.
Hey, go ahead and... okay?
Asuka's butthole,
is really tight...
It feels really good!
Me too,
my butt also feels good!
Your thick cock stirs my butt up whenever it strokes in and out.
I like you.
I love you!
I love having sex with you!
Amazing.
This is amazing!
My butt feels like its burning...
Asuka.
Asuka...
Asuka!
It's deep. It's deep!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming again!
And it's my first time...
My first time doing anal,
and I'm cumming...
I'm also, about to...
Give it to me!
Pour your semen in my butthole!
I'm going to cum,
I'm going to cum with you!
I'm releasing it, Asuka!
I'm cumming,
I'm also cumming!
Wow...
Lots of Ryou's...
Asuka...
What's wrong?
Just hold on here.
Wait.
If you were my chat partner...
then that means I actually told you those kind of things!
I know a lot of embarrassing things about you.
Since that day Ryou and I are
still doing video chats, but...
Okay.
Oh, so Ryou's already logged in.
I'm home.
Ah, welcome home.
Surfing the net right after coming home...
Don't you have anything better to do?
Speak for yourself.
You're right I guess.
Whenever I sit down in front of the computer,
my pussy starts craving for Ryou,
and it starts to throb...
Hey.
Hmm?
Can I come over there again today?
Yeah.
Now it has become the signal for sex.