Amano-san!!!!
Aoi!!!
This is...
Amano-san, Amano-san, are you there?
Please answer me!
Ugh... she's not here...
I feel bad...
I can't stay here...
Translated by SubDesu-H
Medical Treatment full of shame
As I remember... This is director's room...
Substitution of Midori
Again...
It's not Mom
Substitution of Midori
Why are you punishing me?
Do you know why you are going to be punished?
I don't know.
It's because you broke the promise with Hinoki, your Mom.
You promised that you'd be with me forever.
Yes... but...
Ogishi's son... Ah, yes, he's Takumi-kun right?
So you finally understand that that's the reason why you broke the promise?
Ouch!
Say what we promised.
I need to let her understand that I'm not doing this because of anger or hatred.
Ouch!
Say it, Midori.
What's that clothing?
The black clothing of promise for Kai-sama's funeral.
Do you want to stay as a bad girl Midori?
Are you not caring for me and Hinoki?
I'm sorry, I'll be friendly...
I'll be friendly.
Takumi... With Takumi-kun too?
With Takumi-kun.
I'll be friendly with Takumi-kun too.
I'll play with him.
Yes, good, good.
You have me Midori.
This is the last thing left by Hinoki.
This is Hinoki's other self she left for me.
You look just like your mother.
Say "Please punish me"
Eh? Why?
I can't say that...
Hinoki... Midori's mom was able to say that properly.
So you'll say it too Midori.
My mom said it...?
Why is Midori scared with the act which Hinoki loves?
Why is she confused with what Hinoki desired?
You're being punished right now.
So say it, "please punish me"
Please... please...
Please... punish me...
Say "I beg you" Midori.
I... I...
You're a good girl.
You're a good girl Midori.
Midori is a good girl.
What's the matter Midori?
There's still one more left.
The most important promise.
I'm... I'm... the same...
I will be Mom's replacement.
Yes... Midori... you're a good girl.
You're a good girl Midori,
You're great Midori.
No... No!!!!
No no!!
You can't Hinoki!
I didn't think that I could taste your body again.
No... No...
I'm not... I'm not my mom...
It's Hinoki's taste..
It's Hinoki's juice..
More... More... release it more.
NO... NO!!!
I don't want to, I don't want to!!!
Hinoki!
I can't be my mom.
Midori... I... I...
I'm not my mom...
Midori.. What's the matter Midori...?
I'm not my mom!!!!
Midori!!!!
Broken Girl
Where am I?
Is this Kurumi's bed?
Are you Kurumi's doctor?
Is this Kurumi's hospital?
Oh my, this is terrible
The Endocrine System, Nervous System, the Cardiovascular System
All these parts are messed up because of the medicine.
The sexual organs are also messed up.
I don't know how's she been used.
I understand why Aoi-san pitied her.
Pity, self-projection, and guilt.
Kurumi is a broken girl so.
I can only be a broken doll.
Even if you collect the parts of the doll.
You can't make me a perfect girl.
Ahahahah
Pussy being left wide-opened
Forgive me
I can't feel my strength...
Why...
Why am I in this pose?
Where is my bed...?
It seems she has woken up
She's saying something in front of me.
This girl... Oh, it's Midori.
Midori??
Good Morning.
The medicine is taking effect perfectly.
Director, are you really...
Yes... I will Midori-san.
Oh? Hey it's the Director.
Oh? It seems she's in a good mood.
With this, I think things will go smoothly without making her cry like last time.
Ok then, let's start the diagnosis Aoi-san.
No, I don't want to be hurt.
Aoi-san, please excuse me.
What..? What...?
No!...
No...
I don't want this...
Ya.. Yanagi-sensei...
The preparations are ready.
Come.
Close the door...
And lock it.
Sterilize your hands with the alcohol over there.
Uhm.... what are we going to do?
What's this medicine for after all?
It's for a slight examination.
Let's test if your illusions are from your memories or not.
What's that medicine right now?
We need time to let the medicine take its effect.
So tell me about the memories, about the persons.
The memories?
Then, what will happen if we can't copy the files to the hard drive?
Even though there are many files written, all will gone if you shut it down.
We can't recover it.
Then the injection a while ago was...
Yes, if we make it simple,
but complete.
Inspecting it's effect from the injection a few hours later.
It will temporarily cause some memory loss.
Memory is like...
Register, Preservation, Remind.
Learn, keep in mind, remember.
It will be divided into three functions.
I'll use a computer as an example for you to understand.
Register, is the input of the data.
Preservation, is storing of the data.
Remind, is the reading of the data
The long-term memory stands for the hard drive,
and the short-term memory stands for the RAM.
Short term memory, meaning the data saved in the RAM,
will be deleted when you turn off the computer.
Do you have an idea what I'm gonna do to you?
The situation that's going to happen right now
If I can see it as an illusion tomorrow...
Then that illusion will be...
Not a hallucination that came out from my mind.
Then let's start it.
Take off your clothes.
Eh!?
We're going to have sex.
Sensei...
Sensei... this is so sudden.
Don't worry.
You'll forget this when you wake up tomorrow.
Sensei... I'm cumming...
Do you have any experience with anal sex?
Huh?
My vagina has lost it's function.
It will secrete a juice but...
It won't contract, and won't do a peristaltic movement.
I'm sorry...
Here, put it in.
Don't restrain.
Sensei...
Go ahead...
Yes...
If you do it along with the breathing,
It will come in smoothly.
Sensei...
It's so good!
I like it...
Right there... thrust deeper!
Sensei... It's so good...
Sensei's ass is so good...
Yeah, I like it too.
Try moving it.
Sensei... I'm... cumming...
I'm cumming!
It's deep... Good...
Go ahead and ejaculate.
Sensei, Sensei!!
It's hot, it's hot, it's hot!
Sensei...
He's being deceived by two pieces,
But he only moved 1 step.
Well it seems things went as smoothly as I formulated.
Hello, I'm Kasuga Midori.
Let's be friends.
A dream?
Tick... Tock... Tick...
Eh? It was my...
How are you feeling?
I've been injected and I was explained something...
But when I woke up, I was already in my bed...
It seems you lost your memory properly.
Eh? What do you mean by memory... Sensei...?
Come to my room when night comes...
Oh yes, have you heard about Amano-san?
If you are looking for her, she already went home.
Eh!?
Is Takumi-sama also suspecting that...
Something scary is happening in the underground...?
Oh... No, I didn't mean that...
Here, this is the thing you asked me to look for.
Wow... ah...
I'm happy!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Pin it properly so that you will not lose it again.
Yes, yes.
I will not lose this anymore.
Kurumi-chan...
Uhm...
I heard that Amano-san went home.
She gives her regards to you.
But she wanted to investigate this place so much,
Even how she wanted to investigate the truth.
But she's doing so much, that she searched my desk.
I see...
No... no...
She was about to destroy my puzzle.
I understand.
Sorry for disturbing you...
Oh... wait a minute.
Hinoki-san has been in a good mood recently.
Please get along with her from now on.
Amano-san went home?
No, it's impossible.
She even asked me desperately...
She even did it to me.
The family that seems to be happy.
Hinoki-chan, she has the same name as...
The wife of the Director, and Midori-san's mother.
Hinoki-san, who passed away.
Hinoki-chan who doesn't take off her black clothing.
What kind of relationship did they have?
Hinoki-chan, have you met me before?
She's alike.
I see...
She's alike with Midori-san.
I'm full~~
Well then Kurumi-chan...
It's time to take your medicine.
Are you always taking this much?
Yes, Aoi-san is also taking this too.
So Kurumi is also fine.
Aoi too?
Why? Is it bad?
Amano-san... did she really go home?
Oh...?
It's Amano-san's lighter...
This is made to be a camera!
I see, so she used this to take the evidence...
But why is this important thing left here...?
I see so she's still in this hospital.
What's the thing you wanted to show me?
Of course, my collections.
I received the remaining internal organs that Director obtained.
Do you want to see it?
Internal organs!? Don't tell me...
It's a joke.
There's a clear objective for the Director's internal organ collecting.
Me too, I don't have any interest other then the internal organs of woman.
Sensei... this is just a joke right?
You must see this one...!!!?
Sensei...
Why are you here?
It's because sensei called me...
What are you saying!?
Get out of here!!!
I'm busy!!
I understand...
Takumi-kun...
Yes...
It seems the rain won't stop.
When will we be able to go out?
Open your eyes when you hear the door close.
Then you can see the illusion, same as always.
Y...yes...
Even if she said to look...
Those illusions are...
Those illusions are super natural perceptions of the past.
This is...
Start of the test.
Examiner: Yanagi Hiroko.
Subject: The patient, Ogi Takumi, who recalls himself seeing sexual illusions.
The purpose of this examination:
Verification that this illusion is a super natural perception of the past.
Well then...
The subject is in a state of sexual excitement.
The examiner and the subject are having anal sex.
The vagina of the examiner has already malfunctioned.
He's clinging onto me, and the sensation of his hips pushing is really...
I'll accept it all...
and I will counter you back more.
More... deeper...
Sensei... I'm cumming...
Ejaculate inside me...
I will squeeze it...
I will squeeze it all...
Release it.
Return your conscience.
Focus your senses here...
What did you see?
Me and Yanagi-sensei...
Correct.
So you remembered it...
Then Sensei and me really...
Uhm... did that thing!?
I can't even believe it myself.
I did that hypnosis for the course of inference.
Will I be like this forever?
You're asking for treatment?
I don't know...
I just discovered the result what's happening to you right now.
It's impossible, No way...
That thing.... It's really impossible...
Get out already.
But...
I'm confused here too...
Get out...
It's all crazy.
My mind...
Sorry for being late.
Here's your food.
Sorry...
I don't have an appetite.
I see.
Then you can take it easy after having rest, so...
Eat it just a little...
The real Midori-san is so kind but...
Hinoki-chan... Aoi...
Ahahahah
Pussy being left wide-opened
Forgive me
Yanagi-sensei... Amano-san...
Its not only the voice and heart being lost
Verified that this illusion is a super natural perception of the past
Ugh... uahh, arghhhh
It's swollen, and it's red
I will have sex with him...
It's so good, It's so good, It's so good and I'm going to cum again
I understand... I understand!!!
Do you really want to show me that much?
Then I will face you until the end!!
As I thought, it's moving.
This dreadful smell, what are they burning everyday?
We're always together in the underground
They are seeing inside my stomach
Kurumi-chan's place...
I'm not... going to Kurumi-chan's place...
Oh... you're talking about Kurumi-chan?
It's alright, so just behave.
Her cerebrum must not be functioning.
No... I'm going...
I'm going to Kurumi-chan's place...
Can't you listen to what I say?
You can be with her later,
and forever.
I will line you in the same closet.
Kurumi in the small jar,
Aoi in the big jar.
You two will be sitting beside forever.
Really!?
Thank you director.
Thank you...
I will do it if you're that happy.
Well then, enter the jar and wait for her later.
I'm not comfortable with this.
For sensei, Kurumi is an important toy for you.
You want to play with her in your hands until she will break completely right?
It seems you really like Kurumi-chan that much.
If you know it, please restrain.
Kurumi-chan... Kurumi-chan...
The Director is doing that thing...
It's swollen, and it's red
A voice...
Amano-san?
It's so good, It's so good, It's so good, and I'm going to cum again...
My pussy, it's shaking again...
My pussy is wet and it feels so good.
The shaking is getting harder...
I want to... I want to feel good quickly...
More... more... please make me feel better.
There... it's so good.
I'm cumming...
No... I'm cumming...
Ah... It's so good, it's so good...
It's so good and I'm going to cum again...
Amano-san... no... way...
No one's here...?
What's this...?
No... it's gross.
No... these things...
Please rape me step father
I see them again...
The thrusting smell of step father's is spreading inside my stomach
punishment
Takumi-kun?
Director...
Are you alright?
It seems you're so dim.
I think I'm alright.
Where have you been at this late time director?
My... my...
I thought Amano-san went home already went but,
are you the one doubting this hospital next?
Just what you saw, I arranged all the specimens in the underground
Why at this time?
It's because these things are gross you know.
I'm doing this so that patients and the nurses can't see.
Are you alright with this?
I was a bit scared,
but I'm alright.
Because it's just a specimen right?
It's a human's...
I extracted it by myself...
and this is not an ordinary specimen.
What do you think?
Not an ordinary specimen...
What are you gonna do with this?
It's the puzzle piece.