SubDESU-H Presents
Eh? Where am I?
W-What?! N-No-!
No, no!
No-!
No...
I've got you!
I'll rape you again, then.
That isn't much of a reaction...
How about I shove it in you?
No, no-!
No!!
Hey! Don't squirm so much!
No-! Help me!
I want to give my first to Taku-chan!
Look it's in!
N-No...! No!
Taku-chan, help me!
S-Stop it, please!
N-No, n-no...!
D-Don't cum! Please don't cum inside me!
P-Please! Not inside, not inside!
I, I don't want to abort another baby...!
Abort?
I see... I see, I see!
You were pregnant!
T-That's why I don't want to go through that again-!
Please! Please don't-!
I-I want to die, I want to die!
If you want to die so much...
I-I can't breathe-!
I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die!
What's this?! You're squeezing me so much!
H-Help me, Taku-chan...
No one's going to save you!
Taku-chan-!
I'm that Taku-chan!
What's with this tightening?!
I-I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum-!
No, no!
Get in!
H-Hatsunaga-sensei?!
Mi-Mizuhara-kun! What did you do to sensei?
Sensei! Get ahold of yourself!
Sensei, sensei!
Muchizuki-san, I heard you were raped by Mizuhara-kun too!
Apparently it was your first time too!
Stop it... Stop it... Stop it!
No!!
I'll make you feel good again!
Mizuhara-kun's cock smells so intense! Sensei is getting too excited!
Can you tell? The vibrator is going into you...
It's okay to be honest! It's not fun when you're constantly being violated, is it?
So you might as well enjoy it!
I'm feeling good!
Despite the fact that I'm being violated, it feels so good!
That's it! I'll do it harder!
T-This is-! This is too much-!
Muchizuki-san! Me too! Do it to me, too!
I'm about to lose my mind!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum...
I'm cumming!
What is it?
Don't I always tell you to knock first?
What do you want?
If not, then leave! You're so annoying...
Stop looking at Onee-chan like that!
Nee-chan, have you had sex before?
Wh-What the hell are you saying? Are you stupid?!
You haven't?
O-Of course I have!
Then how do you moan?
What is your expression like?
What on Earth are you saying-?!
Wh-What the hell are you thinking?!
You're not going to get away with this!
S-Stop!
No!!
Ta-Takumi!
No!
Onee-chan's breasts are so warm and soft!
D-Don't do that-!
I'm your older sister!
No way-!
No!
Ta-Takumi! D-Don't-!
No way, this isn't happening!
Ta-Takumi-!
Takumi? S-Stop!
No! Stop it!
I-It's entering me-!
No, no!
Ta-Takumi-!
S-Stop this already!
N-No...
Chisa-chan, you're finally going to accept me, aren't you?
W-What the hell?! Stop that!
I want to become one with you as your mother!
You're not my mother!
My only Mom is the one that died!
Hey you! What did you do to her?
The same thing I did to you.
This is crazy! Everyone's gone mad-!
No!
This is connected to mine, you know!
N-No!
Don't-!
Chisa-chan! I'm glad you're so happy!
When I put this inside of you, it digs into me too!
Chisa-chan, it's in!
I-I'm so happy! Mom is so happy right now!
You're amazing down there! It's incredible!
I-I'll break!
Pull it out, pull it out!
P-Please, please pull it out!
I-I'll tell you about my replacement!
Your replacement?
It's true! I'm not lying!
I'm sure that you'll like her more than me!
S-So-! Please stop!
S-She's my friend. I'm sure that you'll be satisfied, so please-!
What should I do?
Please!
Sign: Staff
Good morning!
Ah, good morning.
It's Amatsuka Miruku in the flesh!
You're on in 20 minutes!
Amatsuka Miruku
I have to hurry!
Be quiet.
No-!
Miruku-chan, you may be surprised, but I bring a message from the producer.
A message from the producer?
That's right.
U-Um-!
What is it?
U-Uh...
I'll finish soon, so please get out.
Don't worry about me.
N-No...!
That's a pretty extreme outfit you've got on.
T-This is also in the producer's interest... N-No! I mean, under h-his orders...
Oops, I can't let you do that!
B-But-! I need to wipe myself!
Never mind that, Miruki-chan. Can you see this?
Miruku-chan, you know the situation we're in, don't you?
N-No! No!
Your part as the heroine in the next feature film relies on this.
B-But-! I'm about to be in a live concert!
I-I'll do it afterward, so please not now-!
What are we going to do about the film then?
I don't really mind if you're not up for it...
I-I'll do it! Please let me do it! But I'm nearly out of time!
Please, please finish quickly!
I see, then I won't hold back...
You smell like urine!
It's like I said!
This is why it's good!
B-But...! No! Please don't lick me so much!
Please stop!
Stop-!
U-Um! I-I really need to get going!
Please let me go soon!
N-No way!
I'll finish up quickly!
B-But-! If you do it now, I'll...!
P-Please! I-I promise that we'll continue after-!
Then let's forget about your part in the film...
You're so mean!
No more!
Shall we stop?
I-I understand, so please hurry!
Then I'll do as you say...
My cock is entering Miruku the idol!
So thick-!
It's in all the way!
It's so tight and nicely shaped!
Please finish this quickly!
Eh? Do you want me to move so quickly?
You like it hard, don't you?
Eh?
N-No, I don't!
How is it? How is it?
Isn't this good? Is this hard enough for you?
No-! This is difficult for me-!
I can have the part of the heroine for this, right?
Maybe this has brought you closer to being the heroine.
Maybe?
What do you mean maybe?
I forgot to tell you, but there are still other conditions.
C-Conditions?
It's...
N-No way!
That was the message from the producer.
B-But! If I do that, all my fans...!
No, I think that they'll like it!
N-No way!
T-They'll like it?
But if I can show them what they dream of me as an idol, then-!
I'll cum inside you!
Y-You can't!
My concert-!
Did you forget about the event after this?
I'm gonna cum, then!
Miruki-chan, you're feeling good, right?
Y-Yes! It feels good, it feels really good!
If it's that good, I'll make sure to let out plenty inside of you!
Yes! Please do so!
Let it out!
Please let it out!
H-Huh?
I-I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
Thank you very much...
S-So for that film, I...
I said there were other conditions, didn't I?
Oh right, this concert...
I wonder what I'm so nervous about?
Then we must get ready.
Yes!
Everyone! Do you like Miruku?
Do you love me?
If you love me, you wanna have sex with me, right?
You can do anything you want to Miruku today!
No! Stop!
No, no!!
No!!
No!
No, no, no!
Stop, stop-!
No-!
No!
As if I'm gonna get caught!
I'm not done yet!
I'm gonna rape more and more!
All women should be raped.
They should scream and have me cum inside them to bear my children!
Women are made for my cock!
Women are born to be raped!
This is rape! Rape rape rape!