the bloodtype is A.
W
~ Sex Beast ~
Man, morning practice...
What the hell?
Everyone, I suppose you already know the reason why I summoned you here.
I'd like to introduce our new leader.
Third year, class B, Mutsuki Jouji-san.
The hell? New leader?
It can't be.
Huh?!
Quiet!
Aren't you listening to me?
If you please...
I'm Mutsuki. Nice to meet you.
Even though I'm the new leader,
it's not like anything is going to particularly change.
Please rest assured.
However, my orders are absolute.
Understood?
What was that?
He asked if you understood.
Y-Yes!
G'mornin.
'Mornin.
What does all that mean?
The second victim, eh?
I dreaded as much – this is the worst case possible.
It can't be helped.
Please allow me to undertake an investigation of the teaching staff.
Ichijou-kun, it's a request for dispatch
Which school might it be?
Your alma mater; the private School of the Holy Spirit.
How nostalgic.
There appears to have been a malicious incident-
-involving the child of a noted family.
We will send you the necessary data in time.
Please do your best.
By all means, leave this to me.
This will mean one more gold star on my record.
That confidence is certainly related to the fantastic sex.
Makes me want to request another private “meeting”.
When the chance arises...
Come on, anytime you want.
Okay!
Yes!
I've... never felt... this good!
Listen to me, Maki.
This is the difference between a winner and a loser.
Remember it.
Yes.
Amazing!
And then, I will become the ruler of this school.
Everyone who's never noticed me-
-will be forced to acknowledge my existence!
Maki, get in front of Rie and open your thighs.
Do what I ask already.
Yes.
Rie, lick it.
But!
You’re getting enough pleasure the way things are,
so let Maki feel some of that, too.
Yes.
Thank you very much!
Who should the next incident happen to?
What's wrong?
Now that I'm here, you won't be allowed to simply do as you please.
This evening, by will of the sorcerer,
Mutsuki Jouji, who has been granted with the powers of evil,
Someone free of sin...
shall fall prey to venomous fangs.
Voice of Satan!
Use my body to fulfill my wishes!
Athaniel, give me the force of the moon!
O spirit I desire,
I call upon your powers of eternal malice,
and summon thee.
And I grant this request unto thee; give me your power!
Punishment is necessary for a sinful body.
With such a horny body as this,
how do you plan to serve God from now on?
You might say you don't like it,
but your body can't lie.
In front of the God you believe in,
you're being dirtied by a man's cock.
Your faith is nothing but make-believe.
Our evil god is appropriate for you!
I'm going to cum!
Now that she's become one of us,
there can be holy energy ceremonies here anytime.
We've become one step closer to the day when our master will rule the school.
This is holy water.
Show your obedience and offer all of it to your insides.
Morning!
Now, it's Ichijou-sensei's turn...
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ichijou Nozomi.
I'm only here for a short time, as the school president said,
but I look forward to working with you all.
I'm a beginner in every field, so I might not be very good,
so please bear with me.
Also, if you have any problems or want to talk,
don't hesitate to come ask me.
There's a possibility that the culprit is among these students.
I have to proceed with the investigation without revealing my true identity.
Based on the bloodstains left behind,
There's a high possibility that some kind of ceremony took place.
And, the ones who were violated were virgins.
After the first incident, did anything change?
It doesn't matter how small.
No, nothing in particular.
I see.
Well, if you remember anything, please let me know anytime.
Yes.
... I don't know...
I want the names of students who felt something strange after the incident.
The woman's blood types, I can figure out by looking at the nurse's office data.
Name
Seisei Rie
Hometown
Tokyo
Birthday
1/23/1984
Blood type
O
Height
148 cm
Address
167-0051
Suginami district, Midtown. 4-32-5
October 7th?
Yes. Do you remember what you did in class the next morning?
I don't know...
Did something happen that day?
Sensei, you're almost like a detective!
I'm collecting data for a report I have to write for graduate school.
It's an investigation of the sexual preferences of young people.
Is that so?
Excuse me!
You didn’t tell her things she has no right knowing, right?
Naturally. She's going around asking about that evening.
Definitely suspicious!
What's more, something's fishy about that woman.
We have to report her to Master.
Yes!
After we cum, let's go see Master.
Magic circle?
I don’t think it could be someone from the outside.
Profanity against a chapel or worship hall-
-could be a mark of defiance against the school.
The culprit and victims both-
-must undoubtedly be somehow related to this school.
Yes!
I'm cumming!
Black magic?