www.SubDESU-H.net
What's wrong?
Get on with it.
Go on.
H-Hey, that girl...
Yes Aniki!
She has been acting a bit weird for some time now.
Watch this. Gonna tease her a bit.
Are you for real, girl?
This is great!
Don't just enjoy by yourself over there.
Let us join, too.
Hey, girl.
Because you're masturbating in a place like this...
Here, take a look.
My thing here has become this stiff.
What are you going to do about this, eh?
What are you going to do, girl?
Seriously?
I can't believe this woman.
She's a real bitch.
I can't get enough of her...
Woah, you're already this wet!
How is it?
Does it feel good?
This girl is...
If it's like this, then we'll just have to satisfy her all the way!
Gotcha, Aniki!
Oh, no. That's...
How's the taste of my lust?
It's delicious.
Your cock is very hard and stinky!
Stir up my pussy more!
B-Bro, this butthole wraps me tightly.
I can't get enough of it!
That's good. That feels good!
Please thrust into my pussy and asshole!
This is wonderful!
Okay, let's release everything we've got inside her.
Okay!
Okay, good work.
W
Molester
License
Does it feel that good?
"There's a train conductor here who's acts lewdly during duty hours."
The rumors are already spreading.
If this continues, won't the train conductor be fired?
If that happens,
then there's no helping it.
But, more than that...
With that thick cock of yours...
I want you to...
... tease my...
... my wet pussy.
My slovenly pussy!
Using your cock, please...
Oh no, I can't endure anymore.
Insert it in me now! In my pussy!
Onee-chan...
Oops, sorry about that.
Seems that I'm not in the mood to listen to someone today.
Do you feel bad that I didn't take the front hole?
No, anal is also good.
I'm feeling it... More, more!
Is that right? You're really desperate to get it in your asshole, huh?
Yes, it feels good in my asshole.
I can't stop...!
Onee-chan...
Now then, I'll be taking Onee-chan's pussy!
Homura-chan...
Onee-chan...
Aoi-oneechan!
Come inside me, Homura-chan!
Here I go.
Onee-chan!
Th-This feels great, Homura-chan!
Onee-chan and I are connected to each other.
This feels good, Homura-chan.
Push it, push it in more!
Onee-chan!
My butt is...
My butthole feels hot.
My pussy feels very tight.
Onee-chan... Onee-chan, my nipples...
They feel great!
I'm going to cum again because of Homura-chan.
I'm cumming!
This is amazing!
Onee-chan!
Me, too. Me, too!
That's good, you two.
It's perfect.
In the end, the clues stopped here.
I guess I really can't fully solve it by myself after all.
The clues about the man named Sawanagare Taichi,
who destroyed my life,
stopped right here.
Have you found out anything about me yet?
Ouch!
No!
Stop this!
Well? How does your punishment feel?
No, stop...
Please stop!
Ouch...
Ouch!
Onee-chan, you're really wonderful.
Takako-chan.
Takako-oneechan.
Why are you...?
Takako-chan, I'm sorry, but we are now...
... sex slaves of Sawanagare-san.
Sex... slaves?
Okay, let's continue now that all you three sisters are assembled.
Oh, no. Stop...
No!
It hurts...
Please stop!
Poor Takako-chan...
Becoming red like this...
We will appease it for you, okay?
D-Don't... Onee-chan...
Homura-chan, no... Don't tease it...
Takako-oneechan's breasts really look delicious.
Don't do that, Homura-chan.
You two... No, stop...
I'm...
I'm going to lose it...
Oh, no... I can no longer....!
Now, Takako-chan.
Get your wet pussy fucked by a real cock.
Stop that. It's...
It's my first time.
It's okay.
It'll feel good soon enough.
No... Stop, stop!
No...
It hurts, it hurts! No...
Here, Onee-chan.
I love to have my pussy licked by Onee-chan.
Please, okay?
Homura-chan,
what a lewd pussy you have.
Pussy... Homura-chan's pussy...
Feels good... It feels good!
Do it more...
Suck it up more!
Feels good, it feels good!
My pussy feels good!
Do it more. Push it in. Go deeper! More!
Aoi, you want to get in her, too?
Inside your younger sister?
Yes, I'll be entering her now.
Eh, Onee-chan?
No way. Are you....?
No, Aoi-oneechan...
If you... If you thrust in me like that...
Oh, no. It's supposed to be my first time,
but I'm about to cum!
I'm going to...
I'm going to cum because of Onee-chan!
No!
Stop this already...
Why?
Even though I want to stop... I somehow can't stop...
Th-This feels good!
Yes! This feels good!
It's slowly starting to feel good.
It's starting to feel good.
I-I'm really going to cum.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Please, release it.
Cum inside me.
Please, let it burst inside!
The hot feeling's isn't stopping!
I'm at my limit!
I'm... It's about to come out...
It's coming out...! It's going to come out inside my pussy!
I'm cumming!
Okay.
Now you three are my sex slaves from now on.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Female Use Trailer
I thought that this trailer was for females only.
But it's really quite packed.
The city really has lots of people I guess.
Oh, I must be careful of my speech!
I'm sorry!
Don't put your hands there!
Hey,
where are you touching me?
I-I'm sorry!
Hey, you seem to be a molester.
Eh? No way I'm...!
Can you come over here a bit?
I'm...
Hey...
You're really quite sensitive to make noises like that.
We'll make it feel better for you.
Stop... Don't tease me like this....
But this part is already like this, see?
Don't!
It's already dripping wet with lewd liquids.
Don't... No...
Don't lick it...
Everyone's watching us here...
Stop...
Wow, there are more and more liquids flowing out.
Don't lick it like that.
Don't play with my butthole...
D-Don't... Oh, no...
Please stop...
I'm feeling it...
... in this place. No...
I can't...!
That's good.
Do it more.
Lick it... Does my breasts taste good?
This is...
... delicious.
Good, your butt's twitching.
So cute!
Your pussy is also throbbing.
It's really erotic.
No... don't–!
Here, I'll do your pussy like this.
You can't do that... Don't play with my pussy...
Okay, it seems that the preparations are complete.
Now, let's begin.
No way...
This is supposed to be a trailer for female use only...
No...!
It's entering! It's entering me!
You're cute when you scream in pain like that.
Eh?
I want to take a bite of her already.
Taking the cock completely like this...
Your pussy is now getting stirred up.
No, my insides...
If my clitoris gets played like that...
I'll feel itchy to do it!
What a lewd girl.
The pussy's insides are throbbing.
Don't say that!
It feels... It feels good!
Oh, no!
My pussy's being penetrated...
M-My pussy is...!
I'm cumming!!
Huh?
I wonder what happened?
Where's Sawanagare-san?
Where are the other passengers?
There's no one here.
Was that... a dream?
By the way, I haven't gotten your name yet.
What's your name?
Yes, it's Ishizaki Otome.
I just came from the rural area a while ago.
So it's Otome-chan?
That's cute.
Otome-chan, where are you staying?
If you haven't decided yet, why don't you stay at our place?
All three of us are siblings, so if it's okay with you...
Is that okay?
But before that...
Well, can all of you please
take care of me one more time?
Please.
Of course.
We'll be glad to.
www.SubDESU-H.net