W
Are you scared?
You’re so adorable, Megumi.
Yes...
Do you want my juices too, Megumi?
Yes.
Drink up, Megumi.
Yes...
Do you want me?
Yes... Do me lots.
Wh-What’s this?
You’re a man?
I’m not a man.
Nor am I a woman.
I am of a clan that possesses traits of both sexes.
In your language... I am... a god.
Your jewel... belongs to me now.
What color is this ecstasy?
So beautiful.
What a clear sparkle... and a clear color.
You truly possess an amazing heart.
So they found me.
It ends here, evil goddess.
Jewel Blaze
Tenshi ga kono  star o
The angel takes my star
Star no ue de heart candy
And leaves a heart candy above it
Mote asobu kimi
You toy with it,
Hana midori  no afternoon
On a flowery, green afternoon,
Monokuroomu o doro tsuki
Muddying up the monochromatic scenery,
Madowaseru ruby
The rubies seduce me.
I’m not going to let them catch me.
Star jewel
Open up!
That analogue funny face
Analogue no funny face
Utsukushisa sika mienaku naru
Makes me unable to see anything but beauty.
Kimi no koto ni naru to boku wa sounen ni kaeru
When you’re near me, I return to the prime of my life.
Star jewel tenshi no kieta yoru wa
Star jewel, on the night the angels disappeared...
Star jewel, star jewel, konna ni mo shizuka da
Star jewel, star jewel, it was unbelievably quiet.
Star jewel
That girl’s jewel... Return it at once!
Not to the likes of you!
Then you leave me no choice.
Your jewel too!
Can you withstand my pleasures?
You’re beautiful.
Wh-What?
I want to see the true you.
What is your name?
I have no name to give to the enemy.
So adorable.
I won’t hand it over.
Then I have no choice.
My name is Natsumi.
Shinno Natsumi.
This is my mission.
Your jewel... What color is it?
Sorry for the wait, Miss.
Thanks.
Now you’re back to normal.
Your good heart belongs to you.
Who are you... Where’s Lapis?
Lapis?
Where’s Lapis!
That’s her name?
Lapis...
She won’t come back.
Why not?
Because she did something horrible to you.
No! She didn’t do anything bad to me!
No. She tried to steal something precious from you.
No! I gave it to her! I gave her everything!
Yes... But it was all an illusion.
So forget it.
I gave it to her!
I gave her everything!
Good work, Natsumi.
Reiko?
Looks like the case is closed.
Did you retrieve the human jewel?
Yes. I gave it back to its owner.
Though the evil goddess escaped.
Oh.
Then you cannot act for a while.
The evil goddess who stole the jewel... Her name is Lapis...
Lapis?
The enemy has increased their activity lately.
They must be plotting something horrible!
Mei, have you noticed anything?
Mei...
No. They’re just being very reckless.
A little more showy than they’ve been before.
I agree.
So we have to stay on our guard.
Natsumi, when you find them, steal the jewels from them without hesitation.
But... I have a bad feeling about this.
It’s like we’re ganging up against our own kind.
We goddesses come from another planet, Planet Goddess. We are an abnormal species...
Stained in sin, the other goddesses have chased us away from our planet.
Our mission is to prevent them from returning to their mother planet.
The evil goddesses steal 'jewels' – or, the hearts of pure humans –
and are trying to use them as a power supply for their hidden spaceship.
The only method to return to our home planet, Planet Goddess,
is to energize this large ship...
So, Ruby, how is Lapis?
She lost her jewel and is in a catatonic state.
It will most likely take two thousand years to recreate her spirit.
So... Which goddess put Lapis to sleep?
She disappeared.
We believe she has disguised herself as a human and walks among them.
Oh...
Do you want a mouth, Dectite...
Zircon-sama... please give me an order.
What do you want... Ruby?
Order me to avenge Lapis.
Our mission is... not to fight the goddesses.
It is to collect as many jewels as possible.
But...
I do not wish to lose any more of my clan!
Do... Do you hate her so...?
You need... revenge?
Zircon-sama!
Do your job well.
That is the condition.
I will.
I won’t forgive her...
That goddess who did this to you.
I’ll never forgive her.
Lapis... Lapis....
Lapis...
Lapis... Your heart...
Your power... Share it with me!
What’s wrong, Reiko?
I sensed the waves of a pure heart crystallizing.
There should be a jewel nearby.
Impossible!
But we just got one of the evil goddesses.
Were there more nearby?
Trace it at once.
Reiko, can you help me?
I’m sorry.
Huh?
Was someone here just now?
I’ll go do it!
Natsumi isn’t revived yet, isn’t she?
Umph.
Woopsie!
Yahoo!
Will I lose again?
If love is a sin... then this universe was born from sin.
And if that is so... then I will carry the burden.
I won’t suffer the same fate as Lapis!
I will have you give Lapis her heart back!
What an ugly scene for you.
Your jewel... will be mine!
Now... don’t be scared.
You’re beautiful.
It seems you have unbelievable power.
Your jewel... is showing its power to me through your flesh.
Such immense power.
Ecstasy.
Pleasure derived from yourself.
You will surrender your body to it!
Yes...
What a huge bud.
Fitting for such a big heart.
No... Not that... Anything but that...
You will not... defeat me!
Wh-What are you...
No... Don’t look...
So pretty.
You’re... almost... there...
Me too...
You’re so beautiful, darling.
This jewel... will not go to waste.
Natsumi.
I’m fine.
I retrieved the jewel.
Thank goodness.
I’ll come to back you up right away.
Don’t let this one get away!
Roger that.
You fell for it.
That was not a human jewel.
It is one from the evil goddesses.
My little sister... Sapphire’s heart crystal!
When a goddess’s heart is dirtied by an evil goddess’s jewel,
she will either suffer for all eternity...
Or she will become one of us – she will fall.
What?
Why... A goddess with a black wing?
Natsumi!
Don’t let her escape!
Mei! Take care of Natsumi!
I want to chase her too!
Sorry. Let me borrow this.
Sheesh! Natsumi!
Natsumi, your wings...
Oh no... Stay away... You can’t...
You butt in too far.
What?
Because of you, the plan has gone haywire.
I won’t give you my jewel.
I have no need to steal it.
It’s always been mine.
What? Why... What...
No... Stop it!
You...
You were...
Natsumi!
Why?
I’m sorry, Mei.
I forgot...
What happened, Natsumi?
I... I...
No...
Don’t... Don’t, Natsumi!
Don’t, Natsumi!
We’re both goddesses... Sex is unforgivable!
I can’t stop it!
I want you!
No more... I’ll...
Aren't you a goddess? Natsumi!
I'm, not a... goddess.
R-Reiko...
I will help you.
Come now, Natsumi.
You’re almost there.
What’s this?
Reiko, what is this thing?
Keep this a secret.
But...
At last...
The time for awakening has arrived.
The time has arrived, it seems.
My feelings will be released here!
Tenshi ga kono  star o
The angel takes my star
Star no ue de heart candy
And leaves a heart candy above it
Mote asobu kimi
You toy with it,
Star jewel
Hana midori  no afternoon
On a flowery, green afternoon,
Monokuroomu o doro tsuki
Muddying up the monochromatic scenery,
Madowaseru ruby
The rubies seduce me.
Star jewel
Analogue no funny face
That analogue funny face
Utsukushisa sika mienaku naru
Makes me unable to see anything but beauty.
Kimi no koto ni naru to boku wa sounen ni kaeru
When you’re near me, I return to the prime of my life.
Tenshi ga kono  star o
The angel takes my star.
Bara no kaori no shandy
And this rose-scented shandy
Nomi hoshita kimi
You drink it until there’s nothing left.
Star jewel
Rossai  no jewel case
The rossai jewel case
Mozaiku iro doresu ruu
Is a mosaic-colored dress ruu
Utai dasu ruby
The rubies begin to sing.
Star jewel
Dejitaru na very  case
This very digital case
Hayasa  de shika dake naku naru
Makes me only able to make love to you at a high speed.
Kimi no koto ni naru to boku wa kumo  ni mo naru
When you’re near me, I can also become clouds.
Star jewel tenshi no kieta yoru wa
Star jewel, on the night the angels disappeared...
Star jewel, star jewel, konna ni mo shizuka da
Star jewel, star jewel, it was unbelievably quiet.
Star jewel
Tenshi to kono  star o
The angels and my stars
Kizu mo kisu  sae mo tsui  saki  iyashiteru kimi
Their wounds and kisses are both soothed by you,
Star jewel
Star jewel.
Ren’ai no auction
The love auction
Mirror site no maboroshi
The illusion of the mirror site
Sore o ai to yobu
We call those 'love'
Star jewel
Star jewel.
Stereo no full pace
With the stereo at full pace,
Setsunasa ni shika dakenaku naru
I can only make love in a lonely state of mind
Kimi no koto ni naru to boku wa kanashimi ni kureru
When you’re near me, I writhe in sadness.
Star jewel tenshi no kieta yoru wa
Star jewel, on the night the angels disappeared...
Star jewel, star jewel, konna ni mo kirei da
Star jewel, star jewel, it was unbelievably pretty.
Star jewel
Analogue no funny face
That analogue funny face
Utsukushisa sika mienaku naru
Makes me unable to see anything but beauty.
Kimi no koto ni naru to boku wa sounen ni kaeru
When you’re near me, I return to the prime of my life.
Star jewel tenshi no kieta yoru wa
Star jewel, on the night the angels disappeared...
Star jewel, star jewel, konna ni mo shizuka da
Star jewel, star jewel, it was unbelievably quiet.
Star jewel tenshi no kieta yoru wa
Star jewel, on the night the angels disappeared...
Star jewel, star jewel, konna ni mo kirei da
Star jewel, star jewel, it was unbelievably pretty.
Star jewel
sennen  no jikan o hitori de
Alone for thousands of years,
eien no kodoku o takaku
My eternal solitude rises high.
sasayaka na kioku no kodou ga
Faint waves of memories...
sore wa koi nan da to tsubuyaku
...tell me that that is passionate love.
amai mitsu  de sasowareru kedo
The sweet nectar seduces me,
sono sugata o mita hito wa nai
But no one has seen my true form.
yume mo koi mo ai mo yoru mo
Dreams and passion and love and nights
soshite asa mo
And also mornings
nemuru megami maru de mukae o matsu (?) shoujo
The sleeping goddess is almost like a girl waiting for someone to rescue her.
dakara daite daite daite subete o daite
So please hold me, hold me, hold me, embrace all of me.
daite daite daite eien no kodoku kowai kurai
Hold me, hold me, hold my eternal solitude so much it frightens me.