SubDESU-H.net
That was delicious.
You girls…
~Natsumi Oblivion~
W
Side Story
~Natsumi Oblivion~
Natsumi Oblivion
Star Jewel
~Natsumi Oblivion~
Side Story
Gaiden
~Natsumi Oblivion~
Side Story
Nice to meet you!
I'm Jinno Natsumi.
I'm a burdened female high schooler attending St. Maria Academy.
Indeed!
Good morning, Student President!
Good morning!
She was looking at me just now!
Oh please, you’re just seeing things.
You’re wrong!
Good morning, students, good morning.
Mayuri Onee-sama!
You're just far too beautiful!
Good morning.
The student council president, Kokuyouin Mayuri-senpai.
With her divine beauty and talents…
She is truly the biggest, most eye-catching flower in this school.
The biggest dream of all of the students…
is to be ordered to come to her sleeping quarters to pleasure her.
And I, too, hope that someday…
Throb
Wait?
Wait a minute…
Sorry…
Wh-Why at a time like this?
I’m such an idiot.
That’s right.
The “burden” I mentioned earlier, is this thing that started growing on me…
This strangely “masculine” thing…
Is this… I think… it has to be… that.
Why do I have it?
Because I’m going through puberty?
I’ve heard some fish change sexes many times as they grow up.
But am I really gonna turn into a boy?
I can’t be…
But despite all this, I can’t afford to stay home from school!
After all, I’m trying to win the grand scholastic prize!
Oops-oops-oops…
Onee-sa… ma!
Oh my, are you okay?
Y-Yes! I’m sorry.
Did I step on you?
I don’t mind.
That badge… do you intend to join the student council?
Yes. Trainee number 69.
Jinno Natsumi.
Oh. You’re a cute one.
Tonight… would you join me… in my bedroom?
What?
Why?
No way!
You suck, Natsumi!
I hear the president gave you an executive order!
Glare
Yes, that’s right.
Why did she choose me of all people?
Their glaring is really stinging me.
Pat
Now, now, don’t be so stiff about it.
Just go over there and let her have your body!
She’s right… I shouldn’t be stiff.
Why is it happening now?
What should I do?
Let Onee-sama have my body… which means…
Naturally, that part, too… she’ll see it…?
No, no, that can’t happen!
Onee-sama is a hardcore lesbian!
She thinks that when two women make love, any sort of thing that resembles a piston is in bad taste.
She thinks that like animals, we should stay still, rub our bodies,
and feel skin on skin – that is the way to make love.
That is the way.
Earlier, there was once a girl who was called to her bedroom and…
Umm, Onee-sama… I have one request.
Would you please put this on and fuck me?
Just get out of my sight!
And take that filthy thing with you!
That is the legendary dick-aversion…
The defining characteristic of Mayuri Onee-sama!
If she finds out I have a real dick on me… she might freaking kill me!
What should I do?
Natsumi? You’re disgusting!
Scum like you is banished from the student council!
No, I sentence you to expulsion!
No! Onee-sama, you can’t!
Sign: Changing Room
Did you hear?
A student council girl went missing again.
That’s the third one this month!
That sure is creepy.
Yeah.
Wait for me!
It’s my turn…
Throb
S-Sensei, um, my period…
Oh, really? Then rest out, dear.
It must be my period!
I’m not lying!
Dicks sure are… inconvenient.
Oh! What the hell is happening to me?
Just give me a break!
How can I suppress it?
Natsumi, are you okay?
You look really pale.
Sorry, I’m fine, I’m fine.
And so, when you solve the problem with this formula, the answer comes very easily.
This will be on the test.
Now, come to me, Natsumi.
I’ll take care of you until the morning.
Yes.
Onee-sa… ma!
Huh?
Do you smell something weird?
Yeah.
Could this be… that thing?
It’s that thing, isn’t it?
What? What?
No way. What’s that smell?
I… I have to leave early!
Wh-What’s this?
I’ve heard about this.
Is this… semen…?
So much is coming out.
Wow, it’s soaking!
I mean…
That felt good.
N-No… this… doesn’t feel good…
It’s something I’m… cursed with…
That’s right.
If I cum lots, I’m sure… my stupid dick will… shrivel away.
This is therapy… it’s therapy!
Onee-sama…
Wait for me… okay?
Jinno Natsumi… will pleasure… you with… her female body…
It didn’t go away.
I guess it’s hopeless.
That felt great.
Damn you, dick!
Why did you do this to me?
Now there’s no way I can face Onee-sama.
But that felt so good…
Whap!
What the hell?
What’s wrong with that!?
What’s wrong with having a dick?
For months I’ve been dreaming of receiving Onee-sama’s invitation.
And finally this miraculous night is upon me!
Grumbling over my problems won’t make them go away!
I won’t lose hope!
I won’t let a stupid dick make me lose!
A woman walks her path alone.
Natsumi… go!
Onee-sama… I mean, Mistress, please, have your way with me.
Why are you dressed like that?
Did I dress the wrong way?
I should have known – so you really dislike this sort of male fantasy cliché?
No… I don’t dislike it.
Now, I think I shall take advantage of the situation and give you an order.
Lick me.
Sparkle
Okay!
You can’t hold back, can you?
You naughty girl.
Show yourself to me.
P-Please look.
Recently… it suddenly came in.
You might not believe me, but…
I thought I was a normal girl…
I suppose a hardcore lesbian like you wouldn’t go for a hermaphrodite.
A girl with an ugly thing like this on her crotch… you must hate me.
That isn’t true at all.
This is beautiful in its own right.
I’m so embarrassed!
N-No! It’s dirty… please…
No…
Don’t, don’t, don’t!
It’s cumming!
Onee-sama is… with her mouth…
This is like a dream!
W-W-Wait, not in your boobs!
Just hang in there, it gets even better.
No… not this… I’ll cum!
It’s cumming… cumming all out!
Wh-Wh-What is this thing!?
Hmph. Now I see what you really are.
A pink bud.
How beautiful it is.
As I thought, you were one who dares defy us.
You pretended to be a moron to get closer to me.
But luckily for me, my technique is great.
And now, I will use my great technique to make that flower open.
Onee-sama! Your dick? Your dick? I thought you hated them?
We evil goddesses use ecstasy as a weapon to steal the jewels from human hearts.
Using just my penis to extract it is easy enough…
but I prefer to use my fingers and all of my skin.
And slowly pull it out.
That means the jewel will shine the way I like it.
That is all.
How fantastic!
Goddesses sure are different.
This is the best feeling!
Now, cry out more.
Inside your ecstasy, you will release all of your powers!
Why?
What is… happening… why is this…?
Goddesses? Mayuri Onee-sama? What are you talking about?
I merely… lusted after you… and I…
I… huh?
Who am… I?
The Planet of the Goddesses was dyed in evil.
Those who sinned fell to another planet… Earth.
Those who were banished, in order to return to their mother planet,
needed to transform human hearts into jewels to power their return.
That is where… their power comes from.
St. Maria Academy?
Yes. This year alone, two students have gone missing.
There’s no clues at all and the cops have given up – something fishy about it, right?
I agree.
Shall we investigate?
Who’s going?
I'll pass.
I’m too busy!
Jeez! Reiko and Mei are just too lazy!
What do they think of our mission anyway?
Hey, you! Don’t go in there!
Whoooosh
I’m so happy you’re safe.
She took a direct hit to the head.
I thought she was dead.
I just remembered!
I was sent to Earth to protect the humans from the evil goddesses!
I am… a good goddess!
And the jewels you stole, I’m taking them back!
Wh-What are you…?!
Impossible!
How strong are you?
What are you doing? It’s completely different from before!
Power… This is the power of a true goddess.
Just like when you were licking me earlier.
Oh, no… I didn’t mean to… I’m sorry…
It’s cumming… cumming… I’m going to cum!
We’re not finished yet.
The real fun begins here… right?
After all, I’m going to cum plenty inside of you.
This feels amazing!
Oh no, I’ll cum… I’ll cum again!
Oh no… I’ll lose my mind!
Mercy, please!
Pssssht
Wow, her boobs got smaller.
I see, she used the power of the jewels to alter her appearance.
Shhhht
Jewels retrieved.
Time to send them back to everyone.
Looks like Natsumi finally got her memory back.
Good grief. She really caused us such a panic.
Let’s go home.
Wait for me!
Good morning.
Huh? Is Natsumi ill today?
Who’s that?
Who is that? Natsumi!
I was gonna ask her how things went with Mayuri Onee-sama last night.
Who’s Mayuri?
What the hell are you talking about?
Who? Oh please!
Onee-sama is Onee-sama… wait? Who was she?