Translated by SubDESU-H
Misaki Shunin no Buka Kyouiku Hen
You're getting lazy lately, you know?!
If you can't do your job properly,
then I'll teach you directly with my body.
Prepare yourself.
Though you can't do your job properly,
but when it comes to something like this, you're doing so much good.
You're being like this.
Just what are you imagining in your head?
I wonder what everyone would say, if they saw something like this.
Your thrust is weakening, you know?
Don't loosen your strength!
Don't say something cowardly like that,
and you call yourself a man?
I'm getting excited too.
You're a virgin, right?
If you're not going answer, then I'm not gonna let you go.
You said that your penis was going to ejaculate, right?
Does it feel good?
From the tip of your penis it already come out, you know?
It's getting slippery.
You're totally a pervert, getting excited from my feet like this.
Is it actually your hobby after all?
Hey, say that you want more!
If you don't say it out loud,
I won't understand.
It's getting big.
Do you want to cum?
Do you want to release your sperm from your dirty penis?
If you want your penis inside my lovely pussy,
then I need you to show me your determination.
I'm not satisfied yet with this.
It feels good, right?
There's a reaction from your penis.
It's okay, let it out!
Let me see your determination!
What is it? You want me to suck it?
You don't have any restrain, do you?
Did you wash your penis very clean?
The smell feels... so horrible...
It's so delightful...
The smell keeps flowing out...
I'm getting excited...
Even though I'm being aroused like this,
I don't feel ashame of it.
Don't let such a cowardly voice out.
I wonder what will happen, if I keep doing this.
Did you like being sucked like this?
Is it okay with you?
Do you want something more?
Did you feel it, it went through my throat...
Mouth's pussy...
It's good, isn't?
You can't let yourself come out yet, okay?
It's bitter...
But I can't really stop this feeling,
your juice keeps flowing from the tip of your penis.
It feels good.
Your penis is getting big in my mouth.
It's full in my mouth...
Even though it's rotten, it's not rejected.
It's good isn't it, between my breast?
If I keep doing this, I'm gonna feel it too.
This really feels good, right?
Me too...
Your hard penis is touching my erected nipples.
It's okay.
It's really hot, did you feel excited from it?
My pussy feels drenched too...
It's beating around...
You can let it out.
I feel my nipples rubbing on your penis as well.
You want me to lick the tip of your penis, right?
The bitterness is flowing out from it.
You're gonna cum? You don't have to hold it, okay?
A lot of it is cumming.
Did my breasts really feel that good?
Your balls is hitting my breast too.
It came out onto my face...
It's really an amazing smell, I feel so much muddy.
It's really delicious.
It pulls me out...
Your expression looks so delighted,
are you happy?
Do you really want to lick over it?
My pussy feels soft and good, doesn't it?
Lick over it more!
That's right you're doing good, aren't you?
My pussy is drenched so much...
Your licking over it, making my juice
keeps flowing out from my pussy.
Make my pussy cum!
As I thought you have a big size, right?
It's hitting...
the deep part of me.
Hey, you're a virgin penis...
Why don't you try to make me cum?
Or is it really all that you can do after all?
Is it okay for only you to get satisfied?
Let me feel good as well.
That's right you know what I'm talking about, right?
Why don't you do it, like I told you before.
Hey, make me feel more good!
I won't forgive you, if you cum before I do!
If you're doing it only this hard, then you're
not better than a beast.
Don't make a voice like that...
I've not even felt good enough, you know?
With this thrust...
It feels good.
Thrust deep inside me!
If we're talking about it, then it's from the front, right?
But, I'm yet to feel your determination...
You lack endurance too...
You can't let the rush come into you!
Make the same rhythm with my hips
and also your body as well.
If you're keep doing something like that,
then I'm not gonna feel that much good.
More...
Put it more deep inside of me!
Then we're down to stamina challenge, aren't we?
I feel you thrusting into my womb too!
It keeps rubbing the inside of my pussy...
It's not enough for me!
You can see my lewd figure from there, right?
Did you really feel that good?
You're getting to much excited.
You're movement is getting stronger...
It's good...
My pussy feels hot...
Your penis feels hot...
It's great.
You want to release it?
It's okay, you can make the inside of me...
drenched with your sperm!
If you can't hold it anymore, just let it out!
How much did you hold inside your thing?
I feel a lot of your sperm flowing into my stomach
I just can't take all of it...
I'll let you inside my womb.
You're getting weak, strengthen yourself!
Hey, move more!
If you're doing that hard, I can't...
I'm gonna feel it!
You're hitting my deepest spot...
I can't stand it anymore!
You've got some confidence, haven't you?
I can feel your ejaculated juice inside of my womb.
Here, did you see the lines of our body?
It's making a perverted voice.
You're a really good one...
More... More of those strong hips inside of me!
I'm... I'm cumming too...
Try to make my pussy cum as well...!
Don't make that cowardly sound...
I won't let you feel good alone, you know?
I'm going out of my mind...
It feels so good and my hips wont stop moving!
It feels sticky all over, but it's not over yet...
I'm not feeling satisfied yet...
What are you doing? It's not like we've talked before.
I hope you can do it like this in your job as well!
The deep... It's hitting the deep part of my womb's entrance...
My hips is moving by itself...
I'm getting too much excited...
It keeps thrusting inside of me.
I... I really love penis, you know?
This penis is really great!
It's amazing!
It's hot, the inside of my stomach almost melt down!
It's good... just keep it that way... keep thrusting inside me.
Make a release from all of your stress from work!
The rotten penis keeps thrusting inside me...
Do you want to release it?
Say it when you're going to release it!
But, I won't forgive you if you cum by yourself.
The perverted voice is echoing around!
No.. I can't hold it...
Release a lot inside my pussy!
My pussy is beating over it...
The sperm is coming out a lot from your virgin penis...
Even though you're working that hard,
you're still not good enough.
This is the way of my guidance, you know?