Are you awake, Sylvie?
I understood your feelings, Arima-dono.
If I said I wasn't happy... I'd be lying.
You didn't flinch or push me down because of what I said.
Honestly, my heart was beating non-stop.
This is the first time I've felt like a real woman.
My mind is a little confused right now.
I hope you can give me some more time.
Allow me to become myself, and move forwards with you.
Let me borrow the shirt.
I still plan on staying here with you for a while.
Sylvie.
I've got to admit...
When you pushed me down, I was a woman.
Arima-dono.
What are you-
I'm responding to your feelings.
T-That's despicable. I already told you to wait.
Yet you're doing this now...
I can only do this now.
No!
No, stop it.
Original Video Animation
Vol. 1: "Spending the morning with you"
T-That's enough already.
You're always touching that sensitive spot...
If you rub it...
A woman's body...
Why won't it obey my orders?
Wholeheartedly... rubbing inside me.
My mind is blank, I'm...
No, this kind of feeling is...
W-Wait... Teppei...
You shouldn't force yourself to hold it in.
Marchez!
Is this alright, Teppei-sama?
Are you not going to greet her?
The caterpillar has emerged from its cocoon to become a butterfly.
It'll still be hesitant in its first few days.
"Oh, I can fly."
"The world looks different now. It's too bright." Is that right?
Even though it's still that caterpillar from before.
Since you repeat this everyday, even I have memorized some of it.
I don't have the right to be in that world. That's probably it.
You're wrong. I should be the one saying that.
It's a priceless experience for me to stay by your side.
Teppei-sama.
You don't want to be seen, right?
The lady of Van Hossen is someone with abstinence.
Thank you for your intentions.
Is my approach too forceful for a lady who's so conservative?
Rather than your gratitude, I'd prefer to have your forgiveness.
Sorry for the wait, Sylvia-sama.
The car to collect you has been prepared.
Teppei-sama seems to be looking for you.
Did you see him?
Please tell him that I'll be heading home first.
I'll be fine on my own.
OK, as you wish.
Both of you were at the battle hall just now, right?
Yes.
Judging by Arima-dono's expression...
What were you two talking about...
No... it's nothing.
It is part of my duty to stay by Teppei-sama's side and listen to his wishes.
I only feel satisfied when Teppei-sama is happy.
Yuu-san, you've changed already?
S-Sylvie!
It's Arima-sama!
Oh, is that him?
All that's left is... the maid whom you always bring along.
Shameless.
Even though talking to other masters and maids is part of etiquette,
you must still know your place, Arima-dono.
Aren't you embarrassed? Doing something like this...
Even though we serve you, you treat us without prejudice.
Natural kindness like that is Teppei-sama's biggest charm.
But I hope you'll allow me to carry out my duties.
The next head of the Arima family shouldn't be underestimated by others.
I'll be at fault if I make you worry.
That shy personality of yours...
I hope you'll allow me to fix that.
If by blindly following your orders...
...I can make you understand your position, that'd be great.
Disgusting... This is definitely unforgivable.
And I can't be forgiven either.
There's no chance of being forgiven.
The dirtiness of those remaining memories of the girl who has sworn herself to you...
How does she do it? Like this?
I can't forgive myself for thinking about tying you down after just blowing you once.
Especially...
I can't forgive you for wanting to use your body to tie me down.
I can't forgive your despicable actions in toying with me.
Sylvie, doing this at a place like this...
What happens if someone sees you?
A maid serving her master... Why should I think about it so much?
It feels slightly different when I use my breasts...
It's hot...
I do have some experience.
My father told me women should know a little about things like this, so he gave me some dirty books.
This is something you would do at night.
How is it? Does it feel weird?
Ah... no...
It's fine if you like it.
Your attitude is finally changing into that of a guest.
Am I cute?
Compliments like "cute"... I don't really... like it.
But if you look at me with such anticipation,
I can't help but answer your feelings.
How does it feel if I do it like this?
I don't really know how to do it to make it feel more comfortable.
Please tell me.
Is this alright?
What? It got bigger... and it's so hot.
Sorry, I can't hold back anymore.
A substance that creates life...
I didn't think it'd be so hot.
It feels warm.
Arima-dono!
W-What are you doing? Please stop!
Why?! I thought it'd be over once the male came.
But the girl isn't done yet...
You absolutely can't.
We just did it last night... doing it again is...
I have to reward Sylvie's love for me.
If so, positions will once again...
P-Please stop it at once... Arima-dono!
"Teppei"... Didn't you call me that last night?
I can't, something like that...
I already said it last night.
That's totally like lovers.
Lovers...
Please stop.
It's so deep, so hot, if you put in there...
But... you can't. I can't respond to those feelings of yours.
So, don't come, you can't!
I already said no, but why does it still feel so hot, so huge?
Wait... huge? That's bad!
You came so many times last night... you can't do it again today!
Something like that... you definitely can't!
Just now, it quivered a little. If you don't stop now...
Oh no, it's getting bigger... You mustn't... Hurry up, hurry up!
What's the meaning of this?
You didn't listen to me and came so much inside me.
You're still in me? Again? N-No way...
It's barely even two days.
He's only someone who did it with me...
Why am I so manipulated by him?
Could this be...
It must be part of Father's plans.
Yesterday morning...
Teppei-sama.
Something urgent has come up. Sorry to disturb you.
What time is it now?
7:05 AM.
I know you're very tired, but please.
Wake up. I don't have the power to decide what to do in a situation like this.
Making a girl wait... That's hardly something a gentleman would do.
Sorry to bother you this early in the morning, Arima-dono.
Good morning, Teppei Onii-chan.
Papa, you know, won't be home for today and tomorrow because of work.
During this period of time, please let me and Onee-chan stay here!
Who?
I'm standing right in front of you, so don't ask.
Still as sharp as always... What a dishonest person.
I only got told yesterday, so I'm really troubled as well.
Don't say it as if you don't want it.
Onee-chan is such a tsundere.
It's true that our parents gave birth to both of us,
so we should accept what we've been told to do, value such feelings and live on.
However, parents still don't have the right to decide our fate.
Isn't that right?
Do you really hate being my fiancée?
I'm slightly hurt.
That attitude is your problem!
If you had declined it directly...
I love you, Sylvie.
Isn't it about time you regretted it?
You said those words on the spur of the moment, didn't you?
I'm a girl born to a family of honourable knights with the right to succeed the throne.
I have an inevitable responsibility to my country.
It's not permitted, be it bounded or unbounded.
You're actually forcing yourself on me. Don't you feel despicable?
The most important thing right now is for you to understand my feelings.
I feel troubled if you force me like this.
My resolve is absolute. If you think a few words will work...
That's why...
Arima-dono!
We, the nobles, exist to guide the people.
Do you realise you have thrown away your freedom?
That's foolish.
You... actually developed... a bestial desire... towards someone like me?
Don't use words like "bestial desire"...
It's too sad.
No...
Such violent behaviour... Do you want me to hate you?
As long as you're by my side, Sylvie, I don't mind even if you treat me like scum.
So you also want to ignore how I feel by doing this?
What we're about to do... is ugly and dirty.
If you've considered our respective positions, all the more you shouldn't.
If you've been tainted, can you go back to being a girl?
I'm no longer a child. You're about to turn me into a woman.
You're not thinking about backing down right now, are you?
I might turn into an annoying woman. I won't forgive you for taking my first time away.
I'll make you pay for it with your entire life.
I'll always tie you down.
We're connected...
Arima-dono and I are one now.
You're coming... It's tearing me apart...
Your hot thing is... coming!
Inside me... it's burning. Why... my body from the inside...
You're about to set me alight... It's getting numb.
It's moving.
It's moving... Your rod is moving inside me!
You're such a terrible person for making me suffer like this.
No, it's all connected...
I'm totally exposed.
So hot... It's tearing me apart... It's almost surging into my head.
Oh no, I don't want to be making such dirty noises.
What's this? I'm losing myself... It's scary.
What are you going to do to me?
Stop it, Sylvie. If you make it so tight, it might go off anytime.
Don't say such foolish... such strange things.
I'm different from you. I'm not so shameless to desire for you.
More... more... forever together as one!
No way.
You're using so much force, it's hot...
Soon the only thing I'll be able to feel is the heat!
I'm feeling faint from the heat.
My consciousness... is melting.
The hot thing is coming... inside... right inside me!
No, that's not me, no!
So hot... It's scalding me.
Your seed is flowing into me.
It's hot... I'm about to be consumed by your heat!
It got bigger again!?
But you already came... So why again?
Just what are you...
This many emotions... I might not be able to take it.
You didn't like it?
I don't dislike it.
I only said I couldn't take it.
Idiot.