This is troublesome...
What is so troublesome?
N-No, it's nothing.
Everyone is enjoying the private beach to their heart's content at the moment.
How about we join them, Kaede-san?
Yeah, well... maybe...
Well, how about I take over and look after our luggage?
It'll be fine!
This is a private beach, so no one else is around.
No, I mean, I don't feel too well...
Huh? Kaede-san, is it by any chance, that you can't swim?
H-How rude! I can swim a little if it's in a pool!
It's just that... the ocean is a bit...
If that's the case, I'll come too!
Then you'll be fine, right?
Y-Yeah, I guess...
If you insist, Ryuuichi-kun...
Ryu-Ryuuichi-kun, don't you dare let go!
You'll be fine!
It's still shallow here.
That's true, but...
I-I just stepped on something?!
H-Hey, if you stick that close to me, I'll...
Hey-!
What is this?
Even though you said that you'll escort me,
you were actually this hard down here!
N-No, this is...!
We shouldn't be doing this!
What's this? Could you be peaking already?
That's not it, but...
D-Doing such things here-!
I see. Then, does that mean it's fine if we were to change location?
Presented by Shikkaku
I may not be as big as Kyouko-san or Manami-san, but...
But my breasts are quite a sight too.
A-Are we really going to do this?
Oh, it's much harder than before!
You're getting excited just by looking at me, aren't you?
I-I'm sorry, I...
It's fine, since I'm the same way.
Huh?
See? I'm this wet already.
This is because of your penis...
That's why I'm...
Ryuuichi-kun-!
Ryuuichi-kun!
Kaede-san...!
T-That's it! You're quite good at this!
Y-You can do it harder!
R-Right there-! That's it!
Good, that feels good!
More, more-!
D-Don't lick me in such places!
It feels so good!
More!
Amazing-! It's amazing!
That's quite the tongue technique!
Ka-Kaede-san, I...
Of course, there isn't any need to hold back.
Kaede-san...
Then, I'll...
H-Hurry up!
Y-Yes!
That's it, that's it-!
I-It's so deep-!
I-It's so good! It's amazing!
Do it harder!
Lick me! Lick me!
Lick my breasts! That's it!
My pussy feels great as well!
I-It's really hot inside of you, Kaede-san!
I-Is that so? Does it feel good?
That's it; I feel good too!
It's just as I had heard. Your penis is the best!
Eh?
I can tell by watching Chinatsu-kun and Manami-san.
They've all been awfully lively lately.
This feels much better than what I had anticipated!
It feels amazing, Ryuuichi-kun!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum-! I'm gonna cum!
I came so much...
Ryuuichi-kun, that was amazing.
Do you still want more?
Hey, Kaede-san.
Chi-Chinatsu-kun?!
It's not nice to hog him all by yourself.
You should share with others.
That's right!
Since we're like family, lets all get along!
Ryuuichi-san, it looks like you've done it with all of us now!
Ma-Manami-san, why did you tie my hands?
Oh I see!
So you finally lost your virginity, Lisa-chin!
Congratulations!
H-How do you know that?!
There's no way we wouldn't have noticed when you moan that loudly at night!
First times are great, aren't they?
It's so innocent that it even makes me excited!
Also, who would have thought that she would cum so much?
Maybe Lisa-kun has some interesting qualities as well?
J-Jeez! Don't say such weird things!
Ryuuichi-kun also remembered about Lisa-chan the next day,
so he could masturbate!
M-Mom! Stop that!
Mom is too erotic!
O-Onee-chan, did you perhaps...?
It couldn't be helped!
Ryuuichi-kun's cock was too cute! So on impulse...
On impulse? While only wearing an apron?
That's amazing!
You were saying things like "cock" and "pussy" the whole time..
Just as much as Manami-san when she was doing it!
I felt that I wanted to do whatever would make Ryuuichi-kun feel good!
I came so much too!
Can you put it in my butt next time?
Eh?!
Is that okay, boy?
Hey, what are you-?
Quiet.
This is punishment, so you'll have to pay for it!
D-Don't do that! If you touch me there now, I'll-!
You just came before so you're quite sensitive, aren't you?
What beautiful breasts!
Manami-san-! That's too much!
Amazing!
You're dripping wet here!
Your pussy is soaking wet, Kaede-san!
That's amazing boy! It feels great!
It's amazing! I'm gonna cum!
I can't hold it anymore!
Chinatsu-san, this is amazing! It's clinging to me!
It's fine! It's fine, boy! Do me harder!
Boy, you've kind of... got better at this...!
I'm about to cum! I'm gonna cum!
I can't stop it!
I'm cumming!
No!
Amazing...
To think he would put it into her ass...
Does it feel good?
That's no good, Lisa-chan.
You would hurt yourself if he were to put it in right away.
You have to get used to it over time.
Don't-! Onee-chan, this is...!
You're so cute, Lisa-chan...
Onee-chan... Onee-chan, don't-!
This feels so good...!
No!
Lisa-chan...
Well then, we should get you accustomed to this first.
O-Onee-chan... I-I'm gonna cum again!
Wonderful, Lisa-chan. You've got a nice expression there...
Ah, now that Onee-chan has seen your aroused face...
I've started to feel kind of weird...
You're so cute, Lisa-chan...
Now then, Lisa-chan...
Onee-chan's breasts... Her breasts...
You're so cute, Lisa-chan. You can suck Onee-chan more.
Thank you Onee-chan, I love you!
I-I've always wanted to touch your breasts at least once.
Is that so?
How are they? Are they delicious?
Yes, really delicious...
I'm so happy, thank you.
Well then, how about we get started?
L-Lisa-chan!
That's it, Lisa-chan. Lick me more! Make me wet!
No-! Stop that, Manami-san!
How does it feel to be played with by another woman?
Does it feel good?
I-It feels really good!
Where exactly does it feel good?
My breasts! My breasts feel so good!
Jeez, that's what I've just started touching!
Look, it's this place!
The place here that is all w-e-t!
You have to say the lewd places out loud!
What was that?
I didn't hear you!
M-My pus...
Yes?
It's my pussy! My pussy!
My pussy that you're playing with feels so good-!
So... please-!
Okay! Well done!
Well then, here's your reward!
Don't do that, Manami-san! That's-!
N-Not so deep-!
No, I'm about to wet myself!
I-I'm going to cum again!
This is good, boy!
Really good! It's so hard!
A-Anal sure is the best!
Do me harder!
This feels good! So good!
This is great!
My pussy, my pussy-!
This feels amazing!
My pussy feels so good!
It's thrusting even deeper into my pussy!
Go on, Ryuuichi-kun!
Thrust! Thrust harder! Do my butt! Thrust it into my butt!
It's so good!
Wonderful! Mom is gonna cum. She's about to cum!
Mom is cumming!
Yeah, right there, Ryuuichi-kun!
I've been played with plenty by Manami-san, and I was wanting something more!
So good! My butt, it feels so good!
I didn't know anal would feel this good-!
Stop! I'm going to cum again!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming-! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum-!
Lisa...
Ryuuichi, Onee-chan has changed me so much...
So I'll be fine if you put it into my butt now.
Look, I've inserted so many...
Ryuuchi, p-put it in...
I want you to finish me... Please...
Lisa...
Good! My butt feels so good, Ryuuichi!
Anal is amazing!
A-Amazing, it feels tingly!
Ryuuchi... Ryuuchi!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I-I'm gonna cum-! I'm about to cum!
Oh my, what a wonderful sunset.
Looks like the whether is going to be clear tomorrow too.
Well then, the sun is about to set.
We should head back to the hotel now.
Sounds good!
We will continue once we've returned to the hotel.
Eh?!
We're going to do it again?!
What are you talking about, boy?
Of course we are!
I want to taste you some more.
Doing naughty things in the bath with everyone doesn't sound all too bad, right?
I haven't been done in the butt yet.
I've finally gotten used to it,
s-so do it properly until the end, you got it?
Everyone here loves you very much!
We won't let you sleep tonight!
I see.
This place...
It's my sweet home!