l've been married to lchiro for 5 years...
We left Tokyo with our daughter and decided to live with his family.
l'll see you later, Mitsuko.
Take care, Honey.
You too, A-chan.
OK Mama.
Have fun with your friends.
OK, bye-bye.
lchiro's family, the Takayanagi, is the longest and oldest traditional family here at this village.
l now bare that honorable family name.
Take care, Kouji and Kaoru.
See you...
Do they hate me?
Mitsuko?
Yes, Mother?
She is married to Tomizo Takayanagi, lchiro's father and brought her son, Kaoru, with her.
Although l call her Mother, she is young and beautiful.
Mitsuko, we're not that different in age so you don't need to call me Mother.
Yes, Mother...oh.
l have a flower class today, so l don't need lunch.
Please take care of the house.
Summer draws near.
When no one is around, l am responsible for the care of my father in law.
l need to go to his room and make sure he takes his medicine and is not suffering.
Father, l brought you some medicine.
Come in.
Excuse me.
How are you feeling?
Mitsuko, can you please help me get up?
Yes, Father.
Father, the medicine.
Sorry to trouble you.
lt's not a big deal.
Mitsuko
Yes?
l'm sorry, but can you wipe off my sweat?
Alright, let me take your clothes off.
Underneath that cloth lies a huge monster!
My heart races as l feel a strange urge running through my body.
When your body is weak your sexual desires grow.
l'm sorry, but can you please stroke my hard penis?
Please, l beg you.
Just this once, promise me!
l know, Mitsuko.
l feel sorry for him...
lchiro would understand.
Or so l told myself and grabbed his...
lt's so hard...
and big!
Suddenly, l blank out and begin to loose sanity.
Get beneath the cloth, touch it directly Mitsuko.
Rub my balls and stroke my son.
lf this was lchiro, he's be done already.
lt's been more than 10 minutes but his thing continues to stand proud as it pulses.
That pulse, vibrating through my body, made my womanhood warm
and l felt myself getting wet...
H...here l go, Mitsuko!
His yellow sperm lands on my face and into my cleavage...
l'm sorry, lchiro.
lchiro, please hold me in your arms tonight.
However, it never happened...
l have to get up early tomorrow.
Besides, we don't want to wake Aya.
Few days later.
Mitsuko, can you please...
W...we had a deal.
lt was just that once.
Was it really?
F...Father, please stop.
lt's not bad or anything...
Besides, you should listen to your elder's wishes.
Promise me....please let this be the last.
l know...
How is it?
And then again...
And again....
Father some how knew that l'm not sexually satisfied and each time we meet, it escalated.
l'm afraid of myself...
lf he comes on to me again....
Father, stop this!
Hey Mitsuko, can you please...
W...we can't. We can't do this anymore, Father.
My cock has been aching for a release since morning.
Please do something about it, Mitsuko.
But...
You have a young and beautiful wife....why?
Mitsuko, a person with your youth can help prolong my life.
Simply licking off your sweat from your armpit makes me feel younger.
F...Father...
Mitsuko, just help me out a bit.
Father, you said that last time and l did it...
Really? l don't remember.
Please help, Mitsuko.
Alright, but this will be the last.
His thing is so big...
Bigger than lchiro's, and longer...
l was always wondering why that young woman married this old man.
She is loved every night by this manly man.
lt's so beautiful...
l can taste it throughout my mouth...
No, l can feel my saliva building up...
So embarrassing...
Damn it, l forgot my ticket.
Are you satisfied now...Father.....
l'm going to my room to change.
Looks like l'm not satisfied yet.
Please finish what you've started.
No!!
Father, this isn't...this isn't what you promised!
Please, no more, no more!!
Just a little, just a little bit inside you.
N...no, don't! Don't!!
No!!!
lt sure went in easily even though you said no, Mitsuko.
lt's so tight around my ''son''!
Father...
Here...here.
No one's here, scream all you want!
No, don't move!
No, give me more!
You're such a cute bride.
Such a waste for lchiro.
How is my big dick, looks like your hole loves it!
Well, how is it?
lf you don't tell me the truth, then...!
And!
l...l'll say it, l'll say it!
Your big thing is so wonder...wonderful!
Better than lchiro's?
Y...yes, yours is....better!
You were great, Mitsuko.
This is not right...
Please keep this a secret from lchiro.
l know, now suck everything out.
Yes, you're so good Mitsuko.
So good that l'm hard again, see.
Father, no more after this.
Father, it's....great!
Cuming...
Cuming....
Cuming, cuming!
l'm...cuming!!
Mr. Takayanagi...
Mr. Takayanagi.....
Hey!
Mr. Takayanagi.
What's wrong, not feeling well?
Need the nurse's office?
l have a headache so l'll go home...
That's not good.
Go home and get some rest.
That rich brat always get off easily.
My head hurts?
His face hurts my eyes!
Recently, l saw the principal and his teacher apologizing to his father.
Looks like they have connections with the mayor and the chief of police.
My Bro said they even have one with the Yakuza.
Asshole needs to die.
Father, please forgive...
What are you talking about Mitsuko. We're just getting started.
B...but...we've been doing this for many hours...
Please, let me use the restroom.
What?
You want to be tickled by a brush you say?
lf you insist!
Cu...cuming.....
Why are your nipples so hard, tell me.
Because...
You get turned on when you're embarrassed!
You're a dirty bride, Mitsuko.
lt's time for my medication.
Stay there until l come back.
lt'll take a while for the medicine to kick in.
No, Father please take off these ropes!
Smell your urine while you wait.
Father's so cruel...
After all that taunting....this is stressful....
Kouji!
No, don't look!
No!!!
What are you doing, stop!
Don't s...suck on it...
N...no, Kouji...don't look!
You're wet with peepee and it's shinny.
Please, don't look Kouji...
lt's embarrassing...
T...that's my....
Vagina, my sister's vagina....
Sto....it's really dirty, Kouji....!
Ass, my sister's ass...
No, don't lick such a place....
Thanks, Kouji...
lt's so big...
lt's so big, thick and the shape....
No, if such thing goes inside me...
K...Kouji, d...don't.
Anything but that...
You proudly shacked your ass in front of Dad
Do you hate me that much!?
That's not...
This can't....Kouji and l are siblings.
Even if we aren't bonded by blood!
This can't...!
Even if it is forced!
We can't do this!
Because it's going to feel good!
He came without sticking it in....?
Kouji, was this your first time...?
D...don't make fun of me!
Damn this cunt!
Who gives a shit about the hole Dad and Brother has used!
l'll use your.....Ass!
S...stop!
Hold on, l'm almost ready...
l'm inside my Sister's ass...
Sis, your ass feels great!
Your stretched out ass welcomes me in deeper.
lt's great!
My butt....
What, do you like it up the ass, Sis?
My Bro would flip if he sees this.
D...don't, talk about l...lchiro.
l'll touch your clit too, so cum like what you did in front of Dad!
M...my butt...
My butt...l'm cuming!
Sis....
My only wish was to have a small but happy life with lchiro and Aya...
Why has the wheels turned this way...
What am l to this family?
Am l a sex doll for Tomizo and Kouji?
Am l here just to relieve other's sexual needs?
Am l a Mistreated Bride?