Ryuuichi! Don't be so irresponsible.
I know!
What are you saying so suddenly?
You had s-sex with Chinatsu-san and Manami-san, right?!
Your d-dick has been rubbed and licked by Chinatsu-san, right?
That’s because Chinatsu-san, she was the first to...
What are you saying, even though that was your first time, you were moving your hips and e-ejaculating a lot.
You're really dirty Ryuuichi.
You watched it?
Even if you don't have a place to stay, it's weird to stay in a house full of girls!
You even got a hard on looking at Manami-san’s boobs while bathing with her.
I couldn't help it, that’s why...
You even let her say dirty words while having sex, didn't you?
Like d-dick, p-pussy, a-anal...
That was Manami-san’s request.
She said she'd get more excited that way.
Are you stupid?!
But there’s one more thing that I can’t forgive.
What?
You watched it, right?
Watched what?
That is... You watched me... masturbating.
Eh?! That’s... Umm... it's...
Masturbate...
It's your fault too.
You didn’t close the door...
You should also ^*#()%E*#!
Huh?
I said... you should let me see you masturbating.
What?
That way we’ll be even.
What’s that?
This is a problem, how can I tell her to make her stop.
I got it.
If you want it that much, how about a side dish?
Side dish?
Yes, a side dish.
If you let me see you masturbating, then I will accept your request.
She’ll give up with this.
Sure.
What?
I said sure.
I’ll let you watch me masturbate or whatever.
In exchange, you must masturbate too.
Do you understand?
Y-Yes.
Oh my, another serious matter again.
H-How about this?
Even though you say that...
You should also start doing it.
I think we should stop this.
This is not good.
What are you saying?
I'm even going this far and you’re still complaining?
I-I’m sorry.
If you’re a man, then take off your pants as a man!
Wow...
Kyuuichi's dick is getting bigger.
He got turned on while watching me masturbate.
Wow...
I’m embarrassed.
It's so smelly.
What a dirty smell.
I’m feeling weird.
No...
Misa, you got horny by the smell?
Is it not ok?
I got...
Is it weird?
Am I weird?
You’re not weird.
I’m like this too.
I’m... feeling...  so... good... now...
If I watch... Kyuuichi's... no... Masturbating...
Wow... amazing.. it's like..
I’m feeling it.
It feel so good... No...
This... No...
Cum with me.
Cum with me Ryuuichi!
Squirt it on me!
Please squirt the sperm on me!
Wow... what a smell.
So it's like this...
Wow... it's still big...
Misa...
If you do that...!
Ryuuichi... Ryuuichi...
No...
Ryuuichi... it's so good.
Misa... I can't...
Okay... but do it gently...
I’m... it's... still my first time.
Okay, don’t worry.
Misa’s pussy is all wet.
You dummy, don’t say such dirty things.
I’ll forgive you because you’re Ryuuichi.
Be gentle...
O-Okay...
I never knew Misa was this cute.
Here I come.
Okay.
As I thought it's tight.
O... Ouch!
Ouch! Don’t move.
Okay... I understand.
Should I pull it out?
Don’t move I said.
Okay...
I think it’ll be alright after a little longer.
Okay... I’ll stay put.
Ryuuichi... thank you... I'm sorry...
It's ok... let's take this slowly.
Ryuuichi...
Hmm?
Try pulling it out slowly.
Are you alright?
Yes, I think.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
Don’t force yourself.
Ryuuichi.
Try putting it in again.
Do you think it's okay already?
I think so.
Then I’ll put it in slowly.
Sorry, does it still hurt?
Yes, but it's better now, you can keep going.
Ryuuichi.
Okay.
Misa!
Just continue...
Are you okay?
Yes I am.
Don’t force yourself.
Thanks but it's alright.
Sure?
It's good.
It's just my first time but...
Wow... it's so good.
It really feels so good
Ryuuichi it's so good
More, more...
I’m really doing it...
I’m having my first time with Ryuuichi.
I’m really doing it.
It's rubbing inside.
If you squeeze that much, I’ll...
It's alright, you can release it.
Until the end.
But...
Please, let's...
Misa!
I’m going to cum! I’m going to cum!
Hey Ryuuichi
How was I?
That’s... I mean... Compared with Chinatsu-san and Manami-san
Compare what?
I mean of... my... pussy, was it good?
What?
I said, was my p-p-pussy good?
Don’t make me say it so many times.
So cute...
Yes, Misa’s pussy was very good.
Ouch!
Ouch...
Why did she slap me?
Even though she’s the one who’s asking.
But...
I said, was my p-p-pussy good?
I didn’t think she had such a cute side.
Oh my, I'll want a side dish if I think of it.
Ryuuichi-kun, I brought the laundry.
Oh...
This is...
This is the end.
I have made excuses to mom to not make her mad.
But now... I really have to get out of this house.
Huh?
You should close the door if you do something like that.
Mom?
Don’t worry.
I will help you.
Hey wait, this is not good.
But Ryuuichi-kun's dick is hot already.
Look.
It's so hard and...
It's wet at the tip.
Mom!
This is not good, even though we’re not blood related...
Hey wait...
Thanks for the meal.
Ryuuichi-kun, you don’t have to hold back.
I’ll take it all, whenever you want to do it.
I’ll do anything to make you satisfied today.
Anything.
Mom...
How’s this attire?
Mom... you’re beautiful.
Ryuuichi-kun.
No...
You pervert.
Sorry mom.
It's because I'm... I'm...
Oh my...
Even though you just released it a while ago.
You’re already this hard.
Your dick is tough.
It's so hot.
Come here.
Stir my pussy with your sturdy dick.
Okay then...
Here I come Mom.
Good, it's so good.
Ryuuichi-kun, it's so good.
You know, I wanted to do it with Ryuuichi-kun...
Have sex with Ryuuichi-kun...
I wanted to have sex with you.
Ryuichi-kun...
I love you Ryuuichi-kun.
More, thrust into me more.
Penetrate me faster.
It good, it's so good.
Ryuuichi-kun’s dick... Ryuuichi-kun’s dick is...
my...
thrusting in my pussy.
Stir my pussy...
Mom...
It's so slippery.
It's so erotic.
Sorry.
For feeling so good.
Good...
It's coming!
I feel it so deep.
Wow it's so good.
My pussy... my pussy...
Mom, you’re amazing.
You can do it in the ass too, right?
Your right.
I wanted my ass to be penetrated by Ryuuichi's dick.
Good...
Good... It's so good...
The boobs and the ass...
It's so good.
Mom, the tip of the vibrator is touching...
S-Sorry, I can’t hold it any longer.
I can’t stop.
Good...
Thrust my ass more
It's so good.
How good.
Touch... Touch my boobs more.
The ass...
The pussy...
Mom, don’t touch that part.
Here’s the return.
Mom.
Mom, this part is the best!
I see, so my pussy, my pussy is the best.
I’m happy.
Okay, you can release it anywhere you want.
Anal, pussy, mouth, anywhere Ryuuichi-kun wants to.
You can release it.
It's coming... It's coming.
It's coming.
Release your sperm inside my pussy.
Release it.
Ryuuichi-kun's dick...
Release it!
I’m cumming... I'm cumming.
I’m cumming.
The sperm is coming inside....
It's coming inside my pussy.
Mom...
You made such a mess.
You’re such a bad boy.
I’ll clean it up.
Mom!
How troublesome.
I see, what a nice body you have, Manami-san.
Anything fits you perfectly.
Chinatsu-san, it fits you perfectly too.
I also bought a new one.
W-What happened to you?
Chinatsu-kun won a prize in the lottery.
What?! You kidding?! Really?! That's amazing!
It’s to a resort hotel and a private beach on the south island!!
I can’t just stand here, I’ll go buy some swimsuits!
Have a safe trip!
She’s energetic.
The sea, huh?
This is going to turn out to be a problem.