National Mock Exam
Result Announcements
She really is a model student.
I've heard from rumors that she's a snob.
I guess she's on a different level compared to us.
Wearing the facade of a model student in public wasn't something I wanted.
To be honest, I really wanted to be friends with everyone.
Renketsu Houshiki
ORIGINAL ANIMATION
Is there supposed to be class in here today?
I wonder what's going on?
Who are you trying to kid?!
Trying to take us for idiots.
It's not like that... I'm... I'm...
Bullying? I should hurry to a teacher-
Ahh, how aggravating. This is why you don't have any friends.
Friends?
Just because you're a little better at studying, you've become arrogant.
Being good with studies but not making friends...
I didn't mean it that way-
Then explain yourself clearly.
I hear that even the girls hate you.
I know that you're always alone.
Aren't you being ostracized?
Just as I thought, you may look pleasant on the outside, but inside, you are a complete mess.
Simply studying and not interacting with anyone else.
Even when we talk to you, you disregard us.
That's why you are so hated.
I-I didn't intend...
Why don't we be your good friends then?
You must be happy, right? To have such many friends suddenly.
N-No... it's alright...
What's wrong? Can't you be friends with us?
That's not...
Then it should be OK, right?
Eh? U-Um...What do you...
It means enjoying each other's company!
No!
Open wide!
S-Stop!
Please let me go!
What's this? Who would have thought that a girl who only studies would wear such plain panties?
Ah, don't you look cute in it?
Wh-Why are you doing this...
Why? Weren't you wanting to be good friends with us?
I-I didn't mean-
When a man befriends a woman,
there can only be one outcome.
N-No! I don't-
We said that we're going to be your friends, so just go along with it.
N-No! No!
Now then, let's get to know each other.
NO!
Don't you have a really loud voice?
It's very adorable too.
But this annoying mouth...
It was my first kiss too...
Shall we get down to business already then?
Wh-What do you-
Stop!
Please stop...
Stop...
No! Don't!
No! Stop!
Don't...
No! Th-This is...
Don't... This...
N-No... Please stop...
I don't want this...
This girl... her panties became soaked the moment she started feeling good.
No...
I-I'm not feeling anything...
I'm almost at my limit.
M-Me too.
Wh-What?
Come on, hold it.
Over here too.
U-Um...
This...
Grasp it more tightly.
That's right, stroke it just like that.
Not there!
Come on, next up is taking it in.
Um...
Taking it in...?
I am next.
Please stop alr-
Alright, I'll be putting it in then.
Pu-Putting it in...
Anything but that...
No... I don't want this... No...
N-No... Anything but that...
Let's be good friends from now on.
No! Stop it now!
But first, there's the hymen, right?
I-It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!
That's something you'll get used to after a few times.
N-No way...
Please...
Take it out...
It hurts! Please...
It hurts...
Not inside... just not inside
Does it feel good?
Still want more?
Yes... I want more...
Yes! Give me more...
I really wanted to see
what was truly left of myself.
Please use this to restrain me...
Then violate me...
Please...
Is this really alright?
Yes.
I am...
I...
Hey! What are you doing over there?
You were not showing up.
What is with that woman?
How should I put it? That she's a 'blind' girl?
What big tits!
Whoever this girl is, she's wearing the uniform of T Girls' School.
What is a lady like yourself doing in a place like this?
Hey you, what's your name?
There's no way she would tell, idiot.
Hey, look at this! This pussy is already overflowing with juices.
What a beautiful shade of pink, and it hasn't been used yet.
Wow, it's my first time seeing something like this.
I can't wait to put my cock inside her!
It's no good. I can't wait any longer!
Me too!
Same here!
Although it's my first time, there are so many men...
Even my ass is being used...
but it feels good!
You guys! What the hell are you doing here?
This place is our...
Ah! How about you gentlemen join us as well?
This woman is a depraved, perverted slut.
Apparently she yearns to be violated, so there's else nothing we can do.
My goodness, young girls these days are really something.
Doing things like this!
I'm gonna shoot my load really soon!
Say, why is this girl doing something like this?
Like I said, it's because she's a fucking slut.
But for her to get acquainted me,
she can't be hiding her face.
Woah, she's super pretty!
Amazing! She's really cute!
I-I'm gonna cum!
M-Me too!
How about shooting it all over her face to experience what it's like?
Agreed! Agreed!
Come on. Over here too.
Amazing...
Semen...
There's so much of it...
Why is a girl like yourself doing something like this?
That's right, and you look so lovely too.
If you don't talk, nobody's going to understand.
Hey! Raise your face.
Are you embarrassed of your face being seen?
Well then, open your mouth!
Come on, come on, come on! Move your waist!
I'm gonna cum again!
Me too!
I'm cumming as well!
Don't be ashamed.
Exposing yourself to be seen like this feels good, doesn't it?
Also...
What is it?
Boss.
There are still plenty of men who want to see you in action.
Come on, stand up. Let everybody have a good look.
Now then, let's have everyone take a good look at you.
Amazing!
Everybody wants to get to know you.
I'm...
I'm... strange...
Being seen by everyone
is great.
I'm coming!
I am coming in front of everyone!
Coming!
COMING!
Haven't had enough, have you?
I am so happy.
Being able to make such good friends with everyone here.
And just like that, I got acquainted with many people.
However...
What's going on?
Eh?! What?
What's with that girl?
Just as I thought, that girl and us
are on entirely different levels.
In the end, however,
what I hoped for was to have female friends.