It feels so good!
That's great! Give me more.
~The Sin of Desire & Disgrace~
Second Half
More! Lick there more!
Great!
Nozomi, it feels good.
Mistress Ayano, you are so beautiful.
That's great. Lick more.
Please don't stop.
What's going on there?
The girls are having fun.
Mistress Ayano, will you use this?
Yes. Do it. Give it to me both ways.
Okay. Lift your legs a little more.
Yes. Don't tense up. Here I go.
Good!
This is great!
Let me get a peek, too!
Just a little.
Out of my way!
Make me feel better. Hurry.
Yes Mistress Ayano.
More! More!
Good!
More and harder!
Nozomi. You do me too!
From the front this time.
Yes, mistress Ayano.
Great!
Miss Ayano!
You satisfied yet?
Just a little more.
Delicious.
Me too.
Nozomi, how good did it feel
to have sex with that detective?
I watching you the entire time,
when you were having sex.
That's well...
Why did it have to be you?
Why could it not be me?
Mistress Ayano...
I've been waiting all this time!
I've been a good girl all this time!
Mistress Ayano!
Why won't Father play with me? Why?
Mistress Ayano.
I'm so Ionely.
I want to play with Father.
Mistress Ayano. Please don't cry.
We'll play with you instead of Father, okay?
Father.
Satoru, you did it
with that maid, didn't you?
Emm... yep.
I swear, you're so bad
when it comes to women!
Jewel searching?
That's what it was supposed to be,
but I can't find any clues.
What was that suspicious passageway?
I don't know.
It doesn't look like it was made recently.
Probably the ancestors
of the Nakakoujis made it.
You mean the late Master?
No, it's older than that.
They were small, but this family had a name.
It was probably for safety.
Or perhaps the founder was into that kind
of stuff in the first place.
Do those girls have anything
to do with the case?
They have to have some connection.
But I don't know.
Something's not right.
Not right?
Yeah.
That's right. Did you bring that
database file I asked about?
Yes.
What are you looking for?
I just have a certain hunch about this.
That's the lady we just saw having sex!
Why is a private tutor doing
in a database for criminals?
I get it now.
How is she doing?
She has calmed down now.
I put a little something in her drink...
now she's getting some rest.
I see. You must be hard for you, Shibata.
Having such a troublemaking master.
It's nothing, I'm planning to serve her as
long as this body will let me.
I'm envious of her...
for having a person care for her
as much as you.
You yourself must have
had a great deal of trouble...
as you know, Miss Tanimura,
she can be quite a handful.
I do give you this caution however:
Do not overstrain yourself.
Thank you. It's nice to know you care.
It's you! Don't scare me like that!
What's there to be scared of?
Why are you scared?
Your face, what else could it be?
I'm sorry, madam.
Hey, isn't Mistress Ayano about ready?
What do you mean?
She was pretty out there last night.
She'll be calling you "Mother" soon enough.
If she'd be calling you Daddy?
It hurts.
This isn't the time to be joking!
We got unwanted guests.
Get with it!
Stop that! Get you're hands off me,
you're hurting me!
As long as we can get Ayano,
that old fogey Shibata isn't a problem!
You're the expert, aren't you?
We don't overdo it, we don't under do it,
we just make her ours.
Look who's talking. You seem to be
enthusiastic about Nozomi.
That's right, she's got a body
worth training.
Listen,
it doesn't matter how much you train her
if the most crucial thing isn't working.
Shut up!
I'm worried about that detective.
Keep an eye on him so he doesn't
do anything unnecessary.
I'm going to eat breakfast.
Breakfast?
Wait a second. What about me?
What the hell!
I don't want to be left alone here!
Thank you for the meal.
Nozomi, can you make me
a sandwich later on?
Okay.
This mansion is just too big.
I get hungry just walking around.
No problem, I'll do it.
Master Kido.
This is where you are.
This is the map of the mansion.
I apologize I got it to you so late.
Thanks.
If there's anything else that you need,
please feel free to ask me.
For now, this'll do just fine.
Then I leave the case in your hands.
Mr. Shibata?
Yes.
This yard...
Does it have a small pond over there?
No, there is not one there anymore.
I see.
But there was one before.
The spring dried up,
so we had the pond filled in.
That was approximately 8 years ago.
Detectives are a dime a dozen.
What was the reason you picked me?
An acquaintance suggested you.
There was no particular reason.
Are you sure about that?
Fine, then, I'll leave it at that.
I'll be leaving you now, sir. Excuse me.
Breakfast is served.
It looks so good! Let's eat!
And here's the map
of this gigantic mansion.
What's up?
After you're done eating...
I want you to add
the passageways to this map.
You want me to?
It can be rough. Just make sure it's easy enough for me to read.
All by myself?
I have some business to take care of.
So, I'm off.
No way!
I don't want to walk around
that creepy passageway all by myself!
I beg you, you're the only one
I can count on, Mei.
Yes, I'll do it, I'll do it.
Hello there.
What's wrong?
I'm here to study with a sexy teacher.
How about that lesson
I played hooky from last time?
Aren't we sincere.
Depends on the teacher.
I like sincere students.
It feels so good!
As expected from a beautiful tutor.
What do you mean?
You got a hot body.
You think?
Yeah.
Your students must've been leaping
out of their seats. You naughty teacher.
That's right. Naughty teachers,
always eat their students.
How many students
have you eaten like this?
I don't know. I never counted
how many dicks.
Not how many dicks...
you've eaten female students,
too, haven't you?
Well, I don't mind girls.
I like them for a change.
How was Ayano?
You already did her, didn't you?
How about it?
It doesn't have anything to do with you.
What...
There used to be a pair of con-artists
who made a bundle with clever plans.
The man-woman duo would aim
at rich old people.
First, they would coax their victim
using the woman's body.
When the victim was head-over-heels
about the woman, the man would appear.
Before the victim knew it, his insurance and securities were transferred to the woman.
And the old man,
stripped of everything...
...is placed in a home,
filled with despair.
It's the oldest trick in the book,
but everything's planned out perfectly.
They raked in the cash as the police
scratched their heads.
T-That's an interesting story.
It's hi-tech nowadays,
and our industry made sure...
we're on top of things
with the latest criminal database.
So, what exactly are you getting to?
A beauty and a beast.
I just happened to see you playing
around with Imada.
Plus, a while before you two came
to this mansion...
those con-artists vanished
without a trace.
Bingo!
My job isn't to bust your operations.
I'm cool as long as you don't bother me.
Don't worry. Nothing's going to happen.
I promise.
Why's that?
We finally were able to get in,
but the previous Master died before we could act...
...and the successor is that little girl.
Our plans were ruined.
All you need to do is switch to the missy
and set things on track, right?
But this mansion is no good.
This mansion is encompassed
with some sort of mysterious magic.
I think Mistress Ayano is the cause.
Ayano is?
She may look young,
but she's actually fairly old.
There was no need to train her.
She was already fully developed.
She's making me crazy
just by being with her.
So? Where did you hide
the jewel in question?
Jewel?
You guys didn't steal it?
There's no point to stealing that.
We planned to take
the entire mansion in the first place.
I see. So that's how it goes.
I know what's up now.
You've got to be kidding me!
I'm not going along
with this farce any longer!
Mei! Screw this place!
We're going home! Pack our stuff!
I shouldn't have asked her to do that.
Mr. Shibata. This was all your doing,
wasn't it?
You knew everything from the start.
Think as you will.
This ain't no joke!
You have a right to be angry.
But first, visit Mistress Ayano.
She has been in bed all day.
Would you please pay her a visit?
But...
I beg of you. For the sake
of Mistress Ayano, pay her a visit.
What kind of relationship did Mistress Ayano
have with the late Master?
They weren't blood-related, were they?
The two were tied together with a love
far deeper than that of a parent-child.
The late Master had everything.
Of course he had money.
Title and honor as well.
But the only thing he was missing
was a family to love and be loved by.
When his parents passed away
and he become...
successor of the Nakakouji name,
he married.
A son was born unto him,
but it did not last very long.
One day, during his life of loneliness,
the late Master asked me an odd question:
"Shibata, how would you
like to raise a fairy?"
A fairy? You don't mean...
That girl is a fairy?
No, it was probably just a figure of speech indicating a girl as lovely as a fairy.
When I first met Mistress Ayano
at the orphanage, she was like an angel.
Without any hesitation, the late Master
took Mistress Ayano in...
and brought her up under his own care.
They both loved each other from
the bottom of their hearts.
I have never seen such a life filled
with such deep love anywhere else.
Those glorious days continued until
the very day Master passed away.
In the end, the fairy was left incomplete.
Again, I beg of you...
please, go and cheer
Mistress Ayano up for me.
Mistress Ayano sees the image
of her father in you...
and is yearning to fulfill those desires.
You just said...
that the late Master had a son, right?
Didn't you say that?
Yes.
And, that's...
Just as you think, sir.
15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
How much more is there?
A fairy?
That mysterious latency she shows
every so often is like that of a fairy.
If the father had created a real fairy
through his own death, then it's an irony.
Looks like your awake.
Why are you here?
Shibata asked me to be here.
He wanted me to cheer you up.
I'm so happy!
Father, you're finally right by my side.
Here we go again.
Listen up. I'm not your father,
you understand that?
Please, hold me like you used to.
Like I said...
No, hold me!
I was so lonely.
I so wanted to see you, Father.
I'm so happy.
Father hold me.
Don't ever let me go.
Ayano.
All right! Lick me more.
Good!
It feels good. I'm so wet.
Yes, lick me, don't stop! It feels great.
You are great...
I can't wait, Father.
Hurry, give it to me, Father!
Father...
Y-You are the best!
Come on! It feels so good.
I am cumming...
That part... No...
Father...!
Looks like this way is a dead end.
What room is this?
A lab or something?
What's this?
Some sort of drug, maybe?
Who the hell are you?
Well... You know... I...
I know. You're with that detective,
aren't you?
What were you doing here?
I haven't done anything...
Tell me!
I said I haven't done anything!
Fine. I'll ask your body. Come here!
May I, sir?
Come in, please.
Have you recalled anything?
I've had a nostalgic feeling
ever since I set foot in this mansion.
But now I remember it clearly.
Is that so?
It was a while back,
probably when I was around 3.
I lived in this mansion.
With Mom and a father
whose face I can't remember.
I barely remember walking
around the island.
We were single-parent family,
but we lived a pretty wealthy life.
When Mom died,
she left me a large fortune.
Tracing it back,
it was the money of Nakakouji.
You called me here to make
me remember that?
The jewel was never lost
in the first place, was it?
No, it wasn't, just as you surmised.
It is right here.
As I thought.
That was some elaborate
performance you put on.
Forgive me for all my lack of courtesy.
I assure you, it was
necessary Detective Kido.
I might as well add another act
of insolence and ask you:
Would you become the successor
to the name of Nakakouji?
I'm a detective hired to find a jewel.
And now, I have found the jewel.
My job is done, it only makes sense
that I go home now.
The Mistress will be heartbroken.
When she wakes up, give her my regards.
So long.
So you're the successor. Fuck that!
No!
Mei!
Is that your partner?
Yeah, it's my assistant,
but looks like she messed up.
You fucker. Why'd you come
back now, you little prick?
Calm down. There's no need for violence.
Shut up!
If you're not going to succeed,
then give the money to me, asshole!
Or else.
Didn't you give yourself out as a clever con-man whose policy was playing it smart?
It all rides on time and place!
You.
What're you doing?
Don't move!
Or you're going to be toast.
You bitch!
You're back-stabbing me?
This house is nothing but evil...
Mr. Kido, I beg you to take charge
of this house, please...
for the sake of Mistress Ayano.
Satoru.
The detective business suits my style.
I'm not the type of character
to become master of this family.
I can't be Dad's replacement.
I'm not the person you're looking for.
Father, you're leaving?
You can't go.
I've been a very good girl.
Father, you're leaving me again?
I don't want that, I'm so lonely.
Don't leave me by myself, Father.
I'm not your Father.
Forget about the past and find
new happiness elsewhere.
That's the only thing I can say right now.
No!
Look out!
What happens?
It's a fire, run!
Miss Ayano!
Hey, hurry up!
It looks like, I can't part
from this house, either.
Are you certain?
Yes.
Satoru, what are you doing,
let's get out of here!
Satoru! Satoru!
And so this case ended.
The island, the people, my own past...
they all disappeared with the flames...
like a wonderful imagination.