Hey you, are you Detective Kido?
Yes, I am.
Are you from the Nakakouji mansion?
Yes. I am Imada.
I have come to pick you up.
Mr. Imada, is that it?
Yes, it is.
It really is a Ione island.
Yes, this is the only boat that ever docks there.
So that's it.
Looking back three days ago,
it all started from a single letter.
Satoru, did that letter work?
Yeah, looks like it.
All right!
What kind of case is it?
This is just a missing item case.
Missing item?
Yeah.
In regards to the family property,
a missing article was confirmed.
Therefore, I would like to request
a search for the mentioned article.
It sounds like a rich person wrote it.
Well, it definitely isn't a normal person.
This paper's high quality,
maybe even special order.
Plus, it's sealed with wax on top of that.
You're right.
And it covers my travel expenses
with a ticket to boot.
Incredible! The guy must
really be rich!
Hey, you're going to accept the case, right?
But this place is in the middle of nowhere.
Can you even believe that?
What are you whining about?
The electric bill, gas bill, water bill, credit card bill, and the rent.
And to top it all off,
I've yet to get my last bonus!
What? I'm always paying your bonus
with my body.
No! Don't lick there!
This has its own benefits.
But sometimes, I want cash as my... bonus
...please.
Kido... Kido! It's great!
Is it my illusion?
Master Satoru Kido.
I have been waiting for you.
I am the butler, Jusaburo Shibata.
Right. So you wrote the letter, then?
I certainly did.
Welcome to the mansion of Nakakouji.
And so, I was led to this strange, beautiful,
almost illusionary world by a single letter.
Without knowing it was my fate.
~The Sin of Desire & Disgrace~
First Half
A jewel, you say?
Yes.
Half a year ago, my previous master
passed away...
and I investigated his fortune
as requested in his will.
But of all the property he owned,
the most important one was missing.
That jewel you mentioned?
Yes, tradition has it that Nakakouji's successor is to be entrusted with this,
the proof of inheritance.
Proof of inheritance?
Yes. It has no meaning in the eyes
of the law, but it is a family treasure.
It's important you understand this.
I see. What does it look like?
This is it. The only known picture.
It is a large ruby set in a ring.
I hear is a very rare type,
called "the blood of a phoenix."
A ruby. Where exactly was it kept?
For many years it was hidden
in the study of the master.
It was locked away in a safe
with other valuables.
But it was only that which disappeared.
So you want me to find it,
is that correct?
That is correct.
But still, something's not quite right.
It's hard to believe that a petty thief
came all the way here to this lone island.
Even if he did, there are plenty of other
valuables that could easily have been taken.
It doesn't explain why
just the ring would disappear.
So you say, that you think it was
the work of an insider?
I didn't say that.
For example, the late head of the family
could've hidden it somewhere.
I don't understand.
Why would he do such a thing?
I'm just giving a possibility.
I'll need to investigate...
Shibata! Stop it!
I thought I told you to throw away that jewel.
This is the current head of the household,
Mistress Ayano Nakakouji.
Mistress Ayano, this is the detective
I was talking about, Master Satoru Kido.
Nice to meet you.
Shibata! I am the successor to the name of Nakakouji...
and I say forget about that rock!
No, Mistress, I cannot do so.
Old men are so very stubborn!
A detective. A real one.
He looks plain if you ask me.
You may be my just my type.
I hope you find what you're looking for.
She's a beautiful young lady.
Yes. She is very dear to me.
For her sake as well
I want you to do everything within your power
to bring the missing jewel here, please.
I leave everything
in your hands, Detective Kido.
I understand. I do my best to find it.
I am Nozomi Watase, the maid.
I'm at your service, Master Kido.
Ask me anything.
Nice to meet you too, young lady.
I will lead you to your room.
Actually, I want to check out the study first if convenient
Okay. This way, then.
Miss Watase, how long have you been here?
It has been nearly a year, I believe.
So the late master was still alive
when you came here, right?
Yes. I was finally able to live...
thanks to the fact that he took me in.
What does that mean?
I lost both of my parents
at the exact same time.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have asked.
This is the study he used.
Hi.
Excuse me! I wasn't aware
you were in here.
It's okay, I was just looking something up.
This is the detective that will
look for the late master's ring, Master Kido.
This is Mistress Ayano's private tutor,
Kaoru Tanimura.
Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure
to meet you too, Miss Tanimura.
You can call me Kaoru if you want.
Is that so. Then you can call me Satoru.
Hey, I'll show him around here.
So, you can leave now.
Very well, then.
Excuse me.
Thanks for you help.
You're a live-in private tutor
at this mansion?
Yes. Mistress Ayano is physically
weak and can't go outside often.
That's why I come here to tutor her.
Then that must be a lot of work.
No, actually it's not a lot of work.
If anything, it's boring.
There's no where to have fun here.
And one other thing:
There's no young men around, either.
Sometimes I feel like something stimulating.
Satoru? What's wrong?
It's very strange.
I feel like I've seen
this scenery before.
Come, you must be tired.
Why don't you sit down here?
No, I'll pass. That job's already been taken.
I'm sorry, but I need to investigate,
so could you please leave me by myself?
Fine!
Go ahead. Take your time.
That's the feeling I had since I set foot
in this mansion.
Déjà vu? Really weird.
All these books are first editions.
What a nice collection.
Master Kido, dinner is now being served.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Mr. Shibata, can you tell me
where Miss Ayano is?
Mistress Ayano is not feeling well.
Today, she said that she will
not have dinner.
I see. You must be worried.
Yes. I certainly am.
What's up with these two.
They don't look the bit worried.
Now, then.
A hidden passage?
That's some mechanism.
My compliments to the maker.
How's that? Does that feel really good?
I can't understand.
How about here?
There...
How's it? Is it good here?
Or here?
You like it?
Here too? You feel it here, too?
Your tits are getting hard.
Use your hips more!
Grind it more and move it around.
Still not enough. Let me see.
I'll make you feel more ecstasy.
Here it is.
Good, I'll give you something fatter.
That's it. All you have to do is feel good.
Remember where it feels the best.
And pass this ecstasy straight on to Ayano.
That's the least I can do, being impotent.
Give me more...more!
I'd like to stick around for more,
but unfortunately...
it's back to the investigation for me.
This place is bigger than I thought.
How far does this actually go?
A dead end?
This is...
Father?
Father.
Is that you, Father? I was lonely.
Ayano was so lonely, Father!
Hey, Miss Ayano!
Was it because I was a bad girl
that you didn't come?
Father?
Hey, what are you doing?
Miss Ayano, stop that.
Miss Ayano!
Snap out of it!
What was that all about?
Mr. Shibata, She called me Father.
What's going on?
Have you any idea?
I'm trying not to
upset the mistress of the house.
I ask of you to not inquire about things
unrelated to your job.
It's a strange place.
I can't handle it on my own.
Yeah, I'll see you soon.
Mademoiselle.
How do you feel?
I'm fine, thank you.
Is that so?
That's good to know.
But still, do I really look like your father?
Last night...
You know what I mean.
Last night?
Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
Find a jewel. That's all there was to it.
He's hiding something from me.
What does he expect me to do about it?
Miss Watase!
What is the matter?
I just wanted to ask you something.
You can ask anything.
Do you clean the entire mansion yourself?
Yes.
I see. Must be hard work.
No it isn't. It's my job, after all.
You clean the study as well?
No, It is forbidden to touch
anything in that room.
It's off limits for me.
Is that so?
Which means the only person who would know about the hidden passageway is Shibata.
What's wrong?
It's really nothing.
You're trembling.
No, I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
Miss Watase.
Are you being picked on by anyone?
No.
Then why are you trembling so much?
Are you afraid of men?
No, it's not anything of the sort.
Don't be afraid. You can tell me the truth.
I want to help you.
No, it's...
Am I a bother?
No, not at all.
It makes me feel...
...so good.
No, not there!
As I thought.
Because of that weird lotion,
she's become real sensitive.
You want this?
I want it.
What do you want me to do with it?
Pu...
You want me to put it in?
Then before that.
Yes.
This... girl.
It's hot.
Despite her innocent looks,
she's got some technique.
Now it's my turn!
Hurry, give it to me.
All right.
More! More!
Deep! Deep, please!
Master!
Give me more!
More! Harder!
Master... Master.
Mistress Ayano.
Mrs. Kaoru.
Yes?
I have a favor to ask, okay?
Y-Yes.
Nozomi, you come too.
At your service, madam.
I'm so tired!
That wasn't very nice,
telling me to come here suddenly...
and by then end of today at that!
Sorry. I really needed some help.
I paid for the entire commute
all the way here!
The sea at night is cold and scary;
it was hard on me!
I got it. I'll throw in
a special bonus for you.
I won't trust you any more!
In the first place...
I haven't even received
my previous bonus yet!
In the end, the matter was unsettled.
Hey, are you listening?
What could that be?
Who knows.
But I'm pretty interested
to see what it is.
I can't say it'll be interesting
for a woman to watch.
I'm interested too, you know!
More!
Make me feel even better.
This is...