I love this!
Keisuke!
Onii-chan...
Father was diagnosed with cancer
It won’t be long...
That’s why... Mother told me to hurry and get married...
As she cried her eye out.
Sake
Kasugano
Spirits
Domestic Beer
Genuine Sochu
We are very glad.
I didn't think he’d actually do it.
I haven’t really had a girlfriend before.
I was at a loss at what to do.
Keisuke’s too good to go to waste.
It was really just a coincidence that the marriage proposal was given to us.
And before I knew it, her parents already accepted it.
She’s not pretty at all...
Onii-chan’s fiancé.
You think so? I really think she’s a wonderful girl.
She's perfect for a goof-off like Keisuke.
But Keisuke’s still only 29. To just arrange a marriage...
Misaki. stop your complaining.
Help me carry out the food.
She and Keisuke are ten years apart from each other.
She grew up later in my life, so I may have spoiled her a bit too much.
Ever since she could walk she’d never want to leave her brother.
Mom, don’t tell them that...
Oh, we’re in front of Tomoko-san. so no wonder he’s embarrassed.
Don’t they get along great?
She doesn't have any siblings in the house, so I'm sure she s a little jealous.
Renketsu Houshiki
ORIGINAL ANIMATION
Onii-chan...
I love you...
Good...
Onii-chan...
You're rubbing...
My clitoris.
Good...
It feels wonderful.
I... I...
I'm...
Onii-chan... Onii-chan
I'm... I'm going... I'm going to...
You came before you even went inside me.
Misaki...
always wanted to marry you.
Onii-chan... You love Misaki. don't you?
You're kidding...
We're siblings.
You always... watch me in the bath.
You like me at least that much, don't you?
I didn't.... know what else to do then.
You know, you're the only man that Misaki has ever looked at...
Ever since I was born...
You should... get a boyfriend.
Brand Sake                              Domestic Beer                                        Genuine Sochu
Kasugano
Spirits
Keisuke...
Tomorrow we're going to meet her parents.
We have a lot of things to do, so we'll be out for a while.
OK...
And be sure you aren't late.
It'll be the first time we meet Tomoko's father.
I know...
Hey, where's Misaki? Her room?
Misaki has been sneaking around the shop on her cell phone all day.
It could be her boyfriend since she always uses the shop's phone too.
Who is he? Where's he from?
Where have you been, dear? She's had one for a while.
Huh? A game? I have things to do tomorrow, so I can't.
I'm sorry. I'll see you next week.
You said that I should get a boyfriend, so...
Your sister doesn't really follow along with your family or you, does she?
Your sister's so young and pretty so I was surprised...
But I...
Wasn't really...
Received very well by her, was I?
Well anyway, would it be possible to move up the marriage date?
I want... I want to hurry and get married.
He asked me to go out with him a while ago.
Guys from the soccer team are well-liked.
They're really popular with the girls.
So some annoying guy you met on a Sunday is your boyfriend?
Some fake, insinuating prick?
Do you really love her. Onii-chan?
It's because of you that Misaki exists; that I don't love anyone else.
Do you believe me? Misaki was born because you were so lonely by yourself.
Misaki was born to be with you.
Don't say such scary things.
Tomorrow you're going to officially ask to marry her, right?
Maybe Misaki can make it so it doesn't happen.
Misaki...
Not, I'm kidding.
Misaki doesn't want to cause you any trouble, Onii-chan.
You know. Mom and everyone are asleep.
Wa- Misa-
You're already so hard...
It's wonderful.
Onii-chan... does that feel good?
Onii-chan, that's my -
Onii-chan...
Don't, Onii-chan!!
It's embarrassing!
It's such a pretty shade of pink.
Don't. Onii-chan!!
It's embarrassing!
Don't look at it!
Onii-chan!
Coming!
No...
I spilled all of your come!
I'll clean it up.
Don't make... so much noise.
Onii-chan...
Hey...
Are you just going to put it in like that?
You're going to put it inside Misaki?
Onii-ch-
You're... all the way... inside me.
No, don't put anything in my ass!
Stop-
Don't... I'll co- I'll-
I'll come!
Don't... do that to my breasts.
Onii-chan!
It's deep... inside me.
No...
Onii-chan, not so hard...
I'll...
Break apart!
No more!
I'll come! I'm coming!
Does it feel that good?
It does!
I'll come! It feels that good!
Do you really love it that much?
I do! I love how your penis feels!
I love every movement you're making!
Onii-chan! Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
I love you! I love you so, so much!
So much!
Hey, what about you?
Tell me!
Good... Your penis feels so intense!
Good. Keep going.
I'm coming!
I'll release all of it inside you.
Release it!
All of your come. Put all of it inside me!
Misaki is going to come too!
Misaki won't come until you do!
Onii-chan! Onii-chan! Onii-chan!!
Onii-chan... I love you so much...
Keisuke? Are you awake?
We're all leaving. The meeting time's at 3:30, all right?
Don't be late, all right?
All right.
Onii-chan... more...
Not yet, it's still before noon...
But, it's better to be early.
Misaki...
It's time... for me...
Not yet. You're still like that.
And Misaki's still like this.
Good!
Onii-chan!! It's great.
I can't make them wait...
Right now I still have a good hour.
I can talk my way out...
But I absolutely have to leave by 2:30...
M-Misaki, that's enough
Onii-chan, how's this?
Onii-chan!
So much... I'm so tired!
Misaki's pussy is getting so much!
It feels wonderful!
Wonderful!
This is the last... round that I can do.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan!
Hey...
Hey...!
You're going to leave me?
Onii-chan...
Brand Sake                               Domestic Beer                                          Genuine Sochu
Kasugano
Spirits
I heard that Tomoko's father is really strict.
I can't upset him.
I have to hurry...
I have to leave a good impression on him.
Onii-chan, are you absolutely sure you have to go today?
Of course I'm sure...
If you go to see that person today, things will keep going as they are...
And next month will be the ceremony...
I don't want you to... Misaki really doesn't want you to!
Onii-chan... Hey, Onii-chan!
That's enough! Let me go!
I'm sorry, I just thought I'd ask...
I didn't really think you wanted to go.
Misaki wants to be with you forever.
Then, Misaki will be your wife!
You can't. There's no way...
Is it?
I don't look like the rest of the family. And we're far apart in age.
So, if we really wanted to...
The party you have called is not available.
Please leave your name and a message after the tone.
Hello? It's Mom. Misaki, are you there?
Did Keisuke leave yet? If he hasn't, then tell him to hurry!
I know you'll make me a happy woman...
I love you...
I really do have to go.
Everyone's waiting.
I can't screw this up.
No!
Don't go, Onii-chan!
Stop!
Let go of me!
Onii-chan...
I'm sorry...
Hello!? Keisuke!? Are you there!?
It's almost time!
Hey! Keisuke!!
But. I love you... Onii-chan...
I'm sorry...
Onii-chan...