I see, so you keep yourself quite clean down here!
Well done!
Chi-Chinatsu-san, we really shouldn't be doing this!
But... it smells a bit.
Eh?
It smells like a chestnut blossom, or perhaps like a squid.
I-I'm sorry...
There's no need to apologize, but tell me next time!
Eh?
It means that I, Chinatsu-onee-san,
will be your oral lover instead of your right hand.
You're quivering already. That's why young boys are so cute!
Chi-Chinatsu-san!
Your balls are throbbing!
Are you about to cum?
I can tell you're holding it back!
If you make that face, it makes me want to eat your cock...
I-I'm about to-!
Since you're doing your best, maybe Onee-san should be serious...
That's it, you can cum in my mouth like this...
Uh, I'm sorry!
Young boy, you're still so energetic!
Hey young boy,
Eh?
do you want to taste my pussy?
U-Um-!
To tell you the truth, I'm already soaking wet...
See?
Hey... Lick me. Lick my pussy.
I'm gonna rub your cock like this!
Chi-Chinatsu-san-!
Young boy, you're getting hard!
How's this?
Hey young boy, do you wanna graduate from your virginity while we're at it?
Eh?
Like I said, do you wanna have sex? You don't?
N-No! Please do!
I'll make you feel good soon...
Your cock is coming inside me-!
It's sliding deep inside me-!
T-This is amazing! So tight, it feels so good!!
Yours is hard too...!
It's so hot! Just stay like that-!
You don't need to do anything!
B-But-!
You can leave it up to Onee-san!
Hey, can you hear my lewd sounds?
My pussy...!
It's making such dirty, squishy sounds!
Chinatsu-san-!
Onee-san is gonna get even more horny from this!
See? She's gonna shake her hips more, like this!
If you do that, I'll-!
Chi-Chinatsu-san!
N-No! Hold back!
It would be a waste if you came this early-!
More! It feels so good!
Your cock feels amazing!
Chinatsu-san-!
You're thrusting up so much!
Hey, you're being too rough-!
No-! I'll really-!
I-I'm... I'm gonna-!
You're gonna cum, right?
I think that'll make me feel good too!
Let it out-!
Let out your semen inside my pussy-!
I-I-I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm gonna cum-!
You sure let out a lot...
U-Um, I'm sorry...
It's fine, I'm the one who said to let it out.
All you have to do is tell Onee-san when you want to do it again.
Then we can do something like this again...
No, we can do something even more arousing n-e-x-t t-i-m-e!
This summer, I, Moroboshi Ryuuichi,
have been in a harem situation during the holiday.
I was living on my own when I became a college student...
However, a few days ago...
The apartment that I was living in burned to the ground...
That is why I came home to live with my step-mother. However...
Since she's too young and naive, she had four other lodgers living with her.
They are: the upper-classman Chinatsu-san,
and Kaede-san who is a lecturer at the same university.
Together with Manami-san, who works at the local family restaurant,
and Lisa, my mother's younger sister and my childhood friend.
In this harem situation, I'm being treated like a toy by them...
In many ways.
Oh? Hasn't Ryuuichi-kun come down yet?
Oh yes. He's later than usual, isn't he?
Maybe I was too greedy last night...
Oh? Chinatsu-kun, that's a comment I can't ignore...
What do you mean?
What were you greedy for?
Oh, how exciting! Don't tell me that you...
What?! What are we talking about?
It doesn't concern a virgin like you, Lisa.
Being a virgin doesn't matter!
Anyway, what are you guys talking about?!
That looks fun from here, but don't some people need to get going?
I guess you're right. It's nearly time.
I-I need to get going to my part-time job!
This is getting interesting!
Who would have known such a thing would happen?
Ryuuichi-san~!
Are you there?
Yes, I am at the moment!
Understood~!
I'll be out shortly!
Click?
Eh?
It feels pretty elegant to have a bath in a morning!
No-! Um, Manami-san! I'm still taking a bath!
Yes! That's why I came in!
Eh?!
I wanted to take a bath with you, Ryuuichi-san!
U-Um, that's...
You sure are sturdy, Ryuuichi-san!
I'm sorry-! I...
It's fine!
You're getting hard from seeing me naked...
I'm very happy!
You shouldn't do that-!
Oh? You don't like these things?
N-No, I like it, but...
Then isn't it fine?
Did Chinatsu-san give you a titfuck?
Eh?!
I'm sorry! I asked something a bit naughty!
No, um-!
Can you tell?
My nipples are already so hard!
Isn't it perverted?
It is...
Your cock is getting hot and quivering again!
Manami-san-!
I-If you do that, I'll-!
That was tasty!
Oh?
I get like this really easily...
It's fine!
Please make Manami's pussy feel good this time... with your cock...
It's going in!
So deep! It's entering Manami's pussy so deeply!
Y-Your lips and down there are both so hot...
No! You shouldn't call it "down there"!
Eh?
P-u-s-s-y!
Pussy!
You have to say it in a more lewd and naughty way!
Ma-Manami-san-!
Your cock-! I love it!
It's so hard and sturdy!
My hips are moving on they're own!
Yes! It's so dirty!
The sliminess of your pussy and your erotic expression!
No~! It's embarrassing!
Is it erotic?
Is my expression so perverted?
I-If you move like that, I'll-!
No-! It feels too good, I can't help myself!
Even though it's so embarrassing-!
My perverted pussy isn't stopping!
I can't stop myself!
Please... Please play with Manami's pussy some more!
Ryuuichi-san!
I-If you'd like, could you please use this?
W-Where did you get such a thing?
That's it! It feels so good!
Please, please keep going! Please play with my pussy more!
Please do more lewd things to me!
No-!
Hey, what are you...? No-!
N-No!
T-That's it!
My pussy and my butt... Do them at the same time!
More! I-It feels so good!
No-! My pussy and my butt... I'm gonna cum-! I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
You sure came a lot...
I-I'm sorry!
I couldn't hold back...
It's fine! Your cock is hard again!
Manami-san-!
You can do whatever you want, Ryuuichi-san...
Please use Manami's pussy all you want!
I'm so happy that I could die right now!
More! Thrust more!
Thrust more into Manami! Keep thrusting inside my pussy!
I want you to shove your cock inside me!
M-My butt is getting stretched!
Manami-san, do you like saying perverted things?
T-That's right! Manami is a pervert!
I-I can't help but get aroused from you pounding both of my holes!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum-! So good-!
But Manami-san-! You normally seem like such a distinguished woman!
N-No-! I'm sorry! I'm sorry that my pussy is so erotic and perverted!
Manami-san-!
No, stop-!
If you do it like that, it'll feel too good!
No-! You'll think that I'm a huge pervert!
I-I wouldn't dislike you!
In fact, I'd be really happy!
I'm somewhat happy too-!
Harder, do it harder!
Manami's gonna get dirtier!
So please do it harder!
It feels so good with you pounding my pussy with a vibrator in my butt-!
My breasts too-! They feel amazing!
I'm feeling too aroused! This is incredible!
Manami's pussy and butt are being pounded from both sides-!
They both feel so good!
My pussy, it'll become too dirty-!
Manami-san-! I'm about to cum-!
G-Give it to me! I want your cum!
Pour it out inside Manami's lewd pussy!
Please teach my pussy a lesson with your semen!
So good-!
I love it, I love it! My pussy feels so good! I'm gonna-!
Oh whoa, it's so much...
You let out so much...
I-I'm sorry!
I got too excited and I came too much...
No need for apologies.
I came a lot too!
It felt amazing!
Ma-Manami-san!
Ryuuichi-san! You've definitely got the qualities of a pervert!
Just as I expected!
Oh yeah, Manami-san. Where is that vibrator?
It's in my pussy.
Maybe you should take it out.
Nope.
I couldn't get to sleep that night after what happened with Chinatsu-san and Manami-san.
I can't sleep...
No-! I-I can't be doing this-!
This is wrong! It's like I'm a pervert!
I-I can't believe it smells so good!
This is wrong! I can't be doing this-!
H-Huh? Isn't that my towel?
It's his smell-!
It's such a lewd and perverted smell, no-!
No! I-I'm gonna cum-!
Ry-Ryuuichi, Ryuuichi! I'm gonna cum-!
W-What's with Lisa? She's normally so cold towards me...
Please cum with me, Ryuuichi-!
I love you!
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming-!