Bro, how much more sleep do you need!
You sleeping in on a holiday is not helping at all.
Man, why won't you answer.
You won't win my love like this!
No response...
That's it, l'm coming in.
Bro, it's morning so wake up...Bro!
Bro, your cute sis is going to get mad!
Wake up, it's morning!
Bro, come on!
Hot diggity, l want croquette.
What is he dreaming....
Come on Bro!!!
You awake now?
No...
You just did, wake up!! Come on!
Stop shaking me!
Not stopping.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
By the way, your breasts are shaking.
Pervert.
Dear Sis, all guys look at them.
That's just you Bro.
Hey, don't fall asleep!
Stop shaking me!
My neck still hurts from the blow you gave me!
l'll give you a kiss on the cheeks so smile for me.
Aww, not forgiving me?
My scars are deeper than the oceanic trench.
Fine, how's...
H, hey...
We don't need to hold it in anymore...
l want some attention you know.
lf you really mean that, l'll...
lt's OK, l want you too...
Bro, do you like them?
Of course.
Because it's mine?
l see, l'm so happy.
What, sucking on them so soon?
Your nipples are getting hard.
Stupid Bro.
Don't say such things.
No, this is driving me wild!!
What's wrong, why are you breathing so hard?
l don't know, but it feels good...
Just by touching your breasts?
Yeah...
Then, l'm continuing.
No, my chest, well...
Where do you want me to touch then?
lt's not really touching, well...you know....
What?
l want...yours.
What's wrong Bro?
Uh, nothing...
Mei's so cute that l almost fainted.
Like this?
My butt...you can see everything.
l want to see everything.
Mei, you're very wet inside.
And you're really hard, Bro...
My breasts at the same time...
Your hip movement is making me...
lt's hitting in deep!
ls that where it feels good, Mei?
Why am l feeling so warm....?
Hey everyone, Bazooka ln
Festival 2 is about to start!
Boys and girls, make sure
you watch in a well-lit room.
lt can't be! Why is this anime on now?
Today is a holiday special episode.
What, a holiday special!!?
lt's starting!
My favorite anime with my favorite heroine, Kyoko-chan!
What's wrong Bro, you're acting strange?
Uh, er, it's nothing Mei.
Society Princess, Kyoko!
Starting with the sexy transformation scene...
lt ain't holiday special for nothing!
lt got harder inside me!
My body, my body!!
Bro, what happened, you're rough now.
Answer me!!
Bro!!
Can't hit me!
Wow, come on, you can do it!
D, do what?
Uh, er, it's nothing.
lt got bigger again!
Stop!
Bro got rougher!
Pink Flash!
No, this is making me cum!
Here l go!
C...cuming!
You're finished!
Finished!
l...l...
M, Mei!
Bro!!!!!!
Bro, what happened to you today?
lt felt really good.
R, really?
Well, see you next week.
Hey...
Y, yes!
Don't tell me you were watching
TV while we were doing it.
l, it was an accident.
lt was a show l normally watch and...
So you were looking at the TV and not me.
Don't tell me you were fantasizing about her.
She knows!
Anything else to add?
Uh, l'm telling you...
Bro, why are you always like that!
Either way, who would've thought
that anime would be on at that time.
l can't let my guards down, TV!
l'm done.
You going out Bro?
Yeah, Renka-san called me out.
But it's a holiday!
You'll never understand.
lf l disobey orders, they will kill me.
Forgive me, Mei!
Just as l suspected, the Akiba.
lt's like l'm inside an anime world.
That's one of the things about the Maid Cafes!
Maid Cafe?
Allow me to explain.
Maid Cafe's are around Akiba and cute ''moe''
waitresses dressed as maids take your order.
A very nice and good cafe.
l see, l learned something new again.
With the way you're going, you'll
soon be a great Akiba-style too.
Then l guess l need to keep my secret until then.
Eh, secret?
Not telling.
What are you hiding from me?
Now l'm very curious!
lt might be a secret that you never would've thought.
Like...
l'm really an alien from Planet N54.
What are you saying Ren-san.
She's way too into the Akiba-style.
But, l like it.
Stupid Bro dreaming about her.
l'm jealous!!
Tada, the pictures taken at the convention are done.
This is cute Tamae.
See!
Um, was l called out just to look at pictures?
You're so mean Nikita-kun.
Just, what do you mean Just!
l thought you would like it...
Tamae-san, there's no need to cry.
You made her cry.
What a bastard for making a girl cry.
lt's all my fault so please don't cry!
l'll do anything you say!
Really?
Y, yeah.
Alright, take his clothes off!
What are you two doing!
Hey, don't touch the zipper!
You said you'll do anything!
Just let us take it off!
Not the undies!
Well, there it is.
Hm, it's cute.
lt's getting bigger.
Wait a second!
Why does it always come down to this?
Don't talk back.
You took our virginity.
l said no, but you forced yourself on me.
Hey, don't make up things!
D, double the pleasure.
Nikita, don't you want it now?
Stupid me can't say no, stupid!
Come on Nikita, start pumping.
Amazing, your pussy is getting stretched.
l never seen sex this close.
Don't stare...!
Renka-chan, it's so...amazing.
Watching this is making me want to have sex!
Over here, stick your tongue
inside me as if it's your cock!
lt feels good.
My juices are flowing out.
Nikita, you're big!
lt's filling me up and l'm...!
Your tongue is giving me
sensations l've never experienced!
Renka-chan, l'm cuming, cuming!
Don't cum, we'll cum together Tamae!
OK Renka-chan, lets cum together.
l'm gonna...
Me too, l can't!
Cuming, cuming!
Renka-chan, l'm cuming too!
Not yet...cheers!
Nice, you downed that one.
Bro was all acting like an idiot in front of her...
What a jerk.
l know, l understand that feeling.
Drink...drink with me and forget everything.
We're staying up all night!
Where in the world is Mei...
R, Ren-san!?
Seeing Ren-san is an apron is sure beautiful.
lt feels as if we're newly weds.
Crap, l almost fainted again.
Bro!
What's wrong, Bro?
Nikita-kun's parents died in front
of him due to a tragic accident.
Who are you?
Can you understand?
l don't think you can understand Nikita-kun's feeling.
Who...who are you?
l've always cheered on Nikita-kun.
Always....and now you come
along, taking him away from me.
l won't let you...l won't let anyone take him!
Bro!
Bro.
Nikita-kun, stop licking there...
But Ren-san, it tastes really good.
What about here?
T, that's!
Don't you like it here, Ren-san?
Because it feels good.
lt's sensitive.
Not there again.
Nikita-kun, it's not fair.
l want to taste yours too.
Sorry Ren-san, but l really want to do it.
OK, push it in me.
Nikita-kun, please...stick it in.
Nikita-kun, it's coming inside!
My body is responding to it!
l feel really good too.
You're making me feel really good Nlkita-kun!
l will make you feel even better then.
Don't pinch them!
Why, because it feels good?
Nikita-kun, don't kid me.
Why...this feels so unreal.
Now, let me make you feel better.
How is it Nlkita-kun?
lt's amazing, Ren-san.
Ren-san, l can't hold it...any longer!
OK, let it all out.
Ren-san!
Are you alright?
What about you, isn't it on your face Ren-san?
Ren-san...?
Yes?
That...thing on your head.
What is that?
What, you can see it Nikita-kun!?
Yeah.
Ren-san?
Bro!
She isn't here...
lsn't this where we first met?
Didn't you look at me like that
on the day of the accident?
Nikita-kun, do you remember the
day your parents passed away?
Ren-san, how do you know about that?
That same day, l broke a rule.
l loved you so much that l
interfered with your destiny.
Destiny?
An exhibitionist can only be an exhibitionist.
l wasn't supposed to change
the destiny of a young soul.
So, l was supposed to be dead through that accident.
Nikita-kun.
l always thought it was strange.
lt was a really big accident, but
l was alive without an injury.
ls it because you saved me?
What are you?
l'm God's servant.
Well, not anymore.
For changing a soul's destiny, l was punished
to stay here not as an angel nor a human.
Until today.
Ren-san!
Thank you, Nikita-kun.
You can do well without me.
Ren-san, please don't!
Come back!
Good bye, l wish you happiness with Mei-chan.
Ren-san!!!
l remember now.
During that incident, you were comforting me.
l was very sad and lost, but you were there.
Bro...
Mei, why are you here?
l saw a weird dream.
l felt uncomfortable and l started
to get worried about you.
Hey Mei, do you know Ren Aoi?
No, who is she?
A friend of yours?
lt's nothing, it's just my imagination again.
Jumping Gemini, l totally forgot about
the rerun of Kyoko-chan's special episode!
We're going home Mei, l can't miss the opening!
Watching it again!?
You will always be an Akiba-style.
Akiba has an angel.
A beautiful angel in the shape of a girl.
Wait up Bro!
l've seen it with my own eyes.
Akiba's urban legend, do you...
Believe in it?