I'm sorry Hirayama-kun, for having you help me out.
Don't worry, it's nothing.
I can't let a girl hold such a thing anyways.
I'm really bad at this type of thing.
I can't even enter the science lab by myself.
Because, seeing such strange creatures is so disgusting.
Nakayama-san, you're really cute.
Renketsu Houshiki
ORIGINAL ANIMATION
Thank you very much.
You really helped me out.
Hirayama-kun, you're really kind.
You see,
I'm actually pretty bad around guys.
For some reason they're scary... and somehow dirty...
But Hirayama-kun is fine.
Since you're cute like a girl.
You sow.
Whose face did you say looked like a girl?
Hirayama-kun, why?
No, don't...
No!
You're so wet,
and you say you're bad with guys?
Please stop.
Please!
What should I stop doing when you are feeling so good.
T-That's because Hirayama-kun is...
It hurts.
Why are you doing such a thing.
No...
In general, you know, watching just isn't enough.
I don't think there are many guys as manly as me...
What?!
See,
This time you are going to make me feel good.
Ah, I want to put it in.
You asked why I was doing such a thing.
It's obviously because I want to.
I'm getting ready to cum.
Make sure to take it all.
Stop!
You can't! That is..
Oh, you were a virgin.
It hurts... It hurts.
Don't talk about something that a guy doesn't know.
Please...
Please, it hurts.
Take it... Take it out.
Even with all this, you are so wet.
You like to touch yourself, don't you.
I don't...
Look, this is so much better than doing it by yourself.
I'll make you feel much better...
What?
Stop.
Just stay still...
You can't do it to my butt.
Stop!
Not my butt!
Amazing! A virgin with both holes stuffed.
You aren't dreaming.
This is reality.
N-No.
Stop already.
Stop what?
You say that while feeling so good.
Even when you're violated you feel good.
Just a complete sow...
T-That's horrible!
You mustn't do this!
Are you going to cum already?
It's the first time you've taken a cock, and your ass is so wide that you're going to cum?
Such a thing isn't...
Ha, just cum already!
No...
I going to...
I'm cumming~
You're so cruel, I liked you but...
Even if it felt so good, it's a shame...
You still don't understand, you little girl.
Little girl?
Think of the meaning of that by yourself.
That's...
No... Nooo!
No!
Don't trap me in a place like this!
Return my virginity!
Hirayama-kun~
Hi!
This is where you were.
Morika-san and Aikawa-san, what's going on?
Hey, hey, are you free right now?
Come with us for a bit.
Sure... but, what are we going to do?
We'll have some fun~
Audiovisual Room
That totally suits you!
So cute!
It's so great!
You're cute!
You're so cute!
Your legs are so slim.
The skirt looks so good on you!
But it's kind of vexing, right?
Yeah!
Yeah.
Let me take a picture so I can send it to the magazine.
You really are like a girl.
Your legs are so pretty.
A-ah... Look what happened because of you girls.
You are going to take responsibility for what you did, right?
Hey, suck it more respectfully.
You like it, don't you.
Hirayama-kun, Misa can't take it anymore.
Put your huge cock in Misa.
Is that the attitude of someone who wants something?
Hey, why do you call yourself by your own name?
In an era that loves white skin, why are you tan?
You're so stupid but why do you have such confidence?
You can't take it anymore, right?
I'll lick it.
I can't take it anymore,
I want your thick cock.
Alright, I'm putting it in.
You're so mean to me Hirayama-kun,
stick it in Misa too.
Please stick it in.
In Misa too!
In Misa too~
Shut up! You should be satisfied with just this!
Horrible~
If you want money, do it with Old guys.
It's all the way in! All the way in!
If you want cock make a club and suck them dry.
More... More!
That's amazing!
Misa, you're such an idiot.
Don't act like such a great person.
I'm coming~
I'm coming!
Here, this is our cellphone number and names.
Let's do something dirty again when you are free.
Hey, hey
it's okay, right?
Let's do it again. Please~
Haven't you had enough you despicable tramps.
It's not going to be like you think.
You can't have whatever you want.
Don't get attached to me!
No way...
Let's have fun~
Let us out Hirayama-kun!
I use to be only interested in the boys from Host Clubs, but I'm totally in love with you right now!
I'll give you everything~
Hirayama-kun~
Professor Fujimori?
I've been searching for you.
Do you have some time?
Hirayama kun, lately, you've been skipping class and your grades have been falling.
Is there something troubling you?
If so, won't you please tell me?
Are you being bullied?
I know what happened before you came here.
I heard about how you were called gay and a transvestite,
and treated like a monster by everyone around you.
But if you are being bullied here, what should I do?
What should we do?
No..
You know, it's not good to jump to such a conclusion.
Hirayama-kun?
I'm sorry.
So, please, forgive me.
Even I am a man.
Hey, teacher... It's big, isn't it?
T-That is...
No... stop...
Suck it, teacher.
No way, that's...
Don't!
Hirayama-kun...
Please...
Do you want it, teacher?
quickly put your big cock...
S-So good!~
Normally, in front of everyone you act so big...
But in front of my cock you are nothing but a dirty hoe...
So thick...
So deep...
It's in so deep.
More...
Harder...
Hey, I'm going to cum, teacher.
Come!
Let it all out!
Inside me...
Inside me!
Hirayama-kun!
If it's about your grades, I'll do something about it for you!
So let me out of here!~
Idiot. That was really easy.
She says such things, but when it comes down to it, she's just like that.
Hey, who do you think is doing it the most in our school?
Let's see... It's definitely Katakura-kun after all.
Look, it's Katakura-kun.
Isn't he great? He's definitely the best at our school.
That's for sure. He's always surrounded by women.
Aah, I want him to be my boyfriend.
A-ah, I wonder if there are any better women...
I've tried all the dogs here...
And I don't want to touch the ugly ones.
I've been searching for you, Hirayama-kun.
Who are you?
I'm Katakura.
Hirayama kun... I've always thought you were cute.
No, seriously.
Someone! Someone save me!
It's okay, once we start you will feel good!
E-Even so...
Save me!
A guy! I definitely don't want a guy!
The lock! Open the lock!