Look at my pussy.
See? It's so wet.
Look all the way inside me.
Take lots of footage of me being dirty.
Look how much my butt spreads now...
Can you hear me making gushy sounds?
It feels so good!
What's the meaning of this?
I was thinking about uploading this to the Internet.
How could you do something like that, knowing how she feels?
Yuna is in love with you...
You're the one who told me I could do anything to her,
even if she's my sister.
Depending on your actions, I might change my mind.
I'm not giving you the painting.
I'll leave the paintings to you.
What I want is you.
If you take my sex lessons instead...
I'll stop what I'm doing to Yuna.
What do you say?
You leave me no choice.
Come in.
Yes, Brother.
Yuna! What do you think you're doing?
I'm doing exactly what you told me, Mom.
But...
Yuna, lift up your leg and show Megumi-san your pussy.
Yes, Brother.
Spread it with your fingers so she can take a good look.
She's wet already.
I can't believe she was a virgin a month ago.
I'll be able to fit up to my wrist soon.
No, don't! You can't! No! Stop! Help me! Mom!
Stop it!
Yuna! Are you all right?
I'll take Yuna's place!
Take place for what?
I'll take Yuna's place and take your sexual beatings instead.
Is that right?
Yes, you can do anything.
S... Stop!
What are you doing? It hurts!
I wouldn't want you to be fighting back, so...
But...
Please... Yuna is... Please, not in front of Yuna.
Please...
Yuna's don't even compare to these.
I think they're drooping a little.
How could you... It hurts.
Kyosuke-kun, don't fondle me so hard.
S... Stop, Kyosuke-kun.
There's a stain on your panties.
Were you aroused by seeing Yuna naked?
Don't be foolish!
Yuna, take a look. Megumi's feeling it.
No, Yuna. Don't look at me.
Don't violate me in front of her.
You're getting hot.
No, stop.
You're pretty tight for a woman who's had a kid.
What's wrong? Can't wait?
Yeah.
Yuna. There's no need. You don't have to do it anymore.
That's not fair. You're getting all the spanking.
Yuna, you're...
This isn't why I'm doing this. I said I'll take Yuna's place.
Yuna's doing it on her own. I have no right to stop her.
But...
Yuna, wait your turn, okay? I'm going to pleasure Megumi-san first.
You two....
I want you to like Brother, too.
I want everyone to live happily.
Wait!
No!
Well? How do you like the taste of cock? It's been a while for you.
It feels so good you're speechless?
No, stop, Kyosuke-kun...
No, I don't want this.
I'm getting violated by my step-son and I'm feeling it.
Mom, does it feel good? You should say it if it feels good.
Yuna...
Megumi, you're feeling it, right?
No...
You get off when I hurt you.
You're wrong... No...
You wanted to be beaten, right, Megumi?
Please, no more...
You're about to cum.
No, you're wrong... No...
Cum, Megumi!
Nooo!
At this moment it was obvious to me.
Both Megumi and Yuna were masochists.
Excuse me, but only staff is allowed in there.
My mother... Is Megumi Wakao out?
Are you Megumi-san's son?
Yes.
She went to do some errands. I'm sure she'll be back soon.
Would it be all right if I waited in the office?
I really can't...
That's not good... Has my mother told you anything?
It's about my father's inheritance. She told me to wait for her...
in the office because she didn't want other people to hear.
She did?
Yes.
Thank you.
Um...
Megumi-san seems very tired lately.
Did something happen?
It's probably because my father's exhibition is coming up.
Good luck with the preparations.
The Yearn of the Morn.
It's my father's first piece, and also his masterpiece.
But it's not listed in the raisonne my father left behind.
My father said it's supposed to be paired with The Night's End, but...
Why did you come here?
You might as well display it in the gallery...
if you're going to put it here.
I told you already. If people see it,
the Ministry of Cultural Affairs and the tax office will...
I didn't come here for this painting.
Here? Are you insane?
Let's show Dad how well we're getting along.
This is crazy.
If you raise your voice, the woman on the floor will hear you.
You didn't change-- you're wearing the same thing.
You're the one who told me to.
Are you embarrassed?
Of course I am. Look at how I'm dressed in the office.
I think it suits you, because you enjoy getting abused.
Your breasts are still impressive, no matter how many times I see them.
No, not here. I can't. Please, at the house.
If Nakuru sees me... Kyosuke-kun.
I have no intention of stopping.
You're the one who said you'd take Yuna's place.
Make me cum before that woman notices what's going on.
But...
No...
Come on. Do it, Megumi.
What's wrong? Don't you want me to leave?
Do it like you mean it. Yuna's much better at it.
Might as well... You've got a nice rack, give me a titty-fuck.
Well? Come on. Get to it.
This is something Yuna can't do.
Don't say that.
Come on, use your mouth.
Did you get horny from giving me a titty-fuck?
What a slut. Drop your ass and take it in.
But...
If you don't hurry, she might walk in.
It's fine by me if you want to stay naked.
Stop enjoying it by yourself. Hurry up and move that ass.
But...
You want me to go home, right?
Shake that ass more!
Can't you move faster?
If you do that, I'm going to feel it. I can't stop myself...
No, I'm going to cum. I'm gonna cum!
No, I can't stop.
Hey, shake that ass more.
Grab your clit and make yourself cum.
No, I'm going to cum...
Yes, it makes my pussy feel so good.
I'm going to cum again. I'm going to cum.
Megumi-san.
No! Don't look at me, Nakuru.
No, don't move. I'm going to cum. No, don't look at me!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
How did this end up being like this?
I offered Yuna to Kyosuke-kun, and everything...
was supposed to go according to plan.
I never imagined he would lust after me.
Even if he approached me, I thought I could handle him.
I didn't think I would enjoy it so much.
I can't believe getting abused could feel so good.
I'm supposed to be Kyosuke-kun's mother...
Yuna is in love with Kyosuke-kun, and I'm lusting for his cock...
This is so evil of me...
I'm sorry, Yuna...
Many models have posed in this atelier before you, but...
I bet you're the first to pose like that.
I wish Dad could have seen you like that.
W... What are you doing?
No! Stop, Kyosuke-kun!
It's Dad's favorite brush. Feels good, right?
Your nipples are so sensitive.
No...
They're getting hard already.
Stop...
Megumi, how about here?
No, if you do that there...
Jeez. You're dripping already.
No, don't stick that in...
No, I'm feeling it. No. There. More. Give it to me.
How about here, Megumi?
No, stop! You can't! It won't go in! Don't put it in.
No, if you do that, it's going to come out. Stop...
Please, no more, Kyosuke-kun... It's going to come out.
I'm going to pee.
No... Don't look at me...
You were holding it.
You're terrible.
Please, Kyosuke-kun...
Make me cum... Make me cum and make me forget everything.
What do you want me to do, Megumi?
Your cock... Please stick your cock in my pussy.
You've finally learned how to beg.
Yes. Please...
Fuck me, Kyosuke-kun.
Make me cum...
What is that?
I thought it might hurt you without it.
No!
You can't! Not up the butt! No, stop!
No... Pull it out... Pull it out, Kyosuke-kun.
Here I go, Megumi.
No, Don't move! My butt... My butt's going to break!
Please, no more, Kyosuke-kun.
Is this the first time you're getting it up the ass, Megumi?
The suction is great.
Don't toy with me...
You're feeling it up the ass, too.
Don't say that...
Yes... It feels so good up the butt...
No, I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum from anal!
Cum, Megumi!
I can't, anymore! I'm cumming!
Come on, let it out, Megumi.
Don't make me do this... Why are you doing such horrible things to me?
Did you forget our promise?
You're terrible. Is it useless to plead?
How does it taste, Megumi?
It's so good. Your cum... Your cum tastes so good, Kyosuke-kun...
This piece is the answer to The Yearn of the Morn...
Kyosuke, Megumi, Yuna. There is something I must tell you.
Before I made my debut as a painter,
I trained under a female painter named Azumi Murayama.
It was before my own painting style had come together.
A few years later, Azumi passed away. Before she died, she said...
''There's a piece where only the sketch has been finished.''
''l want you to finish it and release it.''
I had no intention of releasing it as my own.
I did it so I could give back to her.
But temptation took hold of me. I released it as my own.
It was released as mine, a no-name artist's first piece, instead of...
Azumi Murayama, a female Showa Era artist's last piece.
That piece is The Yearn of the Morn.
Decades had passed, and one day, Megumi, an art dealer, visited me.
She had known The Yearn of the Morn was Azumi Murayama's piece,
just as I knew Megumi was Azumi Murayama's daughter.
Perhaps I wanted to make it up.
But there are no lies in my love for Megumi.
But Megumi will probably never forgive me...
for releasing her mother's piece as my own.
Megumi, Kyosuke, please forgive me.
This all started from my selfishness.
I don't want the two of you to have any rifts.
Also for the sake of Yuna, who doesn't know anything.
I am the one to blame.
I wish for the three of you to love one another.
This is the note that was hidden behind The Night's End.
Now I know why you were so caught up with that painting.
I'll leave it up to you to display The Yearn of the Morn or not.
It's up to you if you want to stay here or not.
I can also leave, too.
I want you to think about how Dad felt, too.
What's wrong, Brother?
You're acting strange.
I am?
Yes.
Brother, is something wrong?
Wanna fuck?
I wish the three of you to love each other.
We're such fools.
Yes... Brother, it feels so good. Please, I can't wait any longer.
Fuck me. Give it to me, Brother.
Hurry, give it to me. Brother.
Yes, it feels so good.
Yes! Yes!
Brother, fuck me more!
Fuck my pussy until it breaks!
Brother?
Mom?
This is what he wished for, and what you also wish, right?
Is it, Yuna?
Yes, Mother.
Please, Kyosuke-kun. Please fuck me.
Yes... More... Wriggle it inside of me...
Brother, abuse me, too... I want to cum with Mom.
Okay, Yuna.
Yes, Brother! More, suck my pussy!
It feels so good.
Yes... Kyosuke-kun, I'm gonna cum! Fuck me! Fuck me more!
Mom, it feels so good. My pussy feels so good.
Yuna, me too.
Yes, Brother! Ram my ass more!
My pussy... Yes, yes!
Mom, let's cum together!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Yuna, me too. Me too!
I can't believe his piece was found.
They say an artist's representative piece is his first one, but...
when I see it next to The Night's End,
I see more of Kazuma Wakao's artistry in this one.
It's a piece where you see his soul.
And I sense an understanding of life in The Yearn of the Morn.
I agree.
It's very interesting.
Brother.
Kyosuke-kun, what's wrong?
Nothing, Mom.
Meeting you in the darkness inside me...
was how I knew I was still alive.
While I understand what kind of things are allowed,
I still have to shut my eyes.
Like a swaying blossom, trying to adjust,
rippling in the water,
the river of time, in its course toward ruin,
will lift my apprehension.