Tetsuko-san, please turn this way for the camera.
You too, Tamaye-san.
Comic convention... This is so unique.
Yeah, after all, some guys do dedicate their life for it.
Excuse me?
Um, am l not welcomed here?
No, of course you are welcomed.
Yeah, that's right. You don't belong here.
That's you. Hey, why are you here!?
lt is none of your business, Bro. Where ever l go, it does not concern you...
Dear Sun Goddess. l, a weak hearted man, couldn't choose between Ren-san or the Comic Convention.
So, l brought Ren-san to the Comic convention.
Then, somehow this girl came along against my will...
Well, well...
Why are you guys standing here like zombies?
Huh, because it's a new atmosphere for us.
Atmosphere? What are you talking about? You brought your girlfriend.
You guys must have a hot atmosphere.
Hey, hey, Renka-chan. Don't be so jealous just because she has bigger hooters...
The Pit...
Pit
l know! Mei-chan, Ren-san, why don't you two cosplay as well.
No, not me.
lt is all right. You girls are so pretty. You two will definitely look great, OK?
KT-san, What a...
Ok, Nikita-kun. Let's go over there, the frontline!
Hey, hey!! This way, this way!!
Strike a pose!
Please look back
Like this?
That is good. Magnificent!!
Bend over for me!
You like this?
How about other poses!
What!? lt is embarrassing
Oh wow, the Comic convention is damn good. Don't you agree, Mei?
Yeah? Mei?
Mei?
You were having a great time because of Ren-san, weren't you?
lt doesn't have to be me. You are glad as long as Ren-san was there?
Hey, Mei? What are....
l hate you nowadays.
You do many strange things and come home really late and leave me out...
You don't think of me anymore, never.
You know that l won't always be at your side, right? Don't you understand!?
Mei!
Mei... don't tell me you are...
Holy shit, what am l going to do!?
Mei's falling for the dark-side!
l did not really want to come, but ...
Hey, Hatoko-nee. lt is me.
l'm going to come in!
l cannot believe this girl...
l got you
Damn you, you smell like alcohol.
You have balls to come seduce me this late.
Stupid, lt is me, Nikita! Think straight, you drunken girl!
Hmm, now that you mention it...you look like Nikita.
l'm the Real McCoy, fool!
Hey, Nikita. lf you want to have sex, just say so.
lt will cost you 25000 yen though.
The amount is just like an actual price.
Ok, l give a little discount for you.
Thanks...
Wow, Mei is...
Hatoko-nee, what should l do? You are my family. Don't you have any advice?
We are a family, but none of us share the same blood.
What color is your blood!? You don't care if Mei falls for the dark-side!?
You are so slow, don't you get it?
She is jealous of your relationship with Ren-san.
She is really jealous.
Mei is in love with you.
What...!?
And one more thing.
You don't realize my feelings too, huh?
Hatoko-nee, are you drunk?
Don't you want me?
You're not denying me, so you do want me.
What!? Hey!
What? Does it feel good?
She knows what men like.
Hehe, your joystick is getting hard.
Oh...do you hear that? The nasty sound coming from my...can you hear it?
Can you feel that? Can you taste it?
This girl is too horny.
Yes, yes, Nikita-kun, this is so good. How about you? lt is good, huh?
Your big sister feels so good, my baby boy.
What is the matter with you, Hatoko-nee? Did alcohol finally get to your brain?
lsn't this your favorite Nikita-kun, isn't it?
You're just treating me like a baby.
You just don't understand my world, Hatoko-nee.
You are not doing it the way it's supposed to be done.
How about this?
Doctor, l have a chest pain. Can you examine me, please?
Now we're just playing Doctor.
But this might be exciting me more.
What... do you want to be my doctor?
Here's a stethoscope.
Why do you have one?!
Doctor, my pulse rate is increasing.
Ah, Doctor, please hurry! Please check me up!
She should have become an actress...
Why, why is your heart pounding?
Doctor, this feels so good that l might have a heart attack!
Oh my god! Ok, l've got to give you a heart massage.
Oh yes! Doctor, that is too much! My heart rate is increasing too much!
Oh yeah, oh yeah! l am really getting into this!
Ah, Doctor, l can't breathe right. Please give me CPR!
Certainly.
Ah, Doctor, what is the next examination?
We need to do emergency procedure on you!
Oh, yes! Doctor, this operation is so great!
Hmm, l am the best doctor in the world though l am not certified...
Yes! Doctor!
l am going to cum soon!
Ok, Doctor, l am cumming, too!
Hatoko-nee...!
All l wanted was to get some advice about Mei. Hmmm...
After Hatoko was adopted from the nursing home, l was born. Then, Mei came along afterwards.
Mei was abandoned by her biological parents and has a big scar emotionally.
With the love my parents gave her, she learned to smile, but my mom and dad are gone...
You are so slow , don't you get it?
She is in love with you.
Mei...
l am coming!
Mei!
No, Bro.
Hey, Bro.
l know how you feel so don't say a word. l, too, do love you.
Bro...
Bro. are you telling the truth?
Yes, l swear on my Ztar Warz collection.
Bro...ther...
Mei,...may l?
Of course. You are the one l love, Bro.
Mei...
Th..That is... Ah!
You have beautiful tits, Mei!
Brother, are you measuring my breast? Your touch is so amazing...
Mei, l never heard you like this before.
Because you are... my breast... Ah
Bro, that is...
l want to know more about you.
lf you say so...
How is it? Feel good?
l am not sure...
But l am getting hot, Bro.
How about this?
No, that is dirty...!
Hey, that is... my anus... Dirty...
Stop, Bro... Mei is going crazy....
Bro, my whole body is getting very hot. What am l going to do? l never felt like this before...
l'm cumming...Bro!
Bro!
l'm cumming...
Now it's my turn to make you feel good.
Me... Mei... What are you...
Let me try this...
Feel good?
Yes, it does. Where did you learn this?
When l was cleaning your room, l saw boxes of games...and saw many pictures like this...
How...How can l explain...?
Bro, juice is coming out...
Ah...l am going to cum soon.
What should l do?
Why don't you lay this way? Let' s cum together.
Ah... Bro!
Mei...!
l'm so happy...
Finally we two are one....
Yes, we are.
Yes, yes... you are coming inside...your penis is in...inside of me.
lt's so hard that it's vibrating inside me!
You make me feel good, Bro...
This is the first time l saw this side of you.
Your delivery is so great.
l never thought that the incident with Tama-chan could be utilized at this moment...
Yes, Bro!
Okay! Mei wants to be one with you...
Mei...
Bro... Mei is so glad to get to know how much you love me...
Mei is not going anywhere.
To be honest, my biological father gave me a call.
He regrets what he has done and wants me to move back home.
He really wants to start over...
Mei was at loss what to do.
l just couldn't talk about this with you because you were coming home late due to the club activity...
But now, l know you love me so Mei is going to stay with you forever.
l love you, Bro...
C'mon Hatoko-nee. You were totally wrong.
Why was l dreaming about this now...?
Bro, l love you so much.
May l?
R...Ren-san!? Sure, you are so welcomed, please!
You look exhausted.
Really?
Ren-san, aren't you bored to be with me?
What?
Well, you know... We are living in really different world or...
l'm not bored of you, actually, l want to get to know you more.
l also don't mind that...you play bishojyo games...
What!? How did you know about that?
Renka-san told me.
Damn daughter of Maleficent.
Hey, don't say that.
Sorry.
l wonder if we look like couples, sitting together like this...?
Nikita-kun, l have a favor to ask you.
Are you sure you want me in your house?
R...Ren-san!?
l love you, Nikita-kun. l just cannot control myself.
Ren-san, l...
Don't say it!
l know how you feel, l hope...But l can not hold in my feelings.
l don't care if you think l'm a selfish girl, but please...don't leave me alone tonight.
Ren-san...
Why do l always get myself in a situation like this?
This situation is like something from "Sleepless in Seattle"!
Ren-san, your nipples are touching me.
You are so warm, Nikita-kun.
Don't lose, don't lose your composure, Nikita Shindo.
You have a lovely sister named Mei!
Holy God! l can't believe how soft they are!
This is just like one of Mary Carey' s stuff.
Ren-san.
Yes.
May l have a hug...?
l really want to hug you...
Nikita-kun...
Whatta heck is Bro doing? l am goingto punish him when he gets home.
l am somehow very nervous... Maybe because Ren-san is here.
l feel like she is untouchable.
Nikita-kun, make love to me.
Nikita-kun...!
Oh yes, we are finally one...you, Nikita-kun, is inside of me.
You are very warm.
Make love to me harder... Nikita-kun.
l never knew that...being with you like this...is so comfortable.
l am starting to feel really good.
Ren-san!
Nikita-kun!
l feel the warmness from deep with in me, Nikita-kun..! Nikita-kun..!
Oh my, you are still hard, Nikita-kun.
l apologize that he is a beast...
R..Ren-san?
Guys like this, don't they?
What...?
Breasts.
You are so adorable.
l cannot believe that pretty Ren-san is doing this...
P...please... it is embarrassing so...
please don't stare at me.
Oops, l am sorry.
Oh shoot! lf you do harder...!
Oh...that's a lot of cum.
Ren-san, you are so great...
Bro!
Devi-Girl!?
Who are you calling the devi-girl!
Bro, what time do you think it is!?
lt is morning, MORNlNG! l stayed awake for you all night! You, Bro...
Well, under certain circumstance, there are so many reasons...
lt is Ren-san, isn't it?
Uh oh.
And you spent the night.
Hmm, so this is how Devi-Girl feels when transforming...
Mei-chan...?
That's it, l'm not goingto forgive you today!
Crap, she is going to kick my ass!
Hold on, listen to me...?!
No excuse!
Dear Dad and Mom.
lt has been a while since Mei and l start living together.
At that time, l was so anxious to raise Mei up and was so worried... But l am fine now.
Mei has become a true woman.
Take my Lariat!
Oh, no, please, please forgive me. Please, Mei-chan!