Dear Sun Goddess.
You've been giving us too much rain these days,
l mean today is Thursday and it is a very important day for me.
This is the day to visit Akihabara.
l don't think it's a good idea to give us rain on this day.
Well, that's alright because l'm here to pick up bishojyo games.
Ohh, l love myself doing this.
Gotcha, l'm running and gunning back home.
Huh? Was there a park here before?
Am l getting lost in my own neighborhood?
lt's Tita...
She must be Tita, the heroine of the movie ''Lapota, the Castle in the sky''.
Damn, she noticed me checking on her.
Wait a second, what's this feeling?
We only made an eye contact.
Hey, Bro. You are home.
You look so exhausted. What's the matter with you?
No, nothing. l lost a bit of hit points.
l will be fine once l cast a cure spell.
Um, okay. Where are you going, Brother?
My room, where else?
Awww, that's too boring. lt' s my day off from school, you know?
l don't give a damn.
C'mon!.......
Hey, what is that bag?
What did you get? Let me see, let me see!
Hey Sis.
Yes, my brother.
Never mind.
Hey, Bro. Damn you.
l am sorry, my sister, Mei. l still cannot reveal my
secret l've been keeping from you for 19 years.
No, no, l just cannot tell you....
l am an Akiba-style.
Oh, yes.
More, more and harder. Not yet, don't cum...
No! Stop it. lt is....
H, hey, l told you to knock on the door before you enter my room, l always te...
Y, you are...Tita. Tita!
Paju.
l finally found you, Paju!
W, what is going on here?
The pirates are chasing me.
What, do you mean the Doll family!?
lt is a matter of time before they get here!
Please, help me Paju!
OK. Don't worry. l'm always on your side, Tita.
You are so beautiful.
lt is embarrassing. Don't stare too much, please.
Wow, your nipples are perking up.
There.... i..s...
You don't like.....
No... as long as it is you, Paju.
Tita, you are so tasty.
Do you like it better inside or outside?
ln... lnside
Yes, there, right there.
Wow, your juice is pouring out.
Don't say that.
lt is so good.
Oh, l am cumming.
Don't cum yet. We are going to cum together.
That's so deep....
Are you all right?
Yes, we are one.
Paju, you are getting bigger inside.
Oh, god. l have never had this before.
lt's hitting me deep inside!
Let me give it to you harder.
Ahh, can you hear my pussy juice...lt feels so good.
ls that good?
This is too much. l gotta cum.
We are going to cum togother.
l know.
Wow, this is so good, keep pounding me, Paju!
l cannot hold it anymore.
Yes, le..let's cum to..together!
Sigh, again l made up my own fantasy story...
Tita.
He is looking at himself and smiling. Weird.
He's always been weird. But even more so now.
Even during class, l find myself thinking about that girl.
l cannot believe that l am in love with a living girl...
What are you doing, Nikita Shindo!
You will be sticking with the Akiba way, all the way! Alright!
This is it. l cannot go back once l step in.
The Alternative Trivia Research Club! lt's the club for the hardcore maniacs!
Excuse.... me.
Huh?
Oh?
Um... What are you doing?
l'm fitting into a costume.
Oh, l understand...d. What am l doing!?
Sorry!
Why was she dressing in there?
And it was a maid's uniform.
l'm done dressing so you can come inside.
Um, ok...
l am sorry to surprise you.
No, no. lt is my fault.
She has an unbelievable body.
She has a baby face, but yet a pair of gigantic tits.
Furthermore, those glasses and maid's uniform.
She is exactly like a heroin from a bishojyo game.
The Alternative Trivia Research Club...
it's more hardcore than l thought.
Do you want to join the club?
Yes, l am Nikita Shindo.
My name is Tamaye Akiyoshi. Call me Tama-chan.
N, nice to meet you..
The club president isn't here yet.. Can you please
have a seat and wait.
Yes, sir!
Huh?
l am also waiting for the president.
ls she the famous wonder girl?
Hmm,
he still isn't here.
l, l can't take this any longer!
l'm not use to being with only a girl in the same room!
l guess she has no problem with it.
Huh, wha!? What's wrong with you!? Tamaye-san!
You look restless and l think you cannot handle this kind of situations.
Tamaye-san. l have no idea what you are doing!
Don't tell me you are not use to being with a girl alone?
Well, l am an Akiba style man.
Don't say that.
Even if you are an Akiba style, you are still a man.
Alright, as a newcomer, l'm going to give you a personal lesson.
How is it? A real woman is good, isn't it?
How can this possibly happen like this?
How soft her tities are! l just found a new hobby.
That's it, l'm going for it!
Nikita-kun, don't forget who's giving the lesson.
Well done, Nikita-kun. Now why don't you suck on it?
Ahhh, do not suck so hard all of sudden.
OK, it's time for Step 2. We are going to unite.
Wow, you are fast paced!
l think there is something missing.
l get wet easily so if you don't stick it in
now, l'm going to go crazy.
So, please...Nikita-kun, stick your hot joystick in me!
Okay, if you say so.
lt is coming in.
This is what the inside of woman feels like.
lt's so warm and....
That's right...stick it in deep as you can...
Seeing Tamaye-san so excited is turning me on as well.
Don't be so rough from the start...
But it feels so good!
Hmm... My juice is pouring out.
My lower body is squeezing. l have never had
something like this before.
lt is my turn to move.
My pussy and your dick are touching each other, can't you see?
Yes, l can see it.
Nikita-kun, you, too. Move! lt will feel better for the both of us.
But l cannot hold any longer.
What? We just started.
Oh my. lf you move too much......
You look like you need to let it out, Nikita-kun.
lf you like me that much, l'll let you soon.
But, you've got to fuck me harder now.
Nikita-kun, more...more!
Give it to me harder. Harder!!
Yes, there, right there, l can't hold it. lt's killing me!
l can't hold any longer!
Cum, cum on me. Cum all over me.
l'm cumming. Nikita's cumming.
You made it. Your penis is still pumping a lot of cum out.
The Alternative Trivia Research Club, watch out.
Hey! l'm so sorry for being late;
l was watching the Late Show Anime l taped.
Hi, President, Good morning.
Good morning, Tama-chan.
Who is this?
This is Nikita Shindo. He wants to be a member.
Wh...What?
Nice to meet you.
How come you are stareing at me in a jokingly way.
Because this is the Akiba style.
Well, it is OK. l am the president of this club,
Tomoki Kuribayashi. Call me K.T.
Here you go, his nickname.
By the way, Tama-chan, ls that maid costume for the comic convention on this weekend?
Yes, isn't it pretty?
Comic convention?
Nikita-kun, are you a comic convention virgin?
Virgin....
Ok, then this is going to be your first one.
You already know you're my first.
OK then, next Saturday we will celebrate Nikita-kun's welcoming party at the convention.
l agree.
Comrades, we will be friends.
K.T.-senpai
ls this the right thing to do?
Thank you. Please keep supporting me.
Wow, that was Tetsuko-san.
Although she is not a popular radio actress, she does make quite an appearance.
Man, no way am l going to wash my hands today!
Excuse me? l have something to ask you.
Man, who is bothering me now.
Umm...
Ti.... Tita!
Huh?
Crap, l didn't mean to say that out loud.
Well, my name is Ren Aoi. Have we met before?
Uh, er, no...
So her name is Ren-san. what an elegant name she has!
l am here to buy a hair dryer, but this is my first time in Akihabara.
l have no idea where to buy it...l was wondering if you can show me around?
What!? Are you sure you want me.
Yes, certainly.
Dear sun goddess,
l'll quit playing Bishojyo games late night and stop tuning into the actress's radio show.
So, please! Please give me a bit more of miracles!
Uh, well, it's such a nice weather, don't you think?
Thank you very much today. l really enjoyed.
lt was a piece of cake, haha...
Akihabara, it is a good area.
After all, it is the sanctuary of the Akiba style.
Can l see you again?
May l?
ls she asking me out on a date?
Please?
Yes. l will be more than happy to see you again.
Ok, then l will see you on this coming Saturday here.
Bye now. Thank you so much for today.
lt means... This Saturday...
Oh, shit! l have to go to the comic convention this Saturday!
Holy....
Damn, What should l do?
Oh no, not again.
Hey!
l am so sorry.
Hey, you! Stay at the door and don't move an inch!
Why does this always happen to me...?
Wait a minute. l might have seen the costume before.
What the hell do you think you are doing!?
lt is just an accident.
No. On purpose. lt must be on purpose.
What ever you say, the door was unlocked and how would l know you are undressed.
Today is the third day of the radio actors' surprise event!
And there is no place l can change my clothes in Akihabara.
What? What is the matter with you?
lt is you, Tetsuko-san. You are the radio actress, Tetsuko Misaki.
W, why do you know my acting name?
l have been a fan of yours since you were Tetsuko in "My sister is a Stewardess".
But why?
You reminded me of a bad memory.
Was it because it was a Bishojyo game?
Bishojyo games are hard to work with!
...What about it?
Like the sex scenes. l just didn't know anything...about it.
Are you.... Are you a virgin, Tetsuko-san?
Again, surprise attack.
My next job is another bishojyo game...
What do you have in mind, Tetsuko-san?
That expression...it seems as if you have something mischievous planned.
Please help me with my acting.
Just a little bit.
What kind?
Sex.
What?
Something must be wrong. Even bishojyo games don't have such a flow.
Don't take this the wrong way. lt is just a practice for my acting.
How about my feelings?
l need...help.
You are very serious. l understand.
Please let me help you.
You don't have to be so obvious.
lt came out naturally...
Work habit or something?
N, no, and it's not a post recording line either.
Hey, don't you use your fingers too much.
No, there is the entrance.
You are getting wet.
Stupid...Don't be so straightforward.
You are making me blush.
No, not there, it' s dirty.
Let me know if it hurts.
Certainly.
This is so good, Tetsuko-san.
Aren't we supposed to be stopping some where in the middle, right?
You can't stop like this.
Well, she never cares about my feelings.
D, does it hurt?
No, it is all right. Do it right.
How do you feel?
l don't know what to say. l am moaning no matter what.
ls that so?
l like it when you stab it in deep.
Like this?
Oh no! N, no l can't stop moaning...and l'm getting really turned on.
Getting turned on?
l want you to fuck me harder.
Ok, l give you harder.
This is my first time but it feels so good.
Am l a whore?
Tetsuko-san...
Call me Renka.... Please...
Renka...
l am cumming!
Renka-san, Me, too. l am cumming!
Please cum!
Stupid brother.
Hello, this is the Shindos.