You like taking it in both holes at the same time?
Oh yes, yes.
Cuming!
Oh, it's in so deep.
Cuming, cuming, cuming!
l can feel it...
Cuming!
lt's still hard!?
Good...
Oh god, yes...
Good.
Ma'am.
l came so much in your ass!
Hey, lets switch holes.
Come on, work harder so you can make my friend cum.
Ma'am...l'm going to cum soon.
Give it to me...
Give it to me on my face!
He's going to cum inside me again.
Oh no...
Cuming!
What, he's still hard!? But why?
M, Mother...
No, not the butt...
lt'll make too much noise...
lf you don't squirt the cum out, we can't fuck your ass again.
Ma'am, now that your ass is cleaned, l'm going to start with your pussy.
Oh god.
You came again, pervert?
Lets stretch that ass.
You are so damn sensitive.
You're such a pervert, l've never come across a woman like you.
Lick the dick that was in your ass.
What!?
You can cum all you want, Ma'am.
Ma'am, you are so damn sexy.
Mother!?
Koji, l love you...cuming.
Oh shit man.
lt's time to leave.
Dam you whore, how many times were you fucked!?
How did you like those young guys?
You were crying in lust.
Damn whore, learn to control your damn urges!
l only did it because you...
You dare talk back to me bitch!?
lt's up!
l will punish you for sleeping with other men!
Speak up!
Move those hips!
You're a stupid whore that can only think about dicks!
Come on Sumie, put your effort into it!
Cuming, cuming, cuming, cuming, cuming!!
Brother, am l doing this right?
Yeah, probably.
Kouji.
Can l have a moment?
Your mother...wants to talk about something.
Alright, l'll be right there.
Kaoru, you can finish the rest yourself.
You don't need me here anyway, l'm useless.
l believe Kouji is in a greater shock than l am about...that incident.
Kouji won't mention a word about it and there's nothing l can do.
Why did she do that?
Both of you, sit right there.
Such an uneasy feeling...
You two must despise me...
Of course not.
You must have a reason.
Other wise, you wouldn't...do that...
No matter what l say right now, it'll only sound like an excuse.
But please listen...no hear me out.
l want you to know.
The truth about Tomizo Takayanagi.
Before coming here, l use to work and reside with a famous Sado family.
One day, the family's son and l fell in love.
His family did not like me, but l was living happily with him and our child, Kaoru.
However, that happiness didn't last forever.
The institute that supported the family went bankrupt.
On top of that, they lost more money with stocks and real estate.
He found a new girl and ran away.
Loosing the property seemed inevitable, all of us were giving up on hope.
That's when Tomizo volunteered to help.
He was a pupil of the class, but at the same time he was also a VIP because of his power.
However, his help came with a price...he wanted me and Kaoru to move in to his estate.
Of course l declined.
But the family convinced me otherwise.
l couldn't refuse when they were begging me so desperately.
And that's how l came here as his third wife.
l didn't come here because l wanted to, but as his wife and Kouji's mother, l did the best l could.
But...
He didn't look at me as either a wife or a mother.
l was merely a...''toy'' to satisfy his needs.
l was raped day after day, almost non-stop.
He wouldn't even let me properly take care of Kaoru.
lf l lost consciousness, he would splash water on me.
After a few months of being here, he started inviting guests.
Every night after, l was violated by strangers.
Lawyers, rich and famous, politicians and so on.
Different men using me for their lust...
About that time, l learned a secret.
Tomizo was the one who tricked my ex-husband in loosing all that money.
lt was all his doing.
For his own desire...
That's so...cruel.
Yes, you're right...
But, l have no right to think that.
All those encounters made me a person who can't live without sex.
l'm afraid of myself...
l know exactly what you mean, Mother.
lt's natural for a woman to be like that, because...
l as well...
l'm so sorry for having to tell you this story...
By the way, why were you two in the closet?
W, well...
We were having sex.
We watched you get fucked as we were having a little workout.
ln other words, we were fucking.
That wasn't the only day.
lt's been going on for months.
ln the restroom...
The bathtub...
On her bed.
You name it, anywhere.
She even lets me fuck her ass.
l can't get enough of her body.
But you two are brother and....sister.
C, can't be...
Mom, where are you?
lt's time for bath, bath, bath!
lt's okay for you to go, Mitsuko.
But...
Please go, l want to talk to Kouji alone
OK...
Oh, Mom!
Well, lets go take a bath.
OK!
Kouji, why...what made you like this?
You use to be so kind and caring, even took care of Kaoru.
lt's your fault.
lt's all your fault!
l can't explain myself.
But when l saw you having sex with those two, my memories came back...
When l was young, l was heading to the bathroom...then l heard voices.
l walked toward the voice, then...
l saw you with men and...
Stop!
lt's...my...fault?
To us, you act like a mother, but in front of other men...
A whore!
Stop it Kouji, l'm your mother...
So you're alright with my dad, but not me?
T, that's not it Kouji, but...
You neglect me like my dad and my brother...
Kouji...
Just for now...l will be yours, Kouji...
Mother!
Mother...
Kouji...
Mother!
lt's so hard...
l never had one this hard.
Beautiful...
Mother, let me stick it in!
OK, l'll take everything you give me.
Come...
Come inside your mother.
l will take care of you.
Mother, l'm cuming!
Mother.
Kouji.
Kaoru?
Kaoru, wait, listen to me!
Kaoru, wait!
M, Mother?
lt's nothing, don't worry Mitsuko.
Kaoru!
Mother and Kaoru arguing?
That's hard to believe.
Lets play house, brother.
Excuse me, Kouji.
What happened between you and Mother?
You, Kaoru and Mother have been acting strangely...
Nothing...happened.
Nothing at all...
Kouji.
Your mother...l am thinking of leaving this house.
lt's not because of what just happened.
l just found out recently.
My ex-husband's estate, even with help they couldn't keep their doors open.
There's no need for me to repay them any longer.
Besides, l can't have Kaoru...
So...
That's great news.
lt's best that you two move away and live happily together.
There's no reason to listen to that bastard.
You're alright with that?
That's not for me to decide.
You and Kaoru should be living happily together.
l'll just go back to days before you were here, not a big deal.
Man, l should've slept with you a long time ago.
l waited this long, for such little time.
Well, l still have Sis, so l won't be deprived or anything...
Kouji...
l'm sorry.
Mitsuko.
lchiro?
ls that for my father?
Yes, he hasn't been out of his room lately and...
the food he's been eating are mixed with medicines.
l'm starting to worry.
l'll take it to him.
lt's OK.
OK...
l wonder what came over lchiro?
K, Kouji!
W, what are you doing to Mother!?
No...l'm the one who wants it.
This is the only way l know how to make Kouji happy.
Mother, what are you saying?
Mltsuko, l can understand why you are so into him.
l too am addicted to his manly thing.
l'm going to cum, drink it!
S, she drank it!?
Lets go to my room, Sis.
l'll take care of both of your asses.
Your ass is lonely, right?
K, Kouji, please let me rest...
Three times in a row, i, it's making me crazy!
Alright then...
lt's your turn Mother.
His appetite and energy makes me think...
That he doesn't want this to end forever.
Kouji, you're fucking your mother's ass so hard that...!
Bodies touching bodies, tied together with lust..
l can tell that he is trying everything he can to hide his sadness.
l'm right here.
l won't go anywhere.
As much as you want me, l also want you...
A mother, a sister, a friend, a lover, l'll be whatever you want me to be.
l'll be yours...
What did you say?
Say that again, Sumie.
Here.
l want to file a divorce.
What?
Looks like l fell asleep.
Sis?
Kaoru!?
Brother...l don't want to be away from you.
A bitch that l bought with money is telling me what to do!?
lf you forgot who's women you are, l'll make you remember Sumie!
K, Kaoru...you're a....girl!?