Ryuuichi! Cut it out already!
I know what you did!
W-What is it so suddenly...?
With Chinatsu-san and Manami-san, you...
W-Well...
You had sex with them, didn't you?
Having Chinatsu-san stroke your c-cock, and...
And getting her to lick it, too!
B-But, she was the one who...
Jeez! Even though it was your first time, you were thrusting like there was no tomorrow!
And you...
And you came so much as well.
You're such a pervert, Ryuuichi!
W-Were you watching...?
Besides, even if you don't have anywhere else to live,
it's crazy that you thought returning to a home full of home-stay girls was a good idea!
Even when you were doing lewd things with Manami-san,
you got so hard just from looking at her breasts!
Well...! That couldn't be helped...
Moreover,
when you two were doing it, you were constantly making Manami-san say lewd things, too!
Thing's like "c-cock" and stuff...
A-And "pussy"...
A-And "anal"...
T-That's because Manami-san requested...
She said that she'd get more excited that way...
Are you a moron?!
But, there's something more unforgivable that you've done...
You saw, didn't you?
Saw... What?
T-That's...
Where I was... doing lewd things to myself...
Eh?! No, um... that's...
W-Well...
Pervert.
Uh, well...
It's not only my fault!
Since you didn't shut the door properly, I...
Show it to me!
Like I said, s-show me yourself m-masturbating, too!
Eh?!
Then it'll be fair!
W-What's with that...?
This isn't good... What can I say to end this peacefully...?
I-I know!
Fine, if you insist that much, then give me material!
Eh? Material?
That's right, material.
If you show me yourself masturbating again, then I might consider it.
I bet she'll give up from that!
Fine, then!
I-I said fine!
I'll masturbate for you or whatever!
But in return, you have to show me as well!
Understood?!
Y-Yes!
T-Things are getting out of hand again...
Presented by Shikkaku
H-How is this...?
Well, even if you ask me...
You should start, too!
L-Let's stop this...
This isn't right...
What on Earth are you saying?!
Even though I'm doing this much for you, are you still going to complain?!
I-I'm sorry...
Then be a man and take off your pants!
Eh?!
Amazing...
Ryuuichi's cock is so big...
I-Is he getting excited from looking at me?
Amazing, it's so... So embarrassing!
I can even smell him from over here...
It's such a lewd smell!
I'll start feeling strange...
No, it's too much-!
Lisa, are you getting excited just from the smell?
I can't help it-!
From his smell, I...!
I-Is it strange...?
Am I strange?
It's not strange, I'm like this too, after all...
I-I'm starting to feel good, too...!
N-No...!
From watching Ryuuichi m-masturbate, I...
No-! When I watch, I...!
No-!
Amazing-! It's... N-No-!
It feels so good!
It feels amazing!
No... This is... No-!
I'm gonna...
Cum! Cum with me!
Ryuuichi! P-Pour it on Lisa!
Let out your semen all over me!
S-Such a strong smell...
So it's like this...
Amazing, it's still so big...
Lisa-! If you do that...!
Ryuuichi... Ryuuichi...!
No-! Ryuuichi, it feels too good!
Lisa, I can't...
O-Okay...
But be gentle, okay?
I'm... Well...
It's my first time, so...
Yeah, I think it'll be fine.
See, your pussy is already dripping wet, Lisa...
Jeez, you pervert!
Don't say such embarrassing things!
S-Since it's you, Ryuuichi, I'll allow it...
P-Please be gentle...
Y-Yeah...
I didn't know Lisa was this cute...
I-I'm putting it in.
O-Okay...
It's a bit tight...
I-It hurts-!
A-Are you okay?!
I-It hurts!
Please don't move!
Okay, got it...
Should I take it out?
D-Don't move-!
Please don't move just yet!
O-Okay...
I-I think I'll be alright in a moment, so...
Sure, I'll stay still.
Ryuuichi...
Thanks... Sorry about this...
No, it's fine.
Let's take our time.
Ryuuichi...
Can you slowly take it out...?
Are you sure?
Yes, I think...
Then...
Sorry!
I-I'm alright...
You don't have to strain yourself...
Ryuuichi, can you put it in again?
Are you okay now?
I think so...
I'm putting it in slowly...
Sorry-!
Does it still hurt?
Yeah, but less so than before...
Please continue, Ryuuichi...
Alright.
Lisa?!
Please keep going-!
Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm fine...
You mustn't push yourself...
Yes, thanks, but I'm mostly fine now...
Really?
Yeah, it feels good...
It feels good! Even though it's my first time, I'm...!
It feels good!
A-Amazing, this feels amazing!
Ryuuichi, more... More!
We're really doing it!
I'm really having sex with Ryuuichi!
We're actually doing it!
It's going in so deep!
I-If you tighten around me that much, I'll-!
It's fine, let it out like this!
I-I want it to be complete!
B-But...!
P-Please, cum, cum with me at the same time-!
Lisa-!
No-! I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
No-!
I-I'm gonna...!
Hey, Ryuuichi...
How was it...?
Eh? What do you mean?
Um, well...
Compared to Chinatsu-san and Manami-san, was I...
W-Were you...?
Was my... Uh...
Well... D-Did my pussy feel good?
Eh?! What-?
Like I said, was m-my...
I was asking if my pussy felt good! Jeez, don't make me repeat it!
S-So cute...
Yeah, your pussy was great, Lisa.
Ow-!
That hurt!
She didn't have to hit me...
She was the one who asked me...
But...
I was asking if my pussy felt good!
Who knew she had such a cute side to her?
Oh no, when I start to think about it, I'm beginning to want seconds...
Ryuuichi-kun, I brought you your laundry...
Oh my.
Wha-! T-This isn't...
I'm caught red handed!
Now that I think about it, one of the reasons I left was so that Mom wouldn't ever find me like this...
I'll leave this place for sure next time.
Hey, wha-?!
You mustn't forget to shut the door properly when you're doing something like this.
M-Mom!
Don't worry.
Mom will help you out.
This totally isn't right!
But your cock is so hot, Ryuuichi-kun...
See?
You've gotten so hard and you're leaking from the tip!
Mom-!
You mustn't do this-!
Even if we aren't blood related-!
Wait-!
Thanks for the meal!
Ryuuichi-kun, you don't need to hold back.
Whenever you're backed up, Mom will take care of it!
Today, Mom will do whatever you want, Ryuuichi-kun.
Absolutely anything!
Mom...
H-How does this look?
Mom... You're beautiful.
Ryuuichi-kun...
Oh, jeez...
You're such a pervert...
Sorry Mom, but I-I'm...
Jeez, this sure is troubling...
You came just before, but...
Getting hard like this already...
You sure have grown down here!
It's so hot...
C'mon, Ryuuichi-kun...
Please put your towering cock into Mom's pussy...
My pussy... Please mess up Mom's pussy!
Alright then, I'm putting it in, Mom...
Yes, that's it, Ryuuichi-kun!
That's it!
Mom has actually always wanted to do it with you, Ryuuichi-kun!
I wanted to have sex... I wanted to have sex with you, Ryuuichi-kun!
Ryuuichi-kun! Ryuuichi-kun, I love you!
More, thrust me more!
Thrust inside me with all of your strength!
S-So good!
Your cock, i-it's...!
It's going into my... Your Mom's...
It's going so deep into Mom's pussy-!
Please mess up my pussy-!
Mom-! Your insides are so wet, i-it's too pleasurable!
I'm sorry!
Mom is feeling too good-!
So good! It's reaching my deepest spots-!
Amazing, amazing-!
M-My pussy...!
M-Mom, it's amazing!
I didn't know that you could do anal, too!
That's right!
Mom really wanted you to screw her butt really hard with your cock!
So good-!
Good! It's so good-!
Both my breasts and my butt feel... Amazing!
M-Mom, I'm hitting the dildo you inserted up front!
I-I'm sorry, M-Mom can't bear it any longer!
I can't stop myself!
That's it, thrust inside my butt from below-!
That's it! It's amazing!
I can't bear it...
More... Rub my breasts more!
My butt...! My Pussy...!
M-My butt...! My pussy-!
Mom-!
Don't do me there!
Then, to pay you back...
M-Mom!
Mom! This place is the best after all!
Mom's pussy is good, isn't it?
It's good, right?
I'm so happy!
It's alright, release it wherever you want!
May it be my butt, my pussy or my mouth,
let it out wherever you want!
Release as much as you want!
I-It's coming, it's coming-!
I'm coming!
Release all your semen... in Mom's pussy, Ryuuichi-kun!
Let it out, let it out!
Your cock is so good...
Let it out!
I'm coming! I'm about to come!
Your semen is about to come into my pussy-!
M-Mom, I'm tired...
Getting yourself so dirty... you're such a bad boy.
Mom will clean you up...
Mom-!
Seriously, taking care of you is such a chore...
Heh? You sure have a nice body, Manami-san.
Everything you wear suits you!
Same goes for you, Chinatsu-san. It suits you really well.
I bought a new one as well!
What's going on here?
You see, Chinatsu-kun won a trip in a lottery at the shopping district.
What!? No way! Seriously!? Isn't that amazing!?
A resort hotel and a private beach on a southern island in the southern sea!?
I can't wait any longer!
I'm gonna buy a swimsuit!
Take care!
She sure is excited!
The sea, huh?
This sure has gotten troublesome...