Kaoru, you're a...girl?
Brother.
l've always...
Brother...
W, w, what are you trying to say Kaoru?
We're brothers...l mean, you're my sister...?
Can you please explain?
l'm so confused.
Ok.
A long time ago...before coming to this house, my mom made me do this.
She told me to pretend l'm a boy, and never reveal myself as a girl.
But why?
l don't know exactly why, but...
She said it's to protect me from that man.
She must be referring to my dad.
Besides, l can't have Kaoru...so...
So that's what she meant.
But today Mother said...
We need to leave this place before you get involved.
There's no reason to stay here.
l know she's trying to protect me.
But, l...l don't want to be away from you.
l want to be with you...forever...and ever.
Kaoru!?
l saw you having sex with mom.
She's different from Mother or Sis.
Mother looked happy.
She's skinny.
Please do to me, the same thing...you did with mom.
l have to protect her from harm.
lt'll probably hurt.
lf it's you, l'm fine...
Are you sure about this?
B, Brother...
lt's so...
B, Brother, it's dirty down there.
l'm going to stop.
l know you're scared, don't force yourself.
You're just lost in the situation.
No, l'm not.
You want to continue or would you rather cuddle?
Cuddle.
See.
But you're hard, Brother.
S, stop that!
Before we cuddle, l want to make you happy...
lt's my first time but l hope l can pleasure you, Brother.
She's serious.
She isn't good, but...
Kaoru.
Kaoru, it's good.
Kaoru, stop, going to cum!
lf Kaoru stays here, dad will eventually find out that he's a she.
l do think she should move out with her mother.
Brother, don't leave me...
l never thought l would be worried about others.
Where is Sumie, she should be here by now?
Good morning, Mitsuko
Good morning, Honey.
You're up early on your day off.
Mother is running errands for Father.
l'll take Father's breakfast to him, just have it ready.
Thanks.
H, Honey, wait.
One more thing.
Don't go near the storage.
Mother...Mother...Mother?
lt's unlike Mother to go out without telling me.
She has to be around here somewhere.
Mother?
l never noticed these stairs before
Mother!
Mother, l'll free you!
Brother!!!
Kaoru?
You're a girl? How dare you trick me all this time.
l love young girls like you, l'll take care of you!
What's wrong, cry like the bitch you are!
You're my bitch forever, got it!?
You whore!
ls it hot Sumie? l'll plug your ass with it.
l'll dlip the wax in your ass, slowly.
No, please forgive me...
Sis, have you seen Kaoru?
Kaoru? No, l haven't.
That's strange... her shoes are still here.
Come to think of it, l haven't seen Mother or Father either.
Father too?
Speaking of strange, lchirou said don't go near the storage.
The storage?
Shit.
She lost consciousness again...
Fucking bitch!
You're making a mess with your shit and piss!
How can l get hard, whore!?
You're useless.
Please forgive her!
Oh yeah, there's the young one.
Nothing is better than young girls.
Smooth skin!
Stop!
lt's hard, it's hard!
You like?
What's this, you're taking a piss?
Please...stop.
This is the best elixir to keep me young!
No, please help me Brother, Brother!
What the fuck are you doing!?
Kouji!
Brother?
l'll kill you, you old piece of shit!
Damn brat!
Brother!
Can you stand?
Yeah.
Untie Mother and get out of here.
What is this?
Who's there?
lchirou, come help me now!
lchirou, you listening, lchirou!?
You were supposed to die two weeks ago.
Your endurance surprises me.
You probably would've lived another 10 years.
You know...by natural causes.
l can't wait that long.
l used a drug that can't be traced, spent lots of money on it too...
Yet you die by fire.
You continue to betray me.
Well, l can at least thank you for cremating yourself.
B, bastard!
Kaoru, go first.
No, Mother first.
Brother!!
Kaoru!!
What tragedy...
l wish you the best.
OK, thank you very much.
That's the last guest.
Yes.
Well, l need to get ready.
OK.
The fire that happened three days ago burned the entire storage.
lt even cremated his body.
lt's strange that a fire started in a storage, but an investigation never took place.
Clean up tomorrow, get some rest for now.
l'll bathe Aya tonight.
l'm sure he's behind it.
lt's hard to say, but he looks very satisfied.
l don't think anyone is truly sad that he is dead.
lt's sad that no one really cares about him, though.
How are you feeling?
l'm fine, did everyone leave?
Yeah, there was a lot of people.
He sure knew lots.
Heh, he's old.
By some miracle, Kouji was not injured heavily and was burnt only a little.
Man, l'm suddenly in pain.
l think l need to suck on those to heal.
Kouji, not right now, they'll...
l'm in pain, in pain, l need tits.
Kouji won't say what happened in that burning storage, but...
Oh, you two better stop.
Remember, she's the star.
He did everything he can to protect...my dear Kaoru.
You saved me Brother.
My body, my soul.
Please have me...take me.
Go on Kaoru, let him take care of you.
Please take care of Kaoru, Kouji.
Better treat her well.
What are you going to do?
Kaoru will be going to an all girl school far away starting next week
Going to live far away from here.
What about Kouji?
He said he wants to graduate first.
After that, he isn't sure.
But Kaoru believes in him.
That Kouji will...
Will come get her one day.
Kaoru?
l'm fine...
My mind went blank...l felt like l was in heaven.
Um, Mother?
What is it?
Make Brother feel good.
l can't do it myself so l need help, please...
Alright, l do need to thank him for saving me.
Please have me as well.
Mother...
l no longer belong here.
Sis!
Where do you think you're going?
Don't forget that you're my girl... come do your daily chore.
Yes.
l know this will end one day, but l don't want it to.
My lust takes over my sanity.
For now, l'll let my lust take over me.
Us girls are probably nothing more than animals caught by the trap set by the Takayanagi family.
This cursed cycle must have been going on forever.
Ever since l came here...
A lot has happened.
And...
lt won't ever end.