Yes... I'm gonna cum.
Cum, Megumi!
I'm cumming!
That's not being fair, Brother. You're only paying attention to Mom.
It's so good... You taste like Mom.
Yuna wanted a family.
No matter how twisted the situation may be, she got what she wanted.
It's a bond created by my sadistic tendencies,
Yuna's yearning for a family, and Megumi's conspiracy.
Everything began shortly after...
my father's death, with Megumi's suggestion.
What is it that you wanted to talk about?
I want you to leave this house.
I'll pay for any moving costs. It's the least I could do.
You're so cold. We're family.
A family? You booted my mother out of the picture and married him!
My father's will states that I'm getting everything.
I'm glad I'll never have to see you again.
I see. So you don't want to give the gold digger any money.
Do you really think chasing me away is okay?
You find it funny?
Listen, you've inherited everything from Kazuma Wakao,
including all of his paintings.
And?
That's the problem. You'll have to pay a huge inheritance tax.
Did you know? The art assessors for paintings are ruthless.
It's common to leave the price tag it got during the economic bubble.
Currently the market price is a third of what it used to be...
In the worst case, you might only get a tenth of what it was worth.
Do you know what this means?
Even if I sell the paintings, I can't afford the inheritance tax.
Exactly. You can try to protect your fortune,
but you might become bankrupt.
You're just saying that because you want the money.
I could care less about you inheriting the money.
His paintings... Kazuo Wakao's paintings he did himself...
Give them to me.
If you give me the paintings he did,
I'll handle the inheritance tax issue.
Give my father's paintings to you?
The rest of the inheritance is yours.
I'm only asking for the paintings. Are you not convinced?
I can't give you all of them.
Then I have a suggestion.
What is it?
Kyosuke-kun, do you want Yuna?
Yes, you can do whatever you want to her.
You want to fuck her, don't you?
You're her mother! You're crazy. She's my sister.
But you're not related. Anyway, about the paintings...
Just give me the rights to the paintings,
and I'll take care of the rest.
And let me stay here a bit longer, and that'll suffice.
Yuna won't do it...
Leave Yuna to me.
Yuna won't refuse you.
I can't explain it to you now, but you'll probably figure it out.
It's so unusual for us to sit and eat dinner together.
It really is.
I'm so happy you're both eating dinner with me.
Really?
Yeah.
Will we be able to eat dinner together from now on?
We'll do our best to make it as often as we can.
Right, Kyosuke-kun?
Really?
But don't force yourself, Mom. I know work is important.
I promise I won't.
Yuna, I need to have a talk with you later.
A talk?
Yes, it's very important.
Okay...
Brother.
Is it true what Mom said? Are you kicking us out?
I finally have a family... I don't want us to separate...
I don't want that.
If I try hard... Will we really be able to stay and live together?
Yeah.
Really?
No...
You're beautiful, Yuna.
Brother... I'm so sad...
It's getting hard.
No!
You're wet, Yuna.
You're lying. Brother, please don't stare.
No...
I... I'm... going to go crazy!
Brother...
N... No!
Yuna! We've gotten this far! You can't blue-ball me!
No, I can't. I don't want to have sex with you like this...
Yuna!
I don't want to. No matter what you say,
I don't want my first time to be like this.
Brother, please. Not like this. I'll do anything else.
You can do anything else.
Anything but, huh? Are you sure, Yuna?
You'll let me do anything but that?
Yes. But please promise me. I want to save my virginity.
Okay. I promise.
I'm gonna get going. Please take care of the cleanup.
Yes, Mother.
Brother...
I... I'm sorry. I got a flashback of last night...
I'm embarrassed. When I think about what I did with you...
Yuna, you remember our promise, right?
Yes...
His masterpiece, The Yearn of the Morn,
is missing from his  raisonne.
Why did he do that?
Brother...
It's my father's raisonne-- a catalog of my father's works.
He made it himself while he was in the hospital. He gave it to me.
Please, Brother...
Please only bully me in the house...
How does it feel not to wear any underwear?
It's embarrassing.
You're wet, Yuna.
Someone's gonna notice.
You're enjoying it.
No...
I have a lot to teach you.
Huh? No!
So we'll do this design, then?
Yes... You can go home for today, Nakuru.
Okay.
How unusual. I think this is your first visit here.
I heard you're doing an exhibition of my father's works.
We're behind schedule, so we're not ready to do it yet.
The Yearn of the Morn isn't displayed.
Oh, the tax office and the Ministry of Cultural Affairs...
are starting to eye the piece.
I can't display it so carelessly.
Do Not Enter
Staff Only
I see.
Chemistry Lab
Let's try this one today.
Where do you want it, Yuna?
Not there!
Right, the promise! Then let's do this one.
No, it'll tear!
You can handle this.
But... I'm scared, Brother.
You said you'd do anything.
I want to see you moan in pleasure from this.
But...
Where do you want it, Yuna? Here? Or...
Why don't you tell me?
In the butt...
Whose butt?
My... Please put it in my butt...
You're terrible, Brother.
Come on, Yuna. Tell me what's happening.
Go on...
The test tube is going in my butt and...
What do you see inside?
I can see inside my rectum.
My butt hole... My butt hole is going to get loose.
Brother...
Your juices are flowing out of your pussy again.
You're lying...
I didn't know you could feel it through your asshole.
Don't... You're wrong...
Then why is it gushing out?
Don't do it so fast... I...
Oh, no!
As my sadistic tendencies took over, I started Yuna's training.
Was Yuna a masochist in general?
I was impressed with how well she kept...
enduring the embarrassment.
I started to see a change in Yuna after each time...
she reached ecstasy, and I started to taste...
a bittersweet guilt and satisfaction.
It's hot!
Perhaps this is what you call immorality.
Brother...
I'll do anything, hurt me more...
Hurt me lots more...
I love you, Brother...
Brother...
Mom.
Are you getting along with Kyosuke-kun?
Yes.
You should become more honest with yourself.
I'm happy as long as we can stay together.
By the way, I saw Dad's book the other day.
Which one?
Brother said it was a raisonne. He said Dad made it.
I see...
Kyosuke-kun.
Can I see the raisonne that Kazuma Wakao compiled himself?
How do you know about it?
Oh, Yuna. Sure.
How uncharacteristic of you. You're not putting up a fight.
Oh, that's right. There's something I wanted to ask you...
about this raisonne.
The Yearn of the Morn you're hoarding isn't in here.
Brother.
Yuna, raise your ass up high.
L... Like this?
You're gonna get punished now.
You told Megumi-san about the raisonne, didn't you?
I did...
You're hurting me, Brother!
Because of your blabber mouth, I lost a one-up on her!
Yuna, do you think it's a good thing to trouble me?
It's a bad thing.
Yuna's been...
Yuna's been bad.
So...
So please punish me.
Yuna's been bad. So... Please punish me!
Yuna's been very bad. More! Punish me more!
Yuna, you told her because you wanted to get punished, didn't you?
Yes... Please give me a more harsh punishment.
Why are you so wet, Yuna?
You lie...
You feel it when you're in pain.
No...
You feel it by getting your ass slapped. You're a masochist.
No, I'm not...
Yuna, what do you want me to do with this?
Your pussy is answering for you.
You like it when it hurts, right? Say it or I won't put it on.
It hurts and it's starting to sting, but it feels good.
Does it feel good, Yuna?
It feels really good. It feels good.
Then do you want one here, too?
But that's...
Beg for it if you want it.
Please put a clothespin on my clit.
Yes, it feels so good!
Please, Brother! More! Pull harder!
Pull it as if you're going to rip my nipples and clit off!
It's so warm.
It feels so good.
C'mon, Yuna! Hey!
We're gonna be late. Come on!
Serika, wait!
No way!
Serika!
Brother!
Brother. Brother, dinner's ready.
Are you not here? Brother?
Kyosuke, I made that painting as something for our family.
It's my answer to The Yearn of the Morn.
That painting contains all of the answers.
The Night's End. It's the title of that piece.
Father. Father...
Talk to me about this when I get back.
I'm still at the crematory.
Oh! Hi, Brother!
Kyosuke! Come here and join us.
Mother...
Um... Can I call you Brother?
Sure, you're...
Yes! I'm Yuna. Nice to meet you. Brother.
Brother!
I wonder how people see us?
I wonder if people think we're siblings or lovers?
Your guess is as good as mine.
I was really happy when you asked me to go out with you today.
You haven't paid much attention to me since the last time.
This was on a whim.
You had me worried. I thought you were...
There are times when I want to know how you feel too, you know.
Brother.
You used to laugh a lot when you first came to the house.
You were eighteen.
But ever since Dad went into the hospital, you smiled less.
When I see you lately, it reminds me of the time when you first moved in.
The time when you used to laugh so happily...
Can I call you Brother?
I'm so happy.
What is it?
No, nothing.
Brother. Do you really think Mom is after the inheritance money?
I don't think that anymore.
Good.
But her overprotectiveness for The Yearn of the Morn is...
I'm sure she's after something, but...
Brother... Do you not like her?
You know this too, but...
Dad started dating Megumi and left my mother.
Soon after, my mother became ill and passed away.
I know it's not just Megumi-san's fault...
But sometimes I think to myself...
Maybe she would be alive today if they'd never gotten divorced.
Sometimes that thought crosses my mind.
But if Mom and Dad had never gotten married,
I never would've met you!
I want the three of us to live together!
Forever...
Tie me, Brother...
Please, Brother, tighter...
Yes... The rope is digging into my pussy. It feels so good...
You've gotten really good, Yuna.
I'll make you feel really good.
Brother, lie down.
Okay.
It feels really good, Yuna.
It's oozing out.
I'm gonna cum!
That was really good, Yuna.
Brother, why are you keeping our promise?
I'm the one who took advantage of the promise.
I did terrible things to you,
but somewhere inside, I didn't want you to hate me.
If I broke our promise, I thought that I could never see you again.
I was always alone waiting for Mom.
I ate alone and cleaned all alone. All alone...
That's why I was so happy when I got...
a brother and a father all at once.
Having a family is so nice...
Fuck me.
Now that I know that you care about me, it's okay.
Please stick your cock in my pussy.
I'm coming in, Yuna.
Okay.
It's coming in! Your dick is coming inside of me.
Are you okay?
Yeah...
I'm going to move, Yuna.
I feel it. I feel it. I feel your cock.
It's so good. It's all the way inside.
Fuck me harder...
Yes... It feels so good...
Yuna, do you want to get fucked with this too?
If you want it, put it in yourself.
Really? It's so big... Can I really?
Yes! It's going in!
I can put it all the way in my butt!
It's mixing up my insides!
My insides are going to come out.
The vibrator and your dick are rubbing against each other inside me.
It's amazing! I'm going to cum! Can I cum? Can I cum, Brother?
I'm gonna cum too, Yuna.
Cum, Brother! Let's cum together!
I'm cumming!
Brother...
But is this really right?
Will my sadistic ways be satisfied with Yuna alone?
I was starting to realize a new desire awakening.
Meeting you in the darkness inside me...
was how I knew I was still alive.
While I understand what kind of things are allowed,
I still have to shut my eyes.
Like a swaying blossom, trying to adjust,
rippling in the water,
the river of time, in its course toward ruin,
will lift my apprehension.