A TOHO - O.B. PLANNlNG
PRODUCTlON
Based on Tetsu Adachi's
"Weather Report Girl"
I can't believe the old guy tried it!
You're serious?
Where does he get off
thinking he can pull that?
C'mon, just for today!
I said I set up that meeting
with the agency! Come on!
Hey!
You tryin' to make a fool of me?!
I said no!
Watch it.
Don't be so full of yourself, Keiko!
Because she...
SHE is coming back from France.
Your reign is over!
Keiko!
"She?"
WEATHER REPORT GIRL 2
Kaori Shimamori?
Yeah. She's been working
in France for the last two years.
As a demotion, right?
Did she get in trouble with a guy?
Not at all.
She isn't a tramp like you.
Well excuse me for being a tramp!
Look. Look. I'm a tramp.
She's from a rich family.
Dad's a member of the Diet.
So, she's just a
girl with connections.
Me! Me! I'll take it to her!
Like hell!
I'm giving this to Kaori!
A man would be proud
to get a job offer so soon!
Japan's changed, hasn't it?
What's the latest from Paris?
You're even more beautiful now!
Welcome back, Kaori.
Welcome back.
Merci. I'm overjoyed to
get such a warm reception.
So, you can still speak Japanese.
Japan's number one, right?
'Scuse me!
Keiko Nakadai!
So, you're the infamous
Weather Report Girl.
Kaori Shimamori.
How do you do?
You're a cool one, aren't you?
Just 'cuz your
daddy's such a big shot.
You've had it so easy growing up...
...you can't believe anyone
would ever be your enemy!
You little punk bitch!
I'm just a regular
employee making a living.
Don't go saying I use
my father's influence.
I don't want to have
anything to do with him.
Quit talking tough, bitch!
Things have changed
while you've been gone.
I'm running things in
this TV studio now!.
My, such mighty words
from a weather girl.
Haven't you heard?
The news anchor's a bit more important.
No more tits and ass shows.
From now on we're going
to have a decent news show...
...with Kaori here the lead anchor.
You can keep doing your
strip show, if you like.
That's it.
Put her in her place!
I hate flowers!
Stop it!
Why, you...!
I challenge you to
a duel! To the death!
Lemme go!
To the death, I say!
Keiko...
Keiko! Keiko!
What's wrong?
She's on soon.
I know she's in there,
but she won't answer.
Huh? It's open.
Wait, you can't just go in!
It's okay. Keiko, we're coming in!
Keiko!
Well?
You aren't...
Of course.
No underwear.
And when the light hits it,
the show really begins.
So, does this get
a rise out of you?
NEWSCASTER 9
Hello, everyone. Tonight we begin
a new series: Newscaster 9.
I'm your main anchor,
Kaori Shimamori.
P.M. Murakami said he'd call
an immediate meeting with...
...the other ministers to discuss
effective countermeasures.
They reached a
mutual agreement and...
You sit there, reading
your teleprompter script...
...and I get to show up any
way I damn well please!
Go ahead. I'm ready for you!
Yeah, everybody! Come on!
Diagram
Drastic action is expected
to improve the situation.
We have something just in.
At the Japanese embassy
in Nigeria early this morning...
Come on, raise this thing!
It's stuffy in here!
C'mon, move it!
This thing weighs a ton!
That report from Nigeria has
caused a change in our schedule.
I can't wait anymore!
Maybe if I started a fire...
Here we go!
Okay, let's do it!
Night!
The mike isn't there.
Get off the cord!
What the hell...?
Sorry. We thought
we could make it, but...
The news report ran over.
Why, that... THAT...!!
She stole my spot!
I had to wait down in that little
hole in this getup for an hour!
I'm not training to be a magician!
This was a once in a lifetime chance!
You...!!! I'm sorry.
I wasted time on that Nigeria
report and killed the schedule.
I didn't handle it as
well as I could have.
Besides that, I was disorganized
and ended up throwing everyone off.
I'm sorry.
Okay, people. Move it!
We're on battle stations tonight!
Get some people over
to the Foreign Ministry.
The press conference is at 11:00.
Get all the facts, okay?
Bet there were a lot of
calls about Newscaster 9 tonight.
Yeah. The lines
were jammed before.
They started ringing as
soon as the newscast began.
As soon as it began?
The reaction to Kaori
has been outstanding!
We had our hands full.
Sorry.
Are they still ringing?
Yeah. There've been
about 400 calls so far.
Hold it! How many were
complaints about me not going on?
Ummm... None, I think.
Nope, no one.
Not one?! Right.
Go on, enjoy yourself.
You get your kicks out of
feeling superior to other people.
We're all just employees.
The employees make the company.
Popularity like yours is
a fleeting thing.
What'll you do when you're thirty?
Get married and quit?
You're a disgustingly
boring woman.
But apparently more
popular than you.
She wasn't on...
Keiko wasn't on TV last night.
I'll leave it here.
Thanks.
Kei... Keiko...
Oh, Yamagishi.
Good morning.
Why are you dressed like...?
I'm acting like a new girl should.
I didn't know that.
She's still new here?
Keiko, what happened?
I shouldn't try to
rise above the rest.
I won't be an idol forever.
Can't let the fickle
audience lead me astray.
Stop it! I don't want
to see you like this!
Keiko Nakadai! You are the
almighty Weather Report Girl!
Well, aren't we looking
modest these days.
I'm through playing your games!
Just lemme have you, bitch!
I can do whatever I want to you.
Director's privilege!
Get her! Get her!
Choke the life outta her!
If I was dead I wouldn't
even let you lick me!
What are you gonna do?
Quit?
Piss off! I'll get back to where
I was even if I have to crawl!
Hold it!
Mr. Chairman!
You're out of the hospital?
This is no time to be
laying in some sickbed!
What have you done to
our gold mine, you idiot?!
Gold mine?
Mr. President!
What is all this?
The floor couldn't hold
all the letters protesting...
...Keiko not being on last night!
But no one called in about it.
Because your fans
were jamming up the lines!
Ms. Shimamori, if you bump
the weather report again...
...a full-scale riot may
break out! Remember that!
Yes, sir.
Keiko's disappeared.
You don't think she fell
with the mail, do you?!
Transform!
I'm back!
If I'm wet, it's only
because of the rain.
Why did I even believe it'd
turn out any differently?
But if I can't sleep,
that's because of you.
Everywhere I go, people
just seem to irritate me.
So all I do is just take a
deep breath and try to go on.
A woman's heart is like the
changing weather, you see.
And a kiss like that isn't
enough to set it ablaze.
After the rain stops, let's go.
Let's get our hearts racing along.
When it clears up,
we'll love like it's paradise.
After the rain stops, let's go...
As you can see, Newscaster 9
is beating all other news shows
With its 30% share,
the program is unmatched
However...
Our ratings data this
month shows all our programs..
...outside of Newscaster 9
are getting clobbered
Keiko and Kaori are
the prized boxed melons...
...in a store full of rotten fruit!
Come forth,
our Goddesses of Fortune!
These two will become
the new face of ATV!
We'll have a huge promotion
campaign to enhance our image.
I'll do what I can to help
us through this crisis.
I don't like working with her...
But we're all in the same boat!
Okay, let's get a picture
for the company newsletter.
Uh, you can keep
your clothes on for this.
Okay, you two.
Shoulders together. Smile.
As slutty as usual, eh?
I'll do what it takes to prove
I'm number one here at ATV.
Flashing your tits won't
keep you popular forever.
Maybe I'll think like that
when I'm as old as you are.
If your career lasts that long.
At least my figure will last
longer than yours.
Okay, have this and
this ready for tomorrow.
Michiko, we're running late.
Let's get to the rehearsal.
Right.
"Climb Mt. Niitaka"
She's calling...
She's calling for me!
Michiko! The rehearsal!
I couldn't find this belt.
Figured you'd know where it was.
But I found it anyway, so it's okay.
For that?!
You weren't working
or anything, were you?
Well, yeah...
It's just some stupid
voice-over stuff, right?
You could blow that off.
Yeah, you're right.
And who got me kicked
into that stupid job?
Since you're here, why
don't you clean up this place?
Oh, and the laundry needs to be done.
Sorry. I'll try to keep on top of it.
Harpy! Hellspawn bitch!
What's wrong, old timer?
You look blue.
Miss Shimamori.
Are you really just doing
the morning radio show now?.
And some voice-overs, too.
Nothing that gets your
face on the screen, huh?
Things didn't work out
being the old weather girl?
Yeah. That's a job for young girls.
Like Keiko Nakadai?
I think it's time Keiko took a fall.
There's something about
a really nice restaurant.
Even the air seems different.
If the PR staff hadn't let us come...
...I doubt we'd ever have seen
one of these from the inside.
Presenting Miss Kaori Shimamura
and Miss Keiko Nakadai!
Keiko... She's lovely...
Let's get some good pictures.
This is for the train station
and in-car ad posters.
Let's work together for once.
Rather sleazy dress, isn't it?
What?!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
All right! I won! I won!
The wine list, Madame.
Do you know about
wines, Miss Nakadai?
A bit.
Then choose for us, please.
Stupid women. Do they even
know the right wines for a meal?
The choice of wine in
French cuisine reveals...
character intelligence, and education.
Kaori must have learned
it in France, but had Keiko do it.
This is Kaori's direct challenge!
Keiko's in trouble!
We'll be having saute
of fresh foie gras...
...and Valencia oranges
for dessert, right?
Right.
Well then... A Bordeaux.
Chateau Lafite Rothschild.
What year?
Do you have a '59?
A magnificent order, Madame!
Forgive me, I misjudged you.
I'll fetch it at once!
They call it a perfume for drinking.
Its rich, mellow bouquet makes it
like something from another world.
I caresses the tongue like a
rainbow over heaven's rose garden.
And its beauty...
Besides that, 1959
is considered to be...
...one of the finest vintage years of all.
And this wine has been
ripening for nearly fifty years!
It cannot be called a
mere wine at this point.
No! This is a gift
from the gods themselves!
What are you doing?!
You fool!
This isn't some sports drink!
You have to take a sip and
roll it around on your tongue!
As gently as you might
suck the breast of a virgin.
I feel like I've just given
away my innocent daughter...
...and watched her get raped
on her honeymoon night!
Keiko, cut it out!
This is business!
Hold it! Keiko,
what are you doing?!
Oh, gross!
Gotcha!
'Scuse me, miss!
Let's go!
All right! All right! All right!
Good morning.
Morning.
This is the new poster?
Jesus Christ...
"Conquering the land,
giving head to the age..."
No...
NO-O-O-O-O-O-O!!!!!
You have access to her apartment?
I'm sorry I've been having
you take such close care of her.
Well? What sort of
man does she see?
I don't think she sees one.
That can't be!
A shameless tramp like
her MUST see a man!
But there's no sign of one!
What are...?
Listening devices.
Keiko's going to be at a
staff meeting tomorrow morning.
While she's gone, I want you
to plant these in her apartment.
If she should suddenly head
back, I'll warn you with this.
Stop the operation and pull out!
She seems to have a sixth
sense about any threats to her.
We have to be careful.
Gotcha.
Unfortunately, the authorities
ordered us to pull these posters.
This is a surprise?
And it was a good shot of me, too!
Miss Nakadai?
You haven't had lunch yet.
Want to come with me?
Sure. Well, what brings on
this change in the forecast?
You inviting me to lunch.
I think we should
work a few things out.
Like ideas for the new posters.
What's the matter?!
"Red Hot Burgers"
That was close.
Hello?
Oh, Kaori! I'm all set.
Where are you?
I'm going to be having
lunch with Keiko.
I'm calling from the
lobby of her apartment.
Yes, the lobby!
Of course she's with me!
I may be a little late,
so tell the others.
Talk to you later!
Even if I turned off the
AC and left right now...
Why was my apartment so cool?
Someone must have been in
there using the air conditioning...
...while I was out.
And the only person who
could have done that...
I don't know!. It wasn't me!
Don't lie to me!
Tell me what you did!
Confess!
Knowing her, she WOULD do that!
She has a wild animal's
sense of self preservation.
Oh, welcome home.
What's with you?
Did I tell you to come?
You went in early today, right?
I figured you didn't
have time to clean up.
Well, you have good timing.
We have a guest.
Hi there.
Make something for us.
You can have these.
Your cooking's better, anyway.
I'll fix it in a sec.
Imagine, lunch for
ATV's biggest stars.
I'd better do a good job.
I see you've trained her well.
Even though she
was once your superior.
You can borrow her if you want.
No, thank you! Why don't we begin?
Fine with me.
Okay, bring on your boyfriends, Keiko.
What the...?!
Great! Craps out on
me just when I need it!
There! There! Oh, yes!
What the hell is...?!
She knows!
Too bad, Kaori!
You can buy bug detectors easily.
This is high-tech Japan,
not France, you know.
Buy some quality
equipment next time.
Curse you, "Made in Japan!"
First the bugs,
now you're following me.
How unexpectedly low-class.
I'm through fooling around.
I challenge you, Keiko!
It's time someone
bloodied your nose.
How about one pool lap?
A 100 meter freestyle race.
Think you'll win?
I was the best one on my
high school swim team.
Kiddy pool stuff.
Set!
Go!
The flower suit girl's fast!
She's gonna win!
Cheater! Stop it!
Get back here!
I won! I am the winner!
I'm scared!
It's a damned shame, those two.
Two gorgeous women, fighting.
Who wants to see that?
Powerful! Vivacious!
And elegant, too.
Wow! They're great!
And the finish!
You watched the Olympics last night.
As did you, apparently.
Come in, Michiko.
I'm here to discuss
things with Keiko again.
Right...
How boring. Look what they've done.
"People of the World, Believe in Tomorrow."
I liked the old one better.
Wouldn't you be
embarrassed if your parents saw it?
You should stop thinking
like an ordinary person.
Well, I AM an ordinary woman.
What?
Your beauty hides
something far more extreme.
Something not easily
brought to the surface.
When you realize that,
you'll be changed forever.
You'll be a totally new person.
I envy you, Keiko.
She cleans, does your wash.
Everything!
Naturally.
She even licks my panties clean.
Really?
Of course, she washes
them properly after that.
Stain removal, huh?
Oh, she's making that up.
Right, Keiko?
You cleaned these before.
Look, Michiko. See?
Don't...
Didn't you?
Keiko, stop it...
Keiko, not when there's
someone else here.
Don't get so uppity!
And why are you the only
one who's fully dressed?!
Undress! All the way!
Stop it!
Good morning.
Kaori... When did I...?
You're one to talk.
I've never seen a strip
or S&M show that good.
Keiko's extreme, but you're
something else altogether.
Not bad.
I got embarrassed just watching you.
Don't say that.
But, it did excite me a bit.
Michiko, Keiko's asleep.
Kaori...
Do to me what you did for her.
It's... Keiko's face!
Is it love or just infatuation?
I don't need that
kind of talk from you.
Sorry, but this whole
thing isn't fun anymore.
See you again.
Yeah, in a hundred years!
The burning I feel in my heart...
...burns for lots more guys than you.
When you burn for her,
but she's not there for you...
...is when a girl seems
to shine brighter still!
I take my time as
I strip off my clothes.
Shining bright in just my naked skin.
On a passion-filled vacation,
I don't want this to ever end.
Oh, this dazzling sky,
I wanna hold it close to me!
On a passion-filled vacation,
in a fire we build on our own.
Burning on and on, wherever we go.
On a passion-filled vacation,
I wanna reach up and embrace the sun.
Wanna be free and
let my passions ignite.
On a passion-filled vacation,
I'll let my troubles sleep it away.
As I stand alone
in the flowing breeze.