And this low pressure system
over the Sea of Japan...
...will be bringing the
first spring breeze tomorrow.
Announcing both the
end of the long winter...
...and the coming of spring.
You really think a new girl
can fill in for you, Michiko?
It's just for one day.
And it's only the weather corner.
What are you saying? In this day
and age, a weather report girl...
...can be the secret idol of
salary men and college students.
Me? An idol?
"KEIKO NAKADAI"
Oh, yes... Oh, yes!
Uh, Keiko? Are you in here?
Who's there?!
Of all the rotten timing...
I'm sorry! But they want to
see you in the news department.
What do they want
me up there for?
Uh, well... I heard they
chose you to stand in for...
...Michiko Kawai to do
the weather corner.
- Really?!
- Yeah.
Well, why didn't you say so?!
Keiko!
The day I've been waiting
for has finally arrived!
Wha...?!
WEATHER REPORT GIRL
These are the ratings for our
competition. And here are ATV's.
ATV is coming in dead last
in the ratings race.
It's terrible!
Even out on the Ginza...
...none of the girls can name
a single one of our shows!
Some of our sponsors have
already said that if these...
...ratings continue, they're
going to dump our programs!
- Or so they say.
- Then we have no choice!
I say we get all the girls who
work here to do a striptease!
Maybe at the tail
end of prime time.
I agree with him!
Mr. Chairman!
We musn't overlook any
method to survive this crisis!
Sir!
Whatever it takes, get those ratings...
GET THOSE RATINGS UP!!!
- Mr. Chairman!
- Hang on, sir!
Mr. Chairman!
I'm really surprised.
This picture looks nothing like you.
Oh, you think so?
I've dressed like that since
I started here a year ago.
But why? You're so beautiful.
Because this is a TV station...
...and pretty girls like
me are a dime a dozen.
Trying to be the flashiest
one won't get you anywhere.
The clever eagle who
hides her claws, huh?
Oh, please! I don't
have any claws to hide.
Fangs, perhaps?
I just want to get ahead.
And I'll do whatever it takes.
God, Kimura looks so stiff!
Her wedding dress is beautiful, though.
Oh, there's Michiko!
Of course she'd look beautiful on camera.
Well, she is ATV's star TV announcer.
She made it the biggest of
anyone from our college class.
Misuzu Tamaru started out as
a weather girl. You know that?
- Really? - Uh-huh.
And Etsuko Koyama
started on a tabloid show.
With your brains and your education...
...I just know you'll go even
further than those two have!
Oh, I doubt that...
Being able to interview you,
the light of my college life...
...would make becoming
a reporter seem worth it.
Thanks, Samejima.
The earthquake which shook the
Kanto area today caused...
...an escalator to stop suddenly,
injuring a group of...
...high school students out on a class trip.
The accident occurred on the Saikyo
platform of the JR Shinjuku station.
Miss Nakadai, it's almost time.
All right!
Keiko Nakadai... I don't
know how ugly you are...
...but you're bound to make
me look great in comparison.
That's why I chose you!
And now the weather.
Filling in for Michiko Kawai
is a new announcer here at ATV.
Miss Keiko Nakadai. Go ahead, Keiko.
WEATHER CORNER
Good evening. This is Keiko Nakadai.
The first spring winds blew
through the Kanto region today.
Who... Who is she?!
The abnormal weather brought a
downpour to the northeast...
...causing damage in some parts.
Turning now to Hokkaido--
- Who is she? - She's great!
Keiko...
Hokkaido was hit with an
unseasonably heavy snow storm...
...with Asahikawa getting 40 cm.
This skirt I'm wearing is 10 cm
above my knees, so 40 would be...
...about this deep!
You idiot! Look what you've done!
This isn't some midnight sex show!.
It's a decent 9:00 news program!
If you want to show
your panties to anyone...
...then show 'em to your boyfriend!
My boyfriend would get to see
what's BEHIND my panties!
That little tramp!
And you should complain only
when nobody watches the show!
"A decent 9:00 news program?"
All the viewers care about is
what tie the anchorman's wearing...
...and what the co-anchor's legs
look like under her miniskirt!
What did you...? You...!
Yes, he's in. Mr. Higemasa, telephone.
I'm busy! Tell 'em to call back!
But, it's the chief!
What?!
Gimme that!
Yes, sir. Sorry, sir.
It'll never happen again.
Yes, sir. Of course.
I'll... Yes, sir.
The chairman caught
last night's news cast.
Last night's? But he was in the hospital.
...is 10 cm above my knees,
so 40 would be...
...about this deep!
The Weather Corner really made him
feel good in his hospital bed.
From now on, News PM 9's
weather report girl...
Keiko Nakadai! It will be you!
Trouble! Everyone's calling in
about Miss Nakadai last night!
The phones are jammed!
Our ratings last night jumped 15%!
They haven't been that
good since the Gulf War!
No...
No problem!
If I'm wet, it's only because of the rain.
But if I can't sleep,
that's because of you.
What a beautiful day!
But if I can't sleep, that's because of you.
Everywhere I go, people
just seem to irritate me.
So all I do is just take a
deep breath and try to go on.
A woman's heart is like the
changing weather, you see.
And a kiss like that isn't
enough to set it ablaze.
After the rain stops, let's go.
Let's get our hearts racing along.
When it clears up,
we'll love like it's paradise.
After the rain stops, let's go.
Let's both just lose control.
I'll hold you like...
Hey, it's 9:30. Pops! Change the channel
Gotcha.
Hi there! It's weather time again.
I'm coming to you tonight from
under the blooming cherry trees.
This alone gives joy
to my dreary existence.
Can't argue with you there.
So, did you students taking
your entrance exams do well
Or not so well?
Not so well. I screwed up my fourth try.
Spring is still young.
Enjoy it while you can.
And for those who didn't
make it, hang in there.
Throw out your chests.
Like THlS!
Keiko...
I want to be with you!
You should be more careful, Keiko.
What do you mean?
You don't know who's watching
you on TV, or where they are.
If you turn on the wrong kind of
guy, you could end up in trouble.
Did I turn you guys on?
- You were really sexy!
- The absolute best!
They seemed to like it.
If you do get in trouble,
no one'll be there to help you.
I know that. Perfectly.
It must have fallen in during my report.
Mine! Mine!
All right! Here's some more for you!
I've come about the part-time job.
So here I am.
I'm supposed to be applying
to that prep school.
What am I doing?!
Keiko!
What's the hold up?
- I just wanted to see you...
- Autograph? Some other time.
Come on! Crack it open!
Oh, right...
There we go!
I'm so hungry I could scream!
Keiko.
Don't you remember me?
"Me?"
Yamagishi, from high school.
Yama-what?
Yamagishi.
Oh, yeah! Hey, it's been a while!
You were with us on
graduation night, right?
Yeah...
Yamagishi...Weird guy...
Yamagishi!
So, Mr. Class 3 Yamagishi!
You want to lay me, huh?
- No shit? - Let him do it!
Keiko, in front of everyone?!
How could you?
What's that mean? What do you
think we'd do if we were alone?
You wanna see me naked?
I feel so hot. Why don't I undress?
Keiko Nakadai's Greatest Mistake!
I can never hold my alcohol.
I wasted myself on that
little piece of filth!
So what? All he did was see me naked.
No, wait! It didn't end there.
Something else happened...
Take your clothes off, too!
Don't let Keiko be the only one!
Cut it out, you...!
Look! Keiko's sick!
I'm gonna puke...
Get a bowl!
No, it's coming! Plug my mouth!
"Plug it?"
Thank you.
You there. Wait.
Take this to Miss Nakadai,
the weathercaster.
Oh, just for her.
Careful. She can be a real
terror when she's hungry.
I know.
About Keiko. I'm...an old friend.
Oh, you don't say?
Well, see that she gets it.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Michiko Kawai,
the old weather girl?
They moved me over to morning news.
It's because I can't be as flashy as she is.
Compared to her, I'm nothing.
That's not true! That's not true at all.
Thanks. Nice meeting you.
Excuse me, Keiko. I gave you the wrong...
Oh, you already ate it?
What do I do with this?
YOU EAT IT!!!
What are you doing here?!
I'd almost forgotten about it!
Now I remember it all!
Just disappear! Or drop dead!
You little insect!
You can't really mean that!
I still love you...
Just go away!
I'd forget the whole thing in
four seconds if you just left!
I'll stomp that ugly little dick of yours flat!
Don't you understand?!
Your teeth marks are still all over it!
No woman can love me when
another woman's teeth marks...
...are all over my dick!
You've scarred me for life!
You're the only woman
I can ever have now!
Shut up! Just shut up!
I'll never drink again!
Or even show my panties!
I'll be a good girl!
I always just wanted
to be a nice girl!
Keiko...
What the...?!
Why's my stomach...?
Keiko, what's wrong?
Well, well...
My dear predecessor, Miss Kawai.
What brings you to my dressing room?
Must get to toilet...
No! Can't move! If I do...
You're always attacking people!
That's not the way you
should act when you work!
No, I don't want to argue with you.
Even if I was logical about it,
they'd just call it a girls fight.
Especially considering your short temper.
You're pretty cool
and you know the score.
But I'M the popular one.
I have to be here every day at 4:00 am!
It's your fault I'm stuck
doing "Weather at Dawn!"
While you get to party in Roppongi...
...I have to go to sleep
early like some little kid!
If you hate it, then flash a
little panty and get popular.
Oh, for heaven's sake!
You sound like a kid!
Give it a try! Lift that ol' skirt high!
Just thinking all the time
doesn't get anything done.
That idiot must've eaten some.
Maybe it's for the best.
Who knows what sort of terrible
vengeance she'd exact...
...if she found out
I poisoned her food.
I need a safer, more secure way.
Keiko. You seem to
have a lot of enemies.
Enemies?
A dog got into your room
after the accident.
A dog?
They were using it in
one of the other shows.
It ran into your room
and ate some of that lunch.
- And? - Same thing happened.
Just like the part-timer.
Turned his guts to water.
- You mean...? - The lunch was doped.
That pork cutlet was covered
with dissolved laxative.
Laxative?!
Okay, spill it! Who gave you the lunch?
I have proof! It was covered with laxative!
Only someone working
here could have done it!
You're the real victim here.
You disgraced yourself in public.
Lost your human dignity.
Someone's responsible.
Why take the fall for them?
If... If I say who did it,
what will you do?
Just ask them not to do it again.
Bullshit! I bet you'd kill them!
Oh, so you're covering for them!
You're in on this conspiracy?!
You protected me this time.
I'm sorta grateful to you.
I was thinking I could keep
you around as a bodyguard.
It was... Michiko Kawai.
What? Keiko can't go on tonight?
Said she overdid the karaoke last night.
Cracked my voice on a Chages medley.
Anyway, that's the story.
Can you fill in tonight?
Well...
I can do this! If brains and
education won't let me win...
...I can still do it on looks alone!
I won't lose to a woman like that!
This is my chance to
get back into prime time!
The ratings are at 20%
Can't be too hard to keep 'em.
Tea for you.
Thanks. Leave it there.
Yes, miss. Excuse me.
She actually drank it!
Too bad for you.
NEWS PM 9
Good evening, this is News PM 9.
I'm anchorman Hijikata.
And I'm co-anchor Kondo.
Calm down. It's in the bag. Don't worry.
Almost time, Miss Kawai. Get ready.
Right.
Good evening. Michiko Kawai here.
I'll be filling in for
Miss Nakadai this evening.
Here we go.
Jeez... She's going all out
for just one night's work.
Doubt the ratings'll drop tonight.
God, I love working here!
That low pressure system which
brought heavy rains to Kyushu...
What's the point?
She's six years older than me
and still trying to compete!
We should see heavy rains
hit the Pacific Coast as well.
Like this? Is this the way you like it?
God, you viewers are all idiots.
You couldn't understand
anything complicated.
Okinawa's already seeing its rainy season.
This week, Kyushu will also be...
What the hell?!
And... And, uh...
"What's wrong? Go on."
In Kyushu this week...
There it goes.
I spiked that tea you drank
with gorilla-laxative.
Your stomach'll be going
through hell in a minute.
Laxative? Keiko Nakadai!
But when? How?!
Excellent brandy...
By next week, the entire country
will be in the rainy season.
What'll I do?! Say "Excuse me,
I have to take a crap really bad?"
No way in hell. If I did that,
they'd can me for sure!
"Three minutes. Hurry!"
Three minutes left!
These two masses of sea air
will...move in over...
...the islands...and bring
the rainy season to us!
You won't beat me, Keiko Nakadai!
I'll show you just how tight
those gymnastics made my ass!
Anyway!
These two masses of sea air
pushing together are...
Something's wrong with Michiko.
Should we cut away?
We've got two minutes.
Let her go on.
If one of the masses is
stronger, the pressure will...
Oh, yes! You've got it bad!
I'm just doing to you what
you were going to do to me.
An eye for an eye.
As these masses push against...
Push against...each other...
No use... Can't hold it! I can't...
Chance of rain tomorrow.
Chance of rain...
Chance...of...rain...!!!
The boss said he wanted to fire you.
They can't do that! I'd have to
start my career all over again!
If you agree to be my assistant,
I could change his mind.
I won't! I'd sooner be fired!
Yeah, they gave me a private
office, but forgot the chair.
Yeah. Don't worry.
My assistant's helping out.
What's that? Don't worry.
Talk to you later.
I have an apartment nearby.
Those are the keys.
I want these panties washed!
You're going to use the machine
this late at night?!
Use your tongue! Lick 'em clean!
That's the way. You'll do that every day.
I've been getting the oddest
feeling in my back.
You make a lot of strange
acquaintances as a reporter.
We got some real winners here.
We've been waitin' for ya!
Great. We get paid to do a gal like this!
Now, Keiko... You will die!
You can't get away.
Just relax and lose the clothes.
All right then. I'm game for a fight.
That's better.
Why, you...!
I'll break it!
It's your fault! Shoulda just
let us do you in the first place!
Michiko, save yourself!
Someday...I'll write a book about you...!
The panties I cleaned...
How could I have
known you knew karate?!
I've washed you so many times,
but l've never seen any bruises.
Not even a single scratch!
Fool! I am a genius at everything!
"Tetsudo-ltoh Karate
Correspondence Course Now Ended."
Is it love or just infatuation?
I don't need that kind of talk from you.
Sorry, but this whole thing
just isn't fun anymore.
See you again.
Yeah, in a hundred years!
The burning I feel in my heart...
...burns for lot more guys than you.
When you burn for her,
but she's not there for you...
...is when a girl seems
to shine brighter still!
I take my time as I strip off my clothes.
Shining bright in just my naked skin.
On a passion-filled vacation,
I don't want this to ever end.
Oh, this dazzling sky,
I wanna hold it close to me!
On a passion-filled vacation,
in a fire we build on our own.
Burning on and on, wherever we go.
On a passion-filled vacation,
I wanna reach up and embrace the sun.
Wanna be free and let my passions ignite.
On a passion-filled vacation,
I'll let my troubles sleep it away.
As I stand alone in the flowing breeze.