After a long winter, spring is attempting to blossom.
Farewell, Futaba-chan...
But I still have Wakaba-chan.
Morning!
You are not allowed to come here!
It's started again...
Trying to monopolize my Futaba-chan!
It's nothing like that!
Then. What's this?
You bastards! You read it again!
That it's all about him makes me jealous...
No matter how you read it, Futaba-chan's lovey-dovey feelings are very direct.
Oh well. The advent of spring isn't just for you.
That's right! Soon, the girls will return here, to Kanenone!
Six months have passed. The all-boys Kanenone Academy will become...
Co-ed starting next year.
Indeed, spring is coming to Kanenone.
Green Green
Erolutions
Kutsuki-san, you want it bad, don't you?
Pardon?
To meet him.
Not particularly... I...
You're rather ungainly at these kinds of things. But it's pretty cute.
We're right behind you, too, Sis.
Yes!
Here we are!
Wha-What's this?
Eh? That's me...
I'm sure it's Ijuiin and Co.'s doing.
Thank you gods!
Ejaculation
Togemura Super! Togemura-san Face Attack!
I've missed this...
Everybody, I'm back!
Indeed. The real thing is still the best!
You guys haven't changed, huh?
Not at all!
Sensei, I'm looking forward to the coming year with you!
Sure sure... But I'm not playing around today.
I know. But later, I want you to take care of my frostbite.
Frostbite?
If I play with your statue like this every day...
My important place will become frostbitten.
Hold it, you're getting into a weird mood.
Anyway, that's a real frostbite!
Not your face! Cover your lower half!
But I have to admit, you're quite bold.
Umm... You've got luggage with you, right?
Yeah, thanks.
Wakaba-chan! I wrote a song for you - please listen to it!
My cactus girl, Wakaba!
Wow, I've missed this place.
So you'll stay here for two nights.
Yeah.
Is that bag too heavy?
No, not at all.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
It's nothing, really.
Sis?
Whose...
Room was this again?
Yuusuke-kun!
Midori!
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing.
This has always been a storage room.
Storage room?
Really?
Yuusuke!
Hey...
What is it, Futaba-chan?
Didn't some girl use this room before?
Nobody's used it.
I see.
I guess I made a mistake.
Yuusuke!
Leave us some of the girls' luggage for us to carry, too!
You're hogging them all!
Why do you carry everyone's luggage?!
According to Dr. Takekan, women easily fall for
Guys who treat them with unaffected benevolence!
So not only were you
Trying to seduce Futaba-chan, but Wakaba-chan and Sanae-chan as well!
Umm, Senpai!
Onii-chama...
Oh! Onii-chama...
Tenjin!
You idiot!
I'm so jealous of him!
You had a haircut.
Doesn't suit me, I suppose.
No, it looks good.
Umm...
I'm sorry I made you come with me.
No, don't be! I...
I also had something to say.
What's it?
Thanks for your letter.
I'm glad to hear you got it.
Cellphones can't get a signal here and since there are no computers,
The only solution I could think of was a written letter.
Did it cause trouble?
Not really. Well... actually,
My friends got excited over it.
I thought so.
That's why...
I didn't dare writing one thing.
I understand.
I said it, right?
Youth...
Yuusuke-kun!
Midori!
Shh. If you make too much noise,
You'll wake up Tenjin-kun.
But you...
Just be quiet. I'll make you feel good.
Midori... wait.
See, you're all fired up now.
What's going on?
Yuusuke-kun!
Wait a second. What's wrong with you?
I... I came to make you feel good!
I couldn't leave you alone, you see.
Mido... ri.
Yuusuke-kun!
Yuusuke-kun...
Midori...
Hey, Yuusuke-kun. How do you feel about Futaba-chan?
Midori, you...
You like her, don't you?
You're...
I never imagined saying this sort of thing to you...
This isn't about me. It's Futaba-chan we're talking about.
I think I want to... hold her dear.
Then it's okay.
I'm happy, you know. That's why I want you to be happy as well.
I love you because you're so sweet to Futaba-chan.
Midori!
A dream, huh...
It won't come off.
I knew a cruel man named Yuuji...
Well, if it isn't Kutsuki-san!
Drunk again, are you?
No, i'm not!
I saw you earlier today. You didn't confess your feelings to Takazaki-kun.
In that case, I'll show you how it's done the adult way.
Sensei...
How's that?
Smells like booze.
Sensei!
Ah, Futaba-chan! Long time no see!
Who... are you?
The Angel of Love!
That excessively energetic voice makes me feel somewhat nostalgic.
Hey, Futaba-chan.
If you hesitate, your feelings may not reach the person you love.
Are you truly content with just memories?
Didn't you come here for more?
Give it your best! You and Yuusuke-kun are both important to me.
Don't keep your true feelings to yourself.
I'll cheer for you.
Ah, that place... You can't...
What a weird dream...
Nostalgia...
This...
Who's that girl?
Takazaki... We've been here before, right?
There was someone else besides us.
Futaba-chan!
In the mountains like this, Yuusuke really is in the mood for it.
Mood? In what mood?
When a man and a woman are alone, there's only one thing to do.
What's there to do besides eating rice?
You're right; there's only one thing they can do.
That bastard. He's trying to ditch us
Without even saying 'No' to our faces.
A ditch?
Unforgiveable!
He's hogging everything to himself!
Hold it!
Wait, Senpai!
Sanae-chan! What happened to you?!
She suddenly started to run and then fell ill.
Don't... disturb those two.
I just wanted to say that...
Sanae-chan!
She came all the way here just for that!
How considerate of her to think of her Senpais!
Senpai! If you don't take her to Chigusa-sensei soon...
Leave it to me!
What a position!
You idiot! This  is a position!
A position! A cool position, isn't it?!
No! Just keep quiet and watch me!
This  is the true meaning of "position"!
This is it! This is what I wanted!
Umm... I just wanted you to take her to the nursery...
I came here to check it.
In a dream,
A girl came to me...
And told me to do my best.
Oh, yeah.
That same girl had disappeared beyond this tree.
Midori...
Do you remember her?
A memory of her.
The only girl I look at now,
Kutsuki, is you.
Sanae-chan!
Thank goodness.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Just rest here for today.
I'll stay here and watch over her! And then... and then...
Sensei,
Please examine me.
Oh, your breath is ticking on my skin.
Ah, what am I thinking?!
Watching over, huh? It'd be perfect if I could do the same with Wakaba-chan.
Togemura Super Whateverlator:
Togemura-san Bottom Attack!
It's great that you're alright!
Watching over...
I thought of...
The new attraction I thought of yesterday!
Doc-to-student watch-over love!
Need to cool off?
It's shrinking! Vanishing!
There you go.
Yuusuke-kun...
Are you done already?
That was fast!
I came too soon.
Well everybody, we'll meet again next term.
Our time is already over!
Come faster to us next term!
Faster, faster, faster, faster!
"Are you done already?"
Sensei!
Well if it isn't Haruno-san, but arriving now...
It's over already, so we're going back.
Huh? Over already?!
After all the trouble to get here...
Coming before me was despicable!
Sorry.
But I'm looking forward to it!
I wonder if the next term will come fast...
Right, boys?
Sure, it'll be great to become co-ed... right?
Huh? Hey Yuusuke, what's up with you?
Nothing...
The segregation is over already! The girls will come next year!
It'll be great. By that time, I'll be a senior myself.
Yuusuke-kun.
Yuusuke-kun...
She called him by his given name!
I can feel the love!
M-Maybe...
That
They've done it!
Pla
And that!
ce
And this, too?!
Futaba...
Wouldn't it be great if the next term came fast?
Yeah.
All right! I'll make it when I become a senior!
I want to be a senior faster!
I'll get to it fast when I'm a senior!
Quit saying fast!
Green Green
Erolutions
Guess who I am?
I am-
If it's just for you...
It was Midori
It was Midori!
Guess who I am?
I am-
Just where are you looking?
It was
Futaba
It was Futaba!
Guess who I am?
I am-
Onii-chama, this is embarrassing...
It was Sanae
It was Sanae...
Guess who I am?
I am-
Togemura-san Attack!
It was Wakaba with Togemura-san!
Guess who I am?
I am-
I'll eat you...
Since I'm Chigusa
Since I'm Chigusa.
Guess who I am?
I am-
Look at me more!
I'm Bacchiguu Sanjou.