Are you awake, Sylvie?
I am aware of your sentiments, Arima-dono.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't happy.
My words did not deter you, and you pushed me down...
To be honest, my heart was racing.
It was my first time... that I felt like a woman.
But I feel really confused right now...
I'd like some time.
This is so I can continue to walk down my own path, by your side...
I'll borrow this shirt.
I want to be with you just a little longer.
Sylvie...
I have no choice but to accept this.
You made love to me, and I am now a woman.
A-Arima-dono...
W-What are you doing-
Inflaming your desire.
T-That's not fair!
I just told you I wanted to wait, but you didn't listen...
This is all I can do right now.
You can't!
No, you aren't going to stop?
UFW-FAKKU Presents
Part 1: Mornings With You
You had enough yet?
You keep... going for where I'm weakest...
If you focus on them...
W-Why doesn't... a woman's body...
...do as it is told?!
Warmth... is coursing throughout my body...
My mind is going blank...
I... I...
No... this sensation...
Hey, w-wait...
Teppei!
You don't have to hold back.
Marchez!
Good work!
Are you sure, Teppei-sama?
About not speaking to her?
Caterpillars pass through a pupal stage before becoming butterflies.
I think the first few days are going to be perplexing.
"Huh?  I'm flying."
"The world looks so different now."
"It's too bright... isn't it?"
"Though my mind is still that of a caterpillar."
You tell me this every day, so I remember it clearly.
I'm not worthy of intruding into that world, I suppose.
Perhaps I'm the one who has it wrong.
I'm able to have valuable experiences because I'm by your side, serving you.
Teppei-sama.
She probably doesn't like to be in the spotlight.
The daughters of the Van Hossen family are modest individuals.
Thanks for your concern.
Maybe I was too forceful on a modest girl like her.
I would greatly prefer your forgiveness over words of appreciation.
Huh?
Sorry I kept you waiting, Sylvie-sama.
A vehicle to escort you has been prepared.
Teppei-sama seems to be looking for you.
Have you seen him?
Please tell him that I've gone home first.
I'll be fine on my own.
In that case, I'll do that.
Weren't you were in the dojo earlier?
Yes.
It seemed like you were with Arima-dono.
What did he say...
Actually, it's nothing.
It is my duty to stay by Teppei-sama's side and fulfill his desires.
I am happy only when Teppei-sama is satisfied.
Yuu-san, you changed already?
S-Sylvie!
It's Arima-sama!
Is that really him?
This lingering scent...
Is it not from the maid who's always serving you?
Have you no shame?
Perhaps it's rude for me to barge into the master-servant affairs of another family,
but show some moderation, Arima-dono.
Aren't you embarrassed at all?
Doing things like this...
You treat even us servants as equals.
This kindness of yours that is never forceful
is what is most attractive about you, Teppei-sama.
However, please allow me to fulfill my original duties.
We cannot allow the Arima family heir
to be taken lightly by those around him.
If I allow my master to be worried all the time,
they would accuse me of not knowing my place.
Teppei-sama's radiant personality will continue to shine.
I want him to get used to it through me.
If obeying everything you say will help you realize your current status, I'll gladly do anything.
How lewd.
Something like this will never be forgiven.
And I will never forgive you.
There is no way I will forgive you.
You caused your fiancée to bear
such impure thoughts, such filthiness...
How did she do it?
Like this?
I won't forgive myself for wanting to bind
myself to you after making love to you just once.
Furthermore...
I won't forgive myself for allowing you to
use my body in a despicable ploy to bind me,
and for allowing you to keep toying with me!
S-Sylvie!
This isn't the place for this...
Someone might see-
A maid serving her master.  What's there to be reserved about?
My breasts feel different, don't they?
It's so hot...
Even I know a little about this.
My father had handed me some lewd books, telling me I should learn how to be a woman.
This is apparently also a part of night life...
Well?
Am I doing it right?
Uh, well...
I hope this pleases you.
You're finally on the receiving end.
Am I... cute?
I don't really like... such praise...
But when you look at me so expectantly...
You make me want to respond to it...
How does... this feel?
I... don't really know...
How to make you feel even better...
Tell me...
Does this feel good?
What?
It got bigger... it's so hot!
S-Sorry, I couldn't stop myself.
So this is the essence of life.
Is that why it's this hot?
What sacred warmth...
A-Arima-dono?!
W-What are you doing?  Stop!
Why?
Isn't it over for the man after he comes?
But it isn't over for the woman.
D-Don't do this.
We just did this last night, to do it again is-
I have to return the love you gave me, Sylvie.
But then I'll be on the receiving end again...
C-Could you please stop, A-Arima-dono?
It's "Teppei."  Didn't you call me that last night?
You can't... that's...
I... I already told you last night...
Doesn't this make us lovers?
Lovers...
S-Stop...
It's in so deep, and so hot...
If you go all the way in...
But I can't...
I can't answer your feelings...
So please, go away...
Go away...
I already said no, but why are you so hot and big...
Wait... big?
No!
You already came so much last night...
You can't come again today.
There's no way that's acceptable!
Did it just throb?
If you don't stop soon...
No, it's getting bigger...
No... stop, stop!
Just what are you trying to accomplish?
You came so much inside me without warning...
Wait, we're still joined together!
Again?
No... no!
Hasn't it been only two days?
We've slept together only so many times...
Why do I let him do whatever he wants to me?
Doesn't this mean...
I'm playing right into my father's hands?
Morning Before Yesterday...
Teppei-sama.
Excuse me, but this is an urgent matter.
What time is it?
Five past seven.
I understand you are tired, but I beg this of you.
Please get up.
This is not something I can judge.
It's rather ungentlemanly to make a lady wait.
Pardon me for intruding this early in the morning, Arima-dono.
Morning, Teppei Onii-chan.
Huh?
Daddy won't be home for the next two days because of work,
so he's entrusting us to someone else until he returns.
To who?
We're standing here right in front of you.
Is it not obvious?
You're so mean today.
You really are a jealous girl.
I was informed of this last night, against my will.
I'm not very happy with this either.
You shouldn't sound like you don't want this at all.
You know, Onee-chan's a real tsundere.
It is true that our parents gave us our lives.
I suppose we should accept what they entrust us with,
and live our lives respecting these sentiments.
Even so, our parents have no right to determine our fate.
Don't you agree?
Do you really dislike being my fiancée that much?
That kinda hurts.
It's that exact attitude!
You have a problem, too.
If only you had flatly refused...
But I like you, Sylvie.
Shouldn't you be regretting this by now?
Are you sure you didn't say that
because you were caught in the moment?
I am a woman born into a respected noble family in line to the throne.
I am obligated to fulfill my duties to my country.
I cannot afford to bind someone, or be bound to anyone.
How dare you take it against my will!
Don't you think that's despicable?!
What's important to me right now is telling you my feelings.
Forcing them onto me will only burden me.
My determination will not falter with just words...
In that case...
Arima-dono!
As nobles, we are obligated to lead our people!
Are you prepared to set that free?
You fool...
Do you... really...
...lust after my body... this much?!
Don't describe this as lust.
It hurts my feelings.
No...
Treating me so roughly, too...
Do you really want me to hate you?
As long as you stay by my side, Sylvie,
I don't care if you think I'm despicable.
Are you trying to steal my heart with this?
What we are about to do is an ugly and filthy act.
If you think about where the both of us stand, it's even worse...
Well then, after I defile you...
Do you think you can go back to being a girl again, Sylvie?
I'm no longer a child.
You're about to turn me into a woman.
Don't tell me you're having second thoughts now?
I might become a troublesome woman.
I won't forgive you for taking my virginity.
You will atone for it even if it takes the rest of your life.
It will bind you forever.
We're becoming one...
Arima-dono and I... are becoming one...
It's going in... it's tearing me apart...
It's so hot...
It's so hot, and it's going in!
M-My insides... are burning...
How...
It's warming my body from the inside...
You're making me burn up, it's getting numb...
You're moving...
You're ravaging my insides...
You're a horrible person...
You're giving me so much pain...
No...
You're joined to me...
You'll know everything about me...
It's so hot and numb...
Even the inside of my head is burning...
No... I don't want to sound so lewd...
What's this?
I'm losing myself... I'm scared...
What are you doing to me?
Don't, Sylvie, I'll come soon if you squeeze so hard!
You fool...
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm different from you...
I don't seek shameful things like you do!
More...
More, I want to be with you forever...
Joined to you forever...
How could you...
You're thrusting so hard...
It's so hot...
I can't think about anything other than the warmth...
I'm about to faint...
Your warmth is making me faint...
My consciousness is...
...fading...
Something hot is coming from inside me...
Inside me...
No, this isn't me...
It's not!
So hot...
It's so hot, it's burning me...
Your semen is flowing into me...
It's so hot...
Your warmth is filling me up, it's filling me up inside!
It's still big?
I'm already full...
It's coming again...
What are you...
I won't be able to handle your feelings if there's this much of it...
You don't want to?
I didn't say I don't want to.
I said I wouldn't be able to handle it.
Dummy.
UFW-FAKKU Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Timer/Typesetter: Sindalf