The "Tales of the 15 Beautiful Girls Adrift OVA: Hehe
Combo Sex at Southern Island Episode" will start now!
Kirameku suiheisen no hate
Drifting from the edge of the sparkling horizon
Nagaretsuita tokonatsu no Love Island
To the shores of the love island of everlasting summer
Minamikaze ni notte yatte kita
We've come here by riding the southern winds
Love Affair koi no mahou ni miserareta no
Love affair, I'm captivated by the magic of love
Nee joushoukiryuu ni notte kimi wo tsukamaetai
Hey, I want to ride the rising air and catch you
Daisuki
I love you
Aoku hirogaru umi he
Towards the wide blue sea
Tobikonde miyou hajikeyou
Let's jump in, release ourselves
Terenaide waratte
And laugh without being shy
Kyou mo manatsu no taiyou
Today too, the midsummer sun
Yaketsuku hodo ni terasu yo
Shines to the point of sunburning us
Bokura no mecha happy koi moyou
This is our super-happy love pattern
Do mother-daughter
combos
taste
like
newlyweds?!
Do mother-daughter
combos
taste
like
newlyweds?!
Do mother-daughter
combos
taste
like
newlyweds?!
A pure and innocent girl who
looks up to Kazuma as a father
Haruna's mom, cool
and incredibly sexy
This island used to be unpopulated,
but it is now where I live with my harem of 15 young girls.
This thing even drifted on shore for me...
Surprisingly, I'm living quite the cultural life here.
Daddy, what are you doing?
Is that a video camera?
It's 8mm film, not a video camera.
As your fill-in-father, I believe it's my duty to preserve my cute daughter's growth on film.
Okay!  Be sure to film me a lot, Daddy!
While you're at it, how about filming both mother and child together?
Ah, Mommy.
I work as a model, so I love being in the camera.
M-Missus, your daughter's watching...
Mommy and Daddy are so close!
I want to play too!
Why don't we play house then?
What?
I'm not a kid anymore.
There's a variation of playing house that even adults can enjoy called "pussy house".
Pussy house?  What's that?
That's a pretty naughty... fun-sounding name.
It's a role-play that trains inexperienced girls to be good wives by simulating night life.
The husband has returned!
Welcome home, darling.
Will you have dinner now?
Will you shower first?
Or will you have... me?
Hmm... what should I do?
You obviously comfort your wife who's all turned-on
from waiting for her beloved husband to come home.
That's the head of the family's duty.
I see.
I think I'll start by having you.
Darling, we shouldn't do this by the door...
Mommy, what comes next?
This is where the real part of
"Pussy House", or "Pussy" for short, begins.
I'll teach you what to do, so do it with your daddy.
Okay!
That's right, you need to lick that.
O-Okay.
Ooh, my cute daughter's first blowjob...!
Hang in there, Haruna!
Daddy is watching closely!
I will!
My kiddy wife is licking my dick like it's a lolipop...
Incredible!
Some kind of yoghurty stuff came out...
That's the sperm from a male.
Alright, the night life of a married couple continues!
Oww!
The first time always hurts, Haruna.
Kazuma-kun, be gentle, okay?
Sure, but...
It's really tight, her pelvic muscles are squeezing down on me hard...
This shouldn't be a problem for a strong male!
R-Right...
Mommy, my insides are really hot...
It feels kinda weird...
You just had your hymen torn,
but you're enjoying this already.
You really do have potential!
My mind's going blank, I feel like I'm gonna fly!
Oh my, you came on your own before your husband did...
You're a hopeless wife.
As her mother, I'll be sure to clean up the mess she left behind!
This is it!
It's been so long since I had a guy!
A-Amazing, missus...
Your pussy is unbelievably tight for someone
who's given birth, and that intense thrusting...!
I'll squeeze the semen out of you until your balls are dry.
I like my boys wild.
M-Missus!
This is it!
Sex with young guys is more about the power than the technique!
They can't get enough of women because they're inexperienced...
I'll make your boobs feel good too, Mommy.
Haruna!
How many years has it been since you've sucked my boobs?!
I'm having sex as a woman and breast-feeding as a mom...
This happiness is incredible!
Ugh, you're squeezing even tighter...
I-I can't anymore!
You came!
You're shooting your hot come inside me!
I'm coming!
Startling
Medical checkup
Sisters-combo
Startling
Medical checkup
Sisters-combo
Startling
Medical checkup
Sisters-combo
A kind and caring
nurse-type android
A cold android with
euthanasic abilities
What do you want?
I'm just filming this down, so keep doing your thing.
He's behaving suspiciously.
You have the wrong idea.
So, are the two of you collecting edible plants?
We're collecting medicinal plants.
That's boring, so how about we
relive our childhood and play doctor?
But we aren't playing...
We're genuine doctors.
We also have no childhood memories.
Both of you can be the patients, and I'll be the doctor.
That way, you can understand the fabulousness of playing doctor,
a game where you learn what
might come in handy as we play!
I see.
Alright!
So euthanasia isn't needed...
Well, let's start the medical checkup!
Please lay down over there.
Aren't you going to examine us?
Examine?
Yes yes, of course!
Well, please expose your breasts.
Okay.
You're a robot, so why the hell are you wearing a bra?!
I'm 85D.
Incredible!
I'll have to squeeze... no, examine these by touch.
Ooh, they feel great!
Viva the progress of science!
The day when all women can have boobs like these is near.
When that happens, small boobs will truly be precious!
Oh no!  Your heart isn't beating!
I-I'm a robot so I don't have a heart...
But...
There's this throbbing feeling in my chest for some reason...
I wonder if the throbbing's from around here?
When you do that, I...
Ooh, something's wrong with your groin!
I'll have to examine that too.
Open your legs...
Like this?
These are the V-shaped open legs of fantasy!
It takes a robot to hold this position for a long time.
Smells good!
You're supposed to be a robot, but...!
Please stop!
I shouldn't have feelings like this,
but it's so embarrassing when you sniff at my groin!
Incredible, you're all wet from
embarrassment even though you're a robot!
Please don't look, it's embarrassing!
Ow...
Your examination is overly inefficient.
You fail as a doctor for making your patients wait.
W-Well then, next patient please...
Quin-san, where do you feel unwell?
Listening to my sister made me feel all warm down there.
Okay, let me take a look.
This is bad!
Your clitoris is swollen!
I've never heard of such a disease.
I'm finding no matching medical cases in my search either...
Let's take a closer look.
That's a lot of sexual fluids.
This could be dangerous.
W-What should I do?
According to Super Godhand K...
You'll both need an injection!
I'll start with Quin.
Sep's injection is next.
How does it feel to be injected with your younger sister's sexual juices?
Your penis and Quin's sexual fluids... inside me...
It's all slippery...
It feels so good!
I really want you to inject me with my sister's sexual fluids.
Looks like I have no choice.
There, savor the taste of your sister's
sexual juices, you sister-complex robot!
Another shot for you, Sep!
You'll mess up my AI if you keep
rubbing the insides of my vagina!
This sensation is beyond my ability to compute!
I'll overload if I receive any more pleasure!
Quin, let's short-circuit together!
Yes, let's blow our fuses together, Sister!
Quin, Quin!
Sister, Sister!
Sister...
Quin...
Careful not
to overeat  !!
Thick
and
creamy
yam   combo
Careful not
to overeat  !!
Thick
and
creamy
yam   combo
Careful not
to overeat  !!
Thick
and
creamy
yam   combo
Boyish genius girl
with a thirst for knowledge
Upholder of justice and
strongest super student president
Hey, Kazuma.
That's quite something you've got.
Ema, you pervert!
I'm talking about the camera, not that.
I have no interest in your dick.
That really hurt my guy pride...
Well, I need someone to record my experiment on film.
I'll reward you if you help me out.
I don't mind doing nudes if you're fine with my body.
I'm in, I'm in!  I'm totally in!
Ema, what did you call me all the way out here for?
Wait, Kazuma?!
What are you planning?
Suspicious of me already?
I don't blame you, though.
Kazuma, I hear you've recently been using that video camera to film the girls' shameful acts!
I'm confiscating it in my position as student president!
I won't bow down to you so easily today.
I'll film your shameful act too, Prez!
How dare you disobey the student president!
What?
What is this?!
It's my genetically-engineered yam.
I figured I'd have you, the strongest lifeform on this island, test its strength and endurance.
It's wrong to genetically engineer food!
No no.  Its productivity, nutritional worth, and taste...
I've already proven that I've significantly increased all of these factors.
I just need to confirm its ability to self-defend.
Let's see...
Mmh, delicious!
I feel more energetic too.
Yam really is great.
Not even the student president can show it any moves.
Your panties are showing, though.
Stop it!  Voyeurism is wrong!
I'm filming you straight up, so this isn't voyeurism.
What nonsense!
Your threats don't scare me!
Ema, are you going against justice too?
I'm just conducting an experiment.
My desire for science has nothing to do with justice or wrong.
And sacrifices come with scientific development!
Prez, you shouldn't go around looking shameful like that.
It's against the school rules!
I'm running out of patience!
Not like you had any anyway!
You won't break free from the yam even if you run out of patience.
There's no need for that!
This calls for the emergency button!
Switch on!
Looks like I'm in trouble too.
Hey, you both okay?
This looks to be a bad situation...
At this rate, the yam will propagate...
And all the lifeforms on this island will have itchy skin.
I have to do something...
Kazuma, have sex with me.
This yam is weak against semen and female vaginal fluid mixed together.
You sure about that?
I won't say anything that isn't backed scientifically.
Okay.
Could you caress me instead of putting it straight in to stimulate secretion of my vaginal fluids?
Yeah.
Show some moderation in your indecent acts!
This isn't an indecent act.
It's necessary for justice!
That's right, Prez...
It's to protect the soft and sensitive skin of us females...
Is this wet enough yet?
Yes, reagent A is ready...
Now, mix in reagent B!
Gotcha.
You're bigger than I thought, Kazuma.
You're just small down there, Ema.
I see, it's something I wouldn't have known without an experiment.
It's tight, but I'll start moving, Ema.
Okay.
It's a criminally indecent act to have sex in front of others!
This isn't in front of you, so we're safe!
That nonsense again?!
Prez, please pretend none of this happened...
Illicit sexual acts are against the school rules!
No, stop!
I can't stop now.
Ema feels way too good inside.
You're stopping!
Any more of this indecency is...
Ema, I'm...!
Yes, Kazuma, come...
Shoot your semen inside my vaginal fluid-filled pussy!
Ema!
Wow, it actually worked...
We're almost there.
Alright, Kazuma, help the prez too.
What are you talking about, Ema?!
We can't use the same mix
since the yam is now resistant to it.
We must change either the vaginal fluid or the semen.
I'm the only guy here, so that means...
Exactly right.
Hurry up and have sex with the prez!
Wait!
It's wrong to have sex without your partner's consent!
No, Prez, we're doing this to take down the yam.
I think it's just.  Won't you assist me?
Well...
The ultimate aim of this is to defeat the yam.
It's an act of justice.
Looks like I have no choice...
Let's do this before you change your mind!
You don't have to grope me or whatever...
Just put it in and come inside...
But we can't have too little vaginal fluids...
H-Huh?
It looks like you're ready.
Did listening to me and Ema having sex make you all wet?
N-No...
But you're all w-
Just shut up and get this over with quickly!
Fine, fine.
Only girls who work out like you are this tight!
Y-You're being too rough!
You're thrusting it all the way inside me!
You did say to get this over with quickly, Prez!
I did, but...!
You're really wet down there.
Do you feel good, Prez?
T-That's just...
This is ultimately for the sake of justice...
...and not to feel good...
This doesn't feel good...
This doesn't feel good!
H-Hurry up and come!
Otherwise I'll...!
Prez, I'm coming... argh!
It's here!
It's like you won't let my dick go...
A human victory.
However, I doubt this is the last yam we'll see.
Kazuma.
Prez, justice has prevailed!
There's still some evil to take care of.
Justice has prevailed.
However, I doubt this is the last we'll see of Kazuma.
A dream?
Was that all a dream?!
No, I'll make the dream a reality!
I won't need to fear even the prez with those things around!
Ema, Ema!
Please genetically engineer those yams!
Daddy's full of energy, as usual!
I'm stranded on an island with a harem!
There's no way I can just let my dreams end as fantasies!
Mabushii hizashi wo zenshin ni abinagara
As I bask fully in the sun's bright rays
Nagarenagasarete hirogaru umi wo miteru
I stare at the ebb and flow of the wide sea
Koushite yasashii kaze ni dakarete itara
Being embraced like this by the pleasant wind
Kagayaku mirai wo kitai shichaisou da yo
Makes me anticipate the shining future ahead
Chikasugite demo tooi
Too close, but also far away
Kyorikan wo ima koso kaete miseru yo
Now is the time to change this sense of distance
Chance
Chance!
Anata no koto dake wo zutto miteta
All this while I've had eyes only for you
Kirakira na aijoukousen haato wo neraiuchi
I'll snipe your heart with this sparkling beam of love
With my overpowering appeal that would mesmerize any girl
Donna onna no ko mo kasumu kurai
Kurakura watashi no miryoku de anata no hitomi wo hitorijime
I'll focus your eyes only on me
UFW-FAKKU Staff
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze
Timer: Sindalf
Typesetter: Exhausted