One of the male students was hitting on her.
Watching her just stand there unable to give a reply...
It annoyed me for some reason.
Hey, you!
She's obviously uncomfortable, okay?!
Um... thank you so much.
You too-
And that was all that it took.
You too!  If you don't like him, then just say so!
Yes... I'm sorry.
What's your name?
Me?
That was how I met Sumiya Kana.
Kana...
A
ki
So
ra
~ In a Dream ~
How long are you going to worry about it, Kana?
Well, I passed out at Sora-kun's house...
I don't really remember, but I feel like I saw something incredible before passing out...
Pull yourself together!
Sora-nii is a complete idiot.
You have to take the lead, Kana.
M-Me?
You can do it.
No other girl is prettier than you, Kana.
I guarantee it!
Nami...
Thank you, Nami.
Hey, Kana.
I have a great idea...
It looks like your fever's gone down.
Yeah.
Aki-neechan, I can do that myself now.
Too bad.
Didn't you take care of me when I was ill?
So...
Aki... neechan...
Looks like you're still feverish down here.
But we need to keep it clean.
Aki... neechan...
It's alright, Sora.  Just let it all spurt out along with your fever.
No... no...
...neechan...
It's ready to go already.
Sora-nii!
Hey, lovey-dovey couple...
Could you not flirt in front of me?
Now now, isn't "couple" a little embarrassing, Nami?
Didn't I say lovey-dovey couple?  Geez.
Aki-nee, Sora-nii'll never get a girlfriend if you keep treating him like that.
And what's wrong with that?
Right, Sora?
Uh...
Of course something's wrong, dummy.
Nami?
I think you'd be a good match.
You and Kana.
Sora-nii!
You're coming with me tomorrow for something, okay?
For what?
What else?!
You're really nervous, Kana.
I told her I wouldn't come, but I should still watch over them...
Sumiya-san!
Sorry I'm late.  Did you wait long?
No, not at all.
Hey wait, where's Nami?
I thought she left before me...
Something urgent came up for Nami, so I don't think she's coming.
Really?
And she was the one who made me come and help with the research...
Something about buying outfits for me...
That'll be the excuse...
I'm sorry, Sora-kun.
Oh, no.  I'm sorry too.
So what should we do now?
Should we do this another day?
Um, I...
I'm fine with just you, Sora-kun...
Huh?
As long as you... don't mind...
Okay.
Since we're already here, let's have some fun.
Okay!
Hey, Sumiya-san...
Yes?
How about a movie?
Looks like it's going okay for now...
Geez, she's hopeless without me.
I've never done one of these...
This is where you pick the frame.
Which one do you want?
Um...
What the hell?  There's something wrong with Sora-nii knowing how to pull off a date.
And what's more, Sora-nii doesn't even see this as a date.
Doesn't this feel like a date?
Huh?!
Sorry, was that weird?
Oh, no...
Nami was supposed to come with us today anyway.
I'm sorry.
I was lying when I said something urgent came up for Nami.
Huh?
She said this was so that you and I could be alone together.
Nami came up with it all for my sake...
That's why... I was so happy that you thought of this as a date, Sora-kun.
Oh wow... what is she doing?
I-I had a lot of fun today!
Well, now that it's out...
Sumiya-san.
Did you know there's a store around here that sells cute Western clothing?
We came today to do some research anyway.
And... I think there'll be plenty of clothes you might like.
Would you like to go?
Sora-kun...
Okay!
What in the world am I doing?
I've always admired you, Nami.
Do you remember when we first met?
A guy was asking me out and I didn't know what to do.
Then you appeared, Nami.
Honestly, I thought you were a little scary at the time.
I forgot all about that, it was so long ago...
But... I also thought you were really cool.
W... What?
I was thinking it would be nice if I could be as straightforward with my feelings as you.
Is it really okay to just come in?
Yes.  We're just here to shelter from the rain for a while.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry, Sora-kun.
Kana and Sora-nii?  Why?
It's all because I wanted to match these with the clothes in the clubroom...
It's okay.  Nobody knew it would start raining so quickly.
You should take your clothes off.
You'll catch a cold.
Yeah.
Um...
I'm also going to change my clothes...
So could you close your eyes for a while?
Oh... okay.
Kana?
No way!
It's okay now, Sora-kun.
Sumiya-san?
I'm sorry, Sora-kun.
Before I knew it, I just couldn't stop myself...
Did Nami plan this too?
No... this is of my own will.
Part of me wonders what I'm doing...
But this is how I feel.
U-Um, Sumiya-san...
If you cling onto me, I'll...
Sorry.
Don't apologize.
Does this mean you recognize me as a woman?
What?  Of course you're a woman, Sumiya-san.
Nami told me something the other day...
That you like girls with breasts my size.
You can think of this as a selfish request.
Please let me pleasure you with my breasts.
What's going on?
Sora-kun, it's incredible...
Am I... doing it right?
Does it feel good?
Yeah...
It feels... good...
I'm so happy.
I'm glad my breasts please you.
Sora-kun, it's so hot...
S-Sumiya-san.
Amazing...
I can feel it throbbing between my breasts...
No, Sumiya-san... I'm gonna...
Please...
Go ahead and come.
I'm coming.  I'm coming...
C-Coming!
So this is what you taste like, Sora-kun...
Nami, it feels good... really good...
What's this?
I'm... inside you, Kana...
Nami...
It's so hot.
It's so hot...
Ah, that's right.  I'm...
Kana!
Kana, I...
I can make you feel good now, Kana.
Because I have this...
Kana, it feels so good inside you.
Yours feels good too, Nami.
I've always wanted to do this.
Kana, I'm gonna come.
I'm gonna... come...
Please... come...
Inside me... fill me with your come!
Kana... Kana...
Together, Nami... let's come together!
It's coming out... Nami, your come is filling me up...
Kana!
We've finally become one.
Aww, rain again today?
I don't like the rainy season.
It's so humid.
Yeah.
Hey, Sora.
Aki-neechan...
Sora, do you feel good?
No, if you do that...
You don't have to hold back.
Just like this...
Aki-neechan...
Hey, Kana...
Why don't you want me?
Is it because...
...I don't... have one?
So how far did you go?
Weren't you alone together?
With Sora-nii in the clubroom at night...
Did the two of you have sex?
N-Nami?
So you kissed?
I see.  So it went well.
Yes.
To tell you the truth, Kana...
I saw it all.
Even the moment your lips took that thing in...
Thank you, Nami.
You're always taking care of me.
I'm a coward and can't do anything on my own.
You gave me courage, Nami.
It's all thanks to you.
I see.
So it's all my fault.
I masked my deceitful lies with
empty words of encouragement.
This must be my punishment.
Hey, Kana...
Yes?
I like you.
Ever since the moment I first met you.
Me too.
Nami, you're the greatest friend I could hope to have.
Now and forever.
Born on the same day.  Raised in the same environment.
We're twins who've lived the same lives.
Yet...
Sora-nii...
You...
Nami?
Did they feel good?
Did Kana's boobs feel good?
Nami?  What happened?
Nami?
They felt good, didn't they?
You love boobs, after all.
Hey...
How did they feel?
I'm sure you fondled them a lot.
Stirring them around roughly...
This thing... give it to me.
I was so jealous of you.
Just because you have this thing...
Why do you take everything I want away from me?!
Nami, are you crying?
Nami?
Wait, this is wrong...
It's fine!
It's fine, so please, leave me be...
Nami...
It's going in...
Sora-nii, you're going all the way inside me...
Nami, you're going too fast...
Don't... do it so fast, or I'll...
Sora-nii... you're stirring up... my insides...
Nami, I can't anymore...
I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come!
It's okay...
It's okay, you can come inside me...
So...
More...
Break me!
Amazing...
It feels amazing, Sora-nii...
Me too...
Sora-nii, my insides and my body feel so light...
Nami, I'm coming.
I'm coming!
I'm coming too...
I'm coming... I'm coming!
It's coming out... it's spurting and pouring into me...
I'm being... violated...
Hey, Nami...
What?
Do you like Sumiya-san?
Dummy.
What are you doing, Sora-nii?
You'll be late.
Y-Yeah.
Come on, run with Onee-chan!
That's embarrassing, so cut it out, Aki-nee!
Let's go, Sora.
Y-Yeah.
There's just one thought in my heart
Tatta hitotsu no omoi wo mune ni
Thank you
Arigatou
Didn't we meet by chance on the long road home?
Zutto tsuzuku kaerimichi guzen deatta ne
Let's go home together
Isshoni kaerou yo
In my happiness, I can no longer hide these feelings
Hashaide sugu barechau kono kimochi wo
Laughing.  I'm fine today, too.  What are you doing?
Waratte kyou mo heiki nani wo shiteru
So that you wouldn't notice me
Anata ni kizukarenai you ni
I walked just a little slowly
Sukoshi yukkuri aruita
I'm engrossed with how time flies by just like that
Anata ga iru sore dake de atto iu ma ni
Just by being with you
Sugite yuku jikan ni muchuu ni natte ita
If time won't stop for us, I'll wish over and over again
Toki ga tomarenai to nandomo negai
Because I'd like to stay like this forever
Kono mama zutto iraretara ii noni
There's just one thought in my heart
Tatta hitotsu no omoi wo mune ni
I love you
Daisuki yo
UFW Staff
Translator: Ershin
Timer: commander`A
Editor/Typesetter/QC: Raze