The "Tales of the 15 Beautiful Girls Adrift: Exciting Harem Episode" will start now!
Kirameku suiheisen no hate
Drifting from the edge of the sparkling horizon
Nagaretsuita tokonatsu no Love Island
To the shores of the love island of everlasting summer
Minamikaze ni notte yatte kita
We've come here by riding the southern winds
Love Affair koi no mahou ni miserareta no
Love affair, I'm captivated by the magic of love
Nee joushoukiryuu ni notte kimi wo tsukamaetai
Hey, I want to ride the rising air and catch you
Daisuki
I love you
Aoku hirogaru umi he
Towards the wide blue sea
Tobikonde miyou hajikeyou
Let's jump in, release ourselves
Terenaide waratte
And laugh without being shy
Kyou mo manatsu no taiyou
Today too, the midsummer sun
Yaketsuku hodo ni terasu yo
Shines to the point of sunburning us
Bokura no mecha happy koi moyou
This is our super-happy love pattern
Ba-dump!!
Full Nudity at
the Steamy
Hot Spring!
Lone wolf of a classmate who
doesn't get along with anyone
Island god
with canine
ears and tail
I can't believe a fully-equipped and practically brand new digital camera drifted ashore.
It feels like I'm leading a richer life than back in Japan.
There's only one thing for a guy with a camera to do.
Thanks as always, Monkey-chin.
That's it!
Nanashi, I'll wash your body for you.
You're a kind person to offer to serve a god of your own will.
I'm sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
I'll deal you divine punishment if you don't do this properly!
Yeah yeah, I'll clean you properly.
That's enough-
Careful!
C-Chiba-san?!
Nanashi, you're so cute!
You're really fueling my burning love for animals!
S-Stop, Chiba-san.
It's a serious sin to defile a god!
I'm not the one at fault.
It's your fault for being too cute, Nanashi.
What kind of bratty excuse is that?!
If I allow a human to toy with me, my pride as a god will...
Wait, Nanashi.
Your body is so smooth and your tail is so fluffy.
It's wonderful to touch!
Not my tail, it's really sensitive...
Nanashi, why are you so lovely?
No!
Looks like your tail's really sensitive, Nanashi.
We're doing such lewd things even though we're both female...
As a god, I can't allow this!
I'm not really a lesbian.
I just love cute animals.
Don't treat a god like me as an animal...
No, I may be a god, but I'm still sensitive down there!
Nanashi!
Chiba-san, you're so wet down there, and you're rubbing against mine...
Nanashi, Nanashi!
No, Chiba-san!  Any more and I'll...
Don't grab my tail!
I didn't touch your tail.
Shit.  I got too into it and my hand slipped.
Kazuma, you...
You horny little monkey!
Oh, no!
This is my chance!
It's time for revenge.
Help me out, god!
What are you doing?
I can't be the one who gets toyed with all the time.
Though, I'm not exactly happy with helping Kazuma out...
Let me go, Nanashi.
Don't, Nanashi.
S-Stop, don't touch-
Damn it, I'm getting turned on from being groped by this guy...
Your nipples got hard.
P-Please, anything but this!
I'm not the one at fault.
It's your fault for being too sexy, Chiba.
No!
You...!
Now do you understand how I felt?
S-Stop, Nanashi...
I'm coming, Chiba.
It's not everyday that you get to see Chiba like this.
Die, monkey!
An exciting
twin sister
photoshoot!
Gloomy younger twin
sister who likes curses
Cheerful and cute older
twin sister and classmate
Oh, it's Kazu.
He'd probably die even if he isn't cursed.
Like I'd die!
Pity.  I'll have to curse you, then.
Don't!  Your curses really are dangerous!
Kazu, what's that?
This is...
The Hatsushima line of digital cameras, NTR15B.
What the hell?  You really know your stuff.
I, Kage, am the brains between us.
And I, Hikari, am the body!
Get out of the way, darkness.
I'll curse you if you infringe on Onee-chan's rights as a model.
It's fine, Kage-chan.
My beauty is the property of all humankind!
Onee-chan, your radiant personality is just too bright!
Be sure to make them pretty!
You can count on me!
Well, Kazu?
Am I sexy?
Yeah, you are.
I am, right?
I'm pretty confident about my body!
Wait, Kazu.  Just what are you taking pictures of?
This wasn't what I meant by "body"!
Sorry, sorry.
Onee-chan, I can feel the pounding of your heart.
Does being photographed by Kazu turn you on?
Geez, Kazu.  You photograph me like you're licking me all over.
Am I really that attractive?
Y-Yeah.
I guess I'll give you some extras for being honest!
No!
Get out of the way, darkness!
I'll curse you if you lust after Onee-chan.
How dark!
Now now, it's perfectly normal for a healthy guy like him to get a boner from fantasizing about my pussy.
Onee-chan...
Since we're at it already, let's have your pictures taken too!
O-Onee-chan, really?
Kage-chan, we're identical.  We have the same genes.
That's why I'm sure you're also pretty attractive!
Right, Kazu?
Y-Yeah.  You're right.
Only if we're talking about her appearance, though.
Look.  Even Kazu, the lover of cute girls, said so.
Let's do this together, Kage-chan.
Okay.
If that's what you want, Onee-chan, I'll do it.
This pose... is embarrassing.
It's adorable, Kage-chan!
H-How's this, Onee-chan?
Good job, good job!
I like to remain in the shadows, but I'm being observed...
All my private areas are being seen...
Here, say "ahh".
Ahh.
Kage-chan, did you get fatter?
I'm pretty sure we have the same weight.
Does that mean that I got fatter, too?
T-That's not what I meant.
Hey, Kage-chan.
You're turned on, right?
That...
That's not true.
There's no point in hiding it.  I know.
We're twins.
Kage-chan, you know too, right?
I'm all wet down there.
Onee-chan...
Kazu, take more cute pictures of me.
Look at me, being all perverted!
Keep looking!
Hey...
Look at me, please!
Onee-chan...
Kage-chan, if you masturbate too...
I'll feel twice as good!
Onee-chan, I feel really good, too!
It's like you're caressing me, Onee-chan!
I can feel you too, Kage-chan!
Kazu, it's your fault that we're this turned on.
Won't you take responsibility?
Won't you?
We'll start with Kage-chan!
Onee-chan?
Can I really?
It's rude to ask that of a girl who's already ready.
Onee-chan, I'm not ready at all...
Look, she's already really wet.
I'm digging in!
Oh, no!  This feels so good!
Onee-, I'm so turned on!
You look so cute when you feel good, Kage-chan.
It's making me feel good too!
Kazu, make me feel good too!
S-Sure!
It's going in!
Onee-chan, you're the one being fucked, but it feels like I'm being fucked, too!
This is bad.  It could become a habit!
You're both really tight and feel exactly the same inside.
You really are twins!
Kazu, put it inside Kage-chan.
Then, put it inside me again!
Alright, I'll do just that!
Here it is!
This time, it really is inside me!
It's also inside me...
I don't know whether it's inside me or you anymore!
I have two to satisfy, but I'll do my best!
Onee-chan!
Kage-chan!
I'm coming!
Come!
This is a pretty good picture, if I say so myself.
A naughty
extracurricular class
under the blue sky!
Timid, clumsy, pretty, and
big-breasted crybaby teacher
Childhood friend
who's always
clinging onto
the protagonist
This is read as "sense of shame".
Got it, everyone?
Yes!
Be sure to take notes.
Okay!
Oh, Shiraishi-kun.
It's Kazu-chan!
Yotsuya-san, we're in the middle of class.
Sensei, what are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
It's not.
Go and stand if you don't know the answer.
It's been standing for a while already.
The answer is "class".
I'm having a class.
I mean, I'm a teacher.
But I haven't been able to use this skill since I came to this island.
At this rate, I feel like I'll be mistaken for someone useless.
So, I thought that I'd show everyone my merits as a teacher.
I see.
But there isn't much point if Koto is your only student.
Exactly!  No one wants to be my student!
My classes are failing!
Why are you her only student, Koto?
I was thinking that it'd give me something to write in my diary.
A student as terrible as Shiraishi-kun wasn't able to tell this was a class...
How can she say things that would hurt a student so naturally?
Cheer up, Sensei.
Everyone knows that you're a wonderful person.
Shiraishi-kun.
You wear glasses...
Have huge tits...
And you're a female teacher.
You're blessed with excellent virtues!
I don't think glasses and huge tits
have anything to do with it, though.
I know!
If it's a subject that would interest everyone,
people would take your class and respect you!
An interesting subject?
That would be...
Health and physical education!
In other words, P.E. with focus on health.
But health and physical education is beyond my expertise, so I don't really know much about it.
In that case, you'll study it with me!
So that you can run a health class,
let us study male and female bodily
differences, and how babies are conceived!
Pistil
Stamen
Kazu-chan, that's just weird!  I don't see the logic!
If you want to study the mothering body...
You can do it with me.
Declining birth rates have become a serious problem on this island.
Let us study in order to come up with a countermeasure.
What?  Really?!
You'd go that far for me...
I'm so moved!  I'll do my best!
I'll also do my best, Kazu-chan!
Sit.
Beg.
Stay.
What?!
I'm doing this for Sensei.
If you behave, I'll give you lots of love afterwards.
Really?
Really.
Really really?
Really really.
Definitely, okay?
Hmph.
Well, let's start from the beginning.
Sensei.  An important part of the act of reproduction is making the male reproductive organ erect.
I read from a book that fellatio is an effective means of achieving this.
But Shiraishi-kun, your penis is already erect.
This is nowhere near enough.
Sensei, it seems that you have a lot to learn about the male body.
Now, suck it and see!
O-Okay.
She's sucking her own student's dick...
What an exciting situation!
It actually got even bigger...
That's because it's set to expand at set intervals.
I'll have to study this more.
Sensei, now we'll use your breasts...
Shiraishi-kun, you want to touch your teacher's breasts?
You're like a kid.
No.  Like this, Sensei!
You'll use your hands to rub your breasts against my penis!
This is the secret health technique, "Boobjob"!
I had no idea my breasts could be used like this.  How deep.
Sensei...
No... it's sticky and smelly...
Shiraishi-kun, I won't get pregnant if you don't come inside.
Don't worry.
I, Shiraishi Kazuma, have the most sperm in all of Japan!
If only you'd be this passionate in your other subjects.
Look, I've already recovered.
Let us continue.
It's the first time I've ever tried
making a baby, so please be gentle.
Sensei!
I'm actually having sex with my student...
Sensei, I'm gonna come.}
Are you ready to be inseminated?
I'm fertile today, so please come lots inside me!
Let's make lots of future students!
Sensei!
Your hot stuff is flowing inside me...
Hey, just how long are you making me wait?
Ah, Koto.  I got too into health class and forgot about you.
It's my turn next, got it?
A-Alright.
Finally... finally!
Kazu-chan's finally gonna stick it inside my already dripping pussy...
It went in!
Kazu-chan's semen tastes so good!
Yotsuya-san, the way you use your tongue is really lewd...
Where did you learn that?
Koto probably does practice exercises by herself from start to finish.
Kazu-chan... more, more!
Yeah, yeah.
Kazu-chan...
Come on, keep licking Sensei down there.
Understanding the bodies of others is part of the health class, right?
It feels so good!
I'm gonna come again...
A female student is making me come again...
My dignity as a teacher...
N-No!
I'm coming, Koto!
You're coming...
Kazu-chan, your semen is entering my womb...
With this, we're now officially man and woman!
Huh?
You tried to peek at us at the hot springs,
so Chiba beat you up until you lost consciousness.
I see, so all of that was...
...probably just a dream, I'm sure.
Mabushii hizashi wo zenshin ni abinagara
As I bask fully in the sun's bright rays
Nagarenagasarete hirogaru umi wo miteru
I stare at the ebb and flow of the wide sea
Koushite yasashii kaze ni dakarete itara
Being embraced like this by the pleasant wind
Kagayaku mirai wo kitai shichaisou da yo
Makes me anticipate the shining future ahead
Chikasugite demo tooi
Too close, but also far away
Kyorikan wo ima koso kaete miseru yo
Now is the time to change this sense of distance
Chance
Chance!
Anata no koto dake wo zutto miteta
All this while I've had eyes only for you
Kirakira na aijoukousen haato wo neraiuchi
I'll snipe your heart with this sparkling beam of love
With my overpowering appeal that would mesmerize any girl
Donna onna no ko mo kasumu kurai
Kurakura watashi no miryoku de anata no hitomi wo hitorijime
I'll focus your eyes only on me
UFW-FAKKU Staff
Translator/QC: Raze
Timer: Sindalf
Editor: Nikon
Typesetter: Bob64