I'm sorry for what I did the other day.
I insisted on taking your uniform...
And I... soiled it.
There is no need to worry about that.
I can provide you with as many uniforms as you want.
However, the heart is different.
If I was able to help connect your hearts, nothing else matters.
You're still a child.
Or am I the child?
I'm still so childish compared to her.
How immoral. Have some shame.
What in the world am I thinking about?
Good morning, Sylvie.
You're up early today.
I have morning practice.
Well then, I'll be excusing myself.
How shameless...
How shameless... How shameless!
Doing such things in broad daylight...
What is wrong with me?
I can't even face him properly now.
Good morning, Teppei-sama.
Did something happen?
You don't look very well.
No, nothing happened.
You don't seem too well.
Now, come this way.
UFW-FAKKU Presents
Part 2: Nights Where I Don't Want To Be Alone
What in the world are you doing?
Are you telling me to do whatever you say?
Well, you did say you wanted me all to yourself.
I simply wanted to speak to you...
Because you looked like you were in pain...
You're the one in pain, Sylvie.
You've been holding back all this time, right?
Your smell is seducing me.
Arima-dono, you too.
Haven't you been holding back as well?
Y-Yuu-san?!
Princess Van Hossen's unfriendly attitude...
Has it not been hurting your feelings?
Well...
I haven't been able to masturbate
ever since she came to this mansion, and...
W-Whoa, t-that was a joke!
All of the indecent material in your luggage has been disposed of.
It's become like this...
Perverted things are bad.
That is why I will take care of it for you.
Have some shame.
Hasn't it only been two days since we last did it?
Yet you're still so insistent...
B-Besides, this is not something can be done in public.
It's all your fault for ignoring me.
Fine, I'll agree to do this indecent act.
I can't have you blaming me unreasonably.
Then...
Pledge yourself to me like a knight.
I, Sylvia Van Hossen...
...will become Arima Teppei's, for just one day...
Say forever instead, even if it's a lie.
Today is all I can promise.
I pledge to be your... your slave...
...f-for one day!
Well said. You can come now.
Unfortunately, I won't climax from just that.
No... not there!
No, Arima-dono... not there, no!
I understand.
I'll admit it.
Please, Teppei, no more...
I remember this feeling... anything but that...
Teppei, please!
The bathrooom... let me go to the bathroom...
I don't want you to see me shaming myself!
I want to see everything about you, Sylvie.
T-That's enough...
Are you trying to mock me?
Are you making me suffer a humiliation worse than death...?
Aren't you my slave?
You have no right to decide, Sylvie.
That has nothing to do with-
No, no more!
I'll come... if... you put your tongue in directly like that!
I really can't take any more...
Teppei!
I've even pleaded so many times...
People like you...!
Don't make that face.
I want to see what your face looks like when you feel good.
Like I care, geez!
It's coming.
I can't stop it!
My strength is leaving me...
No, no, no!
In a place used by every student in this school...
My filthy smell is...
We can just clean it up later.
We'll find a rag or something soon enough if we look.
But for now...
You truly are an irritating man.
No matter how irrational it is, you keep trying to break into my heart.
You simply looked on after making a lady urinate in public.
Men like you don't deserve my respect.
Neither do men who immediately lust after my body.
I'm scared that you'll hate me even though I'm always lusting after you.
But when you're here in front of me, I can't stop myself.
I-I would've hated you long ago if I could!
Furthermore, I'm to obey your every command today.
But another time like today will never...
Don't be so passionate from the start...
I... I can tell that you're getting hotter and hotter!
It... It's changing the shape of my insides...
...and rubbing against me...
Sylvie, you're also...
Don't say it out loud!
Things like that...
You're the only one who needs to know.
For you've turned me into this kind of woman...
An unreserved woman with no shame...
It's all a big mess...
My values, my pride...
Everything has been destroyed!
I can't go back anymore!
That's what you've done to me!
You'd better... take responsibility!
Responsibility for stealing my heart and rationality!
You're horrible...
You're gradually making me unable to hide my own shame!
It's enough for me alone to be shameless.
From now own, make love to me when you feel the need.
Everything, inside me...
Y-You're going to come soon, aren't you?
I can feel it getting bigger and trembling inside me...
Let it out...
It's much better than...
...soiling the floor or my uniform!
Make sure it doesn't spill out...
I don't want more things to clean!
Hurry...
Hurry up and come!
My... my waist is losing strength!
Y-Yes...
It's coming again already...
Together!
Teppei, I'm gonna come... so come with me...
I... I'm coming!
I'm coming!
So it can be said that you have taken care of some private matters?
That may be so, but what I did was forceful.
I think she really hates me now.
It is not enough to simply know how to sweet-talk in the social world.
You still need to learn how to treat a lady properly, Teppei-sama.
Why don't you think of this as a good experience?
Of being caught cheating?
It is but discipline if it is with a maid such as myself.
Telling her that should settle the matter.
Discipline?
So that was discipline, and this is also discipline.
I see.  You don't intend to turn back.
You can say no if you don't want to.
For those born into a family of knights, breaking a vow is unacceptable.
That's all there is to it.
But now you're my slave... aren't you?
I've changed as well.
I've worn a dress unsuitable for me because you told me to.
Being treated as a frail woman feels quite pleasant.
How indecent.
You let out so much of that hot liquid inside me earlier,
yet you're still this hard.
Don't think that you can always have your way.
Seriously, it's so hard it's almost embarrassing.
If I were to be teased by this hot thing,
I would probably swear myself to you for eternity.
You're beautiful, Sylvie.
More than anyone.
You're sweet-talking again?
Just how shameless... are you?
And just how shameless am I?
Above all, my body has learned...
...the fact that I have become your woman.
It's gradually pushing in...
I shouldn't, but when you're inside me...
I can't... I can't anymore!
Rebuke me...
Rebuke me for how filthy I've become.
My body that was meant for my country now belongs to one man...
Please, Teppei.
I want us to at least come together...
A big one's coming... I'm coming!
Don't make me come alone!
I'm coming!
If you make me pregnant,
I might just have the resolve to become yours.
No, ignore what I just said.
How unfair of you to just sit there and listen.
I love you.
That's all I want to say.
Saying something like that at a time like this is even less fair.
I did think that binding myself to you by getting pregnant might've been a good idea.
Women are crafty creatures.
Keep that in mind.
That's enough, Maria!
Sit in your own seat while you're eating.
You're making it difficult for Teppei to eat.
If it's difficult for you to eat, go "Ah" and I'll feed you, okay?
Did you give Onee-chan permission to call you by your first name?
Papa said that a man cannot always let a woman have her way.
I'm sorry to disturb you during your meal.
Teppei-sama, there is something I must urgently report.
You look wonderful... almost dazzling.
You're attractive in your school uniform, when you're fencing, and in your dress...
But I admire you most when you're dressed this way, Sylvie.
Thoughtless words like that can be offensive.
I wouldn't have hesitated before I met you.
I wouldn't have thought twice about throwing my life away as well.
But it's different now.
Just now, the Flemish Principality is...
I'm afraid.
My home country has become a battlefield.
What can a little girl like me do there?
I might lose my life...
...or be detained there.
I probably won't be able to return to this country...
...nor see you again.
The mere thought of that...
...shows that I've really become your woman.
But you're still going to go, right?
I feel that I'm a very jealous woman.
Others will take my place beside you if I leave.
I know it'll happen, but the thought of it is enough to shake my resolve.
Is saying "I'll wait for you" not enough?
Must I show you my resolve?
Then you're the one who needs to brace yourself, Sylvie.
I'll have you show me all of your shame.
I'm more than ready.
I've been bound to you ever since we first met.
I'll give you all I have as a woman.
I'll carve my womanhood onto your manhood.
Burn the sight of my lasciviousness into your eyes!
Only you...
Only you can see!
It's so hot!
It feels like it'll melt from your fingers!
No, it's coming...
I'm coming... I'm coming, no!
Don't forget.
You're the only one...
...I'll show this side of me to.
Only you...
Laugh at me for being such a shameless woman.
I feel like I'll drown in this liberating feeling...
What's wrong?
Do you scorn my shamelessness?
Didn't I already say that I'd be improper tonight?
Not there!
N-Not that dirty place!
You really don't want to?
No... it's okay.
My ass... my ass!
Is... Is this okay?
Yeah. I want to know every last part of your body.
The fact that I can't see it directly is the only thing keeping me sane.
I'm so embarrassed I could die.
But a part of me is happy.
Because I can finally have my reward.
No, no way...
It's going in... no, no!
Teppei, it's better than anything I've ever had... It's amazing!
Perfectly... It fits perfectly!
That's quite a shock.
N-No...
I-I just love being intimately connected to you...
I want to feel you inside me forever...
I'm trembling with pleasure from my ass... that abnormal place!
This is the woman you swore to love forever!
I won't let you take it back now...
Don't forget!
I won't forget either...
We'll only be able to see each other in our dreams for a while...
So don't hold anything back...
This warmth, this hardness, and this shape...
I want to take it with me!
Good... that felt so good...
I'm about to...
So...
Do it...
Come... Come!
Finish this by shooting all of your come...
...inside this fillthy woman!
Your thing... is messing me up...
What did Sylvie talk to you about?
She warned me not let my guard down.
Huh?
She said that you are skilled in using a woman's shame to make her yours, Teppei-sama.
Apparently, a woman like myself would be tamed in one night.
What kind of evil man does she take me for?
UFW-FAKKU Staff
Translator: aznskman
Timer/Typesetter: Sindalf
Editor/QC: Raze