You're really sensitive, Reo.
Mai...
It's kinda cold here...
It's okay.
Soon, your body will grow warm, and you'll forget that you're cold.
N-Not there...
Everywhere that Mai touches... feels so good!
Does it feel good?
I want to hear you moan, Reo.
D-Dummy!
What are we gonna do if someone hears us?
It's fine.
Everyone's already gone home.
I know that much, but...
I don't wanna.
If you're gonna act that way...
Not there!
No, Mai... Mai...
Reo, I get so turned on when I hear your voice.
M-Mai...
It's true.
So, please... touch me too...
Wow... you're so wet down there.
You're so cute, Mai.
No, you're the one who's cute, Reo.
That's not true.
All of the sensitive spots on your body are really cute.
I-If you suck my nipples that hard...
But, they're getting harder and harder...
That's because of you, Reo.
I'm getting really turned on just from you touching me.
Mai!
Hey!  If you do that...
I want to hear Mai moan.
If you keep licking me there, I'll...
No, Mai!
No!
No, I wanna make you feel good!
Reo...
Mai, no... if you keep going, I'll...
It's okay, Reo.  Come.
O-Okay...
Sono Hanabira ni Kuchizuke wo
Becoming Your Lover
UFW Presents
I'm sure this cold is because we did it in the infirmary.
Jeez, it's all Mai's fault!
Mai's probably in class right now.
I want her to stay by my side.
I don't want to be alone.
Mai...
M-Mai!
W-Wha-
How are you feeling?
What are you doing here?
Hey, now...
I only came here to see how you were doing.
I-I can deal with something this minor.
Oh?
Were you crying from being lonely?
No, I wasn't.
I really wasn't crying!
Okay, okay.
If you don't calm down, your cold won't get any better.
Aren't you still supposed to be at school, though?
Yeah, but I was worried about you, so I left early.
You left early?
Your face is a little red.
Do you still have a fever?
Yeah... it seems like you still have a fever.
Reo, are you in any pain?
I'm... a little thirsty.
I'm thirsty!
I want to drink some water.
Here.
I figured you'd want some, so I
picked up a few things on the way here.
Wai...
W-Wait!
Do you want some more?
I... I'm okay.
Reo, you're sweating.  Do you want to change?
N-Not really.
That's no good.
If you want to get better, you need to change your clothes and rest.
R-Really?
If you're changing, I'll wipe your body down for you.
You haven't taken a bath yet, right?
I-I can do it myself.
I'm fine...
Oh, come on.  There's no need to be embarrassed.
Just leave it to me.
I'm fine!
I can do it myself, I don't need you!
H-Hey!
You're gonna make your cold worse.
Give it up!
Geez, Mai... you're so pushy.
Just leave it to me.
I'll get a hot towel and
change of clothes ready right away.
Reo?
It's okay.
I'll be by your side all day today.
Mai!
Why are you following me?!
It's because you're running away...
Could it be that you hate me?
Am I bothering you?
N-No!
It's the opposite.
I like you, Mai!
You... like me?
You don't bother me at all.
I... really like you, Mai!
Reo, you...
...like me?!
You dummy!
You should have noticed it sooner.
Well... um, I...
It's just so sudden...
I'm a bother to you, right!?
That's why you should just leave me alone!
I was able to let Mai know how I feel,
even if she'll hate me for it.
Reo...
I... like you too, Reo...
Really...
Oh, don't give me that attitude.
I'll prove it to you.
Mai...
Sorry to keep you, Reo.
Did you wait quietly?
I'm sick.  Of course I waited quietly.
Sorry for leaving you alone.
Don't get too upset.
I'm... not really upset.
Then... first off, let's get you washed up.
Okay.
Are you cold?
I'm fine.
Reo, lower your arms.
Sorry.
I can't stop myself...
I want you right now, Reo.
D-Dummy!  I'm sick, you know!
It's fine.
If you get a fever again, I'll stay by your side and nurse you back to health.
Wai-
Reo?
You don't want to kiss me?
That's not it.
I just don't want to get you sick.
I wouldn't mind catching a cold if it's from you, Reo.
B-But that's...
...not good.
I-I guess you're right.
You're sick, after all.
It's not a good idea to do perverted stuff.
Sorry.
It's fine.
I just need to cool my head a bit.
I'll be here all day.
It's because I want you to touch me, Mai.
Reo.
Then, I won't stop.
That's fine, right?
You don't stop even when I tell you to, anyway.
Yup.
You're shivering.
I'm sorry.  You must be cold.
Mai's smell...
Your body's actually quite warm...
Of course it is.  I'm sick...
Let me know if you feel uncomfortable.
It feels all tingly where Mai is licking me.
Does it feel good, Reo?
I-I'm not telling you.
You're not gonna tell me?
Reo.
I want you to tell me.
Then, I can make you feel even better.
Mai, you pervert.
But, I just want you to feel good.
N-Not there!
Your pussy isn't telling me to stop.
You're already wet.
M-Mai!
Wow, Reo.  It's getting wetter and wetter.
No!
Don't make so much noise down there!
It's so embarrassing,
but I can't stop, it feels so good!
Reo...
Reo, I love you.
I love you!
You came, didn't you?
I-It was too stimulating...
Mai, you pervert.
Sorry, Reo.
I'm really sorry.
If your cold gets worse, I'll take
responsibility and nurse you back to health.
No, don't just suddenly spread my legs open...
You're cute, Reo.
Mai...
D-Don't!
No fair!
It's not fair...
I want to hear you moan, too!
Mai...
More...
Touch me more...
Me too, Mai!
Mai...
Let me hear you moan.
Your moans are for me, only!
Reo!  Reo!
Reo...
Do you like me?
What's with that embarassing question all of a sudden?!
Reo, I want you to tell me.
I... love you, Mai.
More... keep telling me!
I love you!
Mai, I love you!
Words can't express how much I love you.
Reo...
I...
I love you too, Reo...
38.5 degrees...
Looks like I caught your cold, Reo.
Geez...
I told you so.
I'll be fine.
So, go on to school.
Okay...
I'll be fine.
If I take this day off to rest, I'll get better!
See?
Right?
Okay, okay.
See ya.
I guess I was a little cold to her...
Reo.
Why...
You know I can't do anything alone.
Hurry up and get better so you can go with me.
Thank you, Reo.
Somehow... that makes me really happy.
D-Don't say stupid things.
Hurry up and get better.
I'll be by your side until you get well.
Until my cold gets better?
So...
You won't be with me after that?
I'll always...
Even after your cold gets better...
And anyway, you won't be able to leave me even if you wanted to.
I wouldn't...
l-let... you...
Reo.
UFW Staff
Translator/Timer: Kusion
Translation Checker: Ershin
Typesetter: Kemeko
Editor/QC: Raze