I'm doing this much for you, but you're still not waking up...
What's more, it's me who's doing this for you...
Ah, you woke up!
Miharu!
Geez, and I took the trouble to wake you up in pleasure...
You can't hold back anymore, right?
Then hurry up and come!
You came so much so early in the morning.
You!
Geez...
No~
You're so wet this early in the morning...
Ah, I can feel your breath...
I'm only this perverted in front of you, you know?
It's because I'm with you that I become perverted, Ushio...
No...
Hey, I want you...
Don't!
Ushio, don't tease me!
It's going in...
Your dick went inside me this early in the morning, Ushio...
You're so rough, Ushio...
There!
No...
You're rubbing against my pussy...
That... feels good!
Amazing, you're reaching all the way inside...
You're hitting my womb, it feels so good!
Yes, thrust hard against my womb!
Ushio!
I'm about to come!
Together with me...
I want you to come with me, Ushio!
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
You're coming so much inside my womb...
Geez, what were you doing?
We're gonna be late, late!
Geez, it must be because your parents aren't around that you humped me so hard!
What do you mean "humped", Miharu...
Since you came so much inside me,
I might get pregnant!
What do you think you're saying out on the street?
Nobody's listening.
Even so...
Nobody would believe that you didn't stand out at all in the past if they saw you now.
The past doesn't matter, right?
Or are you saying that you're not satisfied with the way I am now?
N-No...
Then, there's no need to worry.
I don't want to let you see the way I was.
Those times...
I don't want to go back to those times.
That's because the me now has met you, Ushio.
S-Sorry...
It's okay.
Even so, there are times when I don't want you to hate the way I was back then, either.
Huh?
It's nothing.
Let's go!
Yeah.
Miharu!
Miharu, are you okay?
Miharu?
Hey, Miharu!
Miharu!
Part 1:  Sis is fast asleep now... ♥
Translator/Editor/QC: Raze | Timer: Klipper | Typesetting/QC: Nikon
UFW Presents
~Miharu After~
Amazing, amazing!
You can't wait any longer, right?
Lie still for a bit.
It's gotten all big now, and it's twitching.
It's going in...
Just a little more, and it'll go inside...
Wait, Miharu!
What?
I'm no good because I'm a virgin?
B-But you made fun of me for being a virgin...
Doesn't matter, right?
Anyway, I gave you my super previous virginity,
so I'm gonna use you to feel really good!
No, you're not allowed to touch!
If I didn't push you down, you wouldn't
even have the guts to have sex with me.
I'm not gonna let someone like you touch me...
I'm the one who's violating you,
so I'm the one who decides what's okay to do.
N-No!
You're thrusting up with your hips...
No, this is... my first time, but I feel so good...
No, I'm coming...
It's my first time, but-
I'm coming!
She's so pretty, it's like she's passed away.
She's passed out .
I was just wondering if Sis would've
wanted to be the female lead in a tragedy.
Stop trying to be cute, too.
I'm not cute?
I guess you are.
Your lover's unconscious, but you're still hitting on other girls.
Futaba-chan!
You're unfaithful as always aren't you, Sempai?
Since you were still a virgin.
Why are you so mean?!
It's the first time I've seen the cute side of you in a long while, Sempai.
You're easy to break, as always.
What you just said was pretty scary.
Fu... taba.
Sis, are you alright?
Miharu.
I'll go get the doctor.
Huh?  Where am I?
Are you okay?
You fell down and lost consciousness,
so you were brought to the hospital.
No way... how?
You were on your way to school...
School?  Why am I...
Futaba, why do you have that uniform on?
Amnesia?!
They think it's only temporary,
but what if she remains like this, never recovering her memories?
No way, she'll be fine.
Yeah, you're right.  She should be fine.
Sempai, my parents will be visiting soon today.
I'll contact you about her condition later, so please go rest a little.
Yeah.
If you fall sick too, that would be really bad.
You're right.  Okay.
And so, I've come here with Sis!
What do you mean, "and so"?!
You never gave me an explanation!
Geez, you're so caught up in all the minor details.
I already said that, in order to recover her memories, this place would be the best.
You're omitting too much!
Well, I guess I kinda understand.
But will she be physically okay?
It never was a serious physical injury to begin with,
so she should be fine if we just let her rest normally.
Though, it was tough to get her here.  Sis is really shy.
Just getting her to come here took a lot of work.
She was always this kind of person.
N-No, I...
Well, she was like this until she got into high school...
Sis, say hi to Sempai.
Don't just keep showing him your back.
Geez.
Oops!
Come on, you shy girl.
Are you okay, Miharu?
Miharu... Miharu?
Irifune-kun's calling me by my first name?
Geez, that's all you do.
Come on, say hi to him properly.
Please take care of the both of us!
Both?
I'm really here at Irifune-kun's house...
And... he's supposed to be my boyfriend?
It looks like she's lost all her memories
starting from when she got into high school.
So it looks like she doesn't remember being your girlfriend, or the lucky draw...
I'm dressed like this, and I'm going out with Irifune-kun...
I'm... really...
So, she can't remember meeting me, either?
I thought that she might recover he memories if she's with you, so I...
Your dad actually agreed?
That part was easy.
Even so...
So you heard what she used to be like?
She was always by herself.
Indeed, I did.
The topic came up this morning.
She said she definitely wouldn't let me see what she used to be like.
But you saw it anyway.
Well, Sis is still pretty adorable this way, right?
She's the complete opposite of how she usually is.
It's kinda refreshing-
No no no, we have to recover her memories.
It's not something you can rush.
No... Futaba seems to be having so much fun talking to Irifune-kun.
With this kind of stuff, the timing's important.
So we'll just be patient and look after her.  Together.
I-I want to talk to him, too!
... not really.
Huh?  Together?
Yep.  Together.
N-No, Futaba's even holding his hand...
We have a girl here who seems to be having a lot of fun fantasizing.
I-I see.
Now that you know Sis' true nature,
True nature?!
all that's left is to go to bed.
And... what's this?
Your family's off vacationing, right?
I just thought I'd make use of you, sex slave.
Don't use words like that, Futaba-chan!
H-Huh?
She was so embarrassed just a while ago...
N-No, Futaba, I really won't be able to s-sleep like this...
I fixed her up with some sleeping pills, so...
What's the meaning of this?
I'm pretty sure I gave her more than enough, too.
You shouldn't be saying that...
Now that Sis is fast asleep...
Sempai.
W-Wait, we can't.
Oh?  I could just do whatever I wanted to you when you were still a virgin...
Sempai...
Make love to me.
Futaba-chan...
You're thinking about it, right?
Stuff like "Futaba-chan's so perverted", and "I wonder if I should do it".
That's right.
I'm a horny girl who really wants you, Sempai.
It's getting hard...
It's been so long since I had your dick, Sempai...
It's so good...
It feels so much better than doing it by myself...
Your hand is so warm...
Your smell, too... it's been so long...
I'm getting really turned on...
Sempai, just lie still,
since I'm the one who pushed you down.
Your dick has grown up just a little bit.
It's so full of life, though it's not very faithful.
It's responsive as always, Sempai.
Now I want to tease you as much as I can.
Wait...
You like it kinky don't you, Sempai?
Amazing... your dick is really heating up sandwiched between my leg...
No... I thought that this would be strange,
but I'm getting really turned on...
Sempai, there's so much precum...
Are you going to come if I keep going like this?
It really thrills me to see this expression of yours, Sempai.
But, no.
It's not fair that only you get to feel good.
Make my pussy feel good, too.
Your lover's right beside you, and your dick is about to go inside her sister's pussy, Sempai.
You're making an improper face.
What would Sis think if she saw this face of yours?
You make that kind of face, even though you're going to come inside me soon...
Sempai, your dick's going all the way in!
I've put all kinds of things in, but your dick is the best!
All kinds of things...
I'll tell you next time!
It's been so long...
So hard...
No, you're gonna make me come!
Your dick feels so good, Sempai!
I-I'm coming!
It's been so long since I had your dick.  I'm gonna come!
So good, Sempai!
I'm... coming...
I'm coming!
You're shooting your semen inside me...
I'm taking in Sempai's semen inside my womb while Sis is still asleep...
It's still coming out...
There's so much of it...
Sempai.  I know I can't be Sis' replacement,
but until she recovers her memories... okay?
Ah, it's spilling out...
What a waste...
I wonder if the smell of this can recover her memories?
I suppose Sis was perverted to begin with, Sempai.
Sis, be sure to rest well, okay?
Avoid any strenuous exercise until your memories recover.
W-We'll be back as soon as we can.
Take care.
I'm so refreshed!
Since you shot so much of your come inside my pussy last night, I feel really great!
Futaba-chan!
When you can't help it anymore, you can use my pussy anytime you want, okay?
Even if it's class time.
Ah, wait!
It's like a dream...
I can't believe I'm able to be with Irifune-kun...
Before, all I did was look at him...
But all this about us being lovers is actually true...
We got into the same school and became lovers...
I changed that much?
I had no friends and was a coward, but we got together...
And we even went as far as having sex...
This is so embarrassing... is this really true?
It's like I became a completely different person...
But, this smell is real.
It's his smell.
The smell of Ushio-kun.
I must be weird.
Since this morning, it feels like I'm
surrounded by some kind of smell...
I keep smelling it, and it makes my
body feel hot, I see Ushio-kun's face...
I'm so ashamed!
It's as if Ushio-kun is making love to me...
No, I can't...
No...
I can't... do something this embarrassing...
But I can't stop!
No, no!
I'm doing something this embarrassing in Ushio-kun's room...
No, I'm gonna...
I'm...!
No way... I can't believe I did something so shameful...
Ushio-kun.
Miharu.
U-Uh, um, umm...
Umm...
Uh...
Um, Ushio-kun... uh, umm... I...
Miharu.
Ushio-kun?
Oh no, I'm kissing Ushio-kun!
I wonder... somehow, it feels like I've done this before...
It's nostalgic, it feels like something we've always done...
No, Ushio-kun, I'm, you know... yeah?
I don't mind because it's yours, Miharu.
No...
This is embarrassing, Ushio-kun...
This is my first time doing this...
I-I... umm...
So I've had sex with you before...
S-Sorry I rushed things.
M-Me too, I showed you such an embarrassing side of me.
But...
This position...
It's twitching...
It... doesn't hurt.
No...
It's rubbing me inside... it's nice!
Amazing...
So it feels this good?
No... I won't be able to hold back...
No...
It's good, it's so good!
Ushio-kun, amazing...
This is amazing!
It's rubbing against me all the way inside...
What should I do?  It feels so good!
You feel so good, Ushio-kun!
You're rubbing my insides...
You're making me go crazy!
No, Ushio-kun...
I'm, I'm...!
Wow...
I had no idea it would feel this good.
Ushio-kun...
Sempai, you're horrible!
I can't believe you went home during lunch break!
Sorry.
I only came back to grab something I forgot, but then I had something else to attend to...
Geez, at least let me know!
I was looking all over the place for you!
Y-Yeah.
Even someone as nice as me would get mad if you do something like that.
I-I'll go back to my room.
Did you have sex with Sis?
So you did.
Forcing her even though she's lost her memories...
I didn't force her!
Hmm?
W-What?
I'm thinking what I should do to punish you.
Punish me?!
I'll make it so that your dick won't want anyone but me.
Now, for a shower!
Would you like to shower with me, Sempai?
No.
Ushio-kun.
Miharu!
I thought you were asleep.
I was thinking of doing that,
but you were talking with Futaba...
So you're pretty friendly with Futaba.
Though, it shouldn't be surprising,
since she is your... lover's sister...
What am I saying...
Miharu...
Umm, I'm sorry I'm saying weird things.
Are you jealous?
Huh?  W-Why would I be jealous of my sister?
I'm sorry, forget I said anything-
Miharu.
You're really cute.
No...
Sempai...
He actually had sex with my sister even
though she's the way she was back then...
It's time to declare war, I think.
If we do it here, Futaba will-
You say that, but it turns you on, doesn't it Miharu?
No... she'll find out about this!
It's... going all the way in...
No... it's rubbing me so much...
It feels so good!
You feel really good, Ushio-kun...
Hey, don't do this with anyone else...
I'm sorry.
I'll definitely recover my memories...
So...
Do this only with me.  Only me!
Miharu!
No, if you do it this violently, I'll come!
I can feel you, Ushio-kun...
Make me feel really good!
Give it to me, Ushio-kun!
Inside me, lots of it!
So... good...
You're filling me up!
That's because I like Sempai just as much as Sis does.