Haru-kun, this is a little embarrassing.
Summary up to the previous episode
My maid, Akina, is attending to me today.
Y-Yes...
You're so hot down here, Haru-kun.
Akina, your fellatio is amazing.
It feels so damn good when you wrap your tongue around me.
Will you make me come, Akina?
Yes, use my mouth to feel even better.
I'm coming, Akina!
Akina...
N-No, not there...
Haru-kun, the way you use your hands is really perverted!
You're all swollen down here.
Since when did you become
such a perverted girl, Akina?
That's not true at all...
Akina, you're amazing.
You're dripping wet.
Hey, can you hear it?
N-No more!
Haru-kun, no more!
Put it in!
Here I go.
Akina, it's so hot inside you, it feels like I'm gonna melt...
I'm coming, Akina!
H-Haru-kun...
It's so deep...
Your big dick is so deep inside me...
Akina, one more time!
Y-You can't...
Didn't you just come inside me?
Haru-kun, you're coming inside too much...
It's too much!
Akina, I'm coming again!
Your come is overflowing out of me, Haru-kun!
Wow, it's nice and slippery from all the come...
Man, I'm gonna...!
I can't anymore, Haru-kun...
I'm coming too...
I'm coming again!
Akina... Akina!
Wow, I came so much...
Geez, Haru-kun. You try too hard...
Akina, it's fine-
Huh?
Haru-chan's dick is sturdy as ever.
I'm going after Natsumi.
N-Natsumi-san, did you forget about-
Oh no, Haru-chan.
That's a secret.
Haruomi, I'm going next.
Haru-kun is mine!
This is your punishment for not telling us.
No trying to steal him.
Geez...
Well then, Haru-chan.
Let the service begin.
♥
UFW
Presents
Kanojo
x
~Exciting life together with three sisters~
Episode 3 - The City: Festival, Bath, and Harem Paradise
Shiki-kun's meal is pretty grand.
Did something happen, Akina?
N-Nothing really...
T-Technically, Haru-kun and I are...
Did Haru-chan say so?
Um, not really...
Haruomi is just in heat.
Mind your words!
Haru-chan is everyone's Haru-chan!
Haru-chan is a boy after all, so as long as he's around such attractive girls...
I don't think anyone would blame him for being unfaithful.
L-Listen now, you two!
Natsumi-san!
I need to head out soon.
Wait, Haru-kun.
Here's your lunch.
Here.
Thanks.
Huh?
See you later.
Whoa, this isn't bad.
It's actually pretty good.
Yo, Haruomi.
Do you think MinMin Ice can win this year?
The exhibition fair.
The Tanabata district new ice cream products fair.
The summer festival starts next week, doesn't it?
On the last day, the big shots of the area get together.
You didn't know?
Your shop won three years in a row,
while our shop ended up third place last year.
Well, it's no surprise since MinMin Ice is delicious.
Let's not even talk about Golden Stone and 101, both of which are national brands.
There's no way Häge-Dazs could rival MinMin Ice's flavor.
I know, but I still want to fight this out!
Fight this out?
Yes.
This isn't a request. It's a proposal.
Contract
Excuse me.
Yes, welcome.
One of your famous ice creams, please.
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
I hereby confirm the above information to be true and correct.
Primary
Name:
Honnouji Tsukasa
This should do.
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
I hereby confirm the above information to be true and correct.
Primary
Name:
Honnouji Tsukasa
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
Primary
Name:
Honnouji Tsukasa
Secondary
Name:
Shiki Haruomi
All right, you're going to obey me if I win.
And you'll be making a MinMin Ice promotion video for free.
Also, hidden cameras and the like aren't allowed.
I know.
Oh, I forgot to say this, but since our shop recently joined the 101 group, it'll count as my victory if they win.
Akina, Akina, Princess Akina...
I'm home.
Seriously, Natsumi-san's ice cream can't possibly lose.
Oh well, if this can get the store more publicity and stop Honnouji's pranks,
I'll kill two birds with one stone.
Welcome home.
Did I surprise you?
But of course!
What's with her?
Natsumi-san.
I want to talk about something...
This isn't good enough after all.
I knew it.
This way...
At this rate...
This won't do.
Natsumi-san.
Ice Cream of
the Highest Quality
What's wrong, Shiki-kun?
Byakudan, can you read this language?
It's about herbs, right?
Herbs?
Yes, herbs.
It's used in the ice cream, right?
I see... ice cream, you say...
I can translate it for you if you'd like.
Really?
That'd help a lot.
All right, but let's go to the rooftop, okay?
Hey uh, Byakudan?
Stop...
Byakudan, w-wait!
Haru-chan, thanks for finding the notebook.
No need to thank me.
That notebook contains the recipe for the herb ice cream my father used to make.
I was really happy when you brought it over.
You really helped me again.
Don't mention it.
I'm glad I helped you out.
W-What?
Natsumi-san?
You're so cool, Haru-chan.
Oh...
I mean go, Natsumi-san! You're holding everyone up!
I need a special type of lavender that grows only on that island.
You seem to like that place a lot.
Yes, my father and I often used to take the
boat out there to pick them a long time ago.
We don't have the boat anymore though...
So in Akina-chan's words, "Haru-chan is a hard worker"!
Huh?
Oh, you two are late.
You're too early, Onee-chan.
Driving is cheating.
Huh? Where's Haru-kun?
He's being a hard worker.
Damn it, I'm making no progress at all!
I can't move another inch.
Haru-chan, you're amazing!
My pleasure.
Rest for a bit, Haru-kun.
I'll help out in your stead.
Haru-kun, good work.
Thanks.
Huh? Where's Mafuyu?
Mafuyu-chan is selling written oracles up there.
Ah, there you are.
Looks like you're actually working hard.
That wasn't nice.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Haruomi, draw a written oracle.
Oh, those.
All right.
Yet another predictable outcome...
Sign: Terrible Luck
Lemme try again.
Sign: Terrible Luck x2
Sign: Terrible Luck x3
Sign: Terrible Luck x4
That's because of your bad karma.
"Terrible luck" isn't always a bad thing, you know.
Is that supposed to make me feel better?
Sign: Terrible Luck
Who to wait for
The long-haired blond
who is already by your side.
You should choose what's small
over what's big.
Haru-chan, thanks for the lavender.
It's nothing if they'll make your ice cream taste better.
MinMin Ice will win again this year.
We won't lose to 101!
Oh, leave the cleaning up to me.
It's fine.
S-Sorry...
Haru-chan, thanks.
Ever since you moved in with us,
I feel everyone's gotten happier.
It's the other way around, Natsumi-san.
I'm the one who should be thanking you and the others.
Well, I suppose I do feel tired every now and then.
I like that side of you, Haru-chan.
N-Natsumi-san...
Hold still, okay?
Natsumi-san...
T-This is...
I'll help relieve your fatigue, so let it all out.
Natsumi-san, this feels really good...
Your nipple's all hard now.
Your dick is standing straight up too.
Natsumi-san...
What is it, Haru-chan?
Haru-chan...
Haru-chan, you really love breasts, don't you?
Yours are just too nice.
Enjoy them as much as you like.
Natsumi-san...
Your breasts feel really supple.
Really, Haru-chan...
Haru-chan, how's this?
I-It's so soft... It feels great.
Natsumi-san.
It's kinda naughty how your dick goes in and out.
Haru-chan, are you gonna come?
The way your breasts squeeze me is amazing...
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming, Natsumi-san!
Natsumi-san.
Haru-chan...
Your butt is so big and soft.
Haru-chan, don't do that...
It went right inside you, Natsumi-san.
Haru-chan, please...
Natsumi-san, I'm putting it in.
Amazing...
Your dick is so deep inside me...
Haru-chan, more, squeeze my breasts more!
Natsumi-san, it's so deep and hot inside you...
I feel really good too!
Haru-chan, deeper... deeper!
I'm coming, Natsumi-san.
Shoot your come inside me, Haru-chan...
Your thick come, lots of it!
It's good, but...
How is it?
It's good, but it's no different than usual.
Then that's good.
Huh? Why?
Three days until the exhibition fair, huh?
I'm starting to get nervous.
I'm home.
A-Am I dreaming?
Uh, y-you know...
I'm feeling kinda dizzy.
Mafuyu just came in, but now she won't talk.
What's with her?
Haruomi, are you turned on?
W-Well, what am I supposed to do?
I'm in the bath with a cute girl.
Am I cute?
Well...
Maybe if you were a bit more honest with yourself.
You're the only one who says that.
Mafuyu, I need to get out soon...
Haruomi, do you like girls with big breasts?
I don't mind either way.
Your thing moved again.
Y-Yeah, well...
You really are a beast.
Yeah.
Hold still.
M-Mafuyu, where did you learn this?
Your dick is getting bigger.
Face me, Haruomi.
My breasts can make you feel good too.
I don't think that'll work.
But then I can't beat the other two.
Here.
It feels great if you do this.
I-I know that!
Your dick is all big and red.
You feel so good that you want to come, right?
Yeah.
It feels great, Mafuyu.
Go ahead and come, Haruomi.
I'm gonna come.
I'm coming!
W-What, Haruomi?
Look how wet you are, Mafuyu.
Haruomi, n-no...
It feels... It feels so good!
You're about to come, right?
N-Not there!
Did that feel good?
Y-Yeah.
You're still all hard down there, Haruomi.
I'll let you put it in if that's what you want.
Let me?
Put it in!
Fill my pussy with your big dick!
How's this, Mafuyu?
Does it feel good?
It feels good...
Your dick is going all the way in and making me come...
Your dick is making me come!
I'm coming too!
I'm gonna come!
Come!
All of it...
Shoot all of your come inside me!
It's coming out...
So much... So much of your come, Haruomi...
Tomorrow is the day of the exhibition fair.
I don't think I was of any help in the end.
The rest is up to Natsumi-san.
You forgot something.
Fell in love?
As if!
Believe in Natsumi.
A gentle flavor.
It's very steady with flavor for its
own sake without being too fancy.
I apologize for what happened last time.
But you came again.
Ice Cream of
the Highest Quality
You really are just like him.
It was delicious. Thanks.
Thanks for visiting!
The 42nd
Tanabata
District
Ice Cream
Exhibition
Fair
Main
Conference
Room
The 42nd
Tanabata
District
Ice Cream
Exhibition
Fair
Main
Conference
Room
The 42nd
Tanabata
District
Ice Cream
Exhibition
Fair
Main
Conference
Room
Natsumi-san, how did it go?
Not so well!
101 won first prize.
O-Oh no...
Great news, Onee-chan!
Our shop won!
It seems that 101 will leave Tanabata district tomorrow for some reason,
so they lost the right to be in the fair.
Didn't this man use to work at Dad's place?
Now that you mention it, I think I've seen him before.
It's definitely him.
Ooh, hello.
Why are the two of you here?
We've come to take Shiki-kun to extra lessons.
Extra lessons?
You're an enemy.
That's your introduction?
That's what my instinct is telling me.
Look how popular you are, Haru-chan.
Akina, Natsumi, I declare a temporary truce.
Truce?
It doesn't look like my problems are going away anytime soon.
Huh? Shiki-kun?!
Haruomi ran away.
Hey, Haru-kun!
UFW Staff
Translator: Fractor_Draconis
Timer: RainbowTheMadness
Typesetter: Bob64
Encoder: ar
TLC/Editor/QC: Raze