"Unlocker: Please select a Keyhole within the next 30 seconds."
I had to pick someone. Otherwise everyone would die.
Just like Class Rep did.
What should I do?
Who should I choose?
"Rika Makiba."
"Huh? Me...?"
"No! I don't want to do this!"
"Even if it's Senpai..."
"This is... This is..."
"This is still my first time!"
"Natsuki Aoi."
"I-I'm fine."
"I couldn't let the others take part in this."
"This is my duty as a teacher."
"Plus, you're a victim as well."
"Am I wrong, Takatou-kun?"
"...Right."
"Senpai is kind, so..."
"You won't do anything mean to me, right?"
"You won't pick me, right?"
"I trust you, Senpai!"
Makiba didn't seem to realize what her words meant.
She didn't seem to realize that she was saying to rape someone else besides her.
"No... Don't..."
"Save me!"
"I'm... This is..."
"Going to kill me...!"
"I'll... do anything else besides this!"
"So please..."
Did she really expect someone to save her at that point?
I...
"S-Senpai... Please... Don't!"
I want to watch you struggle and suffer submerged underwater!
Note: ...Rough
Ejaculation count: ...Once
Keyhole: ...Vagina
"N-No!"
"M-My... virginity!"
"You're awful!"
So she really was a virgin!
"Can't breathe!"
"I'm... I'm gonna die!"
"You're not going to die from this."
"It... It hurts!"
"Take it out!"
"By 'it' you mean my dick, Makiba."
"My dick is inside of your pussy."
"Take your dick out already!"
"I-It hurts!"
"It hurts down there... it's going to break!"
"I'm gonna drow--"
"Don't grind around inside of me...!"
Ahh, I couldn't take it...
Raping a girl felt great.
Even a small girl like Makiba had a vagina of her own that was designed to take a male's dick.
"Your dick... is getting bigger!"
"My pussy... is gonna break if it gets any bigger!"
"It got bigger? That's because I'm about to cum inside of you!"
"No!"
"I might get pregnant... if you cum inside!"
"You might. But I'm still gonna cum. I'm gonna shoot my load inside of you."
"Don't!"
"Don't cum! I'll get pregnant!"
"We still haven't cleared the unlocking conditions."
Note: ...Rough
Ejaculation count: ...Once
Keyhole: ...Vagina
Note 2: ...Keep her head underwater after beginning to thrust and until ejaculation.
"Gonna cum!"
"You're cumming inside!"
"Your semen's inside of me!"
"No! Stop!"
"Cumming inside of me..."
"I-It's so hot!"
"I'm gonna get pregnant!"
"Verdict: clear."
"Makiba..."
"Why...?"
"Why did you pick me?"
"Please... if you like me even just a little bit..."
"Don't do anything mean to me."
"I can't say that I like you like that."
"If you said that you liked me..."
"I would accept anything you do to me."
"What? You'll just act like those horrible things I did to you don't matter because we both like each other?!"
"I don't know! I don't get complicated stuff like that!"
"I... don't want to think... that you're a bad person..."
"Interval will now begin."
"I'm glad your wish was fulfilled."
"I bet you've wanted to do that for a long time."
"And... I'm sure you want to do even more cruel things."
"So what?"
"Seems like things will get even more entertaining as the game progresses."
"Who knew we'd have a beast participating in this terrifying game...?"
"I wonder what the others would think of this?"
"Was it fun? I'm sure it was."
"I had fun too."
"So I'll stay quiet for now."
"In exchange..."
"I'm not going to be your slave."
"I'll choose whoever I want to next."
"Turn 2."
"Assignment phase."
"Unlocker: Please select a Keyhole within the next 30 seconds."
I'll choose who I want to violate of my own free will.
In order to put an end to this game.
What should I do?
Who should I choose?
"Are you listening to me, Takatou-kun?"
"Do you sweat often, Sensei?"
"I caught a whiff of the moist scent of your panties the moment I ripped your stockings apart"
"Don't..."
"Don't smell it..."
"My student's dick... is inside of my pussy...!"
"P-Please! I'm not wet yet!"
"So be a little more gentle!"
"So you're not a virgin."
"Who was it? Who was your first?"
"No! Don't ask me that!"
"You have inverted nipples, huh. I'm surprised."
I guess she had a complex about that.
"Ow!"
"Y-You're gonna tear my breasts off..."
"If you grip them that hard!"
"Sensei! I'm gonna cum!"
"D-Don't! Don't do it!"
"Your dick... Your dick's getting bigger..."
"You're gonna cum! You're gonna ejaculate inside of me!"
"You're gonna shoot your thick load..."
"While crushing my tits with your hands!"
"You're cumming!"
"Your hot seed's shooting inside my womb and pussy!"
"You came inside of me..."
"Your semen's seeping into my walls..."
Cum inside and tease her nipples
while she's restrained.
...Twice.
"It's not over yet, Sensei."
"You're..."
"Gonna cum one more time, huh..."
"H-Hog tied like this... My udders swaying about..."
"Even though I don't want you to see me like this..."
"But I still want to see you like that."
"You're being too rough!"
"My pussy's gonna break!"
More... I wanted more...
I wanted to see her in agony even more!
"D-Don't do that!"
"You're violating my inverted nipples..."
"W-With your thumbs!"
"I'm gonna cum, Sensei!"
"I'm gonna cum inside of your womb!"
"Your dick's getting bigger!"
"You're gonna cum! Gonna cum inside again!"
"Gonna cum! Cum inside!"
"My teacher womb! Is turning into my student's semen storage bank!"
"Even my ovaries are drenched with your semen!"
"Your semen's so hot! You're gonna burn my tits!"
"It's pouring into my inverted nipples!"
"My student's dick milk..."
"Completely coated my womb and boobs..."
"Completely violated them..."
"What should I do...?"
"Verdict: clear."
"Turn 3."
"Please assign a Keyhole."
"Rika Makiba."
"Why's it so hot?"
"Plus it's so ugly."
"It's gross..."
"You're gonna jerk me off, Makiba."
"But I dunno how to."
"I'll teach you."
"Say the following while you do it."
"I have to say that?!"
"It's up to you. We'll die if you don't, though."
"No! I don't wanna die!"
"I don't want to but... I can do it."
"Grip your penis... Stroke the underside with my fingers..."
"It's getting wet..."
"This is pre-cum..."
"It smells so much."
"It's so stringy... It's gross."
"My hand's all sticky..."
"The smell's seeping into my hand..."
"Now say it."
"I'm so happy... being able to service your dick..."
"No! It's going to soak into my skin!"
"It's all over my swimsuit and skin..."
"I'll always smell like semen like this..."
"We're not done yet."
Ejaculation count: ...Twice.
"There's one more thing left to do."
"Your dick's going inside!"
"It's deforming my womb!"
"My... My precious baby room... is going to be destroyed!"
"Don't cum... I don't want your semen!"
"I don't want your dick milk!"
"It's so hot..."
"I don't like being cummed inside!"
"Don't dirty my womb anymore!"
"I hate you, Senpai..."
"Verdict: clear."
I don't get it.
I don't get it at all.
Why do you do such mean things to be and then be so kind to me after?
I hate you so much, but...
I was determined to hate you, but...
I never wanted to do anything on my own...
Always laughing and crying and having others help me...
So I wouldn't have to think for myself...
But he wouldn't allow that.
Senpai's the only one who wouldn't put up with that.
"Turn 4."
"Please assign a Keyhole."
"Natsuki Aoi."
Muscle relaxant
"Please don't look, Takatou-kun."
Semen milk
"Let me rest for a bit more."
"I'm sorry."
"What're you apologizing for?"
"Well, if I look like I'm not in good health..."
"I'd be burdening the others and you, too."
Semen milk
With laxative
"P-Please let me use the bathroom."
"Babies don't talk."
"Don't worry. You're just doing what you have to."
"You're doing your best to save everyone."
"Am I wrong?"
"You're..."
"You're too kind, Sensei."
"That doesn't change the fact that I've done all these terrible things to you."
"Why not get mad at me?"
"How... can you still be so kind to me?"
"This is nothing."
"Not only am I older than you, but I'm also your teacher."
"That's why I want to protect everyone. Especially you."
"I'm not worthy of th--"
"That's why I can't show favoritism, but..."
"I guess I am a girl after all."
"Don't worry. You can rely on me as much as you want."
"I want to eventually rid you of any of your worries."
"Sensei."
"Will you..."
"Forgive me someday?"
"Interval will now begin."
"There's a secret underground path under here."
"Can we get outta here from there?!"
"L-Let's go!"
"Right. We don't have much time."
"I'll stay behind."
"Huh?"
"I feel like I was here before a long time ago."
"I want to reclaim my past and find my true self."
"O-Ow! My leg!"
"I'll draw their attention! You guys escape!"
"Kanae! Wait! Don't do anything stupi--"
"She'll be fine. Let's go."
"Is this the exit?"
"We can't do it! We can't escape!"
"I'm not going to let them catch us and make this a game over."
"We can still turn back!"
"Don't move!"
"Capture them!"
"I won't let you get in our way."
"I knew it..."
"You were with the game master's side all along."
"Sensei? What's going...?"
"I've been investigating you ever since I accepted this mission."
"You're the one controlling these collars too, aren't you?"
"You can't be serious..."
"Don't think that you can cut off our consciousness."
"These are your brain waves, aren't they, Nemu Manaka-san?"
Just how prepared was she?
She had cars and planes prepared for us.
And then we were here before I even knew it.
"Hokari-san and Byakuya-san are both safe."
"We should just relax until things are taken care of."
"What happened to Nemu?"
"I thought you'd ask me that."
"She'll be tough to deal with, but..."
"We should at least have her reflect on what she's done."
Sensei never told me anything else besides that. She always gave me the slip.
She never even told me just who exactly she was.
"This is your punishment for having your way with me."
"You better prepare yourself."
"I can't live without you, Senpai."
"You better take responsibility for that."
"Your dick's so big..."
"You're gonna burn my throat with it."
"This is the dick that stole my virginity..."
"Am I..."
"Doing a good job?"
"You're filling my mouth with so much pre-cum."
"Cum inside of my mouth!"
"Shoot your load in my mouth!"
"Cum! Cum in my mouth!"
"I can do things on my own."
"I even swallowed all of your dick milk."
"Look at your hard dick..."
"Cumming so quickly because of my soft tits."
"I'm not letting you go just yet."
"Wow... It's like I've got a burning rod between my tits."
"More... I need more..."
"Make my slippery tits... drink more of your cum."
"Impregnate my tits with that thick cum of yours."
"Cum for me... Cum for me!"
"Shoot your dick milk out!"
"Y-You're poking my womb with your dick!"
"It's so deep... It's so deep inside of me..."
"You're stretching out my pussy with your dick!"
"Your rough dick's amazing!"
"My pussy feels so good from my student's thick cock!"
"You're grinding around inside my pussy!"
"My orgasmic pussy is squeezing your dick!"
"Please give me your cum!"
"I can tell you're about to cum!"
"It's okay. Cum inside!"
"Shoot your semen out from that ferocious dick of yours!"
"Please cum inside!"
"I'll squeeze out all of your burning hot cum!"
"I'm gonna cum! Gonna cum!"
"Cum inside of my climaxing pussy!"
"My womb drank all of your delicious semen."
"I've never cum this much before."
"My insides are filled with your hot cum."
I was a little worried about what would happen, but...
I was sure things would work out.
So long as I was with them.