They're really strict with the rules!
Didn't they say that the people from the swimming club weren't here?
Wait, are you really gonna take everything off?
You shouldn't wear anything while taking a shower.
The water is going to be full soon.
They're about to come back!
They'll see you if you don't lower your head.
But... I'm already...
Pay attention and fuck me harder...
What if some boys come-
Hold it just a little longer.
I really can't...
This is your punishment.
Don't worry...
I'll apologize...
If you're going to pretend to be an honor student, you should know your place.
I'm not really...
Hajime-chan...
Geez, you're always so crazy...
A beautiful girl getting soaked is a superb sight!
Hajime-chan, you old man!
You're not allowed to develop it!
It already went into the film inside my heart.
Dirty old man.
It's because you're always so careless.
I think you should try and be more careful from time to time.
You're one annoying girl.
Hey, what was that?
It seems like the boys are here!
No way!
Isn't today a day off?
My panties aren't here!
Neither are mine!
I'm sorry for being bad...
I'm sorry for being a bad girl...
But...
It was all your fault...
You were comparing us.
I can't win when you compare me with Asa-chan...
You win at being naughty.
If you keep thrusting like that,
my body will melt and I'll get even more naughty...
She fell asleep.
I see why... This feels really good.
Nat-chan, how about you?
Hey, let me pretend to be the little sister...
Asa-chan will be my older sister and I'll be her younger sister.
You'll be my sister's boyfriend.
My sister won't wake up anytime soon.
Onii-chan, don't you want to do anything naughty?
No...
Asa-
No, your sister will wake up.
Why are you saying no?
Is it because you like my sister?
Yeah...
Liar.
If you really liked her, you wouldn't be this...
...hard.
Bad people need to be punished.
The one who likes my sister...
...is like this now.
I really like making things grow...
...because I'm in the gardening club.
You're dirty.
My sister is right next to us...
But I don't care.
You traitor...
Wait, Hajime-chan!
It's Onii-chan, isn't it?
So suddenly...
You're so sneaky...
I'm going to tell my sister...
She's going to hear us!
My sister is going to hear us!
Then the three of us can do it, that way it'll be fair.
I don't want all three of us to do it...
You can't just watch.
Just watching is...
If you go that fast...
No!
I'm going to melt if you go that fast...
My pussy is shaking in front of my sister... I'm even drooling...
I don't want to be watched.
You're still imagining?
Stop it, Onii-chan...
It's embarrassing...
Feeling like this?
Onii-chan, stop it...
I can't hold it any longer...
No...
I'm going to come...
I'm coming...
I'm sorry that I'm coming with the person my sister likes...
The person that my sister likes is thrusting deep inside me...
It feels so good...
Hot stuff is coming from inside of me...
I'm sorry for being a naughty girl.
I can't hold it any longer...
I'm coming again...
Coming twice in one day...
Hajime is an idiot and unfaithful pervert!
It's not like I don't want you.
How about having a threesome with me?
He's the worst!
Note:
Go the extra mile - the cleaning crew
He's really the worst for treating me like a kid!
Eh?
I'd kill myself if someone saw me.
He's not someone who would do anyone he gets, right?
It seems like there are no swimming club members.
If I were you, I'd forgive him.
It'd be great if you could turn this into a chance.
Temptation is scary!
What should I do?
Woman are different from men; they can't do it every day.
But I really want him all to myself.
Hey! Turn around!
Hey, we can't do this all of a sudden!
Stop it!
Say something...
Just sticking it inside me without saying anything...
You're just like an animal!
But it's better than usual.
Idiot!
It's because you're so hard!
I don't often see you this hard, so I want to take all of you inside me...
At this moment, I have him all to myself.
No!
We're going to be seen...
I don't like anyone but you looking at me...
I feel proud.
There was someone!
We're really going to be seen!
No, I only want you to see!
No, I'm coming...
I'm going to come...
I'm coming...
So good...
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Is it all right for summer to end like this?
It's all right; we still have a long night.
I'll do daytime visits instead of night time visits just for you.
Hajime, you...
Note:
To Asa-chan, I'm having a farewell party, so I'll be out late tonight, Mom.
You're careless.
Remember to lock the door when you're by yourself.
No, you lack common sense...
...for letting yourself in.
Yes, tonight, I'm a pervert.
No, not like that...
No...
No, you're too sly...
No, you really can't!
I get it, that's why I came over.
No... No...
It's a dangerous time to do it, right?
What are you talking about?
You can't come today...
No...
I told you, you can't do it today...
Coming in so suddenly, your thing is filling my insides...
It's really full...
I won't be able to leave if I get pregnant, idiot.
If we do it every day and we get pregnant, what'll we do?
I'll do my best as a dad.
I'll quit school and find two or three jobs.
That's why you're an idiot!
I don't want to leave you.
I know your secret.
You're leaving after the summer, right?
Did Nat-chan tell you?
It's a guy's intuition.
Actually, I've been paying a lot of attention to the two of you.
But I don't want a baby.
I don't want you to hold me up because of that reason.
Even if I don't have one, I'd still be a troublesome woman.
I would hog you all to myself.
Also, I would be arguing with Nat-chan all the time.
It's good competition for you two.
Both of you became really naughty during the summer.
Don't compare us!
You're cheap!
I don't want to lose.
No, I won't lose to anyone.
I thought you didn't want it today.
Idiot, you're the one who forced yourself in...
You're really cheap!
I can't hold it anymore!
I want to be your burden!
I want to belong to you!
I can't hold it...
I'm coming...
I'm going to come!
You're about to come too, right?
Your penis got really hard...
It was shaking like it was going to ejaculate...
A lot of hot stuff came out...
I might have your baby now...
Nat-chan would be mad if she found out I got it first.
I see, you found out, right?
You're so slow with the important things...
I was thinking were you hiding a tail because you were being so bad.
Geez...
Do you want to find out?
No...
It's embarrassing if you do that so suddenly...
You're so good...
Geez, just the two of you by yourselves...
Because it's the last night...
Let's do it together, okay?
Hajime...
The festival ended...
Our summer ended like this.
Leaving behind a secret between the three of us.
I'm not running away from home, I'm independent now.
Me too.
I've become unbeatably mature, haven't I?
We're back!