Our Swimming Club captain.
Minagawa-senpai.
Her personality is a tomboy.
Her figure is good, too.
But most importantly!
Even the tournament swimsuit she's wearing can't hide
that huge rack!
Waku-subs http://wakusubs.wordpress.com
Soushisouai Note: The Animation Breasts 02: Boobs! Boobs! Boobs!
Shit.
It's dark already.
Geez, why didn't that bastard wake me up?
He's so cold...
I don't have the key, so it can't be helped.
Besides, there's nothing valuable inside.
C-Captain?
U-Um, could you get the towel for me?
Takase.
Warm Poolside
I was dead sure everybody had gone home.
The walls surrounding are tall.
I won't have to worry about being seen at night.
So I come here to swim alone at times.
S-Skinny dipping?
My breasts hurts,
wearing the tournament swimsuit.
After I tried taking it off
I felt exhilarated from the awesome sense of liberation.
From then on,
I got hooked...
W-Well...
I won't tell anyone.
So don't worry.
Captain?
Arigatou.
I'm sure if it's you, Takase, you'd keep it a secret.
But I'm still slightly worried.
So...
Can I add another layer of insurance?
I don't have any experience.
Please don't be too rough on me.
C-Captain.
I've also not done it before.
Really?
This is your vagina, Captain.
It's slightly getting wet.
It's always like that when I swim naked.
Captain, something sticky is flowing out.
It's a bit sour.
Don't push your tongue so far in.
The hymen will break.
Sorry, I got too excited.
Seriously, we're gonna do it next, right?
It's my first time..
I want it to be the penis and not the tongue to take my virginity.
Captain.
Lick this part now.
Lick my clitoris.
I'm pretty weak down here, I'll probably climax in no time.
That's too hard, Takase!
Look! I'm going to cum.
I'm coming...
The penis is actually really ugly.
Captain, are you really OK?
Don't tell me you hate it?
Girls like me without any femininity .
That's not true.
Geez! You're really hard to get.
Do you want it or not?
I want!
That's it.
I've also done my own thinking.
It hurts.
It... h-h-h-hurts!
Will it start to feel good like this?
Are you all right, captain?
Maybe we should..
I hate doing things half-assed on the first time.
All right, I'm going to try moving.
It's rubbing.
How's it, Takase?
Me going in and out.
You seem to be in a whole lot of pain.
Because it really hurts.
I feel pain in surges if I don't move.
Help me out here, Takase.
Y-Yes!
It's moving.
It's less taxing on me this way.
Your breasts are jiggling a lot, captain.
Don't keep staring, it's embarrassing!
I didn't know breasts are actually so soft.
Captain!
I only find them really heavy like this.
My shoulders ache too.
They get in the way when I swim.
People tend to ogle at them.
So you actually noticed?
Of course!
Captain, I'm already...
It's hot!!!!
It's flowing inside of me.
It's.. still coming in.
Captain, I've a request.
What is it, Takase?
Can you let down your hair?
You want to see?
I've only seen you with your hand tied.
Because the hair is heavy, it's troublesome.
Well, it's not like I can't.
Suddenly being requested upon,
I feel embarrassed all of a sudden.
Just... like that.
Captain!
You're going again just like that, Takase?
My vagina still hurts.
Sorry, but Minagawa captain is way too cute.
I can't stop myself.
Don't sugar coat your words.
It's true!
It feels great, this!
It's totally different from when I do it myself.
You do it yourself too, captain?
I do. I masturbate everyday!
Because it's a good feeling.
But it feels even more great doing it with someone else like this.
Captain, if you're so rough...
I'll!
Takase, my vagina is feeling weird.
It obviously hurts but yet I feel great.
Captain!
It's coming in again, the hot stuff!
It's all accumulated in my womb.
Your vagina is squirming and sucking me.
What are you saying? It's you who came all over me.
My vagina responded to that.
This is amazing.
I didn't think sex would feel so good.
Captain, does it still hurt?
A bit, but I'm getting used to it.
My hymen might already be broken perhaps from the vigorous actions of swimming.
Takase, you're really energetic!
Your vagina feels damn good, I can't stop myself.
So it's my fault?
That's right, because you're too cute!
Thank you, Takase.
No one has ever said that to me.
That's why I'm become so awkward due to my shyness.
Takase, this is my first kiss.
I'm going to be very honest here, I can't help it.
You're just too adorable.
Takase, I didn't expect you to be so persistent.
Captain, your vagina is contracting.
Is it all right if I just cum inside like this?
I got it. Just do as you pleased, Takase.
You can go all out.
Captain!
What's this!? Something's coming!
Captain! Captain!
Captain, are you all right?
Rather than painful, I'd say I can't calm down.
There's this feeling like there's something still down there.
I'm sorry.
No need to apologise.
What's wrong?
The stuff you came just now is flowing out.
Look, it's all sticky.
I didn't know it'd actually flow out.
Captain! Why aren't you wearing your underwear?
Cover it up!
Don't worry. I live around here.
I feel at ease this way.
This isn't a matter of feeling more at ease.
What are you doing, Akihiko-kun! Don't get in the way!
My bad.
Can't be helped. He's still new at this.
All right~ Eat this, you piece of shit!
OK! With that, I'm complete.
Now what? Are we having another shot?
Sorry, I need to be going soon.
Madoka-senpai! You're leaving already?
I've an appointment.
I leave you to Natsumi and Yurie.
Be sure to properly level up!
S-Sure.
Well then, I'll see you again at club tomorrow.
Your name is... Akihiko-kun, right?
Yes.
Where are we going to hunt next?
Unfortunately...
Madoka is most likely going on a date later.
She recently got hitched.
You didn't know, right?
Could it be you're playing this game
just so you can get closer to Madoka-chan?
Serious?
I see! You should have fun at a time like this.
Go all out and have fun.
Right?
Hunting-type Girls.
Natsumi is as impatient as ever.
Kuramochi-san?
Sorry, I couldn't resist it any longer.
All right! Both of you, look over here!
Boobs, jiggling.
Hey... Nakatsu-san!
Yurie-chan, you're so daring!
Akihiko-kun.
So.. soft.
How does it feel? This is a girl's breasts.
Isn't today this first time we've met?
Why would you let me go to such an extent?
If it's out of sympathy..
I really hate that.
I like the fact that you've backbone.
It's true I do pity you to some extent.
But I really think you're cute.
Even so, do you hate it?
No...
It's pretty well taken.
Aki, you're quite the popular guy, aren't you?
Aki?
You can call our first names directly if you want.
What now?
Are we still going somewhere?
Of course!
We promised to have fun all out.
Oh, why don't you all come to my mansion.
There's no one at home today.
W-Wait, what are you doing?
Don't worry! My bath is huge.
The three of us can go in together.
That's not the problem here...
I really love this smell.
My brain is nearly hooked to it.
What's this? Isn't it all set and ready to go?
Here I go!
What's this?
Akihiko-kun, does it feel good?
How does it compare to doing it yourself?
Worlds apart.
This constant feel of being sucked.
Don't hold it in.
You can cum anytime you want.
Don't do that!
Yuri-chan is such a meanie.
How can you do this to a cherryboy?
What's going on here?
Amazing! Incredible!
Are you kidding me?
It's dirty down there, Natsumi-san!
No, it's not. Don't worry about it.
We're getting inside the bath anyway.
Akihiko-kun, your asshole is rather tight.
My finger is almost gonna break.
You came... so much.
Yuri-chan, that's sly!
I wanna drink, too!
If you want to drink
You've to drink it the first time it comes out.
It's still a bit of a squeeze with three people.
I know right...?
But it's fun bathing together.
I know.. right?
Yuri-chan, it's my turn next.
Fine with you?
Can't be helped.
This is what's the deal.
Akihiko-kun.
Time to graduate from a cherryboy.
That's...
You at least must have anticipated
something like that would happen, right?
That's not wrong to say.
Are you still thinking about Madoka-chan?
It's not really that...
No fret.
I won't allow you time to even fret.
Come on, here.
Akihiko-kun.
It's best you properly enjoy this moment.
I don't have so much in me.
Look. Get it now?
It's slowly entering.
It's totally inside now.
Congrats! Akihiko-kun.
Natsumi-san, you shouldn't!
My insides.
How does it feel? Tell me!
It's hot. My glans seem to be tipping onto something.
That's my uterus.
All right. I'm going to move more and more.
Wait... Yurie-san.
Stop! Don't do that!
I can. You already graduated from virginity with good grades.
I'm serious here, don't!
Incredible! Your penis is throbbing.
It's all right. You can cum inside.
Akihiko-kun, you came a mountain.
Sorry, I came too fast.
Don't apologize.
Girls don't care about that.
Besides, how does it feel?
Your first girl.
It's only a moment, I can't really recall clearly.
I see.
I, for one, clearly felt your penis. Akihiko-kun.
I took your cherry, thanks a lot.
No prob..
OK now! Stop flirting!
Akihiko-kun, you still have what it takes, right?
B-But...
Look. It's already sooo wet.
You can also cum inside me.
Hurry up.
Yurie-san!
Yes, right there.
All at one go, OK.
I like the feel of being penetrated suddenly at once.
Here I come!
It's so tight!
Yuri-chan is such a whore.
Girls shouldn't be making sounds like that.
What are you saying? You're even more of a slut.
That's so not true.
I don't make such noises.
But this dick is..
Really out of this world.
It's tipping my womb.
Yurie-san, your vagina too!
It's cramping down on me.
It's fizzling at the depths.
Hey, Akihiko-kun. I'll let you in on something.
Do it like this and that.
That's not really nice.
It has to be done by a guy.
I'm counting on you.
What?
It contracted a notch.
Told you!
She's horny.
Come on, now. Give her a few more spanks.
Why...
No...
I...
Being spanked...
My ass is on fire.
No.
Sorry.
Please let me off.
I'm... I'm gonna...
Are you all right? Your butt cheeks are cherry now.
No fret.
Does she look like she hates it?
I think I'm about to cum again.
It's fine.
Take it down at one go.
Yuri-chan.
He's gonna give you a final shot!
Semen, is it coming soon?
No!
If it comes in now...
NOO~!
Yuri-chan.
You're climaxed out.
I'm jealous.
How are you feeling?
The feeling of orgasm by a cherryboy.
The best!
Seriously.
You're giving him the chance to see the embarrassing side of me.
It's better, right?
Must have felt really good.
Um..
Natsumi-san, your nipples are...
Yup. They are inverted.
Stop staring.
Akihiko-kun should do something about it.
It'll pop back out.
Do something about it?
That's right. Suck it more.
It's erecting! It's coming out!
My inverted nipples!
They hard and erected!
She came! She came!
Akihiko--kun.
That was so not enough.
Again. Let's do it again.
I want it so bad.
I beg you, stick it in!
Hurry! Hurry! Faster!
Natsumi-san?
Have mercy!
So sorry, Akihiko-kun.
Please accede her request.
Otherwise, she'll go on like a machine gun.
Fantastic! Brilliant! Amazing!
Told you. It's like I've said.
This is her slut call.
Totally weird, ain't it?
It's squishy, and stirring. I like it.
My cunt is vibrating.
More squishing please!
Penis! Penis! Penis!
I'm quite sure she won't recall it later.
I feel like filming this down for her.
My tits! Do my tits!
Natsumi's slutty set of rack.
Bully them more!
Natsumi-san!
Yes, that's the way! Just like this!
Twist my nipples.
I'm hooked on the feeling.
More! I want more! Tease me!
Don't being so spoiled!
This is my first time.
Very soon, it's gonna cum!
I'm coming! I'm cuming! I'm going!
But you're stabbing me so hard.
It's squeezing me dry!
Your pee is all over there place.
But it's my first place seeing her so intense like this.
All credit goes to you, Akihiko-kun.
Have more faith in yourself.
That's not it..
Amazing.
It feels damn awesome.
I'm surprised to hear.
To think you even preyed on younger ones.
One, two.
A~KI~!
I regret to say.
He's got to be doing lots of running from now on.
You won't be looking forward to that place today.
It's fine. I'm cool.
It gets harder when you're tired.
As long as it stands, it's all good to go.
I'm so excited.
As many times as you want it~