Are you concentrating properly?
Of course!
This fellow doesn't seem to agree.
K-Kiriha!
Does a maid's feet feel so good?
If you beg this maid with a devilish figure like that of a goddess
to gently discipline you
I might even allow you to stick it in.
Waku-subs http://wakusubs.wordpress.com
Tsun Tsun Maid wa Ero Ero Desu
Vol. 02
A Maid's Discipline Begins From the Ass
Chapter 1: Ero Ero at the bath.
Master washes maid's body.
Thank you, god.
I don't get you.
You've already touched and licked it countless of times.
Yet, you'd still get horny over this getup.
Because the girl I love is wearing it.
You're way too timid if that's all you're doing.
I can't hear you.
T-That's!
Hey! Are you bullying me or are you asking questions?
I love you, Kiriha! I want us to be together from now on.
That's sly.
It tickles... master. Please stop!
Answer me, quick! By your master's orders.
You moron! I don't want to say it out of momentary pleasure.
Like I said, please stop. Master.
Your answer?
I like it.
Face me while you answer.
My face during a confession.
As if I'll let you see it!
I love you, too. Eishun.
Really?
You want me to ditch you?
Sorry, please don't.
Getting right down violating me after the confession.
Purely a beast.
Before that,
Swear that "I'm a failure in life. Please let me become Kiriha-sama's slave!"
I'm a failure in life.
You haven't swore about the slave part!
I'll still stick by your side even if you protest.
It's in!
To think he's using such a quality formula to propose.
My womb is actually accepting the proposal on its own!
I love you, Kiriha!
Wait! Again?
The spot it's rubbing is different from the usual.
I can't, give me a break.
Don't run away.
I'm going to climax you like this, Kiriha.
Please do.
You're a maid that belongs to me.
I'm going to leave my mark on your lewd body.
My asshole will become loose.
Stop it! I'm going to be ruined.
I'm coming! Because... master came.
Anal and vagina together...
I'm coming!
No way! You still had more?
Again!
Simultaneous climaxes.
Isn't it about time we get out?
It's not over yet.
It's still gonna flow out no matter how much you wash it.
Your method of washing is too weak.
I won't allow someone I love to be weak.
I adore you, Eishun.
I won't let go of you, ever.
Chapter 2: Ero Ero during punishment
To think you'd actually put an adorable maid on leash.
What a seductive butt.
My shameless cunt is totally exposed.
Playing rough, are you?
It's hard to swallow, but you're doing well.
Beg me! You slutty maid.
Are you happy?!
This is punishment!
I'm sorry, Master.
You better reflect on yourself!
Please discipline this lewd maid who's feeling horny from spanking more.
Don't. Please, not my asshole.
You're horny from the punishment?
You maid of bitch.
He's encircling my weak point around the asshole.
Master!
I'm gonna give this lewd maid some punishment!
Your penis is entering my ass, my asshole!
Please don't move! Master!
What's this?
From the anal all the way tipping the womb. Don't do that!
No, no! My asshole is going to climax from the dick.
It's a great feeling, Master!
My ass is going to cum!
The depths of my insides seems to be on the verge of melting!
The you right now...
Is the cutest!
He's inspecting my after climax expression. What a lowlife.
How long are you going to stare?
Until you start begging me.
Down there... a bit more, please.
Do you desire to be violated by this penis?
Please punish me, Master!
Properly discipline my vagina!
Your dick is just so amazing!
It's overflowing from the inside.
Don't kiss me!
Master!
Don't hide!
No, don't!
Not my armpits!
I love you, I really love you!
Master!
I love you too!
Stop teasing my climaxing vagina.
I won't be able to stop cumming.
It's here! I'm coming again!
That's such a bastard, Master.
But I llike it.
I love you, Master!
Please spare me from there.
No, stop! Not like that!
I want to cum inside, Kiriha.
Please plant your seed in me.
Please make my masochistic cunt...
pregnant.
Kiriha!
Your internal ejaculation.
Made me cum!
Being a maid is great.
Please punish me even further.
Master.
Eishun! I bought some souvenirs back!
G-Good morning, Mom!
I know you're energetic early in the morning.
But you should put something on, quick. You'll catch a cold.
So noisy in the morning.
Oh, Kiriha-chan?
Good morning, Auntie.
Kiriha-chan, I'm leaving this moron to you.
You can count on me.
I'll make sure to properly educate him.
What should I do?
Doesn't it work well if auntie approves of it?
Love you, Eishun.
Mutual love?
In the case, she might start being more lovestruck around me.
Well, then. It's punishment time.
I'm kind enough not to confiscate all your assets.
But I'm still going to let you pick one.
Give thanks to this benevolent being.
A. Rob a young girl's chastity, trample over her mind and body, dispose her like a rag.
B.You become the maid, I become the master.
Should I say she's honest, or she's just rebellious.
C. Take responsibility. Hire me as your only maid for life.
I understand, Master.
Thanks, Shun.
This punishment game won't end until either party gives up.
I won't give in so easily.
Sure seems that way, Master.
END