It's time to wake up, Master.
Good morning, Master.
Morning.
That outfit is...
Is it to your liking?
Yeah, especially the boobs region.
Haha, boobies!
Master.
Soft and fluffy breasts.
It tickles.
You're finally awake. Seriously, you're a hell of a scum and slow master.
What are you doing at this hour, Kiriha?
Besides, what's with that getup of yours?
I'm a maid. Not only are your morals lacking, even your eyes are rotten?
What do you want?
I'm going to gorge out those puppy eyes of yours.
Have mercy, Kiriha-sama.
I'll forgive you for that.
Tsun Tsun Maid Wa Ero Ero Desu (Tsun Tsun Maid Is Totally Lewd)
Vol. 01
Disciplining My Master
Waku-FAPsubs
Everything: Naoya
http://waku.blog.com
Isn't it about tell you give me an explanation?
Is that an order as a Master?
Yes, it is.
Auntie asked me to.
Please look after the worthless maggot.
I'm a maggot?
Oh, sorry about that. A maggot is unable to perceive itself as a maggot.
What a pity, you could be considered a beauty if you weren't so foulmouthed.
I think that part of her is adorable.
And also her crystal clear skin.
Not to mention that huge deep valley of hers.
How brutal.
What'd ya do that for!?
This is punishment for yelling your disgusting desires so early in the morning.
So I was thinking aloud?
It's fine in front of me.
Please don't expose your perverted sexual desires in front of others.
I'm really sorry.
Auntie made me wear this to keep that infinite sexual desire of yours in check.
Aren't you unable to resist this getup of mine?
That's low! To actually capitalize on my fetish for maids.
I agreed to it reluctantly on account that we are childhood friends.
I'd properly give you a dressing down even if you thank me.
It's just a diversion from losing that game the last time.
I know it, you're just getting back at me by dressing as a maid.
W-What are you talking about?
So, what sort of game are we playing next?
This operation takes care of Master while eliminating erotic tendencies.
The winner is decided by the total points at the back of the three command cards.
Cards are designated a maximum of ten points each.
You lose when you accumulate more than fifteen points.
Sounds interesting! Let's start quick.
The themes are centered around the basics of a maid's daily chores.
If that's the case, the more I want to satisfy my maid fetishes
the risk of losing the game will increase.
But I'm unable to withstand such a bust.
Summon, Ero Maid!
This fellow is saving me a lot of trouble by blatantly exposing his desires...
It'd be meaningless if I don't choose such an erotic maid outfit.
I'll follow the command by serving you wearing this outfit.
Be happy that a beauty like me is serving you while wearing something so sexy.
You should weep tears of gratitude.
Seems like I won't lose out even if I win or lose.
Well then, I'll see you tomorrow. Master.
That Kiriha, she got rid of all my treasure.
Kiriha, serve me properly.
Come and attend to your master.
Milk them using those huge rack of yours.
I-I'm coming! Kiriha! Make sure you drink them all.
Here you go, Master.
Oh, arigatou!
So Master has the hobby of using maids to jerk himself off.
Making me give you all sorts of service... in your fantasy land.
Sorry!
I won't do it again, I believe in Jesus.
I don't want to hear you apologize.
What should I do?
You're my master now. Think for yourself something like this.
Are you not angry?
Imbecile.
Idiotic-lewd-worthless piece of shit master.
Hey, your eyes are scary.
Be obedient. Right now, I'm going to give this miserable and pathetic master service.
It's already erecting from my mere touch. Incorrigible.
Are you happy to be jerked off like this by your maid, Master?
I'm gonna stop if you don't answer.
It's feel fucking good.
Only that? Don't you feel happy?
Of course I'm happy! A girl that I've always like is touching me like this.
You're actually confessing at such a time? What a pathetic Master.
I'm going all out!
You better suck on my dick until the end!
I can't help it if it's a command.
Be grateful, perverted Master.
Be sure to sound off when you're gonna come, Master.
I'll squeeze your balls so hard if you don't.
I'm coming!
Stop it! It's very sensitive now.
No way, I'm going to tease it somemore until it dries out.
It's not exactly tasty, but it's addictive after some time.
Why do you look so calm? At least be slightly embarrassed.
I behave however I want to.
Seems like you won't be satisfied just from having a pure and adorable maid beauty jerk you off.
I'd lose all dignity as a man if I give in like that.
It's an order! Take responsibility and appease me.
I've do it since it's an order.
Master who's a cherry boy with pseudo-phimosis.
What sort of wretched and lewd humiliation will you subject me to?
Titty-fuck me with those huge breasts!
OK.
He's not even asking for a kiss. Just how pathetic can this guy get?
Your delicious tits are the best!
Are you fine just staring at them?
Are you getting horny from thinking about taking my titty-fuck virginity?
Your intuition is spot on.
I can tell precisely because it's Master.
What are you gonna make me do?
Move up and down.
Or massage them left to right.
Lightly kiss and suck the top portion.
I don't want to. You never even kissed me.
I didn't catch the last bit.
It's nothing!
Here, are you satisfied now?
What do you think of my boob service?
Of course it's fantastic!
It's warm and firm.
Your penis is throbbing, Master.
Go ahead! violate my breasts by coming on them.
I'm going to cum like this, Kiriha!
This is special service for you.
Kiriha!
S-Sorry.
The maid game started with much turmoil.
I've been at the mercy of Kiriha for almost a week.
You know the consequences if you dare move.
Are you kidding?
"Maid disciplines Master" card.
Know your place! I'll properly discipline you.
Your precum is already out. Does it feel so good to have your dick bullied by a maid?
Getting teased while being able to see the panties, it'll surely erect.
Dimwit! I'm showing you on purpose!
Don't get all embarrassed now.
Shut up! You're just an imbecile who can't even force yourself on a maid!
You'll get mad if I'm rough.
Of course!
But...
I won't decline you.
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is a vagina! A girl's, Kiriha's!
Don't just seat there!
Say something, at least.
I-I'll feel embarrassed if you don't react.
Let's see... you're a slut, Kiriha.
How could you say something like that at such a situation!
But I.. LOVE that slutty part of you.
It's a confession that's fitting of an imbecile master like you.
Bark now if you wish for me to discipline you with my body.
W00f W00f!
A Master who'd dispose of his pride for the sake of lust. So wonderful that it trembles.
To exchange your male virginity, which I won't want even if you pay me,
with my world's priceless and precious virginity, an even exchange.
I-It hurts!
Kiriha.
I'm fine now.
Don't act tough when you're crying.
Let's hurry and continue.
Do you want a maid who'd just lost her virginity to lead you?
I'm happy that you took away my first kiss from the top and bottom.
This is a form of your discipline, say it properly.
I'm really happy! So happy that I might die.
Be more gentle.
No! If you suck so hard...
It's my turn to discipline you.
It's in too deep.. the penis kiss. Seems like I'm the one being disciplined.
I-Incredible.
Kiriha, I'm gonna cum.
No way, this is discipline. It's not sex if you don't cum inside.
I've made up my mind to have Eishun violate my womb with my first time.
The Master has every right to plant his seed into his maid.
It's nice, it's good. Your expression is so seductive.
I was only just a virgin and now my cunt is convulsing.
Hurry and use your semen to ravage my uterus!
It's coming!
It's coming in! All of them!
I've been completely seeded.
Kiriha!
I couldn't sleep.
Good morning, Master.
You're actually awake.
Thanks to you, I'm feeling fresh.
Master, the elements that make up you are probably sexual desire, carnal desire, and lust.
This is!
What do you intend to do today, Master?
To Be Continued.