http://wakusubs.wordpress.com
Mesu Nochi Torare - 02:
Student Council President Conceived
You think Reiko-senpai's appearance is strange?
She does seem rather tired.
Only that?
Well, she does seem more feminine than before.
To slow!
Didn't I say you must come out immediately when I tell you to?
That's why I'm doing just that..
Why don't you try asking her out for a change?
Let's all go to the amusement park! Go!
Reiko-senpai is really adorable in civilian clothes.
No!
I can't... anymore...
No way, something so hot coming in!
It's so sturdy.
No.. I can't anymore...
Why?
Why does it feel so good?
I thought I heard Reiko-senpai's voice.
Just throw away such childish underwear.
Wear something that makes me big and horny.
Let me pick some for you.
The hot stuff...
There's so much.
Day off a few days later
Misaki-chan is such a slowpoke.
And she was the one who came up with the idea.
I'll get something to drink.
What do you want, Reiko-senpai?
Anything is fine.
Thank you so much!
This is just awesome!
Besides, your cunt is just too lewd. Misaki-chan.
I've really wanted to do it for a long time.
My dick was always hard and erect whenever you brush past me.
Cuming inside when you're not even wet feels pretty good.
Get your ass over here!
Bring your pseudo-boyfriend over.
Let's have an enjoyable day off together!
I'm having some fun with Misaki-chan first!
Thanks a lot, pseudo-boyfriend.
For you to take time to accompany us.
Let's all have fun together.
You should get started too, Yasu-san.
Now come here.
Pseudo-boyfriend, look carefully.
Her preferences in underwear has changed due to another man.
Your girlfriend.
That just means she already belongs to me.
Do you get it now, cherry boy?
Stop it.. Please, stop it.
No. Please, I beg you.
I must not be swayed by him.
I've got to reject him.
S-Senpai?
Stop.. kissing me.
I knew it! You absolutely love my kisses.
You got tighter so quick.
No.
That's not true.
Or have you taken a liking to my penis?
You said mine is bigger than your pseudo-boyfriend, right?
Look! How terrible.
You're a carnivore.
Already changing your mind after being fucked only once?
No...
You mean yes, didn't you?
It feels good to be pregnant.
Getting pregnant...
No way!
Just like that...
This is wrong! Stop!
Amazing.
This penis that have made me into a woman
is so deep inside me!
So hard yet so hot. My mind is in a mess!
You're feeling so good that you're latching on me!
Hey! What do you think? I'm asking you!
Yes...
Your penis is delicious.
No!
I'm saying stuff like that because he forced me to.
I don't mean it.
All right, I'm gonna cum.
Make sure you properly tighten your cunt.
Yes!
You're such a whore, Prez!
Getting pregnant after losing your virginity.
It's considered very lucky, you know.
No.
I don't want to get pregnant.
But it'll feel fabulous.
When you ejaculate after climaxing.
Listen! Make sure you properly visualize it.
Inside your womb, the scene when my sperm catches hold of your egg.
What's this?
It feels so great!
Cuming inside without a care feels damn awesome!
My child is implanted inside here.
Tei-chan.
Can I have her conceive my baby?
Sure!
I'm cuming!
I'm cuming! I'm cuming! I'm cuming!
My slutty vagina is going to conceive.
I make you have the same face as her!
No, I don't it.
A face like a slut.
I definitely won't make it.
No! Shintaro-kun.
Don't look at my face like this.
Show it to him.
Your face when you're cradling my dick!
No! Don't look...
Please, stop!
I'm the one who called you.
Well then, I'm counting on you to keep watch.
Dear Vice President.
He's seriously a good chap.
Reiko's pseudo-boyfriend.
He will listen to anything we say as long as we don't spread these photos.
But the one enjoying these bodies
is only me alone.
Don't do that.
It's reaching the top!
Your penis is kissing my uterus.
But...
But it feels good! It's fantastic.
I'm gonna cum! I'm cuming!