Preparations are almost done.
No, geez...
You let your guard down too easily.
Reiko-senpai's such a meanie.
Dressing up is bait for these wolves.
Thank you for waiting.
We're the Home Cookery Club. This is our booth's cuisine list.
Regarding the items needed for the school festival...
We'll be counting on you.
Sure.
Sorry for pushing everything to you.
No! This much is nothing...
Shintarou-kun is the vice-president of the student council where I'm president.
Don't say that.
I've always been relying on you, yet I've never even said a word of thanks.
He's pretty forceful, though he don't look like it.
He's very reliable when it matters. He's my prince.
Waku-subs Credits: Naoya
http://waku.blog.com
Mesu Nochi Torare
Vol. 01
The Framed Student Council President
Hurry up, Shintarou-kun.
What's there to hurry.
What are you saying? We don't usually have alone time like this.
We can't waste even a second.
I thought we're gonna inspect the various segments?
Only? You should learn to understand a girl's heart more.
Senpai.
Wait.
Why not do it here, then.
Prez!
What?
Our booth is giving free juice samples.
Can I ask for your help?
OK. I'll just..
How's it, Prez?
It's good.
Let's go, Senpai.
Thank you for coming~!
This is the last.
Seems like a segment involving a special classroom.
I can't really see much.
Reiko-senpai?
Are you all right?
It's nothing.
Something's wrong. My body's feeling hot.
Are you sure? I'll be there.
Don't worry.
It's totally pitch black here.
Shintarou-kun?
If only he'd be this forceful usually.
My eyes are finally accustomed. Where's Senpai?
Hey, we shouldn't.
At such a place... Shintarou-kun?
I'm gonna get mad.
Don't!
If this continues...
I haven't given you permission there.
I'm starting to feel good.
I climaxed just from the fingers coming in.
Wait, stop!
A virgin's vagina is especially intense.
Somehow, I'm feeling really hot.
Stop, don't!
This is different. You're not Shintarou-kun!
Please! Please, I beg you! This is my first time.
I don't want it... yet.
I see?
Then, I shall turn you into a woman!
Forgive me! No, Shintarou-kun!
Shintarou-kun!
It's not that painful due to the drug.
Your body probably isn't listening to you.
It's such a pity I couldn't experience the feeling of resistance.
You, back then.
Yes! An adulterer's penis!
A virgin's cunt is so tight and squishy, feels damn good!
Stop!
No! No! Nonono! Don't!
Get it out, please!
Stop moving! No. You're not Shintarou-kun.
No. Shintarou-kun!
How does it feel to become a woman from my enormous dick?
How does it feel being drilled by a penis?
Like this, you're my woman now.
You'll spread open whenever I feel like fucking.
It's hurts. I don't want this.
Stop it! Please pull it out.
You know what will happen if you do something like this.
Sorry, I'm sorry, Shintarou-kun.
I'm filming you, it's just at the back.
No way! Don't! Stop!
You're still so rational when fucked like that.
No, don't! Stop quick.
I'm sending you to heaven.
No, stop.
I won't ever forgive you if you keep doing something so horrible.
No!
What's this? My mind is a complete blank.
No way! It's coming. Something's coming!
I'm really worried. Reiko-senpai wouldn't come out no matter how long I waited.
Where'd she go?
I received a text saying after she parted with you,
she started feeling unwell and went to rest. She wanted me to tell you.
Well, there are many reasons when a girl's body is unwell.
It's best you don't probe any further.
What a slutty pressure.
You're horny! That cunt of yours, Prez.
No, I...
Who's the one yearning for my dick? Whore!
Ain't your wet cunt weeping in surrender to my penis?
I'm gonna mark you, and seed you irresponsibly!
Please let me off.
No, don't cum. I'll get pregnant.
I don't a baby. Please, stop quick!
Please let me off, I beg you!
I'm gonna plant my child where you've just graduated from your virginity.
No, you absolutely can't!
NOOO!
Speaking which, you could tell it's another guy's dick just from a touch.
That's because...
Because?
You wanna make me cum inside? Come on!
I won't go easy until you confess.
I got it, I'll confess.
Please spare my insides.
Once, I did it just once with him.
Shintarou-kun.
Because it was bigger and harder than Shintarou-kun's from back then.
I'll use this huge and hard penis of mine to impregnate you!
Be honored!
I feel it. It came so incredibly.
Shintarou-kun...
It's seriously great you didn't fuck with him that time.
Thanks for safekeeping your virginity, Prez!
Sorry for making you worry. I'll leave first today.
My bad, Shintarou-kun.
It's fine.
A boyfriend that would surprise you.