What the heck is happening?
Glasses that cater to your interests.
Known as the fetish glasses.
They are glasses which allows one to see what he wants to.
What I want to see... no way.
What do you see, Hiroto?
What do I see?
Charlotte in the nude.
She appeared out of nowhere this morning.
Dorei Usagi to Anthony (Bunny Slave and Anthony) THE ANIMATION
「Sexual Desires, I will fulfill them all for you」
Waku-subs http://wakusubs.wordpress.com Credits: Naoya & Fomite
Today, we're introducing our new new transfer student.
I'm Charlotte Hatsune. Please to meet all of you.
She's a cutie!
Her hair is long.
You'll be seating beside Maeshima-kun.
OK!
B-Beside me?
A bunny?
Be sure to look out for me, Hiroto.
I-Is that a bunny just now?
Besides, how did you know my name?
Your name?
I'm able to read the minds of others.
Please translate the following paragraph after reading.
An esper...
I've guessed right! Your mind is filled with lewd stuff.
T-That's nonsense!
Maeshima-kun, we're starting lessons. Please be quiet!
S-Sorry.
Hey, I got scolded because of you.
Stop talking to me.
B-Besides, reading the minds of others is all a lie.
I hate lewd stuff.
Really?
Let me analyze your true feelings for you.
Anthony.
Bring out the fetish glasses.
That was how it came to this.
It's huge.
Hey, Hiroto. Do you want a blowjob?
C-Charlotte! Don't do that.
You don't like it?
Don't worry, no one would be able to see me.
You're all hard and stiff. Hiroto's such a pervert.
No way...
That's...
Does it feel good?
Maeshima-kun?
Why are you wearing glasses?
S-S-Shirai-san!
Well...
Are you all right?
Well, this is...
This is a mistake... I...
Have you seen Hatsune-san?
Where did she go?
I wanted to talk to her for a bit as class president.
No way. She really can't see?
Maeshima-kun?
Shirai-san.
Could you please turn around?
Like that?
Put your hands on the desk.
What's this for?
What am I saying?
Maeshima-kun?
This feels unbelievable.
This is bad. Shiraishi-san's ass is right in front of me.
Charlotte! Just like that... I'm almost...
Geez.. what's the matter? Did something get onto my skirt?
Remain like that for a bit.
Say, Maeshima-kun...
I'm coming!
To think I ejaculated with Shiraishi-san's ass in front of me.
Are you all right, Maeshima-kun? You're acting weird today.
She's sucking my...
I'll feel embarrassed if you stare at my skirt like that.
Hey, are you listening?
She's drinking it.
Shiraishi-san, you don't have to bother yourself me someone like me.
No can do! Cuz' I'm the class president.
Her breasts are jiggling in front of me.
I'm really fine.
But you've to listen to what I say.
It'll do you good if you could get along more with the other classmates.
It's not good if this persists.
Exposing yourself completely like that is bad.
Charlotte, please more on the top.
You'll get more distant if you don't interact more with the others.
Wrap your tongue more, bring it deeper, and suck with more force...
Hey, are you listening?
Yes, I am.
With more intensity.
I want to have another go looking at Shiraishi-san.
What are you doing, Prez? The teacher is looking for you.
Oh, really?
Himeno and Kashiagi.
I'm coming right away.
Oh, Himeno is shaved like I've imagined.
Kashiagi's rack is enormous.
This is bad...
I'm coming.
I still want to have a go looking at Shiraishi-san's there.
Here I go!
Maeshima-kun?
Charlotte, be careful not to leak. Make it goes deep down your throat.
Look at me.
Can you really read minds?
I'll see you later, Maeshima-kun.
Look.
Hiroto is a super pervert.
Hey, Hiroto.
From now onwards,
I'll give you the most wonderful, and perfect
Sexual intercourse.
What exactly are you...
Besides, what exactly is the most perfect and wonderful sex?
No idea~
What?
Only you will know.
Don't joke with me.
I've said before, I can read minds.
I got it.
Wai...
Something like that.
I could tell you wanted to see this in your mind.
T-That can't be true.
You want me to spread myself for you to see?
I can do that. How's this?
Close your eyes and look away.
It's wet.
My fingers are inside her.
So this is the clitoris?
Her reaction is incredible.
Charlotte's cunt tastes sweet.
I'm doing something crazy in school.
No! I'm coming! I'm gonna cum!
Is this... pee?
It's not.
Wanna feel how it's like coming in?
But you know... it's my first time, and I don't have a condom.
Coming inside is too much...
What did you make me swallow?
Wait! What's happening?
I didn't do anything.
It's throbbing... it's about to cum.
I can't hold it. I'm coming!
No, coming!
Coming inside like that is bad.
Coming inside, she's all slippery... It's a fantastic feeling.
What you swallowed
was something which fills your mind with nothing but sex.
It's a candy which makes ejaculating and erection continuous.
In short: Unstoppable.
What in the world are you?
Besides, is it really all right?
Doing something like that with a person like me.
It's fine because it's you, Hiroto.
You want me to move like that, don't you?
I know everything. Look at me!
Using the entrance of the cunt to massage your glans.
I... can't hold it any longer.
This is beyond euphoria! I'm gonna cum!
There's so much semen.
Is this all right?
You're coming again.
More. I want to cum inside Charlotte much more.
It's overflowing!
Are you coming from the back now?
It's fine, Hiroto. Come inside me more.
The semen really can't stop flowing!
I'm still coming!
Damn, this is too good.
More.. give me more.
There's no end to it.
Hiroto, I've been keeping my first time just for you.
Charlotte, what exactly...
Hey, you hear that? It's like the sound of someone having sex.
Is it from upstairs?
I think it's coming from there.
Serious?
Doing it at a place like that?
It's still coming.
It feels great. Carry on.
You want to see semen overflowing out of my cunt, don't you?
Put it out slowly...
From now on, I shall fulfill all your sexual desires.
What are you guys doing?
Maeshima-kun?
S-Shiraishi-san!
I-I can explain this.
No, it's coming again!
Shiraishi Miho.
Class president and fully athletic. Good grades.
She ranks within top three of the school's most popular girls.
She's always on her guard in front of guys, and has a serious personality.
She can be described as the idol type flower which is unattainable.
Prez. Prez! Hey, Prez!
What!?
Are you OK?
Maeshima-kun.
Shiraishi-san gave off this vibe in the morning.
Shiraishi-san is now resting at the infirmary.
What about her soiled uniform?
It's washed and dried.
Shiraishi-san seems to be mad.
Forget it. It's already a miracle for her to be concerned about someone like me.
Besides, I still have you around.
Thanks to you, I'm no longer alone.
You should visit her at the infirmary later.
I feel really bad for her.
Yeah. You're right.
W-What's this?
I woke up feeling hot all over.
Maejima-kun and Hatsune-san back then...
They were having sex, weren't they?
No way, I've gotten wet.
Why do I feel so hot?
It's a strange feeling.
Nobody's around, right?
I've never masturbated before.
The edge of this bed... seems pretty good.
My cunt is tightening.
A-Amazing.
Oh dear, what am I doing?
Doesn't this make me a pervert?
But... it feels good.
My waist just can't stop moving.
Oh no! Something is going... going to come out.
This is bad. The bed and my panties are wet.
But I want more..
Taking off my panties in the infirmary and laying my legs spreadeagled like that...
I must be a slut!
Slut! Slut! Slut! Slut!
This must be how sex feels like.
The penis enters here.
Maejima-kun, likewise...
It feels so good! I-I'm coming!
I can't stop it! It's so good.
It's not stopping! More! I want more!
Shiraishi-san, are you awake?
T-This isn't what you think...
S-S-S-Sorry!
Wait!
Shiraishi-san?
I want to have sex!
I'm feeling strange now. I want to have sex badly.
You must be thinking I've gone bonkers.
But is it wrong for me to have sex?
Of course not.
This is... Maejima-kun's...
Amazing, it's become really hot.
Shiraishi-san, I...
I can't control myself anymore.
Don't do that, Shiraishi-san!
S-Sorry. I came all over you again.
It's fine.
I merely got a fright just now.
Because of the smell of your semen,
it's become unbearable inside. So...
I didn't think the penis would be this hard.
Shiraishi-san!
Incredible. Maejima-kun's penis went inside me.
Wait.
Shiraishi-san, no. If you suddenly get onto me and start moving...
You're really tight... inside...
I'm going to come again! I'll come inside, this is bad.
I can't stop now. My insides are begging for it.
I'm going to cum!
It's OK. You can cum inside of me.
Sex. I'm now having sex with Maejima-kun.
Maejima-kun. I beg you. Please give me more.
Mad as a march here.
It's a strong aphrodisiac.
Shiraishi-san who smelled this
would have the unstoppable urge to have sex.
Charlotte. Is it all right to have Hiroto go to Shiraishi-san?
What do you mean?
I mean... your feelings for him are...
Of course it's all right.
I exist here for the sole reason of making his wishes come through.
Shiraishi-san, I feel really good.
I feel good, too. Your dick is so hot and hard. It's amazing.
I'm going to cum again!
The ejaculation is unstoppable.
It's inside me. A lot of it is inside of me.
Harder. Do it harder and destroy me.
Your penis is entering in and out of my cunt.
I'm totally exposed.
Here it comes! It's fantastic. Your semen is filling me to the brim.
More. Fill my womb up to the core.
Shiraishi-san!
Maejima-kun, go ahead. Cum more inside of me.
Give me more semen, Maejima-kun.
Empty more seeds of babies.
Go deeper. Give me more! I want more! More!
S-Shiraishi-san.
Maejima-kun, you're still coming.
Because you're here, I'm not lonely anymore.
But Shiraishi-san seemed to hate me now.
Charlotte?
I've mentioned before.
I can read everything that's in Hiroto's mind.