Karaoke?
I'm not interested. I'm really busy recently.
Liar. Why do you sound so relax.
Really? Well, forget it.
Right now, me and Natsumi are getting cosy with three guys from college.
Actually we are short of one on the girls' side.
Don't you think the balance isn't right?
So cold, aren't you? Yurie!
Aren't we friends?!
Soushi Souai Nouto 01 (Mutual Love Notebook 01) - Girls Who Hate Sex Don't Exist in this World
Credits: Naoya (Waku-Fapsubs)
Kissing your classmate.
Ok, this is Asaoka Madoko-chan.
Hello.
Over here is Miyamoto Mizuru-san.
Nice to meet you.
What's wrong? Do you know each other?
No way!
Is that so...
I didn't think I'd meet someone from the same club here.
I didn't have a choice. I was called in by my highschool senior to make up the numbers.
You'll cooperate by pretending not to know me, right?
But what for? Am I needed here?
Natsumi and Yurie already had sights on their target.
What a joke.
Sorry to disappoint you. You even tried so hard to the extend of showing your belly.
S-Shut the hell up!
What's happening? What are you talking about?
Oh, it's nothing.
Don't tell me Miyamoto-san has taken a liking to Madoka-chan?
Yeah, she's quite pretty.
Really? She's been going on about getting a boyfriend. You can have her.
Nobody's calling you mute.
Hey, Madoka. Why don't the two of you be alone together.
What are you saying?
Yeah, I think it's not bad. Miyamoto-san seems gentle too.
Don't tell me... you called me here because you couldn't leave him alone?
Don't worry~~ We'll pay for the fees.
Wha-
Good luck, Madoka-chan!
How did it turn out like this!
Ok, it's been decided. Miyamoto-san, the rest is up to you.
W-wait, senpai!
What now? We still have half an hour or so.
You wanna sing something to ease the stress?
Lewd!
What are you saying suddenly?
Yeah, she's quite pretty. You said!
I didn't pull that expression.
So sorry to have you specially look after me.
Seriously.
What?!
I'm serious about it!
What?
I think you're pretty, and my heart skipped too.
Thanks...
I really wanna get a boyfriend.
That's your catchphrase.
After that, we kiss, and kiss, and kiss somemore.
So your head is filled with nothing but kissing?
Is it not right?
Well, it's not that. But I didn't think it'd be to such an extent.
Don't you want to do it?
I do want to, but if you're saying out of spite. I won't.
you're really trying your best to hold it in, right? Am I outside your target range?
Not really.
Then it's fine.
I'm happy of what you said just now.
Really?
Since it's come down to this, here
isn't this precisely out of spite.
It's not.
Is this the end?
You really like kissing, don't you? Madoka.
It feels good.
Seems like the time is up.
Are you satisfied with this?
What?
Are you satisfied with just kissing?
Feels kind of exaggerating.
Yeah. It's my first time to a love hotel, too.
Such atmosphere, just turns you off on the contrary.
Really? I feel quite horny, though. It's a room for such a purpose, afterall.
Right, Mizuru?
More please.
Madoka-chan, it's too much.
My tongue is almost gone.
I wanna see your ass.
Will you continue kissing me later?
Sure.
Ok, then.
This is a victory underwear. You're really serious.
Yeah, any problem with that?
Nope.
Your ass is surprisingly big, Madoka.
Shut it.
Your asshole is adorable.
Shut up! Shit, it's already flooding down here.
Madoka, you smell of pee. Did you clean up properly?
Shut up! Hey...!
That place... my asshole. Don't you idiot!
No, don't play with my cunt.
You're really sensitive, Madoka.
No such thing... Oh no!
Mizuru, let's do it. Let's fuck.
Are you really ok? Don't say it's all a lie at this point.
Where are your balls? I want it, I want your dick! Is that fine?
Get it? I'm totally yours, Mizuru. Are you at ease now?
Yeah, I'm all the way inside you. Also, your warmth and softness are slowly tightening.
I can't anymore...
It feels damn good. I think I'm cumming soon.
It's like a dream, your dick is stabbing me tightly. My vagina is feeling it too.
What do you mean it's like a dream?
It feels better and more comfortable than I thought.
It's amazing. Oh no, I'm cumming..
Madoka. I can't hold it any longer. I'm cumming.
Your dick is expanding and throbbing. It's ok, you can cum inside.
Let's cum, let's cum together!
Your semen is coming, coming in. It's so hot.
Incredible, it's sucking onto it.
Hey, are you alright?
Hey, Mizuru.
My chest feels terrible. Can you take off my tank and bra?
Feels better now.
You don't wear pads?
That's rude! Mine are real stuff.
Sorry, but they are impressive. Your nipples are unexpectedly pink.
Well, I don't fuck around with guys very often.
Your areola is a bit big, though.
I'm quite conscious about that.
Sorry.
You're too into it.
Shut up. I can't help it, I can't stop.
I climaxed from the kiss. Fantastic!
Hurry up! The semen from just now is about to flow out.
You're already so vigorous from the start.
Amazing, the feeling is better than just now. Mizuru, you're really something. Incredible!
Awesome, great. It's as though i'm breaking. You're too rough.
That's because you feel too good inside.
But you're too forceful.
This is bad. My tummy is swelling. It's touching the uterus.
Mizuru, let's kiss.
Like this, the uterus tip is about to explode.
Me too, if you're still this tight...
Madoka, I can't anymore. I'm going to cum.
It's ok. As and when you want! One last time inside me.
I'm climaxing now. Let it all out while I climax, one final thrust.
Amazing!!
Shit, there's still more.
Madoka, no I mean manager.
Behave as per usual during club activities.
Got it.
It's fine if we're not in school.
Erm, this Sunday.
Madoka-san! Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, Ai-chan. Thanks.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
The new manager is nice.
Yeah. She might not be extremely gorgeous, but those boobs are something.
Boobs eh?
Why is she attached to you?
The world is so unfair.
Isn't it nice...
Ah, you're on fire. How far did you go already?
Have you touched her breasts? Have you done it?
Don't come so close. You stink!
How's the kiss, what does it taste like?
There's no taste.
Those two are so close to Namikawa-senpai.
Ai-chan!
Yes? Is there anything?
Is Namikawa so cool? If it's Ai-chan, there are surely more eligible guys for you to choose from, right?
Not true.
Sweat Fetish Manager.
Namikawa-senpai, you worked hard!
S-Shindou-san, were you waiting for me?
Are you the only one left?
Yeah. Everyone went back.
Feels like you've been more conscious of us recently...
Shindou-san?
Namikawa-senpai, you smell nice.
It'll be bad if someone sees us.
Sorry, I couldn't resist Senpai's smell of sweat any longer.
Are we really gonna do it here?
You were so close to Nakazaki-senpai and Asou-kun just now.
Unforgivable.
That's just them...
You really sweat a lot today. But you wiped it off.
No matter what, I mean it's disgusting being all sticky and stuff.
I've said before, your sweat belongs all to me.
Is this some kind of joke!?  Ouch, it hits. I got it, I'll do that next time.
Really? Don't break your promise.
The scary part is she doesn't even know she's a creep herself.
Sorry, does your tits hurt? I'll make them feel better.
Senpai's nipples are erecting. Are you feeling horny?
Senpai, could you lift your arms?
It's sweating, Senpai. Please lift them up.
It tickles, Shindou-san.
It's all your fault. You wiped away all your sweat. It's salty.
No, don't.
Shindou-san?
Yes, I'm fine. I only climaxed.
Your sweat made me to horny.
R-Really?
Great. This area hasn't been wiped.
Well, that's true. Our club room doesn't have a shower.
I'd destroy it even if there is.
She's serious about it.
Wow, it's incredible. The smell is very strong.
My bad, there are still intact.
Senpai, I'm gonna strip it off.
It's here. Your region where the smell is strongest.
Shindou-san, you're suffocating me.
Delicious. This is delicious.
Tasty, great stuff.
Why would it be so delicious, Namikawa-senpai?
Just so delicious, this taste.
Hearing you say that, makes it seem like being smelly is my only trait. It doesn't make me happy.
I don't mean it that way. Sorry, am I a bother?
Not really. But you say it as if you're only attracted to my smell.
Shindou-san and I, no Ai-chan, are we compatible?
A-Are you bothered by this sort of thing?
Well, yeah. I'm the older one after all.
Well, why do you want to go out with me?
That's because you're cute, kind and...
And?
Y-Your breasts are big.
Ah, that makes me the same too. Merely judging from appearance.
I feel happy no matter which part of me you praise.
Ai-chan?
I was only attracted to you by your smell initially.
But right now, I'm serious about dating you.
I want to be your girlfriend.
S-Senpai, don't! That's my... no...
But I'm the St. Breast.
This, I know, but...
Desire to touch your girlfriend's breasts. Isn't that natural?
Yes, you can do what you want.
It's really embarrassing looking like that. But, I'm quite happy.
I was thoroughly licked from top to bottom, you know.
Yeah, Senpai. I'm all yours.
This is really some impressive breasts. If I don't cup it like that, it feels like it's gonna slip off.
I was really worried what would happen if my breasts fell out.
But your nipples are properly pointed up, it's lewd.
Senpai, you really like breasts, don't you?
My tits are already erected. Don't suck them.
I-I'm cumming again.
My cunt is already... I beg you, Senpai. Give me your dick, quick.
Ai-chan, could you get on top?
What?
I, for one, want to see the shape of your breasts.
How much do you like them?
I'm in.
It's coming in!
Sorry, Ai-chan. It was too comfortable.
Yeah, I climaxed too.
Senpai, your smell, all belongs to me now.
Hey, Ai-chan.
Could you seat up right, and put your hands behind.
Ok. Is this alright?
Yes. Move your waist just like that.
My breasts are swaying here and there like that. It's embarrassing.
Ai-chan. You're so adorable!
Adorable, no way...
I didn't think you'd be so lewd.
You too, to think you'd have a fetish for sweat. It had never crossed my mind before.
That's not really true.
I only happen to have a liking to your sweat in particular.
Ai-chan.
I'm so happy. Your sweat is so nice. I won't ever let go.
Your insides are melting.
I'm also... going to cum. Cum with me, please, cum it all out.
I want your semen to fill my dirty little cunt, and fill my body with your smell too.
Senpai, Senpai, Senpai, Senpai!
Ai-chan!
I'm cumming!
It's still coming in. My insides are so filled up it's overflowing.
I'm already broken.
This way, my entire body will be the smell of Namikawa-Senpai.
It's already this late.
Oh, Senpai. Leave today's laundry to me.
It's fine, I can wash it at home.
Oh, did I not wash it properly?
That's not it. My parents will become suspicious if she notices the laundry is fewer.
I wish to always be with Namikawa-senpai's smell.
At least leave the underwear, no?
No.
Did we help you cum?
How were we?