Waku-subs     Credits: Naoya/Fomite
http://waku.blog.com
Dark Blue Vol.2 Warmth... being displayed.
Reiya-san, it's embarrassing.
I'm really happy.
I get to see this side of you.
It's your fault, Reiya-san.
You're too forceful.
Yeah. I'm always sweet-talking you, Otoha.
That place is!
Otoha!
If this carries on...
I'll just stand here and watch her...
I-I like...
Can I take this off?
Don't tell me she's even allowed him to go this far!
Is it fine now?
I was only surprised just now.
Just now? Which means before they came here.
I was sweaty, so...
OK.
You're beautiful down here.
Don't do that... Reiya-san.
I'm embarrassed.
I understand you don't really know about these things.
But do you know where I'm touching you now?
I don't know... those things.
Really? But you're already so wet.
This can't be water from the pool, right?
I don't know!
Really? Can I not say it?
I want to hear you say it.
That's called.. the clitoris.
No! My clitoris feels good!
Reiya-san.
If you continue this rhythm...
Please be quiet.
I'll keep this a secret from Reiya-sama.
Are you able to return to your room like that?
Yukito-sama. Are you erected?
I wanna cum.
I wanna cum, please!
I'm going to continue like this making you climax.
There... Reiya-san's tongue... my clitoris.
I'm making sounds... no!
There's only the two of us here.
No way, I'm about to...
You're so cute, Otoha.
Reiya-san.
Amazing! It's overflowing non-stop.
That's because... Reiya-san is really good.
You never know.
It might be because you're slutty.
Don't say that, it's embarrassing.
It's alright. I'm happy as long as you feel good.
It's my turn next, then.
It's unacceptable if I'm the only one feeling good.
So long as you don't hate it.
How could I hate something like that.
How is it?
Is it OK?
Yeah.
It just feels warm, it's mysterious.
If it's fine with you
could you use other than your hands?
My mouth?
It's fine if you don't want to.
Then I'll just use my tongue if it's fine.
Here goes...
Does it feel better like this?
Use more force if it's fine with you.
Yes.
It's tingling.
Because it feels good.
Does it hurt?
It feels totally good
as long as you're licking it.
Is that so?
It's getting hot.
Are you tired?
Sorry, my mouth is...
Don't force yourself.
I'm really happy you're willing to do this much for me.
But I'm the only one feeling good.
Then, can I use your thighs?
My thighs?
This is...
Use a bit more force to wrap it.
Like.. this?
It's so tender.
Reiya-san.
My breasts... it's numb!
If you keep rubbing down there...
Otoha, do you perhaps want me to put it in?
I don't know.
I'm really numb down there, it's tantalizing.
No way, Otoha!
Do you want me in? Otoha?
You?
Of course I want to.
Fine, then.
If it's Reiya-san, I...
I understand. I'll try my best to be gentle.
Ok.
Sorry, please bear with it slightly.
Anyway, I'm inside.
Sorry, I'll try to end this as soon as possible.
Ok.
Relax yourself more.
Yes.
Reiya.. san..
Reiya-san... is inside me
Otoha, finally...
It feels weird.
What is?
You still haven't answer to my feelings.
Yet we already did things like this.
Sorry, I couldn't resist it.
Don't worry.
Actually, I'm already...
Yukito-sama, please wait!
He might come here.
Oh no. I'm wearing such a swimsuit.
Reiya-san, please get that for me.
Reiya!
What's the matter?
Well, someone called and said the bridge will be fixed very soon. We can go the day after.
They called at this hour?
No, they called much earlier.
But I couldn't find you anywhere.
Really? My bad.
Anything important?
Not really.
Are you free to talk, Otoha?
Seems very important.
I'll excuse myself for a bit.
Reiya-san.
Erm... your shirt.
Just return me later.
OK.
That shirt belongs to Reiya?
Otoha, I'm going to tell you something really important.
But before that, could you remove that shirt?
Can't I wear this?
It's only for a while.
But...
You showed it to Reiya, but you can't show it to me?!
It's only for a while.
OK, I got it.
But it's fine with a towel, right.
You really don't want me to look?
Otoha.
I love you, Otoha!
Are you joking?
A joke... no way!
I'm serious about liking you.
Since young, even when apart.
I've always...
Really? Thank you.
Only that?
Yukito-kun, I'm also...
But I can't think about it now that we're stuck in such a situation.
Why? But with Reiya, you were...
Otoha.
The pain from just now.
I'm extremely sorry, Reiya-sama.
Don't make such basic mistakes.
Yes! But, that's...
It's only a game.
It's merely for the sake for exterminating flithy blood.
If it's Honoka, you can do it.
Yes.
That's from..
Shall we go back, Yukito-kun?
I've to return this.
Compared to spending time with me, you rather Reiya?
You saw it?
Nope, I didn't.
I'm sorry, Yukito-kun.
I'll go back later.
Please leave without me.
Why now...
Reiya-san.
What's this?
Yukito-kun was bewildered...
Because of this?
What else was Otoha planning to say back then?
It could be that her feelings are not entirely certain.
After returning the shirt, just maybe...
Reiya-sama has given instructions to start without him.
I see! Today's meal looks delicious too.
Come on Suzu, you should eat too.
You must be famished, aren't you?
Yeah.
Sorry, I don't really have an appetite.
Don't, Reiya-kun.
Everybody else should be there.
You're already feeling so horny, are you fine like this?
Sheesh, don't say things like that.
Besides, we should really get changed.
Now's the only time everyone's gathered at the dining hall.
Yeah.
I've already told Honoka to retrieve the clothes you left at the pool.
I think they are at her room.
I should tell her to bring it over.
Reiya-kun, you meanie...
She was always at his room after returning his shirt?
Always... like that...
Reiya-san.
I love you.
Various stuff happened before coming here.
But I still think your feelings for me are genuine.
Your hands are groping my breasts.
Your breasts are really soft.
Just touching them is enough to melt my fingers.
No way...
No, ithis carries on...
I'm really glad you're able to remain here.
Reiya-kun.
You've gotten big again, didn't you?
Incredible.
You've gotten used to it.
You kept coming in.
So I no longer feel any pain.
It's already so lively since this morning.
Everybody is finishing breakfast.
Everyone is eating breakfast.
Yet we're here doing such a thing.
I don't care about other things when I'm with you, Otoha.
I feel the same.
I feel secure being with you.
It's so deep.
My...
I've taught you before, right, Otoha?
You feel happy seeing my troubled expression, right?
Nonsense.
Seriously...
What? What did he teach you?
Reiya-kun's penis is throbbing inside my vagina.
Forcefully inserting into my slutty cunt.
My cunt is tightly straggling your dick. It feels so good!
This is really embarrassing.
You can see everything.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
That's- No, you can't.
No, it's dirty.
No single region is dirty on you, Otoha.
Really...
Your penis is really inside my asshole.
You're gonna start feeling horny here very soon.
What a whore.
No, I not feeling horny or anything.
Because your cock is pushing inside me.
Amazing, all I feel is your penis inside of me.
It's good. Something like that, can make me feel good there.
Does anal sex feel so good? Otoha.
You're the best. I can feel it in many wonderful places.
If you do this to me, I'll...
Just like that.
Give it to me, just like that.
Just cum directly inside of me with yours.
I feel your penis in entirety.
I'm coming, coming.
I'm gonna cum.
My insides are so filled...
Oh no, my pee.
You're horrible, Reiya-kun.
Geez, stand up, Reiya-kun.
Did I make you mad?
Of course!
I told you to stop.
Yet you still continue doing embarrassing stuff.
That's why...
It's gotten big again.
Hey, Otoha.
I told you to stop.
For Otoha to do that by herself...
Do you want me to finger you?
It's throbbing here and there.
You still have so much in your dick...
Are you alright, Yukito?
Are you sure you don't need some rest?
Yeah, I wanted to eat a little.
In the end, Otoha and him didn't come down.
Don't tell me even now, they're...
Takamine-sama, your dick feels great!
You're finally honest, Suzuka.
This is my favorite penis that made me into a woman.
Geez, Reiya-kun.
A place like this is so embarrassing.
Don't worry, once in a while.
Still forceful as ever.
You're honest even though you say that.
I don't care anymore.
Your cock feels good.
You can go deeper if you want.
Treat my cute cunt...
At a place like that, what if someone sees us?
Don't worry, everyone's asleep.
I'm a bit scared.
But it feels good. It's so full...
You've gotten wet.
You're excited to be in such a situation?
No way.
Your penis is just too awesome.
I'm feeling horny that's all.
Reiya-kun.
You can cum inside me today.
You're so rough all of a sudden.
Your dick is so hot.
Reiya-kun, together let's...
I'm cuming, Reiya-kun!
I'm cuming! I'm cuming!
I can feel...
...it coming in, your...
Internal ejaculation, eh...
Are you awake, Yukito-sama?
But you can go and rest.
What's this?
Honoka-san?
Yukito-sama, do you feel good?
I... can't breathe...
Yukito-sama, I'm so happy.
It's fantastic.
It's fine, Yukito-kun.
Yukito, you're amazing.
I...
Your penis is loving my vagina.
Is this fine? Am I doing right?
It's for two to three days.
There's still Kotomi-chan.
You can rely me for just this while.
Even so...
Amazing!
Suzuka-san and Takamine-sensei actually did it... It's unbelievable.
Precisely because of such situation.
Finding someone to rely on isinevitable.
Really?
That's right. I had actually wanted to rely on Yukito-kun.
But.
Right now...
I love you, Reiya-kun!