Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Ninja 5
Mashiba Aya
Okay, okay, don't rush me!
Hurry, hurry up, man!
Aren't you a ninja? Why do you need it so
badly?
Shut up! Hurry, man.
Okay.
Hurry!
Fuck, okay. Is this okay now?
Oh...wow... a fucking beautiful girl is
masturbating in front of me.
Hey, are you sure that you have explosives in
your body? If I'm going to die...
Hell yeah!
I have ten of them.
You don't have time to run away.
Hey, I don't care, but why don't you jack off and
take them out?
Shut your mouth! Don't order me around!
Because it feels so good.
Ah, no....do something...
No...I'm feeling so
much pleasure...
Good, faster!
More?
Oh, great!
Hey, do something!
Do you feel good now?
I'm feeling it. I'm wanting to cum.
I can't stop it.
Oh, great. She's really feeling good, this bitch.
Look, that ass rocks.
Oh, no...feels so good...good...so good.
Ah, no...more, more...
Fucking great...fuck me more...more...more...
Fucking great.
More, more, fuck me more...
Okay, come one. Great.
Hey, fuck my asshole, too.
No, I need more.
Fuck my asshole.
Please fuck me in my asshole.
This bitch is getting real.
I'm so lucky to fuck this beautiful girl!
Give me more until you burry your cock.
More, more, fuck me more.
Like this?
Yes. Ummm, good. No more...
Feels great!
How about this?
More, more, push it in far...
I'm fucking you deep...
Good, fuck me more...
Fuck me, fuck me!
Oh, shit.
The switch is...on!
W-What?
FLOWER WINDMILL
SUPER TWIST SPIN
Ninja trick, "Flower Windmill Super Twist Spin."
Shit, I was about to cum.
But he was a fucking jerk.
What? What the heck!
I haven't seen a guy who like this.
Dharma doll is falling.
What? It's too unearthly.
I hope he won't suddenly explode himself...
Dharma doll is falling.
Ah...he may not have any tricks, he's bluffing.
I'm not sure if I need to fight him.
Dharma doll is falling.
Fucking shit! Who are you, man?
What's your name?
Dharma.
Oh, shit.
I lost my fighting spirit. I don't feel like living
anymore. Depression setting in.
What am I doing with the fucking Dharma doll?
Yeah, I'd better masturbate instead.
Let's do it.
Ah... I'm feeling... it's good.
It's the best. Masturbating is the best.
Please let me forget about everything.
Love it, love the masturbation!
I want to melt with pleasure!
Make me forget everything.
No more... I gave up.
You won. It's my first time losing without
fighting, but..
I gave up. I lost against you, Dharma.
I'll do anything you want.
I lost and you won.
Do anything you want.
I'm saying, you can do anything you want!
If you want to fuck, fuck me, man.
Fuck, I'm telling you, I lost.
Why are you fucking round?
Come, lick me.
Don't you want it? I'm saying, suck me.
Oh......I got a hard on.....finally.
What?
Have you been waiting to get a hard on,
standing there for 10 years?
That's right.
I had been thinking "someday I would get a
hard on."
The dream has come true.
And moreover, I can have a nice girl like you.
It's like my best dream!
I will cum this time for sure.
After 10 years, finally I can have a girl...oh,
good...
Hey, man, fuck me please!
Okay, come on, come on...
More, more...
Please fuck me...
A nice ass. Very nice!
Please, fuck more, please!
Please, fuck me!
Okay, as you said, I’ll fuck you, girl.
STAB SPIN DHARMA TIGHTENING
Ninja trick, "Stab Spin Dharma tightening."
Oh, my dick...
It's child's play, fool.
It's a piece of cake.
But...
Why in the kitchen?
Fu, fu, fu. Your trick won't work in the rain.
I figured it out.
I know my all favorite tricks need something to
grab onto.
But this rain, it makes me slip, and messes me
up.
What's the matter? Did you fall in love with me?
What the fuck is he saying? Looks so dumb.
Well, if you can't use your trick, I’m going to use
mine.
Okay, come on!
Fu, fu, fu. Be ready, girl!
Ninja magic, "Water Gun."
What's that?
Oh, it's nasty... ah... no... but...
I’m feeling good.
Give up?
I can suck water into my body for a long time.
Ah... not there... oh no, it's coming into... my
pussy...
Come on, it stimulates you more.
Come on, your breasts....
How do you like it? Don't you feel good?
There, that's my erogenous zone...
I'm getting so horny again.
I feel so good. I no longer can fight.
Are you feeling good now? What?
No, not into my asshole...ah...
Please give it to my asshole...and fuck me!
What the hell! You're a fucking nasty bitch!
Please tell me more. Please call me a dirty
whore.
Okay, you're a fucking perverted, bitch!
More, more.
I'm going to give it to your asshole.
Please! More, deeper....
You're sure as hell a fucking pervert.
Power up, come on!
Yes, yes...good, I can feel it...more, stronger....
What a fucking nasty pervert!
Tell me more...insult me...
I’m going to keep shooting 'til you die.
This Water Gun seems to be weak, but if this
acid water makes you burn.
Give it to my pussy, man. Point it at my pussy 'til
my pussy squeezes.
More...more...deeper. Put the water pressure on
high....
It's very nice to have a closer attack.
You must be affected by acid by now.
What?
Oh, shit! That was close.
No! I was close.
Oh, man. Screwed myself.
Hey, what do you think of the way of ninja?
When you're fighting, masturbation on the
battlefield is outrageous.
Shame on you, man.
Did you forget you're a ninja?
Of course, I won't forget it.
SLUG
SPOUTING
SUPER
Ninja trick, "Super Spouting Slug."
Oh, shit!
This bitch was keeping acid water inside of her
pussy.
I see, the inside of her pussy is made with a
special mucous membrane.
Shit! I'm going to get burned, by my own acid.
I blundered.
Thank you for the explanation.
Ah...Please someone, make me cum
For what reason are you fighting?
Hey, give up, girl...shu, shu, shu.
Psycho kinesis? Finally, there is a tough enemy.
Shu, shu, shu. Shut up! I’m going to be your last
fight.
I’m getting an electric shock.
It's not a regular psycho kinesis.
I don't use such dumb magic. Shua, shua, shua.
You have very beautiful hair.
I can make good stuff with this. Shu...
What are you saying, fool?
Shu, shu, you're going to be in one of my
collections.
What the heck! Ouch!
Ninja's hair is good for cloths. Shu, shu, shu.
Shu, shu. Look at my collections.
T-This is...
These are all made with hair.
It becomes lustrous hair.
You must be losing resistance from the electric
attack by now.
I have total control over you.
I don't have power.
You smell good.
Yes, yes, yes, feel it.
Hey, it's not over yet.
Ah, it's going to break it.
Come on! Not yet!
Oh, no.
You need to cum a lot for the hair.
No....more....
I'm going to fuck your asshole, too.
Give me more, more....please!
Hey, cum! Do you like it?
More, fuck me more!
I'm about to come.
Fuck me more, please!
Come on! What a bitch! Come on!
More, more, deeper, fuck me more...
More, more...fuck me...more...more...
What a bitch...I have been fucking her for a hour,
but...
She is not cumming yet...
More, more...
What a bitch...
Fuck me more...more...
What a bitch!
Hey, I don't have time for your shit.
Anyway, I'm going to get your hair.
Fuck you, man!
My hair is not for you, fool.
S-Stop it.
TWIST
SILK
WAVING
Ninja trick, "Twist Silk Waving."
My neck!
Don't be a fool!
God, please listen to my wish!
I'm very sexually active, more than Shinobu and
Lena.
I don't know what I should do. I can't
concentrate on fighting.
I've become so horny by just massaging my
breasts.
And I can't stop it.
But I can't cum easily. That's why I spend time
trying a lot.
God, but, I decided.
I will no longer ask for sex, and masturbate.
I swear! I want to change myself.
By the way, I was wondering.
God, are you a man? Or a woman?
I can see you both ways.
Let me check!
If you're a man, you must have dick, but
you're a sculpture, so you may not have one.
Wow, you got a big one!
Oh, God! I can't stand it anymore.
God, please be my last man before I change
myself.
Here you go.
What a great body!
You're very kind.
God...
God, fuck me...
Ah...more...
More, more...
More, God. It's so good!
More...
Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me. More, more, God.
Fuck me and cum inside!
Oh, no. It's too high!
I'm going to die. But, it's good.
Very good...fuck me....no...but, good....
You lost!
Oh, shit.
You're going to die!
Ninja trick, "Kannon Door Opon."
KANNON DOOR OPON
I didn't want to use that trick.
Fucking shit! Idiot!
Shinobu may make fun of me, 'cause I farted.
Dumb Aya.
He is dead!