Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Man, I can't take it!
Shinobu, what are you pissed about?
The guy in the train was like,
"You've been looking at me."
How stupid!
And what kind of guy is he?
He's the obnoxious type
with no confidence.
It's okay if he's good looking,
You can't be picky since we're in our second year.
I have no interest in players.
Then how did you respond?
Nothing, I didn't say anything.
You didn't say anything.
But your eyes did.
A kick!
What?
I gave him a good kick,
I can't believe it.
He was unlucky for approaching
Shinobu. If only I was there...
Is this good? We are the successors.
Stop saying foolish things.
Hey, hey, how's that one?
Huh?
The two sitting over there.
They're my type.
The one on the right, Aya?
How did you find out?
You stress for good looks, Aya.
You have a bad taste.
Did you see that?
I saw it.
Yeah.
What do you think?
That uniform...
Not from around here.
Possibly...
That was psychokinetic,
a form of teleportation.
The guys with that ability...
Are they from Koga?
Shh... Don't talk about it out loud.
But, but aren't they?
What do you think, Lena?
Probably...
Yea, did you see their eyes
when they met with ours?
If it's true. I wonder what
their next move is.
Yes. We saw them for the first time.
This is our good credit!
Don't think lightly.
My legs are sore.
So tired.
Because it's hard.
You got your clothes all wet.
Because it's so hot, instead of basics.
I rather learn the art of Fire.
We'll learn that in our third year.
Only superficial training is...
Pervert!
Don't worry,
stop acting like a teacher.
Hahaha...
Aya's not here.
Aya always ditches basic practice.
She gets PMS like five time a month.
She's a true cutter.
I hope Aya's doing well.
What do you mean doing well?
The Koga from yesterday...
You're worried if they beat up Aya?
Yeah.
How silly.
That's impossible.
Huh?
What is it?
Aya!
This trick is obviously from the Koga.
What kind of uniform did they have?
The outside looks like
the K.P. institute.
Is that the Koga Institute?
Koga has a total secrecy principle so
I don't know, but probably...
Then let's go raid and destroy everyone!
Our total student population of 350
can't even handle 10 of them.
What?
Then how come we're going over
our training everyday?
That's that, I'm just waiting,
Waiting for whom?
For someone who has the power to
handle Koga single-handedly,
Single-handedly?
Yes, that person might not
notice it's own strength.
Was there a person that strong?
Aya's pretty strong too.
But she ended up like that.
If the ability is present or not,
that will decide Koga's fate.
Anyways from now on, be cautious.
The next target would
definitely be you two.
Yes.
What shall we do?
We should let her rest here today.
Hey Lena. If Aya ended up like that,
I wouldn't stand a chance right?
Hmm... maybe. Don't worry Shinobu,
you're stronger than Aya.
Seriously, both of us will get killed
if we stay like this.
But I've been weak from
the beginning. Nothing can be done.
You don't get stronger because
you're always timid.
Even if you say so.
Then I'll train you!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Training.
What?
No!
It's a review from today's lesson.
Don't put your legs there!
What are you saying?
What else am  suppose to do?
So dirty!
Pervert!
Be more laid back!
Shinobu.
It's from the school building...
Lena, let's go.
What? We're really going?
Probably from the nurse's office.
Yeah, maybe something's
wrong with Aya.
Stop, stop! Stop it!
Blood, she's bleeding!
What are you saying?
Don't you do this kind of dirty stuff?
Stop it Aya, stop it.
Principal.
You two step back.
Don't worry.
She's just unconscious.
You slut!
What's the matter here?
No. I've heard a loud roar
from the nurse's office at midnight.
So I stepped in and this girl...
Get lost fucking pervert!
Principal. What'll happen to Aya?
Look at this.
This is the parasite bug.
A parasite bug?
It's living inside Aya.
Living inside?
This grows inside Aya and
controls her sexual desires.
Hurry and remove this bug!
Impossible, it's too big.
What about Aya?
Once it grows a certain size,
it'll eat the internal organs.
Then...
I was too late. I didn't notice
the parasite bug inside her.
Aya. Aya!
Lena, please. No more trouble,
I can't go to sleep.
When did you become perverted?
Lena. I can't sleep.
Instead of playing by yourself.
Let's have fun together.
I understand. We're schoolgirls.
Before my period I get horny,
but don't have the right guy.
Hey, can I sleep with you?
I'm getting excited.
Lena.
Lena?
Hang on!
Don't look, don't look!
Lena!
Lena, wake up! Lena, Lena, Lena!
More...
More!
More, good...
Lena, you went out cold.
Shinobu, we'll fight for every moment.
Yes.
Remember the trainings, okay?
This is the map of the school
of the Koga Institute.
You can go in from the back.
Be careful of traps and once inside,
find the principals office.
There should be an antidote there.
Koga people keep potions and
antidotes handy.
Yes.
They'll capture us in groups,
It's better if you're alone.
You're one of our top students, so you'll
successfully complete the mission.
Yes, but...
What is it?
What would happen if I fail?
Failure is not accepted.
You'll only get killed.
Yes.
This is it.
Looks like an ordinary school campus.
What is this trap?
Hehe, childish.
Such a low-leveled trap.
Maybe they're low-leveled. Haha...
Just wait Lena,
I'll get the antidote for you.
Fufu, a little rat came sneaking in.
Why do we have to be cautious for her?
She's easily crushable.
She has nice legs.
The one before was good.
but this one looks delicious.
Let's hurry and fuck her.
Wait a second.
Good, go ahead and fall for our trap.
I see. Let's enjoy this.
This is too easy. At this rate,
the principal's office should be found soon.
Around here is the principal's office.
Shit!
Nice view.
You guys...
It's been since the hamburger shop.
Damn! It's you guys who hurt Aya.
Aya? I don't know.
I remember fucking one bitch though.
How should we eat her?
Shit. I was almost there.
Almost? Haha, you're one happy girl.
You really think you got here
without getting spotted.
We saw your every move.
We just waited here.
Well, lets put the parasite bug in her.
Wait, first we'll stick in
our energized cocks.
Stop it...
We can't stop.
Here, take a look at this!
I can't hold on. Here, see?
Stop, stop it!
Come on, come on, come on!
There...
Does it feel good?
I can't stop.
Hey, hold on to her more.
Who is it?
I'm Saizo Kirigakure,
but it's useless to know.
Help me.
Who, who is it?
What are you saying?
Just look at you.
Shut up.
Don't be upside down forever.
Ouch!
You're an Iga right?
Yeah.
Man, Iga people are such weaklings.
Be quiet! You are...
Me? I'm Saizo Kirigakure.
Saizo Kirigakure? You helped me?
My mission. Not my personal interest.
You get on my nerves!
We shouldn't be chatting.
Well well...
Here's a weapon. They're coming here.
Thank you.
This many people already.
We'll split in two at the signal okay?
Move around and don't stop.
Die!
Hey Saizo, stop fooling around!
You're late.
Hurry to the principal's office!
This way!
Why the principal's office?
Because I want to meet the person
in the highest position.
Then is it the Don of Koga?
What are you saying? We're the Koga.
What?
That macho is Sarurobi Sasuke.
We'll leave it up to him.
Not here. It empties out.
There should be an antidote
for the parasite bug.
An antidote?
My friend's effected by the parasite
and I don't have much time.
That thing...
Are you okay?
Do you think I am?
What the fuck is this?
Wha, What the...
It's a weird noise.
Step away!
Looks like this is the
boss of the parasite bugs.
Look, this liquid is living.
Anything moving becomes
a target for the offsprings.
Females should step back.
If not, you'll need the antidote.
Watch out!
Hey...
Don't do it right now...
Later.
No! Hey!
Okay, here goes nothing.
The art of Fire!
Take this!
Yes...
Good job, Shinobu Yarsurugi.
I'm glad for Lena's recovery.
Yes.
How did you defeat it?
Yeah, umm. with the art of Fire.
This way I was able to help out Koga.
Yes.
Dumbass, you almost burned me alive!
Hey, you were about to lose!
Plus...
What?
You're always doing perverted things.
But it's good, right?
Huh? About what?
Ah!
Wha, wha, What?
The antidote. It's burned up!
What should I do? Lena, Lena!
An antidote?
I have the antidote
for the parasite bug.
What?
Koga people have specialties for
medicine.
I see, you're a Koga.
Yup.
Then what about the other guys?
Traitors. They try to
place the blame on Koga.
For what reason?
That is Sasuke's and my mission to find
out.
See you later.
Keep us disguised in your school.
Especially our name.
Why?
It makes our job harder.
Just keep this promise.
See you later!
Thank you.
What wrong, Ms. Yatsurugi?
Are Koga people really bad?
What are you saying?
You were treated horribly.
Aren't they traitors?
Don't get fooled. To keep their promise,
they would even kill their allies.
Koga people aren't human.
They're beasts!
Hey, that's mine!
No. That's yours Shinobu.
Jesus, just recently you were whimpering.
You said it!
Hey Lena, look...
What?