Ninja III
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Stupid. You think you're going to beat me?
Fuck, he's strong.
I'll show you my power.
What a nasty pose! A greenhorn.
Tear her clothes. Come here.
Open. Open it. Super Power, open legs. Open
it up.
Don't look.
Oh...I can see it. Good. Straight ahead...
Now insert...
Good.
How do you like my lower nose?
You don't have any powers now.
You are just a girl now.
How about this. You like this?
Stop it...No...
Harder...Harder...
Good?
Come on, come on, come on...
Stop it.
Come on, come on...
How is it? You don't have any powers now.
You are nothing.
You are wrong.
What?
Super Tengu's Nose Tightening.
W-What?
"Super Tengu's Nose Tightening"
Oh, my dick...
More...
No more...
You...you...
Overconfidence made you not see my real
power.
You are not my enemy. You cannot beat me.
You look like a kid but you have nice moves.
Fuck.
Ok, let's remove your clothes 1st.
I can kill you so easily if I wanted to,
but I want us to have more fun.
Hey, you like it?
You got very nice breasts.
Very soft. You are good for this.
Shut up.
...but you chose your own destiny. If you want to
place blame, blame yourself.
You don't like it?
You are wet now. You are a
girl. You like this? Ummmm, very soft...
Stop it.
It feels good.
How about this?
How is it?
I'll crumple softly...
You like it this way?
How about this?
Do you feel good now?
L-Leave me alone.
You want me to do this?
Stop it...
Come on... Good?
You have a cute face.
You like it? You have nice tits..
Now.
Super Giant Spinnng...
"Super Giant Spinning !"
Oh, man... You make me faint...
Give it up?
Super Giant Spinning Reverse!
Shit.
Stop it.
I cannot stand...
Men are into my breast. You are careless,
damn it.
You are a careless damn girl. You're not strong
enough to be my enemy.
I have been waiting to taste your body.
... Ummmmm, what a nice body!
How about down there? Tastes good.
You are just a normal girl now.
Ok, next I want you to use your mouth.
Ok.
Suck me good.
Fucker.
Suck my dick, bitch. Get into it.
I could shoot
my load now but...
I feel good.
Fuck me now with your big cock. Please.
You want it so bad, don't you?
Here you go. Take it.
Right now.
What?
Super Killing Pendulum.
"Super Killing Pendulum."
How do you like it?
You are shooting on your face, Fucker.
Ok. I admit I lost.
If you say so before, you are not getting hurt.
Your make-up is messed up.
I make you feel good
and enjoy more.
Ok... Ok...
No... No.
It looks good. You have a nice slim body...
Stop it.
It smells so good.
There is nothing better than
girls moaning when they face death.
No.
Come on...Come on...
No...
Come on. Do you like it?
Why don't you moan nicely?
Hey make it loud.
Good... Keep moaning...
Come on...Come on
No.
Moan... Come on... More... Moan...
Stop it...
What's up?
Come on... Moan loudly. Hey...
Hey...
Shit.
You like it?
Good...
You are good.
Come on...Moan.
Come on...Moan a lot...
Moan Sweetly...
Do you like it?
Fuck, nice body.
What a tight hole you got! It
makes me want to come now.
Hey, I want hear more of your moaning.
Ok... Suck me now... Suck it. I can hold more.
Hey, put it in your mouth.
Wow, you suck good.
Oh, great.
Now you can ride me. Do your best.
Oh, good. Suck it harder, bitch.
Now your turn.
What?
Super Sucking.
"Super Sucking"
Your moaning sounds good, too.
Hey, you thought it's easy to get into this
house?
Shit.
This is good timing. I'm horny now.
I have been starving for some girls.
You're going to serve me now.
Shut up.
Suck it...
Good, good... Come on... More...
Open your mouth. Well done.
...Great...
You can make me cum now. Come on...
You are doing better now... Come on...
You think I'm too quick?
But I can cum many
times.
How about this?
One more...Take it...Come on...
You like it? I can cum many times. Be ready,
bitch.
Pervert!
Say anything.
More, more, more...
Ok, suck it now by facing front... do it...
Fake crying...
Super Spouting.
What?
"Super Spouting"
That's it, damn it.