NINJA
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
EPISODE 6
Damn.
Do you believe in God?
What are you talking about?
God is in your heart.
Ready?
We must obey God.
God does not look highly upon you.
Ready?
No way.
Even if you're not, it's God's will.
Alright?
It's not alright!
It's been decided.
You are a witch.
You have a contract with the devil
so you must die.
Understood?
It's God's will.
It's God's will!
You can fool Buddha,
but not this god.
Those crosses didn't go inside you.
They stopped at your skin.
Shit.
Historically, all those that resisted God have died.
So your resistance is futile.
H-He's going to kill me.
This is happening
because you don't believe in God.
If you repent, you might live.
I better go along with this.
I repent.
I will obey.
I believe in God.
That's more like it.
I will verify your sincerity.
W-What?
I will exorcise the witch's spirit
that resides in you.
The witch's spirit is deep inside your cunt.
Let me shove my fingers in deeper.
It's way deep inside.
Oh, wow.
Finger me deeper.
I'm deep in there
I feel the witch's spirit deep inside.
It's the evil witch's spirit.
I'm going to finger you deeper.
Does it feel good?
Your true self is coming out.
I must exorcise
the lewd witch's spirit out of you.
Isn't this great?
Here it is.
It's in deep.
Good. Nice.
Ok. You're gushing wet.
It's time for God's cock
to kill the witch's spirit.
Are you ready?
Come down and accept God.
Come to God, baby.
Now is my chance!
Ninja Sex Position: Reverse Shrimp Cross Hold.
REVERSE SHRIMP CROSS HOLD
What?
What awesome strength!
Damn you.
Oh, no!
My dick! My dick!
My neck is going to break!
My neck...
Oh, my. You're frozen.
Rigor mortis has set in.
Dear God, have mercy
on his poor soul.
I'm such a nice girl.
Dear God, please reward me
with a nicer guy next time.
Ninja, you're not just a chick.
You're a fool.
You're just a baby against my martial arts.
I'm not even sweating.
What's the matter, ninja?
Is that all you've got?
Call yourself a ninja?
You're spineless.
Your moves have no effect on me.
Oh a big talker!
Not enough, eh?
You probably broke three ribs.
But if you insist,
I'll give you more.
Just try it.
You asked for it,
you wench!
You conceited brat.
The way of the ninja is not easy.
You will learn this lesson with your body!
I-Is that all you've got?
You've got the way of the ninja all wrong.
Bitch!
Shut up!
You should be dead by now.
I guess you're a tough ninja.
But this is the end.
You will die by my bear killer hell claw.
Bear killer? You can't even take on a woman.
Don't make me laugh.
Watch your mouth, bitch!
You're a woman?
l didn't even notice.
You look like a virgin.
I’m going to drench you in cum.
They say,
"Don't get caught up in a ninja's pussy."
But she's hurt so bad,
it should be fine.
And her body
is too good to just kill em.
You give good head, baby.
You're lousy with your fists,
but great with your mouth.
Lick my pre-cum.
I love to see you gag.
You may be a ninja,
but you're still a woman.
When you see a big hot cock,
you have to suck it.
Lick my pee hole
with the tip of your tongue.
Yeah, baby.
Roll your tongue around the head.
Suck it, baby.
That's the spot.
That's it.
Right under my pee hole.
Now roll your tongue around it.
You give good head.
You're so pretty.
That's so good.
I-I-I’m going to gush jizz
down your throat!
Suck it.
Suck it hard.
Yeah, turn over.
That's right, baby.
Lick the underside right under the head.
I love these big tits.
Lick my sticky pre-cum.
This is great.
You give the best head, baby.
Now! Nina Sex Position:
Upside Down Octopus Trap Suction Hold!
W-What?
UPSIDE DOWN OCTOPUS TRAP
SUCTION HOLD
I bet you can't breath.
My pussy has more suction power
than an octopus!
Drink my pussy juice
for memory's sake.
The way of the ninja
is not for amateurs.
My claws will strip you naked.
Not just your clothes.
I’ll shred your beautiful skin
and rip out your guts.
This guy's dangerous.
I could get killed.
Slice, slice, slice!
I thought I moved fast,
but he still cut me up bad.
I see.
He's making the air vibrate.
That's right.
You figured it out.
Now that you know,
why don't you surrender?
How long can you withstand this?
Oh, no. At this rate,
I'll be fatally wounded.
What am I going to do?
The fun stuff is over.
Time to die.
That sweat.
Those heavy scissors
are wearing him out.
So it's no big deal.
Ok. I give in.
I'll lose for the first time.
I've never encountered such a strong man.
So I have one last request.
What?
I've always planned to die
after I give my virginity to a stronger man.
Fuck me before I die.
T-That's a nice idea.
A stronger person than you?
I will grant you that mercy.
I have to eat when I drool.
I have no choice.
You pathetic poor thing.
This is the taste of a virgin.
My cock isn't going in.
Mister, your claws are cold.
Yeah, these make it difficult to fuck.
But if I take these off,
I'm weaker than normal.
Please. This is my first and last fuck.
My pussy is all wet and gushing.
Alright already.
You cute thing.
Your pussy is so tight.
You're so wet.
Your big dick feels so good.
You're gushing.
Fuck me harder.
More.
Stick it in deeper.
Give me that huge hard cock.
Look at that cute face.
This ninja is just a young woman.
No.
Spread your gaping pussy!
Yeah, yeah.
You're so wet.
This is called the Pine Needle.
Wow, stick it in deeper.
Scream, baby.
You like the angle my cock goes in?
Yeah, its so deep
in my hot, wet pink box.
I'm going to heaven, baby.
Pump your cock in circles.
Now turn over.
What?
I want your messy hot cum
deep inside my hole!
Now you're seriously horny!
Like this?
This position hurts my back.
I did this
because your body is pretty stiff.
What?
Ninja Sex Position:
Pine Needle Lobster Scissor Hold!
PINE NEEDLE LOBSTER SCISSOR HOLD
What's happening?
You bitch!
Ouch!
Stop it!
I don't want to die!
Take this!
My spine!
It's going to break!
We're just getting started.
You broke my back.
I'm not finished yet.
My superficial wounds will heal.
But what about you?
No, no, no!
Stop!
You are under my spell.
You are under my spell
and you will spread your legs.
You are under my spell.
You cannot resist.
Your body is under my control.
My hands are moving on their own.
What am I doing?
Take it all off.
You are not a ninja.
You're just
a cum gurgling gutter slut.
No, I'm not.
Oh? Is that why
your tits are hanging out?
Soon, you will rub your pussy.
Yes, I want to. (I... no...)
My hands are moving on their own.
Take a good look at my pussy. (No, I don't want this)
A naked ninja.
This is my lucky day.
My body is moving on its own.
Now comes the fun part.
You will do as I say
and get yourself off.
Yes, master. (No... why?)
You cannot resist.
You must obey my commands.
Rub your tits.
Rub it and squeeze it.
Wow!
A ninja is squeezing her tits in front of me!
Next is your pussy.
Rub your clit
until your pussy juice flows.
Stick more fingers in your hole
and move it around.
Yeah, I got two fingers
in my tight wet box. (No, I don't want this.) ???
Keep doing it.
Now come over here
and suck my big hard dick.
That's it. Over here.
I have to suck your cock. (No. I can't do this.)
That's right.
You are under my spell.
It's so big.
Oh, man.
Your tongue's so hot. (Oh, man. More, more.)
She'll do anything for me.
I'll do everything, I've always wanted to do.
Yeah! Sixty-nine!
I've always wanted to do this!
Suck my dick while I lick your pussy.
Stick your hot tongue in my pussy. (I can't do this.)
Hurry up!
Too bad your first sixty-nine is your last.
W-What?
Ninja Sex Position...
PENDULUM FLOWER TRAP HOLD
Pendulum FlowerTrap Hold!
It hurts!
I'm not finished yet.
Do you like it?
Are you happy?
Another one down.
I wanted to play some more.
But he died,
so what can l do?
Is this all you've got?
You call yourself a ninja?
T-This is nothing.
We'll see.
This is a specially constructed rope.
You can't even cut it with a sword.
And in addition...
W-What?
If I pull hard, it will rip your flesh.
It's called "Top Spinner".
You'd better surrender.
No way.
I won't surrender.
Then you will suffer one thousand cuts
on your beautiful body.
You cannot stitch the wounds.
Stitch one wound
and the wound next to it opens up.
You liar.
You're full of shit!
Well, then take this.
Top Spinner!
What
Top Spinner didn't even scratch her.
This woman is a ninja.
She can instantaneously make her body
hard as steel.
I've heard self-hypnotize can do this.
She is already soft again.
The spell must be just for an instant.
Her tits are soft.
She's still unconscious.
This is where she is an amateur.
She's just a novice.
Unconscious and drained of powers.
It looks like she's out for a while.
Totally vulnerable in front of her enemy.
I could kill her anytime.
For fun I'll fuck her instead.
Her box is incredibly tight.
And her pussy is so dripping wet.
I'm going to pump my dick inside her.
Her hole is sucking my cock inside.
Her pussy lips
are wrapped around my shaft.
She's unconscious,
but still getting turned on.
It's as if her pussy is alive.
It's gripping my cock.
Oh! Oh, ohhh...
My balls will explode.
Get on top.
Awesome.
She's still weak.
Yet, she's on top
and moves her ass.
I’m impressed.
I'm speechless.
I'm not weak,
you moron.
Oh, no! (W-What?)
Ninja Sex Position:
Top Spinner!
What?
TOP SPINNER
I'm not finished yet.
Knock it off!
Doesn't it fell good?
Isn't this what you wanted?
We're going to climax!
I spun a little too much.