Ninja 4
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Iga Ninja 500th Anniversary
Little bit more. Hold it 'til he wakes up.
Try to protect. We need to keep fighting.
Yes.
We have for 500 years. We must keep fighting for it.
Iga is such a weak Ninja.
This way.
That's my mission. It's not my taste.
Ah! Saizo, no more...
I'm going to take my clothes off.
Yeah, Yeah...
Ouch!
Every night, you're eaten by a monster
It's going to be intense.
Now... I can't stand anymore.
Ah! Saizo, look I'm so excited...
My tits are so hard and my pussy is so wet...
Saizo, can you hear my pussy's sound?
Ah... good... look at me. Ah... I'm embarrassed. Don't look, Saizo.
Look at me. Oh, no... don't look. Ah...
What do you want?
Ah... your dick in my pussy... ah... your dick in my...
Ah... no... Saizo...
It's going in.
Saizo...
Don't push it too hard... it's going to break...
Ah... please gently...
Saizo...
Ah... I can't sleep.
You really like Saizo, don't you, Shinobu.
Oh my... she came once, so she needs 30 minutes more.
Oh man, I'm going to take a walk.
Ah... I'm doing to cum again... ah...
I wish Aya were here. So she could help Shinobu.
Um? What? Someone is here.
Who is it at this time?
What?
N-No way! Aya...
Aya...
Ouch!
No way... Aya, Aya was...
But that was Aya. I'm sure.
Shinobu, big news. Aya was... There was Aya, Shinobu
Oh, damn...
Stop masturbating every night.
Ouch!
You don't need to hit me, Lena. Ouch hey!
We're going to have Iga festival soon,
but what the fuck are you thinking everyday?
I can't help it, I'm falling in love with Saizo.
How about you, Lena? You don't have anyone you like?
You could be desperate.
What the fuck...
Hell, yeah...
You don't understand my feeling.
Until you love someone.
Hey, Shinobu, you look smart,
but have you seem him once again?
Well...
See, do you think that's love?
I even can masturbate every night.
Don't make me a fool.
Okay, it doesn't sense, something like love, if I can't see him.
Oh no... it's over... I no longer can see him...
No, what are you saying? It... it should be okay.
My love is over.
Oh no. Shinobu. It was an accident. I don't mean it...
That's okay. It's the true. It's over.
Shinobu, don't take it so seriously. Okay?
Shinobu...
Hey, you two.
Ah, the principal!
What happened on the preparations for the Iga Festival?
We don't have enough time, do we?
No, the principal... We have had the meeting for the play.
We have only five days left. Okay?
Yes, of course.
I don't feel like it.
What are you saying? Let's go.
Ah, I saw Aya last night.
It was Aya. Aya is alive.
Aya is still alive?
It's true. I saw her with ninja clothes in the dorm's garden.
Ouch!
Don't listen to her. She is insane.
It's true.
Shut up!
Okay. Let us handle the Iga Festival.
Hey, leave me alone.
Aya is alive...
It's true.
Okay, your next lines,
"I'm going to open your heart with my power of love".
Hey are you listening to me, Shinobu?
There is no such line.
Ah, only Saizo can open my heart.
No such a line!
Shinobu...
Lena, be quiet.
Can you hear it?
Shinobu, what happened?
I can hear it.
Lena, someone is here.
What, what? Who?
There, back of the set scene.
What? What is it, Shinobu?
I don't know, but someone is there.
What? I don't hear anything.
It may be not alive, but...
Lena, let's go.
That's it.
No, what is it?
No, oh, no!
She is Tamura from E class, isn't she?
Fuck! Fucking shit!
She's still alive...still alive...
No... if we move her a little bit, the sharp blade will stick her heart.
She can't move because of that.
She is trying to hold the blade with her muscle.
Oh, no...
Let's try to remove it, Shinobu.
Okay, I'm going to try it carefully.
Please don't move. For five seconds. Don't move...
Yes, yes... little bit more...
Good, a little more...
No...
Oh, no...
She wouldn't die,
if I did it one second faster.
Shinobu, don't blame yourself.
This is Kouga's skill.
It's called "Soondomezashi".
Only Kouga can do this, stopping the blade a little bit before the heart.
And, was that man in the KP school uniform?
Yes.
We saw his right arm inside of her,
and he was dead at a distance.
Okay, and what do you think about this?
I think after the man raped her, he was killed by another.
He was killed by Iga's style,
but she didn't do it under the circumstances.
Okay, so who did it?
I'm afraid to say, but I think...
...Aya did it.
Aya?
Y-Yes.
Y-Yes. I think only Aya can do this,
except Shinobu, in order to fight evenly like Tamura.
Aya is alive.
We're now under the rank C emergence control.
The Iga Festival will go on.
Our enemies are already in our campus, but we don't need to capture them.
Kill them instead.
Wait, principal.
Shinobu,
Kouga is attacking the most delicate part of a woman.
Don't have mercy on our enemy! I'm going to tell you straight out. You're cheated!
Shinobu, I think so, too.
Go now.
No, stop it.
Nice woman. Her pussy is also tight, I heard.
You're Kouga, aren't you? I'm a fiance of Sakai Koutaro.
Do you think nothing will happen doing this?
You're still saying shit?
You don't know anything about it.
He told us to do this.
He told me you look polite, but you're lecherous.
Don't you like to play fingers in you pussy an asshole
Kouga isn't interested in Iga.
You're a very fortunate woman.
Hey let's fuck this woman.
Koutaro orders we're going to fuck her until she'll bleed.
Don't make us a fool. We're not small fry.
Koutaro said, you're easy to wet just for moving your body. Let me see...
Hey, how is it?
What's this? It's drenched. You're feeling too much already.
Okay...
Your body seems to be so good, I heard.
No...
Hey, don't fight.
Take it easy, man. Easy...
Hey, come on.
It looks like she had a pee.
This bitch looks like a squirrel blowing up her cheeks.
She is tightening.
Hey, I'm going to fuck you, bitch.
Okay.
Don't blame me.
It's the order by our boss, Sakai Koutaro.
Here you go.
I won't forgive Kouga.
Never...
Shit! I was to late again.
Shit!
"Soondomezashi" again. It's really Kouga's skill.
Help!
Her womb and intestines are damaged. She won't survive anywas, but
we may be able to get some information.
Hey, who did this to you? Did this man do it to you?
Hey, you're going to be okay...
What?
Woman.
Woman?
What kind of woman?
Fuck!
Fucking shit!
This man is real Kouga, our comrade.
He won't attack Iga.
Killing both cause of silence...
Someone is trying to start trouble between Iga and Kouga. This is a Negoro's trick.
Saizo, there is going to be trouble.
Rank C?
I can't do it alone.
Hope nothing will happen.
What, what, what, what?
Wall, I am a wall. I am a wall.
Okay, I'm going to give you a hot thing.
Nice pretty legs.
Here you go.
Come on, come on, come on...
H-How terrible!
Hey, suck it hard.
Make it wet.
I feel pain.
Hey, girl, you still can take it more...
Don't you like it? Don't you want more?
I need more stimulation.
Hey, girl, give me more stimulation.
No...
It's stuck like a chicken barbecue.
What? What are you doing?
What? He changed his expression.
Ah... oh, my goodness!
Oh, my...
I was patrolling around,
and I saw a woman...
That woman.
Yeah, she was very impressive.
She was sparkling.
It's was so beautiful.
I wonder who she was.
With long hair and with skin...
No way...
Hey, hey, hey...
Ah... Aya?
S-Saizo.
You're naked.
Shinobu, long time no see.
Shinobu, I want you.
W-What are you saying?
Are you dumb? Look at you.
Damn!
I want you.
What?
Please, give me head.
Saizo.
Hey, suck it harder.
What's that? Do it like a professional.
Take it all into you throat.
Yeah, like that...
Work harder, so I can give it to you later in your asshole.
Is this Saizo Whom I know?
I didn't know who he was til now.
I'm going to tell you straight. Your cheated.
Shinobu, I think so, too.
Hey!
Do like a doggie and open your pussy and asshole.
What?
I said doggie style.
Hey, open your legs, hey, bitch.
Hey, it's small.
When you shit, it gets bigger? Hey!
Ah... no...
Hey, your hole is twitching.
No, stop it, Saizo. Please!
Your pussy is also as small as your asshole.
Hey, you're not satisfied with one? It's not enough stimulation, is it?
Okay, I give you two.
Come on... see... you can take them.
Look. Three are not enough...
Hey, it's not enough stimulation, is it?
Let's play something better.
Shinobu!
What? No way!
Shinobu, don't trust him. Kouga is our enemy.
That man is going to kill you.
Shinobu, you have to fight.
This man is not Saizo.
If it's so, he is insane.
I got it. Take it.
Saur, it's your turn.
W-What?
Thanks.
Hey, you did too far, Saizo.
Ah, Aya...
Let me down.
She is very careful, so I need to do it harder.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, Shinobu, I did too much, but it's ok now.
What?
This woman is not your friend. She is a Negoro.
S-Shinobi, don't trust him. Don't trust Kouga.
Shinobu, think carefully. Dead people won't come back.
She may look alive, but she is a tool of Negoro.
No, I'm not.
Shut up, bitch.
Which one should I believe?
Shinobu, don't let him fool you. Kouga is our enemy.
Okay, so you're saying Aya is back?
No my sister is dead.
I'm Ayano, her sister.
I'm her Sister. We're twins.
Ah... Saizo...
Who is that?
Ouch...
That's right.
The principal.
I got a contact from USA Iga,
that Aya's twin sister, Ayano, is coming to Japan.
Ayano is our comrade.
See?
Ayano, I'm going to help you now.
It's getting bad, Saru.
That's right.
Even though you're good, it's over now.
We lost many comrades because of you.
Our guys were also killed by this girl.
You ask for it.
What?
Ayano, you killed the man?
I mentioned it so many times, fool.
Let's kill them.
No, they're not here anymore.
What? Oh, it's too classical.
Eh?
English?
Yup, I can speak English.
Wow! Great!
Nice, so you don't worry about an exam.
Not like that.
Grammar is different than speaking.
But, it's great. Admirable.
Yeah, Aya wasn't good at English.
Moron!
Ummm, that's okay.
But is this okay?
Isn't this Shinobu's bed?
Yes, but it's okay. We can sleep anywhere.
Really?
Really.
Shinobu won't think something weird anymore.
Anymore...
I don't understand.
If Ayano killed the man,
why couldn't she save the girl?
When we arrived, she was still alive.
She had enough time...
Saizo,
who are you?
Umm? What?
Ayano is gone.
I'm here now.
You already understand, don't you?
Yes.
They're still on the campus. One is injured. You must kill him, okay?
Go now.
Yes.
She could be... Iga's savior...
Here she comes.
She's here.
Be careful.
Saru, be cautious. It's a poison pin.
Saizo, look up. She can fly.
Shit! She can do this thing.
Shit! Fucking bitch!
W-What?
Kill her, kill her.
Kill her.
What's this?
That's Ayano.
Is she beaten or attacking?
Saru, start the game.
Interesting!
Go!
Lena...
Hey, I take care of you.
No...
Shall we play, too?
Don't say, no.
No, Saizo...
Shit.
Those two... two guys are...
What?
Stop them.
Ah... what are you doing, fool? Kill her.
Kill her!
Who are you going to kill?
You?
Do you think you can kill me with that?
Yeah,
this knife is enough.
You're cocky.
If I stab the right place.
What?
You are...
over there.
Ayano!
Ayano?
She is okay.
She is in "Soondome".
Can you remove the poison pin from her?
Not yet.
We don't know if she is on our side or not.
Where...
am I?
Ayano.
Your eye color changed. You're back.
A-Ayano.
What's going on?
This girl was manipulated.
She did all of that,
so Iga and Kouga can fight against each other.
But,
she's very strong, even though she was under control.
Our enemy is very serious.
I avoided her trick,
because I was in pain.
You played again.
Ah, Saru...
he might be in danger...
Ah... good... Osaru...
Lena, I'm Saru... not Osaru.
Osaru...
I'm not Osaru.
Hey... hey...
Did you let him run?
Yes.
He ran so fast...
That's right. He was very brawny...
What's going on?
Tomorrow we're going to have Iga Festival. Watch our Kouga carefully.
You can go now.
Yes.
Why mini, fool?
That's okay. No one will notice.
Are you sure?
She is a huge woman.
You look pretty.
Shut up, fool.
Oh, here the are.
I love to open up your heart
by my power of love.
Ah really? Only you can open my heart.
Yes, even though we're in different tribes,
our love is forever.
Ah... I'm happy.
Come to me.
Hey, what a dumb play this is!
I don't understand, but it's a very important play for Iga.
It has been playing the last 500 years.
Look.
Here is the sun rising by our power of love.
So nice, love...
love...
Yes, love...
Love is everything.
Kill them,
both of them.
Kill them.
Reiko, remember.
Remember the scars on your breasts.
Remember who did it to you.
Your scars won't disappear forever.
You chose to work for the school
because of those scars.
Isn't it because you want revenge on Kouga?
Your enemy is over there.
Kill them.
Iga magic,
a thousand cherry trees.
Here comes.
Yes.
Hey girl, you want a cup of tea?
Saizo, don't loaf.
What? Encore?
What are you saying?
Our principal is fighting now.
But that is Iga magic,
Thunder Lightning.
What?
You'll fall in a faint for 3 days if you use it...
Saizo is attacked....
Oh shit. That's Thunder Lightning.
I need to watch out for it.
Shinobu...
Shinobu, no...
I can stop it before it makes full voltage.
Shit! It's too late.
Shinobu.
We did it.
Saizo?
Saizo why,
are you naked?
Shinobu.
Come here.
Shinobu,
I love you.
Saizo,
I love you, too.
Shinobu,
you're already wet.
You feel it so easily.
Shinobu, do you feel this?
Shinobu
Yes, good.
Beautiful,
Shinobu.
Come here,
Saizo.
Make love to me.
I have been waiting for you for a long time.
S-Shinobu.
I can feel you dick.
Ready, Shinobu?
Saizo... please...
W-What?
I can see you want my Thunder Lightning over there.
Damn! Iga and Kouga are united now.
We have wait for 500 years again.
I shouldn't use the Negoro.
Saizo...
Are you awake, Saizo...
Are you okay?
Yes... but, what's going on?
I don't know, but... our principal was trying to give Thunder Lighting...
Yeah,
she was trying on me, but
Yes, and...
I don't know, but I need to get up.
S-Shit,
I'm inside of you, Shinobu.
Sai...
I'm still hard now.
Saizo...
Shinobu,
shall we go on?
No, Saizo...
No?
I don't get it, but at least we saved a crisis.
Look. My dick is in you.
Ah... it's moving.
See.
Saizo...
Shinobu.
Ah... great... your dick is inside of me.
Shinobu, you're tight... you're tightening.
Ah... fuck me...
Ah... Shinobu...
Shinobu...
Saizo I'm cumming...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Are you okay?
Sorry to bother you, but...
Oh, Saru, you look fine.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Oh, I don't know it, either.
Fool!
Oh! Shit!
Saizo, don't move it.
Oh, don't use that alluring voice.
What? What happen, Saizo.
No more... ah...
Saizo.
What? Did I and Saizo win against Satan?
Yes.
Satan was using a lot of tricks trying to fix my memory,
or manipulating Ayano by Negoro.
He tried to make Iga fight against Kouga.
I was failed sometimes, but
I tried to use energy from Thunder Lightning
to stop time for a moment...
I gambled on you, Shinobu.
On me?
Yes.
But I didn't do anything...
I thought you might have some kind of hidden power.
I didn't know what it was, but...
I just played... with Saizo...
That's it.
The power that we, ninja usually forget...
The power of love, you have this.
That's why we could become one again.
Iga and Kouga become one,
no enemy can stand against us.
We're originally from one tribe.
This seems to be as same as the play.
Yes.
There was an answer inside of the play that we have been playing
for the last 500 years.
I see...
That's about it.
Okay now.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Leno and Shinobu.
Yes.
Love one is waiting for you.
What?
Our new comrade.
Hey, Shinobu.
Let's drive around.
What's that?
They are not matched.
Don't say it. Go now.
Don't worry about today's class.
Hey, hold tight.
Help me!
Hey, Saizo, don't play dumb.
No, Osaru...
I'm Saru.
My memory was switched to a nasty thing.
Satan is a terrible enemy.
But...
after I got my memory back, my scars disappeared.
Well, I can find a boyfriend now.
Ayano!
What a frumpy car!
It's okay. Get in!
Let's drive around.
Let's have fun.
Hurry, Ayano.
Okay.
End!