Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Hahaha, what is that? Do you think that would
surprise me, the great Reiko Shinjo?
Un baya sowaka, an baya sowaka.
Come on, even some phony preacher of
some religion clan could do that.
Fufufu, you won't be talking for long.
There there, your cells are being energized.
By the means of levitation, your adrenalin and
hemoglobin merges to increase the cholesterol level.
Sounds bad for your health.
Shut up! Ooh, it's coming, coming, it's here!
What? A giant octopus?
Take this!
My sucker's are as strong as the leech.
Once stuck, you'll never come loose.
When it separates, it'll rip your skin off!
Oh no!
You better watch out!
My mucus is highly poisinus,
so it'll melt your clothes and your skin!
Oh my!
Shit, this is a strong substance.
No, my clothes instantly...
Hahaha, next is your body.
There now, I'll melt your pussy!
Hahaha, with my spell,
the head Kunoichi can't do anything.
In five minutes, your bones would disappear!
I must do something, I underestimated him.
I have to bite him and tear my way out!
Kunoichi, you do pretty well.
But my body regenerates itself.
Next time you get caught it will be your end.
It won't be that easy!
Fool!
No, I was easily caught!
This is the end of you.
I thought with your reputation this would be hard.
But it'll raise my status by killing you.
Ready to die?
No, I'm really going to die.
Huh?
That's his dick.
I see the energy doesn't protect his cock.
Take this! Kunoichi flying claws!
Behold, the horny Kunoichi rider!
This technique of pumping up and down
only by using the pussy .
No cock can handle this.
How sad is it that your body changed,
but your cock didn't.
Damn! Why do weird guys keep showing up?
Fufufu, I, Chindoukouraku,
won't be easy like others!
Yea, your nastiness surpass the others.
My specialty is different from others.
So, it's going to shoot out something to rip my clothes
and make me naked or something?
No, no, no, why do you know?
I speculated it.
Oh, then this is it. Take this!
Oh shit!
I'll make the needle stretch out.
It'll keep on growing until it hits your heart.
This is the end of you.
No! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Useless!
The more you twitch, the further it'll go.
Can't miss out on this,
so I'll fuck this hot chick. Suck this!
Oh, the head of Kunoichi is sucking
and spitting on my cock!
Observe, this is the art of the sparrow counter!
Aah, ouch!
What the heck!
Gradually you'll lose your consciousness.
When I cum, you'll die. It feels so good.
Fucking baldy , acting so tough!
Wha, wha, wha, what?
Horny Kunoichi earth specialty!
Hah, my specialty is different from others too!
Hehehe, you're no match.
l was wondering who the head of Kunoichi is,
and I find out that she's a lusty bitch.
Shut up, damn!
Look, the Shinobi world is a dog eat dog world.
Doesn't matter if you're fine or beautiful, bitch!
Fucking prick!
You slut, what do you mean "prick"?
Ouch, stop it already!
Just because you think you're
beautiful with a nice body?
Shit, I feel like messing up your face!
Now, where should I kick next?
Noooo!
Drooling wet pussy.
Does it feel good spinning around?
Hey, hey, hey, it's going in!
Fucking prick! ouch, ouch!
Stop the dancing!
You fucking prick!
I told you to stop!
Feet pounding steps. There, there...
Hey prick, better not think
that you can do this forever!
Take this step of hell!
Horny Kunoichi reverse dancing of hell!
Fucking prick, can't dance for shit.
This is how you really step your steps!
He has no weakness.
You are full of weaknesses.
Shut up!
You'll die if you get hit on the right side.
That doesn't mean your left side is safe either .
No matter what, you won't get away from my blades.
Man, shut up!
How should I do this?
Regretfully, he's right.
I may really die.
I have to make him lose focus.
Take this!
What the?
He didn't even raise an eyebrow.
Are you an amateur?
What?
Kunoichi girls don't attract me!
W-What?
You should understand I'm going easy on you right
now. I could have killed you three times in that instant.
The next move will be you end.
Now, where do you want the lethal incision?
Oh no, this guy is real!
Looks like you've been fighting weak opponents,
but have pride that the real thing is killing you.
Horny Kunoichi flying claw!
Wha, What?
Weak stuff!
Fufufu, I can tell that you have no experience
with close range combats.
Maybe you never touched female skin before.
No, go away , go away from me...
Female skin smells wonderful, doesn't it?
Please, stop! I need mommy , mommy...
What the heck, he's a mama's boy!
Mommy!
Okay, if you miss mama that much,
I'll return you to mommy!
Horny ninja pussy sucking consumption!
Behold the suction of Reiko Shinjo!
Mommy! Mommy!
How do you like the taste of Reiko's pussy?
Help me, mommy!
It's spinning around!
How is it? Take this!
Hey, hey, taste more of this!
I only tasted mommy's stuff. Mommy!
Shut up with your whining!
I bet your mama doesn't do this!
This guy's pretty good. We've been fighting
over an hour, but he's not losing a breath.
One false move will end my life.
You're Reiko Shinjo. Looks like you're
different from others, but still, a pest.
How should I take care of this?
Shut up, stop the talking and bring it on!
You're stumped. You won't last another five minutes...
You are a girl, but I have no
sympathy. I can't fight a pussy.
What? You perverted bastard!
Three hits in that instant! Shit!
No, four hits.
You should take a close look at the pussy .
I snuck in my serpent in there.
W-What is this?
This is related to the parasite bug,
which will go inside your body and eat everything.
Shit! No, it went in!
Once the bug's inside, your body becomes numb.
I'm gonna take you down!
Shit, my body won't listen to me.
There is no hope.
Art of pounding bear!
A weak opponent, with no will to fight.
Soon the bug will eat up the intestines.
She has a nice ass.
If she wasn't a ninja, I would have made her great.
Take this as your fate.
She has such nice curves.
I stuck in the bug in too early.
With this high potential,
I should not have used the bugs.
My sorrowful error.
But once the bugs are in,
trying to remove it could take me down.
So I shall pleasure myself by watching
This is a nice pussy.
Shit, this is one good pussy out of thousands,
maybe millions.
Man, I should have hit it once.
My mistake. It's still moving!
Shut up!
Take this,
horny Kunoichi crab crunching pussy attack!
I can't breathe...
The power of Reiko,give up?
No, let go!
Feel the power of Reiko!
No, let go...
Let go, let go!
There, I'll give you back the bugs!
No, shit!
The bugs backfired on you!