Hold it, why are you giving me this!?
If this was washed, shouldn't it be clean?
What about the other clothes?
Isn't it obvious?
But, there's a lot of clothes, right?
Just bear with it for today..
Why do I have to bear it anyway?
Since we're family, more or less...
What I wanted wasn't a family!
You're just an inconvenience to me..
B-But.. inconvenience..?
Why are you using the same perfume?
T-That was a present from him..
Using the same thing as me; that's absolutely unacceptable!
Same thing? But it was a present for my husband..
That's why it's unacceptable!
That perfume.. Don't ever use it again!
Miki-chan?
That bastard...
X-Fap Presents:
Hold it! What the hell is this!?
As you can see, it's an interesting photo..
Not interesting one bit..
Is that so?
Then how about showing it to others
and hearing their thoughts?
That's enough of your jokes, such a fake picture...
Fake you say?
Obviously! I wouldn't allow such a picture of me..
Unlike you, my case is different... I'd be troubled if any rumors arise!
W-What's your purpose?
Wasn't it written in the mail too?
Because you're too noisy, so be quiet..
You're in University, can't you read by yourself?
Why you-
Hey, what did I say just now?
I said you're too noisy, I want you to be quiet..
The problem is quite simple...
Will Sis listen to her little brother-to-be... or not?
You...
Really, then...
Under the instructions of the Father, she reluctantly gave a wry smile...
Her ass and pussy was exposed...
What's with you? I was just reading the phone novel...
By the way, that sensual novel.. did you know about it, Sis?
I don't know about such a thi-
Maybe.. She's doing it with her real father in the novel, right?
So, there shouldn't be a problem with me reading it..
It was you, right Sis? Who wrote this novel...
You keep calling me a "mother-con," and yet you're a "father-con".
How'd you-
Now, Sis.. Let me hear the answer to earlier...
If you say YES, then this photo and fiction will be sealed away.
If you say NO, then this will end up in front a lot of people.
Starting with daddy, I guess..
I-I understand... Yes..
Even though you were exceedingly bright and dignified before
How come your voice vanishes when things go sour?
Really, convenient.
YES, I said YES!
A negotiation has been made, I'm glad..
No matter who the person is,
a strange rumor spreading is always troublesome...
S-So, what do you want from me?
Let's see.. for now, how about a study session?
Study?
This is a very important study, so I want your help Sis...
It's a very important study...
Say it out straight then, I want to get this over with quickly..
Yes, I'd like you to teach me about the woman's body, Sis.
A-Are you serious?
Of course, because you see..
You see, I'm a ronin due to misfortune and with so much time..
This is the kind of study I can't do alone, don't you agree?
In short, you wanna violate me!?
You really can't listen, eh..
Or maybe you're making fun of me..?
Screw it, I didn't expect you to respect or understand me anyway..
Then, what is it you want!?
Let's see, for now I wanna see you masturbate..
You didn't hear me?
You're a university student after all.. you've probably become skilled at sex or masturbation..
T-That's..
What? Is that mumbling supposed to mislead me?
I've... had experiences in both...
Then masturbation should be familiar, right?
I think so..
Talking about yourself, but you're being unclear..
I don't know how much of it is considered ordinary..
I see, then in that case..
Where do you feel it most?
T-There I guess..
I can't hear you..
M-My pussy!
Anywhere else?
My nipples, and.. anus.
Oh, you even play with your ass, Sis..
Y-Yeah..
Now it's getting exciting somewhat..
Oh yeah, do it like this...
Okay, let me see you play with your asshole and pussy while masturbating.
My life with papa had been a bit dissatisfying, but still I was content..
Then he got remarried; it was that widow's fault..
Now unpleasant things are getting more depressing...
However, this is the worst!
This guy was videotaping, and even making fake pictures..
No, am I really gonna come from this?
How far will this go?
Could this be my punishment for loving Papa?
Hey Sis, you have to show your colleague properly..
If you don't spread them more, I can't see better, Sis..
Looks like observing you got me all big now..
How about doing it with your mouth?
How am I gonna do something that big!?
Besides, you said only masturbation..
Anyway, this situation is turning worse..
I did say to show me..
But I didn't say "I didn't want anything else."
But.. to put it in my mouth or lick it..
You're not gonna say "No," right?
I-I understand, just licking..
Yeah, and keep on masturbating.
Under normal conditions, I would have rejected without a thought..
I was caught off guard..
Now, I can't refuse..
Even now, I'm being obedient..
Quickly, just let this nightmare end..
Hey, your hand's not moving...
Oh yeah, stick a finger in your asshole too..
But.. I've never put my fingers there..
We have an agreement, don't we?
Or would you rather I put it in?
I understand, I understand...
It hurts..
Enough? This should be enough, right?
Push it in deeper..
I can't go any further..
Hurry up!
My fingers are going in.. my asshole..
Here, hold this tightly too!
It's hurts..
Here, drink it all and
if you spill it I'll punish you.
Spilling this much; looks like this calls for punishment..
No! Tha-
It went in.. went in..
Just being this wet, and I'm already in your depths..
Not just my mouth, even my pussy is being violated..
You seem to be enjoying yourself..
Not one bit!
This guy is rather young, but his cock is dreadful...
Happy even though you're being violated forcefully;
you must be a natural-born deviant, Sis!
I'm not happy.. it hurts!
My voice is just from you violating me..
Then, you're not feeling it, right?
I'm not.. feeling it..
I'm not feeling it at all...
Then, there's no way you'll come, right?
If you do come, I'll give you another punishment..
I won't come even from you..
Then, how about here?
No!
If you tease my asshole, I can't control myself!
No! Not my asshole!
Coming! I'm coming!
Semen.. inside me.. all of it..
Shot inside...
This is too much..
That's because you grabbed me tightly, Sis...
Going on and deciding by yourself..
By the way, you lied about not feeling it so here's the next punishment..
Stop already! You came and you're still not satisfied!?
Too early, I can shoot it at least three times..
Because I seem to have accumulated a lot of stress.
No! No, stop!
Please, stop!
No, take it out..
If you get this rough, I'll really.. I'll really..
..Really c-come..
No...
No, No.. I'm really coming..!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Not yet, we're just getting started, Sis..
Ah, by the way...
Starting tomorrow, I'll be working away for a while, probably go a month or so..
No way! Papa, don't go!
What wrong? A month will pass quickly..
What, gonna be lonely?
But you'll be fine, this time you have a family..
That's why-
What.. still shy about the matter?
Anyway, I'm leaving both of them in your care, Ryouichi-kun...
Sure, you can rest assured..
Of course, I'll take care of that too..
Stop!
Being ravaged, and raped..
Seen in shame, yet..
At that time.. I really felt it..
Even now, I want it..
I want to be violated like that by my son..
Wha-!? What did I just..?
As I thought, that must've been Ryouichi.
But, I want Ryouichi.
If this keeps on, I'll really lose myself..
I'll turn from human into beast...
Mail? At this hour?
If you don't want yesterday's events to
be exposed, then come to the park now
As I thought... Ryouichi..
Nobody's here...
Go to the park's toilet and enter the furthest compartment.
"Put this on and wait?"
How can this be? I'm getting excited just from being blindfolded..
N-No! I can't get carried away!
Right now, I need to confirm if it's Ryouichi or not..
No!
This smell, it reeks yet.. it's overwhelming.
I understand, I'll do it now...
So warm and big..
Just the tip, yet it's so big..
I'm afraid of just swallowing this much..
This shape, odd yet big..
However, his rod's thickness is moderate..
I... know this taste well... Ryouichi..
Am I... the object of Ryouichi's lust?
When did he start to desire me as a woman?
Ah, you're about to come?
Yes, hurry, come..
Pour your hot stuff into my mouth!
Ah, such thickness..
This is Ryouichi's...
More.. I want more..
No... we can't do such a thing... We can't!
No, stop! Ryouichi!
It's Ryouichi, isn't it? We can't.. do this..
That's... that's..
No...
I'm begging you.. anymore of this.. anymore is..
It's useless.. I can't..
Inside.. you really can't come inside!
Please understand, I'm begging you... So please!
No!!
It's coming, it's coming out..
Ryouichi's hot stuff is coming inside me!
No! It's coming.. it's coming out!
Ryouichi... Why?
How am I supposed to talk to him?
But.. if this keeps on..
Sis, this here is very sensitive even though you're a virgin.. right?
No, you can't put that in there.. Let it go!
No, don't!  Don't touch that place!
You can't! Stop! It hurts! It hurts!
No... pull it out, pull it out...
Not a chance, because this is punishment..
No! My ass... My ass can't take it!
It hurts... it hurts... don't...
Stop...
I'm begging you... to... pull it out...
The truth is you wanted someone to play with your asshole like this..
That's not.. true! no!
Don't move anymore, you're spreading my ass!
No... it hurts... no more... stop!
My asshole is getting torn up!
There's only one way to end this, you know..
No way...
What are you?
I thought your pussy was overflowing but it turned out to be my cum..
No! Stop already!
You're satisfied, right?
I'm begging you, stop!
With this, I've conquered all your holes now...
I'll memorialize this day's end by coming in your ass!!
T-Today, wh-
My insides feel hot!
My asshole is on fire!
You even stole my anal virginity..
Ryouichi!
So, you've come...
Mom, you need me.. as a male..
No, I want to talk..
You do realize that it was me who raped you..
Besides, the one that struck first was you, mom!
Before marrying that person..
Mom, you gave me a sleeping drug.. then snuck in later, didn't you?
No way... You realized it then?
Yes, I noticed...
It was your first time doing something like this, right Mom?
That night was indeed totally my fault.
Even now I regret it.
But I already know, that Mom wants to have sex with me, right?
That's why I took the first step..
Ryouichi...
The faces you make when you do it with him and when you do it with me, are totally different..
You enjoyed it when I fucked you, right Mom?
No, no, no.. You're wrong Ryouichi!
You didn't get enough at the park, right?
Here, I'll give you more..
No, no! Ryouichi, stop!
Don't, no.. Stop..
Please, stop..
No, no...
No... no!
Ryouichi, please.. take it out..
Don't.. no.. take it out..
Mom, you're feeling it, right?
Come on, I'll give it where you like it, Mom..
No, not there.. no..
Fe- I'm feeling it.. no..
No.. no..
No, if you keep going, I'll...
Just be honest!
No more.. I can't.. I'm feeling it..
I'm feeling Ryouichi's cock!
You're honest with yourself now.. good..
It's hitting me so deep.. It's so good!
Thrust your cock into my pussy more!
Fuck me senseless!
So good, my tits feel so good..
More, suck it more...
It's so good, give me more!
Here.. my other tit too..
So good~ more, do that more..
I'm feeling it.. Feeling it..
Release all of your desires into this shameful body of mine!
Ryouichi! Ryouichi! Ryo-chan!
It's coming out! Into me..
Y-you two.. What are-?
Oh, you're awake..
Guess Mom was loud..
Sorry..
What's.. going on?
I have no idea...
It's a new family, just the three of us..
This is a joke right? Being violated by my little brother was bad enough..
What are you gonna do now?
Sounds good, let's do that, Ryouichi..
Junko-san?
No, what are you doing?
No more, Junko-san..
Let's get along with each other better, Miki-chan..
No-
No.. I'm feeling it..
I'm feeling it, too..
Well then, I hope the three of you get along well..
Yes, take care..
P-Papa!
Now now, Miki-chan.. See your father off properly.
Take care..
Ryouichi-kun is still sleeping?
Yes, it seems he was up studying until a late time..
Is that so.. Well then I'll be going..
Be careful, okay?
He's gone?
Yes~
Then let's start..
Our new family life..
Team X-Fap:
TL:
BlessedR
Raw Provider:
Mydoom
Timer:
SatsujinShinzou
Typesetting:
Fukkii
Encoder:
TLC/Editor:
Alist1
www.ExtremeFap.wordpress.com
irc.rizon.net #xfap