Ryouichi, I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
Ryouichi, I'm sorry,
I'm really sorry.
Such a thing is unforgivable.
I know a mother shouldn't do this...
But just tonight, just this once!
I won't do something like this again, okay?
So, just this once, forgive me!
Such a thick cock.. it's becoming so hard...
Good.. so good..
No.. my lustful voice is coming out...
I'm a failure mother, aren't I?
Mixing the sleeping pills with your
dinner.. even sneaking in this like..
It's getting bigger again..
My pussy feels hot.. so hot..
Shove your cock deeper into me, give it to me!
Just this once, f-forgive me please...
You're coming, right? You're coming, aren't you?
Good! So good! Give it to me!
Today's a safe day, so
give me all you've got inside!
Come! Let my pussy indulge in it! Come!
It's coming! Cum!
It's filling up my pussy!
I'm sorry...
This will be the last time...
Tomorrow will be just as
usual.. so please forgive me..
I'm so sorry..
I'm the one at fault, for seeing this kind of dream...
I should be the one apologizing..
X-Fap Presents:
Ryouichi~
Good morning, I'm making breakfast now. Just wait a little, okay?
Alright.
Nevertheless, seeing such a dream...
Ryouichi, I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
Ryouichi, I'm sorry.
I know a mother shouldn't do this...
What the hell am I thinking?!
The dream of me and mom having sex..
Such things don't just happen.
By the way, could you do me a favor?
There's a garbage bag over there..
Could you please?
The garbage truck is coming soon..
I got it..
What?
Nothing..
What's this? The useless F-ranked fail student taking out the trash?
It suits you..
You should make a living just like that..
Ah, Miki-chan you're up as well..
So what? Am I an inconvenience?
Even so, what a terrible
smell so early in the morning..
Is this a public dinner?
Food suiting for the poor.
Can I go take out the trash?
Do as you like...
Alone, my mother raised me and soon re-married.
Her partner from a rich family, in Shinjuku.
On the outside, we seem like a happy family I suppose..
The daughter from my mom's second marriage..
My sister-in-law, to be.. Miki-san..
No matter what we do, she treats us as enemies...
Plus, she attends a Women's University..
Compared to me, I failed twice..
Moreover, my expenses
have been covered my stepfather.
Miki-san just sees my mom
as someone who married for money.
Therefore, everything she spits out is sarcasm.. sarcasm.. sarcasm..
I don't like the fact that she came here, either.
Probably, the happiest person in this marriage is...
Ryouichi, good morning!
My mom's partner, Fujisaki Touru...
Where have you been?
Could it be that you were out all night?
I just went to take out the trash.
Oh I see, helping out.. Well done, well done.
This guy, took my mother.
That's right, Papa...
An artist's circle is gonna happen soon...
Oh, Which are you gonna go to?
Nasu? or maybe Karuizawa?
To Nasu, their Country Club Management is better..
Thank you for taking out the trash, Ryouichi.
Ah, how rare to have the family all together.
This is my family now..
Just a show of a family, a fake figure..
Miki-chan, where are you going today?
Community activities.
Is that so; what about lunch?
I don't want any, I'll be coming back late today..
That's not good, girls shouldn't be out at night..
Besides, Touru-san didn't mention this.
Cut it out! Stop acting
like a mother I don't even need!
Papa, will be late as well today...
Mom...
What is it?
You shouldn't care too much about it.
No, I'm not paying enough attention..
Especially an old woman like me..
You're not an old lady, mom!
Ryouichi?
Anyway, don't worry about it...
I guess so..
When I said that, mom's
smile from long ago appeared..
Even if it's just the two of us,
I want to protect her smile...
I want to always see that smile..
No good, I can't focus at all..
Guess I'll grab a drink..
Touru-san...
Touru-san, you're more lively than usual...
It's because I have all this stress piled up..
Oh, Touru-san..
It's been a while, so prepare yourself..
Are you worried about me?
It's the husband's obligation..
Miki and Ryouichi are good children, I know they'll get along well.
What's he saying?!
He doesn't know a thing about mom's troubles!
It's good, Touru-san.
Damn, mom!
Coming, I'm coming.. I can't...
I can't go on...
I'm coming!
Coming!
I'm very happy right now..
That guy, got his hands on that which I can't..
No... He took it..
I-I want to know more about my mom!
I wanna have sex!
Mom, I'll destroy it soon..
this dirty lie, this make-believe family..
Well then, I'm leaving for a bit..
Okay, Be careful, Mom.
Living with Touru-san is going well..
..I thought I would be leading the same inconvenient life.
But,
Miki-chan sees me as an enemy..
And Ryouichi isn't opening his heart to Touru-san...
Even though I married for his sake..
I committed the unforgivable that night..
Maybe, I remarried to get rid of the guilt..
I'm a failure as a mother
But, what if it had remained just the two of us?
No!
St-Stop!
Th-That's!
No! Don't! Stop!
Don't, it hurts.. no, let me go!
No!
Wait! I'm begging you.
I have a husband and a child!
Am I gonna get raped?
Oh, no...
If something that big goes in me, I'll...
No! No!
Ah~ It's big.. going in...
It's bigger than his
No, No! take it out!
No..
My voice is coming out, even though I'm being raped.
I'm being violated, yet, I'm feeling this cock.
It's different from my husband's, such a violent cock...
No, I can't lose myself.. no..
I know I shouldn't.. but it feels so good..
Shortly, I couldn't resist anymore..
What a shameful woman I am..
If you rub my breasts like that... I'm sorry!
Darling, I'm sorry!
No! Not so hard!
No.. Not like that!
This feeling... could it be?
No, stop!
No, absolutely not!
You can't do it inside, no!
Stop, please stop!
I'm still in my period
So please, don't shoot it inside! I'm begging you..
N-no!
No! No! Pull it out!
Stop!
Even though I told you.. not to..
I'm sorry, Darling.. I'm sorry, Ryouichi.
I did it! There's no turning back now...
The rest depends on mom keeping quiet about it.
I know, I just have to confirm it..
As I thought, they're going at it...
It seems mom hasn't mentioned the event at the park.
As long as this flow keeps up..
Mom will eventually betray that person..
And if you get pregnant..
You'll make him think it's his child..
After all.. I cream pied you..
Hiding it for the sake of your
husband... this is what happens..
Next, I'll have that woman sharing my destiny..
Because.. I know..
You and I.. are the same..
My Papa...
My one and only, Papa...
I love you, Papa..
Not just as my father, but also as a man...
Yet... now you've become that woman's...
Look at me, Papa, look.. My breasts and my pussy..
Papa, look at me down there...
See, I've become a woman completely...
No..
I'm being watched..
My.. pussy.. papa's.. papa's big cock...
Give it to me right there..
It's hot... so hot, Papa.
I'm scared, Papa..
I-I'm falling!
No...
Papa, my asshole.. such a place.. no..
Doing such a thing to your daughter is not good...
Coming! I'm gonna come because of Papa!
I'm coming! coming!
These peeping photos alone won't do it..
Next, I need a phone shot..
I'll do that..
Mom drinks this when she
can't sleep, I bet it's effective..
With this.. no matter
what she drinks after the shower..
My bad for being socially withdrawn..
I was free, so I came to play..
How's that? The cock of the little brother you hate..
Sis, open your mouth..
Tonight won't be a dream of daddy..
But rather, a nightmare of your mouth being violated..
Here, that's good Sis.. suck it more..
This is good! so good!
You're servicing the little brother you always make fun of!
I gonna come in your mouth!
Come on, not done yet..
Serves you right!
I got violated.. then kept quiet about it..
That's right.. It would just trouble and worry him.
Besides, I have something to protect... Ryouichi..
M-Mom...
S-Sorry, I thought no one was here..
R-Ryouichi....
What is it, Mom?
I must've surprised you, sorry...
Just when did he become so handsome...
Stop!
Th-That's!
No! Stop!
No..
No... no..
No!
It can't be.. I just over thinking it, right?
Could Ryouichi have...?
Just a little more, Mom...
I love you.. my one and only mom..
Wait for me...
Team X-Fap:
TL:
BlessedR
Raw Provider:
Mydoom
Timer:
Fukkii
2nd Timer:
Snatch
Typesetting:
Fukkii
TLC/Editor:
Alist1
www.ExtremeFap.wordpress.com
irc.rizon.net #xfap