What's all that about, Yu?
Doing that with your sister...
It's not that I like Yuu or anything!
And he's my half-brother.
Hey Kuri, those panties are mine.
Wait, Kuri!
Kuri!
She went into Yu's room...
X-Shinigami Amateur Subbing Guild presents:
Yu, you there?
What? Still taking a nap?
Kuri?
That's so naughty, just what are you thinking of?
It became so big.
Just for a bit...
It's so hard, and...
so warm.
Eh? Anzu-neechan?
What're you doing?
N-Nothing!
Neechan, you were touching my...
penis weren't you?
Shut up, so what if I touched it?
It's your fault. It's only afternoon but it's already so big.
Hurry up and make it smaller.
Don't say it like it's so simple...
Well, it'll get smaller if you "relieve" it.
Idiot! Pervert!
But I can't help it.
And there's no other way.
Other than "relieving" it, there's no other way?
But if were to do it myself, it's kind of...
Hey.
Can I, umm...
Help you out with it?
Do we really need to do this?
Yea, since Anzu-neechan wanted to help me out didn't you?
I got it.
Just this once.
Wow! I'm only rubbing it with my panties and it's already throbbing so much.
Anzu-neechan, not so fast.
If it's too good, I'll come immediately.
What's that? Pervert.
It's becoming so huge in my panties.
What's this?
Something wet and sticky came out from the tip.
It's kinda like the juice that flows from my pussy when I masturbate.
Anzu-neechan masturbates?
Stop making me say perverted things, damn you!
Anzu-neechan, that's too fast...
Serves you right, this is your punishment.
You have to tell me when you're coming.
Sorry.
Oh no, it didn't become smaller?
Seems like it.
You won't be satisfied with just this, right?
What should I do then?
Yea... how about...
Hey, this is embarrassing.
Make it smaller quick.
Sorry, Anzu-neechan.
But it needs more stimulation than this.
O-Ok...
If that's the case...
Anzu-neechan...
I'm not sure how good this will be since it's the first time.
Anzu-neechan is getting wet.
She's feeling it too.
Collect her juices, or the curse won't be lifted.
This again?
Yu, what's happening?
Nothing.
Now then, let me collect the juice.
Just what are you doing?
It's not right if only me will feel good so I'll do it for you too.
No, if you're doing that...
Let's feel good together.
Great, your pussy juice is pouring non-stop.
Idiot, don't say such embarrassing things.
I'm feeling good...
Those breasts feel awesome.
Liquid flowing from your cock are making my breasts wet...
Anzu-neechan's juice is great too.
I can't stop already.
Anzu-neechan, I'm almost...
You're coming again?
Come, release all that you've got all over my breasts.
Anzu-neechan, let's come together.
You made my pussy so wet.
I'm coming!
Me too, I'm coming too... coming!
You're so naughty, it's so much...
But you're satisfied now after releasing so much, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
About that...
No way!
That's enough, Anzu-neechan.
I'll feel bad for you if we continue.
But...
Could it be that...
You want more of it?
Eh? That's...
You're going to stick it in me this time, right?
I'm a bit scared.
Don't worry, I'll be gentle.
Ok... here.
Take it all from me.
I'm going in.
Sorry Anzu-neechan, does it hurt?
It's fine, I'll bear with it.
Then I'll...
It's fully inside now.
Really?
It feels so tight inside Anzu-neechan.
Your cock moved a bit just now.
It won't be painful anymore, relax.
You're not moving?
It's alright for now.
If you're not moving, then it wouldn't feel good right?
Not really.
It's ok, don't worry about me.
But...
Anzu-neechan...
If you're not going to move Yu, then I will.
Neechan.
I get it.
You ok?
Keep going...
Anzu-neechan's... insides...
I'm slowly feeling it when your cock rubs my pussy inside.
I'm feeling good too.
That's great.
Your cock is inside me.
More, I'll let you feel more of it.
I feel something coming from my body...
Hold it in.
Anzu-neechan, I'm coming soon...
Me too...
Whitish liquid.
It's so hot.
I'm sorry, I came so much.
It's ok. It's my first time but I came.
Anzu-neechan.
How long do I need to follow that tube's orders...
Was that...Kuri?
How long are you going to stand there alone?
Ryoko-nee.
What you're doing here?
Nothing.
Could you be thinking of doing ecchi things to neechan?
No way! We're still relatives even if we're not real siblings.
I won't do it again.
I'm joking, just joking.
Idiot, are you still thinking of that?
For Yu, we're really just his sisters.
You're gonna leave us someday when someone important shows up.
Right?
I-I guess.
So while we're here, let us take care of you like sisters always do.
Got it?
Don't worry, we all love you Yu.
You like this?
Your cock is so big already.
You know, Miss Nurse...
My cock is reaching its limit.
Alright, leave it to me.
Cover oneesan's breasts with all your sperm.
Wearing my old school uniform for this...
is actually quite exciting.
Miss Nurse...
It's so hard and hot.
Doing it to my breasts...
Your nipples...
They got hard.
Because its feeling so good.
I'm already...
Come, release it all out.
Heh, it's getting hard again.
This naughty cock.
You think so?
Now its time for penetration.
Miss Nurse...
Are you ready?
My pervert patient.
Yeah.
Such hardness.
It's going in...
That's right, penetrate your oneechan.
Ryoko-nee, you're so wet.
So wet and slippery.
You don't like ecchi nurses?
Its not that...
Collect her juices, or the curse won't be lifted.
This thing again...
Amazing, its throbbbing...
Its throbbing inside me.
Mr. patient, please behave yourself.
I'll clean you with my breasts.
Ryoko-nee, I can't breathe...
Stop moving.
Yu's face feels quite good.
If you do that, no...
Let oneechan do it...
But it feels too good.
You're such a perverted patient.
So troublesome.
This is good...
I'm feeling good too.
Its stirring my pussy.
Don't play with my tits like that.
You'll flatten them.
Is your cock going to shoot out it's naughty juices?
Just a bit more, Miss Nurse.
Really?
No, this is too much... I'm almost...
Ryoko-nee, almost...
I can't, I'm coming... coming!
Its still throbbing... throbbing inside me.
Yeah...
This is weird.
Seems like its still swelling up.
Ryoko-nee...
Hey, how about we try it with the other hole next?
Huh...
It's in my ass...
So tight...
My ass, pussy and breasts were all toyed with by my brother!
This feels good, very good.
Keep going in all the way.
My ass...
My ass is being penetrated...
Isn't it painful?
A little, but I like it this way.
Its getting tighter.
Are you coming again, into my ass?
It's ok for Yu come as many times as he likes.
Ryoko-nee...
Good, my ass feels so good.
Your cock is coming in deep.
I'm coming!
I'm also coming, my pussy is coming too!
I'm coming inside.
Ok, I'm almost...
Seems like you really enjoyed yourselves, you two.
Oh my, you saw it?
This is too much, Oneechan and Yu are so ecchi.
Anzu-neechan, why are you...
Well, if you're going to make so much noise
of course we'll hear it!
Yu-kun, how about letting us join in too?
O-Oneechan too?
That's right. Since it's already come to this, let's enjoy it together.
These breasts...
Here you go, nice and soft.
Mine feels soft and good too, right?
You don't need to pin me like that.
Again...
Kuri?
Hey Yu-kun, where are you looking at?
You don't have time to look elsewhere.
I've been holding it back for quite a while.
Oneechan, you're already so wet.
I can't wait any longer.
Let's go...
I've been waiting so long for this, I'm raunchier than usual.
That's too much...
Oneechan looks like she feels real good.
Yeah, I'm getting horny just by looking.
So big, its spreading my pussy apart.
This... no good...
Its ok, you can come anytime you like.
I'll come whenever you release your sperm into me.
This is embarrassing.
My my Anzu, they're erect already, you pervert.
So hard.
You'll spoil them if you're being rough.
Come on, easy now.
Remove your bloomers for Yu.
Anzu-neechan...
Please don't stare at my pussy so much.
B-But...
Take it easy Anzu.
Move properly and give Yu some pleasure.
Yes.
Why is my body is moving on its own?
Anzu you're really naughty.
No way, I'm not naughty.
Kyoko-neechan... my breasts, no...
Anzu-neechan...
Wait, if its so fast, I'll go crazy.
Then let's stop?
Don't.
Please don't...
Anzu-neechan's, neechan's pussy...
is becoming extremely wet.
Idiot, don't say such things.
Its throbbing inside, feels so good.
Ryoko-nee...
Oh, I've been waiting for this.
Here, here...
Amazing, can a pussy spread that much?
You're right.
Is it because it's Ryoko?
A-Anzu's pussy got spread a lot too.
Lies, that's not true.
We shouldn't be discussing this...
It's getting bigger inside me.
I'm sorry...
Oh you...
It's ok, let oneesan do it for you.
No wonder they came so fast.
This feels too good.
Ryoko-nee, thats too intense.
Because I want it to be intense.
Ryoko-neechan, let me help from here.
Anzu, stop...
Neechan's ass is throbbing non-stop.
Does it feel good?
I can't move properly if you're doing that.
No, this...
Even Yu-kun...
Let's come together.
Don't push your cock in so much.
I just came earlier, but now...
Let me put it in and see.
This is... both fingers went in.
I'm feeling something inside.
Its rubbing me, I'm almost...
Work harder, both of you.
Yeah, Ryoko-neechan and Yu-kun, just a bit more.
More? I can't already...
Me too...
I'm almost...
Ryoko-nee!
Awesome...
Spraying so much...
It still feels warm inside... so good.
"Inanna is the Sumerian goddess of sexual love,
fertility, and warfare. Known to be of dual sex"
After that, the Inanna tube disappeared.
Seems like the curse was finally lifted.
My sisters' wishes can be fulfiled by collecting the "juice". But what wishes I wonder?
Oh wow, it became bigger again.
Yeah, looks like we can go on with it.
Anzu-neechan, Kyoko-neechan.
If you do that some more...
Oh no you don't.
Put your cock in me next.
No way...
Yu-kun...
We'll do more pleasurable things together now, ok?
Ryo-Ryoko-nee.
Maybe the wish made by my sisters, is to be able to stay with me like this forever.
Right, Kuri?
Credits
Beta Translation: bobyc
Timing: renz
Typesetting: renz
Editing: renz and MasterL
Quality Check: renz
RAW Provider: Caotics
Encoding: MasterL
Special Thanks to: Bokudan
Presented by
X-Shinigami Amateur Subbing Guild (X-SASG)
Please visit us at:
http://x-shinigami.browsehentai.com/blog/forum
Thank you for watching.