Movie Research Club
Camp Schedule
August 3
~5 days
Aramichi Risa
Those who are participating in the camp are...
Katou Yasuyuki
Takeuchi Shinya
Yamagishi Yuu
Saeki Hitomi
Igarashi Tomomi and Tanaka Yuuji are not going to participate?
Yes.
No matter what, Tomo-chan?
It's the long-awaited camp after all and yet...
I'm so sorry, everyone.
He's taking care of her mother who is hospitalized,
it's pitiful that only Utan can't participate.
I also want to accompany Utan.
I see.
To you, Tanaka's mother is your future mother-in-law.
Don't say it like that.
Tanaka-kun and Tomo-chan's affections makes me envious.
I wish I had a boyfriend.
To be Yamagashi-san's boyfriend, huh...
Kansen ~Inyoku no Rensa~
Translator: Senjou
Tlc: Jhkplaya888
Timer+editor: Blazersoul
QC+Distro: Yuuto
Well then, next we'll show three movies.
During the individual movies...
Ummm, intermission will be around ten minutes in between.
Every movie is the work of twenty years ago.
Often seen as masterpieces.
Teacher!
Are you alright, teacher?
I'm sorry.
I'm just a little dizzy.
It's all right.
Teacher...
It's better not push yourself...
Perhaps you're right.
Sorry, I'll go rest in the infirmary for a while.
I'll be back when I feel better.
That was interesting.
Although it's was long ago,
we can't underestimate the work of the past.
In the end, the teacher didn't return.
Hey, I'm a little worried with the teacher's situation.
Well then, I'll go take a look.
Takeuchi-kun will?
This guy Shinya, his motive is so obvious.
Because his types are like Shindou-sensei.
Well...
I guess there isn't anything dangerous in the school.
It's not necessary for everyone to go together.
Then, I'll have to trouble you, Takeuchi-san.
If the teacher wakes up,
ask her what she wants us to do next?
If she's still resting, then we should go.
Okay.
I don't think that guy Shinya would do anything bad around the teacher in school.
Sorry for the intrusion.
Shindou-sensei, are you here?
Teacher...
Teacher?!
Ah, it's Takeuchi-kun.
Umm...
Teacher, what are you doing?
Can't you tell? I'm masturbating.
Ma-Mas?
Or if I to say I'm pleasuring myself, will that make you excited?
P-Pleasuring yourself?
Just by using my fingers can't satisfy me enough.
I want something thicker.
Something thicker?
Your penis, for example.
Come here please.
Teacher.
Teacher...Teacher...
As I thought, Takeuchi-kun is still a virgin.
Although I like it rough, please calm down a bit.
This is the hole to put the penis in.
It's called a vagina.
I've penetrated into the vagina.
It's in...
A young man's penis is really good.
Teacher...
Teacher... This is great, Teacher.
You are great, Takeuchi-kun.
Penetrate deeper with your penis in your teacher's vagina.
It's actually so comfortable to have sex.
If would've known, I wouldn't of have to suffer this much holding it in.
If I would've known, I would have raped you.
That won't do, Takeuchi-kun.
Rape is a crime.
If you wish to have sex, I will satisfy you the best I can.
Just vent your gloominess on my vagina.
You don't have to find other girls to penetrate.
I understood, Teacher.
From today onwards, my sperm will only shoot in Teacher's comfortable vagina.
You are such a good child, Takeuchi-kun.
Come on, fill your Teacher's vagina with cum.
Teacher.
I'm cumming.
I should be a strict teacher.
But I'm actually being filled up in the insides,
by a student's hot cum.
I'm cumming!
Takeuchi-kun, I still want more.
Can you still continue?
I'm not satisfied yet.
The number you have dialed is either turned off,
or is no longer in service...
No.
I can't get in touch with Utan.
Please connect...
Hurry and save me, anyone please.
If this continues, I will...
An unknown virus is spreading throughout the country.
After being infected by the virus, the body and the mind will become abnormal.
There may be a sudden urge.
I have to hurry where Utan is.
Utan, save me.
Takeuchi-kun is sure slow.
Yeah.
The teacher is also not back yet.
I think, I should go and check.
Should I try calling Shinya before that?
Katou-san, we are not allowed to use cell phones in school.
We are not even in class, don't be a stick in the mud.
What a detestable girl.
Igarashi-san called.
Use your thick penis to violate me.
I've lost my virginity... That's why it's very painful.
But it's good.
I still want more penis.
In my mouth and here too.
I want to drink a huge load of sperm.
Hello, Igarashi-san?
Hey!
Strange, it seems to have connected, but...
It was hung up.
What the heck is going on?
What is it?
It's coming from the gym.
The voice just now, wasn't it like Shindo-sensei?
It's no use, Shinya is not picking up.
I will go take a look.
You two stay here.
Katou-san!
It's you, Saeki.
Don't scare me.
I'm still a little worried with you being alone.
I'm going with you.
I'm fine, but what about Yamagishi-san?
I already told her to lock the door while we return.
As expected from the student president.
But the president isn't allowed run in the corridors either.
This...
It's because it's an emergency.
Sorry, sorry.
In fact, I'm helpless when I'm alone.
I'm happy that you came.
Putting up a tough guy act.
Men are all like that.
Well then, shall we go.
Yes.
Shinya? Shindou-sensei?
Teacher, is anyone there?
Katou-san?
No!
Teacher?!
Shinya?!
Your penis has gotten harder.
Ready for penetration.
Katou-san.
I've always dreamed for this moment to come.
Saeki.
How's my vagina, Katou-san?
Is it beautiful?
But, no matter how beautiful,
it's only up till today.
From now on, we will use Katou-san's penis too,
violate my vagina.
What are you intending to do, Saeki?
I've been preserving my virginity up till today...
Just for you...
Wait... Wait a moment...
What a sweet and beautiful pain.
My hymen has finally been run through by a penis.
I'm so happy.
Stop it, Saeki!
Why?
Even though, it's feeling good.
Katou-san, are you feeling uncomfortable?
Umm...
I'm feeling good.
having your penis inside my vagina is actually so good.
And...
Being violated by someone you like is great.
Someone you like?
I'm also giving you my first kiss.
It's the first for me too.
But to have other than Yamagashi-san as partner...
Next, I'll want you to penetrate my ass.
Come on, shoot it out, Katou-san.
For my first experience of ejaculation-
Please shoot out your cum, please.
That's not good.
Great, Katou-san's penis is too good.
Saeki, I say it's not good
I'm cumming.
Katou-san's sperm...
Hot sperm is filling up my insides.
I'm cumming.
I came.
Inside Saeki.
I cummed a lot.
If it's like this...
What a waste.
It's still young, it will stand right away.
It's my turn now.
Geez, cut it out already.
Wait, Katou-san.
Everyone is not coming back.
Katou-kun...
Can we watch the news here?
There's a picture.
Due to the unknown virus, Japan has fallen into a state of panic.
Everyone, please calm down.
Currently, the government has set up an emergency headquarters,
to deal with the first stage of the virus...
How can this be... It's not good.
I have to tell them quickly.
I have to return to the Yamagashi-san...
My penis...
Katou-kun?
Yamagishi-san...
Let me do it.
Nooo!
No... Stop it, Katou-kun... Stop!
I want to have sex with you.
Nooo!
Yamagishi-san's lips are delicious.
Please stop it, Katou-kun.
Then, the next will be the real deal.
I could finally to do it with Yamagishi-san...
I'm feeling so happy.
It's like Saeki said, doing it with the person you like is the best.
It's painful.
Please, Katou-kun, get your penis out.
No way, I want to keep doing it till I cum.
You want to cum in me?
That's right.
Isn't it normal to cum into someone that you like?
How can this be...
Rest assured, I will take responsibility.
I will do it with you all my life.
No... I don't want...
I'm going to cum.
It's going to end.
No!!
It got big again.
Like this, you can penetrate into my vagina again.