Please leave it to me!
You...
Mio, nice!
This...
Shuu-niichan's home run!
Game set and match won by Mio-chan and Kei-chan!
Hey! Shuuichi! That was your mistake now!
Since we're at a training camp, put more spirit in it!
It hasn't even been a single game today!
I'm sorry.
Sorry!
Sugiyama-kun... It's because my return was soft...
No, I'm sorry for dragging you down.
T-That's not true!
After covering that part, what should I do?
In that case, you have no choice but to see their point of attack.
When that happens, we'll probably move opposite directions.
Hmm... This way may be better, instead.
That way we can get their attention and attack either side.
S-Sugiyama-kun, should we think of our own strategy?
Sugiyama-kun?
Sorry, what is it?
No... Let's try hard next time, okay?
Translator: tagome
Tlc: Yuuto
Timer: BlazerSoul
Encoder: WolfReborn
QC+Distro: Yuuto
Episode 1
"You can do as you like..."
I should really talk a bit more with Sugiyama-kun...
You can't run anymore.
Mio-san?
Shuu-niichan's part is amazing now.
Will you jizz in your pants at this rate?
Mio... Stop it...
Even if we're siblings-in-law...
This is...
You can't lie, Shuu-niichan.
You're gonna jizz while looking at me, right?
And cum like crazy with your hard dick?
That's...
Hey, you want to do more, right? You want me to do more perverted things.
That's not... For you to say...
Then...
I'll give you a little service...
You want to look at me here, right?
Amazing! It's so hard.
You're really a pervert.
Since you're getting turned on by your little sister touching it.
I...
I am no pervert...
Hey, this liquid is called "pre-cum", right?
It's proof that you're turned on.
You're a pervert.
But, I love that part of you.
So, I'll play with you more.
I'll rub your wet dick.
You're turned on, aren't you?
Wh-What are you saying?
There's no way I'm turned on.
You're about to cum, right?
You're gonna ejaculate from your sister playing with your dick, right?
Like I would... From just this...
You liar!
Then...
This is really perverted...
Show me more perverted things for me!
M-Mio!
Amazing... This is so hot and sticky...
It's still this hard...
It's okay, do what you want with me.
I might not satisfy you with my small breasts, but...
Can you tell? I'm getting really hot down here...
Mio... Let's not go any further...
Do you hate me now?
Or... Are you regretting it?
That's...
I've never regretted it from the first time.
So...
Please don't...
Hate me...
Mio...
It hurts, right?
Don't push yourself.
I-I'm okay.
I-It doesn't hurt at all.
It's okay for you to move.
I'll make you feel better.
Shuu-niichan... You're really perverted... Going so roughly...
It's because you're provoking me!
Shuu-niichan...
It's like... Big...
Mio... Mio!
So you really like my body...
It's because... It's because you're a pervert, right?
You're also perverted.
Doing this with your brother-in-law.
That's right! I'm perverted!
I get turned on when we have sex!
So... Go rougher...
Shuu-niichan... is inside me...
Amazing... It's amazing!
It feels good... Harder... Harder!
Go harder...
Mio... Mio!
I can't... Hold it in...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Okay, go for it.
Go on mine...
I'm cumming...
Cumming... Cumming...
Mio... I'm still...
It's okay... Let's do it one more time.
Mio...
H-Huh...? They were... Kissing... Right?
It's normal for them since they're siblings, right?
But... Why...
Is my heart... So depressed?
Hey, widen it more.
This is... So embarassing!
That's such a perverted body.
Noo, don't look at my perverted body like that...
You're really wet.
You're wrong. I'm just sweating a lot.
Is that true?
Are you not touching it?
I'm stopping. If you want to be touched that badly, do it yourself.
Don't tease me like that...
Touch me... Touch me inside!
It looks like I have to punish this dirty sister of mine.
Hey, did you have another orgasm?
I didn't...
I'm just surprised that you suddenly put it in!
It feels... Good...
It feels so different... From before...
I don't get it, properly explain it!
Your dick is going deep inside me...
My pussy... Is feeling... So good...
Mio...
Shuu-niichan... I'm getting broken up...
It feels good, right, Mio?!
It feels good...
Put it in me more...
Put it in my perverted body...
Who would of thought that's my sister...
I'm sorry...
I'm perverted... I'm a perverted sister...
I'm also a pervert, so it's perfect, right?
Mio...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
Geez...
Hmm...
This is so strange...
I thought Shuu-chan and Ai-chan's pair play would be perfect, but...
I wonder if there's some problem...
M-Maybe... A sexual problem?!
Y-You can't... Shuu-chan...
I'm the teacher...
Sensei... I can't hold back anymore.
That's...
Hey, it's fine, right?
I got it...
Then... I'll use my breasts...
Please bear it with this today...
Does it hurt?
Sensei... Move it up and down like that.
Like this?
Sensei, you're really good.
I've never done this...
This isn't good... I...
Does it feel good? It feels good, right?
No, don't push it in...
Sorry, sensei. I can't stop my hips.
Amazing... Shuu-chan's dick is becoming this hot...
You're also...
No... If you do that to my erect nipples...
It'll make me feel weird...
My breasts feel hot...
Sensei...
I'll make you feel great with my breasts so...
You can... Cum anytime...
Sensei, what are you doing?
Your face seems red...
Are you alright?
No problems at all...
I was just thinking of something.
U-Umm...
If you want, I can be the ballboy.
Saeki-san.
They said today's too hot for afternoon practice, but I couldn't find you anywhere...
I see. You saw me at a weird spot.
S-Sorry... Am I bothering you?
No, that's not it at all.
Thanks.
We're partners after all.
Would you like to hit the ball around a little?
I feel like I'm close to getting it...
Sure!
That felt really good right there!
No, that was luck.
You're a lot...
Saeki-san! We have to clean up the balls!
Okay!
Amazing... It's like a squall.
Since it's sudden rain, I doubt it'd last very long.
S-Sorry.
Wait a moment.
It's fine... If it's you...
I... Was really, really happy when I got paired with you in doubles...
Saeki-san...
Umm... For a long time... I've... Always...
S-Sorry... Right now... I...
If it's Mio-san, I already know.
I don't even care about it.
Just right now... Please look at me.
Saeki-san...
Saeki-san... I can't hold back...
I'm so embarassing.
You're really hot.
You can't explain it...
Don't lick me there...
You're so perverted...
I'm getting turned on by your body.
Please don't say that... It's so embarassing...
That's...
Please... Treat me... Kindly...
Saeki-san, are you feeling it?
I don't know...
You're really...
It's dirty... Becoming so wet...
It's because you're a pervert that I'm going crazy...
I'm going crazy... I'm...
What do you want me to do? I'll do just as you say.
You can do... As you like...
Saeki-san...
I... Want you...
Okay... Please... Take me...
This position is so embarassing...
Sugiyama-kun...
It's so hot and big...
Is that really going to fit inside me?
Relax as much as you can.
Just a little more...
All of it's in.
It's fine... You can move.
It's alright.
I'm okay... I'll hold myself in if it'll make you feel good.
Saeki-san...
Sugiyama-kun is... Inside me...
It feels really good...
I'm glad...
Feel much better...
I'll make you feel good, too...
I'm... Going crazy again...
It's okay, let me see you go crazy.
It's my first time... Why am I feeling this...
No...
You're really cute like this.
Amazing... My body is feeling this...
My body is so hot...
Saeki-san...
It's okay... You can go harder...
You can be rough with me...
I'll pull it out for now.
Wait, Sugiyama...
Lift up your leg.
O-Okay...
It's coming in me...
Saeki-san... I'm about to...
Cum... Cum inside me...
Huh? But...
Please... It's my first time so... I want you...
It's so hot.
Sorry, I...
It's okay.
Please don't apologize.
Saeki-san...
I'm so happy... That my first time's with you.
I was wondering what was going on when you told me to prepare a yukata.
I see. So that's what it is.
I heard that there's a festival held here, so I matched it with the camp.
That's expected of you.
Well, it's a long camp so it's fine to relax a day like this, right?
Y-You know...
Yes?
You look good... In your yukata...
Thank you very much.
What are you two looking so serious for?
M-Mio?
If it's about doubles, you can think about it some other time!
Right?
Mio... You're... Not wearing any underwear?!
You peeked?! You're so perverted!
Oh? That's another bold statement.
You're silly, Mio. You don't have to be so tight on that.
But It looks much pretty without my underwear showing, right?
This is...
Huh? Where's Ai-chan?
That's weird, she should have been following behind us.
Sorry...
Hey, Saeki-san?
Sorry, I was looking at some stores and came late.
Geez, don't get lost here.
Now, let's go.
Umm... Saeki-san... Did you...
Yes... I also... Took off my underwear...
It's a little breezy but...
It's also good like this, right...?
Saeki-san...
I don't mind being thought of as a perverted girl.
It's embarassing, but I really don't want to give up on Sugiyama-kun.