Now, about the training camp for the film research club...
Katou Yasuyuki-san
Yamigishi Yuu-san
Igarashi Tomomi-san
Takeuchi Shinya-san
And myself, Seiki Hitomi.
Besides Tanaka-kun, it's enough if the five of us participate in the training camp, right?
I'll give the news to our advisor, Shindou-sensei, then.
I'm glad you're able to join us, Tomo-chan.
Yeah.
It's too bad Yuuji couldn't join.
Uu-tan has to look after his mother in the hospital.
I wanted to stay with Uu-tan, but...
Uu-tan said at least one of us should be able to participate in the training camp.
"We live in the same house, but you won't have another chance to have a training camp with the others," she said.
I see. Tanaka-kun and Tomo-chan are graduating next year, right?
But you two are so passionate, it makes me envious!
Right, Hitomi-san?
N-Not really. I'm not interested in such things.
Students should be studying.
G-Going out with guys is...
And then they said that's why they keep increasing.
That's an awesome engagement.
Kansen Inyoku no Rensa ~Seiki Hitomi Hen~
Infection Link of Lust ~Seiki Hitomi Episode~
And now we'll take a look at Sanmon's films.
They're all works from at least twenty years ago,
but they're famously known, so they're good to study.
We'll have a 10-minute break between each film.
W-What is this?!
Where's the remote?!
Where's the remote control? Did someone take it?
Hurry and turn it off!
That's Shindou-sensei, isn't it?
No!!
This can't be happening.
I can't believe an instructor was doing such lewd things...
Our instructor's a woman too, so of course she'll have sex, you know.
Oh, how scary.
What should we do? Sensei's gone.
Let's go after her.
Y-Yeah.
Then I'll go.
You?
Yeah, Yasuyuki and me.
Me?
B-But...
It's after what we saw what happened to Sensei, so a guy would be...
But it's late at night, so I think it's better if women didn't hang around.
You should leave this to the guys.
Right, Yasuyuki?
Yeah.
That's true. Let's leave this Katou-san and Takeuchi-san.
But make sure not to make any strange advances towards Sensei.
Strange advances, like in the video just earlier?
On second thought, a guy like you shouldn't...!
Oops. Let's get going, Yasuyuki.
Yeah.
Katou-san.
Be careful, okay?
Yeah.
Yasuyuki, what're you doing?
Sorry!
Yasuyuki, I'll show you something nice.
What? Showing off your new digital camera?
No, no.
Not the camera, what's inside.
I want to show you the footage I got.
Well, it is the latest model.
The details are nice and clear.
What?
You really are just showing off.
Replay
This is...!
S-Shinya!
Screening Room
If I knew this were going to happen, it would've been nice if Uu-tan were here.
S-Should we watch TV or something?
We can get signal here, right?
I'll repeat.
The mysterious virus that has suddenly spread throughout Japan has caused a panic.
We're on air, you know!
No! Stop!
Let go!
Stop! It's not wet yet!
You can't force it in! That's impossible!
Please wait momentarily
Is this true?
I don't think the news would lie.
Uu-tan said that not everything on TV is true.
So was that fiction?
I don't know...
S-Sensei?
Popularity...
Katou-san?
Takeuchi-san?
Shindou-sensei?
The three of them... where did they go?
It feels like a big mess now.
It's state of emergency, so we should meet up with the others as soon as we can.
Then let's split up and look for them.
Sensei!
Um... instead of splitting up more, shouldn't we go together?
You're the one who said we should do it as soon as we can, Hitomi-san.
That's true, but...
Then we'll split up the search parties and make sure to come back here whether we find them or not.
Is that okay?
I guess there's no choice.
Walking by myself in the school at night...
If I'm attacked by someone, what should I do?
How pathetic of me...
To need to go to the bathroom during a time like this...
Oh you're up...
I see this is up and about too.
Now, have you had enough yet?
I'm putting it in.
Wait, Sensei! Stop!
It feels good!
Being raped by the teacher you trust, how's it feel as a virgin?
Sensei took my virginity too.
Now you can say we're hole-siblings.
Sharing the same experience with the same woman, we really are true friends.
You're the one who came onto me, Takeuchi-kun.
How's your first time?
Doesn't it feel good?
Sensei... stop doing this...
You don't have to be afraid.
When I was raped and lost my virginity, I thought I wanted to die...
But now I love it so much!
No way! Sensei, you were raped?
Your first experience was rape?
You've gotten big inside me.
Are you turned on?
Do you want to hear about when I was raped?
Th-That's... That's...
Your penis is twitching.
Are you imagining my cries as a virgin?
I was also inexperienced back then, and when I masturbated, I never used my fingers!
Of course, during my periods, I only used pads...
Sensei, stop it! Stop...
I'm coming!
The first cum of a virgin penis...
Hanako-san isn't in here, right?
I'm glad I made it in time.
I haven't showered yet today, so I have to be careful that I don't smell.
I have to find Katou-san and the others soon.
Huh? The lights are on in the janitor's warehouse.
Is someone there right now?
Maybe it's Katou-san and the others?
You're always showing off your big things.
No!
Sensei, what are you doing? Stop!
What cute panties.
Sensei wore something like this long ago too.
Huh? There's a stain.
No, don't look!
It smells like pee.
Did you get scared?
T-That's not it.
It really is cold being naked.
W-Wait, Sensei, my panties...!
How do they look?
It doesn't look good on someone like you, Sensei.
Give back my panties!
What? What're you doing, Sensei?
Look, look.
Yuu-chan, look this way!
No! No!
Then that's fine.
Then I'll just take a look.
No! Wait, what?
Oh, a sports bra!
Nooo!
So these are Yuu-chan's bare breasts?
How soft!
And they're different from Risa's older ones, they don't sag!
Shut up, fatty.
S-Sensei, what are you doing?
Oh, you don't know?
I'm masturbating, masturbating.
Masturbating while wearing my student's clothes, that's prohibited by professionalism.
But, doing something taboo like this feels so good...
How dirty!
I liked those!
I can't wear them anymore!
Wetting my student's underwear and making them dirty by masturbating is the best!
I can't hold it in anymore! It feels so good!
I'll make myself feel good too.
How soft.
It's a different feeling from inside a woman.
N-No!
How gross!
I'm feeling good!
Now that I think of it, I've never had a boob job.
No! That hurts!
This feels good, Yuu-chan!
What?
What are you doing?
That's good!
Masturbating in front of students feels good!
No, no!
Yuu-chan, I'm cumming, okay?
Nooo!
Ejaculating on my precious student's face, oh...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
No, I can't take it anymore...
I'm cumming!
Nooo!
Come on, lick it clean.
H-How can this be happening?
Katou-san!
It's good I went to the bathroom earlier.
I was about to leak.
Katou-san, we should hurry and contact the police.
In there, well, it's unbelievable, but...
There's a rape happening...
Katou-san?
Katou-san, if we don't hurry, Igarashi-san and Yamigishi-san...
Is that the panic the news was talking about?
Katou-san, things are terrible in Japan right now.
It's possible that Shindou-sensei and Takeuchi-san are infected by the virus the news talked about.
That stuff doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter? Are you serious, Katou-san?
I want to tell you my feelings right now.
Could it be... a confession?
T-To tell you the truth, me too...
Let me do it.
Katou-san!
Let me have sex, Saeki.
I haven't even had my first kiss yet...
There's a man's penis in my mouth...
Even though you're an honor student, you smell the same as any other woman here!
When it comes to women, it doesn't matter what they smell like as long as their holes are useful.
First, this hole...
What, drink that at least.
Even if I like you, I can't drink that much semen...
I've given up.
You can do what you want with me, just kiss me at least.
Why do I have to kiss a face covered with semen?
But that's...
Then I guess I'll do what I want.
I'm hard again.
Katou-san, that's...!
Saeki, I'll be taking it.
Ow! That hurts! That hurts...
So you were a virgin?
I'm so happy, Saeki!
That makes the both of us rape friends!
Katou-san, that really hurts!
Hurry and finish it!
Okay.
Saeki, your insides feel so good.
The pussy of an honored student council head!
That hurts!
I can't take it anymore! Hurry, hurry!
Wait for it, I'll cum for you.
But... if you cum inside...
I... I'll have a baby.
No, if you cum inside my vagina...
Your sperm will fertilize the egg inside my ovum!
No, no!
If you cum in there, I'll... I'll...!
Katou-san's penis is in the hole where I poop...
That feels so good!
The anus of an honor student...
You're amazing, Saeki!
Vagina or the anus... being penetrated by a penis feels great!
It doesn't matter which hole!
Do it more!
It's here! A penis is here!
I hate Takeuchi-san, but I love penis!
So I'll let you do it with me!
I'll be raped by more penises aside from Katou-san's, right?
But Katou-san, you're the only one I love.
No matter how much I'm raped...
So Katou-san, keep having sex with me.
Forever, forever and eternally.