Kottondo~ru
It's summer vacation!
We at the tennis club have arrived on this island for a training camp.
Hey, Rei-chan.
Is it really easier to move around in that outfit?
I really wonder.
I did it!
I got a point against you!
Well, well, Mio-san, you're really great.
Your plays of course, but I really mean your bloomers!
Right?
Bloomers really are nice.
They're shorter than shorts, so it keeps me cooler.
You've really polished up your skills lately. It's admirable.
Geez, what's the big idea?
I didn't have any other choice.
My shorts are all wet from sweating.
Hey! I can see your underwear there.
Shu-niichan, you were looking down there? You pervert.
Idiot!
It's fine. That's one of the highlights of bloomers anyway.
Shu-niichan, you're blushing!
Pervert, pervert!
Aren't you embarrassed?
Mai, why don't we wear bloomers starting tomorrow too?
Okay, Senpai!
I wore bloomers during elementary school too, so I think I'll be fine.
In that case, why don't we wear swimsuits?
Oh. If we play tennis wearing swimsuits, you'll expose something private, I'm sure.
I-I'll be fine! I'll bear with it!
Rei-chan, Sensei didn't bring any bloomers...
Should I prepare some?
N-No, Sensei doesn't need any.
Um, Sugiyama-kun?
You'll be running out on the roads after this, right?
If it's okay with you, can I come too?
Sure.
Th-That's fine with me.
Okay!
It's a training camp for school, so it's important we practice...
But being with the person you like all this time, staying at the same camping center...
I can't help but get excited.
There's so much wind at the ocean.
That makes it just the right thing for running on the roads.
Y-Yeah, that's true...
Huh? I have a feeling something like this happened before...
Oh no!
My boobs are showing up so out in the open!
W-Why?
I should be embarrassed, but I can't believe it feels kind of good...
Saeki-san, should we head back to the center now?
Um...!
Um... S-Sugiyama-kun, if you don't mind...
I uh...
I'll be fine doing it.
S-Saeki-san!
P-People don't come around here much...
R-Right now...
What should I do? At this rate, I'll become an even more horny girl...
Saeki-san, I-I'm pulling it down.
Okay...
All at once?
It's more than the smell of sweat.
It smells like you, Saeki-san.
Don't smell it!
I just did all that running...
That's...
It's kind of wet.
That's good. You were turned on, eh?
No!
Don't do that!
Sugiyama-kun, you're so good...
D-Don't shout out so loudly!
But... Sugiyama-kun, you're so big...
Fill me up...
You're amazing, Sugiyama-kun!
It's so big...
Saeki-san, you really are a pervert.
You're moving your own hips.
No, that's not it!
My hips are... moving on their own...
No, no!
I'm...
Oh, more!
Give me more, Sugiyama-kun!
Saeki-san, you feel so good down there!
I'm so happy...
I'm going crazy!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
Like that... Give it to me!
Give me lots of it inside, Sugiyama-kun!
B-But...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
S-Sorry, Saeki-san.
It's okay.
I'm the one who asked, after all.
But I came inside...
It's okay.
I don't regret any of it.
Thanks.
At that time, I'm sure Sugiyama-kun was feeling bad for Mio-san.
Is it because I forced him into it?
What are you doing moping around by yourself?
S-Senpai.
What are you doing here?
Taking a walk. Taking a walk.
Or did you want to talk to me about something?
N-Not really. It's nothing like that.
You're always like that, Shuuichi. You don't make yourself clear.
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
But that might be the good thing about you.
Did you think I was inviting you in just now?
N-No...
Senpai, back then...
Two months ago
In the tennis club room
Shuuichi, you're already big down there.
Well, that's because...
You're like that just from a kiss.
I wonder what'll happen if I do this then?
S-Senpai.
Or do you prefer them smaller, Shuuichi?
That doesn't matter...
Don't touch them just yet.
Open up your mouth.
S-Shuu...
M-More, give it to me... more!
Geez, you're jumping ahead.
Senpai, I'm already...
Then shall we do it?
Don't stare at me so much. It's embarrassing.
I'm... already wet and all.
Shuuichi, is this your first time?
Sad to say...
That's okay. I'll show you how it's done.
Shuuichi, your dick is so hot and stiff...
Just wait a bit.
I-I'm putting it inside.
Maybe it was a bit lower...
Senpai?
Shuuichi, you're so big...
Wait... I'll put it in... deeper...
Senpai!
It's inside.
Senpai, you're bleeding!
It's just because you're a little too big...
Does it hurt?
I'm fine!
I'll get used to it.
Sorry, just wait a bit more.
You don't have to push yourself...
I-I'm fine now.
Just stay still, Shuuichi.
I'll move...
This... is too good!
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good inside me?
It feels good...
It's hot and really tight!
It's twitching inside!
It's moving inside me!
Shuuichi, you're so big, it feels me up so much...
Shuuichi, I'll make it feel even better.
How is it?
Do you like that?
It feels good, Senpai...
It feels good too...
Senpai!
It's hitting so deep inside!
Amazing, Shuuichi...
Go deeper in!
I never thought it would feel this good!
I'm surprised...
It came out.
Wait, I'm scared...
It's getting even bigger inside...
Shuuichi, you feel so good...
Yes...
It feels like it's going to burst through me...
I'm going crazy...
Shuuichi, you're a man...
I thought you were still a little too young, but this is...
Senpai, I'm about to...
You can cum just like that, okay?
It's okay for me today.
B-But...
I won't let you cum outside, got it?
I said it's okay!
So cum... cum inside!
Senpai...!
I'm about to cum too...
Good, good!
I'm coming!
That's true... of all things, we did it in the club room.
Senpai, why did you ask me to do that back then?
What now? You've asked something boring.
Shuuichi, do you regret doing it with me?
No way.
Thanks. Then that's fine.
W-Wait a sec!
If you stay too late, everyone will get worried.
Better head back soon.
'Kay...
I think it feels good...
If I pull this...
The tip of my boobs get hard...
My underwear's getting wet...
Mio's so wet down here...
If Shu-niichan sees me like this...
I'll get so embarrassed I could die!
It's getting wetter...
What should I do? My fingers won't stop!
No, when I think about Shu-niichan watching me, I'll cum!
No more...!
I-I'm coming!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!!
I came a lot...
Y-Yes?
Um... it's me.
Mai-san?
Sorry for coming so late.
That's okay with me.
Um... I think it's not good to keep things the way they are.
W-Well...
I think so too.
It's like we're the only ones giving Sugiyama-kun trouble.
So I came up with an idea...
W-Wait a moment.
I like you, Sugiyama-kun.
M-Mio does too.
Shu-niichan, I like you.
But when you both tell me that out of the blue...
You like both of us, right?
Both me and Mai-san.
You like both of us, so you can't decide, right?
We feel the same.
I also like Mio-chan a lot after being in the club with her,
and I don't want her to feel saddened.
S-Saeki-san...
So we've decided, Ai-san and I are gonna share Shu-niichan.
S-Share?
You mean like sharing room service?
Yes!
Sugiyama-kun, we'll both be yours.
Okay?
Isn't it a good idea?
Wait, you two! Calm down!
We won't wait anymore...
We're... serious!
We're okay with showing you this even though it's embarrassing, Sugiyama-kun.
L-Look, okay?
We'll only do this for you, Shu-niichan.
M-Mio, Saeki-san...
Please, Sugiyama-kun?
Let's all feel good with the three of us.
Oh, you're so big already.
Did you get this big after seeing us down there?
Wait a sec! That's...
It's hot and stiff.
Let me touch it too.
It really is!
It feels like it's moving.
I wonder how it is over here.
It's kind of squishy and weird.
Hey, that's...
Sugiyama-kun, do you feel good?
Well, of course...
So you can feel it, how dirty.
I'm going to try licking it.
Saeki-san...
Mio too!
How weird, I'm just licking it, but I'm getting so hot down there too...
It's not weird. I'm so wet already too.
We're such perverted girls.
It's so hot at the tip.
Mio too!
I can't hold back any longer.
Mai-san!
Shu-niichan's still getting harder.
I wonder if we can do it...
I'm cumming...
You can't cum yet. Not yet.
Hang in there, Sugiyama-kun.
Amazing, you came so much...
Geez, Shu-niichan, you made us all wet.
S-Sorry...
But it's still so big.
It is.
Hey, make us feel good next.
Shu-niichan, don't move until I'm in completely.
I know...
It's all inside.
This is so good!
It's thrusting so deep inside!
It's going inside... Sugiyama-kun's dick is going into Mio-san..
No! Don't look!
Don't look so close, it's embarrassing!
Sorry!
I... I'm so embarrassed, but I can't stop!
Ah, she's masturbating to us!
She's watching us do it!
She's masturbating to us!
M-Mio, I'm...
No!
If you do that, I'll go crazy!
It's your fault, Mio.
You're so wet...
But...!
No excuses! It's punishment time!
O-Okay...
Punish me!
Put lots into Mio's thing!
It's so big...
Over here, Mio-san's perverted place...
It's all wet.
That's so good!
This is the first time I've felt this!
I'm coming!
Your dick's so stiff!
Shu-niichan, I can't hold it any more!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
It's my turn next.
Saeki-san, I can't do any more...
It's okay, I'll make it bigger soon.
Get bigger. Get bigger.
It's getting harder.
Look, it's getting bigger again.
Saeki-san!
I want it inside to make it feel good.
It's inside!
It's in there... your dick...
Saeki-san, I didn't think you were this dirty...
You're so mean.
You're the one who made me this dirty...
Saeki-san, you're so tight down there.
Geez.
It's so unfair with just the two of you.
Let me in too.
Shu-niichan, lick it.
Lick me down there.
All right. Sorry, Mio.
More, deeper!
Mio-san, your nipples are hitting mine...
This feels so weird!
No! Yours are so stiff...
We're both girls, yet...
I didn't know...
That it felt this good doing a threesome...
It's so strong!
It's so deep inside me!
Shu-niichan, Mio's coming again!
Mio-san, me too! I'm coming!
Mai-san, I'm coming, I'm coming!
No more! It's so hot!
Let's cum together!
Everyone, together...
Huh?
I see...
It's over.
The training camp's over...
Oh no...
I think I became a really perverted girl after this training camp.
Episode 2:
"The three of us together..."