Pleased to meet you.
Before I start talking about that...
I made an X-rated video
that was a big hit.
Director: Yasuomi Umetsu
A sponsor saw the video and asked my
company if we were interested in...
...making an OVA for them.
The president of the company
asked me if I had any ideas.
I had an idea that was for an
audience of all ages, but...
...they were interested in
making an X-rated OVA.
I decided to do it because I
was excited about making...
...an original work, so it didn't
matter if it was all-ages or X-rated.
And, I gave them one plan...
...the planning of "A Kite".
Originally "A Kite" was the
story of a female assassin.
A female main character...
I've always wanted to make a piece that
did not pander to a female audience.
And they also wanted to make
an action animation too.
Even though there was the limit
of making an X-rated OVA...
...I thought I would be able to
make something I wanted.
So, I combined the ideas of a girl
assassin and an X-rated OVA.
That's how it started.
Well, in terms of "A Kite"...
It was my goal to create a piece where
I could be in charge of all aspects.
Nowadays, on a TV series,
all the work is divided.
The system of using individual talent to
create a series has been established.
But for an OVA, it is necessary
to express originality.
It was easier for me to be in charge
of the many divisions of production.
I thought it was the most reasonable
way to communicate with the staff.
In order to visualize the sections
that I had in my mind, for instance...
...in the character
design or screenplay...
...it was better to do it myself rather
than letting someone else do it.
So it wasn't a burden at all.
It was a rather challenging
and enjoyable work for me.
This piece is pretty old...
When the piece was finished, all the
troubles turned into happy memories.
So I don't remember them well.
The hardest parts of production were
the screenplay and storyboards.
They were the most important
parts of the process.
Eighty percent of the quality of the
finished piece depends on them.
That's how it is in animation.
The later processes, such as animation,
final line and photographing...
...fall into place if there is a plan.
So the screenplay and
storyboards are important.
I spent so much time working on
the screenplay and storyboards.
I spent most of the time
I had working on them.
So that means the rest of the process
had to work within a tight schedule.
I remember that I gave
everyone trouble.
My next assignment is to make a
screenplay and storyboards quickly...
Director: Yasuomi Umetsu
...but keep the piece's quality high.
I think if we could have finished the
storyboards of "A Kite" earlier...
...the rest would have
worked smoother.
So the quality could have been better.
Creators are greedy.
We always regret something
when a piece is finished...
...and we try to do it
better for the next piece.
Since there was that
problem in "A Kite "...
I thought that if I was more
efficient in the beginning...
I could have spent
more time on the rest.
The title was derived from...
Well there is the girl assassin,
Sawa, and the boy assassin, Oburi.
These two are the main characters.
Since they are assassins,
there has to be a client.
They have to follow the client's orders.
No one works individually.
They are connected by invisible strings.
I'm comparing them to a Kite.
There is a person who controls and
there is a person who is controlled.
So, Sawa and Oburi exist on strings.
In the end of this story, they
cut the Kite string and fly away.
I decided to use the name
with that connotation.
If I say "this is how the story ends" or
"it's how the character is going to be"...
that would be the end of the story.
I wanted to make the characters live
in people's hearts in their own way.
I want people to keep Oburi and
Sawa in their own imaginations.
That's what I think.
Intentionally, I look at everything around
myself, from buildings to people.
It's important to pay attention
to them all the time and...
absorb things that I can
create something from.
It's like a mental drawer.
When I make my original characters,
I take ideas from the drawer.
Since I create my characters, I want
them to exist as if they were.
Even though they are two dimensional,
I try to create them with a presence.
In order to create that, the characters
need strong characteristics.
I combine many elements
and create a character.
The characters in "A Kite"
were born in that way.
Well, my reaction was like,
"Please do whatever you want."
I don't want the director Rob Cohen
to be tied down by the OVA.
He can have his own interpretation.
I'd like him to keep the spirituality
of the OVA version of "A Kite".
But I want him to feel free to
express his own ideas and...
to make a live action movie of "A
Kite", interpreted through his own filter.
I've always liked to draw
since I was a child...
I wanted to be a comic book artist.
I entered technical
school for animation.
My teacher used to be in
Tatsunoko Productions.
He told me the stories and showed me
drawings from Tatsunoko Productions.
Director: Yasuomi Umetsu
You get a lot of information about
companies in technical schools.
Information you've never heard...
I was curious and
intrigued by animation.
I was attracted by the fact that the
picture moves with sounds, like a movie.
I've been immersed in
animation since then.
I watch animations that
I am curious about.
There are many people who record
animations in my company.
And I borrow them.
I always hear people say, "This
is good." or "That's bad."
And I watch them and figure
out why it's bad or good.
Well, in terms of animations, I
watch them as a part of business.
I can't watch them objectively.
If I watch the work of other professionals,
I get jealous. Especially if it's good.
I'm bitter when I say,
"This is a good piece."
So it's hard for me to
judge it as an animation.
I'm part of the TV generation.
Because of where I grew up, I was
influenced by TV rather than movies.
In the 1970's when Japanese TV series'
were very popular, I began puberty...
I was hooked on the TV
shows of that period.
They made a huge influence on my
taste including my philosophy now.
For example, detective shows,
samurai shows and family shows...
They became my core.
I started watching movies when I was
twenty years old and moved Tokyo.
Since then I was polished by movies.
But I think the TV shows from the
70's are significant in my core.
They were popular shows like
"Taiyo ni Hoero" and "Daitokai".
As a samurai show, "Monjiro's
Hissatsu" and others were in the 70's.
Also, "Kizudarake no tenshi".
Well, thank you very much.
I would like to produce more
animations as much as possible.
I appreciate your support.