Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Masato Suzuki, the producer at Green
Bunny told our company, ARMS, that...
...he knew of an eccentric creator and
wanted to make an animation with him.
We actually had planned
another animation once and...
Producer: Osamu Koshinaka
...asked Mr. Umetsu. Unfortunately
that plan didn't work out.
Years after that happened, we
approached Mr. Umetsu again.
When we asked him, he told us
that he had an idea for a project.
That's how we started
producing "A Kite".
He was very tough
when we were working.
He made people around him
work like they were in hell.
But we knew that for his film,
it would be worth the work.
The staff listened to whatever he
wanted and tried to get closer to...
...the images he had in mind.
He is one of the few
creators who has a power...
...to make the staff feel like
they want to work harder.
I thought he was very talented,
fun to work with, and also...
...he could create an animation
that would satisfy the staff...
...when it was completed.
Well, the schedule management
was the most difficult.
The director had specific and
clear images in his mind...
...so he was never satisfied until
he got exactly what he wanted.
We had to balance between
the schedule and the budget...
It required us to choose
which one had priority.
But the director stuck to what
he wanted until the last minute.
So some staffers always had to stay up
all night to catch up with the schedule.
This happens a lot in
this business but...
He finished the piece after being worn
out from staying up all night for days.
The last minute struggle was
reflected in the finished piece.
There were things I couldn't do anything
about because of the schedule.
As a producer, I still have a sense
of bitterness with "A Kite".
We spent a lot of time
before shooting started.
Mr. Umetsu ate it all.
He ate all of the schedule including
other people's schedules...
We started shooting behind schedule
but the deadline stayed the same.
He did as much as he wanted and that's
why the piece was successful but...
He stuck and stuck to his ideas.
I understood that he
wanted to do more but...
...I had to stop him.
That was my job.
If we could, we would spend more money
and time to go on with the details...
But I think the piece would be boring.
Mr. Umetsu and I always had
discussions on the matter.
I think it's the same
thing with all producers.
What Mr. Umetsu and I did...
Mr. Umetsu worked on the content
of the piece almost 100 percent.
And we tried to make it as
close to his image as possible.
What I cared about was the
representation of that in animation.
There are things you can do in
both live action and animation.
But basically, it was an animation.
I told him once that I wanted him
to care about things that were...
...only possible to
represent in animation.
That was it.
Everything else was under
Mr. Umetsu's control.
I tried to work in compliance
with what he wanted.
I think animation shouldn't have violent
scenes if it is going to be on TV.
This would make it an X-rated
animation from the beginning...
...there wasn't any problem
with that in Japan.
Producer: Osamu Koshinaka
But the way children are not allowed
to see violence in the U.S....
When I was in the U.S., I saw
a movie with a violent scene.
There were six black frames
and right after that...
...a man who got hit was
flying through the air.
I don't think that's right.
Children can tell it's there
even though they can't see it.
It's noticeable.
In fact, the U.S. still
has a high crime rate.
The violent scenes should be shown...
...carefully based on the
creators' criteria or aesthetics.
From the creator's point of view...
...it is wrong to ban all
the violent scenes.
The main reason is marketing.
By putting sexual scenes, we are
assured that we'll have a certain market.
Including those scenes was
a condition we had to meet.
The Japanese animation industry
wouldn't let Mr. Umetsu...
...create freely without the condition.
It's possible.
Since he wants very realistic brutal
scenes, like a severed head rolling around.
Those necessary things for him as
an artist are not allowed on TV.
I'm sure he'll receive recognition
because of his talent, but...
...there weren't any producers
who would let him create.
So in that sense, we
had a better chance.
The movies that I like? I like anime and
that why I'm in the anime industry.
But in terms of movies, I
like old American films.
Old movies like "High Noon",
"Shane" and "Roman Holiday".
In terms of animations, I really
like Japanese animation.
In recent works, I was impressed
by Disney's "Tarzan and Jane".
Disney and Japanese
animation are totally different.
Producer: Osamu Koshinaka
I liked Disney's old animation
like "101 Dalmatians" but...
...I didn't like their new works.
I was amazed by the imagination
in "Tarzan and Jane".
There are many talented creators in
Japan, so we have been creating...
...stimulating animations.
But personally, I'm influenced by
animations from my childhood.
Like, "Gatchaman", "Casshern"
and "Tiger Mask"...
I saw them when I was
in elementary school.
And of course, "Space Battleship
Yamato" and "Umino Toriton"...
That's when I started becoming
an "animation Otaku".
I haven't been planning for this, but...
...I want to make
animations for children.
A boy or girl's adventure animation
for kids around age 7 to 12.
I'm hoping that I will be able to do that.
It's because I don't get to do
those type of animations often.
I always get bloody
and erotic animations.
I want the challenge of doing
something completely different.
It seems like "A Kite" will be produced
as a live action in Hollywood movie.
Also, Yasuomi Umetsu produces
other interesting works.
I know there are many
amazing animations in Japan.
Mr. Umetsu and I always
create interesting work.
We'll continue making anime, hoping
many people will be able to see them.
Please support Yasuomi Umetsu.
Thank you very much.