You just rest over there, okay?
Hey,
could this be
your first time?
Or maybe not.
No, no, no.
You just startled me there.
Besides, you're already dating Oikawa, right?
Oh no, what's this... something's.
Something's wrong!
See? You already came when I put it in.
It... doesn't hurt.
I didn't think you could cum like this if it was your second time.
So that wasn't your first!
You were already doing it like crazy, right?
You also had that condom around with you, so I'm definitely right!
Why?
Why... why.
Why do you have to say that to me?
The hell.
Then you should have told me sooner!
If I did it first, then I could have tried to make it feel better.
Though, we still would have fucked you.
Stop... not there.
Don't,
that's... no.
Don't.
Stop, stop.
Feeling good?
This feels, this feels so different.
It's your first time so you shouldn't be
getting horny like this, you know.
No... no!
That's not true.
I-I'm not like that!
Damn, don't cry!
Why am I suddenly?
No... stop.
If you keep doing that.
You came again.
Does my dick really feel that good?
So, you want to keep it up?
Come on, what do you say?
Say it properly!
Stop, I'm starting to lose it.
No need for such an expression, you know.
Oh well, I'll just have to do it again.
Again?
I wasn't able to take your virginity myself,
but I'm the first to fuck you raw.
Th-That can't.
For real?
You can't tell?
I mean this.
Doing it raw really feels different.
And here I thought you were just acting like you didn't know.
Raw... no, please!
Stop... why?
But you promised.
So what? It's too late to give me that look.
Besides, I never told you that I was going to use it.
Stop!
It feels a lot better without a condom anyway, don't you agree?
No.
No, please stop.
Don't.
Then what?
Shall I cum inside?
Don't!
Stop, please don't!
Why exactly should I stop?
That's.
Just let yourself drown in pleasure!
Come on, Nao.
I'll do everything myself from here on,
so take it all in graciously.
No.
I'm about to cum.
Stop!
Please stop!
Damn.
Don't you just go around dating someone.
Hey, stop slacking around!
We're done here.
Go home already.
But I only got to do it once.
Shut up!
Oh yeah,
everyone said they needed to do something
so they all went home.
Yup, we're done for the day.
See ya.
Hey, are you dating Nao?
We can pretty much tell, you know.
So... who did the confessing?
Oh, I see.
Well, I just got kinda interested.
Let me hear all the details later.
Yeah, see ya then.
So, he's not going to come over today.
What do you want to do?
Wanna continue?
Oh well.
It's really hot today.