You were out for a little while.
What?
Could it possibly be...
That that was your first time?
What the...
Eh?
No, no, no, no, no.
This surprises me.
You also wanted to do it with
Oikawa-kun didn't you?
What is this feeling! I don't like it.
It feels weird!
That weird face your putting.
It didn't... hurt.
It's the second time... Why is still so tough.
This is certainly not the first time.
You always wanted this right?
There's no way you didn't want
this, you always carried a condom.
What the...
Why? Why?
Was it something I said?
What is this...
You should have said something earlier.
If you had told me first.
I would've made things more comfortable.
But now it wont make a difference.
Don't... don't... don't.
No! Don't!!!
No... no...
It feels good doesn't it?
It doesn't!
It hurts... It's not comfortable at all!
At the start it obviously doesn't feels well.
Don't... don't...
This is wrong...
I just can't understand.
Shit... don't cry!
Why is he suddenly doing this.
Please... stop.
If you keep going like that.
Here I go.
Is my cock that good?
Shall I continue?
Let's just say.
That you do!
Don't... I'm feeling very weird.
You don't have to force yourself so much.
Oh well.
Let's do this again!
Again?
Although I'm not a virgin.
This is the first time I've
experienced not wearing one.
Not... wearing... one?
You don't understand?
This seriously feels very different.
You think I don't know how this works?
No don't!
Why...? Why!?
You promised.
What exactly did I promise?
Your face show so much pleasure
when I did it this time around.
And you can't say otherwise.
It feels so much better this way doesn't it?
Please don't.
Don't!
How about I cream pie this time?
Don't! Don't!
And why should I not?
Because!
Because what? This feels good!
So Nao.
I'm going to spurt it all over!
Now gratefully accept it!
No... Don't!
I'm gonna cum!
Not this! Not this!
Damn it!
Don't say that.
Hey! Don't be lazy, get up!
It's over already.
Wake up.
But I only went once.
Shut up!
Oh yeah, yeah... everyone is on their way home.
Today? I just got here... I'll see you tomorrow.
Tsukasa... are you dating Nao?
Have you been together for long?
When did you declare it to her?
Ahh... I see.
Naw... I was just a little curious.
Tell me in detail some other time.
Ok. Talk to you later
There... he won't come over now.
So what are you gonna do?
Do you want to continue this?
It's all up to you.
Today is really a hot day.