So hot,
and so pooped.
Let's take a short break.
The electric fan isn't even making it cool enough.
There's nothing else.
So put up with it.
You two sure are noisy.
Don't let those hands stop now.
Okay, okay.
Oh sorry.
Mom said it's something urgent.
Eh? You're going home already, Riko?
I see, can't be helped then.
Sorry about this.
I'll send you off.
Don't you two dare slack off!
It may be hard to keep those two working, but just keep it up.
Jeez, I know, right?
Oh yeah,
Oikawa-kun's coming later, right?
Y-Yeah.
I bet you two are going on a date after this.
W-Well... umm, I'm not really sure.
Okay, here you go.
Doing it raw is risky after all.
Hey, I don't need this!
It's the girl who needs to be careful in situations like those.
You need to assert your girl power more your know.
See ya.
Till tomorrow, then.
Girl power, huh.
I'm not sure what'll happen next anymore.
Classmate
Sorry, now let's finish it up.
Hey, why are you two slacking off?
Riko-chan's gone home already.
I can't get to work on this without girls around.
What? There's still a girl here, you know.
Shut up, uglyface.
Girl?
Girl's are supposed to be more refined and cute.
You guys are really pissing me off!
Just quit yapping and start working already!
Damn, I really can't control them.
I'm not really in the mood for this.
Anyway, what happened to Oikawa?
He said he'll be late due to club activities.
Hey, isn't that unfair?
I also had something to do earlier!
What? I bet it's just some unimportant business.
Oikawa's lot more serious, different than you guys.
Oh? Defending your "boyfriend", huh.
What? You were trying to hide it?
It's plainly obvious, you know.
Wait... what? What's going on?
Huh? You don't know?
She and Oikawa are a couple already.
For real?
He's got really bad taste!
I can't really see anyone going out with her, of all people.
There's lots of other cuter girls out there, you know!
Now I'm really, really pissed off!
Just keep working on that already!
That was really bad of me to let Yuuji know.
It's going to be troublesome to constantly
hear things from them about this.
Him being a meanie's his trait from the very beginning.
What are you two doing chatting again?
And what in the world are you whispering about anyway?
Oh, it's nothing.
Oh, you see he's.
Hey, idiot!
He's asking if you two have done it already.
It's Oikawa after all.
I don't really think he's already done it,
but looking at you, I can't even get turned on.
Well, have you done it or not really?
A-Are you stupid?!
You're asking me that directly?!
Nothing wrong with it, I think.
There's nothing to lose anyway.
It has nothing to do with you two!
That may be so, but we're still curious.
Stop kidding me, just die!
Anyway, you're getting worked up over this too much.
Then you two have done it already?
Idiot!
Whoa, that's amazing.
Did you say something?
Well, I just realized that you're a "girl" after all.
You've got a sharp tongue, act rough, and are totally uncute.
You never really act like a normal girl.
And yet you already had sex.
Oh crap.
You kinda look totally erotic.
Somehow, I now feel that I can actually dig you.
What?
Looking at you again, you face does look cute.
Hey, you're getting too rude already.
Oh man, see? Now my dick's gotten a boner.
You already did it, right? Amazing.
Just a little, please.
Get me off.
If you don't, I might never be able to continue my homework.
Wait... just wait!
Yuuji, don't just sit there!
Okay, okay.
This guy's getting too cocky.
Well, just calm down a bit.
Yeah, tell him off!
He'll pipe down once you do it once, night?
It's quite hot today, you see.
Alright, bring it on.
Hey, try to be more serious.
I can't with you two!
Once this is over, you'll resume your work, okay?
Just hold it already.
Once this is over
wait, why the hell did it turn out this way anyway?
You really are rough.
Hey, what are you doing?
Well, I can't really feel your passion for this.
I won't!
Your handjob seems very crude,
so just do it by mouth.
What? I never said I'd do it that way!
Wait... stop!
This is unreal, doing it with my guy friends!
Wh-Woah, your cheek feels good.
Take it in already.
Oh, can I really?
It's Nao, so no need to hold back.
Y-You're kidding, right?
I can't breathe.
It feels so good!
Shut up.
Hey, help me with this too.
What... what?
I can't understand what you're saying.
Don't leave me out on this.
Oh no, my mouth really feels stuffed.
Please be over already.
Hurry.
Oh crap, it's coming out.
It's coming out!
Blowjobs sure feel great.
Okay, next is this one.
Ouch, ouch!
Lie down a bit, you can go one more round, right?
What are you saying?
Well, I guess it can be really tough.
So I'll just squirt it all on you.
Open your clothes.
Wh-What?!
Hey, if you don't do it soon, your clothes will be soiled.
What?
I just can't let my clothes be soiled with that!
Just wait!
Here I go.
I'm cumming!
He really squirted it out.
My clothes, aren't soiled.
Jeez, okay we're done.
You're satisfied with this already, right?
Hey, move oven!
Do you really want to end it like this?
The way you look.
I can only see you as inviting someone to do it.
No, that's gross!
I said no!
What are you doing?
So you're actually wearing a bra.
I thought you never wore one because they're too small.
Idiot, idiot!
You two!
Ohh... so you're wearing these kinds of panties.
For real?
Doesn't really suit you.
I guess this is your "dare" panties, right?
What's going on?
What's this? It feels so soft.
Wow, amazing.
You've got to be kidding me!
You said I'd just do a handjob!
Things are really getting out of hand.
There's no pubic hair.
It looks smooth.
Stop!
So, wh-what am I supposed to do now?
Play with it.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Like this?
That's just some totally not erotic voice.
Why?
Ouch!
You just bit me!
And you always used to say that I'm not even sexy one bit.
It's gotten wet already.
But he's gotten really cocky in this situation.
L-Let me go.
It feels so warm.
No, not there.
Stop.
Hey, so you can let out such a cute moan.
That's not.
She really came!
It's squeezing me really tightly!
If I put my dick here.
I can't hold back anymore.
I can do it, right?
Well, I guess she's prepared already.
Something's still.
Huh? It's around here, right?
Huh?
No need to hurry.
That's why you're still a virgin, your now.
Shut up!
No way... no way, no way!
Oopsie, hey, don't move.
You can't do that!
Please stop, really!
Huh? This is quite difficult.
No, I can still overlook this if you stop now.
Hey, do you understand your current situation?
Wait... are you guys.
You can't do anything anymore.
You can't escape.
Don't you understand that you can't resist anymore?
Really this strong?
It's so wet.
Oh, worried about your boyfriend?
It'll be over before he comes.
This spot is.
No, stop.
No, please, don't go any futher!
Please... at least.
He's really going to do it.
Use a condom.
Oh, it's okay to do it with a condom then?
You're way too easy.
Save me, save me please, Oikawa-kun!
Well, I guess I could put it on.
But, I don't have one.
Man, too bad, I'd put it on right away if I had one, you know.
These guys.
I have one here.
So please put it on
have never been scared like this?
See? I knew you two were going all out later.
No, I just got it from.
No excuses.
You like sex that much? How slutty.
What else is there to explain with this condom?
If you really want it badly, I'll use it, then.
So ease your worries.
So... are we ready for the main thing?
I'm really about to.
You're really noisy.
But!
Hey, it's in already.
Can you feel it?
Say something, will you?
You're body's way too stiff.
Are you nervous?
My dick's being sucked in!
So scary. Girl's pussies can be so scary.
I don't understand a thing anymore.
Wait, I really can't pull my dick out.
Come on, relax.
He was a virgin, you know.
Oh, just a bit.
Amazing.
I'm really having sex right now!
Hey, now where's the spunk you had earlier?
You've gone completely docile now.
You're not really like that, you know.
I can feel it all throughout me at times.
What is this?
It's rare for you to be this timid.
You'd have looked cuter if you were always like this.
Oh crap, oh crap.
I'm cumming
I'm about to cum!
Oh crap!
That's really fast, you know.
But, she was really squeezing me tightly.
And why did you pull it out?
We... really did it.
I thought it was about to eat my dick off.
Well, that's a virgin for you.
Oh well, it's my turn now.
Just rest over there.
Just how tight are you really?
I really can't pull the condom out.
Wait.
Hey, could this actually be
your first time?
I guess not.
What.