A-Size
God, it's hot. I'm so tired.
Let's take a break.
The fan's not making it any cooler.
Suck it up, that's all I've got.
You guys need to quieten down.
Move your hands, not your mouths.
Yeah, whatever.
Sorry, my Mom needs me to run an errand for her.
What? Riko-chan, you're leaving already?
That sucks, but do what you gotta do.
Sorry guys.
I'll walk you to the door.
Don't slack off, got it?
It won't be easy keeping them in line.
Don't give up, okay?
Yeah, it's gonna be rough.
Oh yeah, isn't Oikawa-kun coming over later?
Y-Yeah...
You guys are probably going
on a date after this, aren't you?
U-Uh... maybe?
Here, take this.
Doing it bareback isn't safe, ya know?
I don't need this!
Girls need to be careful
when they do these things.
You need to be a bit more feminine, Nao.
Bye! See you tomorrow!
Be more feminine?
I don't know what she means.
Classmate
Sorry about that.
Let's get this over with, shall we?
Why are you guys slacking off already?
Well, Riko-chan's not here anymore.
Can't do anything without
my source of motivation present.
What? If your source of motivation is a girl,
then you've got one right here.
Shut up, ugly!
Girl? Where?
Girls are quiet, nice, cute...
You guys really piss me off! Just shut up
and move your hands, not your mouths!
– Ugh, damn it. This sucks...
– Sheesh, they're so out of control.
Where's Oikawa?
He'll be late because he has
something he needs to do first.
That's not fair! I have things to do too!
Really? Probably something stupid, right?
Oikawa-kun's different than you guys.
He actually takes things seriously.
What, are you sticking up for your boyfriend?
Wait, did you think that was a secret?
It was so obvious.
Wait, what? What's going on?
Huh, you didn't know?
Oikawa and Nao are apparently dating.
You're fricking kidding me! He has such bad taste!
I'd never have paired those two together.
There are so many cuter girls out there.
Now I'm fricking pissed!
Just shut up already and do your homework!
Hey...
What?
So Oikawa and her...
I messed up. I can't believe they found out about me.
It's gonna be annoying now that I've got
these two making rumors up about me.
They've always bullied me, ever since we were little.
Why are you guys chatting when you
should be working? What's so interesting?
Nothing really...
So listen, this guy over here...
Shut up!
He was wondering if you guys
have already done it or not.
Well, we're talking about Oikawa,
I bet he's already made a move, but...
But just looking at you,
I feel like that's not possible.
So yeah, have you or haven't you?
Wh-What the heck are you asking me?
That isn't something you ask the person directly!
I don't see a problem really.
It's none of your business!
Yeah, it isn't. We're just curious.
Eat shit and die!
You're being so defensive.
Does this mean you actually have done it?
Screw you!
Wow.
You got something to say?
No, I was just thinking that
you really are a girl, aren't you?
You have a bad mouth, you're all over the place,
and you're not cute at all... you don't act like a girl, but...
Hot damn, you're already having sex.
That's like weirdly hot.
How do I say this...
I feel like I'm seeing you differently now.
What?!
Now that I get a good look at you, you're pretty cute.
Aren't you being a bit too rude?!
But look, I'm getting so hard.
You've really done it already, right? Wow!
Please, just jack me off a little. Please?
I can't go back to work like this.
H-Hey! Yuuji, don't just sit there!
Yeah, yeah.
This guy is getting way too carried away.
Calm down, won't you?
Yeah, you tell him!
Just one time and he'll calm down, right?
Today's so hot, you know?
Okay, bring it here. Bring it on!
Can't you act a bit more erotic to set the mood?
I can't do it because it's you!
After this, hurry up and finish your homework, okay?
Come on, touch it already!
Okay, all I have to do is finish this, then...
Wait, why the heck am I doing this?!
You're really bad at this, aren't you?
Hey, what are you doing?!
I don't feel any love.
Why would you?!
Your handjob sucks, so how about
you use your mouth to give me a blowjob?
What?! I never said I'd go that far!
No! Stop!
It's not right for friends to be doing this!
Oh crap, your cheek feels so good.
Come on, stick it in.
Really? Can I?
Yeah, come on. Do it already.
N-No way! Th-This can't be happening!
I can't breathe!
This feels so fricking good!
Shut up.
Hey, take care of mine too.
What? What's going on?
I can't understand you at all.
Don't let me be the odd one out.
Stop! I can't breathe at all!
Hurry up and finish already!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Your blowjob felt so good!
Okay, I'm up next.
S-Stop!
You want it in your mouth again?
What are you sayi...
Well, it doesn't look like you can handle another one,
so just let me cum on you. Better take off your clothes.
Hurry up or your clothes are gonna get dirty.
Wait, if his cum gets on my clothes...
Th-There's no way I can let that happen!
Hey, wai...
Here I go! I'm cumming!
He really came... D-Did it get on my clothes?
Okay, okay. Were done now, right?
You're satisfied, aren't you?
Get off me!
Are you sure you wanna leave it like this?
Like this, it looks like you were
the one begging me to cum on you.
No, stop! That feels gross! What are you doing?!
So you really do wear a bra.
I thought you wouldn't 'cuz your tits are so small.
Screw you! Screw you! You guys need to...
Oh, so you wear these kinds of panties?
Seriously? They don't suit you at all.
Are these your "battle undies"?
What?
Oh my god, it's so soft.
Holy crap!
You're kidding, right? I didn't agree to this!
They keep ramping up
the things they're doing to me.
Where's the hair? You're so smooth.
Stop!
Wh-What do I do with this?
Play with it a little.
Stop it! Stop, you jerks!
Like this?
Your voice is so not sexy.
Why is this happening?
That hurt! Why the hell'd you bite me?
You guys are always telling me
I'm not sexy at all, and yet...
You're getting wet!
Oh, so they have the motivation for this,
but not for their homework?
S-Stop! Let go of me!
It's so warm.
No, stop! Don't do that! Don't!
What's this? You're letting out a pretty cute moan.
I'm no...
She came! Holy crap, she came!
Damn, you're so tight now!
So if I put my dick in here...
I'm not waiting any longer.
I can put it in, right?
Well, I guess you've waited long enough.
No, something's...
Huh? It goes in here, doesn't it? Huh?
Geez, you virgins are such a handful.
Shut up!
Huh? No! Stop!
Whoa, don't move so much.
No, you can't! Seriously, stop!
What? Man, this is harder than I thought.
If you stop now, I'll forget this ever happened...
Do you know what position you're in right now?
Huh? Are guys really...
You're done. There's nowhere to run.
You know by now that there's
no point in resisting, don't you?
Are guys really this strong?
It's so wet and slippery...
Oh, are you worried about your boyfriend?
We'll stop right when he gets here.
Is this it?
No, don't! Stop!
Don't put it in!
At least...
They're serious about this...
At least put a condom on...
So it's okay as long as we have a condom on?
You're such a slut.
Save me! Please save me, Oikawa-kun!
I guess I could put one on for you.
But what a tragedy, I don't have any on me.
Looks like I can't put one on for you.
These guys...
I have one... So put it on.
Were they always this scary?!
So you really wanted us to screw you, huh?
No, I got this from...
I don't wanna hear your excuses.
You really wanna have sex that badly? You're such a slut.
How else do you explain having a condom with you?
If you want us to use it so badly,
then don't worry, we'll use it!
Now this is consensual sex.
Am I really going to...
You're so loud.
Yeah, but...
I'm all the way in! Can you tell?
Say something already.
You're stiff all over.
What, are you nervous or something?
Her pussy's sucking me in!
Pussies are so scary! So scary!
It's like... I don't know how to explain it!
I really can't take my dick out.
Calm down, okay? This guy's a virgin.
Oh, I can move a little.
Damn, this is amazing! I'm having sex!
What happened to all your spunk from before?
You've calmed down quite a bit, haven't you?
Didn't strike you as one of those kinds of girls.
I can feel it reverberating in my head! What's going on?!
I've never seen you so docile.
You'd be cute if you were always like this.
Holy crap man!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming! Sorry!
Crap!
Dude, you're so fast!
She was wrapping around me so tightly!
Why the heck'd you take it out of her?
He really had sex with me...
I thought the condom was gonna tear on me.
Yeah, I get it, you're a virgin.
Well, whatever. I'm up next.
You just rest over there or something.
How frickin' tight are you?
I seriously can't pull this out.
Huh?
Wait, you're a...
You're a virgin, aren't you?
Nah, there's no way...
What...?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: fyurie
editor: fyurie
quality check: fyurie