Translation
Timing
Editing
Bushido Philosopher
aka Altruist
bushido_philosopher@yahoo.com
merged by M.D. Geist
Raw provided by JackStorm @ HongFire.com
We shouldn't do this here, Tamaki.
You're right. There are so many young people outside.
Is it a bit big, miss?
Yes, very.
What?
It's quite easy to slip in.
How it does it feel to you?
Really... hard.
Do you need any help?
No... this feels just fine...
Wha...?
It's making squishy sounds.
Shall we put it in?
Accelerando
~ Whisper of Descending Angels ~
You're going to try again today, right?
Yeah.
A lovesick guy goes to a cafe...
...but won't stand up for himself.
Ohashi, just tell her already...
You've liked Tamaki since high school, right?
But, I have to think of Tamaki's feelings.
Don't worry about it.
She doesn't have everything together either.
All right, make sure you do it today.
I-I will.
I have to go on to work, so I'll be going.
I'll be waiting for the news.
Kuromo...
Hey, Tamaki.
You're back here again...
Hey, I'll always be here.
Wait, it's still my shift!
Don't worry. Besides, a maid has been placed on my lap.
That's what you had planned, right?
N-no I didn't.
I wonder if Tamaki is off today.
Ohashi is coming to see you today.
Oh, is he?
Do you think you'd ever go out with him?
Is he trying to ask me out?
If he is...
then he...
would surely be a lot better than you.
Then let's just see if he'll do it.
That's just...
not...
Well, I'd just like to the look on his face...
when he finds out how much of a nympho you are.
Is that all... you have... to say?
You think it'll be different?
Sex with Ohashi?
Sex with... Ohashi?
It's tight.
It's flowing inside me...
W-wait a sec!
What is this?
Can't keep that guy waiting...
If Tamaki isn't here, then I can't do it.
I'll just go.
Welcome.
It doesn't look like it's the three of us this time.
Yeah, it looks like Kuramo is busy now.
Really? I can't imagine what he'd be doing though.
Something wrong?
No, just something smells.
Isn't it the coffee?
Here, doesn't it smell like coffee got in my hair?
No, I don't think.
I have something to do so, sorry.
Take your time.
S-sure.
Guess you couldn't help yourself.
I'm about to explode myself.
Turn around and lift your skirt.
What did he say to you?
He just didn't say anything, like usual.
With these many pheromones, surprised he didn't.
Whoa, it's spilling.
I have a lot to release today.
I still have to put up with that?
Just until Ohashi says he likes you.
Hey, uh... Tamaki.
Huh? Oh, another coffee, right?
Hold on a sec.
Oh, sure, I mean...
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Sorry, I'll be right back.
Don't splash it around.
It's not my fault your ass goes like that.
But...
The bathroom...
That's all... my body... can hold.
Don't spill it just yet.
Are you alright? You feeling bad?
Huh?
I'm fine.
What is it?
Tamaki...
I, uh...
Yes, what is it?
Ever since high school...
I've had... well for you...
I can't take it!
Ta - ma - ki?
Gotta use, the bathroom!
Hey, how'd it g--
MOVE IT!!
Please, let me do this.
Here goes...
Since there's so much of this, it looks like Ohashi...
won't do anything.
Here it comes.
No! If you take it out--
If Ohashi saw this, he'd lose it.
Thank you for coming!
I can't...
I couldn't find what to say to her.
It's a cafe...
What are we doing here?
I didn't think it would matter for a friend to ask such a thing.
I should start to close up.
I'll be out back.
No progress today either...
Ohashi's never going to change.
He should just say it.
Leave him be!
That's what's so good about him.
That aside, give me back my panties from yesterday!
And, stop coming back here.
What's with the weird getup?
Hey, wait.
Ohashi's waiting for me.
Once I change, I can't go back.
I really don't get you!
I thought this place was closed already.
This is a robbery. Stay still.
Please don't joke around like that.
This isn't a joke.
That girl there, she's quite pretty, isn't she?
I wonder if she's alright?
Did something happen to Tamaki?
I wonder...
Why don't you see for yourself?
Is that thing real?
Oh, would you like me to try it out?
Look through that door.
Tamaki?
Take a good look.
Right down there.
You...
What can you expect?
Seeing the the girl you like is quite sexy, isn't it?
Oh, and it seems you can't contain yourself.
If you keep sucking like that...
Don't come just yet.
What is it?
It's good to punish you every now and then.
But you always do that to me.
Make sure to give me some fellatio.
Your friend is over here.
Honestly, did he really have to switch places?
Don't do that so suddenly.
What a pretty, dripping face.
Tamaki...!
Don't try to talk.
How does fellatio from that girl feel?
Now, let's go back to the front.
I'll let you have even more fun.
Just what are you after?
Have you had any real sex before?
Then I suppose you would be a virgin.
Let me see you have sex with her right here.
There's no way I could do that!
It's easy!
All you have to do is just stick it in here.
You don't have to be embarrassed.
We'll both go outside.
But remember...
If you do anything suspicious, you'll get a bullet in the head.
Sorry for taking so long.
I guess I spaced out for a while.
You don't have to spare my feelings.
It's true. I just spaced out.
Tamaki!
Hey, wh- wait.
I have to this.
But, like this...
So suddenly...
Right here!?
It has to be here!
Oh, okay.
How'd it go?
They started.
Tamaki, I can't take it.
Yeah, me neither, so...
Let's put it in.
Can you see it?
Yeah.
Don't move.
I'll do it for you.
Tamaki, that feels great!
Go ahead.
Don't hold it in.
Come inside me.
It's coming out...
All your come.
That girl's really experienced, isn't she?
Well, she did do all that with me.
Hey, why are you hard?
I didn't get to finish up back there.
Speaking of which, Tomoe...
Your tits are hard.
Since we saw all that, shall we?
Let's.
I'll have to clean this up later.
Since you're making such a mess.
Do it, as hard as you want.
So good!
More! More! Harder!
Good!
So - damn - good!
Here it comes!
Y-You idiot! You're coming inside!
Huh? That a bad thing?
Of course it is!
Come inside!
Tamaki!
This way it'll be easier.
Tamaki, make sure not to talk.
You too, Ohashi. Don't make any weird sounds.
Miss, do you need any help?
No, ah-
I - I'm coming, now.
I coming out now!
You really came a lot.
Miss?
How was the size?
Ah, well, it was...
So-so.
I meant his.
Tamaki, we've been found out.
Thank you for watching and supporting my fansub work.
Now please enjoy the upcoming promo. (Also translated.)
Preview
Accelerando
~ Descent of Fallen Angels ~
CONTENTS.2
will be released in April of 2007.
The second one looks like my story.
I wonder what kind of story it'll be.
The wait will surely be worth it!
P.S. from merger+reuploader :
If you plan on releasing more stuff, please do so on --PUBLIC-- trackers !!