What's wrong? Hurry it up.
That hurts...
You're still so small.
Now I have to pack it in there.
Well, rest assured that I can do what Touru can't.
What's with that dirty look?
It pisses me off!
If you mention any of this to Touru, I'll make
sure his father never lands a decent job.
And don't you forget that!
Accelerando
CONTENTS.2 [In the school]
~ Whispers of Fallen Angels ~
Hands up!
Bang!
Hey, don't surprise me like that.
You were waiting for me.
I'm sorry.
No, it's all right.
You'll fuck with nearly anyone.
Let's see how you deal with me.
Yet you're still as bitchy as ever.
It's getting pretty twisted in there.
I wonder why you won't just admit that this is feeling good.
Whoa now. This thing needs some good exercise.
Now then, would you like it inside or outside?
Please, outside!
No fucking way, you don't really have a choice here.
You did say inside, didn't you?
Stop it, you freak!
I didn't have the heart to do it outside.
Do you have another place where you can get money?
I wonder where he'll get the money for the operation then.
Oh damn...
It got all squishy inside.
You're a real screamer.
Tomoe, you're hurt.
Just a little scratch.
I'm all right.
But how are you feeling, Touru?
I'm getting by.
And I have you to thank for that.
It'll be great if you got better quickly.
I almost have enough for the operation.
Then there's the treatment.
For someone like me to get special treatment...
I can't believe it.
What do you mean?
You deserve it, Touru.
Be more confident.
Thank you.
Still going home with Touru?
I'm surprised you're able to face him.
He must be a fucking retard.
You're going with him today too, aren't you?
All over again...
Why don't we end it here today.
You're peeing.
You're really trembling a lot.
Well, doing this with you everyday, something's gotta give.
Tomorrow's gonna to be fun.
Hey preppy.
Going home with Tomoe-chan again?
Hey wait now, I don't appreciate your indifference.
Or the look that you're giving me either.
Hey, glad you came.
You're really in for something today.
Hey, open up!
Shit!
Why won't it open!? Hey!!
Hey!! That you Tomoe!?
Open it!
Tomoe!!
Hey! There's a fire!
Toward the back of campus!
I heard someone's in there!
Were you waiting, Touru?
Touru?
Oh well.
He always waits for me.
Besides, now neither of us has to anymore.
Help me!
Now we can be together forever...
Touru...
Hey...
What's this I'm seeing?
This feels unbelievable.
Where is this?
I feel like... I've seen this before.
Coming!
Same here.
Drink up.
I'm coming!
How... Why did this happen?
Every Wednesday.
At the same time.
He takes his spot.
And does some weird things there.
He peeps into the girls locker room.
Enjoying himself thoroughly.
And the same group talks in the guys' bathroom.
It's so big...
But...
It'll fit in me.
It's such a bad thing to think about.
Inside my body.
It'll be inside me, right here.
I wonder if the girls that are changing...
...are really oblivious that they're being watched?
No, I'm sure that everyone's noticed.
After all girls like that take pride in being watched.
It wouldn't be good if people knew what you were doing.
Move your hands.
Come on, show me.
A-All right.
It's already hard.
Would you like us to calm it down?
Women's hands and mouths all over you...
You want a taste of that, don't you?
It'll be much better than doing it yourself.
Well, how's your first fellatio going?
It feels... great.
I-I'm coming.
Are you done already, little virgin?
This isn't over yet.
Come on, do some cunnilingus.
You wanted to lick one of these, right?
Be sure to rub my breasts strongly.
Rub your hand against me here.
Everyone will take advantage of your whole body.
Not like that would actually happen though.
He's rubbing it so harshly.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, I can't stop.
Just one finger is this intense...
I-Is he coming?
He came. Gross...
But...
So dirty...
Oh, someone's peeing.
So am I.
Wh...
What?
What is... this?
What's going on?
I've always wondered when I'd get a chance.
This must be what you want, since you're sopping wet.
Huh? Those words...
Look how sticky it is.
Would you like us to calm it down?
You wanted to know how a man's
dick inside you feels, right?
Huh? No! Wait!
It'll be much better than doing it yourself.
Yeah...
It's pulsing all around me.
This is great.
Here, take this.
You've always been watching this.
You want to suck it, don't you?
Wow, I never knew that her mouth would feel so pleasant.
Her hand job feels great.
Come on, jerk it like you mean it.
Shit.
I'm coming.
I'm going to come too.
The real thing really does feel great.
All right, let's switch.
Suck on mine too.
That's nice...
Up until now I've had to put up with just watching you.
I should've done this sooner.
Well...
How... did this all happen?
Oh yeah... This situation I'm in...
I wanted to see him like that.
Coming.
Because of that...
Damn, me too.
To watch him.
C-Coming!
What I wanted..
I wanted to help someone...
Seems I already got something good out of it.
I can only offer one payment...
It's not about money...
I only take jobs where I can get a good feeling out of it.
Feeling, huh?
I've heard that you take jobs to
help people so you can atone.
Ever since your former life ended.
I'll do it.