New Space Century: The year 3113
Mankind has left the solar system
in search of life-sustaining habitats.
Thirty centuries have passed
since the planet
Earth was consumed by toxic pollutants.
At that time, mankind commenced a
desperate search for habitable planets.
A few planets were quickly found
and the exodus from Earth began.
The ensuing mass exodus from Earth
resulted in
the creation of
a new interplanetary government;
and it was decreed
that all new planets and space
colonies would fall
under the jurisdiction
of The Allied Earth Government,
the Domestic Union of Arms (DUA).
In outer space, to this day,
divisions of the DUA
continue to comb the cosmos
for new planets,
for untapped natural resources, and
for lands fit for habitation.
Of uncharted planets
involves grave danger.
To this end,
DUA has no choice but to depend
on professional explorers
called Advancers.
Advancers,
the chosen ones who boldly land
on unexplored planets
without concern for their
individual safety and lives,
partake in the most
unmerciful of missions:
Fully exposed human
sacrifices
furthering the cause of mankind.
Today, however,
the once elite Advancer corps
include former treasure hunters
and drifters with
unknown pasts among its honored ranks.
This is Mugal, DUA,
Development Department.
This is Vanessa Gronne, Warden of M-99,
Women's special prison.
When was Tina Owen sent to you?
6 months, 13 days ago,
Earth Standard Time, sir.
Tell her I'm coming.
But Tina is serving
a 2000 year sentence.
I know that!
What a surprise.
She is jailed so nearby.
"Long time, Tina."
I don't remember inviting you.
Don't be so cold.
I've come to set you free.
After all, it was I who first asked you
to take that job;
though you did exceed your authority
by destroying that foul planet.
For the record,
it was difficult even for me
to get your sentence lowered
to 2000 years.
I am not interested in your excuses,
nor intention of giving you mine.
I feel responsible for you.
Ha! I know what's on your mind!
As always, you merely seek
to promote your own self interests by
taking advantage of those
who have no control over their lives;
like me, rotting in this hell-hole
serving a 2000 year sentence.
You're pretty sharp.
Anyway, this new planet is so horrible
that even the bravest Advancers
are afraid of it.
Tina, I need your help.
What's the deal?
If you find a habitable zone,
I'll see that your sentence is voided.
You'll do it? I've brought you
everything you'll need.
And I will procure
anything you request.
Let me take a shower.
...a shower?
Not an air shower either!
It has to be a hot water shower,
Earth-style!
All right...
but that's a luxury in outer space.
This prison doesn't even have
such facilities...
But you can enjoy one in my cruiser.
Don't peek.
I know.
I have no intention of getting
chewed out by you, at least not yet.
R
Ri
Rip
Ripp
Rippe
Ripped
Ripped B
Ripped By
Ripped By H
Ripped By Ha
Ripped By Han
Ripped By Hana
Ripped By Hanak
Ripped By Hanako
You look incredible, Tina.
I am more concerned about
the types of men you are going
to attract than the actual danger
surrounding your mission.
What if I were to run away right now?
I know you won't do that.
You'd never be at peace
on the run with a 2000 year
sentence hanging over your head.
I've studied all your data
on the planet, Omega-13.
The survival rate is a paltry 1.75%.
I believe that's enough for you.
Aren't you overestimating me?
Good luck.
This is Space station M-75.
Level D.
Due to the many transients
who take residence here,
it is rated as
the most lawless station in the galaxy.
Also the largest black market
in the galaxy can be found here.
Hey, sweetheart,
what are you looking for?
I've got a great dick.
Hey, let's have some fun!
You've got an awesome body!
Don't mess with me...
I'll carve your eyes out!
That bitch!
I'm gonna kill you!!
Ready yourself!
What is a nice girl like you doing
in a place like this?
Take a hike.
At least you've got spirit.
Probably more than those outlaws.
Where's the black market?
Hmmm, are you intending
to go shopping there?
I'll find it myself
if you won't tell me.
What do you want?
A ship. One that is suitable
for treasure hunting.
With as many features as possible.
Allow me to escort you there.
3.6 million bol?
This used to be an Advancer,
Captain Ho's favorite ship!
In fact, it is not the type of item
one can usually purchase,
unless Ho is retiring, of course!
4 million bol!
Excellent, Garuda!
You truly have a discerning eye.
Are you planning to go
on another gold hunt?
I'm looking for a planet
where I can escape from women!
Don Juan Garuda must finally
be in trouble!
If you want, this ship can even take you
all the way to hell: Omega-13!
4.5 million bol!
What?
You've got guts young lady!
4.5 million, anyone else?
5 million bol!
5.5 million!
Shit! 5.6 million!
6 million!
What the fuck?!
Shit!
6 million! Sold!
Captain Ho's ship, "Spider,"
is now hers! But do you really
have that kind of money?
Check with the bank at port of entry.
I am Tina Owen, and I just got 6 million bol
in exchange for the newest DUA ship.
All right.
Come and sign the required documents.
You're very lucky. Rarely can one
obtain a prized-ship like Captain Ho's.
On top of it, you out-bid Garuda;
a man with a most discerning eye!
Tina... Owen...
That's too bad.
L-I'm not a thief!
Well, weren't you just trying
to steal this? Weren't you?
I was hoping to carry it for you!
You don't have a place
to stay on this station, yet, do you?
I'll take you there!
Please, let me do things for you!
I'm much more useful than you think!
What about your family?
L-I'm alone.
I'm a space refugee, an orphan.
But don't feel sorry for me!
I'm doing quite fine on my own!
Okay, come on.
R-Really!?
I'm starving.
I know a good place!
What's your name?
Frill.
Okay. Frill, you don't have to pretend
to be a boy in front of me.
You are a girl, aren't you?
Y-You knew that!?
My name is...
Tina, Tina Owen!
Were you watching?
Yes! You were so cool!
And on top of it,
you're extraordinarily beautiful!
Do you want to compete with me?
Garuda!
She's the kind of chick you rarely see.
Leave Tina alone!
She's not the kind of woman
that you flirt with!
What are you talking about?
What are you to her, huh?
Damn...
I'm sorry, but this is the only place
that's open.
But the food here is the best!
Thanks to you,
I was able to get a room with a door.
It's so surprising:
You're telling me that most hotel rooms
on this station don't have doors?
That's right.
"A long time ago, when supply ships
were unable to reach this"
station and its heating system
broke-down, the station's residents were
forced to get their heat from everything
and anything they could burn.
Frill,
do you want to stay here with me?
L-Is that okay?
Do you have any other place to go?
Until the space ship
I just purchased at auction is ready,
there are a number of things
I need you to get for me.
I'll do anything for you, Tina.
But, then... you are going to dump me
after that, right?
I'm going to a place
where I can't take you.
Yes, Tina, you belong to a better world.
I can tell."
No, it's not that.
I'm going to a place where survival
is far from guaranteed.
That's why I can't take you.
Tina?
After you finish your meal,
go and gather as much information
as possible...
about the planet Omega-13.
But that planet is...
It's my mission.
So, you're an Advancer!?
That's right. And if I survive,
I will come back here
so that we can see each other again.
Can you hire me?
My name is Akira Sato.
Have you been following me?
I don't have malicious intentions.
To tell you the truth,
this is the very area where
all my money
and my ship's key were stolen...
from a hotel room without a door.
How stupid!
If I don't take action now,
I am probably going to die
in some ditch on this station.
I've worked on Advancer crews
twice previously;
though both times,
the missions failed...
I have been waiting here
for another job as an Advancer.
What do you know about Omega-13?
I know a lot more
than that little twerp!
Screw you!
I've got sharp ears!
I'll decide
on whether to hire you or not
after hearing more
of what you've got to say.
Frill, can you get the medical supplies
and the parts I've written down here?
And also,
purchase whatever information you can.
No sweat!!
You'd better let me do it!
I'm telling you, you'll feel good!
Stop! Please stop!
We are in God's service!
Even God will be pleased
when you do it with me!
So stop struggling!!
Miss!!
Whoops... They're fake nuns!
She's got a really shapely ass!
Let go!
Stop! Stop!
This will be
absolutely unforgettable for you!
S-Someone! H-Help!
You bastards!
Who the fuck are you?
Garuda?
Joanna!
You maggots...
Garuda, I missed you so much.
Idiot! What were you thinking
trailing after me disguised as a nun?
Garuda, I'm not going to leave you.
Don't run away.
You will leave here, tomorrow!
I've got a job to do, understand?
I owe you one.
No need to thank me.
Your luck has run out, Garuda.
Shut the fuck up!
So far, seven Advancer parties
have left for Omega-13.
But none have returned yet.
Nine parties, actually.
Two other parties were unofficial:
Treasure hunters.
Frill's sharp ears
aren't so bad after all!
See. I told you!
That explains why there's no data
available detailing Omega-13's surface.
The fact that treasure hunters have set
there sights there
indicates that it must
have some valuable natural resources,
even if the planet is uninhabitable!
That's true. However, according to
surveillance data from our satellite,
87% of the planet's surface falls
within the "high temperature" zone.
It could be like a scorched desert.
Worse, even if there is oxygen,
there could also be noxious pollutants.
If you want to quit,
you should do it now.
If I quit now, you'll be unemployed
effective immediately!
Is that acceptable?
What am I going do?
I have no desire to view your corpse.
Akira is a chicken!
I'm going with you, Tina!
Hey!!
Say it's okay, Tina!
I have nowhere else to go.
Please take me with you!
Aren't you afraid of dying?
Nothing compares to the loneliness
of being all-alone...
Okay, come with me.
Tina!
I'm going, too.
I just didn't want to let you go if
I could possibly stop you.
Akira, haven't you been waiting for
an opportunity to go to Omega-13,
from the very beginning?
What!?
What's your real intention?
The same as Garuda's!
He just wants to strike-it-rich!
No, that's not right!!
I'm after the man who killed my parents
and my sister!
I know
that he passed through this station.
Ortega is his name;
a fallen Advancer,
who is now a pirate.
You think he's on Omega-13?
If he's still alive.
Once he strikes gold, however,
I'm sure
he'll pass back through this station.
It is for that day,
that I have remained here, waiting.
Why don't you sleep on it
until tomorrow.
You're not really compelled to go.
Tina, why do you so emphatically adhere
to Omega-13?
As an Advancer,
you should be able to
choose a planet
with a much higher survival rate.
It's a deal I have made
for the commutation
of a 2000 year prison sentence.
Sorry, but I prefer not to discuss it.
Okay. I'm going with you, too.
I can't just simply watch you go.
Good night, Tina, Frill.
He has a crush on you.
What?
He likes you! I can tell.
It's shows in his eyes...
by the way he looks at you!
Frill, a bit precocious, aren't you?
It's so good!! Garuda!
I won't leave you!
It's so good!!
It's good! It's good!
I'm the Grim Reaper.
Do you understand that?
I'll follow you anywhere! Garuda!
So-o-o... Garuda!
Together, we'll... Ah! G-Garuda!
Tina, It's a beautiful planet.
Can you see what's in my mind?
Yes, I am born with supernatural powers.
I can talk to islands,
fish, even plants.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I can link my heart with yours, too.
Is this the planet
you're originally from?
Probably.
But my memory suddenly goes blank
at this point.
Is it by any chance
the legendary planet, Noah?
I don't know.
Noah is only a legend.
No one has ever confirmed
its existence.
Can you see me
when I was at around your age?
Yes.
I only remember that period vaguely,
in bits-and-pieces.
In fact, clear,
concrete memories don't actually
start until I was about 14 years old;
when I was
in DUA's Pioneer Training Center...
What about your family?
I don't know...
I'm sort of like you.
Do you want to see them?
Yes.
But if it is the planet Noah which is
appearing in my memory,
it is probably
nothing more than an illusion I've
created from some past dream.
Try and remember more.
Someday you will learn the truth
once and for all.
Well... I wonder...
Hey, you look cool, Frill!
If you want to propose to me,
it's now or never!
Fool! You're ten years too early.
Is everything ready?
Aye-aye, Captain!
Hey, let's get moving!
Are you going to Omega-13, too?
Who knows? Get in touch with me
if you get in trouble.
I don't feel comfortable
"owing you one."
Garuda must have obtained some
secret data we're not privy to.
It is better not to trust him too much.
Akira?
He is the type of man who would employ
any means to attain his objectives.
Let's go.
It's a gold mine!!
Joanna, you ladies stay here.
Is anyone there?
Garuda! Garuda! Help!!
Miss Joanna!
Eva, what are we going to do?
But Master Garuda told us not to move.
B-But... Let's get out!
Let's go where Garuda is!
Cecil, Eva,
if we stay here we'll get killed.
Come on! Quickly!
Holy shit! Gold everywhere!
Look!!
It's Garuda's ship!
It's being attacked
by an alien creature
coming out of that drifting ship!
"This is Tina from Spider."
"Garuda, come back! Garuda!"
They must all be
inside the drifting ship!
I'm coming with you, too!
Frill, you stay here!
If that creature attacks,
you must flee immediately.
Otherwise, we won't be able
to come back either.
Okay!
You know how to operate this,
don't you?
Yes, I do! Tina!?
Don't worry!
Okay, Tina. Come back soon!
They're not here!
They must be in the transport vessel!
Tina!
Is this a voice recorder!?
S-Shit!
Miss Joanna, run!
Cecil! Eva!
Go to Master Garuda!
No-o-o-o!
Eva!
What a sight.
Garuda!
Joanna!
Eva and Cecil...
Fuck!
There are no survivors here.
I located the voice recorder.
It will tell us
of the last moments on this ship.
Let's get out!
Okay!
Oh... Tina...
Tina!!
Frill!
Tina, hurry!!
Garuda, after you!
I appreciate it!
Wait for me!
Tina!?
Frill, Joanna is okay now.
Good work.
You did well in protecting the ship!
We're now going to enter
the atmosphere!
The targeted landing point selected by
Tina is within the "mild climate" area!
Garuda, play the voice recorder!
This is incredible!
It's the gold strike of a lifetime.
What's going on?
You didn't leave me any water,
any food!?
Are you intending to monopolize
the riches of this planet!?
Drop dead, Ortega!
Why, you son-of-a-bitch!
Ortega!
W-What's that!?
Nauman! ...What happened!?
Akira...
I'll save my revenge for next time.
As soon as Tina discovers
a habitable zone,
we should return to the station.
I can come back here by myself.
I see, that's what it is.
Garuda! Your purpose
must be the same as Ortega's!
Don't bring Ortega into this until
Tina finishes her mission!
Well first, we have to land safely!
We don't know what's gonna
happen next!
You mother fucker!!
Akira!
Garuda is free to go his own
way after we land!
Don't be so short-tempered!
She seems far more reasonable than you.
For the record, I don't want to be
indebted to her any more, either.
So don't worry.
We're entering the atmosphere now!
Frill, let's get ready!
Aye-aye.
Hey, buddy,
you've fallen in love with her!
Temperature: 110 F
Humidity: 20%
No harmful bacteria
or toxic pollutants detected.
We are way off
our targeted landing point.
We're lucky to be alive.
We can just manage
with the oxygen on this planet.
But we should be careful to conserve
as much oxygen as possible.
Thanks for everything.
First, I am going to fix my ship,
"Boar."
Then I'll definitely pay-you-back.
You have
such a strong sense of obligation.
Just don't get in our way,
that's all I ask.
She misjudges me!
Tina... I don't know what to say.
But I could not save your friends...
Be careful...
You, too...
It's hot!
Tina, this is like a sauna!
Akira, once we complete
our initial investigation,
we'll rest until night time.
Aye-aye, Ma'am.
Frill, once darkness falls
it's going to get very cold.
Pace yourself.
Collect samples of all plants, minerals
and small living things,
as you come across them.
Yes, Ma'am!
Stay within sight
of the exploring vehicle at all times.
Since we are consuming
so much energy in this heat,
we will conclude our work.
Aye-aye, Ma'am!
But, Tina?
Yes?
It sure is a hot planet,
and I wonder...
what could have prevented Ortega and
the other Advancers from returning.
Actually,
I was thinking the same thing.
You must not underestimate this planet.
Something beyond your worst nightmares
could suddenly transpire,
so be sure to
never leave yourself exposed!
Sure! You, too, Tina!
I don't see even a single plant...
But then how is oxygen on this
planet being generated?
Frill!
What's the matter, Frill!?
Frill!!
Tina... I...
didn't tell you..., but,
I'm mix blooded:
Half human, half Shamoan...
When my body senses
something abnormal...,
my Shamoan features come out.
And I now feel
an enormous number of plants...
On top it,
they are so powerful and violent.
Akira! Akira!
Garuda, let's go back!
I feel the temperature dropping.
Not so fast.
We came here
to do some treasure hunting!
Do you hear that?
It must be a vein of gold!!
There, the opening
that is showing on the surface!?
Or it might even be Ortega's
and that other guys' excavation site!
Garuda!! Stop!
Wait here.
I will just go in and see what's
in there. That will be it for today.
If something happens,
you drive the land cruiser.
Got it?
Is this Ortega?
Garuda!!
Holy shit! We've got to go back!
Shit!
Tina! Hurry into the space ship!
Frill! Quickly!
Akira!
No-o-o!
Frill!
Frill! Get a hold of yourself!
Ti... Tina?
Okay, listen carefully!
I'll stop them right here.
You go to the back engine room
and open the
emergency cockpit!
The ship will execute
an emergency lift-off!
We will tear ourselves away from them.
Got it!
Akira! Akira! Are you alive!?
Akira!
Are you all okay, Tina?
Garuda! S-Shit!
Joanna!
Holy S-Shit!
Tina, please take care of Joanna!
I am... PAYING YOU BACK!!
Garuda!!
Joanna!!
Tina, hurry up!
T-Tina! Abandon me and run away!
No, I can't do that.
Akira, open the door!
Phew, we've made it...
What a horrible planet!
Tina,
there's something wrong with Joanna!
Take the helm of the ship!
Put some clothes on.
My self-control cannot withstand
much more of this.
No-o-o-o!
Frill, go to Akira!
But...
Go now!!
It can't be...
How do you like
the greatest force in the cosmos?
From now on,
I will rule the entire cosmos!
I'll devour all pleasures
that exist in space!
No-o-o-o!
Tina!!
Ortega!?
You'll be my nutritional ecstasy.
Thank you, Akira.
Idiot!! Don't look!
Tina,
I've forwarded your report regarding
planet Omega-13 to HQ.
Once HQ verifies your report,
your sentence will be reduced
to 1000 years.
Why?!
She found you a gold-filled planet!
You cheapskate!
Is this little one the new crew member
you were talking about?
Yes, the one-and-only!
Hey! Don't forget about me!
So... what is my next assignment?
It is still being discussed.
You can relax here for a while.
Is there anything you want...
Why, a hot water shower,
Earth-style would be nice.
And after that,
I just want to sleep like-a-log.
You shall have it!
Don't peek!