Yuu! Hey, Yuu!
What's wrong
Nothing
Just thinking about something.
Thinking about something? You?
Yeah
So you do take things seriously sometimes
Graduation, right?
You cant decide between college and employment?
But with your current grades,
I think college is a bit of a stretch
So go to Fuzoku with me, okay?
You're as carefree as always
You're as carefree as always.
See ya later.
Wh-What the hell?
And here I was just trying to help you
Jackass!
Takidani-kun.
I need to talk to you about something.
???? Really?
So, then go out with him!
Like, oh my God...
Nor not here.
No!
Don't
Yes.
Harder. Deeper!
Push it deep inside me!
Oh, no!
I cant hold back!
Its coming
Y-Ycs. I cant stop now!
Somethings coming
I'm cumming. I'm gonna cum!
Marry me.
But I...
Onii-chan..
Onii-chan!
I want you to.
I want you to mess me up, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
Nagisa-chan?
Abiko-san?
Nagisa-chan! I..
I can't hold back anymore.
No!
Stop it
But I... I cant stand watching you provide
a spectacle for dirty old men anymore.
I didn't want to do that
but I wanted Onii-chan to notice me.
That's why I want to become a star. So he would...
I'm not good enough?
I love you very much, Nagisa.
No! Stop it
No!
Don't Somebody will see us!
It's so...
Don't
So hot
Don't I can't take any more!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum! I.
Me too!
What did you want to talk about?
Yuuichi, did you decide about college yet?
You too? Everyone and his mom
is nagging me about that
Yuuichi, I've decided to study overseas
I already know that
And I proposed to Kanami
I'm serious
I really love her.
After I come home, I intend to marry her
Kanami! You... What do you want to do?
Of course she said yes,
Unlike someone else I could mention, she's not
afraid to make decisions about her future
I wont let anyone else have her
Don't make me laugh, Kotarou
Future, my ass! Marriage, my ass!
Kotarou! Do you have any idea what
condition Youko is in right now?
Wh-What do you mean?
Youko... is pregnant with your baby
Be a little more gentle, will you?
You're still a kid, all right
That should be okay
IfTakidani-kun punched your
it must've been something serious.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
It's about Kishi-san, isn't it?
How do you know about that?
I ran into her at the hospital
Hey! Arc you okay?
Kishi-san?
I want to get rid of it
Please, what's inside me...
I see.
Infirmary
ThatYouko. She didn't tell me
Stupid, if you ask me.
She really is stupid. I agree.
Urn meantiyou.
Why don't you relax a little?
You take everything too seriously
Yes.
Hurry
This feels great!
I love it
Takawashi-kun, I love this.
Harder. Deeper
This feels great!
Not yet
Just a bit more.
Yes.
Deeper
Scnsci...
I've always... wanted... you
Yes. You can have me.
I'm yours so...
Do what you want with me!
Yes!
This feels great
Harder.
Harder!
Rougher!
Do what you want with me!
More!
Yes!
I'm gonna cum.
Me too. I...
Inside! Give me your all... deep inside!
Fill me up... with your hot cum!
Oh, your little sister did that?
I'm not sure what to do.
You really are stupid.
You're the one who understands Nagisa-chan best
As her brother, you need to have faith in her.
Otherwise, who else will?
Brother huh.
Don't woriy. Kishi-san will be okay.
She's stronger than you think
You should go back to the
people who are waiting for you
The people waiting for me?
Nagisa-chan and another girl, right?
You shouldn't deny how you really feel.
Yes, ma'am.
Go to Youko's place.
I'm sure Takidani-kun is there waiting for her
Kotarou, I want you.
All the way inside! Come all the way inside!
Yes!
This feels great
Hit me deep!
More! More!
Do me harder!
More. More
Mess me up inside!
More. Ail the way inside.
Deeper. I want you all the way inside!
I can't stop.
I cant think about anything
I can only think of you, Kotarou!
I-I'm coming.
Then come!
Come inside of me!
Please, fill me up!
Youko!
Kotarou!
Kotarou, I'm soriy.
But I slept with Takawashi-kun.
Don't worry.
I cheated too.
From now onp look only at me.
Youko..
Kishi
Yes?
Youko
Kotarou?
Yuuichi told me everything
I'm sorry I didn't notice
I may not look like it but I'm pretty stupid
Its not your fault Kotarou
It was my fault
Its not your business anymore.
It is too my business!
The baby inside you is your... is our baby!
But I... I don't want to bother you.
I don't want you to waste your life.
So... So...
I'm going to raise it on my own.
That's what I've decided!
So... just leave me alone!
Please!
Youko!
Marry me
Kotarou?
Onii-chan?
Nagisa?
Keishou!?
Onii-chan! Stop it!
So you put Nagisa in those dirty videos?
He didn't want to! I made him do it!
What?
I was in love with you,
but you wouldn't see me as a woman.
So, I wanted you to notice me more
But that's no excuse for...
How do you feel about your sister?
She's my sister.
Nothing more, nothing less
But I love her,
so I was willing to do anything for herr
even if it was something wrong!
Keishou!
Onii-chan, stop it
Nagisa..
If you only see me as a sister,
then stay out of our business!
Nagisa!
Nagisa-chan.
Come live with me.
Ill make you happy
Abiko-san
Kotarou.
What the hell, man?
Yuuichi, what do you want to do?
Do? Nothing really
What the hell!?
I was jealous of you
Nothing was holding you back,
and you could decide your own future.
But you didn't..
I'm marrying Youko
Marrying!
I'm taking responsibility for what I've done.
I'm moving out and getting a job
See ya later.
Just go back to Shiomiya.
She's always been waiting for you
Merry Christmas!
Yuu?
Where have you been?
Come on, its time to start the Christmas party.
I made it all
Isn't it amazing? How about this?
Kanami... I..
Welcome back, Yuu.
Nice to be back, Kanami
No, this is embarrassing
Inside of me... You... You feel so good!
It's inside. Come in deeper. Please!
Deeper. Hit me deep inside
I love you.
I love you so much.
This is embarrassing
Inside of me. You're.
This feels great
Deeper. Hit me deeper.
Please...
Ifs too much.
I cant.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I love you too, Kanami!
I'm cumming!
That guy. So he really is staying back a year?
He says he wants to graduate with Nagisa.
Congratulations, graduates
Onii-chan, Kanami-san
Thanks, Nagisa-chan.
Congratulations, Senpai.
I guess I should call you that now
Jackass.
That's right
They're here too.
See?
What a cute baby!
What's his name?
Its Yuuichi.
But I'm surprised he asked us to come in our uniforms.
That's just like Yuuichi
So it seems.
What's he doing then?
He says he's going to travel the world
Are you okay with that Kanami-san?
He's just an idiot anyway
That's for sure.
Come on, time to take it