Nagisa!
What's wrong? You're all out of breath
They say your brother got injured in PE class!
He did?
Yeah. He was taken to the infirmary
Take care of this for me, please!
Infirmary
S-Sensei, not here.
Oh, dear. Takawashi-kun, do you dislike me?
No, that's not it
Then it's okay.
No one will come.
Come.
Lick them.
Very nice
Takawashi-kun, you're good at it
Saori-sensei... your boobs are delicious
Suck harder.
Harder
Yes. Right there. Very good.
Down here too, please.
You're unwinding me!
Amazing!
There! There!
Lick me more
Looks tasty.
Ill take it
Wow!
So hard!
So hard! It's so hard!
I love it
Go deeper!
Come closer!
Saori-sensei, it's so warm inside you.
Really? Then get closer to me.
Yes!
Right there! Right there!
Harder! Harder!
Deeper!
Rougher!
Harder!
Yes! Its too much!
You're so good! You're so good!
S-Sensei! Mm gonna
What? Takawashi... kun..
Im.dimming!
That's okay
Cum inside me.
At full force.
Inside of me...
Just cum!
washi-kun.
Takawashi-kun?
Sa-Saori-scnsci?
What's wrong? You're blushing.
Saori-sensei, did I... did I... Huh?
Was I inside of you?
What are you blathering about?
You ran into the goal post in PE class and
were carried in here unconscious, right?
Oh, I see.
That was just a dream
I guess it was.
Oh? Did I do something to you?
No.Um, I mean...
Onii-chan!
N-Nagisa?
Onii-chan, are you okay?
He's okay.
If what you see down there..
is proof of his good health.
This is just..
Um...
Excuse me!
Onii-chan! Waittfor mek
Onii-chan!
Come back anytime.
That was a close call.
But Saori-sensei has really nice boobs
Onii-chan!
What about Scnsci?
N-Nothing!
Come on, we need to huriy.
The club meeting will end without us.
I got it
Onii-chan, have you decided what
you're doing after graduation yet?
No, not yet
Are you sure its okay to be so lazy?
Lazy"? Graduations a year off anyway.
But a year will pass in no time.
Yeah, I understand
But that's okay!
Even if you stay a bum living with our parents forever...
Ill become a star and make enough money to feed you.
I'm looking forward to that
Y-Yuu!
What's wrong
Nothing
Hey! Is your head okay?
Yeah.
Kanami-san, Onii-chan still hasn't decided
what heis doing after graduation
That's not Kanami's business, is it?
What's with your attitude?
What about you? Have you decided what you're doing?
Yup.
Arc you serious?
accepted into Fuzoku University.
Kana... I mean, Shiomiya just got
Yay.
Amazing!
Congratulations, Kanami-san!
Thanks, Nagisa-chan.
What about you, Kotarou?
I'm going overseas to study.
I'm gonna take over my fathers business someday
Doesn't that sound boring to you?
Abiko!
Keishou!
But what about you? You're taking
over the family temple, right?
Gimme a break.
letting you live alone right now?
But isn't that why your parents are
That's just for the moment though.
I want to get into TV.
That's true, he's pretty handy with videos and whatnot
By the way, what about Youko?
Kotarou?
She's going to stay at a hospital.
Hospital? Is she sick?
Well she says its nothing serious.
I see.
Sorry I'm late.
Arc you okay?^
Y Yeah, I'm fine.
Just a little fainting spell.
I see.
Okay. Since were all here nowr
lets start the meeting!
Onii-chan
Onii-chan, I want your hand.
Onii-chan!
Its so warm, and it feels good
No! Not there!
But it feels good.
Onii-chan.
More. More.
Give me more
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, you're amazing. So hot
Do it faster.
Very nice! Amazing!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan..
Nagisa, what were you..
Onii-chan. Onii-chan!
I'm... I'm in love with you!
I know its wrong, but., but.
I cant stop myself
I love you, Onii-chan!
Nagisa..
Onii-chan
I'm sorry
but I only see you as a sister.
Onii-chan!
Nagisa-chan?
Abiko-san.
Huriy up!
Hurry up!
Here I go!
Nagisa-chan, come on!
Very good, very good.
Come on, pass it this way.
Here I go!
Really nice.
Okay, my turn. Go!
Got it
Ohr stop it,Here.
What's wrong, Youko?
Ta-TakawashiLkun...
Mm... pregnant
What did you say?
Does your dad..
Was it., from that time?
Arc you sure?
Takawashi-kun!
No, its embarrassing.
Are you sure about this, Youko?
Yeah.
I broke up with Kotarou,
and I'd rather be with you anyway.
What about Kanami?
She doesn't matter.
Here I come.
Amazing!
You're amazing, Takawashi-kun!
Just from that one time...
No. That's not it
Its not you, so don't worry.
Then, don't tell me it's.
Afterwards, I was able to calm down a little
But just once I relapsed with Kotarou
Does he know?
I don't know what to do.
Ta-Takawashi-kun? What's going on?
What are you doing
Youko
Don't Someone will see!
Stop it
Don't Its too embarrassing.
Not down there.
Please stop.
No, stop.
Dont!
No!
This feels great!
Oh, no, I cant stop!
More! More, please!
More! More!
No!
But., keep going
Youko, I'm cumming inside.
Amazing! You:re amazing,
Takawashi-kun!
Amazing! Amazing
Takawashi-kun, you're amazing
So hard!
Amazing!
Takawashi-kun! Amazing!
More! Deeper!
More! Harder!
Harder! Deeper!
Harder! Do me harder!
Okay, here I go!
Ah, that was close.
Ahr that was close.
Here I go!
Got it
Oh, no!
Yeah! I got it
You're so good at this
It ran away
I don't see why if s so much fun
Just let them have their fun.
Its not one of those things you
can understand intellectually
Watch out!
Arc you okay?
Yes. Thanks
Yuu...
What did you want to talk to me about?
Shiomiya... I mean, Kanami, I love you!
And so, I don't want to mess around
anymore just to console our feelings.
I want to date you seriously
Urn... I.
I promise to treat you well.
I love you!
Takidani-kun...
This is embarrassing.
No! Not out here.
No, not there!
Kanami!
W-Wait
Takidani-kun. Wait wait
Wait Takidani-kun, don't
Kanami!
Y-Yes..
Takidani-kun, you're wonderful
So big!
Amazing!
It feels so good.
You're so hard and so good!
Y-Yes, there!
More! More!
Takidani-kun!
Can I cum inside of you?
Yes! Cum inside of me!
I'm... I'm also..
I'm cumming too!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming
I'm cumming
Where did Kanami and Kotarou run off to?
Arc you worried?
Idiot of course not
Where's Kishi-san?
She said she was feeling ill and went home.
Keishou, where's Nagisa?
She said the bathroom
But she's taking a long time
I'll go look for her
All right Take care.
Nagisa!
Nagisa, where are you?
Answer me!
No! Stop it
Aw, come on.
Nagisa!
Why you...
Cut it out
Get out of my fucking way!
Asshole!
Get lost
Nagisa, are you okay?
Did he hurt you?
Onii-chan!
I was so scared!
Yuuichi, what's going on?
Keishou, take care of Nagisa for me.
Sure.
Come on, lets go, Nagisa-chan.
Onii-chan!
How dare you hurt my sister.
I'll have you arrested!
Sister, you say?
What's so funny?
You don't seem to know what your sister is really like.
What are you talking about?
Lemme tell ya about your sister
She's very famous on the Internet
She's into rape play
What did you say?
My sister would never do something like that!
If you think I'm lying, then just look it up
Hey! Wait!
Your little sister is into rape play.
It's a lie!
It's a lie. Nagisa...
You wouldn't
Its a lie.
Rape Love
It has to be a lie!
Stop it
Nagisa? Why
You don't need to give me an answer right away.
Okay, I got it
See you later.
Take care.
Yo-
TO BE CONTINUED