Oh, it's too small for me now...
Daddy, you kept this with you?
Sure, I've always had it with me...
...even during my assignments in foreign countries.
Always...
...with your swimsuit...
Because it reminds me of you, Tomoko...
Daddy...
You've grown up while I was away, Tomoko.
T-Tomoko...
Tomoko...
Who are you?
Mister...
It seems like you got better.
What are you doing?
It's great to see you, Mr. Kitazawa.
I heard you calling Tomoko's name while you were sleeping...
My name is Yumi Okamoto.
I work as a representative of Nogawa Industries.
I came here to ask you to reconsider extending...
...Taketo Nogawa's stay at your house.
You should talk to Yukie regarding that issue.
I'm not interested in living with a guy who slept with my wife.
So will you leave your house?
It might sound rude, but I must tell you that you may have another problem...
...if you can't satisfy your wife.
Problem?
Yes...
Because your body only reacts to your daughter...
Maybe I was wrong...
Why is this happening to us?
Don't cry, Mom.
We'll never leave you alone, no matter what happens.
That's right, Mommy.
Thank you Rumi, Tomoko...
Immoral
Sisters
Fruits
of
Two
Sisters
Second Night
"Sister Love"
"The Girl with a Father Complex, Tomoko"
How did it go with my father?
I can't be sure about anything...
Oh no, I thought you were the only one who could solve this...
Calm down, Rumi.
I do have a plan that we could try...
Really?
I'll do anything to save Mom and Dad from getting a divorce!
Tomoko, can I ask you a favor?
Me?
Yes.
I found something very interesting in your father's study yesterday.
Something interesting?
Who is it?
Tomoko...
Um, I just thought that you would want to see me in this...
Don't you like it?
O-Of course, I like it...
Really?
Yes, of course...
Thank you, Tomoko...
Come over here and let me see you closer...
Yes...
Tomoko...
You look like your mother when she was young...
The nape of your neck and the shape of your breasts...
Oh no, Daddy...
Ever since we adopted you after your mother died...
...I couldn't think of you as my real daughter.
I couldn't think of you as my real father, either...
That's because we don't have a blood relationship...
I was scared.
I'm nothing but a fake father who gets off from my own step-daughter.
Daddy...
But I won't hold back anymore today, Tomoko...
Daddy, no, we shouldn't do this.
You did a lot of naughty things with Taketo, right?
Why can't you do the same thing with me?
It's not fair!
Daddy, no...
I feel bad for Mommy...
Tomoko...
Daddy, stop this...
If you lick me like that, I can't keep standing...
Your pretty flower bud is under this swimsuit, right?
Oh no, Daddy...
Please don't look at me...
You're so beautiful, Tomoko...
It looks like a pink rose petal trying to keep its sweet honey from flowing.
Daddy, no! Please don't put your finger there!
You said that you felt bad for your mother...
...but your pussy is already so hot.
Daddy, no...
That's right, call me Daddy...
I'll go crazy...
Daddy!
I've been impotent for a long time...
...but now I've regained my energy...
Daddy, it's so big...
I forgot about this feeling.
Do you feel ashamed to have a stepfather like me?
No, I don't.
Tomoko...
Daddy, yours is so hard. I can't believe that it has gotten this hard...
I can't wait anymore, Tomoko.
I'm so exhausted physically and mentally...
Will you comfort me with those lovely lips of yours?
Please, Tomoko...
Please suck my newly awakened dick...
Yes, sure...
It looks like your husband finally got a hard-on.
Why? I couldn't get him excited at all...
Don't look away!
Yes...
Look carefully...
...at what kind of person your husband really is...
M-Mom...
Daddy...
As your father, I need to taste my daughter...
But...
You are not my real father...
But you like it when I say it like that, don't you?
Well, yeah...
I can finally put this inside you...
I have waited for this moment for so long!
Daddy...
I have a favor to ask...
I want you to keep your relationship with us as a family.
I don't want to be apart from my sister, Taketo, Yumi, Mommy, and you...
I love you all. I really do...
Tomoko...
So please Daddy, don't go away!
I want us to be together forever.
People might think our relationship is weird...
But I don't care what other people think, as long as we're together...
Tomoko...
She is a good girl.
She is trying to grab your husband's heart with her body...
...to keep the family together...
Come on, Daddy...
Put it in.
Tomoko...
I love you, Daddy.
My body is so hot. I want you to put it inside me.
Tomoko...
He is inserting his penis into Tomoko's body...
You must be jealous!
Your daughter took your husband!
As long as he is happy...
Don't lie!
You have to be honest, Yukie.
Oh please, harder! Harder!
That's more like it.
Taketo...
You are jealous, right?
Then say you are jealous!
Your husband dumped you, so you must be sad.
Say you are sad!
I'm jealous...
I'm so sad...
Please don't leave me!
Daddy, I love you.
I want you more...
Tomoko, I love you too.
I love you!
Daddy, please...
I want you to love Mommy, Yumi, and Rumi too...
Your penis is so big. It's not fair if only I enjoy it.
We should share it.
Everybody wants your penis too.
Okay, I understand, Tomoko.
I'll fuck all of you.
Thank you, Tomoko, I could finally revive...
Thank you, Tomoko...
Thank you, Daddy...
Please cum inside me...
Tomoko...
Oh Daddy, please cum inside...
Tomoko, I'm cumming!
I'll shoot a hot load inside of you!
Daddy, I'm cumming soon...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Tomoko, let's cum together!
I can feel Daddy's cum inside me...
I felt so good, Daddy...
Harder! Harder!
Taketo...
You must be jealous. You want his love, don't you?
Say that you want to be loved!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to see Dad.
Rumi...
Rumi?
Mom, let's go.
Let's ask him to sleep with us...
Rumi...
Forget everything, and just accept what we really are...
"The House of Sex Animals, The New Kitazawas"
I can't believe what I did...
Even if Tomoko is only my step-daughter, I've had sex with her...
It's over. I'm nothing but an animal...
You!
Now I have proof of the forbidden relationship...
...between you and your step-daughter.
I wonder what would happen if I sent this to the company...
Are you threatening me?
Maybe.
Do whatever you want to do...
I'm the worst father... a father who lost to his own desires.
I deserve punishment...
Wait, who told you that I'd give you punishment?
It's time for us to understand each other...
Yukie...
Darling...
Once a man is corrupt, it's impossible to go back...
Isn't that right?
Now you understand...
All of us here cannot go back to normal anymore...
We're all in the same boat.
It's not such a bad idea if we stay like this and have fun, right?
Forget about what people say.
It doesn't make sense to live in this world, hiding your true desires.
Are you fine with it?
I don't want us to keep pretending to be something we aren't.
We don't have a blood relationship...
...so we need to seek another form of bond...
Yukie...
Darling...
So, from now on, what is yours is mine...
...and what is mine is yours.
That is going to be the rule.
That is fine with me.
Congratulations Taketo, a new family is born!
Yumi...
Let's celebrate then!
Yeah, that's a good idea!
I agree!
Let's have fun tonight!
Oh yeah, you are both doing great...
It's so good, I feel like I've become a man...
You are so beautiful Yukie...
Darling...
You're already so wet. What a horny woman you are!
Oh Taketo...
Do it harder!
That's good...
I like having an orgasm like a man...
Hey, she is ready.
Come on, screw her!
Darling...
Oh Darling...
I feel so good...
How does your husband feel?
You must have missed it.
I feel Taketo's dick inside me...
Yukie, why were you having sex with someone else?
Please forgive me...
No, and if you do it again, I'm going to have sex with Rumi...
Oh no!
Please don't leave me!
You should show your father how mature you've become...
No, I can't, it's embarrassing...
Oh Rumi, you look so cute in gym shorts...
No, don't look at me!
She has a lovely flower bud here...
She is wet because she wants you so bad...
Oh, do you want me that much?
No, please don't go!
Mommy, please suck mine instead...
I borrowed this one from Yumi.
Please suck it, Mommy...
Tomoko...
Rumi, would you suck my dick?
Why do you hesitate?
I know you want to suck it badly...
You've been holding back, haven't you?
You tried to force yourself to believe he is your real father...
But now there is nothing for you to worry about...
Explore your sexual desire with him.
Mom, please forgive me...
Rumi...
That's good, you can lick it as much as you want.
I'm sure your mother will forgive you.
Mommy, suck it hard...
Suck it harder than Sis.
Your tongue is incredible...
Your dad's penis likes that.
Don't you want your daddy's dick inside you now?
No, I can't do that...
Why not? You're not really his daughter.
B-But...
Your pussy is drooling for his penis...
...and you're trying to be daddy's good girl?
You want him to screw you, right?
No...
If you still resist, I'll do this!
How is it? Were you an anal virgin?
Please screw your step-daughter as hard as you can...
The other hole is hungry for you.
Oh yeah...
Oh no, I can't do this with Dad.
Be honest!
You want both holes occupied, right?
Don't say that, it's embarrassing...
I'll come in, Rumi...
No, Dad!
Can you feel it?
You're getting screwed in both of your holes!
Let me screw your ass too...
Both my holes are...
Mommy, I've wanted to screw you like this...
Your daddy's dick is big and hard, isn't it?
Yes, it's so huge...
Oh yeah? So, maybe I should try.
Would you put it inside me?
Of course, if you wish so...
Oh no, don't stop!
I want it more!
What are you saying now? You made such a fuss earlier.
It's my turn now.
Your daddy's dick is screwing me...
I'm sorry Dad...
I was lying earlier. I wanted you to screw me...
R-Rumi...
Dad...
Dad!
I want yours, Dad...
I can't wait anymore!
You finally admitted it, Rumi...
Move your ass faster and harder... make your daddy happy!
Dad, please love me! I want you to love me!
Rumi, I love you... more than my real daughter!
I'm so happy, Dad. I love you too!
Harder! Harder!
It's getting hot inside me...
I'm close...
Please let me swallow it!
Me too, Dad, I want it too!
I'm cumming!
Mommy! I'm cumming!
Me too, Tomoko...
Taketo...
Me too...
You are a member of our family now...
One month later...
I can't believe that you have another business trip so soon...
I thought we finally became a big family with 6 members...
It cannot be helped, but I'll be back soon!
No...
You behave like love birds in front of your daughters...
Oh Yumi...
Today I'll take Yukie, and Taketo is supposed to have my daughters...
I didn't know that you applied a person-on-duty system now!
Taketo, you cum so quickly and get hard right after that!
Shut up, Rumi!
Concentrate on what you're doing!
What, Taketo... hold it longer if you can...
Taketo, do it harder...
Until your husband comes back, would you like to have fun with me?
Yumi!
Yukie, don't be mean to me... are you trying to exclude me?
No, I'm not...
Yumi...
Come back right after you see him off!
Drive Safely
I'll wait for you!
Okay!