Don't act so snotty!
Trying to look like a high-class girl, huh?
Let's do it...
Y-Yeah!
Shit, run!
They're just all talk!
They don't have the guts.
Who's that guy?
Kaneshiro Shouichi, great reflexes, and he's on the swim team...
...but, he's definitely not a studious guy.
In any case, what should we do?
If anything, I can...
It's all right, in any case, your tip...
S-Sensei...
Tell me anything.
I'm your loyal servant!
I can't hold it...
S-Sensei!
Kaneshiro Shouichi, I can use him!
Suzuyo, the one we didn't get last time, and the mother, Kasumi.
This is going to be interesting...
I guess you did well...
That girl is crazy about me...
This is a copy of the exam.
Make sure you put it back in the principal's desk.
Yeah...
Shouichi...
What's wrong? Why are you in the dark like this?
Kotono-san is with her teammates?
Yes, she was going to eat out before coming home.
I see.
You should have joined them.
If you haven't had dinner yet, I have it ready for you downstairs.
Change your clothes and come down.
O-Okay...
At this hour?
W-What's this?
Principal, you came back from your business trip earlier than expected...
All of a sudden, I wanted to see Morisawa-sensei's face...
Please call me "Maiko" as usual...
How darling...
But we're in the premises of the academy, and as the principal...
...I should call you Morisawa-sensei, or the school nurse...
You teaser!
Oh, really, a teaser, eh?
Then I will tease you more...
Oh, ouch...
Don't lie to me.
You're so wet, it went in so easily.
No...
How does it feel?
Do you want me to tease you more?
This one for the other hole...
There...
How is it?
Do you feel it?
I can't take it anymore!
Get down on all fours.
Wow, what a great view!
It's so wet and trembling, inviting me!
Stop teasing or I'm gonna go crazy...
Hurry, hurry!
Oh yeah?
Here I come!
Good! Good!
Morisawa-sensei, this is good!
This vibration is out of this world!
Yes! Yes!
Give it to me! Give it to me in the ass!
Good! Harder! More!
My ass, it's gonna tear...
Not that hard, no!
Yes, Chairman Miyatsuji is scheduled to meet the principal after school.
A sudden inspection, eh?
She is a fickle woman...
That Miyatsuji Kasumi...
Banishing me, the head clerk of Miyatsuji Konzern...
...as the principal of this academy!
She must be relieved, thinking all my fangs have been pulled out...
...entrusting us with her two important daughters.
It's like we gained hostages, isn't it?
Well, they'll come into play in the worst case scenario...
Here...
Like I said before...
...in my hands is a file in which, while I've been "banished"...
...have collected the weak points of Miyatsuji Konzern's trustees.
At the next board meeting...
...I will pull Miyatsuji Kasumi down and sit in the chairman's seat.
When that happens, you,
Morisawa-sensei, will also...
Yesterday, I thought about you all night and practiced...
Kotono...
No, don't stop!
Harder! Harder!
Oh yes!
No...
Faster! Faster!
I'm coming!
Please, come! Come inside me!
You okay?
Miyatsuji-san, you don't look well.
I think the next class will be self-study...
...so maybe you should go to the infirmary?
Infirmary...
You're right. Okay, I'll go.
Should I come with you?
No, I'll be okay...
You want me to put this back at the principal's office?
The door is unlocked, and the principal is on a business trip.
Put them in the very bottom drawer. It locks when you close it.
Kotono, you just do what I tell you!
Y-Yes, Shouichi-sama...
Looking for this?
What are you doing?
What were you doing in the principal's office without permission?
Don't move!
I'm hot!
What is this? What is this feeling that's firing me up?
You are Miyatsuji's daughter!
Miyatsuji Suzuyo, Kotono's younger sister...
She saw us together...
If she tells the chairman, I'll be banished...
...you'll be expelled, and we wouldn't be able to see each other anymore.
What should we do?
The best thing to do is to make her your servant, like the older sister...
Both sisters being my servants, eh...
I have to go to a "meeting"...
So, use this place for whatever you want.
I'll do just that...
You're good.
Here's your reward...
Don't let go.
Keep sucking!
It feels great!
I'm entering.
Chairman?
Principal, what is all this about?
What?
I-Is this...
Somebody leaked this to my site.
This is my own research that supports...
...the investigation of a certain illegal breach of trust.
Is there anything you have to say?
As I suspected, you betrayed my father's trust for your selfish desires.
Don't tell me, that voice...
K-Kotono?
No...
Please be gentle.
It feels good, I love it!
M-Mother?
No, don't look...
Feels so good!
W-What are you doing?
What are you doing to me?
S-Shouichi-san?
You're a virgin, aren't you?
But look, your nectar is overflowing!
Not like this...
Stop...
No...
It's so hot...
I'm getting hot, too.
I've never felt like this before.
Good...
I wonder what the story will be today?
Could be a story of her own experience...
S-Shit!
A secret door?
No more...
What are you talking about?
This is where the mother and daughter duo really begins!
Oogawara, you bastard.
Don't think that you'll get away with this!
I'll remove you before the next board meeting...
Well, at the next board meeting, the chairman will be switched with these here!
In this disk...
What the hell?
How about this disk?
Your predecessor used his financial power, took my lover and married her...
...but now that I think about it, his daughter isn't too bad either...
...along with his mistress.
Don't put me in the same category as her!
Don't you dare talk about her that way!
Morisawa-sensei?
M-Maiko?
That "lady" is my mother!
Maybe that "drink" was too powerful for an old guy like you.
There were a lot of shocking events...
What's this?
Did you plan all this?
It's only just begun.
I think you'll get to experience a lot more than me.
Instead of this old man, I think the young beast is just about to come...
Good-bye...
Oh, it's getting brighter!
What the...
Suzuyo!
W-What are you doing to my daughter?
Daughter?
Stop!
Shouichi-sama...
Please, don't lay a finger on my mother...
Is that coming from the beautiful love between mother and daughter...
...or from wanting me all to yourself?
I wonder...
So you are the mother of these girls.
Wow, it's so well broken in!
Like butter...
Stop it!
No! Please, don't do it to my mother, touch me!
M-Mother?
You're finally awake, Suzuyo-ojousama?
Don't take it out, I'm about to come!
Don't take that one out, either!
Mother is a slave to desire?
Well then...
Come with this!
No!
Please, not my sister!
Onee-sama, no! Please don't look!
Jealousy between sisters, huh?
This is hot!
Well well, you haven't masturbated with this hole?
No, I don't masturbate!
Don't be prudish!
Ow!
It hurts! Please stop!
Fine, then I'll go to your sister.
Shouichi-sama!
Onee-sama!
How's this, beg me more!
Yes! It feels really good!
Shouichi-sama, more, more!
Yes! Yes!
I'm gonna come, I'm gonna come!
No! No!
Not fair! Not fair! Onee-sama!
I'm coming, coming!
No, no!
She came and pissed in ecstasy, eh?
How proper that is...
Well, the one I've been waiting for...
Here you go.
Open your tiny little mouth, and clean Shouichi-sama's important thing...
...that got dirty from your sister's ass.
Good girl.
On to the next!
No! No!
Here I come!
Ow!
Isn't this what you wanted?
Shouichi-sama is coming inside me!
Nice, she came even though she's a virgin...
It looks like both sisters masturbated a lot.
As a reward, I'll really go at it from behind!
All trustees in favor of Morisawa Maiko, recommended by...
...previous chairman, Miyatsuji Kasumi, please cast your vote now.