Darling!
Yukie, Rumi, Tomoko...
Welcome back, Daddy!
How have you been, Rumi?
Great!
You've grown up, Tomoko...
It must have been tough to work abroad for so long.
Oh, it wasn't easy.
By the way, who is that guy?
This is Taketo...
Taketo Nogawa.
He became a new member of our family while you were away.
We can't do this after your husband comes back...
Are you okay with that?
No, but...
We won't be able to do this after tomorrow...
Taketo...
We wouldn't feel safe if there were only women in the house...
...so we asked him to protect us.
Taketo has been staying at our house.
It's good to see you...
...Mr. Impotence.
Immoral
Sisters
Fruits
of
Two
Sisters
First Night
"Return of a Father, a Forbidden Love"
"The Affair of a Young Wife, Yukie"
What is your problem, Rumi?
How dare you say such a rude thing to my father!
We shouldn't have brought you here!
Sis!
I hate you!
I want you to get out of our house!
Is that the reason that you got kicked out of the Kitazawa's house?
You are helpless...
Your father is in jail and you have nobody to rely on now.
You should understand your situation.
Yumi, let me stay at your place tonight...
Come on.
I'm sorry, but I'm busy reconstructing Nogawa Industries.
Man...
This is bullshit.
Sis, Taketo hasn't come back home yet.
I don't care about him anymore.
Tomoko, things have changed now.
We must keep what happened between Taketo and us a secret...
...so it's better that he isn't here.
Sis!
I know it's hard for someone like you to dislike anybody, but...
...it's for us to stay together as a family, so please understand.
No...
Kitazawa Tomoko
Come in.
You're not going to bed yet?
I have to prepare some documents that...
...I need to submit to headquarters next week.
I had better do this tonight.
Yukie...
It has been a while, please let me touch you.
Please stop it.
You know it's not going to happen.
Please, just let me do this...
I'll do my best to get you up.
Please, touch my body, too.
You've became so sensual, haven't you, Yukie?
Oh, it's because...
That's my...
I'm sorry, I wish I could insert mine right here.
Please don't feel sorry.
Mother...
Taketo...
Are you masturbating while watching your parents having sex?
Well, because...
I'll help you.
Taketo...
We've just started.
No, no, Taketo.
No, stop it, please!
What's wrong?
Why are you resisting?
I don't want to do it here.
Don't you think it's exciting?
I want my mother to have fun too...
That's enough, Yukie...
Please stop.
It will just make me sad if you continue...
So...
I'm sorry. But I've been practicing to improve my skills, though...
Practicing with whom?
Well, um...
With me!
Taketo...
I knew it was you.
That's right.
Yukie, let's show him how we do it, okay?
Yukie, what is he trying to say?
Darling...
Even your daughters are getting frustrated because they feel bad that...
...their mother can't be satisfied.
Oh no...
What did you do to my daughter?
Hey, calm down.
You may be a successful businessman...
...but you're lacking something very important.
Taketo, please, stop it!
Shut up!
We should let your husband know...
...who the real man in the house is.
You mean, Tomoko is...
I'll show you what's really happening...
I know what you want is this... young, hard and wild...
I want you to suck it like you always do.
Taketo...
Darling...
What's wrong?
You've been doing this all the time.
Oh no, please...
Just suck my dick.
This is what you're longing for, and now it's right in front of your face.
Show your husband the way you suck my dick.
I-I'm sorry...
Yukie...
Incredible.
She is tossing my dick back and forth in her mouth.
What's the meaning of this?
Meaning?
Can't you see?
I'm showing you who can give real pleasure to women.
Look...
She's getting off from being forced to do something she doesn't want to do.
Please don't look at me.
Your body says something different.
Oh no, I can't do this...
Please, forgive me.
Such a good girl.
You gave up Taketo for your mother.
Yumi, now I feel sorry for Daddy.
I know, I feel sorry that he became useless as a man.
Do you want to satisfy your father?
No...
Oh, you are already excited.
It's so wet down there.
You want a man too, don't you?
Okay, I'll play the man for you.
Okay, I'm ready.
Suck it as much as you want.
Don't be shy, I know you want it.
Yes, that's good, use your tongue.
I feel like I'm a real man.
I feel so good...
Yumi...
You can't hold it anymore, huh?
Let's go to your room, then.
Are you watching?
This is how your wife looks when she is really having fun.
Darling...
You want to switch?
Oh right, I forgot that you can't get your dick hard.
Darling...
Daddy!
Oh, Darling...
I'm close.
I want to swallow your cum...
Please let me swallow it.
Cum...
Oh, Taketo.
That's right, swallow it.
Does it taste good?
Yes, it's delicious.
It's so delicious.
Yumi, let me stay at your place tonight...
Come on.
I'm sorry, but I'm busy reconstructing Nogawa Industries.
Man...
This is bullshit.
Yes, come in.
Oh, it's Tomoko and Rumi.
It has been a while.
You came here to pick up this bad boy, huh?
"Sisters Longing for Bonds, Rumi and Tomoko"
Why do I have to hang out with you?
Idiot, can't you see that she's trying to relieve the tension among us?
So you came to apologize because your sister told you so?
What?
Are you gonna slap me again?
I-I wasn't going to do that.
I'll never go back to your home even if you apologize!
I would prefer if you stayed out of our house, too!
What was that?
Sis!
Tomoko!
I want to get on that one!
I want you to promise me that you will behave in front of my father.
Why?
You know why!
Dad and Mom might get divorced if he finds out about you two.
What do you mean?
You and your father threatened us and raped us.
Oh come on!
If he finds out, we won't be able to live together as a family.
He hates scandals.
Because it affects his promotions, right?
Such concern!
Of course he is worried, especially when we aren't even his real daughters.
Ever since I was little, I was always afraid that he would kick us out...
...if we did something bad.
Who cares?
I'm the only man that your family needs anyway.
You don't understand anything, do you?
Shut up!
I don't get why you've been acting like a good girl since he came back!
No, stop it!
Please stop!
Tomoko?
Please don't do it to my sister.
You can do it to me instead.
T-Tomoko...
Damn, that's good...
Sit there and open your legs.
Like this?
Yes.
I'm going to use something Yumi gave me.
I'm sure you'll love it.
What is that?
This toy can make a girl feel like she is in heaven.
See?
You can feel this even if you have your clothes on, right?
I feel strange.
Open your legs!
Oh no, it's vibrating...
You shouldn't be doing that here.
Why are you upset?
You're just jealous because you are left alone.
No way!
Sis...
Please come closer to me.
Please, I need you.
We're family, right?
We can stay together as a family, right?
Tomoko...
I want to be with Sis, Taketo, Mommy and Daddy.
I want us to feel good together, Sis.
Sis...
You're such a bad girl, Tomoko.
I'm glad, Sis.
Taketo, are you going to cum yet?
Hey, the ride will be over soon.
But it is thrilling, isn't it, Sis?
Tomoko, don't move it so hard...
I can't concentrate on making him cum.
I can't keep standing anymore...
Hey, take a look.
The guys on the gondola next to ours are watching us.
Don't say such a thing, Taketo...
I'm going to enjoy this until the very last moment!
No, I don't want people to see me like this.
Sis, you don't need to hold back.
You're wetter than usual.
Don't say that, Tomoko.
Sis, let him be inside you.
Just sit on Taketo.
You've got a good sister. I'll put it in, then you should thank your sister.
Wow, Taketo's penis is deep inside your pussy.
Tomoko, don't look...
Don't look, it's embarrassing.
Looks like your pussy and Taketo's penis are getting along so well.
Let me make you feel better.
No...
Oh don't, Tomoko!
She is licking my balls...
I'm close!
I'm cumming too...
Taketo, you came a lot.
Let me clean you up!
Taketo, it's all up to you.
You can come home at anytime if you keep the promise.
Okay, I understand.
Taketo, I will be waiting for you.
Come to me.
Taketo!
That's right, swallow it.
Does it taste good, Yukie?
Yes, it's delicious...
Did you get that?
I'm the only man who can give pleasure to the women in this house!
Taketo!
How dare you break a promise!
What, Rumi?
Do you want me to screw you again?
No, it's not about that!
How could you do this to Mom and our family?
Why do you keep torturing our family?
What do you care about this useless old man?
I don't want to hear it!
Just get out of our house right now!
Wait, Rumi...
Please don't kick him out.
I just realized that I need Taketo's body desperately...
M-Mom...
Darling...
Things have changed a lot while you were away...
I'm sorry.
Yukie...
I see, I'm going to leave this house.
Dad...
Let's talk about what we should do later.
Mom?
No, this can't be happening, right?
Tell me this isn't happening!
Please Mom, please...
Mom...