Let's see...
Okay.
Delicious.
Don't act so snotty!
Trying to look like a high-class girl, huh?
Let's do it...
Y-Yeah!
Suzuyo-chan, why are you in a daze?
Oh, Onee-sama...
What were you looking at?
Um, nothing...
Isn't that Kaneshiro-kun?
Onee-sama, do you know him?
Kaneshiro Shouichi...
He's my junior in the swim club.
So, he's one year older than you.
So this is where he's been, when he's supposed to be at the club.
He must have found something more interesting than swimming.
Mother will be late again...
...so I'll have dinner with my clubmates before coming home.
You should have dinner somewhere, too, okay?
See you.
Come in.
Oh hello, Shouichi-kun.
Please wait a bit.
I must finish my report for the academy principal.
Shouichi-kun...
Ouch...
A little more gentle...
Oh no, I'm going crazy...
Give it to me, Shouichi-kun...
Sensei...
Oh no, I can't hold it!
It's okay, let it out, Shouichi-kun!
Mine too, Shouichi-kun...
It feels so good.
Gently, Shouichi-kun...
Hurry, come inside me.
Don't tease...
Hurry, hurry!
Y-Yes! Harder! Harder!
Yes! Yes! That's it...
That's it, Shouichi-kun...
Kaneshiro-kun!
People from the swim team...
Kaneshiro-kun, what have you been up to, not showing up lately...
Well, putting that aside, we've made a plan for the swim meet.
We want you to participate in two categories...
Individual butterfly and as an anchor in the medley relay.
Not interested.
Wait a minute!
We've been working really hard for this swim meet all year...
...and just because of your selfishness...
I don't do anything for anybody...
...and don't expect people to do anything for me, either.
Saeki, aren't you supposed to be at practice?
I'm only a bench warmer.
Oh, right.
You just joined the club to see girls in swim suits...
So, what do you want?
No, no...
Only you can talk to the...
...high-class lady of Miyatsuji Konzern, Miyatsuji Kotono...
...in that manner and be so rude...
High-class lady?
Wait, you didn't know?
Miyatsuji is Miyatsuji Konzerns class president, and...
...she's the daughter of Miyatsuji Kasumi, the chairman of this academy.
Kasumi Miyatsuji is the chairman of this academy?
Yes, that unequaled beauty's daughter!
So that's why she talks like that...
There's also one more, named Suzuyo, our junior in this academy!
That innocent smile...
Being the chairman's daughters as the beauty sisters...
And Suzuyo, unlike Kotono...
Hey!
Come on, I'm just about to tell you my main intentions!
You still want something?
You probably realize this by now, but...
...that Kotono-ojousama, she definitely has a crush on you.
So?
Your grades seem to be falling rather rapidly, right, Kaneshiro-kun?
If you fail the next exam, you'll be expelled...
How did you find that out?
I overheard it at the guidance counsellor's room...
Don't get so serious.
I was told the same thing before you were.
So what?
Meet with her, Kotono-ojousama...
...and let her mother, the chairman, influence the academy...
It's a good plan, right?
I'll do the planning...
Not interested...
You're so popular, aren't you, Shouichi-kun?
Oh Sensei, you were listening...
Saeki-kun's idea isn't bad, but I wouldn't recommend it.
Are you jealous?
That too, but it might take too much time...
...and the exam is coming up too soon.
Well, there is a faster way...
A faster way?
Before we get to that...
Sensei...
I-I couldn't wait. Shouichi-kun, you were late...
The principal's office?
I'll be back the day after tomorrow.
Let the other teachers know as well.
Morisawa-sensei, here are the keys.
Thank you, sir.
Well, the car is waiting, let's go, sir.
Yes.
Come to think of it, the disc with the exam was on the principal's desk.
The principal puts those kind of important things into the...
...very bottom drawer with a lock.
I'm sure the exam information is there, bring the whole thing.
I'll find the exam answers for you...
If you get expelled, I'll be so sad.
Hurry, come!
I'm entering.
Was that Kaneshiro-kun?
What was he doing?
Oh, Kotono-san.
Is the principal not here?
Morisawa-sensei?
That's strange, telling you to stop by...
Oh my, leaving the window open...
Um, Morisawa-sensei...
Yes, Kotono-san?
Oh no, it's nothing...
Excuse me.
So you've been seen, Shouichi-kun.
No need to worry...
With the technique you've learned, all women will go crazy about you...
...they'll do whatever you want.
Make her one of them.
Women are like that...
...especially virgins...
I'm sure she's troubled right now, not being able to tell anybody.
So go find her.
I'll be a little jealous, but it's also exciting.
Leave the rest up to me...
...and take care of the lady as much as you like.
Kaneshiro-kun, what are you doing here?
Get out of here, or else I will call somebody!
Stop it, I will scream!
Interesting.
Scream if you want to, if you don't mind people seeing you like this.
I've had a crush on you...
Please, don't do this.
I won't tell anybody about this afternoon...
So you did see it.
Well then, this makes it easier.
But a promise isn't enough...
What are you going to do?
What are you thinking...
No!
P-Please stop...
It's pretty hot.
You're really sensitive.
T-That's not true...
No, don't!
N-Not like this...
This is embarrassing...
No!
Don't look away...
No, please let me go...
Are you the only one who gets to feel good?
Huh, Kotono-ojousama?
B-But...
Kiss the thing that will make you a woman.
I-I can't...
Well then, do you want me to strip you naked and call someone?
N-No!
I'll do it.
That's a good girl.
Continue!
Y-Yes...
What now? Don't stop.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because I love you...
I don't care if it's a lie...
That's enough.
Well well, I guess you haven't had enough.
Take off your swimsuit.
You've become very obedient...
Move your hands!
I'm watching your most
embarrassing appearance.
Indeed, you're the queen of the swim team.
Very pretty...
Please hurry...
Don't order me around!
Y-Yes...
Lie there and spread your legs.
Wider.
I can't believe that I won't be loved without doing this...
Shut up!
You're about to get screwed.
S-Stop! Shouichi-kun!
Address me as Shouichi-sama, understand?
Y-Yes, Shouichi-sama...
You're wet anyway, right Ojou-sama?
I-I don't know, Shouichi-sama.
You don't know your own body?
I don't, so please find out...
Wow, and this is a virgin?
D-Don't say that, it's embarrassing...
Look at it yourself...
No, I can't...
No! No!
I'll look... I'll look...
Can you see it, your pussy?
Y-Yes, I can.
How is it?
It's wet and nasty...
Very well said...
Well then, here's your reward.
D-Don't do that...
No!
I'm gonna go crazy!
Shouichi-sama, please come!
Ow, it hurts!
I'm gonna go crazy...
Please, forgive me! Forgive me!
You want me to stop?
Please don't stop!
More! More!
I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come, Shouichi-sama!
Go on, clean up what you soiled...
Y-Yes...
This is going to be interesting...