After my mother's death, I was
raised at a convent where I was...
...subjected to
indescribable disgrace.
During that time
my ray of hope was...
...the brief moments I spent with
Andrew, the Prince of this country.
Later my uncle,
Duke Dusse, took me into his care.
Under my uncle's orders I
started the harsh training...
...to become a Love Doll,
the flower of high society.
My uncle's gaze upon
me can be as cold as ice.
But at times, it can
be unbelievably tender.
Several months have passed since
I came to my uncle's manor but...
...I have yet to
understand him.
Madame, the usual
gentleman is at the back door.
I see.
Will you go get Marsha?
Her again?!
The gentleman requests
her so don't make a fuss.
Fine then.
Dear.
What a
troublesome customer.
Mr. L, I have
readied the usual girl.
Please,
go upstairs.
Marsha, Mr. L is coming!
Get yourself ready!
I'm ready
whenever.
Jeez!
Don't be such a bitch just because
you have a high paying client!
People are attracted to others of
equal or higher stature, you know.
A client like him
will be of good use.
It's my chance to
regain my elite status.
I'll do anything
for that!
What would you like
to do today, Mr. L?
I had an acquaintance
make this. I want to test it out.
Oh what
is that?
Get on
the bed.
As you wish.
Do whatever pleases you.
It's amazing...
that thing...
It's so good...
It's amazing, Mr. L.
Mr. L, I've been satisfied
more than enough.
It's your
turn now.
Is your dick hard from
watching me get so hot?
It seems it's
not hard yet.
Let me pleasure
you with my mouth.
That's
enough.
Do not worry. It's not
because you did anything wrong.
Will you
come again?
Yes.
Mr. L, you're
a great client.
But I've decided to exploit
your secret for better profits.
You hear?
Rachel.
The date for your debut
as a Love Doll has been set.
Yes.
It is a ball with the royal family,
appropriate for Lady Rachel.
I've heard that Prince Andrew
who has graduated from...
...the Royal University
will also be present.
I'm sure it will be
a glamorous ball.
Andrew?!
Andrew will be...
Lady Rachel...
...to fulfill your
duty as a Love Doll...
...I imagine that you will be bedded
with many different types of men.
Tonight's lesson is
to bear in mind...
...the man who will bed a
woman for the first time.
I'll get to see
Andrew soon.
I could bear
anything in order to...
I've been awaiting
you, My Lady.
What's wrong? If you're so shy,
we won't be able to do anything.
S-Sorry.
Can you take charge
from here, please?
Yes... you're
doing great.
Okay.
It feels so good. It feels
strange down there. Like it's aching.
Please,
don't stare.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're
still hard.
It feels like you
can keep going.
If we stop here it would be
somewhat unsatisfying, wouldn't it?
If feels wonderful.
You're doing great.
Andrew.
When I think about seeing you soon,
I can endure any kind of hardship.
It's a lesson and I'm having sex
with a man I don't even know but...
...if I
think you...
Rachel...
I love you.
Andrew?!
Please, don't stop.
I want you to hurry and cum.
Okay.
Oh Andrew.
Excuse me, miss!
What do you think you're doing?!
I don't know how much you
spent to bribe the Madame but...
...it's quite bothersome if
you're going to work here!
Do you
understand?
This place
isn't for you!
You hear?!
Today will be the
last time you come here!
Rachel?!
Marsha?!
I heard about
your house.
How
unfortunate.
You say that but you're probably
thinking I deserved it, aren't you?
After all, your bully's
house went bankrupt.
Of course not!
I was
really worried.
Well it doesn't matter,
whichever way.
I was getting bored of
living in high society anyway.
Marsha.
In any event...
...why are you
roaming around here?
I thought your rich uncle was
taking care of you? It's really strange.
T-That's...
No difference between the rich and
the poor in shady business, I guess.
Oh yes!
My frequent client seems to be
a nobleman of high status but...
...his dick
is useless.
I heard it's because of an injury
he sustained in the battlefield.
He may be a noble,
but that's pathetic.
I wonder if you're one of
those pathetic nobles too?
I'm trying to find out
some stuff about this man.
He wears a mask to hide his face
but I don't think that's all he's hiding.
He probably lost
his right eye.
His right eye?
Isn't that a
great mark?
Do you know of
any nobles like that?
If you know something,
tell me. We're old friends.
It would be good of you to
tell me if you know something.
Seems like you're going
through tough times too.
He probably
lost his right eye.
Uncle?
Rachel,
do you...?
I'm sorry. I...
...have a carriage
waiting, so I must go.
I'm glad I saw you.
I won't come here anymore.
I promise.
Uncle is...
...impotent?
Could it be...?
Miss.
Sorry to keep
you waiting.
The head editor is in the
carriage on top of this bridge.
I see.
Thank you.
Hold on a sec!
I don't know why
you asked me to steal...
...the Aristocratic Registry List
from the newspaper company...
...but you've put me
in a real tight spot.
So if the information you're about to
give the editor is some stupid lead...
Rest assured.
Your efforts will be rewarded.
I'll be
counting on it.
Sure.
It's interesting
information but...
...without any proof,
you can't expect me to buy it.
I understand.
He's supposed to come
tomorrow night at eleven o'clock.
Take your pictures or
whatever you need then.
Sounds fine.
That'll be the plan then.
I'll pay you
afterwards.
Okay.
Anyway, is it true that a girl named
Rachel is at that Duke Dusse's place?
That's certain,
but why do you ask?
Oh no reason.
Poor Rachel.
Your uncle is about to be ruined
and everything will fall apart.
All because
of me.
You'll be out on the
streets, in the filthy world.
And I will make my return to
the glorious world of the elite.
Lady Rachel.
I have made the
arrangements about the whore.
Are you sure
about this?
Yes.
Please
go ahead.
Yes, my Lady.
Marsha.
Forgive me.
Everything is
for my uncle.
For my
uncle...
Rachel.
Yes.
I need to
talk to you.
Have you
discovered...
...my secret?
Secret?
W-What are you talking about?
There's no need to hide it.
What the slut was saying is true.
That's all.
Return to your lessons.
Uncle.
What?
The story that you sustained
an injury in battle must be a lie.
If it was a
physical injury...
...you can't expect it to heal
by going to a place like that.
Did you have some sort of mental
shock or did something else happen?
It did, didn't it?
Is that it, Uncle?!
Leave.
Uncle!!
Just get out!!
I don't understand.
I don't understand what you're thinking.
Uncle...
...you're the only relative
I have left in this world.
Please tell me, Uncle.
I...
I'm not afraid to know
what happened to you!
After going through the
lessons of a Love Doll...
...I've nothing
left to fear!
No!
Get out!!
Why?
Do you hate me, uncle?
That's not it.
Then why?
It's because...
It's because you resemble
my sister too much!!
My mother?!
I was in love
with my own sister.
with your mother!!
My sister was the most
important part of my existence.
But the day came when
my sister was to marry.
In despair, to distract my mind,
I was intimate with countless women.
But that was
only an empty act.
To find a new meaning for my
life, I left for the battlefield.
I learned of my sister's death in a
letter delivered on the battlefield.
Since then, I haven't been
able to get an erection.
Poor uncle.
I'm such a fool.
Of all sins, I was in love
with my own sister!!
W-What are
you doing?!
I was able to train as a
Love Doll thanks to you, uncle.
If I can help with the things I've
learned, I'll gladly do anything!
Uncle, please
let me help you!
I swear
I'll cure you!
I swear.
No!!
How can I
be forgiven...
...for having sex with my niece
who's the very image of my sister!
But...
Why uncle?
I just want
to help you.
Uncle!
Uncle!!
Mother?!
Please, explain. Why is...?
After my
sister's death...
I claimed her body and
secretly moved her to this room.
I had her body completely
preserved and gave her eternal beauty.
Rachel.
Forgive me.
Uncle.
As my only relative, you should
be living your life as an aristocrat.
But I have forced you take
the path of a Love Doll...
...knowing it to be one of
the hardest ways of life.
It was because you looked
exactly like my sister.
The strict training
as a Love Doll...
...was meant to make you
into my ideal woman.
It was the method I chose to make
you into a reincarnation of my sister.
Uncle.
Forgive me.
There's nothing
to forgive.
I'm overjoyed to find out that your
love for my mother was so deep.
You lost the
drive to have sex...
...because of your grief over
the loss of your beloved.
You have such
a tender heart.
Rachel.
Dusse.
I am
not dead...
Come... If you love me from
the bottom of your heart...
...be strong and
embrace me.
Sister...
For uncle, my mother holds the
same place as Andrew does for me.
Uncle!!
It feels
so good.
It's wonderful.
It's so good, uncle.
Uncle.
What
is it?
You're fingers
are great but...
...I want your...
But I...
Don't worry, uncle.
Look.
It's really hard now uncle.
Uncle, please
come in me.
It's in me.
Your dick is inside me.
Rachel.
It's amazing!
The inside of my body is getting hot!
It's so wonderfully numbing...
My pussy is...
Uncle.
Rachel... I'm going to...
Oh uncle...
Hurry... Hurry...
Uncle.
Tonight I will make
my debut as a Love Doll.
I have endured such harsh
training to reach this day.
I am sure my mother and
uncle are watching over me.
No!