Huh? Nozomu-kun, are you going
to start living on your own?
W-Well, not until college starts.
Isn't your first choice University only nearby?
Can't you just commute there instead?
My parents were like "try to be independent".
Yeah, I think that you should do just that.
You think so?
Yeah, you tend to just space out at times.
Are you the one to talk, Shiori?
Huh?
Gosh, what are you saying?
I'm already living by myself!
I'm already a veteran compared to you!
Y-You're right.
If I remember correctly, Shiori started to live
on her own due to her parents' work.
Then, have you been doing the
cooking and laundry by yourself?
That's right.
I think I can't just start living by myself.
I'd at least want you to teach me the basics.
I-Is that so?
Hmm? What?
No, it's nothing.
You'll pass over your flat,
if you keep spacing out.
H-Huh? Since when did we get here?
See you tomorrow, then.
H-Hey!
What?
Were you serious about earlier?
That you want me to teach you about housework...
Huh? Y-Yeah...
I've already been living by myself for three years,
so I can teach you a lot more different things.
I can teach you basic stuff if we're in my flat,
and I can even help you study as well!
Really?
But I'll have to live nearby if you'll
teach me about various things.
Is that a key?
What I'm trying to say is...
Do you want to stay at my flat?
Aikagi
"Duplicate Key"
Aikagi The Animation.
Huh?
That's right, I'm in Shiori's room.
Good morning, Nozomu-kun!
G-Good morning!
Breakfast is almost ready, so wait for it.
No matter how I think about it,
this situation is strange!
We're a young boy and girl!
We're talking about a whole month!
Will an unreasonable request like that
normally be approved by her parents?!
However, now that I'm taking
a good look at Shiori...
She sure is so pretty.
Nozomu-kun, let's go shopping
later on our way home.
O-Okay.
Will I be able to hold myself back
for a whole month in this situation?
Phew... And that will do for my laundry.
How was it? Have you gotten a bit used to it?
There's quite a lot to do when living alone, huh?
Okay, I'll give you a lecture about
cleaning the bathroom next.
Alright, then. I'll get changed
so wait there for a moment.
Get changed?
Oh, she means clothes that
are okay to get dirt on.
Sorry for the wait!
Sh-Shiori, what is that?
Didn't I say clothes that
are fine getting wet?
Ehehe... What do you think?
This girl... She's not aiming to do this, is she?
First, we'll simply wash it with detergent.
The impact of her sideboobs is devastating!
Nozomu-kun, are you listening?
I'm listening, yes I am!
You shouldn't be looking away!
Next, we'll have to rinse it good...
Oh, I'll do that.
Oops!
Whoa!
Nozomu-kun, are you alright... Huh?
Whoa—!
No way, Nozomu-kun!
Sh-Shiori... Y-Your hand!
No!
Huh? Are you two not going out yet?
What "yet" are you talking
about? What do you mean?
She always looks after you.
She even started making you
packed lunches lately.
This is, you see...
It's not like you have any
ill intentions on her, right?
Well... Yeah...
Oh, who would've guessed
that a late-bloomer like you
will be able to make him a packed lunch now...
Like I told you, you have to take
action if you like him that much.
Uhh...
I can't tell her that we're already living together.
It's already been a week, Nozomu-kun.
Huh, of what?
I'm talking about how long you've been here.
Oh, it's already been that long.
So, have you gotten used to it?
Well, yeah... Oh...
Is it here?
Huh? That's strange. I wonder where it went.
It went in so deep!
Now even her words have
started to sound lewd to me.
I got it!
It would be great if we'll end up at the same college
and keep living together like this...
Going outside?
Yeah...
But we just went shopping last time.
No, not at the supermarket...
E-Every once in a while, we should eat outside
or go see a movie, don't you think?
Oh, I see... So that's what you mean.
If that's so, of course... Huh?
Does that mean...
I guess that's a no...
N-No, It's okay.
Alright! Then, tomorrow's a date, okay?
Okay... I-I'll be under your care.
I'm sorry, Nozomu-kun!
I made you wait out here.
We have to meet up outside
despite already living together.
It kind of feels strange.
You're right.
So, where are we going today?
Oh, the first one is...
Wow, isn't it amazing?
I'll always remember this!
What's the matter, Nozomu-kun?
I love you.
Nozomu-kun?
I am in love with you, Shiori.
H-Huh?!
I realized it when I started
living with you in that room.
I want to be with you even more.
B-But...
Yes...
That's why I'm taking the entrance exam
at the same university as yours.
I'll definitely pass!
And when that time comes,
will you stay forever by my side?
Yes... Yes!
I want to be with you as well, Nozomu-kun!
You see, I've been meaning to say this to you!
Will you go out with me?
Of course!
They're huge.
Hearing that is embarrassing!
No...
They really are huge.
I told you that it's embarrassing...
Does this feel good for you?
My voice is going out on its own.
Whoa... Your insides are hot!
It's dripping out a lot.
That's because you're touching it!
No, don't! Something's coming!
Could it be, that you came?
I-Is that what it is called?
Yes... I came for the very first time!
That's...
This is all too sudden, after all...
No, it's alright...
This is a special day when
we finally became lovers.
So I also want my first time...
Wait.
Can you let me say it instead?
Shiori...
May I be your first?
Whoa... S-Something's coming out of it.
It is proof that I'm feeling good.
Shiori...
Yes...
Sh-Should it be right here?
You don't have to force yourself if it hurts.
Thank you, but I'll try to do my best.
It went inside...
We made yet another "first" memory.
I'm sorry, I'm only barely able
to hold myself back right now.
No, it's alright...
You can do it as you please.
Nozomu-kun, you're amazing down there!
I can feel it going inside me!
It's stretching me so wide deep inside!
Shiori, your insides are clamping me!
Th-That's because every time you're twitching,
my insides contract on their own!
Shiori, does it feel good?
Y-Yes... It hurts at the beginning,
but I'm alright now...
Shiori, you're sopping wet down there.
That's because you're
rubbing against it so much!
This is incredible!
It's incredible!
Sh-Shiori?
Me too, I want to make you
feel even better, Nozomu-kun!
Nozomu-kun... I love you, I love you!
Me too, I love you so much!
I love you a lot!
Don't do that! No!
I'm... I'm already about to come!
I-I want your stuff... All of it!
I want all of it!
Will that really be okay?
Yes, you can come inside me!
Will it be alright?
I-It's alright...
I-I like to have it the way it feels better...
I want to experience the pleasure!
Right there!
It feels so good right there!
Is it right around here?
That's it! It's making my body shiver!
I love you! Nozomu-kun, I love you!
It's like that same thing as before is coming again!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm coming!
Are you alright?
Yes, I just feel a little flushed...
But I'm glad that I was able
to give my first to you.
I'm grateful as well, Shiori.
I love you so much, Nozomu-kun.
I mean...
Nozomu!
Somehow, it doesn't feel like
New Year's Eve at all tonight.
That's because we've been
studying for the exam every day.
By the way, are you fine
with not going back home?
Yes...
I won't be able to spend
time with you otherwise.
A-At least say something!
Sorry about that.
Alright, then. Shall we start studying?
Huh? Let's at least relax in the New Year's Eve!
We can't! We'll get admitted to college together!
Nozomu, have you solved the problem?
I'll let him sleep a little.
He kinda looks cute like this.
Oh...
Th-This is his fault for falling asleep.
Wow, it kinda feels puffy.
Whoa! It got big!
D-Did something as huge as this go inside me?
It was me who made it hard though...
I have to do something about this.
Oh, it's dripping...
Huh?!
Shiori, what are you doing?
Th-This is... I was just teasing
it a little and it got big!
I didn't know how to make it
go back to normal, and so...
Umm, can you keep doing it if it's alright?
You want me to do it?
Please do so!
Does this feel good?
Yes, it feels so good.
I see!
It feels like you got better on it.
I wonder about that.
I can't take it anymore! I'm coming!
I drank all of it!
S-Shiori!
Can't we?
I-It's okay...
Me too, I want both of us
to feel good together...
Shiori?
Hey, make me feel good this time as well.
Wh-What's happening?
It went deeper than before!
You're not like your usual self,
and it feels new to me!
I only wanted
to make you feel good!
Sh-Shiori!
No, I should be the one
making you feel good today, so don't move!
I'll keep pounding it into my belly!
I told you to stop moving!
I love the way it gently rubs against mine!
It's about time for me to make you come.
Yeah, I want us to come at the same time!
Me too, I've been holding it in all this time!
Then, it looks like you'll be coming a huge amount!
You're such a lewd girl, Shiori.
Yeah, I'm fine with being lewd.
And since I am a lewd girl,
I want plenty of your stuff, Nozomu!
Alright, here it goes!
You're rubbing against my clitoris!
Wow, your dick is rubbing against
my insides, and it's grinding so hard!
I won't be able to hold myself back from this!
No, I'm already about to come!
Nozomu, you too... Hurry up!
Shiori! Shiori!
I'm coming... Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
It feels like we're most deeply connected today...
I feel the same.
But listen...
To help you focus on studying,
sex will not be allowed until after the exam!
N-No way!
Or are you telling me that you don't want
to get admitted in college with me?
I want to...
Good boy.
Alright then, I'll give you a reward.
Time flashed in a blink of eye afterwards.
It finally is the examination day!
It's finally over!
Nozomu!
Huh?
Shiori, why are you here?
I kind of got worried so I came here for you.
So, how was the exam?
Well, I was able to answer plenty of questions.
I see... You did a great job!
We'll be living in this town
after we pass, right?
How about having a little walk around here?
Oh, you're rushing things.
So cute!
So delicious!
Looks like the shopping district ends here.
U-Uhh, Shiori... Shall we go back?
What's up with you all of a sudden...
Whoa... Is this place...
Yeah, so shall we go back?
Shiori?
You see...
I-I promised that until
the exam ends... So, umm...
If you're fine with this...
Yeah, I want us to have sex...
Nozomu, just wait right there.
What's the matter?
Close your eyes and wait
for a little while, okay?
It's okay now, open your eyes!
Shiori?! Those clothes...
They have a cosplay service here, so I wore this!
Alright then, I'll take a look
at the spot where you're hurting!
Whoa!
It's already swollen so much!
I have to hurry up and squeeze out what's inside.
Does it feel good?
I'll make it feel good even a lot more, alright?
Please don't hold back and shoot it out.
I-I'm coming!
I'm coming too!
Hmm... The swelling won't go away...
Okay, then.
Now it's my turn to make you feel good, Shiori.
I'm putting it in.
Yes, give it to me!
Shiori, you came.
That's because I've been craving
for your dick, Nozomu!
I've been holding myself back all this time.
Alright, then... I'll make you feel
good until you lose your mind.
No! If you do it that hard, I'll come in no time!
You're squeezing me so hard!
No, that's because the pleasure is too much!
Slow down... N-No!
Did you come again? Aren't you
a bit too sensitive today?
You're hitting me at a different spot
than usual with this position!
That's a nice thing to know!
How is this hitting your insides?
No, you're rubbing against
the spot that feels good!
Oh, so this is the spot.
I'm coming already, no!
No! Wait, wait... Wait, wait!
Nozomu, I love you!
I-It feels good!
Your insides keep on twitching, Shiori!
Yeah! My pussy is delighted!
It's saying.... that your dick
is finally back inside it again!
Your dick is so hard!
It's rubbing against mine so much!
It feels good, Nozomu! Nozomu!
Right there! You're making my body
shiver as you keep going on!
Not there! Don't do that!
I can't take this... I've been coming
over and over since earlier!
This is bad! I'm almost there as well.
Nozomu, I want your semen! I want plenty of it!
My pussy... I want you to fill it up!
I'm coming! I'm coming again!
Wow, it's overflowing...
N-Nozomu?
I'm sorry, but I'm far from settling down!
W-Wait! I just came so I'm still sensitive...
I'm coming again right now! Nozomu!
I can't stop myself anymore!
No, I'll really go crazy!
It feels good!
I'm coming again!
More... More...
Shoot it in my pussy!
Something huge is coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Nozomu...
Shiori...
Nozomu, I love you.
Phew, that was such a long day.
Here, Nozomu. Good job on the exam.
What's this?
Those are valentine chocolate.
They're homemade.
Really? Can I eat them now?
Of course.
Are they delicious?
Yes, they're so delicious!
Here, have one as well.
No, I'm...
I want us to eat them together.
O-Okay...
They really are delicious!
Hey, Nozomu...
From now on, let's share lots of moments
like this together as lovers, okay?
Yeah... I'll be under your care from now on, Shiori.
Yeah... I love you, Nozomu!
A few weeks afterwards,
the exam results got published.
I managed to pass!
And thus, for each day starting from springtime,
I've been attending college with Shiori!
Now that I think about it,
me and Shiori ending up together
might have already been destined long ago.
I'm home!
Welcome home!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization