I came back
Shit
Put this love envelope on the shoe shelf it's shameful
But the man who loves me must be graceful
So I wanna forgive him
I'll say good-bye to Virgin
It's funny
What's this?
What do you mean?
Policewoman, nurse and girl student
They're my preys
I wanna hunt you
Movie: Maniax 3
EPISODE 3
What’s wrong? Miss it's a beautifual night
Nothing... .
Don't look at it
You come here alone
It's very suitable
Welcome to Ruttish
Satan paradise
I borrow it from your working place
It's a little small
Mine? This minor stuff...
Don't look down others
I will follow your orders
Please return the picture to me
A picture what're you talkin about?
Don't make up ti it's ok
I don't know what're you talking about it's not my business
All are the same
That's too bad stop it
What's this?
This is wireless shaking machine
You're a ruttish woman it's a big shock
No, it's not me
I hate it
It's very cute
Who?
It's your rival, right?
Zhamou's boyfriend
No, he's not
Come here because you love me
Look
I don't like it
I don't know about that man
God damn, it's streaming out
Free me
I can't stand for this
He's a funny guy
Rape Zhamou
Yes
No
Zhamou
Let me look your breast
Zhamou call me brother got it?
No
Call my brother
Please brother no
Scream it's an end monster
It's the rottish woman with a strong smell
How do you know this
I care it
I taste Zhamou fiirst you're the next
It's not simple
It's bad
What? Only this level...
Don't scare people
Don't believe it it's useless
My clothes are broken
Zhamou is blamed by her boss what can we do?
Right? Zhamou
No
Brother
She doesn't listen
Wait there until your turn comes
Ok, let's do it
Still?
Brother free me
It's ready for me to go into
No, stop
The moment for the two lover's
No stop please
No, it hurts
Go out out out
Zhamou's is too tight
I am shooting
Exellent! I'll shoot here
Stop No my stomach
You can't snatch my dinner
It's not reasonable
You can't stand for it, right?
Diyabie
Yes, master
Your virgin will be taken by me
You should appreciate me
How can you...
How? It's good to be caressed by men
No stop
Let me do it
Let me see a witch's clitoris
Your smell is very strong
Do you wash it often?
Of course I do it everyday
It's so sniffy the god don't want you
But take it easy
I am more excited about this
It's coming in
It's loose let me look
No
Stop, please
I am not finished yet
Now I wanna taste it
No, it's too high
No, I am falling
I'll fall down
If you don't wanna fall down
Hold it tightly with my penis
I never did it before
So you can try it
Please bite me
A virgin's vagina is very tight
No, it's early
No, I am falling down
Please, let me go
It's very tight
Good, that's it
I wanna snatch another virgin for your efforts
Is it good! Feel it
Raysou
Fine it's very delicious
It's the best taste
I never had before
After a good meal
I'll come to torture you
No
Relax! Or it'll hurt
This betrays god's expectation
I wanna change you possessed with divine power
As an evil woman
No
I won't lose it
I can't lose
What?
He has a god's blood
How can a man have Ruttish
Satan's power like me
I have lived for thousands of years
Master
How come? It's so poor
Bad! What?
Good morning, Amily
Luther Father
Welcome
Are you busy?
I cam come next time
No, this is ok
The guests are always right
It's a belief in my store
I clean it at once
Are you all right?
It's hurt
God damn
Luther Father what happened today?
I want a candle
Candles I have various kinds of candles
I want a thick, big and red one
We have it in the depository
Wait a moment
I bring it immediately
Hunt Witches at Night
I don't know
It's not our goods
You still wanna cheat us?
You adore a witch who worships Satan
No, I am not a witch
It's so poor
God forgive this man
Ok, I got it
Since you resist this
Prove it if you can
Well
Yours are exposed
This is...
It's shameful
Don't look, no
Don't look at it
The rope you sold to me is very strong
You're so bad
How can you do with it?
You look so cute but you have hair here
Don't you shave it?
But...
Though nobody sees it
You should clean it
It’s a woman's etiquette
It hurts
Luther Father it hurts
I am sorry, Amily
I won't let you feel hurt forgive me
That is...
Right? Do you have candles?
How come?
It's very convenient
How? Burn the hair
It's less hurtful than plucking hair
It's scalding
It's not easy
Let me look here
By the way try the butt
It's hard for one man
What?
No, it hurts hurts alot
No, Luther Father
Don't do it.
I can't endure it
I wanna peepee
Well...
If you do this before us you lose your etiquette
I am sorry Luther Father
So the fire is burn out
It's good as well
There're still many candles
No, don't torture me
No, if you admit you're a witch
I got it
I am a witch
I am a real witch
Luther Father thank you very much
No no stop please
No no stop it
No save me
Luther Father
No no no
It hurts
Take it out Luther Father
That man can't stand for this
Catch these sperms carefully
Luther Father, no no
He saves many sperms in these days
God damn, he shot inside
No
Work hard or you'll suffer more
What?
Why?
How can't you control it?
Or there's a god
Are you all right?
No
A woman takes a bath in the forest
Feel itchy?
Let me comfort you
No stop please
Well, you're juicy
Desire something?
No...
God damn stop it!
You can't come back if you make love with me
What do you mean?
It's very dangerous to you
What's this?
Shit
No no stop it
No, stop
Bingo
I met the best woman
No, you can't...
You're so bad
No...
Right that's fine good job
What? You're...
I can't stop it
What? My body...
It's your fault burn my body
I am powerless
Exellent! I can feel your energy
Give me more
That's so great
Yours are different from other men
What?
It's strange
The power is endless
And it's more and more
What's this energy?
Or you're...
I... can't
Are you a human?
Yes, I am Ruttish Satan
You came from another world
We met before
And it's called God's descendants
I am not a human?
You wanna leave?
Where're you going?
I don't know
Not here
Bring me with you
I...
I feel extremely satisfied as I make love with you
I don't want other women
If you possess me you don't need other's energy any more
Thank you
Ok, let's go
Where's Luther Father?
He won't be here forever