Its great...
If you do that much... I... I...
SubDESU-H Presents
Yama Hime no
Hana
Its great...
If you do that much... I...
Please... I...
Maho
I’m cumming, I’m cumming...
No... it feels so good.
Maho is my childhood friend and...
She’s my precious girlfriend.
More.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Good...
More dick...
Give me more dick.
But she’s having sex with another man.
Good.
My pussy...
I told you so.
- An hour earlier -
Yes?
You're late today...
Naoki?
I’m home Maho.
Why are you here?
You came back to this town?
Yes, I came back.
Sorry, Naoki.
Anyway, come inside.
Hello?
Is everything alright with that phone call?
Could it be that you have an appointment?
No, it's alright.
I had an appointment to meet a friend, but I postponed it.
Welcome home, Naoki.
Naoki, does it feel good?
Where does it feel good?
That part...
Is it here?
Naoki’s juice is coming out already.
Sorry.
I’m at my limit.
Sure, give me a lot.
Release a lot inside.
A lot came out.
Sorry.
It’s been a long time and...
Maho's technique was so good.
I’m glad that you release that much into me.
Hey, this time lets feel good together.
Its been a long time since I tasted Naoki's dick.
Naoki’s dick feels so good.
Maho’s pussy also feels so good.
Its so wet.
No...
Don’t say that...
I was surprised.
You came home so sudden.
You didn't tell me anything that you'll be leaving this town.
I was so sad.
I cried a lot.
Maho...
But I understood because it was Naoki...
I love you, Naoki.
I love you too, Maho.
Naoki, I missed you.
I missed you.
Naoki.
It feels so good, Naoki.
Naoki...
Maho...
I’m... at my limit...
Can I release it inside, Maho?
No, you can’t release it inside.
I can’t?
I want to release it inside Maho.
You can’t.
I said you can’t.
You can’t release it inside today.
When the time comes for me and Naoki to be happy...
Give me a lot inside me.
Ok?
So please, release it outside.
Sprinkle Naoki’s on me.
How long you’ll be staying?
Can you stay here forever?
Since I've come back, I’ll live here from now on.
Sure?
Yes, I’ll be at Maho’s side from now.
Sorry, I think for today there is not much time.
The friend that I promised...
No problem.
I came back so sudden so...
Next time around.
I can’t stay with you a little longer even though you just came back home.
Then why don’t you live with me?
We can live together.
I will get back the time lost while I was not around.
Sender:
Maho's secret
April 27th
Received
Attached file
What the hell.. is this!?
Maho is lecherous
Maho is a whore
You should give up on Maho.
She has another man.
She’s messing around with another man.
Everyone knows it.
You’re the only one in this town who doesn’t know about it.
Do you remember Kamijou-senpai?
Kamijou Masaya.
Kamijou... You mean that Kamijou!?
Yes.
That Kamijou-senpai who's abusive of woman and got disliked because he meddled with Maho.
I never thought Maho would stock with that man.
The frivolous one like him are the ones I hate the most.
Why didn't you stop her?
Isn't Maho your friend?
Why!?
Don’t be so naïve!
Whose fault do you think this is?
Its yours!
Maho wouldn’t be like this if you took care of her properly!
Friend? We ended it already.
If you don’t believe me then go check it yourself.
She refused it at first but now she doesn't.
She’s crazy.
She moans so loud that I can hear her voice over here.
Its troublesome.
They'll probably start soon.
She’s crazy isn’t she? She just kissed you a while ago.
Kamijou-senpai enters Maho's room every night.
He enters the room around the same time you came home.
And do that until morning.
She moans till morning everyday.
Senpai entered the room a bit late today.
Good thing that you two didn’t meet.
You can see it right? Isn’t this crazy?
You’re annoying, Kamijou-senpai is going out with Akiko right?
You’re the worst, saying that you got bored with her.
Don’t be so mad.
You were confessed to, right?
I’m not happy being liked by the person I hate.
The mail sent to you earlier was sent by Kamijou-senpai who complained to me and Maho approved it.
I don’t like men who treat woman as their toy.
You’re quite energetic Maho.
Did you wait that much?
Hey, how long are you gonna continue the...
relationship with that man?
You were with Naoki a while ago right?
I’m sorry.
He’s the one you love so much right?
He’s calling you his girlfriend even though he just came back.
What is it exactly Maho?
Naoki is my childhood friend and our parents know we’re going out.
So what will you do?
You’re going to break up with me and go back to Naoki?
You know that... You know that this shouldn't have happened...
Are you comparing his small dick and my dick?
It can’t be compared.
With this dick, I can’t stop.
She's serious even though she knows she's being watched.
She has the face of a whore.
Naoki!
Good.
It's going in deeper.
It's.. It's amazing.
I can't stop.
I like this.
It's good.
This...
I've waited for this.
I wanted senpai's dick.
But...
I wanted to receive senpai's dick earlier but then...
Naoki came home suddenly...
Naoki was with me that's why...
And Naoki didn't want to leave...
I wasn't able to meet senpai because Naoki didn't leave.
Even though I wanted senpai’s...
I wanted to have sex with senpai.
My pussy wanted you.
I waited...
Did the waiting make you suffer a lot?
Maho is a pervert.
No...
No..
Don’t say that.
No...
No... My body is hot.
It's hot.
Amazing...
Amazing... A-Amazing...
This is... This is...
Feels good...
It feels so good.
Is my dick that good?
No...
Maho is really a pervert.
Don’t say that...
Don’t say such a that.
What’s this? How dirty.
Do you only think of a girl as a sex toy?
N-No I don't.
This broad and perverted are the worst!
Girls won’t become like this!
No...
Oh? Why are you saying no even though your pussy is producing this dirty sound?
N-No.. That's not it...
No.. This is...
No...
If you’re not a pervert, then you don’t want a dick putted in right?
I don’t want that...
No...
I accept it.
I’m a pervert and loves sex.
That part feels so good.
I feel so sad if I can’t have senpai’s dick.
I can’t bear it.
I...
I can’t live without senpai’s dick.
I’m a dick addict!
Oh my, Maho admitted it.
I will comfort you.
Hey Naoki, look, do you get it?
Its my pussy.
I’m already so wet.
I will comfort you of your pain.
Wow.
It came in, Naoki!
Its rubbing...
Your dick...
This feeling, its been a long time!
Its too intense.
I feel it.
No...
I’m going crazy.
Dick...
Give me your dick.
It feels good.
It feels so good!
She’s cruel, right?
She must not do that.
I will do my best to comfort you, Naoki.
Its good.
Your dick...
Your dick is stirring inside my pussy!
Good!
Its great...
Its reaching the tip.
Its coming through my cervix.
Are you ok, Maho?
I’m alright.
We can stop it if you don’t like it.
Its alright.
Please continue.
I’m glad that Naoki was my first.
Maho...
Naoki...
Thanks for taking my virginity.
Naoki, I love you.
I love you senpai.
I love senpai’s dick.
I love it!
I’m only... I'm only senpai’s whore.
It's good.
My body is so hot.
Its tickling and shaking.
I feel it just touching the air.
Good...
Its good.
Senpai’s dick...
Senpai’s dick is entering my pussy.
Senpai’s dick is getting bigger inside me.
Good.
Your dick is pumping and my cervix is tickling and...
It feels good.
It feels good. My pussy feels so good.
Its so good.
Senpai's amazing... so amazing.
I’m only senpai’s pussy woman!
Its lonely that Naoki left this town.
Its sad.
But...
I will bear with it.
I will bear with it
Because its for Naoki.
I’m Naoki's girlfriend so I will bear with it.
It's because I love Naoki.
Because I love you.
I will wait for you Naoki.
I will wait.
I will behave and wait.
So please come back to me Naoki.
I will wait forever for you Naoki.
It feels so good.
It's good.
That part... That part feels so good.
Then, will you break up with him completely?
I will.
I will break up with him completely.
F-For this dick...
I will!!!
Naoki~
You just came... no...
I just came and you put it in again...
Then I will make you remember only my dick so that you will no longer remember him.
Please.
Make me only remember senpai’s dick.
What? I don’t understand what you’re saying?
What do you really want?
I want...
I want to remember only senpai’s dick.
It's good.
If you do that so intensely I’ll cum again.
I will do anything just for this dick.
Good...
I’m a whore born for this dick.
I’m so glad that I met you Naoki.
I love you forever, Naoki.
Your dick is great.
Senpai’s dick is great.
I’m cumming...
I'm cumming...
I was born to have sex with you.
I was born for this dick.
I want to show this to Naoki.
I don’t care about Naoki anymore.
Aside from that, I want senpai’s sperm.
Please release a lot of senpai’s sperm inside me.
Maho, I’m at my limit...
Can I release it inside you?
No... you can’t.
You can’t release it inside.
She’s saying something like that.
How poor.
I will comfort you using my pussy.
It's good.
Your dick... Your dick is stirring inside my pussy...
Do you feel it?
Your dick is pumping...
It feels so good.
My pussy feels so good.
A-Amazing.
I’m cumming... I'm cumming!
Do you want to release it inside?
Its because Maho let another man release it inside her.
It's regrettable, right?
Go ahead.
You can release it inside me.
Release it inside me.
Please release Naoki’s sperm inside me.
Into my cervix.
Inside my pussy.
Release you sperm.
I-I’m cumming, I'm cumming!
It feels good!!
Its flowing.
A lot was injected... into my cervix.
It felt good inside me, didn't it?
You released this much.
Geez Naoki, are you trying to get me pregnant?
But it's alright, Naoki.
Please release a lot of it inside me.
N-No... No!
I can feel it.
I’m cumming again.
I can’t stop.
I love sex.
I love dick.
Its big.
Senpai’s dick is getting bigger inside me.
I'm cumming.
I can’t hold it any longer.
Senpai, please release it inside.
Release a lot of sperm into my cervix just like always.
Please make me cum!
Maho!!
Its coming! Senpai’s sperm...
A lot.. A lot of sperm...
I’m going to be pregnant.
My stomach is full of senpai’s sperm.
It's wonderful.
I’m cumming!
My pussy is cumming
I don't remember how I got home.
I don’t remember anything after that.
After that, I got a call from Maho but...
I couldn't answer it.
Naoki, what's wrong?
I’ll call you again.
Missed call
Recorded
After that call, Maho never called again.
I still can't erase Maho's last call.
Naoki, what's wrong?
I’ll call you again.