I have a secret.
What are you doing?
I thought I'd help out.
Since I usually leave
the housework up to you, Sora.
What did you put in there?
The flavor was a little weak, so...
Apples, vinegar, sweet sake,
and all the stuff down there.
What's that?
The meat sauce smells like
someone put paint in it.
Nami?
We'll probably be having convenience
store meals for tonight's dinner.
Huh?  What are you doing?!
Don't worry.
Times like this call
for the magic ingredient.
If I dump some mayonnaise in...
No!
I'm home.
Huh?  What are you all doing?
On the surface, we're a very normal family.
Mom, Aki-neechan, and my twin sister Nami.
But...
Aki-nee and I...
...have a secret.
A secret we keep from Nami and Mom.
Our relationship.
A relationship that Aki-neechan
and I can't stop.
A secret that must never be discovered.
Ever since that day...
That secret relationship...
...has continued.
Aki Sora
~ In a Dream ~
It looks good on you, Sora-nii.
Come on.  Where are my clothes?
Give them back!
No way.  Come on, put these on too.
Quit whining.
You're gonna be joining the Fashion
Research Club tomorrow, after all.
Huh?  What's that?
The club that Kana and I are in.
You mean, Sumiya-san?
Club Entry Form
Fashion Research Club
I hereby declare my desire to join the aforementioned club.
Name: Aoi Sora
W-When did you...
Take this with you tomorrow.
When did you fill that out?
Don't forget tomorrow!
Cute.
You look like a girl.
Sorry.
It's my fault you have
to prepare dinner twice in a row.
Does it tickle?
Stop that.
It tickles.
It's gotten big.
It's pushing out from these little panties.
Huh?  So there's a Fashion
Research Club meeting?
Yes.  I'm the Club President.
Although, the only members
are Nami and myself.
I see.
Truly, I'm very grateful
you decided to join.
Oh... well, about that...
Am I wrong?
Not wrong, exactly...
I wasn't the one who filled out the form.
Does that mean...
Nami... did it herself?
No, that's not really it, but...
Then...
You'll join us?
Uh, well...
Sorry.  I have to get to my next class!
What should I do?
Aki-neechan?
What's wrong?
Were you thinking something pervy?
I wasn't.
I see.  That's a shame.
A shame?
Don't tease me.
I'm not teasing you.
I'm always thinking about you, Sora.
Aki-neechan.
And besides, Mom said she'd
be home early today.
Really?
Hey...
Are you free after school today?
I wanna be alone with you.
But... is it alright?
Okay, see you later.
Sora-nii?
That was Aki-nee, wasn't it?
She kissed you on the lips, didn't she?
Geez.  I know that Aki-nee
is just being herself,
but you need to cool down your
sister complex a bit, Sora-nii.
I... I'm not...
Family can't stay together forever, after all.
He's not coming.  Stupid Sora-nii.
I kind of expected this.
You can't just enroll a guy into a
Fashion Club and expect him not to resist.
Oh! That's right!
Here you go.
S-So cute!  Sora-kun!
Really?
Thank you, Nami!  I'm so happy.
I'll put this in my box of treasured items.
Hey, Kana...
What is it?
Why do you like Sora-nii?
W-Why, you ask...
Because he's really cute, I guess.
Sorry I'm late.
It's fine.
What's wrong?
Ooh, it's big already.
I'm happy.
We're finally alone together.
Yeah.
Sorry, I'm sure I smell sweaty.
I like your smell, Aki-nee.
Me too.  Your smell, Sora...
I love it.
I'm sure I'm soaking.
I was thinking about
you throughout practice.
Sora... Sora!
I want you too, Sora.
Aki-neechan...
I'm lost.
It's dark, where are you?
Right here.
Here?
Yeah, just like that...
We've become one.
We've become one again, Sora.
Aki-neechan.
Start moving.
Inside me, as much as you want.
It's so hot and tight.
I can't help but put it all in...
I'll take it all.
I can't stop.  I can't stop!
It's okay, don't hold back.
Do it as many times as you want.
I... I'm gonna...
Sora, I'm flying.
I'm flying... I'm flying!
Aki-nee!
Sora!
We'll be together forever.
Forever...
Yeah.
Family can't stay together forever.
Family, huh?
Nami.
Eh?
Can family really not stay together forever?
Probably not.
That's why people fall in love
with others, and make new families.
I see.
Hey, Sora-nii.
Don't you want a girlfriend?
Why?
You Prime Minister of Idiots!
What about... Kana?
Sumiya-san?
Yeah, she's got big boobs and all.
B-Boobs?
What kind of response is that?!
Sorry.
I think you'd be a good match.
Huh?
You and Kana.
It's so hot.
It's like it's about to melt.
We can't...
Nami's gonna wake up.
Don't worry, she's a deep sleeper.
Ah, amazing.
You're about to come, right?
No.
No!
Sora-nii?
What time is it?
S-Seven!
Five more minutes...
It kinda feels like hide-and-seek.
What is it?
What are we gonna do if we get caught?
Leaving early?
Yeah.  When we went to the doctor,
he said she'd be fine with some rest,
but I want to make sure
she gets something to eat.
She'll be fine if you leave her alone.
She'll manage on her own somehow.
I can't do that.
If she eats her own food,
she'll end up even worse.
I suppose you have a point.
That's why I talked to the teachers
and I'm leaving early.
Tell Sumiya-san that we'll talk next time.
Hey!
Geez, that sister complex idiot.
I see.  That's too bad.
It's perfect.
Well, the chest area is a little tight.
It was made for Sora-kun,
so that's only natural.
The fact that it's only
a little tight kinda pisses me off.
Aki-nee's are huge.
But it looks really cute.
Really?
Yeah.
Just like Sora-kun.
Is something wrong?
Telling me I look as cute as a boy?
What's up with that?
Whoa!  Did they get even bigger?
S-Stop that!
Oh, come on.
Just pretend it's Sora-nii doing it.
I can't do that.
Because, you're Nami...
I'm often told we look alike.
But, your hair is different...
How's this?
I'm Sora.
Nami...
No good.
You have to pretend
it's Sora-nii in front of you.
This is a rehearsal for when the time comes.
A rehearsal?
I like you, Sumiya-san.
It's an indirect kiss.
My first kiss was with Sora-nii.
Sora-kun...
Yeah.  That's why it's an indirect kiss.
With Sora-nii.
Um...
Can we do it again?
Sure.
Even though I know that doing
this won't change anything.
Even though I know Sora-nii
is all Kana sees right now.
Even though I know I'm not
the one she's thinking about...
No!
S-Sorry...
Here, I made you some Ginger Tea.
I'll leave it here.
Thanks.
Did you take your medicine?
I took it.
You sound like Mom.
That's because you're like a child.
Stay with me.
Can I really stay?
With you?
Why?
Nami said something.
"Family can't stay together forever."
We can't keep doing things like this forever.
You and I are siblings, Aki-neechan.
It's okay.
It's all okay.
But...
No matter what happens,
I'll never let go of your hand.
I'll never leave your side, Sora.
Aki-neechan.
That's why...
I want you to believe me.
Aki-neechan, you're sweating so much.
Warm me with your body, Sora.
But...
Please.
But, I can't intrude on your family.
It's totally fine.
We're in separate rooms,
and she'll be asleep anyway.
Yeah, but Sora-kun
is taking care of her, right?
There's nothing wrong
with intruding a little bit.
If we don't, that stupid siscon
won't ever leave Aki-nee's side.
That's right!
We've gotta take him away from Aki-nee!
What if...
Well, this is just hypothetical, but...
If Aki-senpai really is Sora-kun's lover...
Sora, your body's nice and cool,
it feels amazing.
Aki-neechan's body is so warm.
It feels good here, too.
Aki-senpai's athletic, smart,
and has a great body.
I can't compare to her at all.
Come.
Come to me, Sora.
It's in...
It's so hot!
It's so much hotter than usual...
That's why...
I think I'm really lucky.
I'm lucky that they can never
be lovers because they're siblings.
It feels... good.
Me too.
Sora, it feels good.
Your body, your lips, even your voice...
Aki-neechan.
Aki-neechan, I'm all the way in.
Aki-neechan, I'm so deep inside you...
I can feel you all the way inside me, Sora...
Aki-neechan.  Aki-neechan!
Sora.  I'm so happy, Sora...
Me too.
Let it out.  All of it.
Ahh, it's amazing.
It's amazing, Sora!
I'm doing this with you.
You're doing this to me!
I'm coming.  I'm gonna come!
Hey, Sora.
What is it?
It's like I've been dreaming this whole time.
Ever since the day we first become one.
Even now, it's like I'm still in a dream.
I'm home!
Come on in.
Excuse me.
You can use that room over there, Kana.
Okay.
Aki-nee!
Hmm?
Where's Sora-nii?
In the living room, maybe?
The living room?
Okay... now's my chance.
I need to hurry and get dressed.
Sumiya-san?
Huh?
Kana?
Maybe she's tired from too much stress?
I caught her cold...
Sorry.
Aki-neechan...
Hmm?
Stay with me, forever.
Yeah.
Aki Sora
~ In a Dream ~
It hurts.
It hurts!
This is a punishment.
For committing a sin.
I tried to lie to my heart.
Does this mean that I shouldn't have?
I don't know anymore.
I don't know myself anymore.
Tell me.
Someone tell me!
OVA Aki Sora.
In a Dream, part 2.