Hey, raise your arms, Sora.
That tickles, Aki-nee-chan!
Hey, did your breasts get bigger again, Aki-nee-chan?
Yeah.
Do you want to touch them?
It's okay.
I'm not a baby.
Even when you grow up and become an adult, you can still suck and touch them.
That was just a game to me back then.
Aki-nee-chan, do you love me?
I love you very much.
I love you a lot too, Aki-nee-chan!
I never imagined...
that one day I wouldn't be able to say those words like I did back then.
Aki Sora
H-Ni Juu
Aki-nee-chan...
You said you'd clean up yesterday!
But I remembered that I'd rented some DVDs and hadn't watched them yet.
Actually, three of them.
That's scary.
If I hadn't noticed, I'd have ended up paying 750 yen in late fees.
It's not nice to take advantage of people that way, right?
You shouldn't be such a slob, Onee-chan.
What should I do?
Should I watch them and pay the late fees,
or give up and return them?
Hey, what would you do in my shoes, Sora?
It doesn't matter.
Either way I lose, right?
I'll clean this up, Aki-nee-chan, so can you—
Hey...
What do you think I should do?
I-I don't know!
Sora-nii!
Where are you?!
Oh, you're with Aki-nee again?
Breakfast. I'm hungry.
Eh? But I have to clean up Aki-nee-chan's room, so make it yourself, Nami.
No.
Maybe I should do it?
No, thanks.
Y-You're mean!
It's not like I can't cook...
You've never made anything properly in your life.
I have!
Like cup noodles...
All right.
I'll clean up quickly and make something, so just wait a bit.
Hurry up.
Thank you.
I really love you!
Sora-kun, are you on duty today?
Sumiya-san...
No, it's Nami's turn.
But she forgot and went to her club activities.
Do you always cover for Nami-chan like that?
No way!
We're twins, but I'm the older brother, after all.
But isn't it strange?
You and Aki-senpai are quite reliable, but she isn't.
Aki-nee-chan is?
She has a great reputation.
She has the best grades in her class,
and she's an extraordinary athlete too.
The girls in the sports clubs are always asking her to coach them.
I see.
Is your ideal type someone like Aki-senpai, Sora-kun?
Wh-Why do you ask?
Well...
If that was true, I don't think I'd stand a chance against her.
Wouldn't stand a chance?
N-Nami?!
You're really dumb, aren't you?!
You're annoying me!
Huh? Dumb?
Kana, let's go!
Talking to him is just a waste of time.
Sora.
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry. I can't believe I forgot my wallet.
You should get your act together.
Even Sumiya-san said everyone looks up to you.
I never asked for that kind of attention.
Actually you're quite a slob, aren't you?
Geez, you're mean.
Ah, okay.
Do you want to play for a bit?
Eh?
Th-This is embarrassing.
Don't worry. You look just like a girl.
R-Really?
It feels kinda breezy down there.
Try swinging the racket.
L-Like this?
Grip the racket tightly.
That's right. Then take a stance like this.
Like this...
L-Like this?
That's right.
One more time.
The scent of summer approaching...
and the scent of Aki-nee-chan's sweat...
I wanted that moment to last forever.
That's what I thought.
Senpai?
Geez... You said nobody would come.
I'm sorry.
But she said you looked cute.
That only makes me even more embarrassed!
If I were you, I'd be happy.
There's no way—
I-I-If you were gonna take a bath,
you should've said so!
Why?
That... would surprise anyone, right?
Sora.
Wh-What?
Do you want to bathe with me?
Wh-What did you say?
We used to take baths together all the time.
That was back then...
You don't want to?
It is not like I don't want to...
We haven't bathed together for a while, have we?
It's gotten bigger, huh?
Your back, I mean.
You're becoming a man, Sora.
Yeah, I am.
Let me wash your back.
Th-That's not necessary.
It didn't use to take a lot of time to wash your back.
You grew big before I noticed.
Hey, Sora.
Did you get turned on from playing tennis?
Th-There's no way I would!
I wonder why it's getting big then.
A-Aki-nee-chan!
Did you get turned on by
the girls in the tennis club?
N-No!
Then, was it because you were wearing girls' clothes?
No!
Then am I turning you on?
You're a bad boy.
Getting turned on by your own sister...
N-No, that's not the reason.
I...
It's okay.
I'll make you feel better.
Come on, loosen up.
Leave everything to me.
Good boy.
You don't need to hold back.
You don't have to think about anything.
Just enjoy it.
Aki-nee-chan... Aki-nee-chan...
Good boy.
You don't need to hold back.
Aki-nee-chan... Aki-nee-chan...
Aki-nee-chan...
No!
I'm home!
Where's dinner?
No dinner tonight, apparently.
Where's Sora-nii?
Looks like he fell asleep already.
Aki Sora
When I was a kid, I got trapped in a deserted house.
S-Somebody save me.
I'm going to die here.
I'm going to starve to death.
Back then, I began to believe...
that Aki-nee-chan would always be there to save me.
I'm going to Kana's place tonight,
so you don't need to make dinner for me.
All right.
Aki-nee-chan...
Aki-nee-chan!
What am I thinking about?
Sora.
Aki-nee-chan?!
I'll make you feel better.
Come on...
No!
Sora?
Sora, wait!
Sora!
Sora...
Sora?
Ah, it's started to rain.
I wonder if Sora-kun will really be okay.
Why are we talking about Sora?
He seemed kinda down.
Nami, maybe you should go home?
Nami?!
Today you're gonna play with me!
Your breasts...
are bigger than I thought.
Kana.
You two are twins after all.
With your hair like that, you look just like Sora-kun.
I can't believe I nodded off and got locked in here.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Aki-nee-chan?
So this is where you were.
How did you know?
Well, what should we do now?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
She's cold.
She got soaking wet searching for me.
I should apologize.
Sora.
Even though you're my sister,
I couldn't resist looking at you and having dirty fantasies about you, Aki-nee-chan.
That's why all this happened.
I'm glad.
I thought you'd leave me when you got older.
No matter how hard I tried to hold you close,
I felt you were drifting away from me.
That's why I'm glad.
I don't want you to leave me, no matter what.
No, this is wrong!
This is wrong. We mustn't!
Because we're siblings.
I don't understand.
Aki-nee-chan...
Aki-nee-chan!
No, don't go!
Sora.
I felt the same way as you, Sora.
I wanted to touch you even more, and had lewd fantasies about you, but...
I don't believe those things were wrong.
I love you, Sora.
I want all of you.
All of you.
Your neck.
Your feet.
Your fingers.
The inside of your mouth.
I want all of you, Sora.
Onee-chan...
Lie still.
You've gotten hard, Sora.
Really hard.
Onee-chan...
This is my first time, but I feel really hot...
You feel really good, Sora!
I've always wanted to do this.
It feels kinda strange.
Really strange.
It's hot... It's slippery.
I've always wanted to do this with you, Sora.
Don't hold back.
I'll take it all in.
Kinda... Kinda...
You can let everything out.
Come inside me!
We're connecting... We're connected now.
Sora, do I feel good?
Yes, you feel really good, Aki-nee-chan.
You feeling good makes me feel good.
Aki-nee-chan, I can't hold it anymore.
If I don't stop now...
Aki-nee-chan, I'm coming now.
Come inside me.
Sora.
You're coming... you're coming, you're coming...
Your come is gushing out.
Everything I'd held in until then shot out.
Everything I had came out and mixed with my Onee-chan.
I don't know if that was good or bad.
I just...
wanted Aki-nee-chan to embrace me, that's all.
That's what I thought.
I'm home.
Sora-nii, is breakfast ready?
Aki-nee-chan!
How could you leave your wet clothes in the living—
Oh, you're back, Nami.
I thought you'd already cleaned up in here.
Didn't you have breakfast at Sumiya-san's place?
I'm sorry I didn't!
I didn't mean it that way.
Do you want me to prepare breakfast?
Don't bother. I'll clean up and then make some.
Thank you.
It's all right.
I love you very much.
Although I'd heard those words countless times,
they sounded a little different now.