Devil's Job
You summoned me?
Here.
It's gotten this big.
Go ahead.
I'll make you feel... fantastic.
Look.
Right here.
It'll feel great.
Yes, yes.
Put it in just like that
my pussy...
Come on...
Sticking it in like this.
Yes, yes.
Be a bit rougher.
Hey... work harder.
Come on... look.
You have to do it like this.
How's that.
My pussy.
Feels great, right?
Hey...
Use your hips.
Your dick will feel even better.
Hey...
Feels good?
Does my pussy feel good?
Look, look.
I'll let you keep doing this.
But put some effort into it.
Hmm? How's that?
Feels good in my pussy?
Yes.
More, more...
Harder... don't hold back... make my pussy... ah...
What's this?
Incredible.
No, not like this...
My mind... my mind's going blank...
No, no!
Ah... terrific.
Even deep inside... feels full...
My pussy... it can't...
No... no...
I'm gonna come...
Coming! Coming! Ah...
Coming...
I'm coming...
Coming, coming...
So... so good...
Wonderful...
Oh no...
It's... too incredible...
My whole body...
Feels relieved...
I still want more...
More...
I'll lick you clean.
What's wrong?
Getting wet again?
Right.
Look.
I can still...
Make you feel even better.
Want to move by yourself?
Go ahead.
Even deep down... ah...
Wait... wait...
No...
My mind's... gone blank again...
Even the depth of my throat...
Dick... feels so good...
So... so intense...
Yes... use my mouth...
Your dick must feel great...
Go ahead.
Just like this...
Ah... your dick... your dick feels good?
Your dick...
Is it ready?
Coming... I'm gonna come...
Ah... no...
Coming...
I'm gonna... gonna...
My entire body...
Feels numb...
I can't keep doing this...
It'll become an addiction...
Hey...
Using my mouth to pleasure yourself without asking.
But...
I can make you feel even better.
Look...
Using my mouth.
Full force...
Will suck it real good.
Feels good?
More... more...
I'll make you feel even better...
Can't I do this?
Again...
We're not done yet...
Keep it up...
Look... look...
Does squeezing your dick like this feel good?
Gotta make sure you keep up that enthusiasm.
No...
Oh you want to cum again?
Hey hey... wanna cum?
Wanna make my pussy all sticky?
Sure...
Come on... come on...
Shoot all your sperm.
Inside my pussy.
So much...
Let's continue...
Huh?
Look...
It's gotten this big again.
Like this...
Here...
Rub... rub...
Feels good?
Look.
My pussy and your dick.
Rubbing together.
Rub rub against my pussy.
Gonna cum like this?
You cumming?
Yes?
Then let's do this...
A dick about to cum, going inside my pussy.
See...
Again...
Cumming again?
You're about to cum right?
Go ahead.
See, see, cumming again?
Cumming?
Coming, coming...
What a load of cum.
Inside me.
There's lots of your cum.
Let's keep doing this...
I'm starting...
We're doing this for you.
Yes, yes.
Give us all you've got.
Look...
Here, does it feel good?
Right here...
You look pretty happy.
Give it to me...
Shamelessly licking you...
I can't stop myself.
Great endurance.
Your dicks about to melt.
What's with that nervous look?
See...
About to cum?
Lick, lick, lick...
Yes...
Ah... so much...
Don't forget me...
That felt good?
Look, look.
Does my pussy feel good?
Then let's...
Make you feel even better...
It's all the way in.
Put your hip into it.
What?
Cumming already?
That's fine.
Come on, come on...
Come on...
You've still...
Got more right?
Look...
Feels good?
Surrounded with pussy.
Your hot, sticky dick.
Watch this... watch this...
Serving you with pussy.
Look, look.
All wet, and slipper.
Look, look, look.
More?
Want to get rougher?
Go ahead...
Your dick...
It's getting harder.
Looks like it's about to cum.
That's fine.
Let it out.
Watch this.
Shoot it out...
You came...
Look.
That look on your face.
They feel great, right?
Look.
What a cute little dick.
You can't hold it any more?
Just a bit more...
Gonna cum?
Go ahead.
Come on, come on.
Watch this, watch this.
You came again.
Feels good?
Weird...
Seems like he came too much.
Ehh... I wanted more.
Thanks for the meal...