I drank it
We'll become as one in heaven
Now we can escape to a place
where that man cannot reach us.
Those were the days...
I guess the poison has started to kick in.
Unfaithful Alice. The girl who
stepped all over my love, Alice.
Shit. Did you think you could get
away from me by killing yourself?
But I won't let you.
My revenge begins now.
Alice
What.... This can't be happening!
Dad!!
Dad.
Ouch...
What's under here?
How did this happen? Don't die on me, dad.
"Alice."
Alice? Did this Alice kill you?
"A woman who betrayed me"
That woman called Alice must have killed you, dad.
I'm running out of time.
I'll soon be dead.
My son, the one I picked up under the
bridge when you were three and took
care of you ever since. Listen up.
A woman, whom I've sworn my
eternal love to, has betrayed me...
And that's why I will curse her,
detest her, and never forgive her.
As I'm dying here, I order you to
take my revenge on her for me.
This is my dying wish.
Your dying wish?
Alice...
A picture of her would have been appreciated, dad.
I've finally found a woman named Alice.
I have my own gun.
That's my father's gun. To kill
her with his gun is to honor him.
Don Jirochou, six bullets
aren't enough to do anything.
You mean you need more than
six bullets to kill one bitch.
I mean...
Omasa, bring in Alice here.
I'll finish her.
Are all of you named Alice?
This diary is written in secret codes
that only my father can decipher.
He must have indicated somewhere
about the characteristics of Alice.
Have you finished deciphering it?
I've deciphered only one of them.
It says Alice has been transplanted
with the best of famous instruments.
Famous instrument?
This is it.
Any object can penetrate right
into that. So how do I check for it?
Okay. Bring them here. I'll
check every single one of them.
Alice from Japan.
Yes. Here I come with my first load.
Next!
Where is the next one from?
A transvestite Alice.
No!! Give me a break.
Next.
Alice from the North Pole.
Alice from Mars.
Land of tiny people
Alice from Lilliput
Alice from Brobdingnag
Land of giants
Alice from Wonderland.
Alice from the mirror world
Twin Alice
An 83-year-old Alice
Wait for me, darling.
That's all of 333 candidates.
What's the data telling you?
There's only one with an extraordinary instrument.
So she is the one. Bring her to me.
Girl number 180!!
Dad, I've finally found Alice.
I'll take the revenge for you.
Just watch me from heaven.
What happened to number 180... no, I mean Alice.
She is so terrified that she wouldn't even budge.
Just tell her I'll entertain her once more...
With my unit.
Enter! Number 180!
What?
What the.... What is this ?
Are you from our rival organization?
I'll ask you just to make sure. What is your name?
A... LI... CE...
You weren't in that group of Alices from earlier.
No.
Come here. I want to check your famous instrument.
This is a device that measures the
level of one's famous instrument.
If the needle goes beyond the level of the girl
number 180, unfortunately I'm gonna have to kill you.
Oh my!!!!!!!!!
I've done it.
Don Jirochou. I've found out who Alice is.
We've got a picture of her. Please
take a look at this. She is the one.
Wait. Where do you think you're going?
I'll take it easy on you since you seem new here.
My name is Don Jirochou.
I'm the sponsor of this army.
I'm sorry sir.
Ok.
Jean!
Jean, are you okay?
Just a little scratch.
Jean, you must endure even if it's tough on you.
If you get fired, we are done for.
I know. Don't let me suffer.
Hey, let me see that for second.
Hold it.
Aim here.
That felt good.
You are here early, Don Jirochou.
Is it true that you've discovered
Alice? My father's enemy...
It was pretty easy to capture
her. It's that woman over there.
Well done, chief.
According to this diary, your dad had created
an incredible woman before his death.
More feminine than femininity itself...
Perhaps, she is the most ideal woman
in this planet that men seek for eternity.
Watch me, dad. Here is that hateful woman
who betrayed you and led you into your death.
Alice, the woman who stepped all over my love
Your beautiful face...
Your great body...
By transplanting certain parts of my skin...
Taken from my brain, my heart, and my dick
I won't let you die, Alice. I will definitely resurrect you.
I will resurrect you even if I have to expend
all of my knowledge, my laboratory,
and my money that I have plenty of.
And when you awake, you will
notice my terror for the first time.
And...
Your body will be altered in a way that
you'll become men's eternal sex slave.
Your face will be even more beautiful than
before... this part needs to be perfect.
I'll make sure you won't laugh
at my small dick like before.
I'll alter your body so that
you'll stay horny all the time.
And you'll obey all kinds of orders...
Until you hurt yourself.
I can't wait till I resurrect you.
It's been exactly 60 years since the day you died.
Cough!
It's falling apart.
But I'm still healthy.
Finally, you will be resurrected today.
You'll become aware of my terror today.
Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam !!!
It's a success.
It's been so long. I've been waiting for this day, Alice.
To congratulate your resurrection, have sex with me.
I'll tell you once more. I'm the
one who made you into a babe.
Using my own skin.
Taken from my brain, my heart, and my dick
Now, please make love to me... gently.
My revenge. How wonderful.
She's truly the ideal woman that all men want.
But this is my revenge... revenge of a man.
What a sad cyborg.
She will live forever even if she wants to die...
Just like me.
As I'm dying here, I order you to
take my revenge on that woman for me.
This is my dying wish.
His wish...
Must be kept.
I've finished, dad.
Don, look out!
That was close.
If she were a second late, you
would've been beheaded.
So Alice saved me.
And that means she ran away.
Unfortunately, that is the case.
It burns!
Use a different tool, idiot.
How shameful, dad.
I'll send Alice to where you are even if I
have to employ my whole organization.
Did you call me, Don?
What is your specialty in fighting skill?
Finishing off an enemy after
blocking off his escape route.
Alright. Go finish someone off.
This family used be the spies
from a rival organization.
He's that greenhorn security guard.
Jean, why are we being followed?
I don't know why we are being framed as spies.
Anyway, we have to run.
Don't kill them. Pursue them.
Just keep pursuing them.
What an odd tactic?
Jean!
Daigoro!
God, please save us
Here she is.
I knew she'd show up. Okay, retreat for now.
Roger.
Mommy.
He is dreaming.
I'm sorry for everything.
The kid is asleep.
Here
I'm a cyborg who was built just for this.
Drop dead!
Seize fire!
I see.
So Alice had appeared as we expected.
That's because the computer
deciphered the code correctly.
Alice is sensitive enough to telepathically
detect one's desperate cry for help.
So she helps whoever's in need of help
and obeys whoever gives her orders.
She is a cyborg who was built
for an eternal enslavement.
What now, Don Jirochou?
Tell the greenhorn guard that he is proven innocent.
How unfair. There was no such
charge from the beginning.
Silence.
Promote that greenhorn guard to commander
in chief of the guards and triple his pay.
Now, please me boy.
No, please stop.
I won't let you get away, my baby.
I'm going to fuck you, baby.
Dear god, please help.
Don Jirochou, I've deciphered another code.
With such an obvious deception,
it's impossible to lure Alice.
Move over. The show is over.
I've been looking for you, Alice.
Oh, how I was waiting for this day.
My father's hateful enemy.
Fuck me harder like there is no tomorrow.
Does it feel good, Alice?
Feels good.
Yes...
Now!
I failed.
The plan has been a failure. Alice has run away.
Don Jirochou is in critical
condition. Send in a paramedic.
Well now i'm unemployed. What terrible luck.
Call Omasa.
I've been here all along.
You bastard...
I know I'm fired.
Of course, you are fired. You made me into this.
But, you've got one more mission before I fire you.
Come over here and listen to me.
I've got a secret. Come closer.
A cyborg's body is mostly mechanical.
Therefore, you only have to make
the machine unable to move.
I see.
What are you getting at?
Rust formula
Rust formula?
Don Jirochou, I'm going to remove your bandage.
Thank you.
So what is exactly my duty?
Paralyze Alice by using rust formula.
That's your duty.
Stinks
Hmm... Rust Formula is...
This is it.
Good luck
How will I insert rust formula into Alice's body?
I guess I'll have to...
What? Did you put rust formula on your dick?
I see.
So what was the outcome?
Am I looking at it?
The outcome is... we are stuck together.
What do we do now, Don Jirochou?
Wait. I'm thinking right now.
Alright. Follow me this way.
Lie down here.
What are you going to do, Don?
To me, Alice is a hateful enemy who killed my father.
And finally, that hateful enemy fell under my nose.
If I don't kill her now, I'm
afraid she might escape again.
Omasa, do you have any parents or siblings?
I have a mother.
I see. I'll take your place by
taking care of your mother.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
I'll kill both you and Alice.
Please don't.
Why do have to kill me, too?
This is only way since you two are stuck together.
Forgive me.
It's finally over, dad.
Alice
What's this?
That's my dick.
Your dick?
Doctor, please reattach the
ripped penis back on Omasa.
Impossible. Too much time has
passed since it was ripped.
What shall I do, Don?
Don't ask me such a trivial matter.
My head is occupied with plotting how to kill Alice.
What?
Shit. What a travesty.
Hey, doc. So is my penis useless now?
Huh? Huh?
Who cares about your small dick anyway?
It's just as bad as not having one.
What am I going to do now then?
Bring whatever you want me to attach on you.
Really, doc?
Can I bring a self-indulgently big one?
Do as you wish.
Wait you horse! Horse!
Shaman, how much would you
charge for that technique?
Don Jirochou, It's not for sale.
Money! Money!
What will you use my technique for?
I want you to do this.
You must be too much in love with her.
If a man loves a woman too much, then
hatred could also creep inside his head.
Do you think I fell in love with Alice?
Nonsense. I only want to avenge my dad.
It's not strange for you to love
her even if you want to revenge.
Alice is truly an ideal woman for all men.
Am I really in love with her?
I only hate her for killing my father.
Clearly, I'm not in love with Alice.
Take it easy there.
If you want it that bad, then I'll do it.
Why would an enchanter want to
live in such a precipitous place?
Slippery
Hmm?
Shit. I've allowed myself to be beaten.
I'm saved by my enemy.
Alice
Water...
Wa... Water...
Water... Water... Water...
Water!
Please get me some water.
Alice just went to get some.
Alice?
Why won't you kill Alice?
You must stay put.
Why did you let her get away?
Kill her. Kill Alice.
I could kill her whenever you want me to.
But, I'm a bit sympathetic for her.
You fool. You are sympathetic for her?
What about the fact that she murdered my father?
But Alice is your lover
The tears she shed were for real.
When you were poisoned by the snake,
she wept because of your suffering.
Alice is a cyborg. She cannot possibly
fall in love with a human being.
It's not strange for her to fall in love.
Without a doubt, you two are meant to be.
How rude. How selfish of you to interpret as such?
Do it! Kill her!
Okay, I'll kill her. But to use my technique
on a person, it requires a certain condition.
You can't let her sense my presence.
So I can't let her sense your presence?
You must let her sense only your presence.
Why don't I give it a try?
Alice, do you like me?
Yes.
Then, try to pleasure me.
Don, this isn't my fault.
Like I told you, you can't let her sense my presence.
However, Alice had sensed my
presence for a split second.
Despite your responsibility, you forgot about my
presence since you were too captivated by her.
That's why the technique was cast upon you.
Daijyo, you are investing a bit too
much money in your laboratory.
Don Jirochou, that is expected.
Because of our big investment, all of our
products are perfectly manufactured.
But despite all that, we can't rid the world of this cyborg?
But didn't we get the 2nd place last year
out of 155 nations? That's pretty good.
Daijyo, I don't allow that kind of logic.
The 2nd place and the last are equally poor.
The last year's winner, Siegel
has great staffs in his laboratory.
The Siegel laboratory is surely noteworthy.
So are you saying you want to buy
off my laboratory, Don Jirochou?
How much do you want for it, Siegel?
What if I refuse to sell?
Of course I made sure that you wouldn't refuse.
Perhaps you kidnapped my daughter and
want a ransom? I'm aware of your style.
Correct. If you don't respond within 5
minutes, your daughter won't stay alive.
I've always loved your dirty
ways. But it won't work on me.
Come on in, my daughter.
Daddy
Hmm?
Alice
That's right. Now I have an
extraordinary cyborg named Alice.
I'm thinking of entering Alice to the
next cyborg fighting tournament.
We are going to win again. Another
victory for the Siegel laboratory.
So you've been staying here. Alice.
Alice, kick that annoying guy out of here
and make sure he doesn't come back.
Dad, I've finally found hateful
Alice, the one who killed you.
I will kill Alice.
But for now, as you can see...
There is nothing I can do.
Sorry.
I see. That must have been frustrating.
Your father's enemy was on the rival's side.
Do you have any cyborg that is ready to be used?
I have a few.
That is a seriously ugly cyborg.
I was more focused on its abilities rather
than its appearance during the production.
Go ahead. Give it an order.
I only have one order.
Seek and destroy hateful Alice.
That was quick.
Good work. So did you make sure
Alice is completely destroyed?
Are you sure you focused on its abilities?
Don't worry. That cyborg was for testing out.
Here is the 2nd cyborg.
I see. This one is much better looking.
In my opinion, the one with a
good look also has good abilities.
Do you know my order?
Sure thing. Destroy Alice.
He's prompt enough to destroy Alice.
What? Did you forget something?
Since promptness is the only merit of this cyborg,
he must have already finished her and came back.
How odd. He had beaten Alice all too soon.
Did you make sure that Alice
is completely destroyed?
I guess the one who has been destroyed is...
Doh!
Daijyo, can't you make a cyborg
more powerful than Alice?
I do have the confidence to make such cyborg.
Bluffing as always... then make one!
To make an extraordinary cyborg, we need
to operate on an extraordinary human being.
No problem. I have a plenty of
my men to provide you with.
As a matter of fact, I know the
most suitable person for the role.
Is there any other way?
No, there is no other way. Don Jirochou
Only way to defeat Alice is for
you to become a cyborg yourself.
So I need to turn myself into a cyborg?
Myself as a cyborg...
To avenge my father, who has raised
wholeheartedly an orphan like me...
I would even turn into a cyborg.
What would happen if you fail the operation?
Your body might end up in pieces.
That would be a problem.
I've changed my mind about becoming a cyborg.
Isn't it too late for you to say that?
You are a step too late.
Stop. Terminate the operation.
Return my body to normal
Nooooo! No! No! No! No! No!
Nooooo! Nooooo!
It's only a dream.
That dream just gave me an idea.
Create a cyborg and make it battle against Alice.
That's right. It's the cyborg plan.
Get a move on with the plan!
Immediately.
Tired...
So what's his weapon?
His greatest and only weapon is...
The fact that his body and yours are
one and the same, Don Jirochou.
After analyzing Alice's brainwaves, the data
proved that Alice is madly in love with you.
Just as I thought.
Even Alice will be powerless
against me if she's in love with me.
Time's up.
I still have 20 more minutes.
Since I'm proven innocent, I'm not
supposed to be handcuffed from today.
That's too bad, Domon.
There has been new evidence
that proves you guilty of murder.
Therefore, you'll be in here for the rest of your life.
What?
No. There must've been some kind of mistake.
My brother
That's 250 million dollars, Don Jirochou.
You are a heartless man.
So when will Domon be executed?
Whenever you wish.
Gas, electrocution or an old fashioned hanging
Which method of death penalty do you prefer?
Hang him.
That's what he deserves.
Stop...I ...
Brother!
I'm Innocent
I'm innocent!!
Oh, please god.
Dear god, please help.
I've been waiting for you, Alice.
That's right. I became a cyborg just to fight you.
Designed to appear whenever and
wherever someone seeks help from god...
What a pitiful cyborg you are.
You insolent bitch!
Are you in pain, Alice?
Since you were born as a slave of love,
your weakest point is your love for people.
Because you are touched by the love
between these siblings, you are powerless.
I'll pull your plug this time.
This is bad. There's going to be a trouble.
Hmm?
What's happening?
Hey!
What's the matter?
Why don't you finish her off right now?
Cyborg, strike her with your final blow!
I must hurry. I must hurry.
Hey you!
Stop it. Stop it.
We only built you in order to destroy Alice.
Who asked you to screw Alice?
A clone?
That's right. After we cloned a replica
of myself, we turned him into a cyborg.
What? Wait a minute.
I'm not your enemy. Your enemy is over there.
Cut it out, you idiot.
Help me, Alice.
Why?
Why does it have to end up like this?
Oh, there you are, Don Jirochou.
As a matter of fact, I forgot to tell
you something very important.
Both of them have a same frequency set in their
microcomputers. Therefore, there was a danger
of Jirochou cyborg turning against you.
Isn't it too late to tell me that?
You had your chance to finish her off
while they were getting busy.
But instead, you attacked the cyborg.
Hmm?
That's because...
But Alice is in love with you.
Without a doubt, you two are meant to be.
Nonsense. How could Alice and I possibly be in love?
Do you really believe that?
Don't be stupid. Alice is my father's enemy.
Even if Alice is the ideal for all
men, I cannot take it easy on her.
Are you sure?
Well, it's not my business.
Jirochou...
That's right. I will kill Alice. To keep my promise with
my father, I will go after her even if it takes a lifetime.
Although I understand it's only game
Stay by my side through out the night
Awake from my dream, another sleepless night
Although I understand it's only game,
Can't bring myself to fool around
Although I understand it's only game
Stay by my side through out the night
Awake from my dream, another sleepless night