I'm now in my classroom with my knickers down, stirring my pussy furiously.
Despite doing something so perverted, do they really not care?
It... it feels good!
Please, look at me!
I'm so wet! Look at my perverted self! Look!!
Look at me!!!
Doing it in front of the person I love...
But he doesn't look my way.
But that's not because he's ignoring me.
It seems that I...
...have died.
Oohara-kun!
That's right. He can't see me since I'm a ghost.
Why did you have to die?
Takahashi-san... I loved you.
C-Could it be that... we had mutual feelings?!
This kind of thing...
Too cruel!!
Shake! Shake your body!
?Unforgivable Round Butt??
Shake! Shake it, baby!
Shake! Shake your only you!
When I see you on a Sunday morning,
kimi ni aisa o na SUNDAY MORNING
I quickly feel all right!
sugu ni kakedasu yo I FEEL ALL RIGHT
The way you kiss gives so many signs.
kimi ni kuchizuke o SO MANY SIGNS
Carry on and feel my heart.
Abi tsuzuke yo FEEL MY HEART
But in truth, I can't hear your voice.
demo honto ha koe mo kakerarenai
My body, and so is my heart, seem about to explode.
karada mo kono mune mo bakuhatsu shisou de
Love is aligning you and you.
ai ha ALIGNMENT YOU AND YOU
I want to quickly see you, cling to you, and tell you that I love you.
ima sugu ai ni to daki yose daisuki to ii o
I'm every time going, but...
EVERY TIME GOING dakedo
I wait, but my true feelings don't reach anyone.
matteru dake ja honto no kimochi ha dare ni mo todokanai
Why?!
Why didn't he tell me sooner?!
It doesn't mean anything since I died! That's cruel!!
I don't want to die yet!
I didn't even kiss him yet.
I didn't even tell Oohara-kun that I love him!!!
Shut the hell up, you fool!!
My nose bleed... is falling... right through the floor...
My nose bleed is...
Honestly!
Dead, yet still a crybaby. That's why I hate brats.
Loitering in my turf...
T-Turf?
Th-This place is...
B-Boy's bathroom?!
Pissing me off!
Hold it! Who the hell are you?!
Me?
I'm the Toire no Hanako-san, Sakurako-san.
This bathroom is my turf.
Sakurako-san the Hanako-san?
It's rare for a ghost to come here.
Would you allow me...
...to hear you out?
I see.
The reason why you couldn't pass on to heaven is because of your attachment to this Oohara guy, is it?
Yes.
What should I do from now on?
Wanna try it?
Kissing.
With you?!
Are you retarded?!
I obviously meant doing it with Oohara.
B-But... I'm... no longer...
This is getting interesting.
It's been a while for my power to be...
...shown to anyone!
Hey!
Is-Isn't it Takahashi?!
No!
Didn't Takahashi die?
Woah! She's fully exposed.
No way.
Everyone is seeing me...
Well...
Calm down, everybody. A very interesting Sex Ed lesson will begin now.
There! Can you see?
Those who can't see, come forward.
No way.
No way!
Well then, this is where you insert your penis.
No. I don't like this.
They're watching... They're watching everything about me!
And next, this is the clitoris.
When doing it with a woman, this here likes to be touched form the top.
The one touching it up here should do it furiously.
Handle it with caution.
Don't look at me like that...
It's too embarrassing!
No good!
Our test subject got embarrassed!
What?
I'm getting this embarrassing spanking, yet...
Somehow, my butt wants more.
Does it make you feel good?
Let's see...
Getting so wet...
You're definitely a pervert.
Well? What's wrong?
Look. Everybody is watching...
E-Everybody, look.
My butt and my pussy.
N-No! My head is going blank!
Hey!
The most important person hasn't seen anything yet.
T-T-Takahashi-san...
O-Oohara-kun...
N-No! If the one I love sees me like this, I can't...
Oohara-kun's penis is so big...
O-Oohara-kun...
Look.
It-It's okay to watch everything about me.
Can you see, Oohara?
This is the pussy of the woman whom you love.
She's flooding just by you watching her...
Yes. It's amazing.
N-No!
It's getting congested.
Her honey pot is turning pure white.
Don't say anymore!
Sorry!
I'm like this, but...
I-I... have loved you for a long time...
Don't worry.
Me too. I've always loved you...
Takahashi-san.
Hey! Hey!
Don't just confess your feelings!!
You blockheads! What were you expecting? Hmm?
You want her pussy to continue where it left off, don't you?
That's not...
If you don't want to, then stop thrusting your dick, you idiot!
Oohara-kun is not an idiot!
He's a very good person!
You slut! Don't look so happy with your white pussy!
I'm sorry!
But somehow... I'm feeling really hot...
I can't take it anymore, either!
No!
If... if you move so roughly...
Okay, come! Come! Come while the whole class is watching!
No!
I'm going crazy! I'm so embarrassed, but I feel good!
It... it feels good! It feels so good!
More... go in deeper...
It's mixing up.
Ta-Takahashi-san... I'm gonna...
It's okay! Come!
Since I'm a ghost, it's okay to come inside.
Lots! Come lots!!
Thank you, Sakurako-san the Hanako-san.
I have no more regrets.
That's quite the satisfied face.
Oh, well. I wonder if those guys can pass on to heaven, though...
Ghosts and humans can't have sex, you know!
So I had to... you know...
Everybody died?!
Well, it's just a gallary.
I thought it should be better like this.
Then... Oohara-kun also is...
Takahashi-san...
It's not fair for just you to pass on to heaven...
Th-That's...
With this...
No! I can't go to heaven like this!
Alignment You! You!
And so, it's been one month since we've been hanging around Sakurako-san.
Right now, our relationship with Sakurako-san has become very good.
Sakurako-san!
Let's play!
H-Hold on a moment!
Sakurako-san?
Ah, um...
You saw it...!!
Looks like I made a mistake!
Excuse me!
You... saw... it...!!
I didn't see anything!!
He... Hel...
Really! That's mean, Sakurako-san!
Shut up!
You didn't even die after I killed you.
Well, yeah, but still...
Anyway, your usual hair turned out to be a wig, did it?
I didn't want to show you this look.
Why? That impression is cute too.
Id-Idiot! Whether I'm cute or not is...
At any rate, there will be big trouble if people make fun of me because of this look.
Make fun of you?
Humans... and our kind too...
This little girl feeling.
Wasn't that a flashback just now?
By the way...
I'm cuter this way?
No one told me this before...
Gosh! Sakurako-san, you're so cute!!
Sakurako-san!
Hey! Stop! Let go of-
What are those girls doing?
Idiot!
You have Oohara, don't you?
I'm a woman, you know!
You say that, but aren't you so wet?
You know, don't you?
I get wet easily.
Look! Down there, you're so...
I can still go on some more!
That's...
I wonder what would happen if I push deeper?
Can I put my fingers in?
Don't!
It... it feels good!
If you say that, you'll get punished.
What an amazing reaction!
Could it be that you've been looking forward to it?
Idiot! As if!
Takahashi! You bitch, I'll get you for this later!
You sure are coming a lot.
It's as if it's semen!
You... My weak spot...
Yes. I know.
Lots of stuff!
Takahashi-san? I was sure she died...
Why?
Ta-Takahashi! You... That is...
Ah... you mean this?
Actually, I got Oohara-kun's!
It looks like we can do this kind of stuff with our ghost comrades.
When did you two...
Sakurako-san.
Let's have lots of fun!
No way.
A girl with such a huge dick...
Amazing!!
That Sakurako-san is sucking my dick!!
Amazing! Sakurako-san, your tongue is moving around!
Sakurako-san...
I-If you keep doing this, I'll come!
At this rate, something is going to come out!
Don't!
I'm sorry! It's... it's coming out!
I'm coming!!
Amazing...
This is what a man's orgasm feels like...
No... It's not stopping...
D-Don't come so suddenly, idiot!
I'm sowwie... Your mouth felt great.
Sakurako-san... If I put this big, lots of come-shooting, penis inside you, then perhaps...
Don't you think it'd feel great?
D-Doing that within campus...
If I don't stop them, something bad will happen...
Got it? Put it in slowly.
If you put something that big inside suddenly...
Sure! I got it!
I won't be putting it in suddenly...
That's...!
My butt!!
S-Sakurako-san's butt is incredibly tight!
N-Not fair! Putting it into my butt so suddenly!
It's hitting deep!
S-Sakurako-san... If you keep moving so violently, I'll come!
It's... it's moving inside my stomach...
A-Amazing...
Up her butt... she's feeling so much up her butt.
Yes!!
S-Sakurako-san...
I-I think... I'm gonna come again!
My butt! My butt!!
I can't hold it!!
No! It's filling me!
Oh, no! It's not stopping!
No more! No more!
Inside... Inside my stomach, lots of your come is...
S-Sakurako-san!
Id-Idiot! If you pull out so suddenly...
Idiot!
Your come is gushing out...
S-Sakurako-san...
I over did it a bit.
I'm sorry.
Honestly! Doing whatever you want...
W-Well, it felt good so it's all right.
Really?!
Gosh! Sakurako-san, I love you!
More importantly...
I want you and Oohara to help me with something.
Yeah.
There's someone that needs to be punished.
Student number 18!
Come here and solve this problem on the blackboard.
Y-Yes!
Yesterday's incident...
What in the world was that?
Ghosts acting strangely...
Wai-
Sensei?
Wh-What? It's nothing. Proceed!
Uh, yes.
You!
Hey, sensei!
O-Oohara-kun, too... Why?
Sensei can see ghosts and touch them, huh?
My spiritual powers have been strong for a long time.
I see!
Wai- Stop it!
Murmur...
Murmur? Murmur murmur...
Enough! Back to your lessons!
There! You continue with the problem, too!
Uh, yes.
Yup! Yup!
We're ghosts, so nobody can see us.
If you don't act normally and do something weird...
I-I know!
But, sensei! You have amazing tits!
Leave them alone!
Well, don't get so angry.
I'll remember this!
Doing as you like in broad daylight...
Your nipples are really sensitive!
Se-Sensei?
It's nothing! Don't stop!
Jeez...
Sensei.
How about here?
S-Sto-
It's really wet, isn't it?
You two, how can you touch there directly?
We can pass through clothes.
That's why we can do this.
Um, sensei. I'm done...
I got it. I'll check your answer.
Okay. Go back to your seat.
Yes.
She's maintaining her usual attitude. Cool!
But, down here she got so wet, didn't she?
Th-That's...
Hey, Oohara-kun. Sensei got this wet. Aren't you going to do it?
Yeah. You're right.
A-Amazing!
If he inserts that into me in front of everyone...
I'll go crazy!
It's self-study!
Faculty Room
Maruyama-sensei, is something wrong?
Y-Yeah. I'm not feeling too well, so I let them have self-study.
Are you all right?
Yes.
The chair... The chair is...
The chair... Mustn't sit...
Sensei, are you not feeling well? Do you want to go to the nurse's office?
My butt... is sinking it in...
No good! A teacher abandoning her students and running away...
You must be punished for this!
Presented by Killer Maid
http://www.killer-maid.net/
Translator:
Dark Master Schmidt
Translation Checker & Editor:
Rengemaru
Timer:
Dark Master Schmidt
Typesetter:
Quality Checker:
Dark Master Schmidt
Encoder: