I'm the Toire no Hanako-san, Sakurako.
The desire you're falling to...
...I'll quickly relieve you from it.
N-No! Stop! Forgive me!
No!
Wh-What the?!
Maruyama-sensei is...
Pushing into her...
Please look! It looks as if something is being pushed in there!
I'm being watched...
Normal people can't see me.
So if I do this...
They can see all the way inside!
There! There! There! There! There!
Whoa... How intense.
Yeah. I just wish she wouldn't use it so roughly...
My penis.
What a slut! Your dirty butt is getting soaked.
N-No! Don't say it! It's embarrassing!
I-It's no use! I can't hold it!
You're really popular, Maruyama-sensei.
I-It's going into the same place...
Spiritually weak humans cannot feel my body.
T-The dicks... inside of me... N-No!
Ma-Maruyama-sensei, I have always been...
N-No! Doing something so perverted in the faculty room...
What are you saying with such an erect nipple?
Ou-
Ouch!
T-Tight!
N-No! My pussy is going to break!
I'm gonna drive your body crazy!!
No! So rough! I'll go crazy!
Come on! Moan some more! Everybody is watching!
No!
Everybody is watching! They're watching my pussy!
Here we go! Come while these guys are watching!
No!
Sensei, I-I can't...
No! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming!!!
Hot...
It may be shocking, but there is a Toire no Hanako-san in our school.
Hehehe...
It's gonna be
fun once they wake up.
Give me
my penis...
Give it back...
Sakurako-san rapes, murders, and acts in a completely arrogant manner.
But despite that, I love her!
E-Excuse me!
Ooshiro-kun?!
Please listen to what I have to say!
I suppose
I'll eat...
Alignment You! You! The Animation.
?Tentacles and the Two Hanako-sans??
Ghost 2! Tentacles and the Two Hanako-sans.
Shake! Shake your body!
Shake! Shake it, baby!
Shake! Shake it only you!
When I see you on a Sunday morning,
kimi ni aisa o na SUNDAY MORNING
I quickly feel all right.
sugu ni kakedasu yo I FEEL ALL RIGHT
The way you kiss gives so many signs.
kimi ni kuchizuke o SO MANY SIGNS
Carry on and feel my heart.
Abi tsuzuke yo FEEL MY HEART
But in truth, I can't hear your voice.
demo hontou ha koe mo kakerarenai
My body, and so is my heart, seem about to explode.
karada mo kono mune mo bakuhatsu shisou de
Love is aligning you and you.
ai ha ALIGNMENT YOU AND YOU
I want to quickly see you, cling to you, and tell you that I love you.
ima sugu ai ni to daki yose daisuki to ii o
I'm every time going, but...
EVERY TIME GOING dakedo
I wait, but my true feelings don't reach anyone.
matteru dake ja hontou no kimochi ha dare ni mo todokanai
Thank goodness.
I've always wanted to meet you no matter what, Sakurako-san!
Who the hell are you?
W-Who?
Hold it! You don't remember?
Come on! When our classmates...
Back then...
Wait a minute...
Why didn't you pass on to heaven?
A-Actually, I have someone that I've always loved...
But I didn't have the confidence to say it.
How romantic!
She still didn't hear it from you, eh?
Um, ever since I became a ghost...
I tried going to see her, but...
For some reason, I can't leave the school.
That's because I'm the one who killed you.
Since I killed you within my turf, you can't leave this place.
I beg you, Sakurako-san!!
Please revive me! I won't be able to rest in peace like this!
All righty.
Wanna revive, don't you? I'll do it.
Is that okay?!
Th-Then, me too! Me too!
Shut up! It's all up to my mood! It'll just be Ooshiro!
She swallowed him...
She's dancing...
A folk dance...
S-Something's coming out!
O-Ooshiro-kun!
Yes! I'm revived, aren't I?!
That body...
A miracle! A miracle!
What? What's wrong with my body?
Wait, what's the meaning of this?!
My body has... My body has...
Huh? That's funny...
There's a dick here. Really mysterious, huh?
Sakurako-san, more wonderful things...
W-What about my penis?
You have such a great dick, and you say you have no confidence?
Sakurako-san...
I will give you your confidence to profess your love.
You should be grateful.
That's right.
Lick it well.
My penis... Sakurako-san is pushing it in, but I can still feel more.
My body really turned into that of a girl.
I'm already so wet...
Oh?
What are you doing by yourself?
Feeling yourself up the first thing you turn female. You're truly a pervert, aren't you, huh?
At my own throat... by my own dick, I'm getting molested. But I'm feeling so good.
I'm about to come.
You should know. It's your own dick after all.
I'm coming! Don't swallow it! Hold it in your mouth!
Hold my semen?
A-Awful... This kind of thing...
She's drinking it... She's drinking my semen.
D-Down there, too...
It feels good!!
Hey! Don't take a break!
Let's go!
It's going in! Inside of me!
We're moving!
It's hot...
Feeling good? In that case, look as I do you!
It feels good.
Please... I beg you. Go even deeper.
How is it? The feeling of your penis and your pussy!
It's a perfect fit!
Even my tits... Don't!
Come on! Come on! Before you confess, you have to be effective!
It feels good! It feels good! My pussy too! It all feels good!
Even though I'm a guy, my pussy is soaking wet!
Then let's come!
Th-That's amazing!
Drive my body crazy more and even more!!
All right! I'm shooting inside!
Me too! I'm coming! I'm coming! Coming!
Oh, my. Creamed again.
If it's like that, I'm better off not reviving.
As to what happened to him afterwards, nobody knows.
What is this?
Here!
Yahoo!!
Sakurako-san!
Hey, Takahashi.
The tropical atmosphere is great, isn't it?
The school's pool isn't that great.
Honestly!
And I've finally put on a swimsuit after so long.
Please cheer up a bit more.
I guess so. After all the trouble...
Gosh! Sakurako-san, what a bold T-back!
Hold- Idiot!
TA-KA-HA-SHI!!!
I'm sorry!
No!
Did you attach Oohara's meat?
But, that's because you...
That's besides the point.
You little...
It's sticking in!
People keep saying you have a nice butt, don't they?!
You've been lately making sweet looks. Aren't you moody?
What's up with you?
Does spanking give you a hard on?
Because...
I wanted to feel good with you, Sakurako-san.
Old School Buidling. Danger.
KEEP OUT
Where did my penis go?
Hey!
You there!
Huh? S-Sakurako-san?
Y-Y-Your tits seem bigger lately!
B-But, Sakurako-san, you pull my breasts too much.
Don't go blaming people!
And so is yours. Small, but cute!
I can't!
Id-Idiot! If you...
Looks fun.
It's been a while, Sakurako.
Tsubaki.
It's not that surprising.
It's not like she's the only Toire no Hanako-san.
I didn't think you could get out from the old school. What did you do?
Not much.
A ghost that knew nothing wondered in. I just stole his energy and that's it.
Oohara-kun...
But eating a mere ghost isn't enough for me, so I decided to barge into your turf.
That guy belongs to my turf. One of my favourites, too.
You knew, didn't you?
Entering...
...means death!
Don't think I'm my old self.
In the 20 years I spent there, I learned many things.
This is one of them!
Tentacles?
Using the old school's vines, are you?
Shi-
Sakurako-san!
You seem to be having so much fun!
Semen is coming out from your pussy and butt.
Sakurako-san!
Sakurako-san...
Since you kept doing it with me, your power...
Sakurako-san.
Takahashi...
Run...
Even the great Sakurako gets exhausted once it's afternoon. It seems that you've become weaker.
You bitch. Involving Takahashi...
You like her?
Don't be ridiculous!
That's...
MY BUTT!!
Fool. Relating to humans makes you a failure of a Hanako-san!
Amazing! The dick is moving my hips on its own. It looks as if it's a huge clitoris!
Don't worry, Sakurako. I'll put this dick to good use!
This is bad. My butt is feeling good.
This idiot! If she keeps thrusting too much, I'll start feeling it!
Good! Come!
Let's come!
What?
You came? What a slut.
In that case, let me use the come to carefully lubricate you.
This is bad. I'll lose at this rate.
If she continues...
Does it feel good?
Feels good, doesn't it?
O-Of course not...
Not very honest, are we?
Soaking wet like this...
That's great! Express your feelings more!
Let me see the pathetic look you make when I thrust into your butt!
This the face you make when I rape your butt?
D-Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!
Aren't you a cutie? Why the teary eyes?
Be happy. I'll have to give you a reward.
Stop! I've had...
It's in! It's in!
It keeps stirring me inside!
Come on! Come on! I'm going even deeper!
Deep inside! It's moving in deep into my womb!
How's that? Is it good?
But I guess the tentacles aren't enough, are they?
What, you're coming with just one thrust?
It's only just beginning!
Amazing! Your tight pussy is great. I suppose a dick has to be stuffed in here after all!
Crazy! I'm going crazy!
Hey! I'm coming!
I'll fill you in good! Once I come inside, you'll submit to me!!
No! If you keep this up...
Sakurako-san, I'm coming, too!
Takahashi?
Sakurako-san, it feels great! I think I'll come again!
Here we go!
You're shooting inside!
How's that?
Not yet.
What?!
You're doing some more?!
H-Hold it! The semen isn't stopping! It's coming out!
Tsubaki, stop already!
N-No! It's coming out!
I don't have any strength! It won't stop!
No way! My womb is... My womb is... My womb is!!!
I'm getting filled!
Umm... are you all right?
Sakurako-san!
I... won!
But you know, I never thought you could possess Tsubaki's body.
A technique from the power of love!
To be saved like this... It's kinda inconceivable...
E-Excuse me...
Oh, it's you.
Eeh? Oohara-kun?!
Yes. Looks like I became a penis.
What in the world am I supposed to do now?
Hell if I know. It's out of my power.
Th-That can't be...
That's cruel! You play with my dick all this time and then you say this awful thing! Then-
Sa-Sakurako-san...
Sorry.
But he's annoying if not stopped.
I've been tolerant because you two were seeing each other.
Just look at how that turned out.
First of all, you are my personal toy, so you just need to do it with me. I have more fun this way.
So, anybody that disturbs my fun...
What's with that face...
Anyway!
What I mean to say that from now on let's work... properly...
So...
...to...
...speak.
Sure.
Presented by Killer Maid
http://www.killer-maid.net/
Translator:
Dark Master Schmidt
Translation Checker, Editor & Slacker:
Rengemaru
Timer:
Dark Master Schmidt
Typesetter:
Quality Checker:
Dark Master Schmidt
Encoder:
How long do you
intend to stay close?!
How long do you intend to stay close?!
The End
V!