So Koide-kun, can I do it down there yet?
Yes, please do!
I'll melt you with my soft tongue and warm body, okay?
Yes!
I'm sorry I came so quick.
It's fine. Cum as many times as you want.
Relax your body.
Don't resist your body's urge to cum.
Just let it all out.
Cum... cum!
Koide-kun...
An-chan? A customer's here!
An-chan! Customer!
R-Right!
Maid Reflexology
Welcome to the cafe!
Allargrando
Bookmark
Koide-kun, thank you for choosing me again!
Please feel good when I'm cleaning your ears.
Okay, go on and lay your head here.
Relax, okay?
Now please turn over.
Hey, Koide-kun. Can I do it down there today?
Yes, please.
Stick out your tongue.
It'd be bad if you made the store dirty...
So just be satisfied with this, okay?
Sorry.
I only do these kinds of things for you.
You might not believe me though...
I do!
Come back again if you liked it, okay?
Thank you!
Have a safe trip!
Maid Reflexology Dolce
Menu
Ear Cleaning
Hand Massage
Shoulder Rub
Please ask for the female
college student on duty, An-can.
I'll have to do my best at work.
There ain't no chick I can't get.
Why? Because I'm the best.
Koide, you don't know the touch of a woman yet, do you?
I'll tell you something. This is the best woman at night!
Y-Yeah!
Report back to me when you get a girl, okay?
I'll teach you how to please a woman.
Damn, you're so cool Satake-kun!
Of course I am.
I'm in the middle of getting this sexy little thing.
Well, getting her will only be a matter of time cause, after all...
I'm the best!
Yeah! If it's you, it's gonna happen!
Why not?
Why won't you go out with me?
This is me we're talking about here!
There's something you don't like about me?
At least give me your number!
Well, we could chat on my blog.
That ain't what I mean!
We're running out of time,
so let me just clean your ears, Satake-kun.
Alright?
Just relax, okay?
Damn.
Ah! Welcome back!
I read your text, Koide-kun.
Is this "Satake-kun" really so cool?
Oh yeah, he's beyond cool!
He's athletic, assertive, and full of confidence
He's everything I'm not.
That guy? Cool?
It's me!
I want to become like him one day...
You can't!
Ahh! Sorry!
So umm...can I do it there today too?
There are plenty of fish in the sea.
Really?
There just aren't any girls who are worthy of me.
You wanna?
You're just amazing Satake-kun!
It's the first time I've felt like this!
It feels good!
It feels like there's less.
Have you been getting your girlfriend to take care of it?
I-I don't have a girlfriend.
I do it on my own.
Hey, Koide-kun, I live by myself near here.
It has been kind of dangerous lately, so I was
hoping I could have a guy walk me home.
You can't?
I can!
Thanks for waiting!
Oh, you're not going to change clothes?
I'm not. Are you happy, master?
We're almost there.
See? That's it over there...
It's me! I'm the best!
Really? Where? Where is it?
Let's go from that side!
But if it's right over there, then...
It's fine, okay?
I'm coming in.
You can sit on the bed and relax.
It smells like her.
Got you!
Soap Land
How is it, sir? It feels great, right?
Yes...
My tightness sure is amazing, huh?
Eden
Yes...
Let's go for another round on the bed!
Let me put the condom on you, okay?
We're gonna have sex now.
Just relax. Don't get tense.
I'm going to start to move.
Just leave everything to me.
You can cum whenever you want.
Don't think about anything.
Don't try holding back.
I'll play with your balls to make you cum a lot.
Just let it out whenever you feel like it, okay?
It's still so hard.
Stay still.
Give me everything that you would've let out while masturbating.
You can cum as many times as you want, oka?
This is the first time I've done this!
My big boobs are coming in handy.
It's fine. Go on and cum whenever you want to.
Man, that sucked. She wouldn't let go of me!
We kept going till I was all empty!
You're so cool, Satake-kun!
As her mouth stuck itself to that huge dick, a
mischievous look appeared on Aoyagi's face.
There was nothing different about
Aoyagi that day at school.
At some point, everyone separated and
formed their own little groups.
People with similar levels of intelligence
and looks hung out together.
These groups were ranked from level A to level C.
A laughs at B and B laughs at C.
I'm in level C.
Hmph. C's dose enough to B.
Hey Okihiko, you have a retest for Physics, don't you?
Crap! That's right. Did you study at all, Nozaki?
I already passed that test.
You're the only one who has to retake it, Okihiko.
Oh God! Oh God, oh God!
What an idiot...
There's always someone worse than you...
No-Za-Ki-kun?
Yo!
Y-Yo.
Aoyagi is a level S.
You look grim today, as always.
She smelled like soap.
She's the vice-president of the student council
and captain of the mini-basketball club.
She's very lively and hardworking.
She draws everyone's attention as she passes by.
Good luck on your retake, Okihiko-kun!
Y-Yeah!
She treats everyone equally.
Aoyagi completely ignores everyone's level differences.
Nozaki-kun, Nozaki-kun!
You look as gloomy as ever.
You think so?
Could you come here for a bit?
I somehow ended up holding her hand.
It was so small and soft.
Nozaki-kun, if it's okay with you, could you buy this?
For 3000 yen.
What's this? A CD?
It's a DVD.
Just watch it for now. If it's boring,
you can give it back to me.
I'm home!
Eat, shower, sleep.
Alright, let’s see what's on this DVD.
It can't be porn, right? It's from Aoyagi after all.
When you watch it, it'd be best to wear headphones.
It's so good! Let's go again!
It wasn't some porn produced by a professional
company, it was a private DVD.
Thanks!
How many times did I fap last night?
No matter how many times I came, I was still hard.
No-Za-Ki-Kun?
Even right now.
Did you get turned on?
From then on, she...
It's so hot! It's hitting me hard!
It's really hard!
It's rubbing me so much!
It feels so good!
Cum! Cum all over me!
Every now and then, she'd bring me a new DVD.
Here's a new one!
For 3000 yen!
It's fine. Put it in.
The guy in the video kept fucking her brains out.
His dick was definitely a level S.
But I began to feel as if the pure smell
of soap that came from her...
Had become tainted all of a sudden.
N-No!
I'm gonna cum!
Cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Nozaki-kun!
Are you watching?
Could you meet me at 9pm on the 18th?
And... come to...
The 18th? That's today.
This is my first time inside a love hotel,
Is it cool for me to just walk in?
It's getting hard to breathe.
Today... me and Aoyagi will...
You don't have to ring the doorbell.
We might have sex!
My legs are cramping up.
Wha-
0...Oh...Okihiko!
What a disgusting face.
Oh... Nozaki-kun.
You're here.
Here you go.
Okihiko-kun, put it inside me!
So good...
So basically...
I was their wallet.
This hotel room costs 3000 yen for 90 minutes.
Those DVDs were of Okihiko fucking her.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
But Aoyagi probably wanted a dedicated camera man.
I'm cumming!!
And that's why she called me over.
As I held the camera like an idiot, I thought,
"Who will be their next wallet?"
I'm cumming again!
She'll probably choose another person from level C.