Samijima Suyoshi.
This guy tricked me and...
I heard that your sentence has been prolonged by one year.
What a shame!
Don't worry, the President is fine.
At least for the moment.
What!?
The Kensaki's group will expand very soon.
You bastard!
What are you thinking about?!
You live in cage.
You shouldn't worry about what's going on outside.
Wait!
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 10: Compassion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
How are your wounds?
Because we had to make once, you think you're my wife?
If that man waiting at outside discovers him, he will cry for sure.
Don't get closer to me.
Sorry.
For the moment...
He is right on this subject.
I let myself carried away by his kindness,
and I started to forget Yakuma-san.
Poor of you.
How did you feel?
I also know the feeling of losing everything.
Huh?
I can't believe that I find it beautiful,
even in a moment like this.
You have only me.
You held back when you hit him.
What?
Higa-san has told it me.
Besides, you see me with a little pity, too.
Could it be in truth you...
Shut up!
It was you who stole me everything!
I stole you everything?
No misunderstanding!
And you always look elsewhere!
Apologize!
Apologize, and swear you never look back to me.
Swear it!
Come on, let's finish it quickly.
His voice is weakening.
He feels pleasure in me.
I'm hopeless.
I betrayed Yakuma-san and Higa-san.
I let myself to carry away by Myoujin Aki!
Stop giving me orders!
I come!
I discovered that you went to see Higa.
Yes.
What has he done to prolonge his sentence by one year?
You seem to consider him your son.
He's a good guy.
I always wanted him to take care of everything with you when he will come out.
No. I'll take care of the rest.
Higa, take it fast!
Your wounds are fine?
Don't get closer to me!
It seems like nothing has changed despite my warnings.
I will give you a warning, no, an advice.
If you approach 3077, I'll send it to the special section.
Don't forget that every act have consequences.
I'll send it to the medical section!
Well.
In these circumstances,
Samejima Gakumisho will resume business now.
It can be sudden...
Are you sure you want to stop there?!
Samejima is going to put all in the air.
I'm sure the president would not have wanted that.
Keep calm, Igarashi.
Time changed.
We can't oppose the head.
What is happening?
I don't accept it!
Igarashi!
Let him alone!
He can't do anything alone.
Yes, he died as if nothing had happened.
And now, as promised...
Yes, we'll see you later.
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!