Miojin Aki.
3077, you have a visitor.
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 02: A visit
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Hina!
Yakuma-san!
They didn't do anything wrong to you?
I'm fine.
That's good.
And you? I heard you had some problems.
It's gonna be a longtime before everything
gets better, but soon everything will be better.
I see. That's good.
I want to get out of here as soon as possible and prove my innocence.
I want to be free and find you.
Is there a problem?
That's not true! At a time like this?
Hina?
I-it's nothing!
Are you all right?
Is there a problem?
No, it's nothing.
Yakuma-san!
Don't look at me with such insistence!
Do you feel bad?
Or is it...?
It's nothing, don't worry.
For another man to do this to me in front of the person I love...
What is it, Hina?
I wanted to see you as soon as possible.
I was so happy that I cried.
What's the matter?
Visiting time is almost over.
You want a kiss?
But there's the window in the middle.
I don't want him to go any further!
Help me Yakuma-san!
Well, I'll see you later.
I love you.
No!
I told you, this is where you pay for the crimes you committed.
That's not possible.
You...
Come with me.
Come in.
These are this morning's.
She's the new little cutie!
Just like you,
this woman has no remorse for the crimes she committed.
Make sure you all hear yourselves, problem prisoners.
That's impossible! No!
You're gonna stay with us, we're gonna have some fun.
Yes, all three of them.
Since this morning you've been getting in our way!
Get the fuck out of here!
You helped me?
I have to stop the bleeding.
Can you take your jacket off?
A tattoo?
I think it's enough, but it's just first aid.
Good!
Thank you so much for helping me.
It's nothing.
I just got mad because they woke me while I was sleeping.
By the way, do you have any experience in this field?
My mother was always sick and I took care of her.
What did you do? What did you do? A woman here is unusual.
J'ai été arretée pour détournement de fond.
I didn't do anything, but no one will believe me.
Why do I tell him that?
I can't trust him!
It's dangerous enough to talk to someone here,
and when I think I'm gonna have to spend a year in this place...
Wake up!
He spent all night like that to protect me?
I'm sorry, I just fell asleep.
The guard's coming.
We're doing an external inspection today.
Well, get out!
He's on my side or...
3077.
Come here.
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!