Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 12: Myoujin Aki
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
What a turn of events.
My partners attacked the vehicle,
you know the rest.
Saotome Hina is with us.
What stupidity.
Why do you need Saotome Hina?
As always, you like questions.
So let me tell you something.
I found part of Akatsuki Yuzuru's private life in your room.
It was the company president who set Hina up.
He has something to do with you and you use it as an excuse for Hina.
Your behavior towards her is understandable.
After all, she is innocent.
And you know that.
That is why...
you protected her.
I'll come back later.
A prisoner transport vehicle was attacked.
It is said that they took the head of the prison hostage
and they both have a wanted notice.
A wanted notice?
I'll protect you even if it costs my life.
Thank you very much.
Higa-san, you got a call!
This is Samejima.
How daring.
Bastard!
I have a proposition for you.
You don't want to join me? You're very useful.
Stop making the idiot!
You set me up and killed the president who was like my father!
Are you planning revenge?
Yeah, I'll destroy everything!
What a shame.
Or rather, I'm looking forward to it.
Yamato-san!
We don't know what they're gonna do.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes.
What he just said scares me.
I mustn't disturb them.
There was a multi-million dollar embezzlement at Akatsuki.
The company's president was involved in some
shady business and received death threats.
Former employee Saotome Hina was charged and sentenced to one year in prison.
Myoujin Aki.
It is motionless and silent.
He's as beautiful as a doll.
If Higa-san is right,
you hate me for the wrong reasons.
3077.
Come here,
Even if I don't want to,
I can't stop myself.
Kneel before me.
Those beautiful cold eyes only see me.
Take your clothes off.
Spread the legs.
You like that, right?
Now, sit on me and put it in.
You want it, don't you?
That's irresistible!
I want to hear his excited voice more!
I want you to feel even more pleasure inside me!
You're still a captive,
and they're all your enemies now.
You'll never have a day off again.
I understand now,
I wasn't a prisoner in that prison.
I am Myoujin Aki's prisoner.
3077,
detach me.
Start from here!!
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!