What happened to her?!
What's your name?
Higayama Tou.
You protected your superior and were charged?
That's nonsense.
I'm gonna kill you!
It doesn't matter.
If you leave here, leave the yakuza and find a better way to live.
We'll accompany you in your reinsertion.
Do you understand?
Miojin-san,
I trusted you.
You always protected us as head of security.
Yet you've changed.
You're obsessed with this woman.
What do you intend to do with her?
A prisoner must not question the supervisor.
Don't forget your place...
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 06: Angels
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
A black angel?
I never thought you'd try to escape.
Miojin Aki!
3077,
I have four important messages for you.
Yes.
First, your only job will be doing the laundry.
Second, you have to be here at 05:00 PM.
Yes.
Third, you're not allowed to take a shower anymore.
It's impossible!
Your attempt to escape is unforgivable.
You didn't have accomplices, did you?
No, of course not! I acted alone!
What to think...?
And fourth...
Your sentence is extended by one year.
This is cruel!
Do you hate me?
I didn't...
Are you complaining again?!
Because of you...
You are my...
What is it?
Stop it, please!
You're still wet.
You're really just a slut.
Stop it, please!
You don't have enough with my fingers, do you?
He takes me so deeply!
No! Stop it!
You hold it really tight.
Besides, the move you're making towards me is just indecent.
No! You are wrong!
I don't think so.
Inside a prison...
I can't believe I'm doing this!
Besides,
I can't be carried away by the nightmare this demon wants to take me into!
Even so, I can't take it anymore!
I-I cum!
You'd better behave yourself.
I've been working at the laundromat ever since.
Nobody... Nobody would help me?!
Higa-san!
I've been looking for you a long time, looking at the surveillance cameras.
What happened?
When I saw Higa-san,
I feel reassured!
Did something happen?
I'll tell him everything.
I... I...
I told him everything. That my sentence will last
a year longer, and what Miojin Aki did to me.
Going through ail this...
must have been atrocious!
It's a little raw, but comforting at the same time.
However, there's nothing I can do here.
I know.
All I need's for you to listen to me.
I wanna protect her.
Is it because she's one of us?
No,
I...
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la.
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!