Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 09: Scar
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Do you know Akatsuki Yuzuru?
He's the president of the company where I work.
You know he's missing?
Huh?
There was a report in Myoujin's office.
If you didn't know, it means he's keeping the information a secret.
This man and the president are...?
They seem to have a link.
Anyway, I didn't get any more information.
I'm sorry I can't tell you more.
Don't worry about it...
There must be something about her disappearance.
Next time I'll get go...
Higa-san!
I'm fine!
Then please don't do that kind of thing again.
Why were you in the Mafia?
You don't have to answer.
It was an old man who picked me up.
He was the head of the Kansaki branch, Kensaki Mamoru.
He's always been an old man of vengeance.
At least that was what many thought.
I supported him as his right-hand man.
Ce qui a dû vexer pas mal de monde.
So...
I was caught during an illegal weapons transaction.
Basically, like you, I was set up too.
That's not funny!
I could count on the old man outside,
but here I can't access any information.
This time we were able to stabilize her, but...
Thank you very much.
I still don't know when the bomb will go off.
I have to live with that.
Even though I know it's my punishment,
I still don't see the end of the tunnel...
This man hasn't shown for three days.
Where did he go?
Myoujin Aki!
He looks a little different.
It's like he's kissing his girlfriend.
It's like his eyes need comfort.
What's that?
Higa-san did it.
While I was looking away,
you let another man lay his hands on you!
Come on!
Take your clothes off, completely!
That's scary. I can't say no to that.
A beautiful white and delicate skin.
But these scars spoil the beauty of this body.
What is your relationship with President Akatsuki?
Don't say that name!
I'll punish the prisoner who turned her gaze away from the law!
Even if you beg me again, I will punish you until dawn...
No!
Lèche-le.
I'm telling you to suck me.
It's impossible!
3077!
I told you my orders are absolute!
He's on the move.
Myoujin Aki moves inside me.
It's hot.
Higa-san, I may be a bitch.
I show a different face in an instant.
It feels good to have sex with that man.
No! I come!
I...
Higa, you have a visitor!
You are...
Do you love your life as a prisoner,
Higa-kun?
I couldn't wait to see you.
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la.
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!