Over here! Quickly!
They're loading a truck?
A woman can't do this kind of work!
Higa!
Get back to work!
Yes, yes.
What's the matter?
This is our only chance to fuck that woman.
No!
Hey!
Calm down, you poor beasts.
It was predictable you'd be their target.
Be still!
Did he save me?
Can you hear me?
As a precaution, I'm sending 3077 to the laundry room.
Received!
3077, go back to the laundry room as a precaution.
This guy again...
Holy shit!
Wait, Higa! Stop it!
Higa's gone!
Like I thought, it would be better if you went alone.
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 07: Humiliation
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Higa-san?
I love you.
I want to protect you.
I'm glad to know how you feel,
but I have a boyfriend waiting outside.
I'm the one who fell in love, don't worry.
My heart hurts because I can not answer his feeling.
Shit!
Higa-san!
If we were in the district,
I wouldn't let that bastard do what he wants to you.
A romantic encounter between two prisoners?
If so, I will give them the appropriate punishment.
Come with me.
I'll humiliate you...
All two.
Stop it!
Please.
Impossible, he intends to do it in front of Higa-san?
This woman is completely submissive to me.
No, don't look!
Look carefully at this woman's true face.
She always makes an obscene face.
Don't look! Even if I don't want it, I feel pleasure!
And then it starts to tighten.
Stop it!
Don't look!
Sorry Higa-san.
I will... I will...
Higa-san, sorry.
No!
She seems to have had more fun than usual.
She really is a bitch.
She might be excited because you were watching her.
What are these eyes?
Are you gonna cry? You don't have any power!
You're nothing but a crazy human without that uniform!
You can say whatever you want. I'm done with this punishment.
This behaviour cannot be tolerated.
Bastard!
He was someone he trusted until she came along.
There must be something I can do for her.
What's the matter, Higa-san?
My stomach hurts. Take me to the infirmary, please.
There's no choice.
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!