Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 11: Reversal
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
It's okay. I'm here.
I'm glad you're here.
You go to the hospital and that's why we split up.
I'm sure you'll feel lonely without me.
Accept this farewell gift, in thanks on my behalf.
A farewell gift?
It's not possible!
Does he do it on purpose?
I mustn't moan!
Because of the blindfold, I'm more sensitive!
Holding back is not good for the body.
I feel good! I will moan!
But Higa-san is sitting next to me!
He might even notice it!
Myoujin Aki feels a lot of pleasure, I can feel it!
Hey, bastard! What are you doing?
Higa-san!
Stop it!
I'm just giving my farewell gift.
It's so pleasant...
Stop it, perverted bastard!
I cum! I cum!
We won't see each other for a long time,
even though I took all my time.
You make me sick!
I'll kill you when I get out of here!
You want to use your specialty on me?!
Wait till I rip your head off!
Shit! What's happened?
Yamato-san!
Igarashi!
Are you all right?
I'm freeing you right now.
We found out he was gonna transfer you,
so we hit it with a car.
It was a little hard.
Sorry.
No, it's ok.
More, the president was killed by Samejima.
You're the only one I trust!
Samejima!
I'll give you the details later.
What do we do with them?
He tried to protect her?
There's something I want to ask you.
Are you all right?
Ouch!
I'm going to escape.
What are going to do, Hina?
"Hina..." He said "Hina".
Your name is Hina, right?
If you stay, you'll go back to your old life.
I can protect you.
But if you come with me,
you will find your freedom.
However, this is the second time you've escaped,
so if you get caught, you're in a lot of trouble.
It's a beautiful and quiet place.
I remembered because you called me Hina.
I'm not 3077.
I'm Hina Saotome.
I don't want to be 3077 again!
I choose to be free as Saotome Hina!
Take me with you!
OK!
Let's go!
Yes!
Welcome back. Where are you going?
I can go anywhere, right?
Don't you care if your mother worries?
You are...
I am Akatsuki Yuzuru. Nice to meet you.
It's delicious!
Of course!
It's a surprise, isn't it?
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!