The sentence for the citizen Hina Saotome
for the acts which are reproached to her
is one year's imprisonment.
Please wait!
– I really didn't do it!
– Hina!
– Stop right there!
I believe in your innocence!
Yakuma-san...
Well, go ahead.
Hina!
Hina Saotome was arrested for embezzling millions of
dollars while she was treasurer of a multinational...
They accused me of stealing the company's money.
She's coming out.
I was convicted of a crime I didn't commit.
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 01: Black wings
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Down on your knees!
I-I'm scared.
Say hello!
What a beautiful face!
3077.
That's what you'll be called here!
3077, answer!
Yes!
I'm Myoujin Gakita, the chief security guard here.
Starting at 02:00 PM today, you will be my responsibility.
You must absolutely obey what I say until you find your freedom, do you understand?
Answer!
Yes.
I suppose you know, but since 2020, it's become a maximum security prison.
By the way, you're the only woman among all the prisoners here.
I'll start with the routine admission. Take her away.
Yes.
Where are they taking me?
Take off your clothes.
I don't want to do it!
A body search is mandatory.
Dépêche-toi.
I thought I told you my orders were absolute.
Why is he doing this?
Take it all off.
It's embarrassing!
Greatly it's over!
All right, is that enough?
Hold on. Lie down here, your legs in my direction.
It's very soft, like a feather. Does he do it several times?
No! Stop it! No!
3077.
What's the matter with you? It's a simple body search.
Why do you react like that?
S-Stop it!
You're in prison, the place where you're gonna pay for the crime you committed.
Why do you have these reactions?
I don't want you to get me wrong.
His fingers go very deep.
No! Stop it!
Are you serious? I want to fuck her!
Hey, get out of here! You have no right to stay here!
If we are "good boys", will this woman give us a reward?
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you, you can't stay here!
No! Don't do this to me!
Where am I?
Listen to me!
You have 10 minutes to clean your room! After that, assemble in the hallway!
List yourself!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Yesterday it was a dream?
By the way, you're the only woman among all the prisoners here.
Thirty-eight.
Thirty-nine.
They're all looking at me! Except him.
Your arm touched me.
Huh! You're the one who ran into me!
– Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! If you keep this up, they'll punish us all!
– They started fighting!
You want to fight?!
I-In your cells!
What an impressive man!
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!