There's got to be a trace on that woman's detention.
It is...
What are you doing here?
Just stay still.
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 08: Bad Person
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Hey, hey, that's bad taste.
Are you gonna do SM with me?
You were looking for something about 3077?
What are you talking about?
Did that woman do something to you?
Isn't it?
I was bored in my cell, so I went for a walk.
Shut the fuck up.
I'll punish you with
a series of lashes!
Hold on!
If you touch that woman again...
At this point, there's no point. Stop it.
And then...
Don't ever make me do this again.
3077, wake up!
With your permission!
This man broke the rules and I whipped him as punishment.
More, his sentence was extended by one year.
3077, it's your fault.
Why?
Understood.
I'm coming immediately.
It's you?
He had to go hard for you to find yourself in such a state...
No.
For a yakuza, his tattoo is like his life.
He held back to let me keep that pride.
Why did he do that?
I was bored and I went for a walk.
That's a lie!
He said it was my fault!
Tell me the truth, please!
I went in his office.
Idiot!
Didn't I tell you not to do anything?!
You were hurt
and your sentence was extended by a year.
That's fine with me.
I can be with you.
Wh-what are you talking about?
No, Higa-san!
I'm already with someone!
Even if I say no, I let myself go...
If you get hit, it hurts.
In your case, it's the same, it's just a reaction of your body.
But my feelings for you are real.
No! I have someone I love!
I am a criminal.
This doesn't concern me.
You thought I was just a good man?
This face...
I don't want other men go see him.
I want to make you mine.
You're very wet.
Is it nice?
No!
Higa-san!
Doesn't it hurt?
Now I only see him!
Higa-san!
I had forgotten that feeling.
Throughout the day, his condition worsened.
You only have to die.
If she dies,
I'll be alone.
Even though I couldn't do anything.
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!