Come on! Start the exercises!
– One, two, three, four, five...
– One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
From now on, you're gonna wear it for morning exercises.
– What he put on me vibrates...
– One, two, three, four, five, six...
Move it!
What's going on, 3077?!
You're too slow!
I have to do this so they don't find out.
I can't take it anymore!
I will... I will...
Looks like she got a little hot on the way out after so long.
Is your wound okay?
Go get yourself treated.
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeamrek.la
Episode 03: Punishment
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Wake up.
I told you you should do the exercises properly.
Why didn't you do it?
That's because you put that thing in me...!
It's still vibrating!
I'll keep disciplining you until there's nothing left of you.
The sin you committed will never be atoned for.
It's punishment for breaking my orders.
This will be the second time I've done it today.
What are you going to do?
Why are you doing this?
What does he want from me?
Don't look over here, please!
It's only a matter of time before they realize.
No! Don't look!
No! No! No!
He saw me when I had an orgasm.
It's a magic mirror.
Go to work.
It is forbidden to rest.
I was given the job of secretary.
I really envy you for having to do such a simple job.
Don't stop,
they're looking at us.
Keep your voice down.
Are you really innocent?
I'll prove my innocence in a year.
I'm Soutome Hina.
Higayama Tou.
I got caught at a mob auction, I got a year to go.
The mob?
Is his tattoo the symbol they use?
I came here for a reason,
unlike you.
Hurry up!
I'm coming.
Count yourself in!
This man is not here today.
That's good.
But because of him, my body and my heart will be destroyed if things continue this way.
The sin you committed will never be atoned for
The sin you committed will never be atoned for...
Mom, I brought you the flowers you love.
They're beautiful, aren't they?
I'll be back.
I'm glad you're still coming to visit me.
Yakuma-san?
This is really weird! I can't stand it!
Huh?
When you've done nothing, you're here and the real culprit is at large.
Yakuma-san?
Hina, you said you'd prove your innocence when you got out of here, right?
Yes, of course I do!
You don't have to wait a year!
You must escape!
I'm gonna help you!
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!