Escape!
Let's get out of here and live together in peace somewhere!
But I can't prove my innocence.
You can try it when everything calms down!
The one who always supported me when I lost my parents in an accident was...
Trust me.
I'm going to try.
I have a plan in place.
You'll get the details by letter.
Don't you worry.
We'll use the shower for your escape.
I already got the itinerary.
But the showers are on the second floor and cannot be used.
So I need you to do something first.
Don't worry. You're gonna be fine, that's for sure!
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 04: A Plan.Nsoftsub: торрент иваниваныч
3077.
I have a message for you.
Your request has been accepted.
Tomorrow, you'll know the rest.
Yes.
In addition, you can wash in the showers every day.
That will be all. Do the best you can.
Thank you very much.
It's all happening like Yakuma-san said!
That day, every two weeks, this man is not here...
He won't be there.
I have to act so he doesn't suspect anything.
3077, it's time. You have to hurry.
Why are you wasting your time?
It's just...
No! No! I'll accentuate his doubts!
Hello, head of security Miojin Aki.
Hello.
Looks like you passed the cooking test,
congratulations.
My dream is to have my own business.
Then let me help you with the publicity.
Thank you very much.
I have to get going.
The other prisoners trust him.
Start eating!
You have 15 minutes to finish!
Higa-san...
Dé-li-cious.
I'm glad,
even though I didn't do much.
Is that weird?
End of meal!
Start cleaning up!
3077.
Come with me.
Could it be that he noticed?
Hurry up!
Y-Yes!
3077.
It would seem that working in the kitchen is difficult for you...
Y-yes!
Great. This has nothing to do with the plan.
So I'm giving you a punishment.
Masturbate in front of me.
Huh?
I thought I told you my orders are absolute.
I can't refuse or he'll be watching me even more.
All right.
You still have that obscene expression.
I make that face?
You wanted it?
No, of course not!
What?! That's impossible! He's coming in!
What a pity, it's only a toy.
No!
Open your eyes.
You do it yourself.
It's nice, isn't it?
No! I'm about to come! I can't take it anymore!
It's your true nature.
You can cum.
You are...
crazy.
Whose fault do you think it is?
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!