I'm finally gonna escape!
Raw: MuchoHentai.com
Sub: KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Episode 05: Escape
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
I'm sorry to say the odds for your mother are slim.
Even if that's the case,
I entrust it to you.
I know that. I know that. That's obvious.
However, this foolish anger keeps growing in me
3077, it's shower time.
Yes.
Even when they wash, prisoners are usually watched.
However, since you're a girl, I don't think they'll go with you.
You have 15 minutes to wash up.
After that, you will go do the work that has been assigned to you.
Yes.
It's dark in here.
Everything will be done by touch. When you're in the vent, go left then right,
right again and finally left. You should see the exit after 10 minutes.
Once you're out and down, run!
I've put a rope for you.
I'll wait for you, Hina.
Ouch!
I have to go on!
Besides, I don't have time to waste!
You're home early. Something worrying you?
No! Anything new?
I've checked the monitors.
There's an anomaly here.
That's true, even if it's very weak.
It's from the showers.
Keep an eye out.
Yes!
The only prisoner who can use the shower at this time is...
Get out of the way!
Yes.
She's got guts.
This is the last crossroads.
I need to go left...
But, if I'm ever wrong...
Great!
I'll be able to see Yakuma-san very soon!
Impossible!
Miojin Aki!
I'm almost out!
You thought you could get out of here?
You thought you could escape me?
NO!
Hina...
No!
I'm gonna punish you for trying to escape.
Stop it!
I'm much more sensitive than usual.
How is that possible in this situation?
He's gonna make me come with his fingers again!
It's not his fingers!
That's not true! It's very deep!
Besides, being in such an obscene position before his eyes.
He's inside me!
You always wanted it, didn't you, slut?
What am I doing?
I should be with Yakuma-san, but I'm here
making love to each other.
It takes me by force and yet this face...
You love him that much?
I-It's wrong!
Stop it, please!
What do you thing?
If I told you I wanted you to hold me a lot tighter on the inside.
That's not true!
That's your punishment.
What a sad face.
Go, cum.
I will... I will...
His face is so sad...
It's like I could see inside him,
for a moment.
Bring the towels? Someone else could...
KawaiiNekoTeam.ek.la
Merci à MuchoHentai pour la Raw!