From that point on, I always went to
Yuu's place just to meet Yui-san.
Why are we doing this in the toilet again?
The thought of Yuu likely to come back home at any moment
makes this more arousing and exciting, right?
Ryouichi-kun.
Where you’re touching is really great.
It feels great at this spot, right?
No...
What should I do?
You know my weak spot perfectly now.
Someone will notice if you moan out that loud.
If you keep sucking that intensely, I'll...
Oh no, I can't stop anymore.
His cock just tastes too good.
Yui-san, you're also playing with yourself at the same time?
That's right.
I'm masturbating while giving you a blowjob.
My pussy is already feeling this horny.
It's coming out.
I'm sorry for this mess.
Hey, Ryouichi-kun, I can't hold it anymore.
Please, put it in.
Use it to completely stir my indecent body up.
Yui-san...!
This is...
This is what I've wanted.
More, thrust it in me more.
Your pussy is twitching really wildly.
Yes, that because I'm cumming right now.
I'm cumming now.
My pussy is going crazy.
Oh yes...
Your dick is hitting me very deep inside.
I'm about to...!
It's okay, cum inside.
Make me cum with your own cum!
It feels good.
This is the first time I've felt like this.
Does that mean it feels better than your husband's?
S-stupid!
Let's not talk about him here!
Don't!
If you fondle my breasts too like that, I will...
Yui-san, your nipples are already this hard.
Your dick is also twitching inside me.
You're about to cum already, right?
Yes.
Me too.
I'm about to cum too.
I'm going to cum!
No, I'm cumming...
It's coming out!
Are you, peeing?
No, stop...
It just keeps flowing out.
I hate this...
But, it's okay I guess.
We're in the toilet anyway.
What should I do?
Whenever I have sex with Ryouichi-kun,
I feel like I'm slowly becoming a pervert.
Yuu, I'll be using your toilet.
Oh, okay.
At that time, I never thought that would happen.
Hey, can you close the door already?
I-I'm sorry!
Amane!
~I never thought it would happen at my friend's place!~
Man, why are you going around the house dressed like that?
It's my first day off in ages.
I'm going to really let myself loose.
This woman is Yui-san.
She's Yuu's aunt.
I heard that the company she's working for is just nearby.
She usually stops sleeps over here when it gets really late.
And I just saw her pee earlier.
But you can't even be that loose with your husband.
That's none of your business.
Oh, so you're married?
I met him at the same workplace.
I won't get suddenly yelled at here though.
And it feels different to be around a virgin bum like Yuu.
I'm not alone here!
Ryouichi has around the same grades as I do,
and he's a virgin too!
Shut up!
Oh, even though you're this cute.
Ryouichi-kun, switch with me for a bit.
Eh? No way...
Ryouichi, we're going straight to the next stage.
Don't just start on your own, that's unfair!
Wait, there's a bomb in there!
Too close!
Wait, with her wearing something this outrageous,
I just won't be able to concentrate!
There, at that spot!
Crap, my crotch is...!
Ryouichi-kun, I just came only this close and it's already like this.
Are you really a virgin?
Th-this is... Well...
You just saw me pee earlier, right?
How unfair.
I want to see your thing too.
Why don't you just look at your husband's thing?
We don't really see each other that much every day.
So he just can't show it to me.
How's your dick now, I wonder?
Wait, Yuu will notice us!
What's wrong? Come on now, Ryouichi!
Huh, he doesn't notice?
Now we're even.
W-wait!
My, it's still sheathed I see.
I'm going to take it off then.
Here now, if you don't play the game well
Yuu will notice.
Her boobs are hitting me!
Its color is nice, quite different from my husband's.
I'm going to do something even better.
Is she giving me a... handjob?
Your horny fluids are already coming out.
So you're getting really aroused now.
It feels too good, the sensation is totally
different from using my own hand.
Your dick is twitching, and it's getting hotter.
Is it coming out already?
Are you about to cum?
I can't hold it anymore.
I need a tissue!
With her mouth?!
Sh-she... She's sucking it...
Alright, I did it!
I completed it!
I really am great.
Oh, damn, I lost.
What did Yui-san just do?!
If Yuu ever noticed this...
What are we going to play next?
Oh yeah Yuu,
the game that you said you've always wanted.
It's currently available at a store near our place.
For real?
Even though it's not yet the official release date?
Could it be a preliminary sale?
Yui-san?
What should I do?
Should I buy it right now?
Hey, are you going?
Then I'm going too.
It's quite far.
Wouldn't it be faster for you to use your scooter?
Oh yeah, you might be right.
Okay, I'm going out for a bit.
Yuu!
Just play games with auntie and wait for me.
Oh? Did you really want to go with Yuu?
Aren't you more interested in our continuation than that?
As a virgin.
But you already have a hus-hus-hus-hus-hus-husb...
What husband?
The workaholic that doesn't want to have sex with me?
Instead, wouldn't you want to know more
about me, who likes cute boys?
Y-Yui-san?
Can you remove my bra?
This is just a different kind of game.
Just pinch and twist it.
Just pinch and twist it?
See? Stage 1 cleared.
Your boobs are...!
You don't just get to look at them.
Th-this is...!
Is this also the first time you've experienced this?
Of course...
Oh, wow.
Your dick feels hot, and it's gradually getting bigger.
It feels like I'm going to lose it too.
Your boobs feel smooth, and soft.
I feel happy that you're getting aroused with this.
Then, how about this?
Oh no...!
Your nipples!
I see.
My hardened nipples are now stroking your dick.
Please stop.
If you continue doing that, I'll...!
Just cum if you feel like cumming.
I'm going to take it on my face this time.
That just squirted out strongly.
My face and my breasts are now all sticky.
Now then, let's get to the next stage.
B-but...
We've already reached this far, are you
still worried about my husband?
It's his fault that I'm now like this.
It's the real deal pussy!
Can you tell?
It's now this wet after giving you a tit fuck earlier.
Yui-san?
That's right, I'm masturbating right now.
And you're currently watching me,
so I get aroused more than usual.
Oh no, I can't hold it anymore.
Here, look.
I'm putting my finger in, stirring myself inside.
Wow...
It's alright.
Just do whatever you want.
Or do you want to stop at this point?
Mr. husband, Yuu, I'm sorry!
I just don't have the will to stop at this point now!
You're sucking it really hard.
You've been enduring for a while now, haven’t you?
Not just my breasts,
but my pussy too, okay?
Okay.
I just peed earlier, so it may smell a bit.
I'm sorry if it does.
Not at all.
Well?
What do you think of the first pussy in front of you?
Yes.
Well, it feels great.
It seems like it's going to melt anytime.
That's just normal of course.
And now how does it feel like?
It's really wet and sloppy right now.
Your tongue is entering my pussy.
I'm sorry, Ryouichi-kun.
My sex fluids just keep on flowing.
I can't stop it anymore.
Okay, now we go to the final stage.
Say goodbye to your virginity.
Yui-san!
This isn't our place,
so you have to keep your voice down.
There, can you feel it?
It's entering inside.
It feels slippery inside!
Congratulations.
You may have lost to Yuu in the game,
but you sure won in the sex department.
Yuu...
Don't leave me behind, okay?
Are you feeling guilty?
Not at all.
That's good.
I've also taken your first kiss.
If you move like that, instead of feeling guilt,
Pleasure is building up...
Me too, I'm getting horny with it.
It's been a long time since I have tasted a dick.
It's totally squeezing me tight.
My pussy is twitching.
This is my first time of having sex after a long time.
So it feels very...
Great...!
Yui-san!
Ryouichi-kun, what do you think?
Does your dick feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to continue with this.
I'm going to show you all of my horny self.
Those movements... I'm going to cum again.
It's okay.
Cum lots inside me.
B-But...!
It's your first time, so just cum inside.
I want you to feel great.
Just cum whenever and however you want to.
Amazing!
That's a young student for you.
You came a lot already and you're still going strong.
I'm sorry, I came first.
Then, I'll have you do it this time.
Eh? Are we going to do it in this position?
Yep.
It'll be a waste if your cum drips down, right?
Yui-san, I'm...!
Your dick became stiff again.
It's okay, come.
Move your hips more.
Okay.
There, keep it up.
More...
Thrust it in until it reaches the very end of your dick.
Okay.
No need to hold back.
You can get a little rougher if you want to.
Make a mess of my pussy using your dick!
Yes!
He's thrusting it in with all his might.
How cute.
Yui-san, does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels really good.
We're doing it while your cum is still inside.
My pussy is becoming even more wet and sticky inside.
I want to see it.
I... want to see it more.
The part where we're connected.
It's completely exposed.
The part where your dick is entering me.
Yui-san, you're horny!
Oh no...
I'm going to lose it.
As you continue looking at it,
I feel hornier and hornier.
Look at it.
Look at my pussy more.
I'm being stirred up by your dick.
Look at my messed up pussy.
I'm... I'm about to cum!
Me too.
Your dick...
There, it's hitting all of my soft spots.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out again.
Cum...
Cum lots inside my pussy.
Please, Ryouichi-kun.
Let's...
It’s coming out!
It's pouring inside me!
It's coming out...
Wow, something is flowing out.
It's my orgasmic fluid.
It comes when it feels very good for me.
Y-Yui-san...
Well?
With whom did you enjoyed playing more, Me or Yuu?
Of course, that would be none other than...
Hey, Ryouichi!
Yuu?!
I already bought the game!
Let's play it immediately!
Yuu, why don't we play it at my place?
Huh, why?
They called me on the phone to come home now.
The room is messed up with Yui san's fluids.
It's okay.
I'm going to clean up the mess here.
Please do.
Ryouichi-kun.
Come visit me again, okay?
Visit? This isn't your house auntie!
Now, now, just forget about it.
Let's go.
What are you hurrying up for?
Let's just go.
Do you want to play it that badly?
No, of course not!