From then, I went to play at Yuu's place
many times in order to see Yui-san.
Why in the toilet again?
Because when you think of the fact that
you could be noticed any moment...
You can get excited just from that, right?
Ryouichi-kun... down there... you’re pressing too hard!
But Yui-san feels good from this place, don't you?
What should I do?
Now you've remembered all my weak spots...
If you make too much noise, someone will really notice!
If you're... that rough, I...
I can't... I can't stop anymore...
Ryouichi kun's penis tastes really good!
Yui-san... are you touching yourself?
That's right... I'm... masturbating
while giving a blowjob...
My pussy is dripping wet... getting so excited...
It's coming out!
I'm, I’m sorry, I... on your face...
Ryouichi-kun, I... can't endure anymore.
Please, put it in!
Stir up my slutty pussy with your penis!
Yu-Yui-san...
This... this is what I wanted!
More... thrust me more!
Yui-san’s... you’re twitching like crazy down here!
Yeah... I... I'm cumming...
I can't help but cum!
I think my pussy is going crazy!
Yes!
All the way... up to my womb...
your penis is hitting deep inside!
I'm... gonna...
It's fine, let it out inside!
Make me cum with Ryouichi-kun's semen!
It feels so good... yes...
I've never felt this good before...
Does that mean, even better than with your husband?
Geez! Don't mention my husband right now!
No... you can't... if you touch my boobs too, I...
Yui-san... look, you're nipples are this hard.
Ryouichi-kun's penis is getting harder,
too! You're about to cum, right?
Yes...
Me too...
I going to cum...
I'll cum!
No, it's coming out, it's coming out!
Is this... your pee?
No... don't...
I can't stop... no more...
But, it's fine right?
We are in the toilet.
What should I do?
When I have sex with Ryouichi'kun...
I'm becoming more and more perverted...
Yuu, I'm borrowing your bathroom for a sec, ‘kay?
Yeah.
At that time,
I never thought that it would turn out like that...
Hey, will you close the door now?
I'm, I'm sorry!
Amanee!
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
I didn't think this would happen at a friend's house!
Geez! What kind of outfit are you walking around in!?
It's been a while since I've been
on vacation, just let me relax.
This is Yui-san.
Yuu's aunt, and she comes to spend the night here
sometimes because her workplace is nearby.
Just now, I saw this person peeing...
You say that but you can't even be
this way around your husband!
Don't say unnecessary things like that!
Oh, so you are married?
Yeah, but we both work.
But I get to be myself without getting scolded here,
And I can meet people who are stupid virgins like Yuu!
Well too bad!
We have about the same grades,
and Ryouichi's a virgin, too!
Be quiet already!
Hmm? Even though you've got such a cute face?
Ryouichi-kun, switch with me for a sec.
Huh? What, wait, that's...
Ryouichi, we're on to the next stage!
Don't suddenly start it like that, no fair!
Watch out, there's a bomb there!
She's so close!
I mean, she dressed like this...
I can't concentrate!
Hey, there, there.
This is bad, my crotch...
Geez, Ryouichi-kun, getting like this
just from me coming a little closer.
Are you really a virgin?
This is... um...
You saw me when I was peeing just now, didn't you?
Wait...
No fair...
I want to see Ryouichi-kun down there, too.
Can't you just look at your husband's.
My husband and I work at different
times and pass by each other...
He wouldn't show me.
I wonder how your penis is doing...
Wait, Yuu will notice!
Haha! What's wrong?
Come at me, Ryouichi!
Huh? He's not noticing at all?
Let's make it even with this.
Wait!
Oh my, it’s still covered.
I'll pull it back for you.
C'mon, you have to look at the
screen and play the game,
or Yuu will notice!
Woah, her boobs are hitting me!
Unlike my husband's it's got a good colour and tone!
I’ll do better things for you!
Is this...
a handjob!?
Perverted juices are coming out already.
Ryouichi is excited, huh?
It’s completely different from my own hand!
It feels too good!
Your penis is twitching and getting hot.
Are you cumming?
Are you going to let out semen?
I can't take it...
I need tissue...
Her mouth?
She's sucking on it...
Woohoo! Victory is mine!
Like I thought I'm good at this!
Ah, dammit, this sucks...
What are you doing Yui-san!?
If Yuu were to notice this...
Alright, what do we do next?
Oh, by the way Yuu,
the game that you've been wanting
I found it at a place near where I live.
Huh? Really?
Even though it's not on the market yet?
I guess they decided to sell it early maybe?
Yui-san?
Hmm, what do I do... should I go buy it?
Huh, you're going? Then me, too...
It's kind of far,
so maybe it'll be faster if Yuu
goes alone on his scooter?
That's true, let's do that.
Then, I'm off!
Hey, Yuu!
Just play games with auntie while you're waiting!
Oh, did you want to go with Yuu instead?
Compared to that, isn't what we started
just now more interesting?
As a virgin.
But, Yui-san has a-a-a-a, a-a...
A what?
A husband who likes work and
wouldn't have sex with me?
Or a cute boy right in front of me?
Yu-Yui-san?
Will you take off my bra for me?
Huh?
This is just like a game.
Just pluck and twist it.
Just pluck... and twist...
See? Stage one cleared.
Your, your boobs!
You get to do more than just looking!
Eh?
Woah, that's...
Is this the first time you have something
like this done to you?
Of, of course!
Amazing...
Ryouichi-kun's penis is hot...
and getting larger...
I think I’m going a little crazy, too...
Yui-san's boobs are so slippery....
and soft...
I think I'm feeling really happy to
see Ryouichi-kun get excited...
Well then, how about this?
Woah, your nipples!?
That's right.
My hard, erect nipples are rubbing against your penis.
Don't... If you do it that much, I...
If you want to cum, do so any time!
This time, I'll take it with my face.
Amazing force!
My face and my boobs are all sticky...
Well, then let's move on to the next stage.
Um, but...
We've gone this far, and you're still
worrying about my husband?
Even though it's my husband fault that I'm like this...
It's a real-life pussy!
Can you tell?
It's gotten this wet from giving
a titty fuck to Ryouichi-kun.
Y-Yui-san?
That's right, I'm masturbating.
I can feel it so much more than usual
because I'm being watched!
No, I can't take it anymore!
Hey look, I'm sticking my fingers inside
my pussy and stirring myself lots!
Amazing...
It's fine, do what Ryouichi-kun wants.
Or should we stop here?
Mr. Husband, Yuu, I'm sorry!
I don't have enough willpower to stop here anymore!
Sticking on like that...
you must have been holding back really hard, right?
Not only my boobs, but my pussy, too, okay?
Yes.
I just peed so...
it might smell a bit...
I'm sorry...
Not at all!
How is it? Any thoughts on your
first time seeing a pussy?
Yes, um, what should I say, unlike on
the internet, it's very real and...
Of course it's real.
What is my pussy like right now?
It's, very, very soaked!
Your tongue is... going into my pussy!
I'm sorry, Ryouichi-kun, erotic juices are overflowing,
I just can't stop any more...
Well then, it's finally the last stage.
Your graduation from virginity!
Yui-san!
This is a dangerous area,
so don’t let out too much noise!
Hey, can you tell? Your penis is going in!
It's so soft and slippery!
Congratulations!
You lost to Yuu in the game,
but now you’ve won in sexual experience.
Yuu...
Don't do it secretly leaving me out!
Could it be you're feeling guilty?
Not at all.
Oh, that's great to hear.
I took your first kiss, too.
If you move... more than guilt I'll feel...
pleasure!
I'm feeling it, too!
It's been a while since I've had
a man's... hard... penis...
Amazing... it's squeezing!
My pussy...
is twitching a lot...
From sex... after such a long time...
It's really...
good!
Yu, Yui-san!
Ryouichi-kun... how is it?
Does your penis feel good?
Ah... Yes!
I'll do...
lots and lots more for you.
I'll show you all my slutty sides!
If your hips move like that...
I'll... I'll cum again!
Cum inside me!
But...
It's your first time, just go ahead
and creampie my pussy!
I want you to feel good!
It's fine, cum as much as your want!
Amazing...
as expected from a student...
You've came several times and there's still so much.
I'm, I’m sorry I came first and...
Then shall I get Ryouichi-kun to do it this time?
Wait, are we going to do it just like this?
That's right.
Wouldn't it be a waste if the semen were to flow out?
Yui-san...
I...
Your penis is getting hard again.
It's fine, come!
that's right, shake your hips like that.
Yes!
Just like... that!
Thrust... in and out more...
all the way to the bottom!
Yes!
Don't hold back,
you can go a bit crazy if you want.
Mess my pussy up...
with Ryouichi-kun's hard thing!
Yes!
He's moving his hips with all his might...
so cute!
Yui-san, do you... feel good?
I do... it's really good!
I'm being stirred up with semen inside...
It's incredibly drenched inside!
I... want to see more!
Huh?
I... want to see more of...
Where I'm connected with Yui-san!
I'm being completely exposed...
I can see Ryouichi-kun's going in to my pussy!
It's really erotic, Yui-san!
I think I'm going to go crazy!
When I'm being watched, I get more and more slutty!
Look!
Look at my pussy more!
Look more at my soaked pussy
being stirred up by a penis!
I'm... I’m going to cum!
Me too...
I... your penis is...
hitting all the good spots...
Cumming... cumming...
Cumming!
Cumming... again!
Come! Let out lots... inside!
Please, Ryouichi-kun, together...
Together!
It's coming out!
It’s coming... out!
Amazing... something came out...
It's called squirting...
It happens when it feels really good.
Yu-Yui-san...
How was it?
Comparing me and Yuu, who is more fun to play with?
Well of course it's...
Hey, Ryouichi!
Yuu!?
I bought that game we were talking about.
Let's play right away!
Y-Yuu, can we play it at my house instead?
Huh, why?
Um, my parents called to tell me
to hurry up and go back...
The room is all wet and sticky from Yui-san's gush...
It's fine, I'll do the cleaning up.
Thank you very much.
Ryouichi-kun.
You're welcome to come over to play again.
"﻿You're welcome"? This isn't auntie's house!
C'mon, c'mon, let's go!
What are you in a hurry about?
Just go!
Do you want to do it that much!?
I didn't “do it"!