Oh no...
This, kind of kiss, is like...
It's like we're lovers or something.
Don't get it wrong.
It just feels a little good for me.
Just a little.
Hey! Stop that, you idiot.
Don't stretch it like that.
It's dirty.
You say that, but it looks like you're just fine.
Both holes are already trying to hold onto me tightly.
Hey, wait.
Don't kiss me like this.
Not my nipples.
What? You've been complaining all day.
But...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming!
This is really the worst.
If some idiot like you pours cum into me,
I might just become an idiot too.
It's fine, you're the one squeezing me
tightly whenever you cum anyway.
That's just your imagination!
Idiot, idiot!
You dunce!
Even if you're not honest
Some hours ago...
Jeez, you never learn, do you, Kawakami.
You...
You didn't have to punch me that hard, you know.
Well, there they go again.
Kawakami could have just quit it,
he always loses, anyway.
Always into some stupid mischief.
You really haven't changed one bit.
Don't underestimate me, Asahina.
I'm not the same man as I was yesterday.
What's with those rubber gloves?
This is something I found during our
co-ed cleaning activity yesterday.
A final weapon handed through generations.
Behold, the long forsaken milk-soaked cleaning cloth!
Looks like it's the end of the line for you, Asahina Megumi.
J-Just wait.
That's really not okay anymore.
No buts!
Take this!
You students are noisy.
Go to your seats already.
Sensei?
Are you alright, sir?
You kids...
Man, doing general cleaning for two straight hours sure sucks.
That serves you right.
You even pulled me into this, how bothersome.
Besides, why are you always so rude to me.
Well, it's because you're where 'Asahina' is, I guess?
So I'm some jinx now?
W-Wait, I guess it's that.
Like when an elementary schoolboy likes a girl,
he tries very hard to make her notice him by teasing her.
In that case, you should have just told me already.
I'm going to dump you straight away, though.
Huh?
What are you saying? That's not it at all.
I don't see you as a woman, not for a second.
Especially with that attitude of yours, yeah, that attitude.
Maybe you're the one who's actually entertaining that idea.
Wh-What? I'm not...!
Idiot!
Thank you, Kawakami.
You saved me.
Kawakami, are you alright?
Because of me, now you're the one hurt.
Your knees.
When you fell down, your knees...
Hit my crotch...
Farewell~
I'm... done for.
Kawakami!
Don't leave me just yet!
What's that sound?
Wait, it feels very good...
Wh-What are you doing, Asahina?
Wh-Why are you sucking my dick?!
It's not what you think!
Th-This is a massage!
I just can't leave it like that, so...
It's my fault after all...
Ow, ow, it's going to break!
I was just rubbing it at first, then it gradually got bigger.
It looks like it's more in pain now, so...
I don't mind continuing, if you want to...
I actually don't want to, though.
I don't really mind you doing it, just do it if you want to.
Cum quickly, okay?
A-Asahina.
Oh crap, I'm about to cum.
Asahina!
Hey, it's not getting smaller at all!
It's gotten even stiffer!
How much are you lusting for me, anyway?
Th-That's not it!
I already drank all that sticky stuff earlier.
You're really troublesome.
It can't be helped then.
I used my mouth, so I'll let you use this one.
It's okay if you don't want it, though.
Asahina...
I-If you insist, then I'll put it in for you.
It's in!
Your thing is really inside me!
Y-Your pussy is amazing.
Oh no...
It feels too good.
It's so wet,
and it's sucking my dick inside.
That's...
Oh yes, Asahina, Asahina!
My pussy...
My pussy feels good!
Asahina!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
A-Asahina, I...
I'm still...
This is amazing...
It's going deep inside.
Any more and I'll...
Your dick, your dick is great!
My nipples...
Don't play with my nipples too much.
I'm cumming, Asahina.
I'm cumming inside again.
Okay, just cum.
Just pour all of your cum into my ovulating pussy.
Okay, if you get pregnant,
I'll take responsibility for it!
Alright, I'll let you take responsibility.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
My pussy is cumming!
I'm cumming while getting pregnant with your baby!
What? Do you have a problem?
Yeah, I sure do!
A crude woman like you should...
Those two are at it again.
They really fight quite often.
But, they could actually be quite close, you know.
Damn...
I'm definitely going to make you cry.
You better prepare yourself!
Okay, challenge accepted.
I'm really looking forward to 'it'.
No, oh no, oh no...
Any more and I'll...
If you stir my pussy more...
No, my clit feels tingly...
Not there...
Not my clitoris!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming while it's being played with!
It's coming out...
No more...
No, please no...
I'm broken now.
I'm completely broken now.
I'm sorry, Takkun.
I can't be your mother anymore...
Stepmother
Hey, Takkun.
You'll be late if you don't wake up soon.
No, It'll be fine.
How about you, Mom?
Aren't you attending the emergency company meeting today?
Oh, you're right!
Oh crap, I'm going to be late!
Now, take care not to get into an accident, okay?
You too, Mom.
I'm heading off, Mom.
Mom, eh?
I wonder when was I finally able to call her that.
Hey, Oichima.
What, Fukumoto?
I heard from a middle school buddy of yours yesterday.
Is it true that your stepmother
was your middle school advisor?
Y-Yeah.
Whoa, it's really true!
You'd normally hate it,
but if she's still that young and gorgeous,
it's still possible, right?
Man, I'm really jealous!
What are you saying?
Being young and gorgeous doesn't have anything to do with it!
But, your old man soon went on a business
trip after remarrying, right?
It sure is difficult for you.
Yeah, It'll probably be New Year's before he comes home.
Don't you get all fidgety being alone with her every day?
No!
Oh, but I think you should be careful.
Of what?
If the husband is away for more than a year,
there's a good possibility that she is already cheating.
I read that in a book somewhere.
Sorry, I'm just kidding!
It's just a joke!
How foolish.
I don't think that's possible with her.
She's... my Mom after all.
Oh, you'll be coming home late?
Yeah, okay.
It's alright, I'll take care of it.
Don't drink too much, okay?
Drinking with the other teachers again, huh?
It feels like she's kept her distance these past days.
Mom...
It's the smell of Mom's pee.
Kyouko... Kyouko-sensei!
Se-Sensei!
Kyouko...
What in the world am I doing?
I know it'll be bad if she finds out about this.
Anyway, Mom sure is late.
I'm home.
W-Welcome home, Mom.
Oh, Takkun, are you still awake?
You're quite late.
Did I worry you? Sorry about that.
I even got dragged to a karaoke.
I'm tired.
I'll take a shower and then sleep.
She smells different than the soap we usually use.
Be careful.
That can't be...
I'm just overthinking things.
Let's just sleep.
Jeez, that Fukumoto.
He should have contacted me earlier if he'd changed plans.
I've wasted my train fee for nothing.
Or so I thought.
I was able to buy Mom's favorite rollcake because of it.
Mom sure is going to be happy.
A man's shoes?
Do we have a guest?
Wait, no.
This voice...
Is it coming from Mom's room?
Maybe Dad came home.
No, Dad would never come home without letting us know...
Besides, those shoes...
No way, this can't be.
Oh, it's intense.
What is this?There's a dick inside Mom!
She's having sex!
Her partner...
Isn't Dad!
No way...
Then, then...
This isn't real.
Mom is... Mom is having an affair!
Seems your pussy's gripping me very tightly today.
Does it feel that good having sex with
somebody else on this marital bed?
No, that's not true.
Your insides are very wet already.
It's too late to act innocent now.
Just who is it that invited a man to the house
while your son and husband were away, eh?
That's because you forcibly...
If you really don't want it, then why don't
you stop moving those hips first?
I can't.
My hips are moving on their own.
Oh no, I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
My pussy is about to cum!
Alright, cum then.
I'm going to cum inside you more than before.
No, not inside...
It's really not safe today.
I'm going to get pregnant again.
What are you saying now?
You had such an ecstatic expression after being
cummed inside lots of times the other night.
This pussy can no longer live without having cum poured inside.
Please cum inside.
I can't hold back any longer.
I don't care if I get pregnant.
So please cum inside me!
Of course, that's the plan.
Oh wow, oh yes...
My pussy is getting rubbed hard.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
A lot is pouring inside.
My womb is completely filled with your sticky cum.
I'm going to get pregnant.
I'm definitely going to get pregnant.
Mom...
Kyouko-san...
Does my dick taste good, Kyouko?
Yes, it tastes good.
Be thankful.
I let you get a taste of the real thing, something
you won't get from your husband.
Okay, that's enough.
Don't worry.
I'm about to let you have a taste of it here.
Oh yes, it's really stiff.
Your dick feels really good.
Which is better, mine, or your husband's?
That's...
Well, if you don't plan on answering...
No, wait.
I'll say it.
Your dick is better.
I love dicks!
Dicks are great!
Alright, good girl.
It's deep!
More, do it more...
Your expression is completely stupefied now.
Seems like your womb really wants to ovulate now.
Yeah, it does.
I'll pour it directly inside then.
Please do...
Now, be impregnated!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming while getting impregnated!
Clean up the mess before the kid returns.