You'll really get it if you start causing trouble again.
Do you understand?
Shut up, you idiot!
Takuya-kun.
Sakura-Sensei.
I'll send you home.
Dad is also coming home later.
Hmph, alright then.
Stepmother
Let me introduce to you our newly appointed
teacher who will be starting tomorrow.
I'm Shimada Kenji.
Nice to meet you all.
Chiba-Sensei.
Shimada-Sensei.
Getting used to this school already?
Yes, I find it great that the students are also quite nice.
Oh yes, I've heard the news.
Eh? Well... yeah.
It's been on my mind for some time,
but I really love him, and I want to be a mother for his son.
Well, it seems I've already heard more than enough.
Oh my, what was I saying?
You sang really well.
N-No, I'm not really good at it.
I'm really thirsty now.
Why am I... no, don't!
Oh no, my pussy feels tingly.
And my fingers won't stop!
My clitoris is getting hard like never before.
Oh yes, my ciit feels great.
I can really feel it as I rub my bulging clit.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
My pussy's about to cum.
Dear, no...
I still feel intensely horny.
I want to have sex.
I want to pleasure myself with a real dick.
I really have to go back now.
Wha-... Shimada-Sensei?
What does this mean?
No way, what is he...?
No, no...
I can't muster the strength...
Don't...!
It's in.
A dick that doesn't belong to my husband...
I-I m being raped!
I'm really being raped.
No...
Don't push it in.
Don't move.
His thick thing is...
Something even bigger and thicker than
my husband's dick is going inside me.
Don't, stop!
Don't stir it inside any further!
You're still feeling horny after masturbating, right?
It's not your guy's dick, but I'll make
sure to pleasure you with my own.
Wh-Why does he know... ?
That drug sure worked pretty well on a woman whose
husband is always gone on business trips.
Drug? When did he...?
Is that why he acted like that?
Your pussy is happily trying to suck me in.
Even if your arousal is mostly due to the drug,
for you to be this lively while being raped...
I can't wait to see what's going to happen next.
No, no... Stop!
You can't go any further!
No way...
I'm being penetrated!
I don't want this, and yet I'm... I'm...
I'm about to cum inside of you.
Don't, please... cum outside!
I'm not going to waste an opportunity like that.
Here I come!
It's hot.
This is the first time someone's cummed
inside this much in one shot.
That was so good.
Wife pussies are the best.
We're going to continue this at a hotel.
C-Continue? No way...
You're also not satisfied yet, right, sensei?
Do it once, and it'll be no different than other times.
I'm sorry, dear...
Takkun...
Don't!
Being exposed like this...
Someone might see us!
Please... stop this already.
We mustn't continue this!
What are you saying now?
Who's the one who kept cumming with this dick?
You were moaning in pleasure whenever I hit your womb like this.
Your pussy can no longer defy my dick.
And I'm going to impregnate you with my seed as I please.
No, don't cum inside me!
Get pregnant, you adulterous pussy!
You're cumming inside me.
I'm really going to get pregnant.
You're going to let me know if you're pregnant.
Don't you dare abort it.
The stew that you make really is the best, Mom.
Thanks.
It was really worth it to have made one then.
Dad and I just weren't born with the talent to cook this stuff.
I'm really grateful to have you, Mom.
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
This slutty pussy's about to cum!
Something like this can never be forgiven,
to bear the child that'll be proof of my betrayal to him.
Please, let me go already.
I can't take this any longer...
What are you saying?
You're incapable of leaving me now.
And I'm going to completely teach you why.
S-Stop, I'm not in the mood for that.
I was also just operated on a while ago.
I know, that's why I'm taking this hole tonight.
No, that part is...
I'm going to completely change it at this moment.
No worries, I'm going to use lots of your
favorite drug-laced lotion on your ass.
No... no...
Please don't use that anymore.
I can insert two fingers in it already.
How about three?
No!
Four.
Your asshole's twitching, sucking, and completely horny.
N-No...
Don't...
I get it now.
I know for certain that this will feel good.
I'm going to go crazy with anal sex.
I'm going to go crazy with a dick fucking my ass!
Oh wow...
My ass feels amazing.
My asshole's being opened wide, it almost hurts...
Please open it wider!
A thick dick is penetrating me.
My asshole feels great.
I'm going to cum in my ass.
I'm going to cum in my ass pussy!
Try to make sure next time that you're son's going out.
I'm going to impregnate you in your husband's own love bed!
N-No way... impregnated on my own husband's bed...
No...
I'm cumming as I get cummed in my ass!
I've heard most of the story from this Shimada guy.
I'm sure he'll come here without suspecting
a thing if I tried to use your phone.
His expression when he first saw me
was very interesting by the way.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Please save me. I'll do anything.
Please save me.
Look at this pathetic face.
His dick is also completely exposed.
If I decide to spread this on the internet,
he'll have no choice but to commit suicide.
Don't you think so too, Mom?
I've already told him to submit a letter of resignation tomorrow.
So I don't think you'll ever see him again.
You're going to take a long sick leave from school.
Wait, Mom!
Where are you going, Mom?!
No, Takuya.
Why?
Please stop her, Dad!
Mom's going far away!
Takuya,
your Mom, you see...
Has stopped being your mother.
Mom...
Never.
I'll never lose Mom again.
Stop... Takkun, please forgive me!
Please listen to me, Takkun.
I'll apologize for everything.
I never intended to do all of that.
Ta-Takkun...?
First, let's clean you here and remove all of his marks.
No, stop, stop!
Don't, don't, Takkun!
Mom, that's amazing.
Your belly's starting to bulge like a frog.
That won't do.
We have to push it a bit to make it flow out of the womb more.
Some of that man's cum might still be left.
Stop. Please... don't push it...
Here I go.
Stop...!
Please...
...forgive me...
I pushed so hard that your pussy's starting to swell.
I can even see a bit of its insides.
I have to push it back.
You just wait, I'm going to put it back into place.
No, Takkun, anything but that!
We're...!
Mom...
It's inside.
It's inside Mom.
My dick is inside!
So these are Mom's insides.
No way, this can't be...
It feels good!
My son-in-law's dick...
Takkun's hard and hot dick...
He's raping my exposed uterus!
This shouidn't be...
I shouldn't feel horny from this, and yet...
Are you getting horny, Mom?
I see, you feel pleasure from being raped by your son-in-law.
That's not...
Takkun's dick... his dick is...!
I'm really happy, Mom.
I never thought you'd feel this horny with my virgin dick.
No, it's not...
That's not what it is!
What are you saying? Your nipples are already this stiff.
This is good, Mom.
Your pussy is trying to suck me in.
No, no, any further and I'll...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Mom, I'm going to cum.
It's coming out!
I'm sorry...
I'm supposed to be your mom, and yet...
Your mom, and yet...
After that, for an entire week...
I was raped without rest, without end.
I'm going to go crazy!
It's too bad you have the flu at this time of the year.
Anyway, I was really surprise by Shimada-sensei.
He just suddenly quit his job.
I heard he was injured quite badly.
I would have liked to at least say goodbye.
You're right...
That's not the problem right now.
I want to have sex right now.
Sex, sex...
I want my pussy and my asshole to be played
with and penetrated all day long.
You're going to attend your classes wearing these from now on.
My body can't live without these things.
I want to cum, I want to cum!
I want to cum with Takkun's dick so badly right now.
Everything's alright over here, dear.
Takkun's also here, so don't worry.
I'm making dinner right now actually.
Wow, I'd like to have some too.
Oh, what's wrong?
A friend of mine left her dogs in my care awhile ago.
I'm having a bit of trouble with their constant licking.
Those are some mischievous dogs.
Oh yes,
can you think of a good souvenir when I get home?
Did you get a break?
No, Takkun, I'm talking to your Dad over the phone right now.
Well, not right now.
Perhaps look for it during the year.
What a marvelous dick.
It's grown very well in such a short amount of time.
I-I see.
It's the best dick that I've wanted so far.
I want to have my son's dick.
So, do you have any ideas now?
I want to have your hot cum inside of me.
I want to be impregnated.
I want to bear Takkun's child.
A baby.
I want to give birth to your child!
I can't really wait anymore!
Hey, what's suddenly wrong with you?
I really, really want your dick!
I want to be impregnated.
For you to say those kinds of things...
Well, I do want to have sex with you too.
Please, stop teasing me.
Hurry and give it to me already.
Y-Yeah.
I'm giving it to you right now.
Remember how big, and how thick it is.
I'm going in, Kyouko.
It's in!
Your thick thing is pushing hard inside me.
Oh yes!
Your dick feels great!
It's thick, very thick!
Is it going deep inside?
Yeah, it's all the way in,
all the way inside!
This is amazing.
My pussy is feeling good.
It feels good for me too.
Let me hear the sloppy sounds of your pussy some more.
No...
Don't bring it too close...
Yes, those sounds are quite intense.
It's as if a dick is really inside it.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
My pussy's about to cum!
Oh no, you're about to cum inside and impregnate me.
Just let me be!
I'm going to cum too.
I'm going to pump it all inside.
I think I got pregnant back there.
That was amazing, Kyouko.
I'm so happy that we came together.
I love you, Kyouko.
The Japanese summer heat really kills.
But, I can already see the delighted
faces of those two as I arrive home.
I'm home!
I'm here now.
Kyouko!
Takuya?
Are they still asleep?
Mom...
Can I put my dick inside you, Mom?
No, you can't.
Because our child already resides there.
When I give birth, I'll let you cum all you want inside again,
so that I can become pregnant.
Really, Mom?
We'll be together forever from now on, okay?