Yoshisuzu
Why can't I remember...
I just don't get it all...
Is it all right?
Why...am I...doing something like this...?
This is strange...
I just got here, and...
And this is the first time that I met Youko-san, yet...
Shougo-sama...
I was told to take care of you...
B-By your grandfather...
This mansion too, everything...
Everything, then...
F-From today onward,
Shougo-sama is my master.
Don't!
Reiko
First Episode
Yoshisuzu
I still don't understand why such a thing happened...
Jii-chan lived here his maid Yoko-san until he died.
I came here when I was in elementary school.
Now after all these years, I live here.
my parents still had business to attend to
so I came ahead alone.
And when I did I was greeted like me that...
Wow! They're all my favorites!
But, how did you know?
Please eat up!
O-Okay.
Itadakimasu!
That beauty suddenly…
She said Jii-chan had left her to take care of me.
Could that mean, Youko-san is...?
What was that geezer thinking?!
In that case, I will get some rest now.
Sure, thanks for your hard work.
You've got school tomorrow, so I will come wake you up at 7.
Goodnight, Shougo-sama.
Goodnight.
Nothing has changed since I've been here.
Except, my nonchalant, eccentric and stubborn Jii-chan who's no longer here.
I should have seen him again before he passed away...
I'm sorry, Jii-chan.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Mutsu-sama!
W-W-What are you doing?!
Good morning!
Are you fully awake now?
What sort of question is that?!
You're too abrupt, Youko-san!
Like yesterday, you...
I'm terribly sorry about that.
I just couldn't hold back any longer after I saw you, Master.
I have already prepared breakfast!
Mmph!
But, was that...
A dream?
This is so nostalgic! I haven't been here since elementary school.
Shougo? It's Shougo, isn't it?
Ryuuji? Takashi! Yuuichi?!
What is that? Why didn't you hurry up and contact us sooner?
You're so cold, Shougo!
My bad!
It's been awhile!
We heard from the teachers that you'd be returning.
But we didn't expect this soon!
It was sudden for me as well!
My parents told me to move here right away when Jii-chan passed away.
Hey, your parents aren't here yet, right?
Does that mean you're all alone in that house with that beautiful maid?
You know about Youko-san?
Of course we do!
Everyone in the neighborhood would know if she's that hot!
I bet you went and peeped at her undressing right away!
Don't say stupid things like that!
Well, we know you don't have the guts for that anyway!
You said it!
Jeez, saying whatever you want as soon as we see each other again.
They'd probably get mad if they found out II already did it with her...
What's wrong, Shougo?
I-It's nothing!
Are you Yoshisuzu Shougo?!
W-What is that...
The captain of the soccer club, Neya.
You went to a different elementary school so you wouldn't know...
...but as you can see he's a dumbass and a total pervert.
I see...
I was wondering what kind of man you'd be, but...
You make me laugh. You make me laugh so hard!
Looks like you've been marked by the weirdo already...
So it seems.
Science Laboratory
You're Yoshisuzu Shougo-kun, the transfer student, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm your homeroom teacher, Rokuhira Sakurako.
But that's a bit too formal, isn't it?
Welcome back, Shougo-kun.
You've sure grown up!
Um, excuse me Rokuhira-sensei, but we have met before?
I guess I can't blame you for not remembering me.
You were in kindergarten after all.
You would often come visit while with your grandfather carrying you.
When I would carry you, you'd feel up my breasts...
Your grandfather would happily say, "As expected of my grandson!"
I-I'm so sorry!
Did you and Jii-chan know each other?
Yes, we we knew each other well.
Well, it did bother me a bit that he'd take things in a perverted direction...
I'm really sorry about that.
Moka! Hurry up!
U- Sorry!
Jeez! What are you doing?
Rokuhira-sensei, please excuse me. I need to go to the bathroom...
Go ahead.
It's an earthquake!
Ro-Rokuhira-sensei! It's an earthquake!
What are you all getting worked up about?
It's an earthquake!
An earthquake? It didn't shake at all!
Huh? T-That's not possible...?
T-That's weird...
Was it poltergeist or something?
This is Yoshisuzu Shougo-kun.
The students who started during elementary school would remember him,
but he came back to this town, and he's going to be studying with us.
Everyone please get along with him!
I'm Yoshisuzu Shougo.
Nice to meet you!
Also, I'm sure you'll all want to introduce yourselves and have things to talk about,
so take first period is self study.
Yay!
Make sure you aren't a bother to the other classes!
So good-
Isn't it an honor?
You're able to have sex with me, Neya Takuya.
I'm having sex with you.
Ah! Takuya-sama! You're amazing! Takuya-sama!
R-Right there!
So good!
You're going to have sex with me,
the smartest and the most athletic student in the school!
It feels so good, Takuya-sama!
Takuya-sama! Takuya-sama!
Uwaa- Takuya-sama! Takuya-sama!
Takuya-sama! Oh Takuya-sama!
Amazing!
Takuya-sama! I'm going crazy!
Takuya-sama! More, more!
Takuya-sama! Takuya-sama!
C'mon c'mon! Take it take it!
Yes! It feels so good!
Takuya-sama!
No!
Hey Yoshisuzu-kun...
Do you remember me?
Yeah, you're Saitou-san, aren't you?
Then how about me?
Um, Kubata-san?
You're spot on!
Ayane-senpai!
W-What is it?
You're my fiancée, Yoshisuzu Shougo, aren't you?
Huh?
But don't misunderstand.
It's not like I've recognized you as my fiancée yet!
W-What was she-?
Hey! What does this mean, Shougo?!
L-Like I know! I haven't done anything!
Don't play dumb!
Ayane-senpai said that you're, that you're her fiancée didn't she!
Yoshisuzu-kun! When did you make a move on Kotou-senpai?
You're the worst!
I said it's not like that!
You can't even begin to comprehend how much we adore Ayane-senpai!
She's lovely, neat, and gorgeous! She even smells great!
Yet, why would someone like you...?!
You're living alone with that maid, and that's still not enough?!
No, like I said...
Calm down.
Hey... Ryuuji? Takashi! Yuuichi!
Infirmary
Please take care of this!
Hey, be more gentle...
Jeez... That hurt...
Oh my, it looks like they got you good.
What's wrong? You look so surprised.
I'm the school nurse, Mizuchi Mone.
You're that transfer student Yoshisuzu Shougo, right?
How do you know about me?
I heard from Sakurako-sensei that a veeery cute boy had come here!
Oh?
It looks like I'll have to do a close medical exam.
M-Medical exam?
U-Um...
It's not like I'm hurt enough to need an exam...
And, how can you drink sake so early in the day?
Don't worry about it!
Okay?
I worry about it!
Where are you looking at?
C'mon, I'll inspect you thoroughly.
You've been making me feel good, so...
Hey, can I ask you a favor?
A favor?
Could you pull it out?
Y-Yes.
Please.
This?
This is...?
What about being his fiance?!
It's just something our fathers decided!
A bastard like him!
Yo, sorry Ayane-senpai.
This ball is like me.
It goes towards girls I like on its own.
You know what that means, don't you?
Disgusting...
For someone like you, the idol of this school,
and someone like me, the number one man in this school, is more appropriate!
Don't you think so?
I don't.
C'mon, Ayane-senpai...
Don't touch me so casually!
Oh, how scary! How scary!
Sniff sniff.
I know! I'll masturbate using this hand tonight!
Jeez! Idiots like him shouldn't be allowed to roam free.
Infirmary
More, more!
Shougo!
Amazing!
Shougo, Shougo!
So good!
This is amazing!
No!
No! Do me more!
Amazing!
Don't!
So big! It's amazing!
No! It's so deep!
So big!
Don't! I'm gonna...
This feels so good!
More!
Amazing!
No more!
No!
It's so deep! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
No, I'm gonna cum!
Mone-sensei... I...
You were great. Incredibly.
Also, you don't have to worry.
That's not evil.
"That?"
What was that...?
That person... I've seen her before!
I've seen her, but where...
Welcome back!
Is something wrong? To be in such a hurry-
It's nothing!
There she is...
This lady...
Reiko...