Yoshisuzu
I can't remember...
Why it became like this...
May I...?
Why am I this...?
This is wrong...
I just got here, and...
This is the first time that I've met Yoko-san, yet we...
Shougo-sama...
I was told to take care of you...
B-By your grandfather...
Including this mansion too, everything...
E-Everything?
F-From today onwards,
Shougo-sama is my new master.
Don’t!
SubDESU-H
Yoshisuzu
I still don't understand why such a thing had occurred...
After my granddad, who lived here all alone with his maid, had died,
I began living here.
I haven't been here since I was in kindergarten.
I came here alone before my parents
who still had business to take care of.
And when I did, I was greeted like so...
Wow! It's all of my favorite dishes!
But, how did you know?
Please eat up!
O-Okay...
Thanks for the meal!
That beautiful lady suddenly did…
She said that my granddad had left her to look after me.
Then, is Yoko-san perhaps...?
What was that old man thinking?!
I'll be going to get some rest now.
Sure, thanks for your hard work.
You've got school tomorrow, so I will come wake you up at 7.
Goodnight, Shougo-sama.
Goodnight.
Nothing has changed since I had been here.
Except, my nonchalant, eccentric and stubborn granddad who's no longer here.
I wanted to see him before he passed away...
I'm sorry, granddad.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Mutsu-sama!
W-W-What do you want?!
Good morning!
How are you feeling?
What sort of question is that?!
You're too sudden, Yoko-san!
Like yesterday, you...
I'm terribly sorry about that.
I just couldn't hold back any longer after I saw you, Master.
I've prepared breakfast!
Umph!
But, was that...
A dream?
This brings back memories! I haven't been here since primary school.
Shougo? It's Shougo, isn't it?
Ryuuji...? Takashi-! And Yuuichi too?
Why didn't you hurry up and contact us sooner?
You're as reserved as always!
My bad!
I haven't seen you in ages!
We heard from the teachers that you'd be returning.
But, we didn't expect you to be this fast!
It was sudden for me as well!
My parents told me to move here at once when granddad passed away.
Hey, your parents aren't here yet, right?
Does that mean you're alone with that beautiful maid?
You know about Yoko-san?
Of course we do!
Everyone in the neighborhood would know if she's that pretty!
I bet you went and peeped at her undressing right away!
As if I would!
I guess you're not smart enough for that anyway!
You said it!
Jeez, saying all you want on our reunion.
I bet they'd get angry if I were to tell them that I had already banged her...
What's up Shougo?
I-It's nothing!
Are you the one who's Yoshisuzu Shougo?!
W-What the hell...
It's Meyaga, the captain of the soccer club.
You weren't here during primary school, but as you can see...
He's an idiot and a total pervert.
I see...
I thought I had a rival, but...
You make me laugh. You make me laugh so hard!
Looks like you've been noted by a weirdo already...
So it seems.
Science Laboratory
You're Yoshisuzu Shougo-kun the transfer student, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm Rokuhira Sakurako, your sponsor teacher.
But that's a bit too strict.
Welcome back, Shougo-kun.
You've sure grown up!
Um, please excuse me, but have we met before?
I guess I can't blame you for not remembering me.
You were in kindergarten after all.
You would often come visit while with your grandfather carrying you.
When I would pick you up, you'd feel up my breasts...
Your grandfather would say, "As expected from my grandson!"
I-I'm so sorry!
Did you and my granddad know each other?
Yes, we were good friends.
Well, it did bother me that he'd take things a little pervertedly...
I'm really sorry about that.
Moka! Hurry up!
Sorry!
Jeez! What are you doing?
Rokuhira-sensei, please excuse me. I need to go to the bathroom...
Go ahead.
It's an earthquake!
Rokuhira-sensei-! It's an earthquake-!
What are you all getting worked up about?
It's an earthquake!
An earthquake? It didn't shake at all!
Huh? T-That's not possible...?
T-That's weird...
Was it poltergeist or something?
This is Yoshisuzu Shougo-kun.
I'm sure the students who started from primary school would remember him,
but he came back to this town, and he's going to be studying with us.
Everyone please get along with him!
I'm Yoshisuzu Shougo.
Nice to meet you!
Also, I'm sure you'll all want to introduce yourselves and have things to talk about, so take first period is off.
Yay!
Make sure you aren't a bother to the other classes!
So good-!
Isn't it an honor?
You're able to have sex with me, Neya Takuya.
I'm having sex with you.
Takuya-sama! You're amazing! Takuya-sama!
R-Right there-!
So good!
You’re going to have sex with me, the smartest and the most athletic student in the school!
It feels so good, Tayuka-sama!
Tayuka-sama-! Oh Tayuka-sama!
Tayuka-sama! Tayuka-sama-!
Tayuka-sama! Oh Tayuka-sama!
Amazing-!
Tayuka-sama-! I'm going crazy!
Tayuka-sama! More, more!
Tayuka-sama! Oh Tayuka-sama!
C'mon! How's this?
It’s-! It feels so good!
Tayuka-sama!
No-!
Hey Yoshisuzu-kun...
Do you remember me?
Yeah, you're Saitou-san, aren't you?
Then how about me?
Um, Kubata-san?
You're spot on!
Ayane-senpai!
W-What is it?
You're Yoshisuzu Shougo, my fiancée, aren't you?
Huh?
But do not be mistaken.
It's not like I've approved of you as my fiancée yet!
W-What was she going on about?
Hey! What does this mean, Shougo?!
L-Like I would know! I haven't done anything-!
Don't play dumb!
Ayane-senpai said that you're her fiancée or something!
Yoshisuzu-kun! When did you make a move on Kouto-senpai?
You're the worst!
I said it's not like that-!
You can't even begin to comprehend how much we adore Ayane-senpai!
She's lovely, neat, and gorgeous! Plus she smells great!
But why would someone like you be...?!
You're living alone with that maid, and that's still not enough?!
Like I said-!
Calm down...
Hey... Ryuuji-? Takashi-! Yuuichi!
Infirmary
Please take care of this!
Hey, be more careful...
Jeez... That hurt...
Oh my, it looks like they got you good...
What's wrong? You look surprised.
I'm Mizuchi Mone, the school nurse.
You're Yoshisuzu Shougo, the transfer student, right?
How do you know about me?
I heard from Sakurako that a very cute boy had come here!
Oh?
It looks like I'll have to do a close medical inspection...
M-Medical inspection?
U-Um...
It's not like I'm *that* hurt...
And, how can you drink liquor so early in the day?
Don't worry about it!
Okay?
I can't help it!
Where are you looking at?
C'mon, I'll inspect you thoroughly...
You've been making me feel good, so...
Hey, can I ask you a favor?
A favor?
Could you pull it out?
Y-Yes.
Please.
This?
This is...?
What's with the engagement anyway?!
It's just something our fathers decided!
That guy! He's...
Yo, sorry Ayane-senpai.
This ball is like me.
It goes towards girls I like.
You know what that means, don't you?
Disgusting...
For someone like you, the idol of this school,
and someone like me, the ace of this school, is more appropriate!
Don't you think so?
I don't.
C'mon, Ayane-senpai...
Don't touch me.
Oh, how scary!
Sniff sniff.
I know! I'll masturbate using this hand tonight!
Jeez! Idiots like him shouldn't be allowed to roam free.
Sign: Infirmary
More, more!
Shougo-!
Amazing-!
Shougo!
Shougo, Shougo!
So good-!
This is amazing!
No-!
No-! Do me more!
Amazing-!
Don't-!
So big-! It's amazing!
No-! It's so deep!
So big!
Don't-! I'm gonna...!
This feels so good!
More!
Amazing-!
No more!
No-!
It's so deep-! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
No, I'm gonna cum-!
Mone-sensei... I...
You were incredible.
Also, you don't have to worry.
She's not evil.
"She?"
What was that...?
That person... I've seen her before!
I've seen her, somewhere...
Welcome back!
Is something wrong? You seem to be in a hurry...
It's nothing!
It's here...
This lady...
Reiko...