Minase-senpai, I've been watching you for so long now.
I love you! Please go out with me!
What was your name again? Chitose?
I'm happy to hear you say this, but...
So you're okay with going out?!
No, no!
I'm just saying there isn't a guy out there who wouldn't
be happy that a girl confessed to him.
Huh? Wait, then...
I'm just not interested in dating night now.
You know we have our entrance exams soon, right?
A student's job is to study, you know?
Oh, that makes sense. You're really cool
so I'm really not the right fit for you.
That's not what I'm trying to say...
You don't need to make me feel better.
I already expected that you'd reject me anyway.
Huh?
You expected it?
Yes. By the way, senpai?
Have you lost your phone?
How do you know about that?
Because it's right here.
What's wrong with you?!
Are you sure you want to take that attitude with me?
What's that supposed to mean?
Maybe I should let the entire school see the photo of this
disgusting pervert that you have saved on your phone.
Y-You...
This was your plan all along?!
I've been watching you all this time.
I've been wanting to train you.
Train?!
What do you want from me?!
Come with me to my room right now.
If you listen to whatever I tell you to do when we're
there, then I'll give you back your phone.
You belong to me
S Girlfriend and M Boyfrend
You really took your dick out, huh?
I only said it as a joke though.
Y-You ordered me to, bitch!
Bitch?
I thought we promised to play nicely?
Th-That's...
That's what?
Spit it out.
You can't break your promise.
Oh?
Getting hard from being pinched? How pathetic.
Th-This is... This isn't what it looks like!
Just give me my phone back already!
Hm, let me see... Maybe if you fap a
bit, I'll feel inclined to give it back.
Here?!
Right now. Can you do it?
I love how pathetic you look when
you're jerking yourself off. I love it!
You're rubbing it like a desperate monkey
who's just learned how to masturbate.
What's this? Your dick's still in its foreskin.
Phimosis maybe?
Does it even feel good to fap with phimosis?
Just watching makes me feel bad.
Shut up.
The pervert should keep his mouth shut and keep fapping.
I bet that you usually fap even harder, don't you?
You really are a monkey.
It feels good to grip your dick so tight that
your blood vessels could burst, doesn't it?
Alright stop that hand.
Wh-What should I do with this?
Huh? If you came, you'd get my room dirty.
I'll keep your complete masochistic nature a secret.
You can go home now.
Not going home?
Doesn't matter to me either way.
Oh dam, seeing you fap so pathetically is
making my pussy all hot and bothered.
It's your fault that my clit is this big right now, senpai.
Hey! Who said you could move your hand?
W-What?!
Why are you so turned on right now?
Is it your first time seeing a pussy?
I thought that because your dicks so
big that you wouldn't be a virgin.
But I guess a big dick kind of turns girls off.
I seriously can't wait any longer!
Cant you be quiet? I'm in the middle of
masturbating, can you keep it down?!
I love that sad puppy dog face you make too, senpai.
If you can hold out until I'm done masturbating,
I wouldn't mind giving you a reward.
Really?!
Wow, I really came in front of you.
Chitose?
What do you want, senpai?
I-It's so hard right now, I can't wait any longer.
Oh? So what?
So... you said that I'd get a reward.
I did?
Please just help me out here!
Then why don't you just force me to?
Can I?
Well if you were capable of that, you would've taken
your phone back from me from the start.
You couldn't though, remember?
A completely masochistic monkey
like you is incapable of doing that.
Why are you ignoring me? Please... finish me off.
You really are hopeless.
You're just a simpleton who can only
think with your dick. This is too easy.
Your dick is rock hard. You like your dick getting
stepped on? Just how much of a pervert are you?
So this feels good?
If it really feels that good you won't be able to hold it in.
I really want to mess up this phimosis ridden dick.
Y-You can fuck it up however you want!
It's not my fault if I rip it off by accident, okay?
You want more? You want to cum?
You want to spray your cum all over me?
Are you really gonna cum from my feet?
Do you really wanna moan like a girl and then cum?
Oh, jeez. Look at your pathetic face after
cumming and the mess you made.
Are you trying to make me clean up after you?
You're so full of it.
You like it right here at the tip.
Don't worry, I know.
Chitose...
Who said that you could lick me?
You really are hopeless.
You're happy that your dick is getting
sucked by my small mouth, huh?
It's the pussy that you've been waiting for.
Want a taste?
Yes!
You're getting so excited about being
able to put it inside, aren't you?
Hm? So that's how you're going to act?
So then maybe I should stop?
W-Wait, don't!
You can just go home and fap while imagining
that your hand is my pussy, can't you?
Chitose-sama, please let me go inside you!
What, this isn't good enough for you?
It has to be inside!
Oh, what should I do?
Please!
Can you swear that you'll never disobey
me for the rest of your life?
I swear my loyalty to you, Chitose-sama!
So, please!
Aren't you a little too desperate?
That's kind of a turn-off, but I like
you when you're honest, senpai.
Your dick's so good!
Senpai, isn't my pussy the best?
Your dick is twitching so much inside me right now.
I don't even have to move, do I? It
already feels amazing, doesn't it?
Y-You're not gonna move?
So it won't feel good if I don't move?
Maybe I should take it out.
P-Please don't!
You want me to move that badly?
Yes! Please!
Alright, then answer my question.
Who took that perverted picture of you?
I can't even think of that right now!
Then it looks like I have to take your hard dick out of me.
Please don't take it out, Chitose-sama!
So, senpai? The picture?
My sister took it.
Your older sister did?
She was mad at me and did that to bully me.
Does she hit you?
Ever since we were little.
Sexual abuse too.
Just like what I'm doing now?
No!
What she did was just abuse.
What you're doing is...
What I'm doing is what?
I never got hard!
But when you started ordering me around
I got hard for the first time!
So that's why your phimotic dick was so dirty, huh?
I feel so bad for you.
Please!
Free me from my sister!
I guess I don't have a choice.
I'll have to paint you in my colors to the point
that you forget all about your sister.
You're not allowed to move unless I say you can, okay?
My pussy feels the best, doesn't it?
I'll pound into your dick... just how good a pussy feels!
I can feel your dick squirming.
I wonder if the phimotic dick wants
to start thrusting itself inside me.
Your tip is twitching so badly.
Are you gonna cum?
Are you gonna shoot your milk out again?
That's fine. Shoot even hotter milk inside my womb!
It's pouring inside me!
Having your seed being sown deep inside me feels so good!
Chitose-sama!
I told you not to move unless I tell you to, didn't I?
Please give me my reward.
First it was licking me, then it was having sex with me... guys
are just never content with one thing, are they?
Chitose-sama, please give me my reward.
Oh, fine.
I'm not going anywhere, so you can violate me all you want.
Do you like rubbing your phimotic dick against me?
Your dick's inside me!
Wait, we're done.
You told me I can do it all I want, didn't you?
We might be pretty compatible, huh Chitose?
Yeah, maybe.
But we're just in a master-servant relationship, senpai.
Yeah... that's right.
Yeah, that's right.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч