Minato-senpai, I always...
had feelings for you.
I love you!
Please, go out with me!
You're Chitose-chan, right?
This makes me happy...
You accept!?
Ah, no, no.
I can't go out with a girl so suddenly.
Huh? So...
We can't go out together.
It's getting late.
Shouldn't you be studying?
You're right.
Minato-senpai is popular.
I'm not good enough for you.
That's not what I...
I understand your discomfort. No problem.
Huh?
No problem?
Yes.
Speaking of that, senpai...
Are you sure you want to say no?
What are you talking about?
Because, here...
I have proof.
Don't joke about this!
Are you sure?
Do you want to keep that attitude with me?
What do you mean?
I've this photo of you.
It shows that you're a pervert.
Your reputation at school would be at stake, huh?
Ugh? You...
How did you get this picture of me?
I always watch you from afar.
I always watch.
Always!?
What do you plan to do?
For now, we'll talk at home.
If you obey me correctly...
You can delete it from my cell phone.
You belong to me
You really showed off your penis.
However, I was joking.
But you ordered me.
"You?"
We made a promise, right?
About this...
About this?
What would it be?
Do you want to give up your promise?
What?
Then it stood erect.
There's no way to avoid...
About this...
You're wrong!
Hurry up and get rid of the photo!
Really...
Masturbate and you can delete the photo.
Here!?
Right here. You can?
Senpai, you should see your face...
It's amazing!
You look like an animal in heat.
Do it with more intensity.
What? Your foreskin continues to hide your penis.
Do you suffer from phimosis?
Masturbating intensely in front of a woman.
Aren't you a little embarrassed?
It looks like you're about to explode.
Shut up!
The pervert must masturbate in silence.
Try to do it faster, okay?
You really are like an animal.
Do you feel pleasure in holding your penis tightly?
OK!
You can stop.
H-How about... What's the problem?
What did you do?
It would be a matter of time until you dirty the floor with semen.
Now you can delete your compromising
photo from my cell phone.
Go ahead.
Aren't you going to delete?
Not that I care.
It's a shame the senpai see...
My wet pussy.
My clitoris-chan is hard because of your penis, senpai.
Hey! I didn't give you permission to masturbate!
I don't believe...
What's made you this way?
Is this the first pussy you see?
I didn't think you were a virgin when I saw your penis.
So, see this girl coming.
I can't take it anymore.
Shut up!
I'll masturbate by myself...
Watch me without interrupt.
Your face is very cute like that.
I feel like I'm about to cum.
I'll give you a reward for holding on.
Really!?
Senpai, I came in front of you.
Chitose.
Senpai, what's the matter?
So... It was really hard.
What you mean?
Well, you know...
I deserve a reward.
Did I promise you that?
Please, anything.
Then you can to come.
Sure?
So if you do, your punishment will be increased.
But if you can't do...
You'll continue to be my servant.
Anything, please.
I beg you, please.
Do you... really just want to cum?
Your naughty penis has a lot of energy.
Your penis is rubbing on my foot.
Only a pervert can have fun like that.
Is that good?
I'll not know if you don't tell me.
Your penis is trembling between my fingers.
I want to come!
I'll decide that.
Are you enjoying?
Ejaculating?
Your sperm want to leave?
Do you want to come?
I wonder if you'll to come it in an effeminate voice.
It's a shame that my sock is
covered with your ridiculous semen.
Are you waiting for me to wipe your penis?
Cheeky slave.
Gulp, gulp!
It's good?
Chitose!
Wait!
Who gave you permission to lick me?
Really... you're hopeless.
I realize that my mouth...
makes your penis excited.
I'm coming!
Now my pussy is horny.
Do you want to come in?
Yes!
My pussy is wet because of it.
Why such a rebellious look?
Should we stop?
Can't be right!
If you want my pussy...
Start begging properly.
Chitose-sama, allow me to penetrate it.
Isn't it enough to rub?
This isn't funny.
What should I do...?
Please!
What will I gain?
I'll do whatever you want, so...
You give up so fast.
This is disappointing.
But I don't hate this side of you, senpai.
Your penis... is amazing.
Senpai, my pussy is the best, huh?
The senpai's penis is vibrating inside me.
If it continues like this, the pleasure will be even better.
Are you going to stay like that?
Can't you feel pleasure in another way?
Maybe I shouldn't move my pussy...
Please, don't stop!
Do you want my pussy that much?
Yes, please!
So, answer my question...
Who took the picture of the perverted senpai?
Now isn't the time for this!
So, your penis will feel alone.
Don't take off, Chitose-sama!
Senpai?
And the photo?
It was my big sister.
Your sister?
She has fun doing it.
Is she violent?
Yes, she always abuses me.
How am I doing?
You're wrong!
My sister is a monster!
And you... Well...
I... what?
It's impossible for me not to have erections.
But, obeying you didn't cause me problems for the first time.
So that's why you had an erection?
Poor little thing.
Please!
Save me from my sister!
What can I do...
Forget everything about your sister.
I'll help you.
Senpai, I order you not to move without my permission.
My pussy is the best, huh?
I'll eat your penis...
with my pussy.
I'm feeling it too.
Do you like it when I make your
penis penetrate deep into my pussy?
Your penis is writhing even more.
Are you coming?
Are you going to let your milk out?
It's all right!
I want to feel your semen exploding inside of me!
I-It's coming out!
Making my pussy cum, this is very good!
Chitose-sama.
Did I say you could disobey me?
Reward me, please.
In bed or with words...
men are always "predators".
Chitose-sama, my reward.
There's nothing to do...
I'm not going anywhere. Then do as you wish.
Do you like to rub your penis before put in?
Your penis went in...!
Wait, calm down...!
You said I could do whatever I wanted!
We were meant for each other.
Maybe.
But we're master and slave.
I think... you're right...
Exactly...