A long time ago...I remember Jii-chan telling me someone else was living here.
Reiko-san, huh?
But why did I her in the nurse's office when the ghost should be living here?
Also, you don't have to worry.
That's not evil.
That's what Mone-sensei said, but...
Don't tell me...that it already possessed me?!
Please excuse me, Master.
W-What do you want, Youko-san?!
Jeez...
I'm here to wash your back.
Vow
Second Episode
Youko-san...
Did you do these kinds of things with Jii-chan too?
No, I have only done this with you.
Were you feeling jealous?
T-That's not it...
You've gotten so hard, Shougo-sama.
Yo-Youko-san...
Shougo-sama.
Okay...
Sho-Shougo-sama!
Shougo-sama...
Shougo-sama...! Shougo-sama!
Sho-Shougo-sama!
Have a good day, Shougo-sama!
See you later!
Is it really okay? Doing something like that every night...
Shougo-kun!
Hey man, sorry about yesterday...
You suddenly getting beat up like that.
What do you want now?
Don't be like that, Shougo.
We did some thinking and realized...
that if you're Ayane-senpai's acquaintance, we have a better chance of getting close to her!
After all, we're best friends, aren't we?
That's right! That's right!
That was until yesterday morning.
Don't say that!
Well, it must be difficult for you guys,
since you're only interested in Ayane-senpai.
For me, Ayane-senpai is my second favorite.
Of course my favorite is first year student Mizuchi!
Good morning, Senpai!
Mo- Moka-chan!
Well then, come with me, Shougo-senpai!
W-Wait a second! Who are you?
I'm Mizuchi Moka from first year.
You're horrible. Have you forgotten about me?
You even made passionate love to me yesterday...
Mizuchi...? Does that mean...?
But I sure was surprised!
Who would have thought that
you would do such a thing with Onee-chan on the first day-
No!
Let's go, Senpai!
We're going to be late!
Y-Yeah...
That man!
Bravo, Youko-san!
You're still beautiful, even while you're cleaning!
You're the maid of maids!
Neya-san, what do you want?
Moreover, shouldn't you be in class at this time?
When you are an honor student like me,
you can choose what lessons you go to!
It's just that this is very puzzling...
Why is such a beautiful and skilled maid like you
serving a person like Yoshisuzu Shougo?
It seems very strange.
Are you insulting Shougo-sama?
No, it's nothing like that.
But I heard that that man has made moves not only on Kotou Ayane,
but I heard that he was with Mizuchi Moka
this morning as well.
Ah~ Youko-san...
If you still continue to judge Shougo-sama like that...
Ouch ouch ouch!
I won't let you off this easily!
Do you understand?
That fresh attitude you have!
As expected, you are worthy of being with me.
Goodbye.
It's not just because I was told to...
I've always loved Shougo-sama...
Takuya-sama, Takuya-sama!
Takuya-sama! More, do me more!
I can't get enough! It's never enough!
That look in your eyes! Glare at me more! Please do it more!
Takuya-sama, please do me, too!
That look, I can't get enough!
More! Stare at me more!
Say it Youko! Please say that I'm better than Yoshisuzu Shougo!
Please say it!
You're the best, Takuya-sama!
Takuya-sama! You're the greatest of them all!
Takuya-sama! I swear that you're the best!
Youko, Youko, Youko!
Youko!
Youko... Ayane... Moka...
They're all... they're all mine!
One, two, three, four!
Two, two, three, four!
When describing the details of the atomic structure of this substance,
it is represented by the number 14,
and accordingly, the substance called nitrogen...
And the atomic number 15...
So, nitrogen and nitrogen 15 are...
Why are males so simplistic?
They're all on edge about Kotou-senpai and Mizuchi Moka!
I know, right!
He's the worst.
Everyone, please cut it out!
Hey, did you hear the rumors about Sakurako-sensei?
I heard! Apparently she took a guy into the science laboratory and...
Seriously? So bold!
You mustn't neglect the lesson.
Please keep everything not class-related to yourselves until after school!
Yes!
But, who knows what'll happen to me after school...
Yes! Lessons are over!
Shougo, we're gonna make you confess
everything about Ayane-senpai and Moka-chan...?
What?
Huh? Where's Shougo?
Hey! Shougo ran away!
He's over there!
Oh crap...
Don't let him escape!
Give me a break!
Don't fuck with us!
We won't let you go!
You bastard! What did you do to my Moka-chan?!
Shut up, she's mine!
No, she belongs to me!
No, she's mine!
I don't care whose she is!
Are you Yoshisuzu Shougo!?
You bastard, what did you do to our Ayane-san?!
Moka-chan too!
I-I said that I don't know!
A-A dead end?!
Wait up, Shougo!
This way!
Hurry!
Shougo!
Huh? Where's Shougo?!
He can't be far!
No matter what, we have to find him!
Yeah!
I don't know who you are, but you saved me!
Mo-Moka-chan?
We meet again, Shougo-senpai.
Welcome to the occult society!
The occult society?
Um, this place is...?
Mo-Moka-chan-?! What are you...?
When I saw you and Onee-chan yesterday, I...
I was like this...
So...I couldn't take it anymore...
I can't calm down, even after doing this all night...
Hey, Senpai...
Shougo-senpai...
So... so please...
Senpai, do me...
Do me, Senpai.
Did you find Shougo?!
Not yet!
Don't let him get away!
This isn't good...
If they find me doing it with Moka-chan, I'll certainly be killed!
Sorry, Moka-chan!
You can't calm down either, can you?
M-My body has...!
Now, you can't run away...
Moka-chan-!
Shougo-senpai!
Se-Senpai-!
Senpai... Senpai!
What is that guy thinking?!
I can't believe he was eyeing Moka-chan, even after doing it with Mone-sensei!
In any case, I'll have to ask Moka-chan for the details...
Oh?
Isn't the occult clubroom door usually here?
That's strange.
W-What's...this?
Eh?!
Se-Senpai!
Hurry, hurry up and put it in!
Put it in!
Senpai!
So good!
Senpai, Senpai!
Hey, Senpai, let's have everyone watch us having sex!
Eh?!
Isn't it great, Senpai?
Where did Shougo go?!
Moka-chan, this isn't good!
Isn't it more exciting like this?
Don't worry about it, let's keep going.
Senpai-!
He's the worst... He's the worst!!
So good!
Senpai!
Right now....and that time...
More, do it more!
Oh! You've grown!
You've gotten taller again!
You just keep growing, Shougo!
San-chan, I brought her along!
Oh, nice of you to come!
Shougo, that's your fiancée, Kotou Ayane-chan!
Kotone-chan?!
I'm Kotou Ayane, nice to meet you.
I'm Yoshisuzu Shougo.
Being your fiancée means that I'm going to be your wife in the future!
My wife?
Yes!
So...
This is a sign of our special promise.
Even if we become adults, you mustn't forget it.
Sure!
I won't forget, Kotone-chan!
It's not Kotone, it's Kotou Ayane!
Oh, that's right!
I'm sorry, Kotone-chan!
It's not Kotone, it's Ayane!
Right...
Even so... Even so... I can't forgive him...
I don't want that engagement anymore!
He is a bad man, isn't he? That Sanji-kun...
Mizuchi-sensei...
Oh? What's wrong, Kotou-san?
You and your sister are too indecent!
Well, don’'t mind it.
But, I didn't know that you had such a fate with him.
I-I don't care about him anymore.
Being engaged is just what our parents decided.
Are you going to run away, Kotou Ayane-san?
I-I'm not running away...
I've just gotten sick of Yoshisuzu Shougo!
It doesn't really matter how you say it.
You're going to run away first from our battle, isn't that right?
Don't say such silly things!
I never run away, no matter what enemies I'm up against!
I was the first person to kiss him!
Hmm... Although it seems someone else had sex with him first...
T-There's nothing special about a male's virginity!
I'm the one who he's destined to be with.
Is that really okay? You're not just up against one.
My grandfather has 10 or 20 lovers too!
Compared to that, I'm only up against three. It'll be easy!
I would like to congratulate you on your attitude,
but for a top student like you, you don't have the numbers correct.
Eh?
You're not up against three, you're up against four.
W-Wait, it's you, Moka-chan, and that maid Youko-san.
Is there someone else, too?
Take a good look.
Se-Sensei... What are you, Sensei?
Don't worry about it, just look.
See, look much much closer...
Huh?!