I remember Granddad telling me that she was someone living here long ago.
Reiko-san, huh?
But why did I see a ghost in the infirmary when it should only appear here?
Also, you don't have to worry.
She's not evil.
That's what Mone-sensei said, but...
Don't tell me that it’s possessed me?!
Please excuse me, Master.
W-What do you want, Yoko-san?!
Jeez...
I'll wash your back.
SubDESU-H
Yoko-san...
Did you do these kinds of things with Granddad too?
No, I have only done this with you.
Were you getting jealous?
T-That's not it...
You've gotten so hard, Shougo-sama.
Yo-Yoko-san...
Shougo-sama.
Okay...
Sho-Shougo-sama-!
Shougo-sama...
Shougo-sama...! Shougo-sama-!
Sho-Shougo-sama-!
Have a good day, Shougo-sama!
See you later!
Is it okay for us to be doing that sort of thing every night?
Shougo-kun!
We're terribly sorry about yesterday...
We didn't mean to beat you up like that.
What do you want?
Don't be so cold, Shougo.
We all put some thought into it and we realized
that if you're her friend, then we have a better chance of getting close to her!
We're buddies after all, aren't we?
That's right!
That was until yesterday morning.
Don't be like that!
Well, it must be difficult for you guys, since you're only interested in Ayane-senpai.
But for me, Ayane-senpai is my second favorite, and of course my favorite is Mizuchi from first year!
Good morning, Senpai!
Mo-Moka-chan!
Let's go, Shougo-senpai!
W-Wait! Who are you?
I'm Mizuchi Moka from first year.
You're so mean. Have you forgotten about me?
You even made passionate love to me yesterday...
Mizuchi...? Does that mean...?
But I sure was surprised!
Who would have thought that you would do such a thing with Onee-chan on the first day...
No-!
Let's go, Senpai!
We're going to be late!
Y-Yeah...
That guy...!
Bravo, Yoko-san!
You're still beautiful, even while you're cleaning!
You're the maid of maids!
Neya-san, what do you want?
Moreover, shouldn't you be in class?
When you become an elite student like me, you can choose what lessons you go to!
But this is very puzzling...
Why is such a beautiful and skilled maid like you serving a person like Yoshisuzu Shougo?
It seems very strange.
Are you insulting Shougo-sama?
No, it's nothing like that.
But I heard that that man has made moves not only on Kotou Ayane,
but I heard that he was with Mizuchi Moka
this morning as well.
Yoko-san...
If you still continue to judge Shougo-sama like that...
Ouch ouch ouch!
I won't let you off that easily!
Do you understand?
That fresh attitude you have!
You're worthy of being with me.
Goodbye.
It's not just because I was told to...
I've always loved Shougo-sama...
Takuya-sama, Takuya-sama!
Takuya-sama! More, do me more!
I can't get enough! It's never enough!
That look in your eyes! Glare at me more! Please do it more!
Takuya-sama, please do me, too!
That look, I can't get enough!
More! Stare at me more!
Sayoko! Please say that I'm better than Yoshisuzu Shougo!
Please say it!
You're the best, Takuya-sama!
Takuya-sama! You're the greatest of them all!
Takuya-sama! I swear that you're the best!
Yoko, Yoko, Yoko!
Yoko!
Yoko... Ayane... Moka...
They're all mine!
One, two, three, four!
Two, two, three, four!
When describing the details of the atomic structure of this substance,
it is represented by the number 14,
and accordingly, the substance called nitrogen...
And the atomic number 15...
So, nitrogen and nitrogen 15 are...
Why are males so simplistic?
They're all on edge about Kotou-senpai and Mizuki Moka!
I know, right!
He's the worst...
Everyone, please cut it out!
Hey, did you hear the rumors about Sakurako-sensei?
I heard! Apparently she took a guy into the science laboratory and...
Seriously? So bold!
You mustn’t neglect the lesson.
Please keep everything not class-related to yourselves until after school!
Yes!
But, who knows what'll happen to me after school...
Yes! Lessons are over!
Shougo, we're gonna make you confess everything about Ayane-senpai and Moka-chan!
What?
Huh? Where's Shougo?
Hey! Shougo ran away!
He's over there!
Oh crap...
Don't let him escape!
Give me a break!
Don't be stupid!
We won't let you go!
You bastard! What did you do to my Moka-chan?!
Shut up, she's mine!
No, she belongs to me!
No, she's mine!
I don't care whose she is!
Are you Yoshisuzu Shougo!?
What did you do to our Ayane-san?!
You took our Moka-chan!
I-I said that I don't know!
A-A dead end?!
Wait up, Shougo!
Over here!
Hurry!
Shougo!
Huh? Where's Shougo?!
He can't be far!
We have to find him!
Yeah!
I don't know who you are, but you saved my life!
Mo-Moka-chan?
We meet again, Shougo-senpai.
Welcome to the occult club!
The occult club?
Um, is this...?
Mo-Moka-chan-?! What are you...?
When I saw you and Onee-chan going at it yesterday, I...
I was like this...
So I couldn't hold back and I...
I can't calm down, even after doing this all night...
Hey, Senpai...
Shougo-senpai...
So... so please...
Senpai, please do me...
Do me, Senpai.
Did you find Shougo?!
Not yet!
Don't let him get away!
This isn't good...
If they find me doing it with Moka-chan, I'll be killed!
Sorry, Moka-chan!
You can't calm down either, can you?
M-My body has...!
You can't escape now...
Moka-chan-!
Shougo-senpai!
Se-Senpai-!
Senpai... Senpai!
What on Earth is that guy thinking?!
I can't believe he was eyeing Moka-chan, even after doing it with Mone-sensei!
I'll have to ask Moka-chan for the details...
Oh?
Isn't the occult clubroom door usually here?
That's strange.
W-What's this?
Eh?!
Se-Senpai!
Hurry, hurry up and put it in!
Put it in!
Senpai...!
So good-!
Senpai, Senpai!
Hey Senpai, let's have everyone watch what we’re doing!
Eh?!
Isn't it great, Senpai?
Where did Shougo go?!
Moka-chan, we shouldn't!
Isn't it more exciting like this?
Let's keep going.
Senpai-!
He's the worst... He's the worst!
So good-!
Senpai!
This time and that time too...
More, do it more!
Oh! You've grown!
You've gotten taller again!
You just keep growing, Shougo!
San-chan, I brought her along!
Oh, good to see you!
Shougo, that's Kotou Ayane-chan, the girl who's going to be your fiancée!
Kotone-chan?
I'm Kotou Ayane, nice to meet you.
I'm Yoshisuzu Shougo.
Being your fiancée means that I'm going to be your wife in the future!
My wife?
Yes!
So...
This is a sign of our special promise.
Even if we become adults, you mustn't forget it.
Sure!
I won't forget, Kotone-chan!
It's not Kotone, it's Kotou Ayane!
Oh, right!
I'm sorry, Kotone-chan!
It's not Kotone, it's Ayane!
Right...
But, he's... I can't forgive him...
I don't want that engagement anymore!
Sanji is a bad man, isn't he?
Mizuchi-sensei...
Oh? What's wrong, Kotou-san?
You and your sister are too loose!
Don’t mind it.
But I didn't know that you had such a fate with him.
I-I don't care about our engagement anymore, it's just what our parents decided after all.
Are you going to run away? Kotou Ayane-san?
I-I'm not running away...
I've just gotten sick of Yoshisuzu Shougo, and-!
That doesn't really matter.
You're going to run away first from our battle,
aren't you?
Don't say such silly things!
I never run away, no matter what enemies I'm up against!
I was the first person to kiss him!
Although it seems someone else took his virginity...
T-There's nothing special about that!
I'm the one who he's destined to be with.
Is that really okay? You're not just up against one.
My grandfather has 10 or 20 lovers too!
Compared to that, I'm only up against three. It'll be easy!
I would like to congratulate you on your attitude,
but for a top student like you, you don't have the numbers correct.
Eh?
You're not up against three, you're up against four.
W-Wait, it's you, Moka-chan, and Yoko-san the maid.
Is there someone else, too?
Take a good look.
Se-Sensei... What are you, Sensei?
Just take a look.
See, look closer...
Huh?!