Nee-san, I can't do this with you anymore.
I have a girl...
I like now...
So what I mean is...
Sorry.
Minato-senpai?
What's the matter?
Right now?
I don't really mind, I guess.
Are you really okay calling a girl out at this
time of day? What if I'm assaulted?
No, I was just kidding.
I'll be right there.
But, senpai...
I'm not satisfied with just being loved by you.
Sorry for making you come meet me out of the blue.
It's fine.
Something wrong?
You're kind of different today, Chitose.
You think so?
Well I didn't really have the time to put on anything decent.
You look really cute.
Thank you.
You know, I like you Chitose.
I know that.
Then let's start dating!
No thank you.
Huh? Why?
Weren't you the one who rejected me?
Yeah, but that's because I was my sister's slave back then.
I couldn't even think about dating someone else!
But you changed me, Chitose.
I changed you?
You're my ideal woman.
You're just my type... a big sadist.
You're the best girl for me.
Your sister's gonna get mad at you if you keep saying that.
She has nothing to do with this.
I can't be with anyone but you, Chitose.
If you really find my huge sadism to be attractive,
you're a bigger pervert than I thought.
Let me think...
From this moment on, you're gonna be a dog.
If you don't move until I say you can, I'll go out with you.
Wh-What? What are you talking about?
Stay!
Got it?
Y-Yeah...
What are you planning?
You'll find out soon enough.
Is it alright to come in now?
Who's that?
What? Come on.
Are you already getting started?
Sorry for the wait.
No problem.
Are you Chitose-san, the organizer of this event?
Yes, thank you for coming.
Whew.
You're a cutie.
Thank you.
I thought the message board said
you'd be bringing another person.
The second person's just here to watch.
What's going on?
Don't move a muscle, senpai.
Oh, I see.
That's what's going on here.
I like it.
Let's head over to a hotel then.
No...
Let's do it here.
At first glance you looked like a prude, but you're
actually quite the pervert, huh, Chitose-san?
You even brought someone to watch.
I'm fine doing this outside.
Same, I'm good with this.
Okay, then whip them out.
And let's get started.
When was the last time we had this much fun?
Why am I
getting hard?
Hey, you're slacking off over here.
Okay, okay.
Feels damn good.
Chitose-chan, you okay just leaving him there?
I'd rather his smelly uncircumcised dick can stay over there.
Hey! That's private!
That's a little rude to the lady.
So, Chitose-chan...
You like circumcised dicks, don't you?
Please grip my dick harder.
Chitose-chan, make me cum!
Make me cum too please.
You guys are still so hard.
You're seriously the best.
I could do this all the time.
Thanks for that great climax.
Wait, is he fapping?
It looks like your boyfriend is quite the pervert himself.
He's not my boyfriend. He's my pet.
I know we agreed on just blow jobs, but
how about we go a little further?
No... I don't think so.
You're too hot. Just cumming one time isn't enough for us.
I'd feel bad for making senpai wait.
Wait?
I don't think he wants to wait, he wants to watch more.
Senpai...
Is that right?
Y-Yeah...
You're the worst.
Between the thighs, okay?
No going any further than that.
I'm good with that.
So, it's time for Round 2 then?
Idiot.
This feels so good!
I like these hard nipples you have here.
O-Ow!
Don't... twist them so hard.
Your dick's harder than before!
You already came so much before.
Feels better than your senpai's doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good, but...
I wonder how he feels right now!
How should I know?
You sure you don't want to stop this?
A stranger's dick might just go inside her at this rate.
Or maybe you actually really want to see it go in?
N-No, that's not...
No, don't move your dick around like that!
It's really gonna go in!
Stop!
Woah there, are you sure you want to move?
If you move, you'll be breaking her order.
But if this keeps going on, she's gonna get raped.
What's it gonna be?
I...
That's right, you don't have to do anything.
You have his permission.
So I guess we can have sex then.
Chitose-chan, you can't wait to have sex, right?
Senpai, I'm really going to be raped if this keeps going.
But you told me not to move!
Senpai, save me!
But if I move, you won't go out with me.
Are you saying that it's okay if I get raped then?!
You're the worst.
Just die!
Okay, let's dig in.
I can't believe you really put it inside me!
S-Senpai, don't just watch! Help me!
Why aren't you helping?!
I'm being raped here, why are you acting like that?!
Looks like you didn't expect this to happen.
Huh?
Wait, is this... am I scared?
Damn! It's so tight!
Oh geez, she's starting to cry.
Shit, I think I'm about to cum.
Cum?! You're not wearing a condom!
Stop! Please, you can't cum inside!
I know you want it.
I don't!
I don't need your cum!
It's so hot!
This pussy's the best.
I just wanna stay like this forever.
It's finally my turn.
Yeah, I know.
Want me to clean her out for you?
– Please...
– I'm fine with her as is.
No more.
I can't help but notice that this hole is
looking lonely, so I'll keep it company.
These voluptuous pounds of flesh...
Don't spread it open!
Such a beautiful asshole.
I haven't even let senpai use it yet!
Oh, so it's still fresh then?
So let's just stop here.
Listen to me!
You can't have sex with me there!
Stop... it...
It hurts!
Well if I don't loosen it up now,
it's gonna hurt like hell later.
Oh shit, her pussy's getting tighter again!
Chitose-chan, you turned on?
I'm not turned on... at all...
That should be good enough.
Huh?
Don't put your dick in!
There are two dicks inside me right now!
It hurts!
You're gonna break my asshole!
Stop!
If you're this rough, you're gonna break me!
You're gonna destroy my asshole and pussy!
My hip is going numb!
Don't cum inside me!
If you cum anymore, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna lose it!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
I'm sorry! Please stop this already!
I feel sick.
You're still going at it?
That's hilarious.
Hit us up whenever, Chitose-san.
Why didn't you help me?
I was just raped.
Y-You told me n-not to move.
I hate you, senpai.
D-Don't say that!
I'll never forgive you.
I'm sorry!
I'll do anything so please, forgive me!
You're such a helpless piece of trash.
If you can hold off on cumming until I say so, I'll forgive you.
But if you cum...
Then I never want to see your face again.
Okay.
It's so tight!
Shut up! Keep quiet!
Senpai, your masochistic dick...
Is it already about to cum just from going inside me?
It really is a brainless hunk of meat, isn't it?
Your dick's already twitching and
it's moving all around inside me.
Your premature ejaculating uncircumcised
dick is anything but a man's dick.
You're nothing more than livestock.
Shut up, you pig!
You're amoral... You disgust me!
Your balls look like they're about to explode.
You're such a masochistic pig. You're
just a lowly animal, senpai.
This doesn't even feel good to me.
I think the dicks from before felt better than this.
That hurt your feelings?
But your dick's nothing but a masochistic dick
that can't even hold its cum in, right?
I don't even want to look at your pathetic face, you pig.
It's about time, isn't it? Come on,
let your masochistic dick cum.
Do it! Cum! Cum!!
Hit me with everything you got!
Become a slave to my pussy!
Live your life only being able to fantasize about my pussy!
That's goodbye, senpai.
It wasn't long, but...
I had fun.
Did you already forget that I told you to
never show your face around me again?
Well, I am the biggest piece of scum.
I already forgot.
There's really no helping you.
Senpai?
If you take your dick out here, I'll go out with you.
What? That's all I have to do?
Huh?!
– What the heck?!
– Yo, look at him!
What a pervert!
Holy crap!
Well senpai, now...
You Belong to Me
translation: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч