Infirmary
Well then Shougo, why don't you replenish your strength
after being abused by those thieves!
She said "thief" right?
Even though the one who made this is also a thief too.
Please enjoy yourself and don't you dare leave a single bite.
Su-Sure.
Listen to me, Shougo.
Today I want to go first,
So don't do anything unnecessary after this.
I want you to save your strength for later.
Shougo-senpai, why didn't you come to see me yesterday?
I've been waiting for you all this time.
So-Sorry... it's just...
Shougo.
Even though I don't know what are you've been worried about since yesterday...
We'll be here to fulfil you anytime you need it.
Sensei, I don't think I understand what you said earlier.
Be quiet for a minute, I'll show you something interesting.
Ah... Senpai, you're so mean.
It's still 100 years too soon for you to beat me at this, you know?
Beside that, Shougo seems to be enjoying himself right now.
Then, please let me know when he's cumming.
No!
Shougo-senpai, I made your face all sticky.
Onee-chan, didn't I say it was my turn next?
Sure... sure!
Sorry, but I'm sure you can fill her up, right?
I'm still cumming from earlier, so it's okay to let it out.
Now, now! We can't let one drop go to waste.
Ayane-san...
Please stop glaring at us like that.
Anata Dake Konbanwa
Reiko
Fifth Chapter
Even though we said to everyone that we're going to class...
Instead we're having sex in this empty classroom.
That's pretty perverted, right?
Senpai?
Who does this seat belong to?
What?
When whoever this seat belongs to returns from their class,
I wonder what their reaction will be when they realize this seat
Is covered with mine and Shougo's perverted smells.
Well then, why don't you thrust it in?
Why don't we cover the entire class room
with our perverted smell?
What don't you understand about me?
Why don't you try to kick me as hard as you can?
I don't mind if you kick me hard.
Please, all of you, kick and tease me!
Now then, honeys!
Why don't you come at me, and walk down the road of bliss together!
Do you want to walk it with me?
Tha-that's impossible!
You don't have to be ashamed!
No~!
Brilliant...
You're fading into the dusk, aren't you?
Sensei.
Is something troubling you?
Or is it possible that you're already tired with all those girls?
No, that's not it... it's something else...
Well, what is it?
I feel so miserable, inside...
You're worried about something like that?
That's a good side of you.
Please don't make me anymore miserable than I already am.
Why don't you go home? I'm sure there's someone there who'll be able to solve your problem.
Eh?
That's right.
Then I'll take my leave.
Be careful.
Do your best.
Where is this place?
Inside a garden?
Reiko-san?
I've been waiting for you to come here all this time.
Seasons changed, time passed by, and I've been waiting.
I can't wait any longer.
That time... when I was about to lose consciousness...
There was an innocent boy who would talk to me when I was about to fade away.
Eh?
Yes, because of him, I'm able to be like this right now.
Shall we?
Reiko-san.
I always talked to you when you were a little girl...
But, somehow I keep forgetting everything about it.
Sorry, but...
It feels so much better when I don't remember.
During the first time...
These words don't mean anything to me,
they were just another thing that will be forgotten soon.
But the more I tried to ignore those words, my consciousness has kept them alive all this time.
I don't know why, but they're something irreplaceable to me.
Eh?
But...
You're the same person who's going to leave me someday.
What's that?
It is something that has been my family for a long time.
It has been close to my heart for a long time.
When you came back to this house...
Even though your face and body have changed...
I know that it's you, Shougo-sama.
We finally meet again.
Reiko-san... I'm-
It's not fair that it's just me.
I'm older than you.
Re... Reiko-san...
Though I'm not sure about everything that happened the first time we met...
I'll prove to you that I know a lot about this.
I'm sorry, I'm just teasing you.
No...
Please... please... don't tease me anymore.
Please, put it in! Quickly!
Please tell me if it hurts, okay?
Don't worry about the pain, I've had experience with Yoko-san and Ayake-san.
E-Eh?
But I'm still a little scared... Will you hold my hand?
Sure.
Here I come.
Yes.
It's okay if you do it harder.
I understand.
Re-Reiko-san.
I... I can't hold...
Me... me neither!
No, please don't look at me!
Reiko-san.
Yes?
Can I do it again?
If you want...
Then...
Okay, stop right there!
Well, I'm sure everyone understands the situation here.
We must settle the score, right here, right now.
I don't mind being used by Shougo-sama.
Even if he's already picked someone else.
Wait a minute, you're taking his side?
We don't have to settle anything, we're all rightfully his lovers anyway.
Right~?
This is the human world, not the other world!
Besides, two of you are the same person, right? Don't take this so lightly!
Uh... No...
Shougo-sama's thing...
Has gotten big...
N-No...
You idiot, Shougo!
Can't you control yourself? Even at a time like this!?
It's rare opportunity that we're all together like this, why don't we join them?
Yes, Onee-chan.
How about you, Yoko-chan?
As long as Shougo-sama agrees.
Wait, why are you all ignoring me?!
Hey, Reiko-chan, get away from that!
Grandpa...
I'm...
really your grandson, after all!
You said you wanted to discuss something with me...
But I can already tell by looking at you.
What... should I do... now?
Let's see...
I'm not sure how I can help you, at all. But I am going to give a warning to those girls.
There's someone who should be able to help you with this.
Is it quite possibly Sensei's lover?
The one who had sex with you in here?
How do you know-
Of course you know about it...
Jeez...
I thought he was studying abroad?
He is.
But he's coming back soon.
Um.. what should I do right now?
Ah, I found Shougo-kun!
Let's go home, shall we?
I won't let you sleep again tonight.
Sakurako-sensei, please help me!
Do your best.
Eh?
Thats the spirit!
Um...
Don't ever give up or let your spirit waver!
Keep it up until Gen returns. Fight!
Charge!
That can't be true~!!!