Minato-senpai,
I've admired you...
and constantly looked at you from afar.
I like you.
Please go out with me.
Chitose-chan, right?
I'm happy to hear your feelings.
Is that a "yes"?
That's not what I meant.
I'm just saying there's no guy that wouldn't
feel happy getting confessed to.
Wait, so you mean.
I can't focus on dating at the moment.
Entrance exams are just around the corner, right?
I really think we need to study first.
You're right.
You're cool,
so I don't particularly fit that persona.
That's not what I'm saying.
You don't need to comfort me.
I expected as much, anyway.
You expected to be dumped?
Yes. By the way, senpai,
did you lose your smartphone lately?
How did you know that?
That's because,
it's right here.
Stop kidding around!
Are you alright with this?
With that attitude?
What do you mean?
A smartphone that has these kinds of photos saved in it.
Maybe I should let the entire school take a peek at it.
You!
You planned this from the start?!
I've been watching you from afar.
I've always wanted to tame you.
Tame...? What is it that you want?
Please come to my room today.
If you follow my instructions once we get there,
I'll return your smartphone.
You belong to me
You really did pull out your dick.
I intended it to be a joke, you know.
You ordered me to do it!
You?
Not talking back is part of the deal, correct?
That's.
That's?
What is it?
You shouldn't break our deal.
Oh?
Getting a boner from a pinch, eh.
You're utterly helpless.
This is.
It's not what seems like!
Give my smartphone back already!
Let's see.
I just might return it to you, if you
pathetically fap in front of me.
Right here?
Can you do it right now?
The sight of senpai fapping.
It really looks stupid.
You look like some monkey who just
learned to fap for the first time.
Hey, your foreskin is rolling on your dick.
Is it the uncut type?
Don't you feel ashamed fapping with that uncut dick of yours?
Makes me want to shrivel up, and I'm the one who's watching.
Shut up.
Just keep quiet and fap, you pervert.
Damn!
You usually rub it harder, right?
You really are an animal.
It looks like it feels more pleasurable the
more your hand slides up and down.
Okay, stop fapping.
Wait, what do I do with this?
You're asking me?
My room's going to be a mess if you start cumming.
I'll keep your masochistic tendencies a secret, senpai.
Now, go home.
Not going home?
I don't mind, though.
Oh no, now that I've seen your pathetic face,
my pussy just couldn't resist.
It's all your fault, senpai, for making my clit bulge like this.
Hey, don't just start fapping.
No way.
What are you getting aroused for?
Is it your first time seeing a pussy?
I thought you weren't a virgin with that big dick.
I guess girls will just get creeped out with that uncut dick.
I can't hold back anymore!
Pipe down.
I'm masturbating here, so don't disturb me.
That puppy-like expression looks cute.
If you can hold it until I cum,
I'll give you a reward.
Really?!
I came right in front of you, senpai.
Chitose.
What is it, senpai?
I... I'm itching for it already.
So what of it, then?
Well... you said you'd give me a reward.
Did I say that?
Please! I'm about to go nuts here!
Then why don't you force yourself on me?
Are you sure?
Though, if that's true, you'd probably have just
forcefully taken your phone in the first place.
But you didn't.
The masochistic monkey didn't have the guts to go so.
I'll do anything, so please!
Please, quell it for me.
You really are helpless.
Just a simple lecherous dick.
All too easy.
Your dick is all stiff now, it seems.
You're too perverted to be aroused with my feet.
Does it feel that good?
If you keep reacting like that, I might not be able to hold back.
I want to make a mess out of that uncut dick of yours.
Feel free to do so.
Don't blame me if your dick gets torn off.
Cumming? Cumming already?
About to squirt it out?
Are you about to cum with my feet?
You seem to really want to cum while moaning like a girl.
Oh my, cumming while having that
pathetic orgasmic expression.
You want me to clean up after, too?
Such a cheeky bastard.
I'm rubbing it vigorously in me,
just for you.
Chitose!
Hey, who told you to lick me down there?
Really helpless, huh?
Getting my petite mouth to suck this dick,
and feeling good as I do so.
Here's the pussy you've been yearning for.
Wanna taste it?
I want to!
So you were expecting me to put it inside.
Oh? So you can be cocky when you want to.
Shall we end this here, then?
No way!
You can just remember how my pussy
feels and fap back home, right?
Chitose-sama, please put it inside!
I can't just rub it with my pussy?
It has to be inside.
I wonder what I should do?
I beg of you!
Will you vow to never defy me again?
I submit myself to you!
So please!
You're getting too desperate.
Really creeps me out.
But, I don't hate you for being honest, senpai.
Your dick feels great!
My pussy feels great too, right?
It's twitching inside me.
It already feels good even if I don't move, right?
You're not going to move?!
It doesn't feel good if I don't move?
Maybe I'll just pull it out.
Please don't!
You really want me to move that badly?
Yes, please!
Then answer my question.
Who took that perverted picture?
I can't think of that right now!
I'll pull this stiff dick out, then.
Wait, don't pull it out, Chitose-sama!
So, what about the picture, senpai?
My older sister took it.
Older sister?
She likes to tease me when she's mad.
Does she treat you badly?
She's always been like that.
She even does sexually violent stuff.
Just like what I'm doing right now?
No!
She just does it to harass me.
Yours is... well.
Mine is?
I never got a boner when it came to such matters.
But, I had my first one when you were pushing me around.
So that explains why your uncut dick has lots of smegma.
Poor thing.
I beg of you!
Stop me from having haunting thoughts about her!
Alright then.
I'll mark you, until you forget all about your big sis.
Don't you dare move, senpai.
My pussy is the best, don't you think?
I'm going to etch it into your dick.
Just how good pussies are.
My hips are starting to feel tingly.
Maybe my pussy is starting to get the hang
of being fucked by your uncut dick.
The tip of your dick is twitching a lot.
Cumming already?
About to cum your milk now?
Go ahead.
Squirt it all out in me just like how you let it all out earlier.
It's seeping through.
It feels good to be cummed inside.
Chitose-sama.
I told you that you can't move.
Please reward me.
First, I let you lick, then I let you fuck.
Men sure are demanding creatures.
Chitose-sama, please reward me.
I'll have to indulge you, then.
I'm not moving here, so just rape me as you please.
Do you love rubbing your uncut dick on me like that?
It's in!
Hey, we're done already!
You said I can do however I please, right?
I think we have good chemistry.
Maybe.
But, we have a master-slave relationship.
I guess you're right.
Indeed, we are.