Shougo-sama!
G-Good morning!
W-What do you mean, "good morning"?!
I'm almost there...
Shougo-sama, everyone is waiting.
Eh?
Ayane
Third Episode
Youko-chan, another bowl!
Yes.
Why haven't you put some clothes on?!
It's fine, right?
There's no school today anyway.
It's fine if no one sees it, isn't it?
Somehow, this is getting quite complicated...
Enough already, let me into Shougo's room!
I cannot let you do that.
I have the right to live with Shougo,
as his fiancée!
I'm also Shougo-sama's fiancée.
Just let me...
What?!
That's what Sanji-sama decided.
I can say that too! Shougo's grandfather chose me!
And that was long before you came to this mansion!
Did you know? The latest articles in the will take priority.
You didn't even know him!
Jeez,
it sounds exactly like something that old man would do.
Moka-chan? Mizuchi-sensei?
Well, that's fine too.
I'm sure he was just trying to make Shougo-senpai happy.
That doesn't mean I have to accept it!
Now then, where are our rooms?
Huh?
Do I get the same room as Moka?
If possible, I'd prefer we had separate rooms.
I'd like one facing south, please!
U-Um, why do you need rooms...?
It's because we're Shougo's wives!
What?!
I'm sorry for giving you more work...
No, it's my responsibility.
Besides, I admire your kindness towards others.
I-Is that so?
Sanji-sama was like that too.
He would often pick up stray cats and dogs and feed them...
They're the same as cats and dogs?
I'm really sorry about this.
Jii-chan was so nonchalant about this.
This must be a bother for you…
Not at all! I never thought about it like that.
But if you were engaged to someone they haven't even met, normally...
Sanji-sama...really cared about you, Shougo-sama.
Time after time...
Over and over...
He'd always tell stories about you, looking so happy.
That's why when he mentioned being your fiancée, I didn't hesitate.
Moka, we're leaving now.
Ehh? But it was just getting good!
You might see something even more stimulating if you come along.
Science Laboratory
Gen! Do me from behind!
Gen!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Gen... I love you...
Science Laboratory
Take care, and good luck with the research. (TL: A reference to the ending of Gosenzo San'e)
Even if it is the weekend, the Director-sama shouldn't be having sex at school!
When did you start watching?
So, what do you want?
You couldn't have come here just to peep.
Hey now, it's concerning that thing I asked you to do earlier.
I was just wondering how it's going.
Oh, that ?
I think it'll work out.
But...
There is something I need first.
"Something you need?"
This is a little too high.
Then it's...this one...
I see...
We were this small.
That's true, it can't be helped if he forgot...
Even though... I can't forget...
We beg of you, Shougo!
Please teach us your
relationship techniques!
R-Relationship techniques?
That's right! For Ayane-senpai!
And Moka-chan!
And Mone-sensei!
Please teach us the technique you used that instantly made them fall for you!
There wouldn't be a point in learning something so useless.
A-Ayane-senpai?
There's no problem with me borrowing Shougo, is there?
Sure! With pleasure!
Come.
Y-Yes...
Takuya-sama!
How is it?
Is my candy delicious?
It is very delicious!
That's right, that's right!
I'm your only real fiancée, right?!
Eh? But...
Apparently it's true that Jii-san set Youko-sama as my fiancée...
And I'm sure Moka-chan and Mizuchi-sensei have their reasons...
But the engagement between us wasn't proposed by someone else!
Shougo you....you promised me yourself!
Promise...?
You just want to do them, don't you?
That's why you say such vague things!
N-No, that's not it...
In that case, I'll let you do whatever you want with me!
WHAT is THAT?!
Huh? What do you mean?
You were touching Youko-chan's breasts so much before!
Eh?
You were doing lots of lewd things with Moka-chan and Mizuchi-sensei too!
No, that's...
Are you saying that you don't feel like doing it with me?
Am I not attractive enough?
Um, that's not it...
Whoa there!
Neya-kun...
Are you okay?
I don't feel too well...
Sorry to make you wait, Ayane!
I'll make sure that you feel it!
Whoa! Medium rare!
White and so soft! It's like extremely expensive rump steak!
Shougo, you idiot!
Neya-kun?
Senpai... If you're into that…
Then please say so!
More!
No!!
Once more!
Se-Senpai...!
You're brilliant!
Shougo! Shougo!
Eh? Ayane-senpai?
Yes, she went straight to the back garden without saying a word upon returning.
Garden?
The promise…
This is a sign of our special promise.
Even when we become adults, you mustn't forget it.
Y-Yeah, I won't forget it, Kotone-chan.
Kotone-chan...?
It's not Kotone!
I told you, it's Kotou Ayane!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Eh, um...
It looks like you remembered it wrong.
I'm sorry...
Oh well, it seems that you remember now, so I'll forgive you.
Senpai?
Hey, we're not kids anymore.
We can pick up where we left off, and keep going farther.