School Infirmary
All right, Shougo.
Recover the strength that the sluts have cost you.
Sluts she calls us.
Didn't another of them make this?
Now eat!
Leave nothing behind!
As you wish...
Listen up, Shougo.
I'm first today.
Go easy on the others in P.E..
I need you to be fit later.
Hey, Shougo.
Why didn't you come over yesterday?
I waited for so long.
I'm sorry.
I was a bit busy.
Shougo.
I don't know what's been bothering you since yesterday, but...
Let us cheer you right up again.
Teach, what you see as "cheering up" is a bit...
Quiet.
Let me show you something interesting.
That was mean.
Grow up before you think about swapping the other way.
More importantly, I think Shougo is having trouble.
Please take over, then.
No...
Shougo... I got you all sticky.
It's my turn, Sis.
Yes, yes.
Sorry about that.
You're fine with her too, right?
I came already, so I can't...
Hey, don't let it go to waste.
Ayane...
Don't just stand there.
Alone with my sweetheart
Reiko, Episode 5
Students are meant to be taught here,
so we must be pretty perverted to have sex in the classroom.
Ayane...
I wonder who sits here.
I wonder how the student who went home after school is going to react
when he smells what we did here.
Now, assault me!
Let's spread the smell of sex across the entire classroom.
Can't you do me this favor?
Come on, kick me in the nuts.
At least step on me.
I beg you, everyone.
Please bully me!
Please kick me!
All right, honies!
Walk a new road of happiness with me!
Will you walk it with me?
This is enough!
Don't be embarrassed!
No!
Brilliant!
Look outside, it's getting dark.
Teach.
Still worried?
Or did Mone and the others wear you out?
That's not it.
It's something else.
Then what is it?
I'm feeling miserable.
Has it come that far?
How awful.
Don't make me feel even more miserable.
All right, go home.
I can talk with you about this, but someone more suitable is waiting.
You're right.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Hang in there.
What happened here?
Is this the garden further in?
Reiko?
I've waited here so long for him.
Time passed, the seasons flew by,
and I waited and waited and got tired of waiting.
Even my consciousness started to fade,
but just then a boy came and talked innocently to my portrait.
Yes.
I received a body thanks to the strength he gave me.
Come now.
Reiko.
When I was a little kid, I talked to your portrait a lot,
but forgot about it.
I'm sorry.
But still, some things were meant to stay buried.
Your words had no meaning at first.
They were just noise.
But gradually they made sense,
and once again I started to materialize here.
And before I knew it, you'd become irreplaceable to me.
But...
Just like him, you disappeared to far away.
Is that...?
This is what bound me to this plane.
Even now it supports my mind.
When you were on your way home,
both your height and face were different from what I remembered,
but still I knew it was you.
Finally I could meet you.
Reiko, I...
This is one-sided and unfair.
Technically I'm older than you.
Reiko...
I was a bit confused earlier,
but I was taught how to do this.
I'm sorry.
I teased you a little.
Please, do it.
Don't tease me.
Do it, quick!
Tell me if it hurts.
I'll be fine.
Youko and Ayane already know what it feels like to lose your virginity.
Still, I'm a wee bit scared,
so could you hold my hand?
Sure.
I'll do it.
Thanks.
I'm fine, although you are a little rough.
All right.
Reiko...
I'm coming...
I too...
Oh, no. Don't look at me please.
Reiko.
Yes?
Can we do it again?
Please.
Okay...
All right, that's it!
Well, we're all in the same boat now.
Decide this once and for all, no hard feelings.
I will bring word of whom he picks.
Hey, you're part of this too!
You say something about settling it,
but we are his wives by law of the deep sea.
Right?
This is the surface world!
Far away, far away!
Besides, you two are the same person!
You're both just heaps of mud!
No!
Shougo's is... rising...
Shougo you idiot!
Are you sex-crazed?
That's just who he is, so shall we partake?
Of course, Sis.
What'll you do, Youko?
If Shogou says I can...
Hey, guys!
Why are we getting back to how it used to be?
Reiko, don't hog him.
Grandpa... I guess I really am your grandchild.
A consultation it is... well, I can tell what it is just by looking at your face.
What should I do?
Let's see.
Instead of warning you about the girls,
I think it is important we think about how you can cope with it.
Oh...
I think I know just the person to advise you.
Is that person your boyfriend?
Did you have sex here?
How do you—
Mone must have told you.
Really, now.
I heard he's studying abroad.
Yes.
He'll be back soon, though.
So, about me...
I have a secret plan, Shougo!
Let's go back!
No sleep for you all night!
Help me, Ms. Sakurako!
Hang in there.
Show spirit!
Hey...
Listen, I'll mix you a tonic.
Hang in there until Gen is back!
Do your best!
You can't be serious!