Shougo-sama-!
G-Good morning!
W-What do you mean, "good morning"?!
I'm nearly done, so...!
Shouga-sama, everyone is waiting.
Eh?
SubDESU-H Presents
Yoko-chan, can I get a refill?
Yes.
Why haven't you changed into something normal?!
Don't be so picky.
There's no school today anyway.
No harm done if no one sees it!
My situation’s getting a complicated...
Let me through to Shougo's room!
I cannot let you do that.
I have the right to live with Shougo,
since he's my fiancée!
I'm also engaged to Shougo-sama.
Just let me...
What?!
That's what Sanji-sama chose.
Shougo's grandfather chose me as well!
Way before you came to this mansion!
Did you know? The latest articles in the will take priority.
You didn't even know he existed when I met him!
Jeez,
it sounds like you're talking about gramps again.
Moka-chan? Mizuchi-sensei?
Well, don't let us interrupt.
I bet they were both just trying to do what's best for Shougo-senpai.
That's why I can't let such a statement pass!
Now then, where are our rooms?
Huh?
Do I get the same room as Moka?
If possible, I'd prefer we had separate rooms.
I'd like one facing south, please!
U-Um, what do you mean...?
It's because we're Shougo’s wives!
What?!
I'm sorry for giving you more work...
No, it's my job.
Also, I admire your kindness towards others.
I-Is that so?
Sanji-sama was like that too.
He would often pick up stray cats and dogs and feed them...
They're the same as cats and dogs?
I'm really sorry about this.
My grandfather was so nonchalant about this. I'm sure all of this is a headache for you…
Not at all! I've never considered it to be like that.
But if someone were to become engaged to someone they haven't even met...
Sanji-sama really cared about you, Shougo-sama.
Time after time...
Over and over...
He'd always tell stories about you, as if he was the happiest man in the world.
That's why when he mentioned our engagement, I didn't hesitate.
Moka, we're off soon.
Ehh? But it was just getting good!
You might see something even more interesting if you come along.
Chemistry Preparation Room
Gen! Do me from behind!
Gen!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Gen... I love you...
Chemistry Preparation Room
Take care, and good luck with your research.
Pretty naughty of you to be having sex at school, even if it is the weekend!
How long have you been here?
So, what do you want?
Is it possible you came just to peep at us?
It's concerning that thing I asked you about earlier.
I was just wondering how it's going.
Oh, that thing?
I think it'll work out.
But...
I require something first.
"Require something?"
This is a little too high.
I wonder if it's this...
I see...
We were this small.
Well, I guess it can't be helped if he forgot...
Even though... I can't forget...
We beg of you, Shougo!
Please teach us your relationship techniques!
R-Relationship techniques?
That's right! For Ayane-senpai!
And Moka-chan!
And Mone-sensei!
Please teach us the technique you used that instantly made them fall for you!
There wouldn't be any use learning such a thing.
A-Ayane-senpai?
Can I borrow Shougo for a moment?
Sure! With pleasure!
Come.
Y-Yes...
Takayu-sama!
How is it?
Is my cock delicious?
It is very delicious!
That's right, of course it is!
I'm your only real fiancée, right?!
Eh? But...
Apparently it's true that grandfather set Yoko-sama as my fiancée...
And I'm sure Moka-chan and Mizuchi-sensei have their reasons...
But the engagement between us wasn't proposed by someone else!
You promised me yourself!
Promise...?
You just want to have sex with them, don't you?
That's why you say such vague things!
N-No, that's not it...
Then-! I'll let you do it with me whenever you want!
What’s wrong with you?!
Huh? What do you mean?
You were feeling up Yoko-chan's breasts before!
Eh?
You were doing lots of lewd things with Moka-chan and Mizuchi-sensei too!
No, that’s...
Are you saying that you don't feel like doing it with me?
Am I not good enough?
Um, that's not it...
Oops!
Neya-kun...
Are you okay?
I don't feel too well...
Sorry to make you wait, Ayane!
I'll make sure that we have fun!
Whoa! Medium rare!
White and so soft! It’s like extremely expensive rump steak!
Shougo, you idiot!
Neya-kun?
Senpai... If you like that…
Then please say so!
More!
No!!
Once more!
Se-Senpai...!
You're brilliant!
Shougo! Shougo!
Eh? Ayane-senpai?
Yes, she went straight to the back garden without saying a word upon returning.
Garden?
The promise…
This is a sign of our special promise.
Even if we become adults, you mustn't forget it.
Y-Yeah, I won't forget it, Kotone-chan.
Kotone-chan...?
It's not Kotone!
I said, it’s Kotou Ayane!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Eh, um...
I guess you just remembered it wrong.
I'm sorry...
Oh well, it seems that you remember now, so I'll forgive you.
Senpai?
Hey, we're not kids anymore.
We can go all the way.