Infirmary
Now Shougo, why don't you replenish your strength after being abused by those thieving cats!
She said "thieving cats" right?
Even though the one who made this is a cat too.
Well then, please eat. You better not leave anything.
Ri-Right.
Listen, Shougo.
Today I'm going first, so don't wear yourself out in P.E.
Save your strength for later.
Hey, Shougo-senpai, why didn't you come to see me yesterday?
I've been waiting for you this whole time.
So-Sorry... it's just...
Shougo.
Even though I don't know what are you've been worried about since yesterday...
we're always here to make you feel better.
Sensei, I don't think I understand what you said earlier.
Be silent. I'll show you something interesting.
Ah... Senpai, you're so mean.
It's still 100 years too soon for you to beat me at this, you know?
Besides, Shougo is suffering right now.
Then, please let me know when he's cumming.
No!
Shougo-senpai, I made your face all sticky.
Onee-chan, it's my turn now, isn't it?
Sure... sure!
Sorry, but I'm sure you can fill her up, right?
I'm still cumming from earlier, so it's okay to let it out.
Oh, oh! We can't waste it.
Ayane-san...
Please stop glaring at us like that.
Anata Dake Konbanwa
Reiko
Fifth Chapter
Even though everyone elee is in class...
we're having sex like this in a classroom.
We're pretty deviant, huh?
Senpai?
Who does this seat belong to?
What?
When whoever has seat returns to class,
I wonder how he'll react will be when he realizes this seat is covered with our indecent smells.
Now, come give it to me.
Let's cover the whole classroom with our indecent smell!
Why don't you understand?
Why don't you try to kick me as hard as you can?
Kick me hard would be even better!
Please, everyone! Tease me! Kick me!
Now then, honeys!
Come at me so we can walk down this new road of bliss together!
Will you walk it with me?
Tha-that's impossible!
You don't have to be embarrassed!
No~!
Brilliant...
My my, you're fading into the dusk, aren't you?
Sensei.
Worrying about something?
Or... are you already tired of Mone and the others?
Not at all! That's not it...
Well, what is it?
I feel so ashamed...
You're worried about something like that?
Good for you, good for you.
Please don't make me anymore miserable than I already am.
Then, why don't you go home? I'm sure there's someone waiting there who will solve your problem.
Eh?
You're right.
Then I'll take my leave.
Be careful.
Do your best.
What is with this place?
Inside the garden?
Reiko-san?
I'm always waiting for you to come here.
Time passes, the seasons change and I'm  always waiting, waiting. I can't wait any longer.
That time... when I was about to lose consciousness...
There was an innocent boy who would talk to me when I was about to fade away.
Eh?
Yes, because of those people, I am able to be here with a body, like this.
Shall we?
Reiko-san.
I...always talked to you when I was a kid...
Yet, I forgot all about it.
Sorry, but...
It feels so much better when I don't remember.
"The first time..."
These words don't mean anything to me, they are just another thing that will soon be forgotten.
But the more I tried to ignore those words, my consciousness has kept them alive all this time.
And I don't know why, but they're something irreplaceable and precious to me.
Eh?
But...
You're the same person who's going to leave me someday.
What's that?
This is something that has been my family for a long time.
It has been close to my heart for a long time.
When you came back to this house...
Even though your face and body have changed...
I knew that it was you, Shougo-sama.
After all this time, I can finally see you again.
Reiko-san... I'm-
It's not fair that it's just me.
Since I'm older than you.
Re... Reiko-san...
Though I'm not sure about everything that happened the first time we met...
I'll show you that I know a lot about this.
I'm sorry, I teased you a little.
No...
Please... please... don't tease me anymore.
Please, hurry up and give it to me!
Please tell me if it hurts, okay?
I'll be fine. I've had the experience with Youko-san and Ayane-san.
E-Eh?
But, I'm still a little scared... Will you hold my hand?
Sure.
Here I go.
Yes.
It looks like I'll be okay if you get a little rougher.
Got it.
Re-Reiko-san.
I.'m gonna...
Me... me too!
No, please don't look at me!
Reiko-san.
Yes?
Can we do it one more time?
Please...do...
Then...
Aaall right, that's enough!
Well, anyway, I'm sure everyone here understands the situation.
We must settle the score, right here, right now.
Regardless of who is chosen by Shougo-sama, I just want to serve him for the rest of my life.
Wait a minute, you're suddenly taking the mistress position?!
We don't have to settle anything, we're all rightfully his wives anyway.
Right~?
This is the human world, the other world is the other world!
Besides, two of you are the same person, right? Don't take this so lightly!
Uh... No...
Shougo-sama's...
Got bigger...
N-No...
You idiot, Shougo!
At a time like this?! Are you an ape?!
Since we're all here, why don't we join in?
Yes, Onee-chan.
How about you, Youko-chan?
As long as Shougo-sama agrees.
HEY, why are you all ignoring me?!
Hey, Reiko-chan, get away from that!
Jii-chan...
I'm...
really your grandson, after all!
You said you wanted to discuss something with me... Well, I can already tell just by looking at you.
What... should I do... now?
Let's see...
I'll warn those girls, but what you're going to do is the important part.
!....There is someone you could ask about this.
Could that person be... Sensei's lover?
The one you had sex with in here?
How do you-
So...Mone told you...
Jeez...
I thought he was studying abroad?
He is.
But, he'll be coming back soon.
Um, by the way...what about me?
Ah, I found Shougo-kun!
Let's go home, shall we?
I won't let you sleep tonight.
Sakurako-sensei, help me!
Do your best.
Eh?
Show some guts!
Um...
Don't give up or let your spirit waver! Until Gen comes back, fight!
Charge!
Come oooooon~!!!