Promise...?
This is the proof of our special promise.
Don't forget it when you become an adult.
Y-yeah,
I won't forget it, Kotone-chan.
Kotone…chan?
It's not Kotone.
I'm Kotou Ayane!
How many times should I tell you?
Eh? Uhm..
After all, you remember it wrong.
I- I'm…sorry.
It's fine now.
You remembered properly it anyway.
I will forgive you.
Senpai?
Hey, we're not kids anymore.
We can pick up where we left off, and keep going farther.
Anata Dake
Konbanwa
Momone
Episode 4
Look, my hands are wet because of you.
Don't push yourself.
Senpai?
I'm happy.
I'm...finally one with you.
This is finally getting interesting.
Huh..
Getting interesting… eh?
Senpai…
Kotone-chan.
I'm at my limit..
Me too.
I... I...
Hey, Shougo…
What is it?
The next time you call me Kotone I'll hit you.
I'll be careful…
I- I'm sorry.
Sorry, the sakura were just so beautiful…
Shougo and I had to look.
Well, with that said...
The circumstances are the same for Senpai too.
What are you talking about?
Sakura. You're having other cherry blossoms-viewing picnic.
You peeked right?
In this place, the voices can be heard in far places.
You too, weren't you making a loud voice in Shougo's room early this morning?
This is my house and,
Shougo-sama is my fiancée.
Who is his fiancée?
There are other people in here,
Have you no shame?!
You're intruding forcibly!
Don't go saying that on your own!
Hey.
Why don't we decide this?
Decide what?
Let's see who's the one suitable for Shougo.
In majority decision.
That's unreasonable.
Who will vote for Youko-chan?
Me!
Who will vote for Ayane-chan?
Then, who will vote for me?
Me!
Yay! I got 2.
Hey, it's scripted even how we look at it.
No, it's beautiful sisterly love, right?
I won't accept it.
I won't accept it!
Well, Shougo-sama is the one who'll decide.
Oh, that's right.
That's right, that's right!
Shougo?
Well Shougo, who are you voting for?
Who are you choosing?
Well? Well? Well!?
Oh, it's a visitor.
I came here by Sakurako-sama's orders.
I'm Beatrice.
Then, what is your business here?
What business does this this Beatrice-san have here?
I came here to collect Shougo-sama's sperm.
Eh?
If you happen to need help, I've been ordered to help you.
How is it?
No! Absolutely NOT!
I see.
That is a problem.
Then, after doing it with any of you...
I don't mind taking it from the vagina.
If possible, I'd like the freshest sample.
Eh?
Understood.
H..hey.
I'll borrow the room in the back.
Hey… what are you doing?
No..
Why is she so strong?
I can't get away....
Don't worry. This is thinner than Shougo-sama's.
No.. no.. no...
Stop it!!!!
How humiliating.
Umm...
Yes?
That... What are you going to do with it?
I wasn't told that much.
I see...
Oh and..
Mone-sama.
Moka-sama.
There's a message from Sakurako-sama.
She said a battle should be decided fairly.
Well then, I'll be going now.
That bitch Sakurako..
It's her revenge for the prep room.
What..?
What..? What..?
Stop, that's enough.
That Mone is a doll made by soil.
Don't worry about it.
Soil?
Doll?
What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Ah... This is a pain.
Are you surprised?
Actually...
I'm a hermit who lives in a mountain far far away.
So..
I can change my appearance freely.
So why is such a suspicious person Shougo's wife?
It's because of Sanji-sama, isn't it?
Correct.
Long ago, when Shougo was born,
That old man made a doll made of tree branches for remembrance.
But how horrible he is, he used the branch of the sacred tree.
A doll?
And then, that old man dropped that doll in the pond where I lived,
And that ritual was to offer Shougo to me.
Ahhhh.. no…
So that's why you're my wife..
Well in short,
I'm an existence higher than you girls.
You can't compete with me.
You're not even a human! How can you be his wife?
You can't even submit a marriage registration, so...
I'll be the wife in the family register.
Hey!
Don't try to take advantage of the confusion!
Yes!
I'm his wife in ways that surpass human family registers!
I'm tied with more than the principal love.
How shameless.
You're not after love, all you want is sex, isn't it!?
Jii-chan you idiot!
Sakura-sama.
I obtained it without any disturbance.
Good work.
I'd like you to prepare the laboratory.
Yes.
Then..
Did you decide?
I'll leave it to you.
Reiko..san?
y
u
r
i
Is Reiko-chan here?
That's.. I feel somethings weird.
I can't sense Reiko-san at all.
It seems..
you're feeling it.
I didn't mean feeling like that..
Sensei, didn't you say she's not bad before?
S.. so.
You can see it right?
Are you worried about Reiko-chan that much?
That's...
Look into her...
about what she really is.
Do that and I'll tell you.
Ohhh.
It bloomed beautifully.
Yes.
It finally bloomed this morning.
Ohhh.
They are cute flowers, huh?
I received it from Mone-sensei but,
She said there's a deadly poison on the flower.
That was just a joke.
You!!!!
You were so cute.
That's...
If I'm going to research..
It should be here...
Ah..
Reiko-san and...
Me?
That man is Rokutaku-sama.
Yoko-san..
Rokutaku-sama is Sanji-sama's father.
Meaning Shougo-sama's great grandfather.
Great grandfather..?
I was told by Sanji-sama before...
Rokutaku-sama is Reiko-sama's former fiancée.
Eh?
But..
Reiko-sama died due to illness...
So Rokutaku-sama got married to Reiko-sama's younger sister.
They had an official ceremony.
That was when Sanji-sama born.
It's almost as if you're jealous.
That day when I first met you, Shougo-sama...
I think the reason I forgot myself and got daring is...
because of Reiko-sama.
That is what I think.
But..
The thing I want to do is..
Shougo-sama.
Shougo-sama...
My... mouth...
boobs...
All... all... belong to you, Shougo-sama!
No!
I'm sorry.
I think she liked him.
Aaah! Why am I worrying about it this much?
I..
Huh? Did she have such a kind smile in this picture?
I see.
Because of the light...
This is it.
That's right… I was always talking to Reiko-san here.
Look, I drew Reiko-chan's picture.
Oh yes,
Here.
It's a stone I picked up in the river.
Isn't it beautiful?
And a dandelion!
Huh..?
Oh this!
I won this in the lottery today.
I'll give this to Reiko-chan.
Why did I forget until now?
If I had remembered, I could have shared even more things with her.
Even though we're always together.
I can't feel her anymore!
It's almost as if you're jealous.