The promise...?
This is the proof of our special promise.
Don’t forget it when you become an adult.
Y-yeah,
I won’t forget it, Kotone-chan.
Kotone…chan?
I’m not Kotone.
Didn’t I tell you I’m Kotou Ayane?
How many times should I tell you?
Eh? Uhm..
After all, you remember it wrong.
I’m… sorry.
It's alright.
You remembered it anyway.
I will forgive you.
Sempai?
We’re not kids anymore.
I’ll make this go beyond that.
W
Anata Dake
Konbanwa
Momone
W
Episode 4
Look, my hands are wet because of yours.
Don’t push yourself.
Sempai?
I’m happy.
I’m finally one with you.
This is getting fun.
Huh..
Getting fun… eh?
Sempai…
Kotone-chan.
I’m at my limit..
Me too.
I... I...
Hey Shougo…
What is it?
I’ll punch you if you call me Kotone next time.
I’ll be careful…
I’m sorry.
Sorry, the Sakura was so beautiful that’s why…
Me and Shougo took time.
Well then,
The condition is the same for Sempai too.
What are you talking about?
Sakura. You’re having other cherry blossoms-viewing picnic.
You peeked right?
In this place, the voices can be heard in far places.
You too, weren't you making a loud voice in Shougo’s room early this morning?
This is my house and,
Shougo-sama is my fiancé.
Who’s the fiancé?
There are other people in here,
Aren’t you feeling immodest of yourself?
You’re intruding forcibly and
Don’t say something on your own!
Hey,
Why don’t we decide this?
Decide what?
Let's see who’s the one suitable for Shougo.
In majority decision.
That’s unreasonable.
Who will vote for Youko-chan?
Me!
Who will vote for Ayane-chan?
Then, who will vote for me?
Me!
Yay! I got 2.
Hey, it's scripted even how we look at it.
No, I’m beautiful and we’re suited, right?
I won’t accept it.
I won’t accept it!
Well, Shougo-sama is the one who’ll decide.
Oh, yes.
Yes yes!
Shougo?
Who are you voting for?
Who are you choosing?
Who? Who!?
Oh, it’s a visitor.
I came here by Sakurako-sama’s orders.
I’m Beatris.
Then, what is your business here?
Then, what is that Beatris’ business here?
I came here to take Shougo-sama’s sperm.
Eh?
If you need help, I’m ordered to help you.
How is it?
No! it’s a big NO!
I see.
I’m in trouble.
Then, how about after doing it to any of you.
I don’t mind if I can take it from the vagina.
I want to take a fresh one if possible.
Eh?
I understand.
H..hey.
Let me borrow the room over there.
Hey… what are you doing?
No..
Does she have insane strength?
I can go away..
Don’t worry this is thinner than Shougo-sama’s.
No.. no.. no...
Stop it!!!!
How regretful.
Umm...
Yes?
Well... What are you going to do with that?
I wasn't told about that
I see...
Oh and..
Mone-sama.
Muka-sama.
There’s a message from Sakurako-sama.
The detail is have a fair fight.
Well then, I’ll be going now.
That Sakurako..
It's her revenge in preparation room.
What..?
What..? What..?
Till there.
That Mone is a doll made by soil.
So don’t mind it.
Soil?
Doll?
What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Ah... This is troublesome.
Are you surprised?
To tell the truth,
I’m a hermit who lives in a far far mountain.
So..
I can change my appearance freely.
So why is that doubtful person Shougo’s wife?
Are you Senji-sama?
Correct.
When Shougo was born,
That old man made a doll made of tree branches for remembrance.
But how horrible he is, he used the branch of the sacred tree.
A doll?
And then, that old man dropped that doll in the pond where I lived,
And that ritual was to offer Shougo to me.
Ahhhh.. no…
So that’s why you’re my wife..
Well in short,
I’m a being higher than you.
You can’t compete with me.
You’re not even a human and who are you to call yourself a wife?
You can’t even submit a marriage contract so,
I’m the wife in the family registration.
Hey!
Don’t steal a march in the middle of confusion!
Yes!
I’m registered as a wife more than the principal rules of the human.
I’m tied with more than the principal love.
How shameless.
You’re after the sex not the love right?
Grandpa you dummy!
Sakura-sama.
I obtained it without any disturbance.
Good work.
Please prepare in the laboratory.
Yes.
Then..
Did you decide?
Here I go.
Reiko..san?
y
u
r
i
You ask me if Reiko-chan is here?
That’s.. I feel somethings weird.
I can’t feel Reiko-san.
I think..
You’re feeling it.
That’s not what I mean.
Sensei said that’s not a bad thing before.
S.. so.
You can see it right?
Are you worried about Reiko-chan that much?
That’s...
How about research about her.
If who really she is.
If you do that then, I’ll tell you.
Ohhh.
It bloomed beautifully.
Yes.
It finally bloomed this morning.
Ohhh.
It’s a cute flower.
I received it from Mone-sensei but,
She said there’s a deadly poison on the flower.
But it’s just a joke.
You!!!!
You were so cute.
That’s...
If I’m going to research..
I think this place should do...
Ah..
Reiko-san and...
Me?
That man is Rokutaku-sama.
Yoko-san..
Rokutaku-sama is Sanji-sama’s father.
Meaning Shougo-sama’s great grand father.
Great grand father..?
I was told by Sanji-sama before but..
Rokutaku-sama is a former fiancé of Reiko-sama.
Eh?
But..
Reiko-sama died with an illness
So Rokutaku-sama got married to Reiko-sama’s younger sister.
And they gone to continent.
And that was the time Sanji-sama born.
It's like you’re jealous.
When I first met Shougo-sama.
I think the reason I forgot myself and got daring is.
Because of Reiko-sama.
Sometimes I think of it.
But..
The thing I want to do is..
Shougo-sama.
Shougo-sama...
My... mouth...
The boobs...
All... all... is Shougo-sama’s!
No!
I’m sorry.
I think she liked him.
Why am I got annoyed?
I..
Does she smiles so kind in this picture?
I see.
Because of the light...
This is it.
Yes… I was always talking to Reiko-san.
Look, I drew Reiko-chan’s picture.
Oh yes,
Here.
It’s a stone I picked up in the river.
Isn’t it beautiful?
And a dandelion!
Huh..?
Oh this!
I won this in the lottery today.
I’ll give this to Reiko-chan.
Why did I forget?
If I remembered, I had shared to her many things.
Even we’re together always.
I can’t feel her anymore.
Seems like you’re jealous.