Nee-san, I can't keep doing this...
I have someone I like now.
So... I'm sorry.
What's going on, Minato-senpai?
Right now? Sure, I don't mind.
Asking to see a girl at this hour...
I could be raped, you know.
I'm just kidding.
I'll be on my way soon.
However, Senpai...
I'm not satisfied with just being loved.
Apologies for asking you out so late.
It's fine. What's up?
You seem different, Chitose.
Is that so?
Well, I had to leave in a hurry, so I couldn't dress up.
You look very cute.
Thank you very much.
I actually love you, Chitose.
I know.
Then let's go out.
I must decline.
Why?
Weren't you the one who dumped me?
No! I was just Nee-san's slave.
I couldn't even consider going out with anyone.
But you were able change me, Chitose.
I changed you?
You're my ideal girl.
You're the greatest girl that does the worst things to me.
If you talk like that, this Onee-san might have to scold you.
That doesn't matter.
It's got to be you, Chitose.
You're a true pervert, liking mean things done to you.
How about this?
From now on you're my obedient dog, Senpai.
If you don't move until I tell you to,
I wouldn't mind going out with you.
Hey, what do you mean?
Don't move. Okay?
What are you going to do?
You'll soon find out.
Can we interrupt now?
Who is that?
Hey hey.
You guys getting it on already?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's fine.
Are you Chitose-san, the client?
Thank you in advance.
What a cutie!
Thank you very much.
Wasn't it only the two of us that we requested on the forum?
He's just going to watch.
What's the meaning of this?
You stay put, Senpai.
So that's how it is?
Very nice.
Let's move to the hotel then, shall we?
No.
Let's do it here.
Despite your looks you're actually a huge pervert, aren't you Chitose-san?
You even got people watching.
I don't mind doing it outside.
I'm okay with too.
Okay, show us your cocks.
Let's get started!
I think I will enjoy this!
Why have I...
Gotten hard?
Hey, help me out too.
Sure thing.
This feels amazing!
Chitose-chan, are you fine with just leaving him?
Uncut cocks aren't that clean after all.
Hey, don't tell them that!
That's rude towards women.
Chitose-chan prefers cut cocks too, right?
Please stroke it harder.
Chitose-chan, let me cum!
Me too, please.
You two are way too eager!
This is amazing, I might get addicted!
Thank you for the wonderful cumshot.
Hey, is that guy jerking off?
Seems like your boyfriend is also a huge pervert.
He's my pet, not my boyfriend.
Although we agreed to only do felatio,
shall we keep going?
I can't unfortunately.
We can't be done only after one shot!
I don't want to keep Senpai waiting.
He's waiting?
It seems like he wants to see more.
Is that so, Senpai?
You're the worst.
Thigh-fuck only. We're not going all the way.
Fine with me!
Round two, huh.
Idiot...
Your thighs feel amazing!
Sure is nice to be antiquated with these young and perky breasts.
Ouch!
Don't twist it so much!
Your cock, it's gotten harder.
Even though you just came so much...!
Doesn't it feel better than your Senpai's?
It certainly feels amazing, but...!
I wonder what he's feeling?
Like I would know!
Aren't you going to try and stop us?
His cock is about to go inside her.
Rather, don't you want to see it go in?
No, that's-!
No, don't thrust so much!
It's really going to go in!
Stop it!
Are you sure it's a good idea to interfere?
You'll be going against her command.
But, if you don't stop it, she's going to get it.
What are you gonna do?
I...!
That's right, you don't need to move.
We got his permission.
He said it's fine to have sex.
You can't hold back much more anyway, right?
Senpai, if this goes on, I'm really going to be raped...
But, you said not to move!
Please, please help me!
If I move, you said you won't date me.
Are you fine with me being raped?
You're the worst. Die!
Well then, let's dig right in!
You actually put it in!
Senpai, don't just sit there! Help me!
What's with that reaction?
I'm being raped, you know!
I don't think he was expecting this turn of events.
Am I afraid...?
So tight!
Oh my, you're crying?
Man, I'm gonna cum soon!
You're gonna cum? But you're not wearing a condom!
Stop, don't do it! Not inside!
I know you want it.
No I don't!
I don't want your semen!
It's hot!
This pussy is amazing! I want to be like this forever.
It's my turn next.
Sure thing, should I clean her up?
No more... Stop it...
It's fine, no worries.
Her butthole seems lonely,
so I think I'll invite myself in there instead.
What a firm and lean butt.
Don't spread it-!
What a beautiful butthole.
I haven't even given Senpai my anal virginity yet!
Oh, so it's brand new!
So, let's stop this...
Please listen to me!
We can't do anal!
Stop it, it's too much!
If I don't loosen it, it'll be worse you know.
Her pussy is tightening again!
Chitose-chan, are you starting to feel good?
I'm not starting to feel good-!
I think we're all set to go.
Don't put your cock in!
Two cocks are inside me!
It hurts!
My butt's going to tear! Stop it!
It'll break if you thrust so much!
It's going to feel too good if you keep going!
My hips... My hips are giving out!
Don't cum inside of me!
If you let out anymore...!
I'm gonna cum...
It's going to blow me away...!
I'm sorry... Please stop already!
I feel sick...
You're still jerkin' it?
What a joke!
Chitose-san, let's have fun again sometime.
Why didn't you help me?
I was raped, you know.
You said not to move...
I hate you, Senpai.
D-Don't say that...
I won't forgive you.
I'm sorry! I'll do anything!
What a helpless little brat.
If you can hold back from cumming, I'll forgive you.
But if you do...
I never want to see you again.
Okay.
So tight-!
Shut up, don't talk!
Who cares about your shitty cock?
I wonder if you're going to cum just from putting it in?
What a shitty monkey cock!
Your cock is throbbing, thrashing about inside me.
You're being such a girl with your uncut cock!
What an unsightly farm animal you are!
Shut it, you ungraceful pig!
It's disgusting!
Your balls are swollen and ready to burst...
You damn shitty ape, you're truly one of a kind!
It's not like I'm not feeling good or anything!
If it's going to be like this, maybe I prefer those other cocks from before?
Are you frustrated?
There's nothing to blame but your own shitty cock that's not allowed to cum.
Don't show your unsightly pig face ever again.
You shitty quickshot uncut monkey!
Go on, cum! Cum!
Go on, let it out everywhere!
Become a slave to my pussy!
Go on and spend the rest of your life imagining my pussy.
It's time to say goodbye, Senpai.
Although it wasn't long, I enjoyed our time together.
Did you forget about not showing your face ever again?
Can't be helped. I'm a helpless little brat, after all.
I've forgotten all about it.
You really are helpless.
Senpai.
If you show me your cock right now, I'll go out with you.
Really, is that all?
Hey, what's he doing?!
A pervert?
Seriously?
Senpai, you...
...now belong to me.
Translation     Tax Peace
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Editing            SRF
Thank god it wasn't NTR? - Shikkaku Fansubs