This is a family gathering.
Why am I here?
I didn't go to work specifically
because of this meeting.
Dad, please explain things quickly.
Yeah, hold on a sec.
Alright. Let's get the Hanabishi
family gathering started.
Dad, what's the point of this meeting?
Starting this summer, you're
all going to live together.
What? I'm gonna live here?
Of course. You must ask your
parents for permission though.
Wait a minute, did you say I need
permission from my parents?
So you mean, we get to all live together?
Ahhh, so we're living together?
Ahh, well then.
No, no, no! I'll be the only guy!
Although we're really close,
living together is different.
Dad.
Saori-nee, you disagree too?
So that means.
I could take care of Kou-chan
from morning til night right!?
We have really different opinions.
Yeah, yeah! I want to eat a lot
together with Kou-chan too!
He might be able to massage me as well.
What the hell are you people talking about.
I really don't care. It makes no
difference weather he lives here or not.
Are you saying that so I get hurt?
In conclusion, all daughters
are in favor of living together.
There's one more thing though.
There's still more!?
This is the really important part.
In fact, I actually have an appointment
with Kouki-kun's father, Akihiro.
I want you to marry one of my girls.
Old man... What do you mean!?
Akihiro and I have agreed that we would
like to become a true family one day.
So. I want you to decide who you
want to marry by the end of summer.
But I see them all as sisters.
Can you decide who you'd like to marry?
But don't.
They also have the right to choose as well?
I don't mind that at all.
Yuri-nee!?
I... I... I don't mind at all!
I don't don't have a problem with Kou-chan.
Momo-nee, Saori-nee.
Anzu, what about you?
I...
I don't have any feelings for Kouki.
That idiot.
And that concludes the family gathering.
Kouki-kun, this summer I leave to you my girls.
What do you mean "Leave to you"?
Tomorrow your parents and
us will be flying to America.
Mom and Dad are leaving too?
That's right.
How could they be so casual about this!?
Kouki-kun.
Aunt Koume.
You have to believe in yourself.
If you try to hide, I can find you.
Aunt?
That's right.
If you don't choose one of my girls.
I could definitely be one of your brides.
Aunt! Why are you so suddenly being.
Hmm? Are you not satisfied with me?
Although I am a mother of 4, I'm still a hot MILF.
Aunt! Why are you talking like that!?
I don't wana hear it!
Kou-chan, you're awake.
Were you having a nightmare? Are you ok?
Momo-nee.
It looks like you have a fever.
Is Saori-nee alright?
Saori-chan also has a fever, but Anzu-chan
is taking care of her. So just relax.
I see.
In your dream, you said you wanted
to decide who to take as a fiance.
Because of all the problems we've had.
Kou-chan always looks sad.
The others have also come to notice it.
Momo-nee, what should I do?
Yuri, Momo, Sakura, and also Anzu.
We're all like different flowers blooming.
And Kouki-kun is shinning on us all.
If Kou-chan were to stop sparkling,
we would all wither away.
And Kou-chan, we all promised, right?
Promise?
Momo-nee.
Kou-chan.
It feels so good.
Kou-chan really love's his sister's boobs doesn't he?
Sister... I...
I'll get undressed.
Kou-chan's thing looks really happy.
Kou-chan's thing is so... hot.
Wait, don't cum yet!
I'll squeeze out your sauce
using the boobs you really like.
Kou-chan is about to cum!
I didn't expect it to be so bitter!
You shouldn't force yourself to drink it.
No way! This is also part of you!
Your cum shouldn't be wasted.
Kou-chan.
Kou-chan is acting like a baby.
Your sucking so good!
Your sister... Is cumming!
My breasts feel so good.
Momo-nee.
Nooo, don't touch me there!
I'm still super sensitive... Please don't.
That feels so good!
No.
Momo-nee, are you ok?
Hey... You didn't listen to me.
I'm sorry.
It's ok, I love Kou-chan anyway.
Kou-chan, are you ok?
I don't want you to get the
fever, but I just can't resist.
It's alright, I'll accept Kou-chan's fever.
Come on, Kou-chan.
Kou-chan, it's so hard!
It's going to the very end!
Yes!
So fierce, so fierce!
It's in my most sensitive place!
Kou-chan! Don't touch my boobs now!
I love it! I love it! Kou-chan!
Kou-chan is driving me crazy!
I promise!
Oh! Kouki, are you ok?
Yeah, I feel alright. Sorry to worry you.
Don't apologize to me, apologize to Momo-nee.
Thank's to you now she's sick.
How about you Saori-nee? Are you feeling better?
Saori-nee?
Oh, yeah. Sorry to have you all worried.
I'll most definitely keep in better health.
There's no need to force yourself.
Hey Kou-chama.
Summer vacation is coming to and end.
Dad is returning tomorrow.
Kou-chama, who are you gonna choose?
Hmm... about that.
Kouki, your no longer sick right?
Let's play a game!
While you were sick, I bought a new game.
What?
The looser will be punished afterwards.
Hey, hurry! Let's go!
Wait, Anzu-chan?
Well, today is the last day of summer vacation.
Sister! Stop playing games.
You said that you didn't have any
feelings toward Kou-cama yourself.
That...
Did you suddenly change your mind
about being Kou-sama's bride?
Huh? Why would I want to be
his bride? That's impossible!
If that's the case, then you shouldn't touch him at all!
Now, go away!
You all love him right.
What would be the point of him looking for a bride.
Keep your Kouki!
Anzu-chan!
Kouki! Chase after Anzu quick!
No... Kou-chan, you're so wild!
Sister.
Since when... Since when do you
care so much about your brother?
I really love Kou-cama.
When you two marry.
I'm going to leave the house.
As adults, we can't all love Kou-cama... right?
Kouki was my first love... It's clear I love him is it not?
So why did you let Kou-cama pursue her!?
Isn't it obvious?
Anzu also loved Kouki-kun.
If I was too selfish about my own feelings.
Kouki would worry about not hurting Anzu's feelings.
Momo-nee can't be left alone
to take care of the household.
What do you think would happen
if we had to worry about this?
You dropped out of school and
now you want to leave the house.
You can't make up for that lost time.
Every time I look at you... I worry.
I love Kouki, but I also love you,
and don't want to lose you.
Momo-nee, Saori, and also Anzu feel this way as well.
You all don't want to be alone.
Therefore, I cannot lie to myself about this.
Well anyways... I'm the older sister.
Kouki, I leave Anzu to you.
Kouki is just so stupid.
You got Saori-nee so angry.
Kouki is gonna marry Saori.
How stupid! I haven't done anything
to give up on in the first place.
The truth is, I love Kouki.
I was just too late to realize it.
Kouki will never find me here.
Kouki is an idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Forgive me for not being able to find
you in this deserted place sooner.
Kouki!?
Why did you come here?
Weren't you gonna marry Saori?
Not really... Anzu-chan, don't
you remember our promise?
When we were little, we all promised to get married.
That can't possibly be correct!
Weather it's correct or not is my choice to make.
Therefore Anzu-chan, I want you
to tell me how you really feel.
How I feel?
Damn it. Fine! I get it.
From now on, these are my true feelings.
Kouki, I really wana do the ecchi things with you.
Like you've done with the others.
What?
Don't be surprised... I already
know what you've done
Yeah... that's right.
Kiss me again.
One more time.
Your hands, they're so warm.
Wait! Kouki!
Don't just look at me naked like this.
It's really embarrassing.
Stop staring so much!
I know mine are smaller than the others!
No, Anza-chan's breasts are cute.
Don't say that with such a straight face.
Don't just say that.
My breasts are being... licked by Kouki!
No!
Ahh, only my nipples!
This is so direct.
Idiot! Don't go there!
Kouki, you're such a dirty pervert!
Ahh, there!
No! That's super sensitive!
At this rate I'm gonna cum!
Kouki, let's do it.
Kouki, please hurry. Put it in!
It's inside! Oww, It's so deep!
Are you ok?
Yeah, I just couldn't resist it anymore, Kouki.
Please go deeper.
Ahhh, it's piercing me!
This is dangerious! I'm gonna lose my mind!
Kouki, give me more. Hurry!
I'm doing it with Kouki!
If you are too loud, others will hear!
It's just... It's coming out by itself.
With this... we love each other.
I can't think of anything else than just Kouki.
It's alright. Cum inside!
Kouki! I love you! I love you! I love you! I love you! I love you!!!
Eh... It's a text from dad.
What does it say?
Tell Kouki the following:
Tomorrow we are going to be
conducting the wedding ceremony.
I want you to decide who you will marry.
I'll marry Kouki!
No! Kouki should marry me first!
What? I'll marry Kouki too!
Umm, me too!
I'm the one who will marry him first!
That can't be! Kouki can only marry one person!
All of you want to be his bride?
Uhh, Kouki-chan!
When I grow up, I want to marry all of you!
But I told you, you can only marry one person!
Japanese saw says so!
Then I'll become prime minister and change the law!
Then we could all get married together!
Kouki!
Kou-chan.
Kouki-chan!
Kouki!
I can't just choose one.
Because I love all of you!