Only one more week until summer vacation's over.
I have to choose a fiancée from one of my sisters by then.
How am I supposed to do that?
Maybe I'm just being selfish by wanting our
relationship as siblings to continue forever.
Fiancée is quartet of elder sisters
Mornin...
Good morning, Kou-chan.
Second
daughter
Momone Hanabishi
Kouki, you little...
Even if it's summer vacation, don't you
think you're sleeping a little too much?
Why are you in your school uniform, Anzu-chan?
Because I have remedial classes.
4th
daughter
Anzu Hanabishi
Aren't you supposed to be focusing
on your entrance exams?
Come on, let's go.
Eldest
Daughter
Yurina Hanabishi
See you later.
Have a good day.
Have a wonderful day.
Good morning, Kou-chama.
Saori Hanabishi
Thanks as always, Saori-nee.
Think nothing of it.
I am simply fulfilling my duty as the maid of this household.
Please enjoy your meal.
It's not fair if you're the only one
getting praised, Saori-chan.
I made some really sweet cookies for him too.
Um, if you don't mind me asking,
how much sugar did you add?
Well, I put so much in. I don't really know.
Didn't you have plans to meet with
your club at school today?
Whoops! I completely forgot!
Okay, I'll see you later.
See you later.
Have a good day.
Do you want some cookies?
I've already eaten breakfast, so I'll pass.
So it's up to me to finish all these cookies?
Saori-nee?
Yes?
Anything I can help with?
Kou-chama?
Ah, yes.
Let me see...
It is a maid's duty to do tasks that her master
does not want to do. However...
It's fine. I'll help however I can.
Th-Then if it's not too much trouble,
could I ask you to get the groceries?
We are out of sugar, after all.
Gotcha. But...
How about we go together?
K-Kou-chama? Might you be suggesting that I go outside?
Yeah, I suppose.
That's impossible! I cannot!
Even if it is a chance to spend time
with you, I cannot go outside!
She's an amazing maid when she's home, but since she's
a shut-in, she's not so good with the outdoors.
If it were within my capabilities, I would
love to go out with you. However...
Even if it's your master's order?
Normally, I would never even think
of disobeying your orders,
but just this once...
I'm just teasing you. Sorry, Saori-nee.
Okay, I'll be back soon.
Oh...
Please forgive me and my inability to accompany you.
Talk about shitty timing.
Saori-nee?
Saori-nee, what are you doing here?
Kou-chama...
When I started thinking about
how you might be stuck in the rain and catching a cold...
I just couldn't stay still, so I came out looking for you.
Are you okay with being outside?
S-Saori-nee, are you okay?
It would appear that I'm not ready to go outside yet.
I am such a happy maid.
Saori-nee...
Next time, don't push yourself, okay?
No, helping her master in his time of
need is also part of a maid's duty.
Not so long ago, I was the one giving you a piggyback ride.
Really?
You have really grown.
This soft sensation on my back is...
We both ended up getting soaked.
Yes. At this rate,
you'll catch a cold.
Saori-nee?
I'll take a bath fi...
Yes, I will warm you up before you go.
Wha... Saori-nee?
It was my fauIt that you ended up getting so cold.
I shall warm you up right away.
Saori-nee, your breasts are touching me.
Kou-chama, your lips are blue...
Saori-nee...
Kou-chama, if you're so rough...
Kou-chama's hands are fondling my breasts...
Your nipples are so hard because of the cold.
No, that's not...
This time, I'll warm you up.
Your breasts are so smooth and soft.
Don't suck on them...
No, not there...
Kou-chama, this will not do.
It is my duty as a maid to warm up my master's body.
Please relax.
I will warm this up as well.
Are you feeling warm? It has gotten so hard.
S-Saori-nee, where did you learn thi...
Pleasing her master is a maid's duty.
Kou-chama's liquids are making such naughty sounds.
Saori-nee, I'm gonna...
Your penis is pulsing and getting real hot.
Kou-chama's hot liquids are...
Please forgive me for being so obscene.
Saori-nee...
I haven't decided who I want as my fiancée yet...
Kou-chama.
You are my master and I am your maid.
Please use me as you will.
Master, your hard penis is...
It went in!
Saori-nee, you're so warm inside.
Master, your penis is getting bigger inside me!
You're so rough!
Kou-chama, I love you.
I've been waiting for this day for so long.
I am so happy right now.
Kou-chama's hot liquids are...
Kou-chama, you're still hard.
Well...
Your pussy is just so...
Geez.
Master, please allow me to service you some more.
My vagina is...
It's taking the shape of Master's penis.
Your penis is hitting my womb, Kou-chama!
I-I love you!
Saori-nee, you forgot to say "master".
Please forgive me, Master!
Saori-nee, you're going to suck everything out of me.
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
Me too!
Master, there's so much of your semen everywhere.
I am your property, Master.
Please summon me whenever you
need anything, Kou-chama.
So Momo-chan, I totally hate the
teacher for my remedial classes.
Oh my, that sounds horrible.
I feel like you're not really listening to me.
Anzu, that's bad manners.
Yeah, yeah.
I want seconds.
An-chan, you sure can eat.
I am a growing girl.
Is that so? It'd be great if you grow some more.
Would you like seconds, Kou-chama?
U-Uh, no. I'm good. I'm full.
O-Oh, okay.
Saori, hurry up!
Ah, yes.
Sorry for the wait.
I'm coming in.
Yuri-nee, knock!
I did.
I'll cut to the chase.
You had sex with Saori, didn't you?
Jackpot, huh?
Just to make sure,
you do remember that you have to choose
a fiancée from one of us, right?
Yeah...
So you're okay with Saori being your fiancée?
I don't know.
What do you mean, "you don't know"?
Having to pick a fiancée out of all of you really
puts me on the spot.
Kouki...
I thought you had grown up a bit, but...
You're still just a child.
Yuri-nee...
But you know, you can't be a child forever.
Me, Momo, and Saori... we all really love you.
Anzu's probably the only one who hasn't realized it yet.
I love you girls too...
So that's why...
you want things to stay the way they are?
Eh? Wha... Wai...
Wh-What are you...
Well, I guess one part of you did grow.
Yuri-nee, this is all so sudden.
It's starting to twitch.
I never thought his dick could get this big.
If you suck that hard, I'm gonna...
Oh wow, you just came in my mouth.
Yuri-nee...
Don't worry.
Just leave your body to me.
So, any thoughts?
It's sexy and just plain beautiful.
Nice bit of honesty.
As a reward, I'll let you touch it.
If you touch me like that,
I won't be able to hold my voice back.
Don't feel my clit like that.
Yuri-nee, you're so wet.
Kouki...
Don't just use your fingers. Use your tongue too.
Kouki, your tongue is wrapping around inside me.
Yuri-nee, you're twitching.
Don't suck like that!
Wai-Wait, Kouki! Time out!
No! I'm gonna cum. You're gonna make me cum!
Yuri-nee, are you okay?
Geez. Well, aren't you acting pretty cocky?
You got hard again?
So are you after my pussy this time?
No, it's just that your reactions are so cute.
It's fine.
I'll accept all of you.
No need to rush. Let's just take this slowly,
okay?
Kouki, your dick is so hot.
You're so tight!
It's going deep inside.
Wait. Just wait a second.
Let's just stay like this for a little.
Wait, is this your first time?
Shut up.
You might think otherwise, but I'm a pure girl.
Yuri-nee, you're too cute! I can't hold back anymore.
Wai... Kouki!
Every time I move, it feels so good.
My nipples are so hard.
Kouki, if you suck that hard,
you're going to wear my nipples out!
Yuri-nee, your nipples are so...
delicious...
Kouki, do it harder!
My head's so hot. I can't think of anything!
Kouki, you're getting so big.
Are you gonna make me cum again?
Yuri-nee...
I'm gonna cum too!
C-Cum!
I'll take everything! Pump your cum into my womb!
Yuri-nee, um...
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about having sex with me and Saori.
Yuri-nee...
Well, it's a bit of a shock that she
beat me to the punch though.
But I'll overlook it as the eldest daughter
of the Hanabishi family.
After all, you're still our adorable little brother.
But promise me this.
Promise that you'll choose one of us by the deadline.
Yeah, I will.
Yuri-nee...
Thanks!
She fell asleep?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: hyakupercent | punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent