Beautiful Honor Student who Madly Loves
Her Younger Brother: Kisaragi Sarasa
She is a beautiful girl with excellent grades, athletic skills, outgoing personality
and is well-esteemed even by the same gender just as one would expect
from a woman possessing both beauty and brains.
Although she was with her divorced mother, she ended up having to live
together with her younger brother after her mother's sudden demise.
One thing led to another and now that they are going to
the same school, she reveals her once concealed feelings.
That is, to make him hers no matter what, an immoral desire.
Sarasa's brother grew up to be the kind of man that suits her taste, but that fact
caused him to be approached by these "unfamiliar bugs" at the same time.
She spent days being eaten up by the anxiety that
some bitch from who knows where might have a piece of him.
This drove Sarasa to make a drastic change in her supposedly extensive plan.
She forcibly sets all the necessary conditions and puts the plan in action on the very day when her brother starts
attending the same school as hers.
Rowdy Junior in School Swimsuit: Reizei Kasuri
Kasuri is a female junior and admirer of Kira.
She got admitted to their school on a swimming scholarship.
She also has a lot of fans due to her cheerful attitude and physically fit body,
and enjoys high popularity together with the beautiful honor student Sarasa.
Kasuri finally got to meet his senior Kira who she has a huge crush on.
Her admiration pushed her to make an effort and attempt
to make herself look appealing to him.
One morning on her way to school, Kasuri comes across Kira.
He thought that it's her chance to greet him and dashed through
without a second thought.
However, Kasuri's body tensed up just when she's about to stop...
A Fine Young Man with an Excessively Doting
and Beautiful Older Sister: Kisaragi Kira
Kira was under Sarasa's care ever since he was a child.
For that reason, he never goes against her will, though he had his own questions about his daily life with his sister.
It's way different compared to what he generally heard
among his friends talking about their own homes:
Sarasa is overprotective and gives him excessive physical intimacy.
She is renowned for being a beautiful honor student.
Although having that kind of a sister is the reason
why he's always been envied, he thought that something
which started at that particular time is way too much.
Despite being still under fire because of his affair,
Kira goes to a Family Restaurant with Kasuri while on their way home.
What appears in front of them is none other than Sarasa
who's wearing the restaurant's staff uniform.
Sarasa shows them onto their seats before he could have any time
to think about why is his older sister is in there.
She lays out a full course meal for him afterwards.
Sarasa makes him suck her tit under the cover of the printed menu
and then proceeds to suck his fleshy member.
Kira is now at maximum arousal and on the verge of ejaculation
due to Sarasa's provided set meal.
Kira's dissatisfied youthful energy pushed to limits
leads him to go after his older sister's body in the washroom.
After spending a risky yet peachy moment,
Kira hurriedly goes to walk Kasuri home.
When he's about to leave, she insisted
on thanking him back for helping her last time.
What he saw next is Kasuri in a naked apron outfit.
Kasuri's sweet scent and child-like figure
instantly gave Kira an erection.
He forces himself into her mouth, making her suck him off,
flailing her around and ejaculating inside.
Right afterwards, he rolls her petite body over
and then later carries her on his arms as she penetrates her,
finishing off by filling her insides up.
Kira, feeling refreshed, leaves Kasuri's room.
Right after he turns around, there stands his beloved older sister Sarasa, staring at him in disbelief.
Nympho Sister
Max Heart
Original Animation
Perverted Home Tutor Sarasa:
A Banquet of Jealousy Punishment, Obscenity at Max!
Last Time on Ane Chijo Max Heart
Not heading straight home after school,
huh? You're a bad boy, Kira.
I never knew that you work here, Sarasa-senpai!
I'm just filling in for a friend.
Not that it matters to you, though!
Oh! Sorry, Kira, but can you move a little further?
I'll put the blinds down.
Okay.
Oh no...
Kira, you're munching on me!
It's alright, I can handle this much.
You're getting a hard-on at such a place...
You can't shoot it out here.
I'm now like this down here
after sucking your dick!
...good!
...way too reckless
That's so deep!
I was actually planning to
make you something at first,
but I'll just make something out of this.
I'm almost there!
Senpai, you are...
...going inside me again!
I'm having a hard time here...
But I can feel you...
This makes my insides feel so amazing!
Oh no!
See you, then. Stay on your toes.
Kira...
I'm not angry about yesterday.
I'm talking about your lame
"just dropping by" excuse.
It's like a girl swearing she's still a virgin
after going out of a love hotel.
I don't really mind you fooling around with her.
I'll let it pass even if you keep doing that.
However, what are those supposed to be?
They're the results of my exams.
Isn't that right?
Then, what are those grades?
Kisaragi Kira                             Rank in whole school grade: 2/352                                    Rating: A
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
.                           Social Studies                       |   Mathematics   |                      Science
Japanese History | World History | Geography | Math I | Math II |   Physics  |  Chemistry  |  Biology
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
.           100           |          97          |        99       |    96    |    100   |     100       |        98        |      97
Didn't I do well? These are good grades.
Is rank number two not enough?
No! You're just part of the crowd
if you're not ranked first!
This clearly shows that you're sex-crazed!
You're wrong! Kasuri and I are, well...
If you started to become serious about her,
sensei will then have to set you straight!
Those memories that you
share with that little bitch...
...will all be overwritten by me!
I-Is what you're gonna teach me
not about school lessons?
This is mental training.
My imprinting wasn't enough, so you
got charmed by that little bitch.
I'll make it so that you'll be unable
to think about anyone else but me.
So this dick went inside
another woman, huh?
I'll sandwich it between my tits,
then give it lots of rubbing.
This is an impossible feat for that bitch.
It's twitching! This sensation is heavenly, isn't it?
It's so sturdy... It's incredible!
I'm the only one who can do this for you.
Looks like you're about to come.
You can't come yet!
I won't allow you to be the
only one who gets to feel good.
Kira, lick my pussy.
You can tear my stockings open.
Right there, your tongue is scraping against it!
Lick it directly with your tongue, there!
Lick my clitoris a lot as well!
It feels good! Your finger is fondling my pussy!
It's as hard as a rock! It looks like
it'll spurt right away if it goes inside me!
Kira, just a little more!
I want you to fill my pussy up with your dick!
Th-This is...
Don't expect me to let you come so easily.
I'll drown you in lots and lots
of pleasure using my body.
If you'll be able to pleasure me,
I'll remove that, alright?
This is incredible! Your dick is scraping my insides!
More...
Make a mess inside me! Fuck me hard!
It fills me up deep inside!
It thuds each time I go down!
No, this isn't like the usual! No way!
Kira, wait! Stop!
I'll make you feel good!
So much that you'll forget all the sadness!
I understand. I'll take it off you now.
That feels good! Right there! More!
Keep indulging on me!
Never think of anybody else but me!
I've been drowning myself into you!
That's good! Make yourself
feel lots of pleasure!
Shoot plenty of it deep inside me!
Make me come just like this, Kira!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
There's a huge amount
of your semen inside me!
Kira, your dick was incredible...
That's amazing.
You just came, but it's already like that.
You even made me wear this,
but you'll be taking it off in the end.
You're kneading my tits.
Oh, that feels good!
Even my ass...
Your dick is rubbing
against mine, it feels great!
You keep grinding against my pussy.
I can't wait any longer now!
Ever since our father left and our mother died,
I grew up always seeing you cook in this kitchen!
Did seeing me here give you
nostalgia? Want to do me?
It's okay since I belong to you.
Do it, I want you
to shove your dick inside me!
I want you to stir me up a lot,
so much so like you're
gonna tear my pussy up!
Yes, it's scraping me deep inside.
Keep pounding me!
You're making a mush of it...
My pussy is now squishy!
Sis, this feels great!
Yes, me too...
Grinding yours against mine
down there makes me feel so good.
Kira, make your dick spurt!
Shoot lots of it inside me—!
There's so much gushing in—!
There's so much of your semen pouring into me!
You'll make me pregnant—!
It went inside me again!
Kira, doing this will make me end up remembering
about sex whenever we eat here!
I want to have plenty of sex with you.
Make a mess out of me!
I want it! I want more of your semen!
I want you to pour lots of it
deep into my womb!
I'm coming—!
Kira, my pussy
is exclusively yours!
Maybe I need to be more
assertive towards Kira-senpai.
I wonder what should I do.
Hmm?
Kira-senpai!
Wh-Whoa... Kasuri.
Jeez! Senpai, you should've
caught me in your arms.
You're too shy!
Here!
Alright, then! See you later, senpai.
4 P.M.
I'll be waiting at the clubroom.
Kasuri
I'll have to sort this out.
K-Kasuri?
Oh... Come in, senpai!
Senpai, listen...
It's because we haven't been able
to spend time together lately.
Y-Yeah...
Listen, Kasuri... The truth is, I...
Kasuri...
Kasuri, hold it right there!
Senpai, I want you to be more into me.
That's why, you see...
I want you to hold me in your arms a whole lot, so...
No way, no one should be
coming here at this time!
Gosh, this is too sudden!
The tournament is close so it can't be helped.
I'm sorry, senpai. It's cramped
in here but bear with it.
I-I think that they'll be out soon...
Huh?
Senpai's dick is hitting against me.
It was limp before, though...
I can obviously tell it.
His dick is stiff while he's with me here.
Hey, Kasuri! Don't do that!
Let's hurry up.
Just wait for a second!
It's so hard...
I really am the reason why senpai
got hard down here, after all.
We're in my locker, so there's
a strong scent of me in here.
And that's why you...
Oh, they're gone.
Hey, let's get out of here quickly!
It's senpai's dick...
Wait! This isn't good, Kasuri!
Senpai, your dick is so big!
Did you know, senpai?
I've never done it since the day you took my virginity
because I wanted us to have more sex instead.
I want you to violate me in my swimsuit.
Senpai, your thing down here
feels warm and hard.
It's so cute!
I can't breathe!
There's so much of your semen, senpai...
Senpai, your dick is going inside me again!
It's going inside me!
Your dick is filling me up again inside!
Yes, your dick is scraping up my insides!
This is amazing!
You're holding me in your arms
while we're having sex!
You're filling up my inner depths!
I'm having sex with you just like this.
I want us to keep doing this a lot more!
It's going deep in my belly!
It's so deep! Your dick is going deep inside.
Your dick is going wild inside me!
Senpai, shoot it inside me!
Shoot plenty of it!
Senpai's stuff!
Senpai, I'm glad that you found me arousing.
Kasuri! I... You see, I can't keep
doing it with you like this...
I knew it! You also think so?
Y-Yeah...
I have to make her stop doing it with me...
Yeah, let's do it next time in my room!
It'll be trouble if someone walks in,
and I want us to be alone!
No, that's not what I meant!
Okay, then! Thank you for today, senpai!
Let's have sex tomorrow as well!
Th-This looks bad...
K-Kira!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization