Beautiful Honor Student who Madly Loves
Her Younger Brother: Kisaragi Sarasa
She is a beautiful girl with excellent grades, athletic skills, outgoing personality
and is well-esteemed even by the same gender just as one would expect
from a woman possessing both beauty and brains.
Although she was with her divorced mother, she ended up having to live
together with her younger brother after her mother's sudden demise.
One thing led to another and now that they are going in
the same school, she reveals her once concealed feelings.
That is, to make him hers no matter what, an immoral desire.
Sarasa's brother grew up to be the kind of man that suits her taste, but that fact
caused him to be approached by these "unfamiliar bugs" at the same time.
She spent days being eaten up by the anxiety that
some bitch from who knows where might have a piece of him.
This drove Sarasa to make a drastic change in her supposedly extensive plan.
She puts the plan in action on the very day when his brother starts
attending the same school as hers and forcibly set all the necessary conditions.
A Fine Young Man with an Excessively
Doting Older Sister: Kisaragi Kira
Kira was under Sarasa's care ever since he was a child.
For that reason, he never goes against her will, though he had his own questions about his daily life with his sister.
It's way different compared from what he generally heard
among his friends talking about their own homes:
Sarasa is overprotective and gives him excessive physical intimacy.
She is renowned for being a beautiful honor student.
Although having that kind of a sister is the reason
why he's always been envied, he thought that something
which started at that particular time is way too much.
With her parents having a divorce and living together with her mother
who later passes away, Kisaragi Sarasa bravely took the responsibility
of raising Kira all by herself while facing numerous challenges.
She is a beautiful girl with excellent grades, good athletic skills and
a pleasant outgoing personality, but with these also come problems for her.
Being an ideal and beautiful woman means constantly attracting people's
attention. She also gets a lot of love confessions even from the same gender,
though she kindly declines each and every one of them.
The only one her eyes can see is Kisaragi Kira.
She raised and groomed him according to her own ideals and preferences.
Sarasa thinks about nothing else but him. So much so that she went
to the trouble of being overprotective of Kira to make sure
that no bitchy worms will be able to latch themselves on him.
Sarasa did all of these just for the sake of the fated moment
when she can eventually unleash all of her desires...
Kira saw Sarasa managing her schoolwork
despite being occupied of extensively looking after him.
Being unaware of the truth behind her motivation,
he looked upon her with respect and admiration.
He worked hard every day as he strove to at least
get slightly closer to her level of excellence.
As a result, Kira managed to get in the same school where Sarasa is.
Being there, he once again witnessed how popular his sister is with everyone.
Sarasa invited Kira into her room for a celebration of his school admission.
Kira failed to notice Sarasa's eyes gleaming with a sharp stare akin to a beast's...
Nympho Sister
Max Heart
Original Animation
Doting Beautiful Older Sister Sarasa:
Onee-chan, it's an open season.
Really?
Next will be the upperclassmen representative,
Kisaragi Sarasa-san.
Please enjoy each and every day
of your school life to their fullest!
The same goes for romance.
Bear in mind of having a proper and
wholesome school life, okay?
That would be all from me, Kisaragi Sarasa.
Sis... Didn't that mouth say something
about proper and wholesome?
Hey... Good morning!
A sibling relationship is different
from a heterosexual relationship!
Isn't this bad in common sense?
It is better to follow your instinct than common sense!
Jeez... Your dick is honest but you're so stubborn!
There's nothing filthy anywhere on you, Kira!
Leave it to your older sister!
I'm going to squeeze a lot of it out for you.
Your semen is pouring out!
I got your dense morning semen!
It's so creamy!
I'm glad that you liked it. Now let me go.
That's right, your dick was pestering me.
Was that my fault?
...
......
......About
......About A Year
At last, now is the time...
......About A Year Ago
to make Kira mine!
Mom left Kira under my care on her deathbed.
I waited until we're commuting to the same school!
But, but...
Starting today, I'll let my instincts
escalate rampantly towards Kira!
Kisaragi-kun, isn't Kisaragi-senpai your older sister?
Isn't she so beautiful and cool as well?
Let's be friends, then introduce me to her!
This is bad. Awakening Kira's instincts also meant
that he becomes a prime target of those hungry bitches!
There's no time for hesitations. Starting today, I will...
I'm home!
Sis, earlier at school, you see...
Kira, this is something
for you from sis
Well, she's in her room.
Welcome home, Kira!
Oh... thank you, my sis...
Oh... thank you, my sister?!
Sis, what's happening here?
Kira, this day came at last!
N-No... Before that, what's with this?
Ever since mom passed away,
fate has brought us together!
Whenever you're under the weather
and even when you're sound asleep,
I've been looking after you for all this time!
O-Okay... Thank you...
Whenever I'm next to you, I also
desperately held myself back
from the urge to shower you with my affection!
O-Okay...
I tried to do my best!
I even want to praise myself for doing so!
And today...
The moment to reap my benefits finally came.
It's the moment that you'll be mine!
W-Wait! What are you doing, sis?
Don't worry, Kira. There is nothing to be afraid of.
You will become an adult in no time.
What the hell, I'm your younger
brother! We're siblings, you know!
You can just follow your instincts.
There's no one else here but us two.
Wait! That's not the problem here!
I kept my hymen intact just for you!
You'll have all of me!
And then, I'll have all of you!
I don't get what you're saying!
What's with you? I'm saying that nobody
else but I can love everything about you!
From your earwax to your anus, and even your smegma!
I love everything about you!
I thought that you're a bit off, but you're a full-fledged pervert.
I'm being serious here!
You're so crazy!
Then, how about this.
If your dick can endure what I'll do
within five minutes, then I'll back off.
You not allowed to touch or lick it!
Kira, your mouth... and your nose...
They're rubbing against my clitoris and it feels good!
Your dick got big!
That's—
It feels good... Your lips are caressing my pussy...
My pussy feels good!
Your dick got stiff so this means that I won!
S-So dicks get as huge
and indecently shaped just like this, huh?
How is it, Kira?
What do you mean "how"?
So you're playing dumb. You're not telling me about it.
I-It feels good...
I want to feel good too!
Sis, are you serious about this?
Of course, I am.
It's a tighter fit than I expected!
Sis, the date! It's a risky day, isn't it?
If we get lucky, we'll go from siblings to parents.
You will be mine for the rest of my life!
That's too much.
Oh, in exchange you'll have this gorgeous,
pristine and perfect sister for the rest of your life!
Wow, your dick is penetrating me!
Here we go.
Kira, you're filling me up inside!
What's this? You're now inside me.
My pussy is getting tightly jammed with your dick!
Your dick is amazing!
I think I'm gonna come even
though this is my first time!
Shoot your semen inside me!
Please, Kira!
Sis, I'm seriously about to...
Kira, plant plenty of your seeds
in my pussy... in my womb!
Your semen is splashing deep inside me!
Wow, you shot a lot of semen...
I feel like I'm going crazy!
Kira, why is it getting big inside me?
Sis, you're making quite a face.
N-No, stop looking at my unsightly face!
That's a proof of you conceding to me, right?
Huh? Not again!
No, wait! This much... right now would be...
No, Kira! Don't be so rough! Wait!
Isn't this the sex you longed for?
Let me see a happy face!
No! Even if you say something like that,
I don't know what to think of it!
No, I'm gonna die if this goes on!
You say that while getting tight.
I don't know!
I don't get anything about it, Kira!
I'm coming again! You're so good
that it's driving me crazy!
I want to have it! I want to
get pregnant with your baby!
Come a lot!
It's flowing in! Such an amazing amount of it!
Kira, your semen is gushing into me!
H-Hey! Sis, are you alright?
I'm home!
Welcome home, Kira! Just wait for a moment, okay?
I'm sorry that you always had to do all the work.
What are you talking about? This is
my duty so don't sweat it.
And also...
Isn't it fun like this, being like newlyweds?
Well, siblings can't get married though.
No way!
You were telling "Isn't my cock great?"
and then you kept filling me up with
semen! What was all that for, then?
Huh? Or could it be that you're cheating on me?
I'm all drenched now!
I'll take over the work so go take a bath.
Okay...
No way... It's embarrassing
when you're staring that much.
You're the one who came here looking like that.
Kira, wash my body.
Just go already.
Kira!
Yes?!
I'm talking about my body, not the plates.
Wash me.
Kira, you'll wash me barehandedly, of course.
Isn't that obvious?
Nothing else can touch me but your hands, Kira.
Yeah, yeah.
Kira, I won't get clean if you
don't wash me properly.
I-I know.
Kira, wash me a lot down there!
Wash it properly!
That's great, Kira...
Stir me up right there!
Your dick is poking at me.
Wow... It's huge!
Sis, you're amazing down here.
Same for you, Kira. Your dick is amazing.
Kira, start plunging your dick into my pussy.
Your dick went inside me!
Your dick...
Even though we're doing something bad...
You're saying that again... You keep
talking about the same things...
You say that, yet over the past year
you kept giving me creampies!
Even if you say that...
Kira, you're being rough!
You keep thrusting deep into me!
My pussy is writhing from pleasure!
Wait, doing it this position in dangerous!
I won't forgive you if I ended up falling over!
You keep on overflowing down here.
That's because you keep on shoving your dick
in me and I don't know what's going on anymore!
You feel good from being teased by your
brother. You really are a pervert, sis.
I'm fine with being a pervert or
anything else when I'm with you!
That's good, Kira!
I'm coming! Coming, coming, I'm coming!
I'm being filled with a huge amount
of semen from your dick!
Kira, you are mine.
Including all of your semen, okay?
You're the only one for me, sis.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
N
Ne
Nex
Next
Next on
Next on A
Next on An
Next on Ane
Next on Ane Ch
Next on Ane Chi
Next on Ane Chijo
Next on Ane Chijo H
Next on Ane Chijo He
Next on Ane Chijo Hea
Next on Ane Chijo Hear
Next on Ane Chijo Heart
Next on Ane Chijo Heart M
Next on Ane Chijo Heart Max
Are you alright?
Ah, Umm... Thank you!
I'm, well... Please excuse me!
Seeing my lover wrapping his arms on another woman
just like a hostile ruffian hurts my feelings!
She's more like a little sister than a woman to me.
Huh?! Don't mess around with me!
There's no way for a filthy
bitch to look like a little sister!
Ouch! Uhh...
Sitting on your face feels good...
Kira, your penis is suddenly...
I'm going to come from this!
Something big is coming!
I'll pour plenty of it into you.
H-Hey, sis! What are you doing?
How is it, Kira? Have you fixed it?
Kira, get it done already.
I am waiting.
Sorry! I forgot something, you see.
Okay, help yourself in...
Kira-senpai, if that's the case...
P-Please wipe me down here as well...
Senpai, look at mine!
Jeez, you shouldn't make women feel embarrassed!