The day before summer vacation
Hanabishi family living dining room
Head of the Hanabishi family
Hanabishi Kantarou
Wife
Koume
Hidaka Kouki
Um, what am I here at this family meeting for?
Eldest daughter of the Hanabishi family
Hanabishi Yurina
Yeah, I left work for this, so why don't
you tell us what this is about already, Dad?
Don't be in such a rush.
Okay then, let's start the Hanabishi family meeting.
Dad, what's this meeting about?
Second daughter of the Hanabishi family
Hanabishi Momone
I've decided to let Kouki-kun
stay here over summer break.
Here? You mean in your house?
Precisely. I already have your family's permission.
Hey, wait. My parents might
have given their permission, but...
Fourth daughter of the Hanabishi family
Hanabishi Anzu
Does that mean we'll be living with Kouki?
Well, if he's staying with us, then I guess it
would follow that he'll be living with us as well.
Hm, sounds great.
Hey, no, it's not okay!
I'm a guy, if you haven't noticed!
Our families might be close,
but living together is pushing it!
Father.
Saori-nee, you know what I'm saying, right?
This means I'll be able to serve
Kou-chama from morning until evening!
That's what you were going to say?
Okay! I'll give Kou-chan a lot of sweets too!
I'll get him to massage my shoulders.
What are you saying?
Don't just decide what I'll be doing like that.
I don't really care either way.
It'll be the same if he's here or not.
That kind of hurts.
For now, it seems that everyone
is fine with Kouki-kun living here.
One more thing.
You're not done yet?
This is what I really wanted to talk about.
Truth is, I made a promise
with Kouki-kun's father, Akihiro.
Kouki-kun will marry a daughter
of the Hanabashi family.
What did you just say?
It's a promise I made with Akihiro.
I promised him that one day, we'd be family.
With that in mind, I'd like you to choose one
of them as your bride during this summer break.
I have to choose one of them?
I've always thought of them as my real sisters.
You've never thought of marrying them?
That's not what I'm saying, but...
I think they should have a say in it too.
Sounds good to me.
Yuri-nee?
I really, really, really like the idea!
I'll be able to serve Kou-chama forever.
Momo-nee? Saori-nee?
Anzu? What about you?
I...
I don't have any feelings or anything for Kouki.
That idiot.
That concludes our family meeting.
Kouki-kun, please look after
my daughters over the break, okay?
What do you mean "look after them"?
Actually, Koume, your parents, and I
will be going overseas to America.
Both of my parents are going?
Yep.
They're not letting me decide anything!
Kouki-kun?
Koume-oba-san?
Have some confidence in yourself.
I don't think we can find a better son-in-law than you.
Oba-san?
If you don't choose one of my daughters, though,
I wouldn't mind being wed to you.
Wha... What are you doing all of a sudden?!
Oh dear, are you not satisfied with me?
I might be a mother of four,
but I still think I'm quite appealing.
That's not what I want to hear from you!
Kou-chan, are you awake?
You were kind of restless, are yoo okay?
Momo-nee...
It looks like your fever's gone down quite a bit.
Is Saori-nee okay?
Saori-chan has a fever too,
but Anzu is with her, so you don't need to worry.
I see.
You kept saying in your sleep
how you can't decide who to choose.
I was happy being able to live with you,
but you never really seemed to be happy.
It wasn't just you, though. We were all anxious.
Momo-nee, I...
What should I do?
Yuri, Momo, Sakurami, Anzu... the four of us
are flowers in the spring and you're our sun.
If you're not shining, we won't bloom.
And... I think you'll be able to make
the promise we made come true.
Promise?
Momo-nee...
Kou-chan...
This feels good.
You really love my boobs, don't you?
Nee-chan, I...
I'll take them off myself.
Your dick seems to be pretty happy.
Kou-chan's dick is so hot!
You can't cum yet!
I'll make you cum with the boobs you love so much.
My boobs are getting so dirty from your pre-cum.
It really is bitter.
You don't have to force yourself to drink it.
Of course I do. It's a part of you.
Spitting it out would be such a waste.
Kou-chan...
Kou-chan, you're like a baby.
If you suck my boobs like that...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
I came with my boobs...
Momo-nee...
No, right now, I'm...
Don't touch me there!
I'm still sensitive there, so you can't touch it.
S-Something amazing's coming!
No...
Momo-nee, are you okay?
Geez, I told you not to.
Sorry.
It's fine. I love you, Kou-chan.
Kou-chan, are you okay?
Not really.
But that's not going to stop me now.
In that case, let me take your cold from you.
Come here, Kou-chan.
Kou-chan, you're so hard!
It's going all the way to my womb!
So good!
This is so rough. You're being so rough!
I'm starting to lose it.
It keeps... It keeps hitting my most sensitive spot!
Kou-chan, don't!
If you touch my boobs now, I'm gonna...
I love you! I love you so much, Kou-chan!
Paint me white, Kou-chan!
It's a promise!
Oh, Kouki? You okay now?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Sorry for making you worry.
Apologize to Momone, not me.
She was trying to get rid of your cold for you,
but now she's the one who has it.
Saori-nee, how about you? Feeling better?
Saori-nee?
Yes. I'm very sorry for being a burden while I was sick.
Thanks to all of you, I'm all better now.
Don't overdo it, okay?
Um, Kou-chama?
Today is the end of your summer break.
Both Father and Mother will be returning tomorrow.
Kou-chama, who will you choose to be your wife?
Yeah, so about that...
Kouki! You're better now, right?
Let's play! I bought a new
fighting game while you were sick.
Huh?
If you lose, there's a nice,
juicy penalty game waiting for you.
Come on, hurry up! Let's go!
Wha... Anzu-chan?
This is the last day of summer break.
Younger sister, play your games by yourself.
Didn't you say that you didn't
"have any feelings or anything" for him?
Y-Yeah, but...
Or, are you saying that you had a change
of heart, and now you want to be his wife?
Huh? Why would I want to be his stinking wife?
Screw that.
Then, anything related to his
future is none of your business.
Get out of here!
Seriously, there's something wrong with all of you.
Wife this, wife that... That's all you guys ever talk about.
What's so good about Kouki?!
Anzu-chan!
Kouki, hurry up and go after her!
Right.
No! Kou-chan, you're so intense!
Onee-sama?
How long... How long do you think
we can remain as just siblings?!
I really love Kou-chama with all my heart.
I would leave this house if
it meant I could be with him.
Don't you love him, onee-sama?
Kouki is my first love.
Of course I love him.
Then why did you let him go?!
Isn't that obvious? It's because Anzu
likes Kouki just as much as we do.
If Anzu doesn't realize her feelings,
she'll be hurt when Kouki doesn't consider her.
Momone isn't even good at doing chores,
and goes at her own pace.
I'm really worried about her future.
Saori, you stopped going to college,
and you're not even able to leave the house.
I'm scared you'll never return to how you used to be.
Every time I look at you, I get worried.
I love Kouki. I'm confident that my feelings for him
are just as strong, if not stronger than yours.
However, I love Momone just as much.
I love you, and I love Anzu just as much.
I don't want any of you to be unhappy!
For that, I'll even lie to myself.
I'm the oldest sister, after all.
Kouki, I'm leaving Anzu up to you.
Because Kouki is such an idiot,
Saori-nee ended up getting mad at me.
I wonder if Kouki will get married to Saori...
I'm the real idiot.
I'm sitting here with a broken heart
and I haven't even tried to do anything.
Does that mean I really do like Kouki?
I realized too late.
He's out of my reach now...
Kouki's such an idiot. Idiot, such a big idiot!
You shouldn't talk behind people's backs.
You should tell them to their face.
Kouki?!
What are you doing here?
Aren't you getting engaged to Saori?
Nope.
Anzu-chan, do you remember our promise?
I promised that I'd marry all of you.
That's not something you can do!
I'll be the one who decides if it's impossible or not.
So, Anzu-chan, tell me how you really feel.
My feelings?
Argh. Geez! Fine already.
These are my true feelings.
Kouki? Do the stuff you did with them with me too.
Just like you did with them.
We're sisters. Just one look and I knew.
Yeah, you got a point.
Kiss me again.
Again.
Kouki, your hands are so warm!
Hey, wait... Kouki!
Sheesh, don't strip me.
It's so embarrassing.
Stop staring at me!
Yeah, I know they're smaller than my sisters' are!
That's not it. Your boobs are really cute.
How can you say that with...
With a straight face...
Kouki's licking my boobs!
No!
You're only playing with my nipples.
This is so embarrassing!
No, don't! You can't!
Kouki, you pervert. You lech!
No, not there...
No... That's...
I'm really sensitive there!
I'm going to cum if you keep doing that!
Kouki... let's have sex.
Kouki, please... Hurry up... Put it in...
It's coming inside me!
Ow!
Kouki, your dick is too big!
Are you okay?
Yeah. If it's your dick, I can stand the pain.
Come deeper in me.
You're so deep inside me!
This isn't good! My mind's going crazy!
Kouki, move faster.
I'm having sex with Kouki!
If you're so loud, someone might come.
B-But...
I can't stop myself!
If I fall for him any more than this,
I won't be able to think about anything but him!
It's fine, you can cum inside!
Kouki!
I love you! I love you!
I love you! I love you so much!
It's a text from Dad.
What'd he say?
Tell Kouki-kun this.
I've reserved a wedding hall for tomorrow.
I'd like him to take his bride there.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
I'm going to marry Kouki when I grow up.
No, Kouki is gonna get married
to me because I'm the oldest.
Oh my, Kouki is going to be
my husband though, right?
U-Um, me too.
I'm the one who said it first!
This isn't going to work.
Kouki can only get married to one of us.
Who do you want to marry out of the four of us?
Kou-chan...
When I'm grown up, I'm going to marry all of you!
Geez, you can only get married to one woman. It's the law.
Then I'll become the prime minister and change the law!
I'll be able to marry all of you then, right?
Kouki!
Kou-chan!
Kouki-chan!
Kouki!
I can't just choose one of you.
After all... I love you all so much!