Beautiful Honor Student who Madly Loves
Her Younger Brother: Kisaragi Sarasa
She is a beautiful girl with excellent grades, athletic skills, outgoing personality
and is well-esteemed even by the same gender just as one would expect
from a woman possessing both beauty and brains.
Although she was with her divorced mother, she ended up having to live
together with her younger brother after her mother's sudden demise.
One thing led to another and now that they are going to
the same school, she reveals her once concealed feelings.
That is, to make him hers no matter what, an immoral desire.
Sarasa's brother grew up to be the kind of man that suits her taste, but that fact
caused him to be approached by these "unfamiliar bugs" at the same time.
She spent days being eaten up by the anxiety that
some bitch from who knows where might have a piece of him.
This drove Sarasa to make a drastic change in her supposedly extensive plan.
She forcibly sets all the necessary conditions and puts the plan in action on the very day when her brother starts
attending the same school as hers.
Rowdy Junior in School Swimsuit: Reizei Kasuri
Kasuri is a female junior and admirer of Kira.
She got admitted to their school on a swimming scholarship.
She also has a lot of fans due to her cheerful attitude and physically fit body,
and enjoys high popularity together with the beautiful honor student Sarasa.
Kasuri finally got to meet his senior Kira who she has a huge crush on.
Her admiration pushed her to make an effort and attempt
to make herself look appealing to him.
One morning on her way to school, Kasuri comes across Kira.
He thought that it's her chance to greet him and dashed through
without a second thought.
However, Kasuri's body tensed up just when she's about to stop...
A Fine Young Man with an Excessively
Doting Older Sister: Kisaragi Kira
Kira was under Sarasa's care ever since he was a child.
For that reason, he never goes against her will, though he had his own questions about his daily life with his sister.
It's way different compared to what he generally heard
among his friends talking about their own homes:
Sarasa is overprotective and gives him excessive physical intimacy.
She is renowned for being a beautiful honor student.
Although having that kind of a sister is the reason
why he's always been envied, he thought that something
which started at that particular time is way too much.
Kira invited Kasuri, the sporty girl, into their home in a whim.
"She lives in the same building", he thought.
"It looked like she forgot her key", he thought.
"Letting her use their toilet is no big deal", he thought.
However, the luscious scent of Kasuri's sweat as she barely stands
with her trembling legs made Kira's fleshy member compel him to never waste
another second, and pick the lock of this flowering bud from an uncharted horizon.
The honor of being her first man is already being handed to Kira on a silver platter,
as Kasuri literally pushes herself onto him in an attempt to give her maidenhood.
Kasuri straddles over Kira with a full assertion.
She voluntarily pops her own cherry as she presses her hips,
losing any traces of self-restraint that she might still have
up to that moment and thrusting downwards.
And in this home which overflows with their lingering profanity
then arrives someone. It is his most beloved, yet most feared elder sister, Sarasa.
Kira barely manages to cover up their adulterous fling,
but Sarasa won't buy any of it. Sarasa tries to show Kasuri the way out.
Kasuri politely declines with a straight face, however, unaware of the situation,
stating the reason that she and Kira have something to talk about first.
Sarasa could only stare in disbelief at this beautiful sporty girl
as she swiftly goes invading the sanctuary
only meant to be for the siblings.
Nympho Sister
Max Heart
Original Animation
A Flirty Older Sister's Seductive Play
in a Family Restaurant: Is the order a bitch?
Last Time on Ane Chijo Max Heart
Seeing my lover wrapping
his arms on another woman
just like a hostile ruffian hurts my feelings!
How did you even come to that?
Sure, I ended up catching her into my arms,
but she's more like a little sister
than a woman to me.
Huh?! Don't mess around with me!
There's no way for a filthy
bitch to look like a little sister!
Your mouth is hitting against
my pussy and clitoris...
They both feel good!
Are you a pervert that gets aroused
by your brother spanking you?
It's so deep!
If you keep pushing it that deep...
This is gonna make me come!
I can feel a big one coming!
I'll pour plenty of it into you.
You're going to drown my womb
with your semen, huh?
Come, Kira!
What the hell are you thinking?
Kira, pull your tongue out.
So we live in the same building, Kira-senpai.
What are the chances...
What's up, you're acting weird.
Y-You see, mama went out shopping
and I'm currently locked out.
So that's it, why don't we go in together?
But I don't have a key with me so
I won't be able to go in our unit.
And... I want to ask if you can
lend me your restroom...
Y-Yeah, that shouldn't be any problem.
S-Sorry, I picked up something that I left inside.
Okay, you can go in now... huh?
Senpai...
S-Senpai!
I love you so much! So... So...
Kira-senpai, make love with me!
It hurts a little, but not as much as I thought it would.
Kira-senpai, this sensation...
Whenever your thing reaches deep inside...
Th-This is...
Is he having a fling with some girl while I was away?
It's only our first year as newlyweds
and he's already cheating on me
in a very cliché soap opera fashion...
Kira!
Welcome!
Huh?
K-Kira...
Not heading straight home after school,
huh? You're a bad boy, Kira.
I never knew that you work here, Sarasa-senpai!
I'm just filling in for a friend.
Not that it matters to you, though!
So this is the reason why she's going home late.
Sarasa-senpai, we haven't had the menu yet.
Oh my, I'll get them for you.
I've heard that this place
is popular for their sweets
so I wanted to have our date here, senpai!
I-Is that so?
Should we get going?
Uhh!
We haven't ordered anything yet.
They're obviously having a date,
and he kept it from me...
This is an ominous sign of home wreckage!
Kira, what kind of bitch did
you pick up and take home?
Oh, welcome home.
I just lent our toilet to a junior from school.
Oh, Kisaragi Sarasa-senpai! Good evening!
Oh, it's you...
Oh, the toilet, huh? Aren't you done already?
Then, here is the way out.
Oh...
Kira-senpai and I have something
to talk about first, so don't mind me.
I doubt that Kira will have his way
and indulge in that bitch...
But still... Oh?
Here you go, this is our menu!
I'll throw in a serving of any sweets for you two!
You can choose whichever you like!
Yay!
Oh! Sorry, Kira, but can you move a little further?
I'll put the blinds down.
Okay.
What are you thinking? Stop!
Oh! If you move that much...
Oh no...
Kira, you're munching on me!
I'm done choosing!
Alright, then. May I have your order, please?
Wow, this is fantastic!
It melts fast so you should eat it right away.
It's delicious!
This one is for you, Kira!
Oh, this is bad! I'll clean that up for you.
It's alright, I can handle this much.
You're getting a hard-on at such a place...
Your dick got so stiff!
You can't shoot it out here.
I'll make you feel good a lot,
but try to hold it in, okay?
Well, then. Take your time.
Oh, Sarasa-chan. There you are.
Can you lend me a hand here?
Oh, okay! I'll be right there!
I'll be on my way, then.
Sarasa-chan?
I'll be able to make it up to
the next tournament that way!
I'll hit the restroom.
I don't think there's something more to it, but...
Oh my, someone's already using it.
Sis, this is the men's...
I'm in the middle of cleaning here!
Cleaning
In Progress
Thank you
for your
cooperation.
I'm talking about cleaning the pent-up lust
off my two-timing younger brother...
I'm now like this down here
after sucking your dick!
Your tongue feels good, Kira!
Right there! So deep!
I won't be able to hold back
if you do it that hard!
No, Kira! I'm gonna...
Huh?
This is my payback for earlier.
One more thing...
No, Kira! What payback are you talking about?
A-Aren't you the one at fault here?
Whose voice called you over earlier?
Earlier...
Oh, you mean the manager?
Wait, Kira!
If you grab my butt so hard...
Manager, huh?
What's up with him, calling his
employees by their first names?
That's just how the manager here is...
Wait, what's this? Are you perhaps, jealous?
That's so sudden!
Hey!
You're being way too reckless right now!
That's so deep!
I just happened to run into Kasuri on my way
home and she said she wanted to eat...
Right...
I'll believe you about today...
But your explanation about
the last time doesn't add up.
I've heard it straight from you...
No, this is so intense!
Oh no, I'm coming!
Kira-senpai, are you not done yet?
No way, that girl came here...
Uh... Yeah, I'm here!
Give me a moment and I'll be done soon.
Oh, okay!
You were taking long, so I...
I'm sorry for the interruption!
No, he's shooting it out right now, of all times!
No! Right now, of all times!
You're kidding me—!
Gosh, I'll be left hanging with just this much!
But going on would be risky now.
What a surprise, your sister was in there.
You never forgot your key today, have you?
It's alright!
Oh, senpai! Come over to our place.
I want to thank you for last time.
I'll prepare my thank you gift for you, then.
That's what she said. Is she planning
to give me something?
Senpai, thank you for waiting.
I'll be giving you my thanks now, senpai.
Wait! About last time... You see...
I'm partly at fault for it!
To begin with, this kind of stuff is...
Senpai... You say that, but... Hmm...
You don't have to hold yourself back.
There is nobody else here but you and me.
Your thing is twitching, senpai.
I was planning to actually
cook you something at first,
but I'll just cook you something using this.
This is how senpai tastes like...
Your dick is going deep into my throat!
I'm almost there!
It's alright, senpai!
Senpai, your stuff is so thick!
O
O-O
O-O-O
O-O-O-O
O-O-O-O-Ouch...
Uhh... I'm sorry!
Huh? Senpai?
S-Senpai!
Wait, not at this position...
It's going inside!
Senpai, you are...
...going inside me again!
I'm having a hard time here...
But I can feel you...
Wow, your dick is ravaging me!
It's so deep!
Your dick is filling me up!
This makes my insides feel so amazing!
Oh no!
Senpai...
I never felt like this before... I'm...
I'm coming!
I'm coming while getting
a creampie from senpai!
See you, then. Stay on your toes.
Kira...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time on Ane Chijo Max Heart
I played it cool at first, but now I'm serious.
You need your teacher to set you straight, huh?
Those memories that you
share with that little bitch...
...will all be overwritten by me!
I'll sandwich it between my tits,
then give it lots of rubbing.
This is an impossible feat for that bitch.
It's twitching! This sensation is heavenly, isn't it?
Right there... Your tongue is tracing on it!
It feels good! Your finger is fondling my pussy!
This is incredible! Your dick is scraping my insides!
That feels good! Right there! More!
The tournament is close so it can't be helped.
I'm sorry, senpai. It's cramped
in here but bear with it.
I-I think that they'll be out soon...
Hey, Kasuri! Don't do that!
Let's hurry up.
Just wait for a second!
It's so hard...
I really am the reason why senpai
got hard down there, after all.
Did you know, senpai?
I've never done it since the day you had my virginity.
I wanted to have more sex with you,
so I want you to violate me in my swimsuit.