Beautiful Honor Student who Madly Loves
Her Younger Brother: Kisaragi Sarasa
She is a beautiful girl with excellent grades, athletic skills, outgoing personality
and is well-esteemed even by the same gender just as one would expect
from a woman possessing both beauty and brains.
Although she was with her divorced mother, she ended up having to live
together with her younger brother after her mother's sudden demise.
One thing led to another and now that they are going to
the same school, she reveals her once concealed feelings.
That is, to make him hers no matter what, an immoral desire.
Sarasa's brother grew up to be the kind of man that suits her taste, but that fact
caused him to be approached by these "unfamiliar bugs" at the same time.
She spent days being eaten up by the anxiety that
some bitch from who knows where might have a piece of him.
This drove Sarasa to make a drastic change in her supposedly extensive plan.
She puts the plan in action on the very day when his brother starts
attending the same school as hers and forcibly set all the necessary conditions.
Rowdy Junior in School Swimsuit: Reizei Kasuri
Kasuri is a female junior and admirer of Kira.
She got admitted to their school on a swimming scholarship.
She also has a lot of fans due to her cheerful attitude and physically fit body,
and enjoys a high popularity together with the beautiful honor student Sarasa.
Kasuri finally got to meet his senior Kira who she has a huge crush on.
Her admiration pushed her to make an effort and attempt
to make herself look appealing to him.
One morning on her way to school, Kasuri comes across Kira.
He thought that it's her chance to greet him and dashed through
without a second thought.
However, Kasuri's body tensed up just when she's about to stop...
A Fine Young Man with an Excessively
Doting Older Sister: Kisaragi Kira
Kira was under Sarasa's care ever since he was a child.
For that reason, he never goes against her will, though he had his own questions about his daily life with his sister.
It's way different compared from what he generally heard
among his friends talking about their own homes:
Sarasa is overprotective and gives him excessive physical intimacy.
She is renowned for being a beautiful honor student.
Although having that kind of a sister is the reason
why he's always been envied, he thought that something
which started at that particular time is way too much.
Sarasa and Kira made love to each other
and he ended up giving her a creampie.
After that, she straddled on his fleshy member,
filled with unbearable lust as she rode on him.
Their first time was in Sarasa's room, where she got deflowered
and climaxed with a face warped up by pleasure. She also intrudes
into his futon just as he wakes up and gives him a morning blowjob.
They copulate in the bath with foamy bubbles all over their bodies as well.
It's been a year since the relationship
that no one can know the siblings have started.
The number of times of being at risk of getting caught
in their depraved acts have escalated way beyond belief.
Sarasa does an excellent job of getting creampies
and sucking him dry. However, she has been feeling restless
lately with their first year anniversary drawing near.
One day, the girl supposedly known as the "School Swimsuit Beauty"
jumps in front of his beloved Kira like a storm.
Never have Sarasa ever thought of this girl as a threat
who can break her and Kira apart from each other...
Nympho Sister
Max Heart
O
Ori
Origi
Origina
Original
Original A
Original Ani
Original Anim
Original Anima
Original Animati
Original Animatio
Original Animation
The Flat-chested Girl Kasuri: Senpai, have sex with me!
Last Time on Ane Chijo Max Heart
Please enjoy each and every day
of your school life to its fullest!
The same goes for romance, however...
Bear in mind of having a proper and
wholesome school life, okay?
That would be all from me, Kisaragi Sarasa.
Sis... Didn't that mouth say something
about proper and wholesome?
Ever since mom passed away,
fate has brought us together!
Whenever you're under the weather
and even when you're sound asleep,
I've been looking after you for all this time!
O-Okay... Thank you...
I tried to do my best!
I even want to praise myself for doing so!
And today...
The moment to reap my benefits finally came.
It's the moment that you'll be mine!
It's a tighter fit than I expected!
My pussy is getting tightly jammed with your dick!
Your dick is amazing!
I think I'm gonna come even
though this is my first time!
Shoot your semen inside me!
Please, Kira!
Kira, wash me a lot down there!
Wash it properly!
That's great, Kira...
Stir me up right there!
Your dick...
Even though we're doing something bad...
You're saying that again... You keep
talking about the same things...
You say that, yet over the past year
you kept giving me creampies!
Even if you say that...
Kira, you're being rough!
You keep thrusting deep into me!
My pussy is writhing from pleasure!
That's good, Kira!
I'm coming! Coming, coming, I'm coming!
I'm being filled with a huge amount
of semen from your dick!
Kira, you are mine.
Including all of your semen, okay?
You're the only one for me, sis.
Gosh... You're so slow, Kira.
Are you lacking exercise?
You sure have some stamina...
That's because I've been exercising
ever since that time with you.
Are you alright?
Ah, Umm... Thank you!
I'm, well... Please excuse me!
Uhh, ohh... Are you alright too, sis?
Phew... That was surprising!
I got embraced by Kira-senpai!
I always knew that he's cool!
He caught me up between
his arms with such ease!
Phew, it's finally noontime...
Under Construction
Sis, how far do we have to go?
I am angry.
Seeing my lover wrapping
his arms on another woman
just like a hostile ruffian hurts my feelings!
How did you even come to that?
Sure, I ended up catching her into my arms,
but she's more like a little sister
than a woman to me.
Huh?! Don't mess around with me!
There's no way for a filthy
bitch to look like a little sister!
How dare you hurt your sister's feelings
not only once, but twice in a row!
That's just a false accusation.
You'll let me at least give you a lap pillow to appease my anger, right?
I will what?
Ouch! Uhh...
Sitting on your face feels good...
Your mouth is hitting against
my pussy and clitoris...
They both feel good!
No, Kira!
No! Wait, Kira!
Don't do that, stop!
Do you have any idea where we are right now, sis?
No!
Are you a pervert that gets aroused
by your brother spanking you?
You're wrong—
No, I'm not! Damn...
Kira, your dick suddenly went in!
Getting drenched like this... So much for
being an honor student. Am I right, sis?
No way! I can't hold myself back
because it's your dick I'm having!
It's so deep!
If you keep pushing it that deep...
No, don't do this! We'll end up getting caught!
What are you talking about after starting this?
If you want to be exposed that much,
then let's show the world.
Kira, don't!
This is too embarrassing even for me!
This is gonna make me come!
I can feel a big one coming!
I'll pour plenty of it into you.
You're going to drown my womb
with your semen, huh?
Come, Kira!
Come!
Pour your semen into my pussy—!
I'm drowning in your semen—!
See you later then, Kira.
I have a P.E. class for today.
Oh yeah, I never did it with Kira yet while wearing my gym uniform.
Why do you look so worn out?
You commuted to school today with
your very beautiful again this morning.
You always say stuff like that...
Well, that's because it's every man's dream
to be pampered by such a sister...
Listen to me, Kira. I need your help!
Huh? What is it this time, sis?
I'm having a trouble with my bra.
The hook won't lock in, so can you take a look at it?
H-Huh? You should ask your
friends for things like that.
What are you saying?
Are you fine with having a stranger
fiddle with your sister's bra?
Wouldn't that be another woman?
What if that girl is a lesbian or into 'girls love'?
Are you fine with it even if
I start to swing 'that' way?
How did you even arrive on that?
No one else outside my family can lay
their eyes on my perfect and chaste body.
That's how a pure maiden is.
"Pure", you say...
Alright, Kira. Fix your sister's bra.
It's your job as a younger brother.
Even if you say that, how can I do it here?
Oh, that's easy.
See, we're totally covered now.
Your sister is such a genius!
Gosh, Kira... I wonder what's on your mind.
Who knows? Just pull the back
of your clothes up already.
H-Hey! Sis, what are you doing?
How is it, Kira? Can you fix it?
What the hell are you thinking?
Kira, hurry up and get it done.
I'm waiting.
We're in such a place...
Kira, pull your tongue out.
Oh, it fell down.
Thank you, Kira.
Oh, we have a meeting after school,
so I can't go home with you.
I know it's sad, but you have to endure it.
Huh?
Kira-senpai? Why are you here?
Don't tell me that you came here to see me...
Nah, I live in this condo block...
What's the matter?
So we live in the same building, Kira-senpai.
What are the chances...
What's up, you're acting weird.
Y-You see, mama went out shopping
and I'm currently locked out.
So that's it, why don't we go in together?
But I don't have a key with me so
I won't be able to go in our unit.
And... I want to ask if you can
lend me your restroom...
Y-Yeah, that shouldn't be any problem.
Thank you very much, Kira-senpai.
Don't sweat it.
Oh... I showed Kira-senpai
an embarrassing side of me...
...but I'm at my limit now!
Kira, I'll mark the days of the
calender when I'm ovulating
so that you'll know when I'm fertile, okay?
Stop right there!
S-Sorry, I picked up something that I left inside.
Okay, you can go in now... huh?
Senpai...
I'm sorry...
I showed him something so
embarrassing, I'm done for...
I'm really sorry for scaring you!
This won't be enough to make it up to you,
but you can ask me anything that I can do.
Kira-senpai, then...
I-I want you to wipe me down here as well.
H-Hey... That's...
Senpai, you said that you'll do anything.
I've never been this humiliated
since the day I was born!
Kira-senpai, don't look away.
P-Please wipe it nice and clean!
To think that such a situation where
senpai touches me will come...
Isn't this good enough?
Senpai... I've been sweating down there, so...
Senpai's hand is hitting my very important place!
I'm sorry, it reeks of sweat...
No, that's not the case. It smells good...
Did he say that I smell good?
Senpai, did I make you hard down there?
S-Senpai!
I love you so much! So... So...
Kira-senpai, make love with me!
W-Wait, calm down!
Senpai... You got hard because of me, right?
I use my limbs on swimming so I'm nimble with them.
Kira-senpai, your cock is incredible!
This really is a bad idea, Kasuri!
Senpai, look at mine!
Put your cock inside my pussy!
Are you okay with this, Kasuri?
I've been telling you that it's okay!
I will give my first time to you, Kira-senpai!
Senpai, your cock and my pussy are kissing!
Mine's small, but...
It can take your cock inside!
Senpai, your cock took my first time
and penetrated me so deep inside!
Kira-senpai took my first time!
Nah, you forced it to me...
Gosh, you shouldn't make girls feel embarrassed!
It hurts a little, but not as much as I thought it would.
Kira-senpai, this sensation...
My crotch squeezes whenever
your thing reaches deep inside me!
Kira-senpai, you're touching my tits!
Oh! That feels great!
Senpai, it feels like I'm floating
when you push me below!
Shoot it from your cock, senpai!
Shoot lots of it inside me!
That would be dangerous.
Senpai, I want the baby seeds from your cock!
Come, Kira-senpai!
Shoot lots of it inside me!
It's gushing into me!
Kira-senpai, your sperm is bursting inside me!
Your stuff keeps on coming inside me.
I'm in heaven...
Kira, I'm home!
Th-This is...
Is he having a fling with some girl while I was away?
It's only our first year as newlyweds
and he's already cheating on me
in a very cliché soap opera fashion...
Kira!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization