Hirokazu's favorite snacks, juice and
the magazine he reads weekly.
Ok. everything's complete.
I'm home.
Hirokazu-kun, I bought the manga you asked me to.
Thank you.
Sorry for my intrusion.
Welcome to our home...
I'll just leave it here.
Hey Hirocchi, your sister is cute.
Is that so...
Cellphone sign: [ (From: Sister; Message: ( "w")]
What does this mean?
Ane Kyun!
The Girls has come in our House
They hang out here to study? I
wonder if she's his girlfriend.
Could they be planning to do something lewd.
What do you want?
There's nothing wrong having my classmate here.
yeah... you're different from me, you have your social life.
Social life?
I've been waiting for you to finish studying... kiss me..
What? Ok since it can't be helped.
She seems to be happy hugging me, giving
sweet voices and kissing lips.
I wonder when did start kissing with our tongue...
At first I just go along as Hirokazu-kun wants.
That's it... since Akazaki is waiting...
Just a little more, please...
His thing is now big...
Wait a little, I'll just take off my panty...
Hold your voice... Akazaki is just on the next room...
This sound, could it that his sister is masturbating?
At any rate, I need to end this quickly...
Oh god, he's penetrating my weak spot...
oh no, if you focus right there I'll soon come!
Hirokazu-kun... I'm about to come!
Nee-chan...
Oh shit... it's from Akazaki!
Hirokazu-kun?
Sorry I have to go.
jeez... Hirocchi you're late... what are you doing?
Umm... my mother just called...
What did she said?
It's not that serious, she said she'll be late tonight.
Is that so?
What?
Say Hlirocchi, do you have a girlfriend?
Why are you asking that question suddenly?
well... you brought a girl home, so do
you really plan on just studying?
Akazaki?...
The way, I don't have a boyfriend right now...
So it's fine if you do it...
Is this true? Akazaki was so cute and she's a dream
come true for me...
But what about my sister?
Hey Hirocchi... take off your clothes...
It doesn't matter if I got a girlfriend
since my sister and I were siblings...
Wow! This Is already erect...
That's because....
Akazaki stop that... that's dirty!
It's fine... It has a strong smell and excreting
juices... it's making me aroused...
You just came a little just now, right?
I'm sorry...
It's OK... I want you to shoot your
hot and sticky semen inside me...
A-Akazaki...
Just stay like that... I'll gonna insert it.
Is it fine to do it raw?
Yeah. Just come whenever you
want and I'll take it everything...
It's inside me...
Wow... It's warm and slimy...
your's too... It's big and feels so good!
So we'll just do it now...
This is great!
Oh no... your dick is....
Control your voice...
Sorry... I can't stop it since your dick is so good...
let's kiss so my void won't get out...
Oh shit... wait...
Your sperm is coming...
I'm sorry.
It's OK... I said you can come whenever you want.
Your dick is still hard, so let's just continue doing it.
I'm sure my sister will find out about this...
But since I'm at this point I can't stop it anymore!
Oh GOD, your dick is penetrating my sensitive part!
Hirokazu-kun is having sex... he's too
rough, will that feel really good?
There... oh shit... It's my first time
being penetrated this deep!
Me too... I feel so amazing!
I'm glad that you liked doing this with me!
oh shit... my breast feels so good...
Akazaki... you're so cute...
I'm about to come... my womb is tightening...
I 'm cumming!
Cum... cum a lot!
Coming while you're penetrating me feels so amazing...
I'm sorry... in the end we didn't get to study at all.
It's ok don't mimd it... anyways
i see you tomorrow at school.
Ok.
cellphone sign: [ (From Sister; Message:("w")]
How lucky of me to experience that and
I'm feeling like I'm in cloud nine...
But I suddenly got a text from my sister
that made me came back to my senses...
There's no other way... I'll just ask Akazaki for a little help!
Onee-san, did you masturbate
while hearing our lewd voices?
I'm sorry, I got turned on after doing something
with Hirokazu-kun a while ago.
If you naked in front of me, I'll forgive you.
Eh! Such thing...
It's fine, I'll undress myself too!
This is so embarrassing Akazaki-san...
Your skin is so beautiful!
No! We are both girls, we shouldn't...
you're easy to turn-on...
If you moan like that, I might get excited too...
My boobs are being fondled...
Hey, your nipples are already erect and hard!
Not there! Don't!
Onee-san, this area is so wet!
This is so embarrassing...
They can see all my lewd parts
Onee-san, you may tease my pussy...
Wow... its twitching and so wet... and this lewd scent!
More... Tease my pussy more...
This is great...
You’re already wet now... I think you're now ready for it!
Hirocehi come on here!
Sister... I can't resist it anymore!
Wait a sec..
Onee-san, since we are all here
Let's make ourselves feel good!
Stop! You suddenly... Please don't be too rough!
Wow... your pussy was already stretched like this!
Oh no... They can see my pussy while
it's being penetrated by a dick!
Amazing! Your pussy so tight!
It's inside me...
Hirokazu-kun... your's is hot inside me...
What's with me... my hips are moving on its own...
I'm going crazy.... my pussy feels so good!
That's it Onee-san... be more erotic!
So we... we three will do it together.
Sister... I'm about to come!
Your dick seems about to come... I'm
also gonna come... with everyone...
I think It's also fine to do with us three...
Wew... I shouldn't think too much of my
desires, such things are only at manga.
But seriously... there's nothing to be afraid of.
Its not that I'm going out with my sister.
Hirokazu-kun?
Yes!?
Well, about our relationship...
ahhm... about that... honestly I can't say that I like you...
since things happen so sudden
and I'm still recollecting myself.
So you stilt haven't given thought about it...
Nee-chan, could it be that you like me as a man?
What...
Her heartbeat is getting faster...
Yeah I love you... I loved you ever since we were kids...
Nee-chan!
Get over me and kiss me...
I want to be with you more...
I'll do it, I'll take off my clothes myself...
Being seen as I take off my clothes
kinda embarrassing for me...
I'll also take off your clothes for you...
Come to think of it... this is the first time he undressed me...
And the last time we saw each other naked
is When we take a bath together...
I'm feelings nervous...
Hirokazu-kun... my nipples are feeling tingling.
Oh no! My body is throbbing, I can't
stop letting out lewd sound!
My clitoris is now stiff, so even with
just his fingers makes me aroused!
Hirokazu-kun, I'm about to cum...
I Want to come while you're kissing me...
Onee-chan!
Nee-chan, even your ass is now wet...
Please don't say such things!
Inserting it now... not my fingers...
My dick will go inside you!
Disappointed with myself since
little brother will get my first time...
But it can't be stopped anymore!
It's inside, right?
Nee-chan, inside you feels So amazing!
Hirokazu-kun, you're stretching my insides!
Amazing! I'm fucking her slowly but it
feels like I'm already about to come!
Akazaki's warm pussy rubbing me feels so good...
Nee-chan's pussy is firmly tightening as if it was sucking me...
Amazing! His dick is penetrating insensitive parts...
nee-chan, does it feel great?
My mind is going crazy... It feels so good!
Well then, penetrating you more and shoot a lot!
Hirokazu-kun!
I'm cumming, nee-chan!
It's fine. You can come whenever you
want... and I'm also about to come...
Cumming! Cumming!
I... I want you to be my woman!
What are you saying? Hirokazu-kun, I'm yours ever since...
He come all the way inside, I don't
regret it... since I love Hirokazu-kun!
I'll be going out!
Good morning Hlirocchi!
I came here to pick you Up... let's go to school together!
Umm Akazaki...
I think I'm really in love with you...
You know... that's kinda...
Hey... let's do it again...
Umm...
Hirokazu-kun, I'll be going then...
Nee-chan!
Maybe it's better for me to be careful with your sister!
Again? A chick? Another strange text pictograph...
[note: His sister texted him with
chick pictograph using symbols.]
As if you're acting like a shy guy...
You should at least consider my feelings for you!
What's with her? I really don't get what she meant!