Hirokazu-kun's favorite snack,
favorite juice drink,
and other tasty small sweets.
Okay, perfect.
I'm home.
Hirokazu-kun, I've bought everything you wanted.
Oh, thanks.
Hello there!
We-Welcome...
I'll leave it here, okay?
Okay.
Hey, your elder sister is quite cute, Hirocchi.
Really?
Sender: Sis
To: Hirokazu
What is this?
Sister-Kyun!
A girl is in our house !
They're going to study here...
Is she his girlfriend?
Are they... planning on having sex?
What is it?
It's fine, right?
I just called a classmate over, that's all.
I guess you're right.
I'm different, compared to myself,
you've got your life under control.
Under control...?
I'll wait until your study session is over.
So, please kiss me.
What?
Jeez, you're really helpless.
She's happily dinging onto me.
Letting out that sweet voice.
And sucking on my lips.
I wonder,
when was the last time that we kissed deeply like this?
Before, you just led me all the way.
D-Done.
Akazaki's waiting for me.
Just a little more... please?
His thing, it's already getting big.
Wait.
I'll take off my panties.
Try to keep your voice down.
Akazak is on the other side of this wall.
Eh? This moan...
Is his sister masturbating right now?
Anyway, I need to finish this quickly...
What should I do?
He already knows my weak spots.
Don't...
If you keep rubbing me there...
I'm... going to cum...!
Hirokazu-kun... I'm cumming!
Nee-chan...
Oh crap, it's from Akazaki!
Hirokazu-kun?
Sorry, got to go!
Jeez, Hirocchi, you're late!
What were you doing?
Well... my parents called all of a sudden.
Your mom?
Y-Yeah, it's nothing that important though.
She said she'd be coming home late.
Oh...
What is it?
Hey, Hirocchi.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What?
W-Why are you asking me that?
Also,
you just invited a girl to your house.
Are we really just going to study?
Akazaki...?
You see, I don't have a boyfriend.
If it's you, I don't think I'd mind doing it.
Is this for real?
She's cute, and also my type,
but Nee-chan's already...
Hey, Hirocchi, why don't you strip too?
N-No...
I think it's perfectly fine even if I go out with someone.
Nee-chan and I are siblings anyway.
Wow, it's already hard.
But that's because...
Akazaki, you don't have to do that, it's dirty!
It's okay.
I'm actually aroused by its lewd smell.
A little bit came out.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I want you to release all of this sticky cum into me.
A-Akazaki...
Hirocchi, I'm going to put in already, okay?
Are you really fine with this?
Yep, and I'm going to take it all.
Just cum whenever you want to.
It's in.
It feels really hot, and it's so soft.
Your stiff and hard thing also feels good.
I'm going to start moving, okay?
Amazing...
I'm feeling all tingly.
Keep your voice down!
Sorry about that.
But your dick feels really g-great, I just can't stop.
How about a kiss?
Let's seal it with a kiss.
I'm about to... oh crap...!
Your cum, it's coming out...
Sorry...
I said it was okay.
I said you could cum whenever you wanted, right?
Your dick is still hard.
Let's keep on doing this.
I’m sure Nee-chan's already noticed.
But, I just can't hold back anymore.
Oh wow...
Your dick is really hitting me where it feels good.
Hirokazu-kun's having sex...
Oh no, it seems really intense.
Does it really feel that good?
Oh yes, oh yes...
I can really feel it deep inside me.
And it's my first time feeling that way.
M-Me too, it feels really good for me.
Maybe we're really compatible when it comes to sex.
I'll be happy if that's true.
This feels intense...!
Hirocchi, not my breasts!
Akazaki, you really are cute!
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
M-My womb is twitching...
I'm going to cum!
It's okay, just cum a lot.
It's rubbing hard inside so it feels really good.
Sorry about that.
In the end we weren't able to study.
It's okay, I don't mind.
Well then, see you at school tomorrow.
O-Okay.
My mind is still wandering from my apparent luck earlier.
But all of it turned upside down upon seeing her message.
It can't be helped.
I'll just have to ask Akazaki for help concerning this matter.
Big sis, were you masturbating when
you heard us having sex yesterday?
I'm sorry, but I happened to hear Hirokazu-kun's voice,
and I started feeling aroused.
I'll forgive you, if you strip in front of me.
Eh? That's just...
It's perfectly fine.
I'm also going to strip, okay?
Akazaki-san, this is embarrassing.
Wow, your skin looks beautiful big sis.
Don't...!
We're both girls...
This can't...
You get aroused pretty easily.
If you keep moaning like that, I'll start feeling excited myself.
My breasts are being fondled.
Look, can you tell?
Your nipples are already having a hard on.
T-That part is...
No...
Not there...
Your thing here is already very wet.
This is embarrassing.
All of my shameful parts are exposed.
Big sis, you can play with my pussy if you want to.
It's really twitching.
It's also wet, and has a lewd smell.
That's... please lick it more.
She's getting aroused by it.
So it feels good for her.
Your tongue...
Your tongue is going inside...!
That should be enough.
Hirocchi, you can come out now.
Nee-chan, I can't hold back any longer.
Just wait...!
Big sis, since we're all here, why don't
we all make each other feel good?
S-Stop, don't push hard so suddenly...!
Wow, amazing.
So a pussy can stretch this far.
I'm exposed.
She's watching me being fucked.
Oh wow, Nee-chan your pussy's really gripping me tight.
I'm being stirred up.
Your thing feel really hot, Hirokazu-kun.
What should I do?
My hips just started moving on their own.
I'm beginning to go crazy.
But it feels really good.
It's okay, big sis.
Just become as horny as you want to.
Let's all do this together from now on, okay?
Nee-chan, no... I'm about to cum!
His dick is twitching.
I'm cumming... I'm going to be cummed in.
I'm cumming with everyone...!
I think... doing a threesome isn't bad at all...
Or maybe not.
Guess it can't really work out that easily, huh?
This isn't some manga anyway.
If you think about it logically,
there's actually no need to feel uneasy.
I'm not going out with Nee-chan anyway.
Hirokazu-kun?
U-Uh, yeah.
Umm...
Are you going out with that girl?
Well, I'm not really sure.
She never really told me that she liked me.
Everything was so sudden, so my heart never really had time to...
If you're not going out with her yet...
T-Then, I want to continue with what we were doing earlier.
N-Nee-chan, do you like me as a man?
Jeez, you're asking me that now?
Nee-chan's heartbeat that I'm feeling...
It's starting to beat faster.
Yeah, I do.
Even when we were kids, I already loved you back then.
Nee-chan...
Kiss me more, Hirokazu-kun.
I want to become one with you.
It's okay, I'm going to take it off for you.
Umm... I want to take it off myself.
Me too, I want to strip you too.
Okay.
Oh yes, perhaps this is the first time
that I've been stripped by someone.
And the last time he saw my skin exposed like this,
was when we were still bathing together.
I feel really nervous.
Hirokazu-kun, my nipples feel tingly.
Oh no...
My body is starting to twitch.
I can't stop moaning...
My clitoris is already hard,
so I'm feeling really aroused just by getting it rubbed lightly.
Hi-Hirokazu-kun, I'm about to cum.
I want to cum while we kiss.
Nee-chan...
Nee-chan, you're already this wet down here.
Please, don't say that.
I'm going in now.
Not with my finger, but my dick.
Okay.
For my first time to be with a family member...
it feels a bit weird, but I can't turn back now.
It's in already.
Nee-chan, your insides feel really great.
Hirokazu-kun, my insides are being stretched.
I'm about to cum already even though I'm pushing slowly.
Akazaki's insides also feel soft, as if it's trying to suck me in.
It feels as if it's giving me a really tight handjob.
Amazing...
All of my pussy's soft spots are being rubbed by his dick.
Nee-chan, does it feel good?
Yes, it feels so good that my mind is going blank.
I'm going to continue rubbing it hard,
and then cum inside at the end.
Hirokazu-kun...
I'm cumming, Nee-chan!
It's okay.
Just cum lots.
I'm going to cum too.
It's pouring in...
Nee-chan, I want you to be my girl.
What are you saying?
I've already been yours for a long time now.
I have been cummed inside, but... I don t regret anything.
I really love him very much.
I'm off.
Hello, Hirocchi!
I came to get you.
Let's go to school together.
Hey, Akazaki...
I think I'm really in love with you now.
W-Well... but that's...
Hey, let's do it again, okay?
O-Okay...
Hirokazu-kun, I'm going already.
N-Nee-chan...!
Your sis might have read our situation.
A-Again?
A c-chick?
Here's another strange emoticon.
What was that?
Getting all lovey dovey back there.
He should really try to understand how I feet.
What is this?
I don't really know!