I can't keep up with Yoshiharu's craziness.
I have to try to avoid him.
Don't say something like that.
Isn't it against the law?
You idiot.
Wait.
It's my first time.
I'm coming!
Your cock is making me come!
Yeah. I have to pull through until spring so we can be normal siblings.
Sana!
Sana.
Sana! Hey!
What is it?
Your brother brought your lunch.
I didn't ask for this.
Well, mom asked me to.
She said you rushed to school.
She made it after you'd left.
Don't look him in the eyes.
You're going to remember that time.
He's grasped my hand again.
Sis...
I want to talk to you later.
Can we talk during break?
W-What?
Am I retarded, talking with that quivering voice?
I'm wearing my feelings on my sleeve.
Now it must seem like I want to...
There's sweat on his hand.
It doesn't feel bad...
Ouch! Ouch!
Sana.
Be more gentle with your little brother.
Why did I come here?
Sis...
Wait...
This hurts... Hey, this hurts.
I can't shake him off.
When did he get so strong?
I've tried to stave it off by wanking, but I can't.
I...
Yoshiharu...
You...
I swear I only wanted to bring you your lunch.
But when I saw you...
But we're at school...
I can't wait until we're back home.
He's too greedy. I've only just lost my virginity.
But...
You're rubbing your cock against me.
I know.
Wait.
Sis...
You're getting wet there.
No... No...
We'll never be normal siblings at this rate.
Don't put it in.
Sis...
But... But...
No.
I said no!
Wait.
Ouch.
All right then, but at least use your mouth.
But...
It's my first time getting a blowjob, so...
But that's...
I can't really tell you what to do.
Will you be happy if I do this?
Yeah.
It's so hot.
So this is what the real thing feels like.
It feels so good. So good.
I can feel his veins thumping.
His hips are shaking too.
He must really enjoy this.
This is fun.
Hey...
Can you take it into your mouth too, not just lick it?
Don't demand too much now.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's so hot and wet.
It felt so good when I kissed you.
I've really wanted to get a blowjob from you since then.
I'm so excited.
Try taking it in as far as possible.
As far as possible.
Yeah.
Like that.
That's awesome.
Sis...
He sounds so happy.
Oh, well.
This doesn't bother me.
I'm happy, actually.
That's it.
I'm gonna come.
I'm gonna come!
Let me come in your mouth.
His cock is so big.
I don't have any tissues with me.
Whoah!
That makes me so happy.
Why?
It's so bitter! It tastes horrible!
Sorry.
What am I doing?
Why did I swallow his come?
It didn't even taste good!
Am I a nympho?
Let me repay you!
Hey! Don't take my panties off!
What's with this posture?
Don't stare at it.
This is so embarrassing.
You're so wet.
Don't stare at it.
You got excited from the licking.
Shut u—
No!
That tickles!
That's close to my butt!
This feels so good.
I get shivers when he's so slow.
Yoshiharu...
You can be more forceful.
What am I saying?
He's going to assume stuff now.
Sis!
He's drinking my piss.
I don't have any strength left.
Wait! Wait!
I can't do it now.
I don't have any strength left...
I can't resist...
Don't just use my body because you feel like it.
Sorry.
But your vagina looks so good.
I wanted to put it in the entire time I was licking it.
You idiot.
Come on, Sis.
Put your arms around my neck.
No, no... I'm gonna... No...
Sis...
I love you...
Don't tell me that now...
Sis...
I'm serious. I love you.
I don't care.
We shouldn't be doing this.
What am I saying?
Don't I love him too?
I hate you! Hear me?
I'll be patient until you love me, then.
Come on, look here.
He's kissing me.
Sis...
He's doing it faster now.
He's going to come soon.
It's so good.
I'm going to come inside.
He's going to come.
He's jerking in and out.
I'm going to come inside.
I love you!
Oh, no... It's just like back then.
I just want to feel good...
Faster!
Go faster with your cock!
Inside me!
He's doing his best until the end...
You're tightening up...
Why does it make me so happy what he said?
I must be crazy.
Sana!
What is it?
Your brother... In PE...
Yoshiharu!
What are you doing, Sana?
But...
He was just feeling a bit light-headed.
Huh?
Yoshiharu, you jerk!
That's punishment for making me worry.
I'm glad you were worried.
I didn't like it.
I'm going back to class.
Know your limit next time.
Hey, wait!
Sis... I love how you smell.
Honestly...
Honestly what?
You're so beautiful.
What are you saying?
It went in smoothly.
Jerk.
It's obvious that it's going to adjust to your cock if we keep doing it.
I can feel it...
Sis...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna come...
Why did you get light-headed anyway?
I was pretty exhausted from work.
Your real job should be studying.
I know.
Is there a reason?
Hey...
You're going to live alone starting with spring, right?
Yeah.
I want to move out too.
Why?
I want to live close to you.
What are you talking about, Yoshiharu?
Oh, no...
I can't hide how happy this makes me...
I'm so glad...
Yoshiharu...
Do you know where I'm moving?
But...
It's around the corner.
Where did you think it would be?
Around the corner?!
I won't tell you that I love you yet.
There's always a part of you that enrages me.