W
Sister Love
Like. Hate.
Love.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Nee-chan, mom's calling–
Hey, idiotic Yoshiharu!
Always knock before opening the door!
I've told you that so many times already, haven't I?
Seriously?
You don't need to get that angry...
Murmuring like that looks depressing, you know?
It seems that I'm hated by my elder sister.
But I...
No matter how coldly she treats me...
I am just hopelessly in love with her.
Woah. Look at them, Yoshiharu.
Looks like the 3rd year girls are having P.E. for their next class.
Oh, that girl's really cute.
Yeah.
Look, that girl with the headband.
Her breasts are so big!
Yeah.
Huh? That's my sister.
Eh?!
I guess she looks cute to just about any guy.
Oh, yeah. Nee-chan will be leaving home this spring.
Hey.
Earth to Yoshiharu!
Were you listening to me?
Sorry.
Nee-chan, umm...
Nee-chan.
You want something?
Can I talk to you for a bit?
What?
W-Well, you know...
What is it?
Please don't be mad at me, but...
Seriously, what is it?
I was asked by a classmate of mine.
What?
That guy is a fan of yours,
and he wanted me to introduce you to him.
What?
What's up with that?
If it's not okay, he said that your mail would do just fine.
Of course it's not okay!
I guess you're right.
O-Okay, then.
I'll just make up an excuse and turn down his request.
Yoshiharu, are you really fine with those kinds of things?
I don't really want to do it either.
Then, you didn't have to tell me that to begin with!
What?
Nee-chan, you've been avoiding me lately, right?
What are you...? Let me go.
You don't have a boyfriend right, Nee-chan?
H-Hey, are you trying to pick a fight?
Sorry that I don't have one.
This spring, you're going to leave the house and live by yourself, right?
If I simply leave things like this and let you go, I feel like I'm going to regret it.
That's why...
That's why before that...
We might even become more distant this way, but...
I love you, Nee-chan!
Eh?
This idiot.
For him to suddenly say something like this...
This isn't fair!
You... idiot.
Suddenly telling me something like that...
It isn't fair.
What? No way!
Oh, no.!
Nee-chan...
Hey...
Nee-chan, I've always wanted to fondle them like this.
Hey, you idiot!
Don't get too cocky!
B-But...
I was just surprised when you suddenly told me that you loved me.
I-I never said that it was okay for you to do this...
Saying that you like me...
You idiot...
P-Pervert...!
This isn't happening!
This... No...!
You're just my little brother!
Hey!
It's wet.
So it got really wet with your little brother's touch.
Th-This is a physiological phenomenon.
It happened on its own because you're fondling my breasts...
You're too persistent...!
Stop fooling around...
N-No...
If this continues...
H-Hey!
Let's go to the bed.
H-Hey, why does it have to be like this?
N-Nobody's asking for it.
Hey!
Nee-chan, I love you!
I already heard that from you!
I see.
Stop!
Hey, stop!
Idiot!
Nee-chan's clitoris is getting stiff.
It's small, but I know it's aroused.
Wait... That's...
Don't!
I'm sensitive there!
Hey, don't...!
Idiot...
Nee-chan...
No, no...!
Wait, it's my first time...
S-Sorry, but I just can't stop it anymore...
I-It's in.
This big thing is in me...
Nee-chan, it doesn't hurt, does it?
Stop...
Umm, I've just taken your virginity,
but I promise to treasure you.
Wh-What are you deciding things by yourself for?
Idiot...
Hit me if you don't want it.
Th-Then I will stop,
and I will also give up on you.
I'm definitely...
I'm definitely going to hit you after this.
So, if you're prepared for that,
then why don't you just do what you want.
Yeah, okay then.
As long as this continues,
you can hit me.
You can hit me as many times as you want to.
That's what I'm....
You're just too cocky!
It's widening...
Don't widen it up like that!
It's opening.
It's unfolding with your cock...
I'm inside my Nee-chan.
Oh, no!
Don't look!
Don't look at it!
Yes...
Oh, no.
Oh, no...
Don't move.
No!
I can't...
I can't hold it in anymore.
I'm losing it...
I'm going to lose it!
No!
Oh no, I'm about to cum.
I don't care what happens anymore.
I'm going to cum inside Nee-chan
and make her mine.
My...
My...!
Nee-chan!
I'm...
Cumming!
My insides are twitching...
Wow...
I've released it into Nee-chan's womb.
It might have been unfair for you that I did it this way,
but I'm serious about my feelings for you,
and I'm going to cherish you, Nee-chan!
That's why...
www.SubDESU-H.net
Ow!
Nee-chan?
I said it earlier, didn't I?
That I was going to hit you afterwards.
Nee-chan...
I even planned on leaving the house this spring, so I could keep my distance from him.
He always comes closer to me no matter how much I try to push him away.
That's why I...
Flowing inside me is Yoshiharu's hot semen...
It's so hot that I feel like it's going to seep into my head.
That feeling...
Yoshiharu...
I love you, Nee-chan!
I'm serious about my feelings for you,
and I'm going to cherish you, Nee-chan!
That's why...
That felt so good.
Yoshiharu's...
But even so,
it was just way too sudden.
Yoshiharu, you idiot!
Eh?
I felt really bad for having surprised you like that.
But...
No, wait!
But if I hadn't been honest about it,
I think I never would've told you about my true feelings, Nee-chan.
A-Anyway!
How long have you been standing there?
Yo-shi-ha-ru...
I won't get angry so tell me already.
Hey!
Let go of my hand, Yoshiharu!
Umm...
Spit it out already.
Since the part when you called my name and your hands were between your legs...
You...!
Nee-chan's panties are wet.
Stop that. It's still sensitive.
I said you can't!
Not there...
It's dirty...
It's not dirty,
but it has the smell of a woman.
No.
Stop!
If you continue that,
my panties will be really soaked.
I'm going to look like a pervert!
I'm going to make you feel good,
so I want you to do the same.
Nee-chan...
Nee-chan's mouth feels warm.
Yoshiharu's cock is too big.
Also, I didn't notice it earlier,
but it really stinks.
And this thing just went inside of me...
This big thing was just inside of me earlier,
and soon it will be inside me again...
Nee-chan, I'm about to cum!
What? No way!
No!
No way...!
Well then, Nee-chan.
Here I go.
W-Wait.
I still have to make you feel good.
It's going inside me...
It's rubbing my insides.
Does it feel good, Nee-chan?
It feels good...
So please move faster...
It's stirring me up.
It really feels good inside you.
Yoshiharu, do you really like my breasts?
I like your breasts very much.
Then... Then fondle my breasts more, okay?
Hey, Yoshiharu.
What is it, Nee-chan?
You love me, right?
Yeah.
I...
... love you, Nee-chan.
I love...
I'm your number one, right?
You are my number one, Nee-chan.
My breasts are...
These breasts are also my number one.
Oh, no!
No...
If you play with it like that...
I'm going to...!
I'm going to cum
with Yoshiharu's cock inside me...!
Don't!
I'm still very sensitive.
Y-Yoshiharu!
It's so big that I'm throbbing inside.
Nee-chan...
You're squeezing me tighter!
It's because your cock is making my pussy feel really good.
I can't...
I can't hold it anymore...
I'll be filled with cum,
be impregnated,
and will become Yoshiharu's woman!
Yoshiharu's cock...
... felt really good!
I'm in love with Yoshiharu...
www.SubDESU-H.net