I just can't put up with his sudden outbursts anymore.
I must try to avoid him as much as possible.
For you to suddenly say something like that...
It's unfair.
Idiot...
W-Wait, it's...
It's my first time...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming with Yoshiharu's cock.
That's right.
I must end this before spring,
and we'll go back to being normal siblings.
Sana!
Hey, Sana!
What is it?
Your little brother brought your lunch.
I didn't ask you to do this, you know.
Well, you see...
I was asked by Mom to bring this.
You left for school too early,
so she made it after you left.
I musn't.
I must not make eye contact with him.
All those things will come back into my mind again.
He held my hand again.
Nee-chan,
I want to talk to you about something later.
Are, you free on lunch?
What?
A-Are you an idiot?
Your shaky voice clearly tells me that
you're planning something else!
Do you really think I'm just going to...
I'm just going to agree just like that?
Yoshiharu's hand is sweaty.
It feels quite good, I think.
Sana, why don't you be a little bit nicer
to your brother once in a while?
Despite my thoughts earlier, I still came somehow...
Nee-chan...
Hey, that hurts.
I said it hurts!
I can't break free.
Since when did he become this strong?
Since that time, I've tried to control
myself and just masturbate alone...
I can't do it.
Yoshiharu, you really are a...
Even today, I only just wanted to bring you your lunch.
But as soon as I saw your face...
That doesn't mean we should do it at school!
But I can't hold back even at home anymore.
Geez...
Just because he's no longer a virgin...
This is still too dose for comfort!
But...
Hey, it's hitting me idiot!
I'm doing it on purpose.
Wait...
Nee-chan, it's already getting wet down there.
No, we musn't...!
We might not be able to go back to being normal siblings again.
Don't put it in.
Nee-chan...
But...
You can't! I said you can't!
Hey, wait... That hurts.
Ouch!
If you really insist on not doing it,
then could you do it with your mouth?
Then that would be...
It's also my first time, so I'm not really sure how to do it.
It's okay as long as I make this feel good, right?
It's warm.
So this is how the real thing feels.
It feels really good down there.
It's twitching.
His hips are also shaking.
So it feels that good...
This might be fun.
Hey, don't just lick it.
Try sucking on it, too.
He's getting cocky now.
There...
It's warm and feels just right.
It felt really good when we kissed.
Then I thought it would even be better if I could get a blowjob.
I'm a bit moved.
Try sucking it all the way in.
Just suck in as much as you can.
There.
Then continue sucking even as you pull out.
There, that felt really great.
Nee-chan...
Letting out such a happy moan...
Well, I guess this is okay.
I don't really hate it anyway.
I rather feel happy, too.
I'm about to cum.
It's going to come out.
I'm cumming.
Let me cum in your mouth!
Yoshiharu's thing is getting even bigger.
I don't have tissues with me.
That somehow makes me feel very happy.
Why...?
It was very bitter.
Yuck.
I'm sorry.
What's happening to me?
After drinking Yoshiharu's cum, I just felt more...
It didn't even taste good.
It's like I'm a pervert!
I'm going to properly do my part, too.
Huh?
Hey, wait...
Why are you taking my panties off?
What's with this position?
Don't look at it too much.
This is too embarrassing.
It's really wet.
S-Stop... Don't stare at it.
Did you get horny when you licked it?
Shut up!
Don't...
No! Oh wow...
It's itching for more...
No! That's my butthole!
You can't...!
Th-This feels good...
I get all numb as he does it gently.
Yoshiharu, try doing it a bit more roughly.
What am I saying?
Now he's really going to lose it.
Hey, Nee-chan!
Yoshiharu's drinking my pee...
Oh no, I'm feeling weak...
Wait, just wait...
We can't do it now.
I'm feeling weak, so I won't be able to resist.
Don't get too cocky
and use my body just like this.
Sorry, but your pussy looks very nice.
I wanted to enter you while I was licking you earlier.
You idiot.
Here, wrap your arms around my neck.
Oh no, my voice...
It's hitting my womb...
I'm...
Nee-chan, does my cock feel good?
Even if you ask me that...
Nee-chan, I've loved you for a long time.
It's the truth.
I don't care about that!
You're doing this to me right now, you idiot.
What am I saying?
When I realized it, I was already... For a long time...
I hate you!
I hate you, undersand?
That's okay.
I'm going to work hard until you love me.
Hey, face this way.
We're kissing...
Nee-chan...
Nee-chan!
He's moving faster and faster.
He's going to cum already.
It feels great, Nee-chan.
I'm about to cum inside.
He's really cumming.
It feels hot, and it's throbbing inside me.
Nee-chan, I'm cumming inside.
I love you!
I want to experience the same great feeling that I felt before.
Hurry!
I love you too, so cum inside me already.
He wants to release it to the very end.
I got squeezed by Nee-chan...
For me to feel this happy because of what Yoshiharu's said...
I'm really starting to lose it.
Sana!
Hey, Sana!
What is it?
Your brother was brought to the infirmary.
Yoshiharu...
Yoshiharu!
Sana, what are you doing?
But...
Your brother just collapsed because of stress.
Yoshiharu, you idiot!
That's what you get for making me worry like that.
So you were that worried...
I'm quite pissed off though.
Well, I'm going back to class now.
Take care of your body, okay?
Hey!
I love Nee-chan's scent.
You're...
I'm what?
You're really beautiful after all.
Idiot.
It went in smoothly.
Idiot...
It's because we do it everyday,
so it's already used to your cock.
My insides...
...feel tight.
Nee-chan...
Nee-chan!
I'm about to...
I'm about to cum...
Just why in the world did you do to collapse due to stress?
I've been busy with my part-time job.
What?
A student's job is to study!
I know that, but...
If there's a good reason for this, then tell me.
Well, you see...
You're going to move out and live alone next spring, right?
Yup.
I'm also thinking of leaving home.
Why?
I want to be with you, Nee-chan.
Huh... What?!
What is Yoshiharu saying?
Oh no, my mind's going blank with happiness.
My heart's also throbbing wildly.
Yoshiharu...
Do you know where I'm going to move to?
But...
It's going to be somewhere near the station.
Where did you think it would be?
That's just nearby!
I'm not going to say that I love him yet.
'Coz he's just so cute that I'm starting to get pissed off.