What, you want to barrow ''it'' again?
Please, Kaoru-neesan.
There's a dojin event soon and
l want to use it as reference.
What's so great about that thing?
Rulisu sure is strange.
lt's her job...
A job?
Of course, l at least make money unlike someone else.
H, hey, are you talking about me!?
At least l don't sleep with random guys.
Hey, don't start a fight.
lt's a Family Affair
Master, please forgive me.
l...l am your dirty little bitch.
Please have mercy.
lt's already so hard...
Rulisu-neesan, you are a cute little bitch.
Master, may l please suck on this?
No.
Just kidding.
Thank you very much!
How is is, Master?
Does it feel good?
Please let this bitch in heat drink some milk.
Alright, standup.
Master, this is embarrassing!
lt's a great view.
This is humiliating, Master.
Forgive me.
Rulisu-neesan, you are overflowing with pussy juice.
Ouch.
lt's such a nice view, Rulisu-neesan.
So embarrassing!
Master, please give me your...hot rod.
Please.
You want...this?
Yes, l do.
Please stick it in!
lf you want to feel good, start moving your hips.
OK.
lt's in...so deep....
Rurisu-neesan...it's so tight!
M, Master, l'm going to cum again!
Rulisu-neesan, l'm about to cum...as well!
lnside, please!
Cuming!!!
l wanted it inside...
You're cruel, Master.
Tokiko-neesan, you should slow down!
Don't worry, we're fine.
Well, how are you doing Keisuke?
H, hey!
Are your man parts working properly?
l will run some tests and see if it function properly.
Don't worry, leave it to me.
Tokiko-neesan, the wheels!
Don't worry, l'm an android.
W, wait!
What ever you are, at least stop the car!
Alright.
Fellatio mode.
Tokiko-neesan, what in the world is going on?
l am your personal love android
sent from the future, Keisuke.
Collecting data.
T, Tokiko-neesan, it's...amazing!
Check completed, hardness 98%.
l still need to do more checking.
Let me collect more data.
Sex mode.
Here l go.
Pleasure level rising.
Extra mode.
Pleasure meter has reached the red zone.
Capacity max.
There's too much data to collect.
An error has occured.
l can't catch up with...
Cuming!
l'm sorry.
l couldn't save the data so we need to do it again later.
Love...l love you.
Manager, please love me instead of your wife...!!
K, Keisuke-kun!
What are you doing here, Kaoruko-neesan?
Well....don't look.
Well, alright.
l'll pretend l didn't see this.
But l would like to see more.
B, but!
lf you can't, l'll just...
Fine!
But it's embarrassing so don't stare.
Alright, just hurry it up Kaoruko-neesan.
Don't tell anyone.
l can't take this.
Keisuke-kun, come here.
l need it!
Fuck me in front of his desk!
Eh, what kind of sis are you...
H, hurry, give it to me!
Push in.
Don't, people outside can see!
Kaoruko-neesan, l'm going to cum!
No, not inside.
Kaoruko-neesan...c, cuming!
No, please not inside!
You came inside?
l'll forgive you today.
And cut!
Good job.
Get some rest.
Time to leave!
OK.
What, why are you here!
Our sisters asked me to
check how your work is going.
Stop being nosy, l don't like it but since l
was introduced to this place, l will work.
Anyway Keisuke, why are you taping me?
Anne-neesan, do you always do this?
You want me to help you with your man-hate?
lt hurts, let me go.
lt's a nice view, Anne-neesan.
Keisuke, l'll!!
Sis, you'll feel better once you accept men.
No, don't look!
Stop, don't come near me!
C, can't be?
You were setting me up from the start.
K, Keisuke?
Anne-neesan, here l come.
K, Keisuke, anything but that!
Don't push it in!
lt...hurts!
lt hurts, stop!
lt hurts, it hurts!
Pull out, pull out!
Sis, doesn't it feel good?
lt might be addicting.
Lies, it's not!
Stop...
Please stop!
Anne-neesan...
Doesn't it feel good to be washed?
Now, let me clean the front.
Turn this way.
Uh, OK.
lt's been years since l washed you clean, Keisuke-kun.
You have really grown since.
Don't be shy, move your hand.
You don't need...
No, we have to clean it.
Move your hand.
A, alright.
There, that's a good boy.
Oh, oh?
ls it embarrassing to have your sister clean this?
lt's getting bigger.
Feels good?
Y, yeah...it does.
Keisuke-kun, do you want your sis to do ''it''?
lt?
Follow me.
Lemon-neesan, where's the water?
Lie on this mattress.
Like this?
Yeah, hold on a sec.
l'll do ''it'' now.
You're so cute, Keisuke-chan.
Well, does it feel good?
Y, yeah...
l'm such a bad sister for doing this to her brother.
But we're not really related so it's fine, right?
Cuming!
Delicious.
Not there.
You're beautiful Anne.
You've become a true woman.
She won't be able to live without a man's touch now.
She's so perverted.
But...
Alright, lets clean ourselves.
Afterwards, again, OK?