Big Sister Love - Like ・Hate・Love (Ane Koi - Suki ・Kirai ・Daisuki) ＃01
Sexlation: Naoya (Waku Fapsubs)
Nee-chan, Mom is calling you.
Hey, idiot Yoshiharu!
I've told you many times to knock before you open!
What's with that? You don't have to be so mad.
They way you whisper when you talk is annoying.
Looks like my sis hates me.
But for me
No matter how cold she is
I can't help but fall in love with her.
Look, Yoshiharu.
The third years are having PE lessons next.
Oh, that chick is cute.
Hey, look at that girl with the hair band.
Her chest are big too.
Oh, that's my elder sister.
Indeed, she looks cuter than the others.
Even her glare from this far is filled with hatred.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Are you listening?
Sorry.
Nee-chan. Hey, Nee-chan.
What do you want?
Can we talk?
What?
That's...
Yeah?
Can you relax and just listen to me?
Like I said, what is it?
A classmate asked a favor.
About?
He's a fan of yours, so he wants me to introduce you.
Huh? The hell's that?
At least meet him if you don't want to.
Obviously not!
Yeah, I guess.
I understand. I'll just randomly think up an excuse to reject him.
Yoshiharu, do you think that will work?
I think it won't be something very nice.
Then you shouldn't have brought something like that up in the first place.
What now?
You've been avoiding me since a while ago.
What do you mean. Explain yourself?
Y-You are not attached, are you?
H-Hey, are you picking a fight with me?
What a foul mouth.
You'll move out when Spring comes and won't be staying here anymore, right?
I might regret it if this continues on.
So, before that happens
We might become even more distant
I love you, Nee-chan.
Eh? You idiot.
Saying something like that suddenly is breaking the rules.
You idiot....
Saying something like this suddenly
Don't you think it's against the rules.
You're kidding? Stop.
Nee-chan.
W-Wait.
I've always wanted to touch you like that, Nee-chan.
Hey, you fool. Don't get to ahead of yourself.
B-But...
I'm only surprised by your sudden confession.
I didn't agree to such a thing.
Do you like me?
Just like an idiot.
You pervert.
Impossible.
This kind of thing.
No-
You're my brother.
Hey.
It's wet.
You're already so slippery and overflowing just from your brother's touch.
It's only a physiological reaction.
My breasts were fondled so...
You're persistent, it's high time you stop.
Don't.
If you continue...
H-Hey.
Let's get on bed.
H-Hey, how did it turn out this way.
I didn't even promise you anything...
Hey, wait.
Nee-chan, I love you.
I heard it just now already.
I see.
S-Stop.
Y-You idiot.
Your clitoris is getting hard.
It may be small, but I can tell just from touching.
Wait.
That's.
No, my clitoris is very sensitive.
Hey, stop it.
Idiot.
Nee-chan.
No.. don't...
Wait a sec, I'm...
This is my first time.
Sorry, but there's no way I can stop now.
A-Amazing.
I-It's inside of me?
S-Something so huge.
Nee-chan, does it hurt?
Stop it.
I-I have taken your first time away
So I'll cherish you for sure.
W-Why the hell are you expressing your resolve by yourself.
Stupid.
You can whack me if you hate it.
Then I'll stop.
I'll give up on you at the same time.
Afterwards... I'll beat you to pulp afterwards for sure.
S-So, be prepared for that.
Do as you wish..
It'd be nice if I could stop this moment in time.
It's OK if you punch me.
How much times you want to, I'm fine.
L-Like I said, don't get too cocky.
It's expanding, my labia is strongly expanding.
Yoshiharu is
stretching me inside.
She's actually my sister.
No, don't look at where you're coming in!
It's enough.
No, I can't anymore.
Stop moving.
No.
I can't
I can't take it anymore.
I feel strange all over.
I'm becoming strange.
Oh no, I'm cumming.
I don't care anymore.
I'm just ejaculate inside her like that.
I'll make her mine.
I, My...
Nee-chan, I'm about to...
Inside...
It's throbbing inside of me.
Incredible, it's flowing out.
I came inside Nee-chan's womb.
I did it with you under such circumstance.
Even though I didn't intend to do.
But my feelings for you are real.
I'll also cherish you.
So.
Nee-chan?
We agreed before that I'll punch you after this.
Nee-chan.
Nee-chan...
Actually, I made up my mind to live alone when Spring comes,
because I want to leave Yoshiharu.
He's still lingering in me...
That's why
Yoshiharu is..
beating inside of me
It's hot, and my brain is all hazy.
That feeling...
Yoshiharu...
I love you, Nee-chan.
My feelings for you are real.
I'll also be sure to cherish you.
It's a good feeling.
Yoshiharu's...
But this is too abrupt.
Yoshiharu, you dumbass!
I feel bad because it was so sudden, that's what I think.
Yeah, but...
No, wait.
If I we don't clear things up now,
my true feelings won't be able to reach you.
Putting that aside,
when did you start noticing me?
I won't get mad, Yoshiharu. So be honest.
Let go of me, Yoshiharu.
About that...
Hurry up!
When you were fingering yourself while calling my name.
Why, you...
Your panties are wet, Nee-chan.
Don't do that.
I'm get really sensitive.
No, don't! That place is...
Stop.
It's not dirty at all.
There's only the feminine taste of you, Nee-chan.
N-No, stop.
My panties will be soaked if you carry on.
I'll start to look like a slut.
I'll make you feel good.
So I want you to help me too.
Nee-chan, your mouth is so warm.
Yoshiharu's penis is too big.
Besides, I didn't notice just now.
It stinks.
Something like that is inside of me.
This huge fellow just entered inside of me.
And it has yet to...
Nee-chan, I'm gonna cum.
What? No way! Stop!
NO!
Nee-chan, let's do it.
Wait.
I've yet to make you feel good.
It's coming in!
It's rubbing my insides.
Nee-chan, do you feel good?
It feels good, so...
you can move faster.
It's churning me.
Your insides are really comfortable.
Yoshiharu, do you really love my breasts that much?
I really like your breasts, Nee-chan.
So, massage them more. OK?
Hey, Yoshiharu.
Yes, Nee-chan?
You love me, right?
That's right, I...
love you.
Nee-chan, that is.
You love me the most, right?
You're the best, Nee-chan.
No, my breasts.
These breasts are my favorite too.
No!
No, if you continue teasing it like that...
I'll...
I climaxed! From your dick...
No, don't. It's still very sensitive.
Yoshiharu.
So big, it's squashing me down there.
Nee-chan.
Your insides are gradually hugging me tighter and tighter.
That's because your cock is making my cunt feel so good.
No, I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to seeded by you inside. I'll belong to you.
Yoshiharu's penis.
It feels great.
I feel I'm in love with...