I've been having non-stop delusions ever since doing it with Yoshiharu.
I'm trying hard not to remember his face.
Isn't it against the rules to say things like that suddenly?
Moron.
Wait.
I-It's my first time.
It came! Your dick, Yoshiharu.
That's right, we haven't done it since Spring.
Besides, we're siblings.
Sana!
Sana.
Hey, Sana.
Sana!
What?
Your little brother brought a lunch box to see you.
Say, what?
Waku-subs
http://wakusubs.wordpress.com
Ane Koi
Suki
Kirai
Daisuki
I didn't ask you to bring it specially for me.
Well, Mom told me to bring it over.
You left way too early.
I brought it after it was done.
I should avoid eye contact.
Or else I might remember that incident again.
Again, our hands...
Nee-chan, I've something to tell you later.
Are you free during recess?
A-Are you an idiot?
That's so old-fashioned.
I can see your intentions so clearly.
As if I'll really go and meet up with you.
Yoshiharu's palms are sweaty.
It feels good.
Ouch.
Sana, shouldn't you treat your brother better?
In the end, I still came.
Nee-chan.
Hey, wait. You're hurting me.
I can't free myself.
When did he become so strong?
Since then,
I've been trying to resist doing it with you.
But I can't resist anymore.
Yoshiharu, you're...
I'm only here to deliver your lunch box today.
But after seeing your face...
Like I said, we shouldn't. We're in school!
But I can't hold it until we get home.
Seriously, he's so horny for someone who just lost his virginity.
But...
What?
It's already hard, you fool!
It's not there yet.
Hey, wait.
Nee-chan.
You're all wet.
S-Stop!
We won't be siblings anymore if this carries on.
Don't enter.
Nee-chan.
B-But...
No! I said no!
Hey, wait. It hurts.
Since you've said that...
Use your mouth, then.
It's also my first time doing this, so I'm not really sure.
I can do it if this can make you feel better.
It's hot.
So this is how the real thing feels like.
There's an incredible feeling there.
The veins are protruding, and it's getting slimy.
I'm glad he's feeling so good.
Don't just lick it. Put it in your mouth.
You're pretty demanding, aren't you.
Yes, just like that. It's so warm. It's also all slimy, feels good.
It was also awesome when we kissed.
I feel kind of touched she's eating me like this.
Can you try swallowing deeper inside your mouth, just like that. All the way in.
This sucking and swallowing reflex... feels really good.
Nee-chan! Nee-chan!
He sounds so excited!
Well, this is fine. It's not like I hate this.
I'm actually quite happy.
I'm cumming! I'm going to release everything.
Please let me cum inside your mouth.
Yoshiharu is getting bigger.
Don't you have tissue?
Woah, I feel so happy for some reason.
Ouch.
W-What's that for?
Bitter and sticky, it's horrible.
Sorry.
What's happening?
I totally swallowed Yoshiharu's semen.
And it's not even the least bit tasty.
What difference does that make me from a pervert?
Um, I'll try my best over there.
Eh?
Hey.
Why are you taking off my panty? Stop!
What's with this position?
Stop staring.
It's embarrassing.
It's soaking down here.
Don't just stare at it directly.
It's so slimy that i'm getting horny.
Shut up.
No... don't!
Amazing.
I'm getting numb.
No way, that place is!
My asshole, don't.
This feels good.
The gradual licking is just like a penis coming inside.
Yoshiharu, give me more.
What the fuck am I saying?
Yoshiharu will surely be getting over his head if I say weird stuff like that.
Wait, Nee-chan.
He's drinking my pee.
I'm completely sapped of strength.
Wait, please wait!
I can't, right now.
I'm so weak I can't even struggle.
Don't get so full of yourself and tamper with my body however you want it.
My bad, but your cunt is just too adorable.
I couldn't help myself but stick it all the way in.
Moron.
Hey, Nee-chan. Wrap around my neck tightly.
No, stop.. It's reaching all the way inside my uterus.
Nee-chan, does mine feel good?
D-Don't ask questions like that!
Nee-chan, you know... I've always liked you. I swear.
I don't know about stuff like that!
Doing this kind of stuff, how would I know?
What am I saying?
Because I've noticed for a very, very long time already.
I hate you. I hate this!
It's fine. I'll give my all until you fall completely in love with me.
Look here.
Ah... a kiss.
Nee-chan!
His movements are quicker than ever.
He's gonna come soon.
It's amazing, Nee-chan. I'm going to cum inside.
He's really gonna cum.
His thing is hot.
Throbbing here and there within me.
I love your insides, Nee-chan!
I want it to be just as comfortable as that time.
Please hurry.
I'm all... prepared for your semen, Yoshiharu!
Hurry!
Cum inside me!
It should be coming out towards the very end.
I'm going to die inside.
To think I'd feel so happy hearing those words from Yoshiharu.
I'm a goner.
Sana!
Hey, Sana!
What's wrong?
Your brother, during PE lesson, he...
Yoshiharu! Yoshiharu! Yoshiharu!
Yoshiharu! Yoshiharu!
Sana, what are you doing?
Because I...
It's nothing serious. He only fainted from anemia.
Yoshiharu, you idiot!
That's punishment for making me worry incessantly.
I didn't think you would be this worried.
I'm still not done yet, but I've to return to class.
Be more careful in managing your body.
Wait.
I like... your smell.
I knew it.
Knew what?
Nee-chan is really beautiful.
Stupid.
It went it so quickly.
Fool.
Because you've doing me everyday.
My vagina has completely transformed into your shape.
It's tightening inside.
Nee-chan! Nee-chan!
Nee-chan!
Oh! I'm.. I'm going to... cum!
In any case, why did you suddenly pass out from anemia.
I was too busy with part-time work.
What? A student's primary responsibility is to study.
I know that, but...
You should be honest if you have reasons of your own.
Well..
Are you really thinking of living on your own after Spring?
Yeah.
I'm going to move out.
Why?
I want to move somewhere near you.
What?
Yoshiharu.
Do you know what you just said?
No way.
I'm so happy he's going to notice.
I'm on cloud nine.
Yoshiharu.
Do you know where you're gonna be moving to?
Still.
It's in the vicinity of the station.
Where did you think I was gonna move?
So near?!
I won't tell you I love you yet.
Because you're just too cute, it gets on my nerves.