I like you, Saori-san
I want to get to know Saori-san.
Me too.
Saori-san's chest is so soft...
Takumi, this...
A bit more gent...
If it continues like this...
Nipples are too sensitive, huh?
Because... They're very sensitive.
I already said no...
Takumi-san is being bad...
Takumi-san, that place is...
Very wet already.
No, Takumi-san
That kind of...
Can't...
Th.. That place...
Don't rub it like that...
That place is...
So beautiful..
Don't look...
I'm embarrassed...
No! Doing it like that, then...
No!
If we keep going like this...
I'd come...
Takumi-san...
I...
want to come with you.
Saori-san.
Become one with me.
Takumi-san...
Put it inside me...
Saori-san.
Does it hurt, Saori-san?
It's okay.
Me, you don't have to worry about.
But...
I want to become your woman...
Saori-san...
Saori-san's inside feels really good...
So tight and so sticky-slick...
Saori-san...
Saori-san!
I can no longer hold back...
Takumi-san...
While inside me...
Can feel good...
I'm happy.
When you shoot...
shoot outside...
Going to... come out!
No... don't... shoot... inside!
Are you awake, Takumi?
Mi-nee! WHAT are you doing?
Aren't I waking Takumi up?
This kind of method has problems...
True.
This place... before I came around,
already looked awake.
Stop it, Mi-nee!
Even if you say that,
this being so stiff and hard,
you're in no condition to meet others, right?
That is... Mi-nee...
Mii-nee!
Already...
A lot shot out, huh?
Oh, Takumi~
This early and already so energetic...
This is...
Ne~ Takumi...
W-wait a minute, Mi-nee!
You want to use my chest again, right?
N.. No.
I...
can no longer, with Mi-nee, do this.
Why? Are you tired of my body already?
I... I already started going out with Saori-san.
Wa...
What does that mean?!
Takumi is my boyfriend already, right?!
Sorry!
Because... Takumi and I already H.
Sorry...
Because... Takumi and I [also]...
I like Saori-san.
It's no longer like before.
Ah. Older brother, good morning!
Morning.
Older brother, today, is really early!
Really?
But, regrettably, older sister already left.
I see.
Older brother!
On the way, can we go together?
Starting tommorrow, it's winter break, right?
That's right.
Normally, on winter break, what does everyone do?
Let's see...
[Making] snowballs and new year's worship.
[Sounds] good~
Older brother, [how about] this year?
Still special activies none.
I see.
Then, no matter what,
[let's go to] new year's worship
Makes one expectant!
We should invite Satuski-san and her sister to go with us, right?
Older brother,
Mmm?
[Bye ]then, I, from here.
Next year,
I and my sister,
take to many fun places, alright?
Promise!
Mmm.
Then, I'm leaving!
Waited long
Uh-uh.
Saori-san.
The new year has arrived.
Let's go to the temple together.
Um... Sorry.. I... New year's holiday, need to work.
Eh? That store, new year's is closed, no?
No, not like that.
The store is closed, but I found someplace else to work.
I see.
Wanted, during the winter break, Saori-san, take everywhere.
Sorry.
When I decided to work, I wasn't going out with you yet.
Saori-san don't have to apologize.
Well, just feeling a little regret.
I am... Really, truly lonley.
Mmm? What did you say?
No, nothing at all.
Finally here! New year's worship!
After snowing, the weather's really great!
Aside from older sister, worshiping together [with others] is my first time, so it's really fun!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Lot's of people here. Be careful.
Getting separated would be bad, so hold onto Tat-chan.
Is that okay?
Mmm.
What's wrong, older brother?
Ah! Older sister!
The work on New Year is to be a Miko-san, huh.
That's good~
Yui-chan, going over there now!
Yes!
Can't... at a place like this...
Why? "Right now nobody else would be here" was what Saori-san said.
That's because...
I'm already excited...
Saori-san is too, no?
Tat-chan New Years already got lost!
What could he be doing?
Yui-chan. What's wrong?
A little... unable to open my eyes.
Takumi-san... too forceful!
Can't... noises... are coming out.
It's okay. Noise won't be heard.
You always say that...
Takumi-san... I... already... already!
Yui-chan... was so energetic.
It's my fault.
If I had only paid as much attention to Yui as I did Takumi-san...
Saori-san, didn't you kept worrying about Yui-chan's matters?
But, when Yui fell over sick, I was NOT at her side!
That...
I'm so sorry, Yui. I'm so sorry!
Ah, older brother.
Today, you came to see me too?
I'm so happy!
Saori-san, because of work, doesn't look like she'll come.
That's okay.
Because I see older brother, I am much more energetic!
Haha. Thanks.
Older brother.
Hmm?
About my condition,
have you heard?
Mmm.
Yui-chan's physical condition,
completely did not pay attention to.
Sorry.
It's okay. Worried I did not want because, so did not say.
But, gave everyone lots of trouble, right?
Trouble, definitely did not give.
[Us] Sisters gave you lots of trouble. Sorry.
Absolutely not.
It's me to gave Saori-san lots of trouble.
Uh-uh.
Older sister and older brother started going out.
The original kind older sister returned.
It's all because of older brother.
I didn't do anything.
I... If older brother became my real older brother, I'd be sooo happy.
Yui-chan...
Also...
Um... That is...
Before becoming my real older brother,
please do something for me.
Mmm.
Because it's Yui-chan's wish.
No matter what's asked, I'll do.
Older brother...
Please come hug me.
Mmm. That's fine.  Eehh?!
Older brother became older sister's lover, I am happy.
But, actually, I'm envious of older sister.
Because of my condition... Would not find a lover...
That's not right!
Because it's Yui-chan...
Comforting words are not necessary.  I just want some memories.
The kind that can let me forget sufferings caused by my sickness.
From the person I like, I want to experience that kind of bliss and pain...
Yui-chan.
Older brother. My last willful wish... please listen to it.
Older brother, I keep feeling my heart going "ba-bump ba-bump" really fast.
So am I.
But, older brother, every night, with older sister...
Yui-chan. Panties I'm taking off.
Ah, older brother, I'm embarrassed.
Older brother, that place is...
Letting older brother lick, feels really good!
Continuing like this, I'd make the same lusful noises as older sister...
that can't be helped, right?
Yui-chan. I'm starting now...
Are you okay?
I'm okay. Older brother.
My body... Older brother completely enter, please.
Is that okay?
Yes. Even though I'm like this, I'm pretty strong!
Well, then.
It's all inside, Yui-chan.
Yes. My body's inside, older brother's is filling it fully.
Older brother, like how you always do with older sister -- hard and fast.
Yui-chan. Are you okay?
Sheesh. Always asking this. I'm already feeling really good!
Yui-chan.
older brother!
Yui-chan. Yui-chan!
Older brother. How could I be, feeling better and better. Like I'm floating...
This is the feeling when coming, right?
I'm going to climax?
If it's at the same time as older brother, then climaxing is fine, right?
Older brother, feels too good...
I... I'm going to come... Coming... Coming!
[With] Older brother, H completed.
This way, there's nothing more to worry about.
Ah!
There's one more.
Older brother, older sister... please let her be happy!
[Even] my portion... Single-mindedly love my sister, please!
Promise!
Yui-chan.
I understand. Promise.
I'm leaving.
Saori-san. Today, after the visit, you have no work, right?
Taumi-san.
Hmm?
I have something to discuss with you.
This is, for me, my favorite spot in this town.
Right now, here, the view is the prettiest.
So then, Saori-san. What did you want to say?
Takumi-san.  Us two... Let's become complete strangers again.
Eh?!
Go ahead and break up with me.
Why?!
Now I saved some money by working, I plan to leave your home.
What are you SAYING?!
I'm sorry... I can't return your feelings.
I can't... continue to like you!
Why not?...
I came to your home, it was all for Yui.  It's because of Yui's disease that we came.
Then I completely forgot about her.  There's now only you in my eyes...
During this period, she's suffering by herself!
Only we can become happy! Yui--she must've kept on hating me!
That's not true!
Yui-chan isn't that kind of person.  Don't you know that too?!
Yui-chan always felt her disease was robbing Saori-san of all happiness.
That's not true!
I know.
Saori-san, you two care too much about each other.
That's what caused the misunderstanding.
Yui-chan's disease is absolutely curable.
At that time,
if Saori-san doesn't have the utmost happiness...
Yui-chan will blame herself for the rest of her life.
Saori-san doesn't want to do what would steal Yui-chan's smile, right?
I like Yui-chan's smiles.
Also, compared to these,
I like Saori-san's smiles even more!
Of course, if Saori-san dislikes me, then that's another thing altogether...
Sheesh... How could I dislike you?
Even if you dislike me... You, I will continue to like!
Saori-san...
Takumi-san. Come!
I want evidence I'm loved.
Takumi-san's... has become so hot already.
Saori-san. So great!
Takumi-san. Up until now, I've always felt really good.
Feeling your cock, my body would become really hot.
C-can't hold it. I'm about to peak...
Coming... Coming... Coming!
Stay inside... I... will come. Coming!
Coming... The sperm feels great...
Takumi-san... Takumi-san... Takumi?
Hey! Wake up, Takumi!
Ah?! Mi-nee. Good morning.
Geez. Definitely can't get up without my help.
Also... You're staring at my body trying to determine what exactly?
Sorry...
Alright. Go ahead and change.
Thank you. Mi-nee, I'm very thankful.
If that's what you think...
If that's what you think... Give me a chance, too.
Mi-nee...
Just kidding!
All right. Hurry up and change. Your cute girlfriend is waiting!
Yes, yes...
Then I'll go downstairs first...
W... wait! Let me leave first!
Still haven't changed at all.
Yahoo!
Satsuki! What are you doing?!
So early in the moring and you're already in the love love territory.
You're gonna be late!
Mind your own business!
Seeya!
That Satsuki...
Even Saori-san is...
Sorry.
But if we're too relaxed, we really might be late!
Wait for me, Saori-san!
Takumi-san! Hurry!