I love you, Saori-san.
I want to make you feel even better, Saori-san.
I want you to as well.
Saori-san, your breasts are so soft.
Takumi... don't...
Be a little gentler. If you're that rough...
You don't want me to touch these?
If you do that, I won't be able to control myself...
I told you not to do it. You're so mean...
Takumi-san, that's my...
You're soaking wet...
Takumi-san...
No...
Not there...
Don't do that...
That's my...
How beautiful...
Don't look at it so much.
It's embarrassing...
No, if you do that, I'll...
If we keep going like this...
I'm going to cum...
Takumi-san, I...
I want to... be with you...
Saori-san...
Let's become one.
Yes.
Takumi-san, I want you inside of me...
Saori-san...
Does it hurt?
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
But...
I want you to make me your woman.
Saori-san...
It feels so good, inside of you.
It's so tight and so wet...
Saori-san... Saori-san!
I can't... I can't hold it much longer.
Takumi-san, you feel so good inside of me.
I'm so happy...
But when you cum, don't cum inside me...
I'm cumming!
N-No way... You can't cum inside me!
Grood morfing, Takumi.
Mii-nee, what are you doing?
Whahram I dohing?
I came to wake you up.
I don't think this is how you wake someone up.
Sure it is.
When I came to wake you up,
this guy was already up.
Don't do that, Mii-nee.
You tell me to stop, but you're so hard that you can't go out in public.
That's your  fault!
Mii-nee!
Too late...
You came a lot...
Wow Takumi, at least part  of you
is a morning person...
This is...
Say, Takumi...
Wait a minute, Mii-nee.
Ah, you want me to use these  again?
It's not that...
I...
I can't keep doing this with you...
Why? Are you tired of my body?
I...
I... I'm going out with Saori-san.
W-What do you mean by that?
I thought you were my  boyfriend!
Sorry.
But we had sex...
But, I gave you my...
I love Saori-san.
It's not like it used to be.
Good morning, Onii-san.
'Morning.
You're sure up early today, Onii-san.
You think so?
Too bad, but Saori's already left home.
I see.
Onii-san?
Can we walk together partway today?
Winter vacation starts tomorrow, right?
Yes...
Does your family usually travel somewhere?
Let's see... Maybe snowboarding,
or to a temple on New Year's.
How nice. Where will you be going this year?
I'm not really sure yet.
I see, we could visit the temple first.
I can't wait...
We'll have to get Satsuki and Mitsuki to come along with us.
Onii-san...
I'm going my own way from here.
Ah, okay.
You've got to take me and Onee-chan to many fun places next year, okay?
You promise?
Of course.
I guess I'd better get going!
Sorry about the wait.
No problem.
Saori-san, let's do a New Year's shrine visit.
Sorry, but I have to work on New Year's.
Huh? The café even stays open on New Year's?
No, it's not that.
The coffee shop will be closed, but I have another job.
I see.
I thought we could go out more over the winter break, but...
I'm sorry.
We weren't dating when I decided to take this job.
You don't have to apologize.
Well, it is a bit of a shame.
I'll feel pretty lonely, too.
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
We're finally here at the temple on New Year's!
I'm just glad it's not snowing!
This is the first time I've done a New Year's temple visit with people other than Saori.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's crowded, so be careful.
You might want to hang on to Taku-chan to avoid getting separated.
Can I?
Sure.
What's wrong, Onii-san?
Ah, it's Onee-chan!
So she's working as a priestess on New Year's.
That's so nice...
Yui-chan, let's go this way.
Yes...
No, we can't...
At least not here...
Why not?
You said it yourself: there's no one around here.
That's...
My switch has just been turned on.
And I'm thinking yours has, too.
It looks like we can't even trust Taku-chan not to get lost.
Jeez, where might he be?
I want 3 takoyakis with mayonnaise please, Sir.
Yui-chan, is something wrong?
Being around this big crowd has made me a little dizzy.
Takumi-san, you're being so intense...
Oh no, I'm going to scream.
Go ahead, no one's gonna hear it.
You always say that.
Takumi-san, I'm going to, I'm going to...
Yui-chan looked so healthy.
This is my fault.
I've been spending so much time with you
that I forgot about Yui.
But you've always taken such good care of her.
But, I...
I wasn't with her when she collapsed!
Well...
I'm sorry, Yui.
Sorry...
Ah, Onii-san!
You're here to visit me again today? I'm so happy!
Saori-san is working today,
so she probably won't be able to come.
Don't worry! Just seeing your face is enough...
...to make me feel much better.
Thank you.
Onii-san...
Did you hear about my illness?
I'm sorry I never realized how sick you were.
That's okay.
I didn't tell you because I didn't want you to worry.
But it looks like I worried you even more this way.
Don't say that!
I'm sorry that both of us sisters have caused you problems.
That's not true. I've caused
way more trouble for Saori-san.
No, you haven't. Ever since she started dating you,
Onee-chan's gone back to being
her normal kind and gentle self.
And it's all thanks to you, Onii-san.
I didn't really do anything...
I was just thinking how nice it'd be
if you were my real brother.
Yui-chan...
And so...
Before we become real siblings,
I want to ask you a favor.
I'd do anything you asked me to, Yui-chan.
Onii-san...
Please do "it" with me.
Yeah, sure thing.
WHAT?!
I'm very happy that you became my sister's boyfriend.
But I'm actually a bit envious of her...
My fragile body makes it very hard for me to find a boyfriend.
That's not true! You should be able to...
I'm fine with pity sex. All I really want are memories.
Being made a woman by the one I love would...
...help me forget about the pain of my illness.
I'd like to feel the pain of pleasure.
Yui-chan?
Onii-san, could you please do me this last favor?
Onii-san, I'm feeling a bit nervous.
So am I.
But you do this with Onee-chan every day...
Yui-chan, I'm going to take your panties off.
Onii-san, this is embarrassing!
Onii-san, that place...
It feels so good...
...when you lick me there, Onii-san!
So Onee-chan makes naughty noises like this, too...
I-I can't help it...
Yui-chan...
Here I go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Onii-san.
Go ahead, you can put it all inside of me.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm stronger than I look.
Then...
It's completely in, Yui-chan.
Yes, I can feel you all the way inside of me...
Onii-san, feel free to move...
...the way you normally do with Onee-chan.
Yui-chan, are you all right?
Stop asking me that.
I can feel just as good as she can.
Yui-chan...
Onii-san!
Yui-chan!
Onii-san...
I feel so lightheaded...
I don't know why,
but I'm starting to feel really good.
Is this what they call cumming?
I'm going to cum, right?
We can cum together, right?
Onii-san, it feels so good.
I'm going to... I'm cumming... cumming!
I had sex with Onii-san.
I have no more regrets.
Just one last thing.
Onii-san, please make Onee-chan happy.
Love her as much as you can,
and love her for me as well...
You promise?
Yui-chan?
I understand.
I promise.
I'll be going now!
Saori-san, are you going to work after we visit Yui?
Takumi-san...
We have to talk.
This is my favorite place in the whole city.
It's most beautiful at this time of year.
What did you want to talk about?
Takumi-san.
Let's go back to being complete strangers.
I...
I want us to break up.
Why?
Once I'd earned enough money at my jobs,
I was planning on leaving your house.
What are you saying?
I'm sorry, but I can't return
the feelings you have for me.
I...
I can't let myself fall any deeper in love with you!
What do you mean?
I only went to live at your house because of Yui.
So that she could get better.
But despite that, I...
I completely forgot about her,
and I only thought about you.
All that time, Yui was suffering by herself.
I was the only one who was happy.
And because of that, Yui probably hates me now!
She'd never do that!
You know Yui isn't that type of girl.
She thinks that her illness has been taking away
the happiness you deserve.
That can't be!
I understand.
You love each other so much you'd both sacrifice yourselves for the other's sake.
I'm certain that Yui-chan's illness will be cured.
When that moment comes,
if you aren't as happy as you can be,
Yui-chan will blame herself for the rest of her life.
I wouldn't want you to do anything
that would take away Yui-chan's smile.
I really like Yui-chan when she smiles.
But beyond that,
your smile is the thing I love the most in this world.
However, if you don't want to be with me,
then everything will change.
Dummy.
There's no way I could hate you.
Even if you hated me,
I would always love you.
Saori-san...
Takumi-san, come...
I want proof that you love me.
Takumi-san,
your dick is so warm...
Saori-san, you're amazing.
Takumi-san...
I feel better than I've ever felt before.
Having your dick inside of me...
...makes me even hotter and hotter!
No... I'm going to... cum...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Takumi-san, you're moving so good inside of me...
I'm cumming again...
Takumi-san... Takumi-san...
Takumi...
Takumi... WAKE UP!
Mii-nee?
Good morning...
For crying out loud...
If I didn't come here to wake you up,
you wouldn't wake up at all.
Besides...
Where exactly were you looking?
I'm sorry.
Now, hurry up and change.
Thank you. I appreciate what you've done.
If you feel that way,
then you'd better give me a chance, too!
Mii-nee...
Just kidding.
Come on, hurry up and change.
Your cute girlfriend is waiting for you.
Yes, yes.
I'll be leaving now--!
Hey, at least wait for me to leave before...
She's still the same.
Satsuki, what the hell are you doing?
If you keep walking in that lovey-dovey way,
you'll be late for school.
That's none of your business.
See ya!
Hey!
Satsuki's just crazy...
Don't you start too!
Sorry to say it, but she's right.
If we walk this slowly, we'll be late.
Wait... Saori-san!
Takumi-san, hurry up!
Subtitles by [Akatsu]
Edited by Zalis