Everything began at that time.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You caught me at a bad time...
It can't be helped.
If you hadn't turned away,
the kitten would've been in danger.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
You should apply pressure until the bleeding stops.
It's your body, so you have to take care of it.
If you got hurt, someone would be worried about you, right?
Bye.
Your handkerchief...?
Dear, you're such a...
Takumi, come here for a bit.
What is it, Dad?
I'm tired--
These two girls, Shirakawa Saori and Yui,
will be living with us as of today.
Get along with them, Takumi.
I'm Shirakawa Yui, nice to meet you!
Umm... Onii-san.
Same here.
What do you think, Takumi?
They're as cute as Mizuki-chan
and Satsuki-chan from next door, right?
That's not the problem!
What do you mean by living with us?
It means you now have a lovely big sister
and a cute little sister.
Even so, to respect their wishes, they're not really adopted.
We never intended to become
a permanent part of your family.
I never had plans of getting along with you.
Umm...
I'm really happy that I have a big brother now!
Yui!
Coming!
Well then, good night!
Takumi, it's morning already! Wake up!
Takumi.
Hey, wake up already!
Oww...
Mii-nee, good morning.
Gosh...
What's so "good" about this morning?
You're going to be late!
Huh? It's already this late?
Also...
What were you looking at while you were greeting me?
Now, hurry up and get ready.
Oh, right.
Mii-nee, some new girls moved into our house yesterday.
I know. I just met them.
You already did?
You're the one who woke up late.
Here, change your clothes.
Thanks.
Get changed and come down to breakfast.
Okay.
Two cute girls are living under the same roof as Takumi...
Hey, Takumi...
Hey! Wait until--
She's always like that.
Are you all right?
Onee-chan, sorry for making you wait!
Good morning!
Morning.
Onee-chan, wait!
We don't intend to become part of your family.
I never had plans of getting along with you.
That hurt!
Taku-chan, morning!
What are you doing, Satsuki?
I'm just saying hi!
Or would you prefer a kiss?
No.
Why?
Don't you do it with Mii-nee every morning?
Good morning kisses~
I don't.
But you might not realize it,
not if she's stealing kisses while you're asleep.
Mii-nee would never do something like that!
Maybe you're a little too trusting.
She's been acting like your older sister for way too long.
What's so wrong with trusting her!
I've always thought of Mii-nee as a real sibling!
I pity her.
Why?
I shouldn't be the one to tell you why.
By the way, where are the beautiful sisters that you shacked up with?
Don't say "shacked up"!
They just left before me. They wouldn't want to go to school with me, right?
Why not?
I wish I knew, but I don't.
Do they hate you because you did something perverted?
I didn't do anything like that!
So you say, but given your age, well...
They may not be related,
but they're still family. I wouldn't do that.
You seem amped up about this.
Okay, let's just leave it at that.
Bye Taku-chan, I'll see you at school.
Don't be late!
Crap!
Saori-san.
Let's go home together.
No thank you.
I was planning to take you around town.
Let's invite Yui-chan, too.
I have something to do.
Really?
Then how about tomorrow?
I'll always be busy.
Saori-san doesn't even listen to what I say...
Come in.
Excuse me.
Yui-chan, what is it?
Well...
Onii-san, I want to talk to you about something...
Umm...
Come on in.
Okay.
So, what is it?
Umm... Onii-san.
Please don't hate my sister.
My sister isn't actually like that.
She's actually really cheerful and kind...
That's why...
So just... please don't hate her!
I got it.
Onii-san...
Don't worry, I'll find a way to make us along.
Thank you!
I made a promise to Yui-chan,
but I can't keep it without having a real conversation with Saori-san.
I'd never seen a girl masturbate before.
So even Saori-san does it...
She's making it hard for me...
Hello, Taku-chan!
Don't go climbing in my window!
And don't flash your panties!
It happens all the time.
There's no need to get embarrassed now.
Would you just get off me already?
I'm thinking you were about to jerk off.
No, I wasn't.
Oh, really?
It's not what you think!
I've seen those two, so I can't blame you.
No healthy male could've resisted their charms forever.
It's not like that.
That's right.
To make up for interrupting you,
I'll be your fap fodder.
Don't be stupid.
Even though my body isn't
as good as Mii-nee's, I'm still...
Satsuki, stop--
It's okay, Taku-chan.
Get yourself off while you look at me.
But you can't touch!
Hey, Taku-chan, I said you can't touch!
Gosh...
You still haven't seen a girl's private place, have you?
Wait, Taku-chan!
Satsuki...
I'm sorry for teasing you.
Taku-chan, you can't...
You can't do this...
Taku-chan...
No, Taku-chan...
Satsuki...
Satsuki!
No...!
Amazing. I never knew girls could get this wet.
No, don't look!
Taku-chan, stop!
Stop...
I'm gonna cum...
Satsuki, I'm putting it in, okay?
Gosh, I guess it can't be helped.
Taku-chan...
Here.
Satsuki...
Wait, Taku-chan!
If you're that rough...
You're so tight!
Taku-chan, I'm going to break!
No, I can't hold it anymore!
Taku-chan, I'm not on any birth control...
If you're going to cum, cum outside!
Outside...
What...?
Sorry, I felt too good inside you.
Taku-chan, you idiot.
Satsuki, was that your first time?
Of course it was. What kind of girl do you think I am?
No, that's not it.
Never mind. But, you can't tell Mii-nee about what happened today.
Also, act normal in front of other people,
and pretend that nothing
ever happened between us.
Okay?
O-Okay...
If you keep your promise, I'll come again when I feel like it.
I might even let you do me again.
Satsuki...
Takumi, it's morning already! Wake up!
Takumi...
Mii-nee, good morning.
You actually woke up by yourself.
What happened?
I went to bed early last night.
It seems like Saori-san is at work.
Doing what?
I heard it was at a café.
Where?
It's somewhere near Hagatsu.
She said she didn't want to trouble you guys for money. What a good girl.
When does she get off work?
How would I know that?
I see...
Here, change your clothes.
Thanks.
You should learn from Saori-san and do things for yourself.
Okay...
Hey, Takumi, I have time today...
So can I walk you to school?
Hey, Takumi!
Sure, let's go together.
I'll get ready then!
Saori-san!
W-What are you doing here?
I came to pick you up.
Nobody asked you to do that.
I wanted to do it myself.
Thanks for the hard work!
Saori-san!
Why?
Yui-chan said it might rain today,
so I thought you might get caught in it.
Really?
Maybe you don't want to walk home with a guy you hate,
but Yui-chan would be really worried
if you caught a cold.
Just live with it until we get home.
If it's for Yui...
Yui-chan is really important to you, isn't she?
Of course. She's the only family I have.
I know I could never be on the exact same level as Yui-chan,
but it'd be great if you thought of me that way someday.
That's impossible. Because, you're that person's...
I don't know what happened between you and my dad.
But I am myself.
It's almost Christmas.
What about it?
Can you go on a date with me on Christmas Eve?
W-Why do I have to go on a date with you?
It doesn't have to be a real  date;
just chatting over tea would be fine.
Unfortunately...
I have to work on Christmas Eve,
so it's impossible.
So you think it's unfortunate.
N-No... Don't twist my words...
It's okay if you work until late.
I'll wait for you by the train station.
I won't go.
I'll wait until you come.
Gosh... I said I'm not going.
Takumi? Wake up, Takumi...
Wake up!
Oww...
Who is it?
Who do you think  it is?
It's Christmas Eve, so how long are you planning to sleep?
Mii-nee!
You have to go on a date
with me today, so get ready.
Why a date?
Today's Christmas Eve, that's why!
And why does that mean
I'm going on a date with you?
Gosh, I swore I was going to give it to you this year...
A Christmas present?
What are you going to give me?
Don't ask a girl that!
Mii-nee, aren't you a little old for that label?
You're mouthing off again!
Takumi, do you want my virginity or not?
Virginity?!
Oh, no! I said it!
Mii-nee, that's...
Because, you've only been thinking about Saori-san and Yui-chan lately...
I thought they'd take you away if I didn't take action...
Hey...
I'll give you my virginity, so you give me yours, too!
Are you serious?
Don't tell me someone already took it!
Was it Saori-san?!
There's no way that'd ever happen.
Thank goodness.
I love you, and I only want to do it with you...
I also don't want you to do it
with anyone but me...
You love...
You actually...
I let it slip again!
I wanted to confess on a date
during Christmas Eve when the mood was good...
And then both mind and body would be united...
Takumi, I love you!
Mii-nee, you really...
Gosh...
You silly boy.
I wouldn't joke about something like this.
Takumi, you're so hard already...
Do you like breasts?
Yeah.
You're such a spoiled child...
Touch them, Takumi.
The front is so wet...
You really like breasts, don't you?
Takumi, I'll give my first time to you.
You don't need to do anything.
I'll make you feel good.
Mii-nee...!
How is it? Does it feel good inside me?
It does...
That's great.
I'm also going to--
Your penis is feeling better and better...
Mii-nee, if you go that rough, I'm going to...
Are you about to cum, Takumi?
Is your penis going to shoot stuff out soon?
Cum inside me!
I want you to ejaculate inside me...
Make me feel good until the end!
But, Mii-nee...
Cum, Takumi!
Do it inside me!
Your semen is coming out...
It feels so hot...
I got it dirty.
Let me clean it for you.
It got bigger again.
Does my mouth feel good?
Now, I'll suck it clean.
Mii-nee...
Are you going to cum again?
Umm... I want you to do it with your boobs.
Well, since you really love breast that much, Takumi...
Mii-nee!
I'm sorry, Mii-nee.
It's okay, Takumi.
Takumi, you can do whatever you want this time.
You can move easier from behind, right?
I guess.
I'm going to thrust, Mii-nee.
It's deep...
It's so good, even though today was my first time...
Even though it's only the second time
you've put it inside me!
Your penis makes me feel so good!
Mii-nee, you're so wet, warm and tight...
Me too. I never thought your penis was going to be this good!
Mii-nee, Mii-nee!
Takumi! Takumi!
I'm going to cum inside again!
Cum! Cum inside me!
Shoot all you've got inside me!
My womb will take it all...
Mii-nee, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum too!
Takumi!!
Sorry, did I wake you?
No.
I finally became one with you...
But we had sex before  the first date.
My plan went to waste...
Before our date...
Takumi?
What's gotten into you?
Hey, Takumi!
I just remembered that I had something important to do...
What could be so important?
Hey, Takumi!
Mii-nee, sorry!
What's going on?
Takumi?
When you've extended the invitation,
you're not supposed to make the person wait.
Sorry!
Maybe I shouldn't have come after all.
But you still showed up.
Well, if you'd caught a cold because I stood you up,
Yui would've felt sad.
Just keep telling yourself that.
But I know you're actually very kind, Saori-san.
But I'm really happy that you came.
Although it's not Mii-nee, I've decided.
Saori-san.
I...
Subtitles by [w.0.0.f]
Edited by Zalis