Everything began at that time.
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You caught me at a bad time...
It can't be helped.
If you didn't turn away, the kitty would be in danger.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Hold it until the bleeding stops.
You should really look after your own body.
If you got hurt, someone would be worried about you, right?
Bye.
Handkerchief...
Father, you...
Takumi, come here for a bit.
What is it, Dad?
I'm tired-
These two girls will be living with us starting today: Shirakawa Saori and Yui.
Be nice to them, Takumi.
I'm Shirakawa Yui, nice to meet you!
Umm... Onii-san.
Same here.
What do you think, Takumi?
They're as cute as Mizuki-chan and Satsuki-chan from next door, right?
That's not the problem!
What do you mean by living with us?
It means that you now have two cute sisters.
Even so, to respect their wishes, they're not really adopted.
We'll never admit that you are part of our family.
I never had plans of getting along with you.
Umm...
I'm really happy that I have a new brother now!
Yui!
Coming!
Well then, good night!
Takumi, it's morning already! Wake up!
Takumi.
Hey, wake up already!
Oww...
Mii-nee, good morning.
Gosh...
What do you mean by good morning?
You're going to be late!
Huh? It's already that late?
Also, where were you looking at while greeting me?
Now, hurry up and get ready.
Oh, right.
Nii-nee, there have been new girls in our house since yesterday...
I know, I just met them.
You already did?
You're the one who woke up late.
Here, change your clothes.
Thanks.
Hurry up and change, then come to breakfast.
Okay.
Two cute girls are living under the same roof as Takumi...
Hey, Takumi...
Hey! Wait until-
She's always like that.
Are you all right?
Onee-chan, sorry for making you wait!
Good morning!
Morning.
Onee-chan, wait!
We'll never admit that you are part of our family.
I never had plans of getting along with you.
That hurt!
Taku-chan, morning!
What are you doing, Satsuki?
I'm just saying hi!
Or would you prefer a kiss?
No.
Why?
You do it every day with Mii-nee, don't you?
Good morning kisses~
I don't.
You might not realize it, but she might be doing it while you're asleep.
Mii-nee would never do something like that!
I don't know if all that trust is a good thing.
She's been your older sister for way too long.
There's nothing wrong with trusting her!
I've always thought of Mii-nee as a real sibling!
I pity Mii-nee.
Why?
I can't tell you why.
By the way, where are the beautiful sisters that are living with you?
What "living with you"?
They just left before me. They wouldn't want to go to school with me, right?
Why?
I don't know.
I want to know, too.
Do they hate you because you did something perverted?
I didn't do such a thing!
Even if you say that, you're at that age...
What you just said might be true, but I wouldn't do that to my own family.
It seems like there's something behind this...
Okay, let's just leave it at that.
Bye Taku-chan, I'll see you at school.
Don't be late!
Crap!
Saori-san.
Let's go home together.
No thank you.
I was planning to take you around town.
Let's invite Yui-chan.
I have something to do.
Really?
Then how about tomorrow?
I'll always be busy.
Saori-san doesn't even listen to what I say...
Come in.
Excuse me.
Yui-chan, what is it?
Well...
Onii-san, I want to talk to you about something...
Umm...
Just come in first.
Okay.
So, what is it?
Umm... Onii-san.
Please don't hate my sister.
My sister isn't actually like that.
She's actually really cheerful and kind...
That's why...
That's why... Please don't hate her!
I got it.
Onii-san...
Don't worry, we'll get along.
Thank you!
Although I promised Yui-chan, I need to talk to her first.
That was my first time seeing a girl masturbate.
That's also Saori-san's...
It became like this...
Hello, Taku-chan!
Don't suddenly climb in like that!
I mean, don't show me your panties!
It happens all the time.
There's no need to get embarrassed now.
Cut it out and get off of me.
Could it be that you were about to masturbate?
No.
Eh?
It's not what you think!
It can't be helped, I've seen those two.
It can't be helped if any healthy male couldn't resist.
It's not like that.
That's right.
To show that I'm sorry for interrupting you, I'll let you masturbate to me.
Don't say stupid things.
Even though my body isn't as good as Nii-nee's, I'm still...
Satsuki, stop-
It's okay, Taku-chan.
I'll lend my body to you.
But you can't touch!
Hey, Taku-chan, I said you can't touch!
Gosh...
You still haven't seen a girl's private place, have you?
Wait, Taku-chan!
Satsuki...
I'm sorry for teasing you.
Taku-chan, you can't...
You can't do this...
Taku-chan...
No, Taku-chan...
Satsuki...
Satsuki!
No...!
Amazing, a girl can get this wet.
No, don't look!
Taku-chan, stop!
Stop...
I'm coming...
Satsuki, I'm putting it in, okay?
Gosh, I guess it can't be helped.
Taku-chan...
Here.
Satsuki...
Wait, Taku-chan!
If you're that rough...
You're so tight!
Taku-chan, I'm going to break!
No, I can't hold it anymore!
Taku-chan, I don't have any birth control...
If you're going to come, come outside!
Outside...
What...
Sorry, it felt too good inside.
Taku-chan, you idiot.
Satsuki, was that your first time?
Of course, what kind of girl do you think I am?
No, that's not it.
Never mind then, but you can't tell Mii-nee about what happened today.
Also, act normal in front of everyone,
and pretend that nothing ever happened.
Okay?
Okay...
If you keep your promise, I'll come again when I feel like it.
We might even have sex again.
Satsuki...
Takumi, it's morning already! Wake up!
Takumi...
Mii-nee, good morning.
You actually woke up by yourself, what happened?
Because I slept early yesterday.
Saori-san seems like she's working.
Doing what?
I heard it was at a café.
Where?
It's somewhere near Faga.
She said she didn't want to trouble you guys for money. What a good girl.
When does her work end?
How would I know that?
I see...
Here, change your clothes.
Thanks.
You should be more like Saori-san and do things yourself.
Okay...
Hey, Takumi, I have time today...
So can I walk you to school?
Hey, Takumi!
Sure, let's go together.
I'll get ready then!
Saori-san!
What are you doing here?
I came to pick you up.
No one told you to do such a thing.
I wanted to do it myself.
Thanks for the hard work!
Saori-san!
Why?
I heard from Yui-chan that it might rain today, so I thought you might be troubled.
Really?
I don't think you would want to walk together with a guy that you hate.
But if you catch a cold, Yui-chan would be really worried.
Just be patient until we get home.
If it's for Yui...
Yui-chan is really important to you, isn't she?
Of course, she's my only family member.
I know it would be impossible for you to treat me on the same level as Yui-chan,
but it would be great if that day ever came.
That's impossible.
Because you're that person's...
I don't know what happened between you and my dad.
But I am myself.
It's almost Christmas.
What about it?
Can you go on a date with me on Christmas Eve?
Why do I have to go on a date with you?
Even though it's a date, I'd be fine with talking over a cup of tea.
It's unfortunate,
but I have to work on Christmas Eve, so it's impossible.
So you think it's unfortunate.
No...
Don't play with my words...
It's all right if you work until late.
I'll wait for you by the train station.
I won't go.
I'll wait until you come.
Gosh... I said I'm not going.
Takumi...
Wake up, Takumi...
Wake up!
Oww...
Who is it?
What do you mean by who?
It's Christmas Eve!
How long are you planning to sleep for?
Mii-nee!
You have to go on a date with me today, so get ready.
Why a date?
What do you mean why?
It's Christmas Eve today!
That's why I'm asking why go on a date with you?
Gosh, I swore I was going to give it to you this year...
Christmas present?
What are you going to give me?
Don't ask a girl that!
Mii-nee, don't call yourself a girl at that age...
You're saying something like that again!
Takumi, do you want my virginity or not?
Virginity?!
Oh, no! I said it!
Mii-nee, that's...
Because, all you've been thinking about recently are Saori-san and Yui-chan...
If I don't do something soon, you'll be taken away...
Hey, I'll give you my virginity, so you give me yours, too!
Are you serious?
Could it be that someone took it already?
Don't tell me you did it with Saori-san...
No, that's impossible.
Thank goodness.
I love you, and I only want to do it with you...
I also don't want you to do it with anyone but me...
You love...
You actually...
I let it slip again!
I wanted to confess on a date during Christmas Eve when the mood was good...
And then both mind and body would be united...
Takumi, I love you!
Mii-nee, you really...
Gosh...
Idiot, I wouldn't joke about something like this.
Takumi, you're so hard already...
Do you like breasts?
You're such a naive kid...
Touch them, Takumi.
The front is so wet...
You really like breasts, don't you?
Takumi, I'll give my first time to you.
You don't need to do anything.
I'll make you feel good.
Mii-nee...
How is it?
Does it feel good inside me?
It does...
That's great.
I'm going to-
Your penis is getting better and better...
Mii-nee, if you go that rough, I'm going to...
Are you about to come, Takumi?
Is your penis going to ejaculate soon?
Come inside me!
I want you to ejaculate inside me...
Let me feel good until the end!
But, Mii-nee...
Come, Takumi!
Ejaculate inside me!
Your semen is coming out...
It feels so hot...
I got it dirty.
Let me clean it for you.
It got bigger again.
Does my mouth feel good?
Now, I'll suck it clean.
Mii-nee...
Are you going to come again?
Umm... I want to do it with your breasts.
You really like breasts, Takumi.
Mii-nee!
I'm sorry, Mii-nee.
It's okay, Takumi.
Takumi, you can do whatever you want this time.
You can move better from behind.
I guess.
I'm going to move, Mii-nee.
It's deep...
It's so good even though it's my first time...
Even though it's the second time you've put it inside me!
Your penis makes me feel so good!
Mii-nee, you're so wet, warm and tight...
Me too, I never thought your penis was going to be this good!
Mii-nee, Mii-nee!
Takumi! Takumi!
I'm going to come inside again!
Come, come inside me!
Shoot all you've got inside me!
My pussy will take it...
Mii-nee, I'm coming!
I'm going to come too!
Takumi!
Sorry, did I wake you?
No.
I finally became one with you...
But we had sex before our date.
My plan went to waste...
Before our date...
Takumi?
What are you doing so suddenly?
Hey, Takumi.
I just remembered that I had something important to do...
What important thing?
Hey, Takumi!
Mii-nee, sorry!
What do you mean?
Takumi?
How can you show up late after inviting someone?
Sorry!
Maybe I shouldn't have come after all.
But you came in the end.
Because if I didn't and you waited for me and caught a cold...
Yui would feel upset.
Think of it as that.
I know you're actually very kind.
But I'm really happy that you came.
Although it's not Mii-nee, I've decided.
Saori-san.
I...