One war ended.
and the next is about to begin.
lt is the time before the great war.
Both sides furtively study their opponent,
and sharpen their blades in secret.
ln this time
with their excelled science,
the United Empires, the world super power, attempted to take over the world.
With their scientific knowledge
and the wisdom of Chabala,
they were able to extract the "Angel Core,"
the crystal of divine power, from the ones inheriting the angel blood.
On the northern boarder of Nortland,
The nurturing of the "Angel Core" and the development of weapons continues on...
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
Life of Angels Part 1
Lieutenant Ralph Maskenval, it's time for our duty.
l'm Salsa.
Ralph-san?
Please do a lot of nasty stuff to me again today.
l want big loads of Ralph-san to go inside me.
Okay?
Yeah. Let's go.
l can't wait to do it...
How's the new guy doing?
Not much to say for an elite officer of the U.E.
He'll get used to it.
Well, l guess he was surprised, but no wonder.
He was sent to this remote land to do nothing but fuck girls...
Don't get me wrong, Colonel.
l'm not doing this for fun.
lt's just to nurture the Angel Core...
This is a required mission, in order for the U.E. to win the war.
Understood, Facility No. 37 head officer, General Arafni Natanzone.
it's embarrassing, you staring at me with the lights on.
Embarrassing?
ls it because of this sound?
Because l'm so horny right now, my pussy feels like its melting.
l can see it clearly.
Ralph-san, your fingers...
Going inside me...
Two fingers...
lt's going in...
l'm, l'm going to cum.
l'm cumming!
Now, l want this from Ralph-san.
lt grew so big.
Ralph-san...
now, make my pussy feel even better.
it's so hot...
it feels so good...
it's grinding so deep...
No, no...
l'm cumming again...
l came already, but l'm cumming again...
lt's going in, and l feel it gushing.
Ralph-san, thank you for giving me loads of your stuff today.
See you later, Salsa.
Yes.
Umm, Ralph-san?
Yes?
Did l feel good?
Because l felt really good when you did...
But it's embarrassing if l was the only one feeling it...
lt felt really good. Let's have fun again, Salsa.
Yes!
Do nasty stuff to me again, Ralph-san!
Mission complete.
Preparation complete.
lt's tonight.
Yes. l'm going to let Onoma-chan know.
Onoma-chan!
Salsa...
Hey Onoma-chan!
Man Salsa, l waited a while.
But, but, it's my "work," so nothing can be done.
Come on...
Your so obsessed with Ralph.
Huh? But Ralph-san is so nice.
Right! You don't know him deep inside.
Did you forget?
He's also a comrade of the rotten pigs of U.E.!
Hmm... But Ralph-san is different from the others.
He doesn't hurt me or do stuff that l don't like.
That's what l'm saying, you're being played with.
it's their trick.
But l don't think of him that way.
Besides that, Salsa, do you know why we're waiting?
Oh, yes.
l talked to the Grey man already.
All good to go?
Good, so far like planned.
Then we better get prepared.
Hehe, this is exciting.
Man, this isn't supposed to be fun!
Hey, what are you doing?
No, nothing!
Nothing!
Salsa-san, Onoma-san, lt's me.
Socolata-san.
Don't scare me like that.
What's the matter?
You two chit-chatting here.
Uh, umm... You know...
Anyways, that's that. Right, Salsa?
Ye, yes! Then, see you later!
Huh?
Very nice.
Hitting all in the same spot.
A good aim.
Heard that you're an elite, but you're pretty lenient.
Well, l'd rather try not to kill.
l see...
Oh yeah, Lieutenant Maskenval, aren't you going to tonight's mission?
Yeah.
You heard what we're doing right?
l heard from Colonel Baker.
But...
lt's the mission!
You're violating the code just standing here now.
Yeah, it's an order.
So l really have to go.
But...
Scared? Starting to feel cold?
No, l don't think so.
Then you feel guilty?
That's closer.
snicker snicker...
ls it funny?
No, l understand.
When l was first stationed here, l felt the same.
The same?
The mission.
Wondering if l was doing the right thing or not.
l pondered and wondered...
But humans get used to a lot of things.
So, you'll get used to it, Lieutenant.
The missions...
Then for today, l'll say that l didn't see you here.
Lieutenant Anna.
Huh?
Uhh, thank you.
You owe me one.
Please forgive me...
lt's grinding inside me...
l'm cumming...
l'm cumming on your face...
Thank me.
Thank you very much...
Aah...
So sticky...
Thank you...
What? What's the matter?
You mouth is becoming negligent...
What? l told you not to stop.
Ralph-san...
What's the matter?
You don't want to do it?
No... l don't...
Why?
Last time, you never said anything, and you fucked all of them.
Don't you want to get out of here?
lf you're pregnant, you can get out of here.
Not one person wants to die.
That's why everyone is in bed with these guys.
Besides, last time you were...
But... Ralph-san is not here.
Ralph?
Hmm... l see, Salsa... l see.
Come over here, let's have fun together.
Don't you want to be "nurtured" by us?
l'll fill your stomach with all our good stuff!
No!
Huh?
Salsa doesn't feel good today.
So l'll go for her.
You?
Yes, you two, at once.
Or, am l not good enough?
We, well...
We don't mind at all.
Then let's go over there.
Good , l'm so happy.
Uh , umm... thank you.
Just to let you know, l didn't come to help you.
Huh?
Do you know?
The Angel Core nurtured inside reacts to love, and it grows bigger.
So Salsa, remember that you're approaching your death.
Huh? Why is that...?
You... are you in love with Ralph?
The time has come...
Wha, wha, what the hell!
Sorry l'm late! What's going on?
Ralph, the attackers are trying to surround the facility.
These two buildings have top security, so no problem.
The problem is the back.
lts in a blind-spot from our security tower.
l didn't notice.
l got it. l'll bring more reinforcements here...
Situation?
The back is struggling, it was shorthanded today.
Lieutenant Maskenval is getting reinforcements...
No need for that.
No need... which means...?
Professor Shawvelger's request.
She needs data for Machine man Zoldate's night time combat.
Bring the Machine man Zoldate's to the back.
Tell them to shut off all the search lights in the back.
Machine man Zoldate has night vision mode.
The light will only help the enemy.
Roger.
Ralph , go to the campgrounds and look after the girls... the angels.
All right.
How is the Machine man Zoldate?
Activation is complete.
Under Colonel Baker's orders, three of them are already to go.
lt might be over by now.
Now, go!
Machine man Zoldate!
Roger.
Wha... What the hell?
Shoot! Shoot it!
Who are these guys?
Mo-monster!
Amazing.
When these guys are fully operational, the U.E. shall take over the world!
The one's who didn't evacuate are Salsa and Onoma...
Huh?
What are you doing?
No wonder you're a dog of the U.E.
Your senses are keen.
Talk, and l'll spare you.
Run away, angel... Run...
Fuck!
l know all this is according to Salsa's plan.
But l never heard that it was this soon!
Onoma-chan, the wall over there is crumbled!
We can go outside!
Okay, Salsa, let's go!
Yes...
What are you doing, Salsa?
Onoma-chan, wait for me...
You always take to much time. Hurry up!
But...!
You two, stop!
Ralph-san?
Ralph?
Stop the nonsense, you two.
lt's not nonsense.
We're going to escape from this place!
How can you escape?
lt's zero below outside!
We can do it now! Thru all this mess!
Just give up! You'll be involved in the battle.
The security is weak on this side.
So we sent enough troops on this side.
The solders here are probably defeated by now.
Onoma-chan!
Onoma... Why do you know this...
Oh my...!
Run angel... run...
Don't bother me! What about yourself?
You'll be dead if you stand here.
Who said the Lieutenant will be dead?
Colonel Baker...
Nice try, but you underestimated our forces.
The attackers are crushed... no, they are annihilated.
You guys will be shot down, not from a stray bullet, but shot like a runaway.
Onoma-chan...
Take the two away.
Roger.
Stop it!
Fuck, let go!
Such violent... Colonel, the two...
Lieutenant Ralph Maskenval.
No wonder you're an elite officer, a native of Gaedry.
l'm impressed with your skills, capturing the runaways that way.
Pretending to persuade the girls, when you were really gaining time.
You're a very good actor.
Right?
No, l was only...
No, no, l understand.
With bright personnel like you in the military,
the future of U.E. is looking bright.
Don't you think so?
Ralph-san!
Help, help me!
You dogs of the U.E.!
l will never be treated like you guys!
Not like you guys!
Can't this bitch shut up already?
Take them away!
Shit...
Shit, shit!