Man, they made such a mess.
Of course nobody's here, but...
Did those two...
The emblem of Dark Mother?
Blade!
l took the woman who was supposed to be used for the Angel System!
lf you want to save her, come to the Dark Mother Castle.
l'll be waiting for you!
See ya!
Go to the castle, huh?
Kyoka...
A nightmare...
l received absolute bliss and comfort from the Phantom Lady.
But why...
Please! Please forgive me...
Please forgive me.
Please forgive us, Phantom Lady!
Forgive you two?
What do you want me to forgive?
Forgive you for failing to capture Angel Blade?
ln order to atone for your sins, you two must be punished.
That's why l'm giving you pain and suffering right now.
Like this!
This isn't working.
Even though l punish you two, you're both feeling pleasure.
l can't call this torture.
You two need more punishment.
Taste it with both your mind and body.
The pleasure of darkness...
And your souls in chaos.
Moena Shinguuji!
Here. Over here!
Do you remember me, Moena?
Or maybe l should call you Angel Blade?
What!
You're going home, right?
l'll give you a ride. Hop in.
Okay...
l'm glad Tenmyoin is all right.
How do you know that?
lt's my job to know them.
But l don't know everything.
For example, let's see...
l don't know about Dark Mother or Angel Blade...
Or why you're feeling sad...
You wanna tell me about it?
l see. So she is...
You know aunt Kyoka?
l only met her twice.
When l took you to the house.
You took me to the house?
Yeah. You were unconscious at the time, so...
Who was that?
What a reckless driver.
Could that be...
Shaiya!
You know her?
l think...
Aunt Kyoka was captured by Dark Mother?
lt looks like it.
And this is the invitation.
ls it a trap?
l'm 100% sure.
But you're still going, right?
Of course!
Right, Moena?
Yes. We'll rescue aunt Kyoka!
Well, there's one problem.
Problem?
We need to find out how to get outside the city...
...and into Dark Mother Castle.
We can't just simply get there riding a bike.
You're right...
Leave it to me.
What?
Ayame...
Phantom Lady.
We have the scan data for the Angel System experiment.
We checked her body right down to the cellular level...
...but we didn't detect any abnormalities.
As for the choker attached to her neck...
We couldn't scan it.
Plus, some parts of her body, mainly, her genitals and her uterus...
...couldn't be scanned from the outside.
ln order to conduct the research in greater detail...
...we inserted a tracking device inside her body...
We will remove the device after we find the core...
...of the Angel System.
Excellent.
Begin the analysis immediately.
The hour of the feast is upon us.
We don't have much time.
That's right.
l'm gonna have lots of fun with this woman.
lt's a huge plane.
lt's not bad.
We're gonna fly through the storm clouds, right?
lf it wasn't this big, it'd be hopeless.
We're taking off! Hurry up and get on board!
You're doing very well.
No...
lt's moving inside...
Oh my...
You pushed them all out.
No wonder you were chosen to be a guinea pig for the Angel System.
You used the nanometallic skin strengthening system in your womb.
But we can put it to better use.
l'm gonna have lots of fun.
You're gonna entertain me.
My, you're shouting out loud.
Does it feel that good?
You're very sensitive...
No, l'm not feeling it...
l can have a lot of fun with those boobs.
l'll take real good care of you.
Look, it's getting hard.
Not there!
You climaxed already?
You're so wet.
Then l'll play with you some more.
l'll give you something real good.
What are you saying?
l...
Wait just a minute.
lt's coming out soon.
So this is the cock belonging to a mutant of Dark Mother...
lt's so huge.
lt looks like it's going to explode.
Amazing...
Now let's enjoy it some more.
l want you to suck on it.
Yes.
That's it. You're doing good.
Next, let's try...
l want you to entertain me...
...with those huge, sensitive, dirty boobs of yours!
Like this?
Not bad.
Feels very soft...
Use your mouth too.
Yes, keep going.
Now, with your dirty boobs...
l want you to make me ejaculate.
Yes.
l'm about to explode!
l'll give you lots of juice!
What an unbelievable amount and the smell...
But it tastes good...
How embarrassing.
You wet yourself this much.
Now here we go.
No...
That huge thing won't fit.
Stop lying.
You know you want it real bad.
l'm not lying...
Amazing. lt's twisting inside.
You really wanted it.
lt can't be...
Why...
l...
lt's the cock of a mutant from Dark Mother, but...
l feel so good.
lt's so intense.
lt's penetrating very deep inside.
No, l can't take it anymore.
l can't stop moaning.
So big.
l can't believe you're feeling it this much.
You're such a slut.
The guy who was at the laboratory...
You gave him pleasure like this?
l didn't do it with him.
No!
You didn't do it?
Liar.
With a sexy body like this...
How could you resist other men?
l'm not lying.
lsato is...
l'm sorry.
l'm gonna come.
You're gonna make me climax!
l'm coming!
l see, so that guy's name is lsato.
lsato...
Phantom Lady.
l know.
l'm expecting a visitor.
Our preparations for the feast are complete.
There's the castle.
That's the Dark Mother Castle?
l didn't expect it to be this big.
lt certainly looks like an evil stronghold.
Aunt Kyoka...
l hope you're all right.
Angel Heart Flash!
Shining Flash!
l don't see any guards...
lt's very quiet.
lt's so strange...
Welcome, Angels.
l'll show you the way from here on.
Our mistress, Phantom Lady, is expecting you.
Come with me quietly.
Aunt Kyoka!
Blade, wait!
We know she's luring us into a trap.
But she hasn't made any move at all. What is she planning to do?
Aunt Kyoka...
Thanks for coming, Angel Blade.
You too, Angel Ender.
Welcome to my castle. l was expecting you, Angels.
My name is Phantom Lady.
l'm the master of this castle, as well as the ruler of Dark Mother.
Your fighting skills are amazing.
You two managed to fight off the mutants of Dark Mother.
But it's all going to end today.
With the feast that's about to take place...
...our struggle will reach a new phase.
Thanks for everything, Nailkaizer.
No problem.
l want you to participate in this feast as well.
What?
Time has come. l want you to begin.
Yes, Mother!
So it was a trap after all.
But what is this?
What's happening to the floor?
My body's sinking!
What the...
What?
What is this?
What are these things?
lt can't be...
General Chloe!
Colonel Elaine!
What happened to you?
Shining Knuckle!
What's going on?
l'm stuck!
Great, l'm surrounded.
l have a bad feeling about this.
Phantom Lady!
Why me?
Why?
lt's because l love you, Nailkaizer.
lt is a custom to submit your loved ones for the feast's sacrifice.
You have nothing to fear, Nailkaizer.
All those who come from chaos simply return to chaos again.
What's going on inside the castle?
l can't just wait for them up here.
Everything in the field is stable.
As the pressure increases, the density is increasing as well.
This cup is filling up with chaos.
Angels! l want you to help me fill this cup even more!
lt's hopeless...
Everyone...
Shaiya!
And that woman too?
l have to do something.
Aunt!
Aunt Kyoka!
The cup is almost full.
Anger, hatred...
Sadness, and happiness...
l want you to fill this cup with all those feelings.
l'm sorry.
l'm sorry, Moena.
l'm sorry, lsato.
What's this?
Everything in the field is going down.
Density is going down as well.
But the pressure is still going up.
What in the world is going on?
Mother!
This light...
Angel Blade!
They freed themselves from the pit of chaos!
lnteresting.
You're better than l expected, Angels!
Mother!
l see.
My Angel Sword has no effect on her.
Phantom Lady...
She's too strong.
How can l beat her?
Moena...
Did you just call my name?
How did you...
Go!
She's so powerful.
Blade, can you hear me?
Shaiya!
l rescued Kyoka.
Let's get out of here!
Phantom lady...
You let us go?
Do not disappoint me.
lf you do, you will die.
Get stronger, Angels.
We're moving forward from here
An Angel flies away into the cold breeze
Thousands of lights are shining bright
l hope the light reaches you, so let's jump out
Ah, destroy the world
l want to penetrate it now Don't stop, don't give up, let me know
lf you never turn me now, are we shining? Punish severely with Angel Heart
l will power any god, l will challenge any fight, loneliness speeds up
Expose all the hypocrites
Now that you're here, let's fight, Angel Blade