One war ended,
and the next is about to begin.
lt is the time before the great war
Both sides furtively study their opponent,
and sharpen their blades in secret.
ln this time,
with their excelled science,
the United Empires, the world super power, attempted to take over the world.
With their scientific knowledge and the wisdom of Chabala,
they were able to extract the crystal of divine power
''Angel Core'' from those inheriting the angel blood.
On the northern boarder of Nortland,
The nurturing of the "Angel Core" and the development of weapons continues on...
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
Life of Angels Part 2
Dear God, please forgive this sinful sister
ls it not over yet?
Like it says on that report,
even though the attack was great,
number of casualties were minimal.
As expected from my new weapon, Silver Crusade Machine man Zoldats.
According to this report, it says there was damage to the electric generator?
Yes, we don't have the material needed to fix it so we are currently cleaning up the mess.
Equipment needed to live and electricity needed for research are both operational.
That's good. The fuhrer will be arriving and we can't make his stay unpleasant.
Fuhrer? ... The fuhrer will be coming here?
We just received the news.
He is here to see the Machine man Zoldats and the progress on our research.
That is so sudden. We must reevaluate the security,
since there are electric connectivity issue all around the facility from the attack.
Well... the terrorist must have given up after that experience.
Actually, they are probably scared shitless even to move.
That reminds me, wasn't there an Angel who tried to escape during the attack?
Do you mean Onoma and Salsa?
The ones under the supervision of Lieutenant Ralph Maskenval.
Those girls? My subordinates are taking care of them.
lf they are in connection with the terrorist
we may be able to get some information from them.
Does the Lieutenant know?
l didn't notify him.
lt might be too big of a burden for the new Lieutenant.
Alright, this is next.
Now, what shall l do?
Onoma-chan!
How many times have you tried escaping?
As if l'll remember!
What's with that stare? Looks like those of a traitor.
l'll show you what we do to those who gives us that look.
Please! l beg you, don't do it!
Damn it!! Give back my eye! My eye! Give it back you bastard!
Give it back? Let's see... where did l put it?
Oops, l'm so sorry. l stepped on it.
Hey, someone just stick it into the new hole.
lf you do that...
Ah, yeah you might die.
But l was told by the Colonel it didn't matter
Since by law, Angels aren't humans.
Fuck... l won't forgive you damn it.
This is the first time l've put it in this hole. Let's see how it feels.
Shit are you fucking serious? Damn, stop it.
Please! Don't treat Onoma-chan like that.
instead, you can take me in her place.
Stupid Salsa, don't say that.
That's interesting. So you are saying you
will take it two at a time?
lf l say yes, would you stop abusing Onoma-chan?
lf you can endure it, l may think about it.
l will take it!
Salsa don't! Don't worry about me.
Don't worry Onoma-chan.
First is this. Don't break from the first shot.
What is that?!
That's too long!
Stop it!
What's wrong? The heads not even completely in yet.
lt hurts! lt hurts! lt hurts!!!
No! No! l can't take that position!
ls that enough already?
Onoma-chan?
You said you wouldn't touch Onoma-chan.
Don't worry, we won't do anything that will kill her.
Onoma-chan! Onoma-chan!
Salsa! Salsa!
They were carried in with scratches and fractures but
they are well on their way to recovery now
Could it be the power of the Angel's blood?
l see. That's good.
ln any case, it's good they didn't die.
They both have high numbers, so it would be a shame
for them to die before we extract the ''Angel Core''.
Anyways, l'll see you later
l gave her some pills so she should be awake in a few hours.
Shit! lt hurts...
Onoma...
lt's Salsa's fault.
Huh?
Because l invited her to come with me.
lnvited? For that escape?
Salsa was doing something for a grey colored man.
A grey colored man?
He is from outside. l'm supposed to bring my findings to the outside.
Zone Mist... So a spy.
When the grey colored man came, Salsa was supposed to run away from here.
But l didn't want to just escape all by myself.
So l asked Onoma-chan to come with me.
But... because l did that, Onoma-chan was...
Ended up like this!
Ralph-san!
l thought it was Onoma who asked you and you were the victim.
lf Onoma dies, it would all be Salsa's fault. All because of me...
Salsa, its not like that.
Clumsy Salsa, what are you crying for?
Onoma-chan! You are awake!
Ouch... My whole body hurts.
l'm sorry! All because of Salsa, you end up...
Stop it, l'm the one who screwed up.
l won't give up. l'm going to get out of this shit hole.
Salsa?
Yes?
Let me sleep a little more.
Onoma-chan. l don't want you to die.
Yeah, and you, Salsa. l don't want you to die.
This is Ralph Maskenval.
Well done.
Professor Shawvelger.
Lieutenant, how are those two?
Like you said, most of their wounds are healing.
l see, that's good.
How may l be of service today?
Professor Shawvelger will give you the details.
We have decided to extract the ''Angel Core'' out of Salsa and Onoma.
Extraction? But...
Numbers are above average. There is no reason not to.
But after you extract the ''Angel Core'', they will...
We think that the ''Angel Core'' is the soul of the Angels.
A body without it's soul is just a corpse.
That means those girls are going to die.
From our statistics, after the extraction, within 3 days organs will stop functioning.
This has already been decided, Lieutenant Maskenval.
Extraction will be performed 3 days after the final assessment.
3 days later...
lt is due to your efforts, Lieutenant Maskenval that the two cores
of those girls have matured enough to be extracted.
Especially when it has only been a short period since your arrival.
Thank you sir!
Ralph. Ralph.
Onoma, what is it?
l am finally able to walk by myself.
There isn't anything they can do about my eye, but everything else is fine.
l've also thought being an Angel was stupid, but in these situations, l guess l'm grateful.
l came to thank you.
Salsa told me. Ralph, you are the reason why we didn't die.
lf you didn't come by, we would have both been killed.
You also watched over me with Salsa while l was asleep right?
Salsa was right. There is something about you that's different from the other guys.
l hate to be fucked by the others but you, Ralph...
l don't mind being fucked by you.
Onoma... you are still hurt,
and l didn't save you or Salsa. ln three days, your ''Angel Core'' will...
Ralph~
Onoma.
Clean up the place where they fucked me.
l don't want you... l don't want to let you two die.
Ah, it's embarrassing to undress.
No... wait!
Ralph.. No... Don't do that.
Please Ralph, if you keep doing that, l can't take it any longer. Fuck me.
Are you alright? lf it hurt, l can st...
No, it's not that. lt's so deep in me it feels so good.
Your pussy feels good too.
l can feel your cock in me. Please fuck me.
You are the only one who treats me so gently.
All the other bastards were rough and forced their cocks in me.
Ra... Ralph, you are so good. l can feel it all the way.
Onoma, what's wrong? Does it hurt somewhere?
lt's not that. l was just thinking that l'm starting to like you.
Oh, well l feel the same way
And that's why l can't keep quiet.
What is it?
lt was just an prologue.
A prologue? You mean the attack was just an...
lt was a test to see how powerful you guys are.
Next time, they will be more heavily equiped.
...That's what Salsa said.
What the fuck! We lost many men. That was just a camouflage?
Next is the real thing.
Salsa said this time for sure, she will escape.
They will be here the day after
But l can't leave here anymore,
even if l may die, l don't want to leave you.
Please let Salsa go!
She's doesn't have any relatives and she was bullied when she first came here.
She didn't have any choice but to join the rebellion.
l beg you, please let her go and let her be happy.
No l can't.
Ralph!
No, l can't let Salsa escape alone.
lf Salsa is to escape, you need to go with her.
lt they find out Salsa escaped during the attack, you will be accused.
l don't think your body can take all that interrogation again.
But...
And in three days, you and Salsa's ''Angel Core'' will be extracted.
lf you stay here, you will die.
l don't want you to die that way
Salsa needs someone to take care of her also.
What are you going to do Ralph?
l'm going to help you escape. After that, l don't know what will happen.
Ralph-san!
What are you doing Ralph-san?
l was just checking the weather
lt isn't snowing that hard.
Yeah.
Yay! l was worried about going outside if it snowed hard.
Ralph-san. Ralph-san.
lt is today, everyone is going to be here soon.
Yeah, l heard it from Onoma.
They said they are going to kill all the soldiers.
Please don't die Ralph-san.
l will be careful.
Okay then. Salsa is going back to her room now.
Lieutenant, what's the matter?
What are you daydreaming about, staring out the window? Something interesting?
No sir. l was just checking how hard the snow was falling.
All this snow makes the view all the more boring.
Anyways, l envy you Lieutenant.
To be able to raise two ''Angel Core'' at a time.
ls that due to your youthful sexual energy?
Don't be shy,
Back in the days, l fucked 5 times, 6 times in one night.
What the fuck?!!?
Shit! Seems like something happened! Get to your position!
Damn it! Hurry your ass up!
l am all ready.
You slow poke. Do you know what would happen if we are left behind?
Calm down Onoma-chan.
How can anyone stay calm in this situation?!
Oh! l forgot something.
SALSA!
You should leave that piece of crap.
The grey colored man told me there is a secret weapon in here.
He said just in case.
Let's go.
Okay.
Don't move!
Where do you think you are going carrying that luggage?
Lieutenant Anna, put your gun down.
Lieutenant Ralph? What's the meaning of this?
l can't just watch you kill them.
l can't let those two die.
Ralph!
Ralph-san!
Traitor. You won't get away with it.
l know that.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
l'll just pretend l didn't see that.
l never came and saw what happened here.
Lieutenant Anna.
Hurry up and get out of here.
lf the other soldiers see you, l won't be able to help.
Thanks.
Onoma! Salsa!
Ralph, l hope you can make things l gave up into reality,
Ralph, what are you going to do from now on?
After l get you safely across, l will return to the facility,
But if they find out you helped us escape...
l'll deal with it when it comes.
You can't do that!
When we get out of here, all three of us are going to drink tea and eat cake together!
That's why until then, we must stay together!
Alright, let's stay together
l promise.
Really?
Come on, don't cry anymore.
Alright, let's go.
Okay.
They damaged the electricity connection last time
so the electric fence isn't working.
That's why they targeted the electric generator.
Yeah probably.
lf we get past here, we are outside of the facility.
Let's do this as one go.
However, life is a bitch. Right? Lieutenant Ralph Maskenval?
You are still young.You are an amateur at acting secretively.
Ralph, we've been follow by this fat pig!
A fat pig huh? Shut that bitches mouth!
Roger.
Onoma!
Okay! Proceed to the next target!
Roger.
Ralph!
lmpossible!
An Angel?!! She awakened?!
Awakening? The blood in Onoma's body?
However, with those wounds, you can't completely recover.
Onoma-Chan!!
That's dangerous!
What is it?
There is a bomb in there!
Onoma!
l'm sorry you guys. This is the end of the road for me.
But l'll make sure the two of you escape.
No! You have to come with us!
No l can't. lt's already a miracle that l'm still here,
so it won't last for too long.
You have to run away now!
ONOMA-CHAN!!!
Salsa, are you hurt anywhere?
Onoma-chan...
Onoma sacrificed herself to let us escape,
we can't let it go to waste. Let's go Salsa.
Onoma-chan.
You bastard! l won't forgive you Ralph Maskenval!
You bastard! All because of you, everything became a waste!
lf you had brought results, you could have returned to the central office!
You bastard! DlE!!
DlE! DlE! DlE!!
l see! You want to die first!
Don't come near me!
DlE! DlE! DlE!! DlE!!!
Salsa Now!
Ye... Yes!
Salsa, are you alright? Are you hurt?
Yes l'm okay.
Sorry but we don't have time to rest.
We have to move.
Okay.
Onoma-chan helped us escape so we must succeed right?
That's right. Let's go.
Onoma-chan... Good-bye.
lt's a feather.
Onoma... lt's Angel's feather.
Onoma-chan.
When we reach town, l'll prepare some cake and tea.
l'll make some for Onoma as well, even though we are not together
They left. You sure its okay to let them go?
Not a problem.
A prey trapped in a cloud like nest, will never be able to escape.
Doesn't seem like they will come back.
They will. That's how it is decided.
ls it that thing you always talk about? Fate?
No one can fight fate.
Even God... nor Angels.