Good morning.
– Good morning
– Good morning.
Hey!
Currently, there are two girls and boys
living in the Fujishima household.
My two older brothers and their wives,
Yukie-san and Shizuka-san.
And then, me.
You need to wash your face
and come downstairs looking proper!
Spoken like a real former teacher.
You really have it together.
You need to do the same since
you're a college student now.
I get it already.
I'll get changed and come back down.
Thank you for your daily display
of affection morning after morning.
If you were just more down to earth,
I'm sure you could get a girl of your own.
I-I'll see you guys later.
ay LTE
Back
Sender: Yukie
Recipient: Fujishima Ryouto
Subject: You Passed
You haven't forgotten that I'm giving
you something to celebrate you passing
right? You need to come over soon.
Congratulations on passing.
Even if it's just once, I'd like to
stick it inside Yukie-san and Shizuku-san.
But no matter how much I love sex,
even I wouldn't lay a hand on my brothers' wives.
I'm home!
Welcome back, Ryouto-san.
Dinner's ready.
Huh? Where are my brothers?
They both said that they'd be home late cause of work.
But seriously, it's such a waste that they're
making their two beautiful wives wait for them.
Wh-What are you saying?
Ryouto-san, you have quite the silver tongue.
No, no...
I'm being serious. Aren't you two unsatisfied?
N-No, we don't think that at all.
Don't even joke about those sorts of things!
That was really scary...
Sender: Ch
Recipient: Fujishima Ryouto
Subject: None
My husband is coming home late again.
I was saving this underwear for him,
but looks like it's gone to waste.
It's Yukie-san from the dating site that I'm on.
Oh, wow!
I can't believe there's a guy out there
who'd leave this body alone.
Don't worry.
He'll come home eventually.
When he does, you'll get the chance to show him.
As long as he has the guts.
Sender: Yukie
Recipient: Fujishima Ryouto
Subject: Meeting
Have you met the person
that you've married?
I have but I'm not going to cheat...
"I have."
There are wives out there who, because they
love their husbands, don't want to feel unsatisfied.
I have but I'm not going to cheat...
The perfect husband, except when it comes to sex.
I'll will that void for you.
I'll fill the gap in your heart.
How about we meet next Sunday?
As long as I don't have any plans...
U-Um... are you Ryou-chan-san?
Ryou-chan?
Yep, that's me, Yukie-san.
I'd laugh in joy at the chance to fuck my brothers' wives
So you were that unsatisfied, huh?
Th-That's not true.
That's not what you said in your emails.
You said that your pussy was throbbing with desire
since your husband wouldn't give you any.
I-I never wrote that...
So you're only doing this kind of thing because you want
to have sex with someone other than my brother?
D-Don't say something so ridiculous!
But you came here with the sole intention
of sucking this cock, didn't you?
N-No I didn't...
Are you betraying Masaki-san?
For me to not betray him, I'd have to tell him
everything that's happened, wouldn't I?
Th-That's...
But I love my brother and wouldn't
want to do anything to ruin our relationship.
If you don't do this, I'll tell my brother everything.
P-Please, don't!
Anything but that...
Please...
Then just give up and have some fun with me.
It'll definitely feel good.
Just today.
Just today, okay?
Okay then, let's get started.
Wait, we're all sweaty.
Shouldn't we take a shower first?
Just like this is fine.
We're gonna get sweaty again anyway.
B-But...
Shizuka-san, do you want me to undress you?
I-I'll undress myself.
Wow.
Damn!
Your body is way too hot!
I really want to do you now!
I like that face you're making.
It really sells the whole "unsatisfied desires"
feel you've got going on.
P-Please don't say such embarrassing things!
Well then, how about you move your hands?
Huh? Did you not hear me?
That's one beautiful pussy.
It doesn't look like it belongs to a married woman at all.
Don't stare at it...
No! You can't!
What can't I do, Shizuka-san?
You can't!
No! No way! No way!
No!
If that's what you're like after what I just did,
the next part's gonna kill you.
P-Please...
We really shouldn't be doing this...
If you do this, I'll never be the same again!
You're already past the point of no return.
We can't! You're not even wearing a condom!
Don't worry. I'll give you some pills after.
Please, take it out!
Something weird is being thrust deep inside of me!
That's right. My dick is knocking
on the entrance of your pussy.
No! That can't be!
So, my brother's didn't go in this far, did it?
I'll show you a world you've never seen before!
No! Stop! I don't need you to do that!
Please! Please stop!
Please stop!
My stomach is turning over!
Shizuka-san, I'm gonna cum!
Wh-What? No way! Stop!
No! Stop!
No!
This... can't be happening!
Let's do this with a bang to commemorate
our first adulterous encounter!
My insides are throbbing!
No! No!
Hot stuff is pouring deep inside of me...
Oh, yeah. Now that I think about it,
I want to do the real Yukie-san too.
You'd feel bad if you were
the only one who cheated, right?
I'll increase the number of accomplices.
All done.
Come to think of it, Yukie-san...
What is it?
You lied about being at
a class reunion yesterday, right?
Huh?
Wh-What do you mean?
My friend said that he was at
a group mixer with a married woman.
You were there, weren't you?
I-I wasn't there because I was at my class reunion.
Oh? So who's this?
That picture...
Why do you have it?
Were you the only one there?
Was Shizuka-san there too?
Sh-She wasn't. It was just me.
I was just asked to fill in so that
there would be an even ratio!
So...
Sorry, but I was the one who set up that group mixer.
With the help of Shizuka-san, that is.
Never figured you'd cheat though.
I didn't cheat!
It's not that I don't get where you're coming from though.
Your heart's satisfied, but your body isn't.
Th-That's not...
So why don't you let me
satisfy those carnal desires?
I'm saying that I'll become your human vibrator.
All in order to protect this family.
Wh-What are you saying, Ryouto-san?!
Are you planning on betraying your brother?
To not betray my brother,
I'd have to tell him everything I know, wouldn't I?
Y-You can't do that!
No way!
Why don't you join in on the fun?
We'll have a blast fucking each other.
There's no way we can do that!
I'm asking you again, would you rather me tell
my brother everything or keep it all a secret?
You're even better than I imagined.
No!
Look at this. You're ready to go, aren't you?
Don't do that, it's dirty...
It's not dirty at all.
I'm gonna lick your pussy now.
No way!
This... isn't right!
No! Stop!
No!
Wait... No... No...
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
Cumming from being licked?
You're the spitting image of a pervert.
I didn't cum! I didn't cum!
So does that mean I need this to satisfy your pussy?
No! It's not going to fit!
If that goes in me,
I'm definitely going to lose my mind!
What is this? I've never felt like this before!
This isn't right! Take it out!
I got it. I'll make sure all of my cum is
"taken out" of my dick and pumped into your pussy!
That's not what I meant!
Stop it! I'm gonna go crazy!
No! No! Take it out!
Damn! Your pussy feels so good!
I'm already gonna cum!
No! You can't cum inside! You really can't!
It's fine, don't worry. I'll give you some pills later.
I came inside Shizuka-san like crazy too, you know!
How did this happen?
No! You really can't cum inside!
I'm cumming!
It's so hot!
Here we go.
Yukie-san, keep what happened today a secret.
As long as you do that,
we can keep living our usual lives.
Yukie-san, need something...
Sorry, but it's just Ryou-chan.
What? Did you have some laundry
that you haven't taken out yet?
So even after all that, you can still act normally?
Please, let's not talk about that.
If you don't need anything, then leave!
I do. I was thinking about thanking you...
Thanking me?
Yukie-san...
This is all thanks to you.
N-No, I...
You involved her under the condition
that I wouldn't lay a finger on you again, right?
Well, that's...
I'm sorry, Yukie-san...
If you really feel sorry for her,
how about you do something about this?
Wh-What do you mean?
O-Okay...
But in return, don't do anything to her anymore.
Masaki-san, I'm sorry.
Shizuka-san, have you ever performed fellatio?
I-I haven't.
I can't believe that! If I were your husband,
I'd shove my dick in your mouth as much as I could.
So why don't we let you try your first act of fellatio?
Yeah, that's right. Lick it gently.
Treat it like you're licking something delicate.
Now try licking it as if it were ice cream.
Okay then, let's have you swallow it now.
Lick the head with your tongue
and use your lips to suck on it.
Yeah, just like that! You have a talent for this!
Okay, let's have you suck on it even more.
Make sure you go past the head this time.
This is better than any onahole... I'm gonna cum!
Shizuka-san, raise your head up and stick out your tongue!
Shizuka-san, you've become
a fantastic pervert of a woman!
Keep your promise...
Don't worry, I will.
As long as you keep me company, that is.
Ryouto-san...
Did you do something perverted
to Shizuka-san again?
Is there a problem if I did?
Th-There is! She's your sister-in-law!
It's inevitable for a beautiful wife to end up like this.
She seemed like she was in a lot of pain.
She must think that this kind
of thing is definitely not right.
You have a point.
How about this? If you become my sexual partner,
I'll leave her alone.
But last time you said that was it!
If you don't want to do it then, that's me too.
Th-That's...
I'm good either way.
I have this magical picture, after all.
Take a look.
I'll... do it. I'll take care of your sexual desires.
Heh.
Come in, Yukie-san!
I've been waiting for you.
You're so erotic, Yukie-san.
Something weird is... down there!
No... I can't stand anymore!
Then how about we do this?
What?
No, not there!
You're getting so wet!
No!
If you're too loud, Shizuka-san might hear us.
Your pussy is really wrapping around me tightly!
No!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna spray it all inside you!
Wait! Wait! Wait...
Adultery?
I can't understand why people would marry
the one they love only to cheat on them.
Well, our wives are as beautiful as they
are faithful, so that would never happen to us.
You say that, but...
Your wives are already dome something
unspeakable with their brother-in-law.
– Here you go.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
editor: punk4real
quality control: fyurie