Apartment Complex
Guide Map
The apartment complex in the late afternoon...
That place is filled with housewives raring for sex.
Who would've thought that the housewives
here are in a sex industry?
There is a secret sex industry in this apartment complex.
While their husbands are away,
these wives can be used as outlets for lust.
That sense of immorality turns men on,
which then become customers.
You're the best, ma'am!
The Housewives at That Apartment Complex are...
Ano Danchi no Tsuma-tachi wa...
Volume 1
Part 1
Room #305: Takei Mitsuru (24 years old)
I love
S&M!
I'll be
waiting!
Gosh, don't take too much time. Hurry up!
He'll be back if we won't hurry!
Don't get impatient.
Something's hot...
Any men will get stiff after
seeing how you look like.
I-It's so hard!
You already got this big!
Here, how sensitive are you down here?
There's so much juice, it's so squishy!
I've been craving for this!
Hey, dear...
Today's a safe day for me...
I'm tired today.
It's been a year since we got married
and moved into this apartment.
As someone who has a strong sex drive,
my sex life with my seven years
older husband is already dead.
G-Gosh!
I was sexually frustrated on each passing day.
I then stumbled upon bondage
online which piqued my interest.
I got hooked into it.
Umm... Was it supposed to be this way?
But the throbbing of my body still won't go away.
My fellow housewives have been engaging
in this apartment complex prostitution.
Give this to me!
I want this!
If you're doing it, then hurry up!
He's gonna come home
if you'll keep dragging this out!
That's right, it'll be a huge trouble
if your husband sees me here.
If you get it then do it already!
You're so snappy.
We're doing it already... Right away...
Do you know what's poking you?
Yes, of course. I know what that is!
Just as I expected from you, Ma'am!
You're well-versed when it comes to what you love!
They're so soft!
I want to keep pushing mine against these!
Don't drag this out! Hurry...
Put it in already!
I'm gonna go crazy!
Well, this one down here is already
slushy and wants to be plugged up.
It keeps on leaking...
Then, I'll have to give it a proper response.
Here, I'm putting it in!
You gobbled it up nicely!
Mitsuru-chan, you're clamping at the tip
of your favorite thing inside!
That's such a nice reaction.
Well then, shall we have you
gobble it up deep inside!
What's up with that distressed moan?
Just a little more and
the whole thing will be inside!
Th-This is it...
This is what I've been longing for!
Here we go... It's all inside!
You're squeezing me tightly!
Is that how badly you wanted a cock?
Has your husband been neglecting you?
Stop pulling them!
It swooshed... Did you come just
from having it put inside you?
Here. swallow my cock
using your naughty pussy!
Come on, isn't a cock that isn't your
husband's making you happy?
You're devouring it with such an indecent sound!
You really are happy, aren't you?
Th-There's no way...
Aren't you getting drenched? Alright then...
How does it feel when I tease
your clit at the same time?
Doesn't it feel so good that you
couldn't answer me properly?
Your pussy keeps tightening around me!
It feels good!
I can't get enough of your pussy, Mitsuru-chan!
It's so deep!
I'll finish it off in your womb!
I'll be coming as well!
You're incredible... You female flesh sleeve!
Make sure to take my semen into your womb!
Don't!
I'm coming!
I'm coming so much!
Ejaculating in your womb is the best!
That's heavenly.
Coming deep inside the pussy of
a gorgeous housewife with no hesitation...
...felt so good!
It's foaming up...
Mitsuru-chan, your pussy is dripping with snot.
You're the best, Mitsuru-chan.
A-Aren't you satisfied now?
Coming as you pleased...
My bad, I ended up coming inside you.
It felt so good so I could help it.
Jeez, hurry up and remove my blindfold!
Yeah, yeah.
I shot so much semen!
Come on, use that cute mouth of yours
to clean and reinvigorate this.
Yes, that's it. Suck it clean using your mouth.
Mitsuru-chan, your blowjob feels good!
Are you always showing that octopus-like face
to your husband whenever
you suck him as well? Damn...
Huh? Are you angry, Mitsuru-chan?
I thought that it felt good for you, though...
Oh... That's it!
I am still very far from coming enough!
Come on, I want to go for
a second round already!
Me too, I want it!
I want this thing...
Mitsuru-chan, that feels good!
My balls are throbbing!
The sound you make while
sucking my cock is so lewd!
Mitsuru-chan, I want to shoot it out now.
Hey, let's do it one more time right now!
I want it from behind this time, please!
We spilled this much semen around.
Won't your husband notice the smell?
Take responsibility when that happens.
Mitsuru-chan, your pussy is so dripping wet!
It's so slippery because of my semen
earlier and it feels great!
You have such an indecent body.
Especially your breasts, you never
had a child yet but they're so huge!
That's a nice expression!
Look at your own face at the mirror!
That arousing expression is nice.
N-Not now!
Hey, come on! Shake your hips harder!
I love this... Your pussy tightens
up every time I spank you.
I'll shoot my sperm there again!
It's gonna get swollen, stop hitting me like that!
Take this, and this, and this!
No, I'm coming!
This plumpness... You sure have a tight squeeze.
This body of yours, its scent makes me horny!
Mitsuru-chan, you smell so nice!
D-Don't pull my hair!
I'll come just from your scent!
I never had it this hard before!
Don't undo my ponytail!
No way...
He's gonna be home!
The more we worry about your husband,
the more exciting it gets, isn't it?
I've decided! For your second creampie,
I'll shoot it out in the same way
as what your husband likes!
I can't take it anymore!
It's your fault, Mitsuru-chan.
It's because you have to mention
your husband on our climax.
Look, it went in so deep!
So remember me when you're
having sex with your husband.
I'll give you a creampie in missionary
position so that you'll remember me!
I'm sorry, so no more creampies!
This isn't the same as with my husband!
That's because I never came
this many times with him before!
You won't be able to forget about me, then.
I'm coming!
It feels good!
It's pouring in, it's pouring in!
It's Mitsuru-chan's second creampie!
This sensation is the best!
I have to make sure that
it'll reach up to your womb...
According to Mitsuru-chan,
her husband sits in his study room
and uses his computer every night.
Then, it'll be the same tonight.
I'm home!
Dinner is almost ready,
so how about having a bath first?
Hmm? Yeah...
Right there, over that chair!
Your wife and I were copulating on it earlier!
Can you smell it?
I'm talking about the stench of my semen.
Izumi•no Apartment Complex.
Part 2
Room #512: Asahina Aya (20 years old)
Baby!
Goo goo, goo goo ga ga!
Wow, they're huge!
Aya-chan, your tits are amazing!
Aren't they bigger than in the picture?
You're right, that's why
I want you to suck like a baby
Goo goo, goo goo...
and drain the milk out of them!
My chock-full tits are haggard!
Aya-chan!
Let's do lots of stuff that
I've been wanting to today!
Goo goo!
What's up with that face? So gross...
Next, maybe I should gobble both
your tits up at the same time.
Huh? No way...
Seriously?
Yeah...
I'm double sucking the tits!
You're sucking them at the same time!
I never had this done to me before!
Aya-chan, your breast milk is delicious!
You're drinking it all by yourself.
Aren't you such a voracious boy?
It should only be for my baby...
I envy your baby!
He gets to suck on mama's tits every day!
You're gulping it down all by yourself...
Jeez, you're a bad boy...
Mama already got wet...
I also happened to be chock-full of milk!
I'm ready now!
They already got this much swollen!
They're full of your milk!
They're the same as my tits.
We'll be needing this, then!
Huh?
Won't you let me have it bareback?
I'll add another 10,000 yen later!
Huh? But...
Hey...
I'll shoot it outside, so let's do it bareback!
Shush! Hey there!
Don't raise your voice, you'll wake him up!
Hey, mama! Pwetty pwease!
I want it bareback!
Shush! Be quiet!
Bareback, bareback!
Bareback!
Gosh, you'll wake him up...
The baby will wake up unless you say yes.
It can't be helped, alright then...
Pull it out when you're about to come!
O-Of course I will!
Alright!
No way, your dick feels incredible!
Aya-chan, bareback sex with you is the best!
You're getting aroused despite
having your child in here!
You really are such a pervert!
It's like mama is eating me down there.
Aren't you one as well, Aya-chan?
You bring men home,
and you let them fuck you.
You have to be quiet.
Having you sneak in to do this is dangerous.
Rwoger that!
Bare pussies sure are the best!
Do you do it with other
customers without a rubber?
I don't, this is the first time I got a customer.
I see, alright!
So, I'm the only one who got to have
a taste of you down there?
You are special.
Bareback sex sure is nice.
Then, I'll hollow your pussy out!
Yes, do me!
Do me more using your cock!
Aya-chan!
Th-This feels good!
Aya-chan, your pussy is incredible!
This is wild, Aya-chan!
My hips won't stop!
He woke up.
See, that's because you were too frisky!
Can I lull him for a moment?
No!
Let the child hear your womanly moans.
It might turn out to be a good lullaby.
Hey...
Aya-chan, I'm about to come. Can I?
I said that you can't!
Pull it out when you're about to come!
Since we already went this far, it'll be the same!
I told you that you can't!
No, don't!
I told you not to!
I came a lot inside you, Aya-chan.
It feels so damp!
Even though I said that you can't...
There's no way I can hold back
from a slutty woman like you.
Your hot stuff is dripping across my asshole.
There's so much flowing out.
My, my, Taku... I'm sorry!
Yes, here, here, here you go!
Jeez, you're just like Takumi.
You leaked so much.
I'll clean it up for you, okay?
Goo goo!
I'll have to clean it up.
You're saving up a lot inside here.
Maybe I should squeeze it
all out until there's nothing left...
You're swallowing it deep
with no hesitation! It's so deep!
Give me your sperm!
That's incredible, Aya-chan...
Your cheeks and tongue are
stroking it in your mouth!
What a lewd mother!
That feels good!
That feels good... Aya-chan, your
vacuum mouth feels crazy as hell!
That's it, Aya-chan!
Such a lovely blowjob face... Oh, goddammit!
It feels as good as penetrating a pussy!
My, my... Did it leak out again?
So, you came again...
Gosh, what a hopeless kid!
Huh?
We won't be disturbing Takumi's sleep here
and we'll be able to do it a lot.
It feels so good!
I'll give you plenty of my milk down here as well!
Even mothers want to get
some cocks as well, right?
Shoot it outside this time.
Didn't you promise me earlier?
You dare say that when
you're moaning in pleasure.
You know that you want
plenty of it inside you!
That's not true at all!
I-I'll become a father...
We're gonna make a sibling for Takumi-chan,
so I'm going to come a lot inside you!
I sad that you can't,
so don't come inside me anymore!
Here you go!
Scream from my cock!
Hey! Aren't you going to be my woman, Aya?
Don't you love my cock? Say it!
I will!
I will be your woman!
Alright! I-I'm gonna come, Aya...
Get knocked up, Aya!
Yes, thrust it lots and lots more into my womb!
It feels good!
Hey, Takumi-chan started crying again.
T-Takumi...
Your mama might have already
found a new papa for you.
After their customer leaves,
the women become normal wives.
I'm pretty sure that they're waiting
for their husband's return as usual.
The husbands come home
without any idea about
what happened in their units.
Another man used their wives in their
own love nests to satisfaction.
When I think about it that way,
some men sure are unfortunate.
Those women at the apartment complex
are more eagerly waiting for me than their husbands.
Alright then...
What kind of housewife should I embrace next?
Izumi•no Apartment Complex.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization