After returning home I visited the local
pool, which I hadn't done in a long time.
There, I ran into Kanako, a girl who was my childhood friend.
When I saw her go into the locker room, dressed in a swimsuit,
I couldn't help myself...
THAT SUMMER, WITH YOU AT THE POOL
Hm? Wait, who are you!?
I-I'm going to scream!
Huh? Wait...
Wh-what are you doing here?
Honestly... you would have been in a lot of
trouble if I'd been anyone else, you know.
You really startled me.
I haven't seen you in so long, how have you been?
You know, this is a staff-only locker room.
I work here part-time as a lifeguard.
We're about to close for the day,
so I'm the last one to use the locker room...
so nobody's going to walk in anytime soon.
Hey, tell me... why did you come in here?
I bet you had something naughty on your mind.
...it's okay.
I think nobody will come in here until closing time,
so feel free.
Why don't you take that off?
Just keep it down, or you might alert one of the security guards.
Just a little bit, okay?
It's a special treat.
You're pretty big...
...How's this?
Don't make any noise, now.
You want it faster?
Okay, I can do that.
It's okay, don't you worry.
You like it?
That's good...
Why don't we kick it up a notch?
Wow, look fit how big it's gotten.
Are you going to come?
It's okay, you can come in my mouth.
This is our little secret.
W-wait a minute, it-it's closing time now, so...
Ah, don't...
Don't look...
I can't keep standing.
Just promise me you'll tell nobody about this.
Be quiet, the guard will he here any minute now.
Aww... don't tease me.
No... I'm not wet...
It's so embarrassing doing this...
Ah, don't...
Aww... you're so dirty.
Hey, be gentle...
It's coming in... feels so big.
...It's okay.
This is a really... embarrassing position...
No... don't...
Don't too rough...
Be more gentle...
Don't look at me so much.
Oh my...
You can come as much as you want.
You can come inside of me...
Did you come like you wanted?
That's good... I'm glad.
Don't worry about today. Just forget what happened.
Let's work hard at college. It's okay, really.
"Okay, I'll forget about it.
Say, Kanako..."
Hmm?
"I've already forgotten what just happened, so...
How about we do it one more time, but as a couple?"
Huh?
Oh... you dummy.
You're such a perv...
...I love you.