Alright!
Yeah!
God, that hurts!
What's he doing?
How about practicing with my little sister?
Ami, got a minute?
Hmm?
I need a favor.
Mhmm.
Have sex with me.
Mhmm...
Sex?
Wait, onii-chan. What did you just sa...
Huh?
Thank you in advance!
Evil Spirit Begone!
That was self defense, so no complaining, okay?
O-Okay...
So you want to meet up with a girl you met online?
And just in case things get serious,
you want to practice with me first?
Yes, that's the gist of it.
Somebody said that he wanted to be a consultant
for idols, so I lent that somebody money.
I wonder what happened to it.
Success is built on one's failures.
Just how many times are you going
to dupe me until you're satisfied?
I'm not lying this time though!
I have proof!
What kind of proof?
She complimented me on my drawings!
Okay, onii-chan.
Ami!
Your brain's turned to mush, huh?
I'll fix it for you, so you stop having these delusions!
Now get the heck out of my room!
Die!
W-Wait!
I'm this old and I don't even have a girlfriend!
Isn't that embarrassing for you too?
Well, yeah, it is...
But either way, you don't ask your
sister to have sex with you.
What?
You're cute, so it's okay!
Wait a minute!
Please, I beg you! Let me have sex with you!
You're my last hope!
I'm telling you, no!
Come on, help your brother out!
Ami!
Okay then.
I'll let you do it with me.
Really?
But you have to pass a test first.
A test?
It's to see if you're qualified to have sex with me or not.
If you don't pass, give up.
Yes!
Hasn't it been five minutes already?
What are you talking about?
It's barely been two minutes.
You're so hard from your little sister's feet.
Look at all this pre-cum.
You really suck at this, don't you?
There's no way that a virgin like him
could survive for five minutes.
Looks like I'm going to win.
Come on, you gotta try harder if you wanna have sex.
I still can't believe you asked me,
your little sister, to have sex with you.
This is reality, not a game or anime.
Geez, you're dumb.
And then you say that you want to have
sex with one of your girl friends?
As if that'll ever happen.
Not to mention, you're a guy who
gets off from his sister's foot job.
Your breathing's getting kinda rough. You okay?
You at your limit.
Cum already.
Come on, don't hold back. Just cum!
Oh, you came.
Geez, you came too much.
Was my foot job really that good?
Three seconds.
Huh?
Five minutes, three seconds.
I just barely passed.
Oh, crap. I got so absorbed in doing
it that I completely forgot!
But he came so much, I bet he's done already.
Hey, w-wait...
Sex, sex, sex!
H-Hold on a second.
Don't rub your thing against me!
But I passed your test, didn't I?
Here I go, Ami!
Wait, calm down, onii-chan.
Evil Begone!
Sheesh, are you trying to rape me?
I'm sorry...
Um... are we really going to do it?
We're siblings, you know?
That's not a problem!
I want to do it with you, Ami.
I never thought you were this much of a virgin.
Thank you very much!
That wasn't even close to being a compliment.
Don't come crying to me if you regret this.
Okay, here you go.
It's what you've been waiting for... the
pussy of your little sister.
Now lick it until I tell you to stop.
Do it already.
Yeah.
So this is Ami's pussy.
It has such an erotic smell.
You just lost your cunnilingus virginity.
So how's it feel to be licking your little sister's pussy?
Does my pussy juice taste good?
Well, I have nothing to compare it to, but...
I like it.
Really?
Then you can lick it some more.
Th-There, that's...
You're getting so wet.
So you like my pussy juice?
You might have some talent for this.
Look. My entire pussy's really wet now, right?
Now that it's like this, we're good to go.
Be sure to remember this.
So that means I can put it in?
Hm, should I let you?
We've already come this far though.
Of course, I'm kidding.
Come here, onii-chan!
It's so soft!
It's coming so deep inside me!
You're sucking me in!
Wow!
My hips won't stop moving!
Wait, onii-chan.
You're being too wild!
Sex is really amazing, isn't it, Ami?
Do you even have enough stamina to keep this up?
Onii-chan, you like sex too much!
Why'd you cum?! You idiot!
Not to mention, you came inside of me!
S-Sorry...
I don't remember saying you could cum.
So, you can't listen to orders?
That's what you're mad about?
Shut up!
Cumming inside without warning is a really big problem.
Let's try this again.
This time, hold it in until I say you can cum.
You came twice already, but you're so big again!
It's so hard!
So being mounted by your little sister turns you on?
You're so cute, of course I am!
So you totally have a sister complex, don't you?
S-Sorry...
I don't really mind.
But you know, onii-chan...
Your dick is being tightly squeezed
by your cute little sister's pussy.
Ami!
You should be more grateful!
I can see everything like this.
You got even bigger inside me!
I'm gonna cum!
You can't! I won't forgive you if you cum before I do.
Y-You say that, but...
It's just for a little longer, so hold it in!
I'm cumming!
Good job holding it in, onii-chan.
Ami...
But, since you came before me, we're doing it again.
It's your duty as an older brother to
satisfy your little sister's pussy.
It's inside me!
Ami, your pussy's just sucking me in.
I feel like I'm already gonna cum!
Already?
Please let me cum!
I think I'm gonna cum soon,
so hold off until then, okay?
Okay, then hurry up and cum please!
You're being too rough!
Onii-chan, you're trying too hard!
Please, I'm begging you. Hurry up and cum!
I guess I have no choice.
I'll cum for you, I'll cum!
You can cum! You can cum, onii-chan!
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan's cum is flowing inside of me!
I was a bit forceful, but...
Looks like you were finally able to do it in the end.
I'll give you full marks for that one.
Time to go meet my girl!
Yeah!
Onii-chan, hold on.
You're going to meet her?
Yes...
You don't get it, do you?
I thought I was ready after yesterday's practice...
Don't be so naive!
You really think you're ready for the real
deal after just one day of practice?
You're kidding me!
I'm not letting you go meet up with her.
We'll start by reviewing yesterday's lessons.
I'll be more spartan about our practice this time,
so prepare yourself, onii-chan!
No!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
editor: bis
quality control: hyakupercent