Takita-san sure has some big assets,
if you know what I mean.
It's like her shirt could burst anytime.
I'd love to stick my head in there.
I wonder what her size is?
If she's an F, then you could totally do that.
Must be nice sitting so close to her.
You get to look all you want.
Well...
Hm? You don't seem too interested.
Do you... prefer fiat chests?
Well, yeah, but...
Mom
Wrehe are you?
Bookstore
Can you ger milk on your way home?
Okay. One carton?
Buy two if you can.
Doesn't it feel like her boobs are a bit off?
Okay, just the milk, right?
Just that for now.
There's a new issue of
Housewives Monthly though.
Really? Could you get it for me?
Could I buy some manga too?
What are you on about? Don't like the shape or something?
No no, that's not what I meant. It's just that her chest is...
Hey, you guys...
I don't mind you talking about this kind of thing,
but at least do it when the person you're
talking about isn't within earshot.
Sorry...
Also, Ookoshi...
You're coming with me for a bit.
Wha...
These boobs wanna be loved too!!
So... Takita-san?
What did you bring me all the way out here for?
What did you mean when you said
my chest seemed "a little off"?
Huh?
Uh, that's not something I'd say to the
person I was just talking about.
Plus, you might be misunderstanding.
I don't care. Spit it out.
This is purely just my opinion,
but I just got the feeling that you aren't
the "big boob" kind of person.
explanation
Those people tend to have a more defined curve in
their back, since their boobs weigh them down.
Yours isn't as pronounced as it should be though,
so I just thought it was a little weird.
I see...
How do you feel about... flat chested girls?
Huh?
So... you think they're unattractive?
Oh, not at all... I don't mind them.
I see. That's relieving.
Keep what we just talked about to yourself, okay?
In return, I'll let you touch my boobs as much as you want.
So you really...
Yeah, I'm wearing pads.
You don't have to go this far,
I'm not going to tell anyone.
It looked like you were going to.
I'll keep it a secret, I promise.
I won't be at ease if there's no incentive
for you to keep it a secret.
You also said you didn't mind flat-chested girls right?
So then, stop complaining and grope me already!
I-I'll do it, don't cry.
I never thought it'd turn out like this...
You can turn around now.
This is what they really look like.
Flat as a pancake, right?
Your boobs are... bigger than I thought.
Stop staring and just touch them already!
S-Sorry.
They're really squishy, even though they're not that big.
W-Well, we've got a deal then.
Her nipples are so firm.
They're getting really hard.
It's my first time, so be gentle!
What?
I definitely thought you've done this before.
If that was true, then I would've
already been outed, wouldn't I!
You have a point.
Pads sound like a real pain, though.
It is, but it's too late to stop now.
My personality isn't great, so if I don't have big
boobs then I have nothing left that's appealing.
Guys were instantly treating me different
when I started wearing pads.
Male
That just made me want to keep wearing them.
Y-You got something to say?
I was just thinking, you're surprisingly cute.
Wha...
D-Don't just blurt out random stuff like that!
What's that? Did he get hard because of me?
Prove it.
If you weren't just lying, prove it to me with your body.
What?
Huh? Wai... What!?
Shut up!
If you actually think I'm attractive,
then cumming with my boobs
shouldn't be a problem, right?
What!?
With her boobs? No way, a boob job?
Well? Are my boobs making you feel good?
The feeling of my dick hitting her breast bone,
while being squeezed between those tits...
H-Hey, say something.
It feels so good, I'm in shock.
What about you?
I don't feel anything.
Try rubbing it against your nipples, then.
L-Like this?
Hold it tightly... I'm going to move now.
What's going on? It's digging into my nipple!
That face you're makings is really cute!
I'm going to cum soon!
You're going to cum? You're really going to cum?
T-This is your cum? There's so much!
How was it?
Even without pads, I still think you're attractive.
Do you believe me now?
Y-Yeah, I guess.
It's fine if I have a small chest.
One month later...
Ookoshi.
I kept my mouth shut, but...
We still met up so she could keep her "incentive" relevant.
Day after day after day...
And the day after that day...
And today too.
Takita-san, I'm cumming!
Takita-san, what's the matter?
I'm definitely not imagining it.
Each time I do this to keep him
quiet, my boobs gets bigger.
I don't really understand why,
but this is a once in a lifetime chance for a flat-chested girl.
I've decided that from now on, I'm going to do
this at least twice a session to keep you quiet.
What?
Be sure to make time, and keep yourself healthy.
That's what she said, but after that day,
we haven't done anything at all.
I should be happy that she trusts me now, but I'm also sad
that we won't be spending as much time together anymore.
Ookoshi?
Takita-san...
Eh?
What? What's going on?!
You said that you don't mind flat chested
girls, but what about big breasted ones?
Huh?
Are these...!?
Yeah, I'm not wearing pads anymore.
They got used to being touched, so they got bigger.
Now, they're bigger than when you
first put your dick between them.
Ah, so that's why you didn't need me
to keep my mouth shut anymore...
That's not it!
I thought, now that my chest is all big,
maybe you wouldn't like me anymore.
Just thinking about that made me really scared!
That's why I didn't want to show you!
S-So?
I remember you saying that you had no
interest in big boobs... was that true?
Takita-san?
Well, I do prefer them on the smaller side,
but, look...
This is my answer.
I got like this just from looking at your chest,
so I don't think you have anything
to worry about, okay?
No, I don't believe you.
Huh?
I'm saying,
prove it by cumming with my tits!
All of it went in!
Her tits feel so warm!
D-Does it feel good?
It feels amazing!
His dick is making my chest feel
so hot... I can't think straight!
I'm going to cum!
Keep thrusting and cum inside my tits!
He's cumming. He's cumming so much!
So he's fine with me, even as I am now.
I might've let out a little too much proof.
Takita-san!?
What's gotten into you?
That was only the first time, right?
How about you cum with this next?
Wanna try it?
Is this really okay?
I want to feel you properly, so don't be too rough.
Takita-san...
I thought it'd hurt more than this,
so I think I'll be fine.
You can move if you want to.
W-Wait a second.
Ookoshi?
I feel like I'm gonna cum, so I'm trying to hold it in!
But you just put it in...
How should I say this...
Sticking my dick inside the girl I
like is really pushing my limits!
L-Like!?
You're tightening up!
He came. He came so much inside me!
Takita-san... Was it really okay for me to cum inside?
Don't stop yet.
You can do me however you like,
just do what you did again!
Y-You're not going to cum yet?
I think I'm going to cum before you!
Hurry up...
Do you like me cumming inside?
When I think about being impregnated by
the guy I like, my mind goes blank and...
I-It just feels so good!
Hurry, give me all your cum!
I'm going to go harder!
Every time you ram your dick inside
me, my pussy starts tingling!
Please! Give me your cum!
I want to feel it spill into me!
You're cumming!
Your cum's inside me!
Well, you satisfied?
No!
O-One more time.
You wanna do it again?
I want to cum while looking at your face.
It's inside me!
You're not going to be rough?
I want to get a really good look at your face when you cum.
Y-You pervert.
Not my nipples...
Even if your chest has gotten bigger,
your nipples haven't changed.
Y-You don't need to say that.
Don't just tease me, do me harder!
I just want to keep looking at the face of the girl I like.
I l-like you too, but move a little more!
Stir up my insides!
My insides are getting so hot
from being used by your dick!
It's throbbing. You're going to cum, aren't you?
Cum inside me! Cum inside me with everything you've got!
I'm cumming!
There's so much of his cum flowing in!
They're beautiful, no matter
how much you look.
She's like the goddess of tits.
Oh yeah, when you said you had a weird feeling
about her chest, what'd you mean?
Oh, that?
Upon closer inspection, I realized
that I was just imagining things.
At least try to wait until after school.
Just what the hell happened here?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hor
editor: biskoi | punk4real