Alright!
Aw yeah!
Ow, ow, ow, that hurts!
What's he up to again?
Ami, do you have a moment?
I want to ask you something.
Have sex with me.
Wait... sex?
Onii-chan, what did you just?
Huh?
Launching... please!
Evil Entity Exterminator!
I acted on self-defense, got any problem with that?
N-No ma'am.
Oh, so you're meeting with a girl you met in chat IRL?
And you want to practice, just in
case that moment comes along?
It's as you said.
I lent you money because you asked
me to be your idol consultant.
They say failure teaches success.
Just how.
Many times.
Do I have to be fooled by your tricks.
Before you're satisfied?
I'm not lying this time!
I'm sure this will work!
Oh, what do you mean, then?
If you compliment what I'm trying to do.
I get it already,
onii-chan.
Ami!
You've completely one nuts, I see.
Don't worry, I'll fix you so that those weird ideas no longer exist!
Get out of my room already!
Die.
W-Wait!
This brother of yours has yet to have a girlfriend all his life!
Don't you feel ashamed of that too?!
Well... yeah, but,
but that's not something you should ask your sister.
What now?
You're cute so it'd be okay!
Hey wait!
I'm begging you!
Please have sex with me!
You're the only one I can count on!
You know I can't agree to that.
Save your brother from peril!
Ami!
Alright.
I can let you do it.
Really?
However,
you have to pass the test I'm about to give right now.
A test?
A test on whether you have the right
to have sex with me or not.
You'll have to give it up if you fail.
Okay!
I-It's been up for five minutes already.
What are you saying?
It's been just two minutes.
Getting it all stiff with your sister's feet,
and it's also dripping wet with your cowper juices.
You really are indeed sloppy.
Onii-chan's a virgin so he can't possibly last for five minutes.
It's an instant victory.
There now, if you don't do better you won't be able to have sex.
Anyway, asking your sister to have sex, huh.
We're not in a game or in an anime, you know.
Are you an idiot?
And you plan to have sex with a girl with
that non-existent charm of yours?
Absolutely impossible.
Besides, you're a pervert who gets
aroused with your sister's footjob.
You're breathing heavily.
Are you okay?
At your limit already?
About to squirt it out now?
Now, now, don't hold it in, just let it all out.
There, it came out.
Jeez, you came too much.
So my footjob felt that good, huh.
Three seconds.
Huh?
Five minutes and three seconds.
Just barely, but I made it!
Oh crap, I got so carried away that I forgot.
But, he'll probably be satisfied once I expose "that"... right?
Eh?!
Hey, w-wait.
Wait, just wait.
Don't just rub it there!
I passed so it's okay, right?
Here I go, Ami!
Onii-chan, please just calm down.
Wicked Buster
For goodness sake.
Are you serious about raping your own sister?
I'm sorry.
Well.
Are you really going to do it?
I'm your sister, you know.
I'm completely good to go!
In fact,
I want to do it with you.
I never imagined your lameness as a virgin was this bad.
Thank you very much!
That wasn't a compliment at all.
I don't care if you regret this later, okay?
Here you go.
Here's your sister's pussy that you've been so badly waiting for.
Now, I want you to lick it first until I say it's okay.
Do it now.
O-Okay.
So this is Ami's pussy.
It reeks of an erotic scent.
He's got my first cunnilingus!
Hey, how does it feel to lick your sister's pussy?
Do my love juices taste good?
I don't have anything for reference,
but I don't hate this at all.
Then lick it more if you want.
Th-That's!
It's starting to overflow.
So you're starting to like my love juices.
Onii-chan, I think you may just know how to do this already.
See? It's already very wet inside, right?
It means it's done preparing itself.
I want you to properly remember this.
So... I can put it in already?!
I wonder about that.
N-No way... but we're at this point already.
I was just kidding.
Come, onii-chan.
It feels so tender!
It's going inside me!
It's trying to suck me in.
Amazing!
My hips won't stop moving!
Hey, onii-chan, you're going way ahead.
So sex is...
is this amazing, Ami.
Will you really be able to keep up for long with that pace?
O-Onii-chan,
you're getting into this too much!
What the hell are you cumming for, you idiot!
Huh?
And you even came inside me!
Oh, I'm... sorry.
I never said you could cum.
You dunce of a brother.
That's what you're mad at?
Shut up!
Cumming inside so suddenly like that.
It's going to be a big problem outside our practice session.
We'll have to do it again.
This time, you have to hold it in until I say you can, okay?
You already came twice,
and yet it's still getting big.
It's really hard.
So you're getting aroused while I take
the lead in a cowgirl position.
I can't help it, because you're just too cute!
You're a total siscon.
I-I'm sorry.
Not that I hate it, though.
But onii-chan.
This guy's dear sister is letting his perverted
virgin thing rub inside her.
Ami!
I want you to savor every second of this!
Wow.
I can see everything.
It's bulging even bigger inside me.
I'm about to cum.
No, I won't forgive you if you cum first before me!
E-Even if you say that!
Just a bit more so hold on.
I'm cumming!
You held it in pretty good, onii-chan.
Ami.
But, you came first, so we'll do it again.
As my brother's dick, its duty is to satisfy her sister's pussy.
That's just how it is.
It's gone in.
Your pussy is sucking me so hard, I'm about to cum already.
Cumming already?
Please let me cum!
I think I'm about to go in a little bit,
so do your best to hold on until then.
Then please cum already!
Wait, you're too intense!
Onii-chan, you're pushing too hard.
Please, please cum now!
I guess I can't help it.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum now!
Cum, you can cum now!
Onii-chan!
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan's cum is flowing in me.
That was a bit forced,
but you actually did it properly until the end this time.
I'll give a star for your efforts, onii-chan.
Offline meeting, offline meeting!
Alright!
Just a sec, onii-chan.
Are you really going to that offline meeting?
Yes.
Jeez, you really don't understand a thing, onii-chan.
Huh?
I think I'm already well prepared after that practice yesterday.
Pathetic!
You're too pathetic to think that you're already
fully prepared with just that one time.
N-No way.
You're not attending.
I'll get back at you after what you did yesterday first.
We're gonna have an all-out super hard training session today,
so prepare yourself, onii-chan.
No!!