It's really amazing.
Takita's "things".
Her blouse looks like it's about to pop.
I want to sink my head into it.
I wonder what cup she is.
It'd probably be around F, I think.
You guys sure are lucky to have seats close to hers.
You get to ogle at it all the time, right?
Huh? You don't seem that interested.
Are you more interested in washboard chests?
Well, that could be part of the reason.
But those breasts, don't you feel something off about them?
What are you talking about?
So you really do love small breasts?
No, I don't mean it that way.
Takita-san's breasts, you see...
Hey, you boys over there.
I don't really mind talking about those topics,
but at least talk about it when the person isn't nearby.
I'm sorry.
And Okoshi,
come with me for a bit.
Umm.
Takita-san?
What are we doing here?
What did you mean earlier by "something off" with me?
W-Well, it's not really something I
should say to the person herself.
Also, I might just be mistaken.
Just cut the crap,
and say it right now.
This is just my personal opinion,
but you don't seem to have the build
of a typical big-breasted girl.
Illustration
Big-breasted women often compensate the weight
of their breasts with an angular standing position,
but in your case, you still stand quite upright.
That's why thought you weren't the typical big-breasted girl.
I see.
You.
What do you think of small-breasted girls?
So they're not that attractive after all?
Well, I don't really think that.
At least I don't hate them.
Is that so.
That's good, then.
What I said earlier... keep it a secret between us.
In exchange,
I'll let you touch me however you want.
So that means.
Yup.
I'm wearing pads.
You don't have to do this, I won't tell anyone.
You look like you're about to spit it our already.
I'll definitely keep is a secret.
I can't rest easy without having something that
would really make you keep your word.
Besides, you said you don't hate small-breasted
girls earlier, right?
So, don't just mutter nonsense,
and start touching my breasts already!
Okay, I'll do it, just please don't cry.
I never thought it would turn out like this.
You can turn this way now.
This is how my breasts really are.
It's totally a washboard, right?
These are... her actual breasts.
So you've been using pads.
Don't just ogle there, touch them!
S-Sorry!
Whoa, they're small, but very fender.
N-Now our deal's set.
Her nipples feel firm, and are actually kinda stiff.
It's having a hard on.
It's my first time, so please be gentle with me.
But I thought you were already quite experienced in this.
I think you can already tell just by touching me, you know.
I see.
It seems that pads are quite tough to use.
They're troublesome to use, but I
can't just stop using them, either.
My personality's kind of uptight about it.
Don't you think my charm as a woman would
be gone if my breasts aren't big enough?
Besides, men look at me differently whenever I wear them.
Which caused me to stuff in quite more, though.
What?
I just found you surprisingly cute.
D-Don't just blabber out things!
What's this?
He's getting a boner, because of me?
Prove it.
Prove to me that you're not just all words, using your body.
What?!
Wait... hey!
Quiet!
If you really think I'm still attractive, you
can at least cum on my breasts, right?
On her breasts?
A tit fuck?!
Well, how's this?
Do my breasts feel good?
That slight warmth, and that soft sensation just makes me.
Hey, why don't you say something?
It feels too good, and I'm still totally surprised.
How about you, Takita-san?
Me? I'm just fine.
Then, why don't you put the tip on your nipples?
Would this be fine?
Just hold onto it firmly
I'm going to move it, okay?
What's this? He's moving it all around.
It feels like my nipples are being drilled!
You look very cute when you're aroused, Takita-san.
Okay, I'm about to cum.
Are you cumming?
You're really about to cum?
S-So this is your cum.
Lots is dripping out.
Well?
You're just as attractive without pads.
Do you believe me now?
W-Well.
So it's alright even if I'm a small-breasted girl.
One month later.
Okoshi.
I've kept my word,
but she now keeps me "silent" about it...
more frequently than ever.
Next day,
the day after that,
and even the day after that.
Even now, I.
Takita-san, I'm cumming.
Takita-san, what's wrong?
I'm really not imagining it.
Whenever I "silence" him, my breasts
become more molded to his dick.
I'm not sure how it worked,
but this is my big chance as a small-breasted woman.
Okoshi,
I'm going to "silence" you twice a day starting tomorrow.
Prepare your time and body for it, okay?
She may have said that,
but I actually wasn't "silenced" anymore after that.
The feeling of longing I had for her far surpassed
any relief she thought I had for not doing it.
Okoshi.
Takita-san.
What?!
What's happening?!
You said you don't hate small-breasted girls,
but what do you think about big-breasted ones?
Th-This is!
Yeah.
I'm not using them anymore.
Seems they grew bigger,
since the time you touched them.
They're now even bigger than when I'm using pads.
I see. No wonder you don't need to "silence" me anymore.
That's not what I meant!
I was afraid that,
you might not find me attractive anymore
now that my breasts have grown like this.
That made me feel so scared.
And I never got the chance to show them to you.
So, what do you think?
You said you're not interested in big breasts, right?
Is that true?
Takita-san?
Well, it's true that I prefer smaller sizes,
but look.
This is my answer.
When I saw your breasts, it just automatically became like this.
You don't need to worry about it at all.
Okay?
No, I still can't believe it.
That's why,
I need you to cum on my breasts and prove it.
It's all the way inside.
Her breasts are totally squeezing me now.
How is it? Does it feel good?
This is so bad.
The part where I'm rubbing him feels hot,
and it's starting to make me feel weird.
I'm about to cum.
Cum it all on my breasts.
It's squirting out. He's cumming lots.
Okoshi's still fine even with how I am now.
I might have proven it too much, I think.
Takita-san?!
What's wrong all of a sudden?
We've just done it once, right?
Can you do the next round here?
Do you want to try it?
Are you really okay with this?
Stop teasing me.
I want to take you all in.
Takita-san.
I thought it'd be more painful.
But, I think I'm perfectly fine.
Hey, you can move too if you want.
J-Just wait.
Okoshi?
I'm about to cum already, so I'm trying to hold it in.
You've just put it in, though.
How should I say this.
When I start to think that I'm actually
having sex with the girl I like,
I just can't hold it in.
Like?!
W-Whoa, it's squeezing me really tight!
It's pumping out.
You're cumming so much inside.
Takita-san.
Did you cum when I came inside you?
Please, don't stop now.
Rub me lots inside.
So please, do it again!
A-Are you cumming yet?
I think I'm going to cum before you even cum inside me.
Please, cum already.
You have a thing for cumming inside now?
When I start to think that I'm actually
being impregnated by the boy I like,
my mind becomes completely blank.
This strange sensation just wells up inside me!
Please, pump it into me already.
I'm going to cum lots!
It feels so tingly whenever you fuck me deeply like that.
Give it to me, please!
Cum inside me.
I want to feel it!
Your cum's pumping inside me!
Your... cum.
Well? Satisfied already?
N-No, not yet.
O-One more.
We're still doing it?
This time, I want to cum while looking at your face.
It's in.
You're not going to move?
I want to look at your aroused face very carefully.
P-Pervert.
No, not my nipples!
Your nippe's sensitivity is still the same
even after your breasts became big.
Y-You don't have to tell me that!
Stop teasing me, and just keep on fucking me.
I want to look at the face of the girl I like some more.
Me too!
But you need to move more!
Stir my insides more.
My insides feel hot as you rub it in!
It's bulging.
You're about to cum, right?
Please, cum.
Cum lots inside me!
I'm cumming!
Lots of his cum, is pumping inside me.
It's really amazing no matter how many times I look at it.
She's a breast goddess.
Oh yeah,
what were you talking about when you said
you felt something off about her breasts?
Oh, that.
After checking it out, I realized that it was just my mistake.
Jeez.
You need to wait until classes are over, you know.
What in the world just happened?