I'm Aoi Mizuno.
School Girl Idol CG Anime
Chocolat
AOI MIZUNO
Alright, why don't you give us your introduction.
Ok, I'm Aoi Mizuno. I'm a school girl and my sign is Virgo.
You look really nervous, you feeling ok?
What do you do in your spare time?
I like reading.
What sort of books?
Hmm... like suspense ones, I guess.
Is that popular with girls your age?
All my friends are reading them!
Gotcha!
So what about any special talents?!
I practice ballet.
How old were you when you started?
About four or so?
Wow! So do you have plans
to be a ballet dancer in the future?
No... Not really...
Haha, I see.
Then what is your dream?
I want to be a great mom someday.
I'm sure you will be.
So, how are you feeling about the shoot today?
It's my first time, so I'm a little nervous...
but I'll try and hang in there until we finish.
Great, well let's get started then.
I'll do my best!
Are you feeling tense anywhere?
My shoulders... I guess?
Heh, been hitting the books a lot lately?
Well then.
We've got a personal massager here,
why don't I try and relax you?
Are you feeling any tension here?
Does it tickle?
If you've been studying too hard,
a lower back massage will give you some relief!
It's very important to take care of the groin area
since it supports your body.
Why don't you get down on your hands and knees?
Щёкотно...
Now, slowly put your hand down.
Don't worry, all the other girls are doing it too.
Ok now, slowly spread your legs.
Try spreading a bit wider.
Let's give the massager from before another go!
N-No...!! St... ooop!!
Now now Aoi, you can do this.
Ah... N-Noo...
I'm gonna take the bandages off now, ok?
Don't worry, it's gonna be all ok.
You can show me without feeling embarrassed.
Ahh... Please st... opp!
Oh, Aoi, you're so pretty.
Pretty on the outside and the inside of your body...
You even feel it around your anus,
what a perverted girl you are.
Why don't you go ahead and practice licking it?
See, it's not so bad.
I can tell you're starting to enjoy yourself now.
Aoi, tell me where it feels good.
Tell me that your pussy feels good...
My... pussy... ahh...
I-It... feels... so g-good...
Ohh... st... oopp...
You're feeling good now aren't you?
Then I'm going to increase the stimulation.
Aoi, I'm inside you now...
Look at it!
О, нет!
Ahh... I'm gonna come... AOI!!
Erghh...!
Well well well...
You like it in the ass?
You really are a dirty, dirty girl.
Oh, now you're thrusting all by yourself.
You naughy girl, cumming first on your own like that.
I can tell you're feeling it now, Aoi.
You're getting so tight!
Oh, haha, you aren't even listening to me anymore.
Ahhh! I'm gonna cum in your ass!
Directer
KOB
Cast
Yuri Ayase
CGI Works
KOB