My name is Harase Yuri.
I'm a University student living outside Tokyo.
I'm living in an apartment
with a 60,000 yen rent,
and the money I get from my parents is very little.
For now I'll work in any job field to
make money for my apartment,
but, this is the first time I've worked so much in the Service Industry,
and wearing the many beautiful costumes there,
work life isn't boring at all.
I'm going to work hard today too!
Arubaito' Shiyo!
~Onee-san is a Cleaner~
Onii-san! Over here.
Hey, Onii-san. Good Morning!
You're healthy as always.
Onii-san is cute~
I'm getting a little hot out here,
with this it'll be easier to move.
Onii-san, the sun is shining and it's a beautiful day.
It feels good!
Onii-san, come over here.
Hurry up.
It's big!
Your penis is getting bigger...
No, I want to touch it.
Doing this kind of perverted thing up here,
I can't stop this thrill.
Amazing, It keeps throbbing continuously.
Please..please stroke it harder!
Please..please keep it up!
Want it.
I want it!
Come..please come quickly!
Look's delicious,
I'm melting down there.
The tip of your penis is letting out a lot of fluid.
Your penis is still throbbing.
How is it? Do you feel good?
Good..It feels good...
My body is moving by itself.
It feels too good, I'm going to cum.
Give it to me! Let that big penis shoot all over my pussy.
Amazing..It's amazing!
Cumming.. I think I'm gonna cum!
Good...
Let's cum together!
Not yet, don't cum yet!
Coming..I'm cumming!
Give it to me..I want it!
It feels good...
Onii-san, you're the best.
I'm sorry, I'm here to wok as a window cleaner,
but I let the window get dirty instead.
Eh, you want me to clean the window from the inside of the building?
That's good for me, how 'bout we change the place and
I'll give you some after service too?
But we're doing it after I clean this up, right?
Good day, my name is Kagurazaka Fuminaka who's been
introduced to you as your maid.
Good morning, Master.
How about some wake up coffee?
I live alone as part-time worker.
Cosplay is one of my hobbies and I've been scouted to be a maid.
It hurts...
Sometimes I'm a little careless,
today I'll work harder on my job!
Please, have a taste of it.
Did it suit your taste?
Thank you very much, Master.
Arubaito Shiyo'!
~Onee-san is a Service Maid~
Ple..Please stop it, Master!
Please...
No..No, you can't!
It..It hurts!!
Wha..What are you doing?
S..Stop it.
Please don't spread peanut butter on that place.
Master...
My body feels strange!
But..It feels so good...
Because it felt so good, the pot is boiling over.
Ma..Master, that place is already wet.
Please don't do something like that.
Master...
No~!
Master, please pull it out.
It's inside.
Master's big penis is inside of me.
It's hitting deep inside of me,
hitting inside of my womb.
Master's penis is inside of my pussy...
Master, please do it harder!
This pose is...
No, I can't hold it anymore!
Please let it out inside of my perverted pussy!
Master, I'm so sorry.
Before you had your meal, I'm the first one
to get a full stomach.
The next time will be in bed?
It's..embarrassing..Master.
Open it..Open it with my fingers?
I understand.
My embarrassing place can be seen all the way inside, Master.
Please..don't do something like that.
No..No, you can't!
No..No, you can't use vegetables for something like that...
Please pull it out, Master!
Good..good..It's good!
It's hitting inside of me!
It..It's good...
Master's penis really feels good!
My hips are moving by themselves.
I want..I want more!
Master's penis keeps thrusting inside of me.
Master, It's amazing!
It's all inside of me, Master.
No, I can't..can't hold it...!
Cumming..I'm gonna cum!
It's coming out...
Master's semen is continuously flowing inside of me!!
If you pull it right now, It would come out...
You were being rough, Master.
I'll prepare some food for you.
You want some dessert?
Then, I want Master's big and hard
penis inside of my mouth.
My name is Hoshikiri Momoka.
I'm a 20 year old University student.
I usually serious at studying in class,
but I'm getting tired from working at night.
Yes, I'm sorry!
Arubaito Shiyo'!
~Onee-san is a Tutor~
Even though I don't look like it, my job is a home tutor.
It's true!
Did you finish it?
You're doing it very fast.
Then, let me see your work.
What is it? You're face is getting red.
Did you get fever or something?
It seems you don't have a fever.
It's strange enough...
No way!
You're thinking perverted things, right?
It can't be helped. Let's wrap up the study for today.
From here on it's adult studies.
Well, open your eyes.
How is it? Is it beautiful?
This is your first time looking at women breast, isn't it?
Try touching it.
It's tender and feels good, right?
It hurts!
Don't do it so hard, okay.
It's soft so be gentle with it.
Your penis is getting so hard.
Then, let's begin already.
You're cute.
It looks delicious.
It looks like an adult penis.
It smells good.
Your men's fragrance is flowing out.
You're gonna cum?
It's too much too early.
It's quite a load.
Even tough you couldn't hold it,
you pass my test.
Your penis is still hard, right?
Let's continue it in the bed.
Then, I'll put it inside.
In here, It's the place that men feel the best.
It's good!
It's good! It's big and hard...
It's keep getting bigger inside my pussy!
Good...
Your penis is so good!
It's deep, deep inside of me.
It's hitting my womb!
I'm feeling it.
Your penis feels much too good!
Don't move it that hard so suddenly!
My women's juice is pouring out.
Good..you're doing it well,
that's the way it is.
It's so good, I'm feeling you move
inside of me.
Good! Keep thrusting inside my pussy!
Together..Let's cum together, okay.
It's making lewd sounds there.
I'm gonna go crazy!
Coming..I'm cumming!!
Today's adult study is finished.
If you get a good grade on the final test,
I'll teach you more good things.