Brought 2U By JPz Records
Listen to my story.
This may be our last chance.
Damn it!
Can't sleep?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Everyone's troubled because of what happened.
Don't...
Don't blame yourself.
We're finally here in Zanarkand.
We've been through a lot.
To be honest...
To be honest, it was a wonderful journey with everyone.
Wakka, Lulu...
Kimahri, Rikku...
Sir Auron...
...and you.
I am truly glad that I had met everyone.
Truly.
I hope we find the Final Aeon.
But you know, sometimes I think about you.
I wonder if I did the right thing hiring you as my guardian.
What's that suppose to mean!?
Because of you...
I kind of want to quit my pilgrimage.
It's like my resolve is fading away.
That's right.
Because of you, I can't decide what to do.
Wait a sec! You serious!?
Yuna...
We have to say goodbye.
We only met each other, just to say goodbye.
If I'd known it was going to be this hard...
I would rather never have met you at all!
Don't... Don't worry!
I'll find a way, you'll see!
Yuna, I won't let you die!
I swear!
There's nothing you can do!
There's nothing... anyone can do...
Don't-! Don't say things like that!
C'mon, don't tell me this is goodbye...
There's still hope!
If you of all people in Spira were to give up hope,
then what am I supposed to do!?
I always tried my best to keep smiling until the end.
Look at me... I'm so helpless...
Hey, kiss me.
What?
Like you did in Lake Macalania...
Just like back then...
Kiss me...
Okay, but it won't be a goodbye kiss.
Okay.
Wha-!
What are you doing?
Please, eyes on me.
I want you to look at me.
Yu-Yuna...
This is me, the real Yuna.
Yeah.
You're really beautiful.
Well, this... is me...
Yeah.
You're so warm.
Don't forget about me, okay?
Yuna.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Come on...
It's my turn.
Yuna... I'm about to...
You sure about this?
Yes.
I love you, Yuna.
I love you!
I love you, too!
I'm... about to come!
I can feel it inside of my body!
It's so deep inside me!
It's happening again!
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
Wait, Yuna!
Shhhh... Stay still...
I want to make sure I'll live on inside of you...
By filling... myself... with you...
Oh, no!
I'm going to come again!
You wanna come again?
Come on...
You want me to fill up your body more, right?
Yes...
Fill me up more!
Yuna, I can't hold it anymore.
Come inside of me!
Brought 2U By JPz Records.