It's summer vacation.
Our parents are on an overseas trip,
and I'm currently living with my beloved sister, Hana.
She took them off while sleeping, huh.
I've already told her many times that
she shouldn't go naked like this.
Of course, it was a moral decision.
But more than that, my nether regions are.
Hey Hana.
You're going to catch a cold like that.
"Drink cum, and you'll get smarter."
She also believed that he that I made up on the spot.
Yes, my beloved sister is,
an extremely idiotic idiot.
So much that you'll wonder how she'll live in society this way.
I, who am now completely horny over her naked body.
On that day, finally.
I love kitties too!
Mitsui Hana.
I'm going to lick lick you all over as a kitty! Chapter
She's still not awake yet with all of this fondling.
In that case.
Hana, I'm sorry.
Onii-chan can't stop anymore.
You won't let go?
Hana!
Onii-chan?
Good morning, Hana.
Why is a dick going in and out inside me?
It feels good for me too.
Then it's no problem, right?
If there's no problem.
But, onii-chan there's.
What's wrong, Hana?
Well, I'm...
I'm going to cum!
Alright.
I'm going to give you your wake up milk now.
Milk.
I want to drink milk.
Onii-chan.
What is it, Hana?
Good morning.
I'm not actually an idiot!
Well, onii-chan?
I think I'm doing even better than before.
We probably need to work on this more.
I guess I should have expected this.
If girls really get smarter if they drink cum,
I bet all siblings would already be doing it.
That's weird.
I'm drinking that much milk from onii-chan every day.
W-Well, in order for it to be effective,
you still need to wait some more.
Really?
Then I'm going to drink lots and lots more of onii-chan's milk!
I may be the worst.
So cold!
I want to drink more!
It's hot today, so it's better to stay hydrated.
Here you go.
Yay!
I really can't resist her demands.
Though, I never thought it'd turn out like that.
Onii-chan.
It's an emergency.
Oh, that's quite wordy.
Have you gotten smarter now?
I'm going to pee.
Oh crap.
I let her drink too much.
Oh yeah.
There's a toilet at the end of this road.
It's going to leak if I don't walk gently.
For real?!
Summer Event
This is the culprit, huh.
I can't hold it anymore.
I might leak while still waiting.
Park Guide
BBQ Plaza
Toilet
Management Office
No Entry
Can't be helped!
Oof.
This isn't the toilet.
Because it's an emergency.
You need to do a standing leak.
Standing leak?
Now, while there's still no one around.
Okay.
Hey, wait!
Hana!
Sit down, sit down!
But you said standing leak, right?
That's when it's a guy!
Crap, too late.
What a relief!
Okay, raise your legs a bit more.
Okay!
Onii-chan, it's leaking out already.
It just keeps leaking as I wipe.
That's not pee.
Looks like we have to let it all leak out.
Please don't rub it like that.
Don't rub it in and out!
I can't?
Do you really want me to stop?
No!
I want my pussy to feel even better!
Alright.
I'm going to make you feel better.
It feels good.
Onii-chan.
I can't wait for it anymore.
I want a dick.
Your dick is in.
It's going in deep inside me from behind.
Getting fucked from behind while standing.
It's called the standing back position.
Standing back?
Amazing. Your dick's hitting me very deeply.
Yeah.
Your womb and my dick are kissing each other.
My womb... it feels good.
It feels so good.
Kiss my womb some more with your dick!
Alright, here I go.
What is this?
It's all tingly where your dick is pushing in me.
Oh no, oh no!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum while being kissed in the womb!
If I kiss you even harder,
I wonder how you'll react?
Oh wow!
Onii-chan, this is amazing!
It's really, really deep!
Womb kissing is amazing!
Onii-chan,
I love this.
It also feels so good for me.
Hana, I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Onii-chan!
So hot.
Your hot stuff is pumping into me.
I wasn't able to drink it again.
I have to drink it to become smarter.
Well,
then why don't we do it like this?
Here we go.
So warm.
It really feels like milk!
I love this kind of hot milk too.
Thanks for the milk!
We're home!
Now Hana, wear this.
Onii-chan, will I get smarter with this?
Yup!
Cats are very smart, you know.
They hunt rats, are very refined,
and they even know how to poop properly!
Wow, that's amazing!
Then if I can imitate cats, I can become smarter, right?
Yup, that's right!
But, onii-chan,
this thing in my butt feels really tingly.
Because you're now a cat,
you need to act like one!
Okay, I'll do my best!
Okay, first groom your fur.
You have to keep your body clean.
Like this?
Oh! That's nice.
You're now very cat-like.
Onii-chan,
it feels better and better for me as I lick it.
My mind is starting to wander.
My body also feels hot.
Next, we'll train you to hunt down rats.
Okay!
Here I go, Mr. Rat!
Mr. Rat is very fast.
Now do you understand how great cats are?
With that you'll never.
Crap!
Now I'm closer to being a cat than ever!
Here's my licky licky, Mr. Rat!
Good, just keep that up.
Mr. Rat is in big trouble!
Prepare yourself, Mr. Rat!
I did it!
Hana, you can't cough out the milk like that.
Looks like you need more training.
Now, this is the inal step for your mind
and soul to become that of a cat!
The real tail...
is this!
Your dick is pushing inside!
Your raw tail is now inside my butt!
You can't lose to this dick tail.
Cats should be able to control their tails freely!
It's moving!
This tail is rubbing hard inside my butt!
No, stop.
It feels so good, that my mind is starting go blank.
You'll be a cat, Hana!
You can never be smarter if you don't!
If this dick keeps on pushing hard into me like this.
I-I'm about to cum.
If you can't use the toilet properly,
you'll never become a cat!
Hana, I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Cats are amazing.
Hana, covered in white fluid,
and with those big breasts.
She's no longer a cat, but more like...
A cow.
But, I can't tell her that, though.