The public pool was crowded, but at least
we can play as much as we want here.
Yay! It's like our own private pool!
Whee!
Yep. Nobody really knows about this place, so it's empty.
It's so cold!
Splash!
Let's splash each other!
You really did it this time, Hana!
The water feels good!
Take that!
Oh no, Hana got you all wet, onii-chan.
Yeah... now we're both wet.
Onii-chan, are Hana's boobs making you excited?
Your dick is getting bigger!
Yeah... I might go crazy if I don't let my milk out soon.
Hana, your boobs are the best.
Hana wants to drink milk!
Oh, onii-chan's dick.
It's so wet, it just slid right in.
It feels good doing it in water this cold.
Your dick feels so hot!
Hana loves your dick, onii-chan. She loves it so much!
If you're too loud, someone might come to check.
But, but, your dick and Hana's boobs feel so good!
I guess I have no choice then.
I'll have to give you your milk soon!
Hana...
Y-You can't squeeze them like that.
You're going to make Hana lose her mind!
Hana's going to cum from having
your dick pounding her insides!
No! Cumming! Cumming, cumming! I'm cumming!
Hey, onii-chan, Hana wants to drink your
milk again when we go home. Is that okay?
Of course it is, Hana. I'll let you drink lots.
Okay!
About that time when the only thing that could
make my stupid sister smart was my XX.
Full blown (All out) cosplay!! Mitsui Hana. <3
The one she loves the most is her onii-chan. <3 Arc
Oh, they're so cute!
Hey, onii-chan, can we get one?
I don't think we can,
but you're cuter than them anyway, Hana.
You mean it? Hana's cute?
Okay, let's go.
O-Okay.
Onii-chan, onii-chan, Hana wants to eat this!
Didn't you just have ice cream? You'll upset your stomach.
O-Okay...
So many cute dresses!
Hey, onii-chan, do you think Hana would look good in this?
Yeah, of course. You look good in anything.
You're just so cute, after all!
Okay, it's time to go.
Cosplay
Parade
Changing Room
You did well today, Hana!
You kept it inside for an entire day.
Hana's a good girl?
Okay, here's your reward.
Yay, it's your dick!
All of it just went in! Why?
You got turned on from people looking at you.
You're really dirty, Hana.
No...
Onii-chan, your dick feels so good!
Didn't I tell you not to be so loud?
No! Onii-chan's dick is going to make Hana cum!
I'm gonna cum soon, Hana. Open your mouth.
Hana wants to cum with onii-chan's dick inside her.
Hana feels really lonely when you take out your dick.
Is it bad? Don't take it out!
Okay, then... I'm going to cum inside you, Hana.
Cum! Shoot your milk into Hana's pussy,
Onii-chan! Cum! Cum!! Hana's...
Your hot, hot cum is going
to shoot out from your hard cock!
Hana's cumming again!
Hana promises she'll drink your cum next time, onii-chan.
Oh crap! The parade's over!
Hana!
Yeah... Wait, onii-chan,
this is the women's changing room.
Snacks! Snacks! Onii-chan,
what kind of snacks are we having today?
Yay! Strawberries! Hana loves strawberries!
Yep, they were on sale. Let's dig in!
Thank you!
It's so yummy! Yum Yum!
They taste okay by themselves,
but Hana likes putting milk on them.
It'd be great if your milk was this sweet, onii-chan.
Oh, yeah, well...
Hana just had a great idea!
If Hana puts your cum on the strawberries,
Hana bets it would taste good!
Yeah, but...
It's complete!
Time to try it out.
It's so yummy, onii-chan!
Really? That's good, then.
Do you want to try it too, onii-chan? Open wide!
If Hana puts this on your dick, it's the best of both worlds!
It's so good!
Hana loves how yummy it is!
Hana could lick this delicious cock forever!
You can cum whenever you want, onii-chan.
These two drinks mixing together tastes so good!
Hana'll share some with you, onii-chan!
About that time when the only thing that could
make my stupid sister smart was my XX.
My days living with Hana went by in a flash.
Okay, it's all clear, Hana.
Hey, hey, onii-chan, will Hana really
not be yelled at for being naked?
It'll be fine as long as nobody sees you.
You've been such a good girl recently,
so I made today an exception.
Yay! The breeziness feels good!
Hana's going home tomorrow.
I have one more reward for you. Close your eyes.
Okay.
Okay, you can open your eyes.
Hm?
Wow, this is so pretty!
What's this for, onii-chan?
It's just a cheap rental dress.
Remember how you were staring at them back at the store?
Yeah... Onii-chan?
Hm?
Um... Hana's pussy has been
throbbing a lot, and it won't stop.
Make Hana your bride tonight, onii-chan.
Of course I will, Hana.
Hana's gonna... Hana's gonna...
You're even better than usual, onii-chan.
You're so amazing! You're so amazing, onii-chan!
You're moving so fast!
Hana!
You came so much, but your dick is still so hard, onii-chan!
Onii-chan... Hana loves you!
– Hana loves you! Hana loves you so much!
– Hana!
One day, Hana will...
She'll become someone else's...
Hana won't go home!
Hana wants to stay with onii-chan forever!
Will you let Hana stay by your side, onii-chan?
Hana!
Hana! Hana!
Onii-chan! Onii-chan!!
It's so hot! Hana's stomach is on fire!
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan? What's the matter?
Did Hana do something bad?
And so, once summer was over, Hana went back home.
Huh? What's going on?
Hi, onii-chan!
Ta-da! Look! This is the uniform
Hana will be wearing next month!
Wait, that means...
Yep, Hana finally learned how to write her own name!
Wow! You're such a good girl, Hana!
– Hana can even get dressed, use the remote, and lock the door!
– She was admitted to the school just because she's able to write her own name...
– That really says something about the kind of school she'll go to,
– Hana can even get dressed, use the remote, and lock the door!
– but Hana took the first step towards her future by herself!
– Mom and Dad praised Hana for getting so smart!
This is all thanks to your milk, onii-chan!
Maybe in a little while,
Hana will be able to ride the train too!
Hm?
Mom and Dad said they're going on another overseas trip!
Again?! Without even saying anything to me?!
What kind of parents are you?!
So, they said, please watch over Hana while they're gone!
Hana wants to drink your milk again, onii-chan!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
encoder: bakaproxy
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч