Why is onii-chan's dick getting big?
One hour earlier
Such a lonely university life.
I, Mitsui Yuuichi,
am currently enrolled in my first choice university,
and am living alone.
I don't have a girlfriend, and my close friends don't live close by.
So I'm stuck here, doing absolutely
nothing during summer break.
Hana.
Hove her more than anything else in the world.
On top of that.
I'm growing conscious of her as a girl now.
The moment I realized this,
I chose a university that was at least two hours
away by plane from my hometown,
in order to abandon these feelings.
Everything I did was for the sake
of putting distance between us.
I'm not sure if it had the opposite effect,
but I now cherish and long for her even more.
She's really cute!
She's a true angel!
Why the hell am I having these thoughts about my sister?
Eh? What?
Onii-chan!
I-Is that you, Hana?
Yup!
Original Animation Disc.
The case of making my stupid sister smart with only my XXX!
The milk-loving Mitsui Hana -Chapter!
I never imagined,
that you'd become such a beauty in the short time I was away.
Really?
I'm a beauty?
Indeed... you really did grow up.
I love milk!
I drink lots everyday!
Looks bouncy and soft, right?
Oh yeah, I have a message from Mom and Dad.
Oh, a message?
Mom and Dad will be traveling overseas this summer break.
They told me to learn as much as possible
while staying at your place.
Which reminds me, how exactly did you get here?
I never knew you could ride buses and trains by yourself.
Well, Mom and Dad dropped me off right in front of your place.
What?!
They came that close without even saying a single word to me?!
Do they hate me or something?
I remember now.
My beloved sister is unfortunately,
a grand, stupid idiot.
The type that forgets something after three steps.
The type that can't even read Kanji,
and anything that has more than three
buttons is beyond her understanding.
She got overly spoiled by my parents
who really wanted a daughter,
and was even doted on too an extreme by yours truly.
The end result is her stupidity.
You'll instantly doubt her functionality in society.
For me to take her in with me is.
This is bad.
Can I hold on to my sanity the entire summer with her here?
The entire two years that I worked hard on.
It's so hot!
W-Wait, why?
I'm always naked at home, you know.
What did you say?!
She never had that habit when I was there!
I'm so envi...
Come on, take off your clothes, onii-chan!
Huh?
Why is onii-chan's dick getting big?
That's.
Well.
That's because I want you to drink my milk.
Wow!
So you can produce milk with your dick, onii-chan?
Are you going to let me drink it?
Yay!
I can drink as much milk as I want!
– I want to drink lots of milk from my dear onii-chan!
– I never thought shed be this stupid.
Huh? Nothing's coming out.
It's not going to come out instantly.
My milk is kind of special, you know.
Special?
Onii-chan's milk has the potential to make people smarter!
Really? Amazing!
I'm really going to drink lots of your milk to get smarter!
I think I may actually be the stupid one after all.
The case of making my stupid sister smart with only my XXX!
You need to make it feel really good
for the milk to start coming out.
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Dick.
Alright, try moving your hand up and down while holding it.
So, like this?
Your dick is starting to bulge and get stiffer!
It's now preparing itself to secrete the milk,
because you're doing it well.
I'm kind of tired already, though.
Then, try caressing it using your mouth this time.
But, your dick will be gone if I eat it.
You'll only have to lick it, like eating ice cream.
Ice cream!
I love ice cream too!
Here I go!
My mouth got completely filled with your dick.
Onii-chan, it looks like it feels great for you.
Are you about to give me your milk now?
Yeah, just continue sucking and licking it.
Also, don't forget to move your mouth up and down.
Like this?
There, you're doing good.
Your tip is starting to taste weird.
That's proof that it's feeling great.
Those are cowper secretions, which usually come
out when a dick is aroused before it finally cums.
Cowper?
I don't understand well.
Just try to remember it, okay?
Once you get smarter, you'll get to drink it even faster.
Okay, I'll do my best!
I want to drink lots.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Is it about to come out?
I'm just glad that you came.
I'm cumming.
Hana, try to keep it in.
Coming... out?
Is the milk about to come out?
It is, it's about to.
So drink lots of it.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Keep it in, Hana.
You can't become a smart girl if you don't drink it.
I-I'm sorry, you can spit it out if you want to.
I drank it!
Good girl, Hana!
You did well.
I did well!
Your milk kinda tastes bitter, though.
It's totally different from a cow's milk.
I'll bring lots of milk for you,
so let's just live together here for the time being, okay?
Okay! Thanks, onii-chan!
I'll be in your care from today.
And that was the start of my summer break together with Hana.
The case of making my stupid sister smart with only my XXX!
I never thought...
she'd keep on being naked everyday.
Hana, bath's ready, so come on and take one.
Okay!
This is bad.
If I continue to look at her naked body like that,
I'll soon lose to my desires and.
No, no!
I'm her dear benevolent brother.
I first need to teach her to stop being naked!
Onii-chan.
Oh, what is it?
If it's too hot, I'll just.
Well.
I want to... like before.
I want us to bathe together like before.
Ninety three.
Ninety four.
Ninety five.
Ninety six.
Bathing with onii-chan, yay!
Ninety seven.
Ninety eight.
Ninety nine.
One hundred!
A-Alright, I'm going to wash your body now.
Okay!
Whoa, they're so soft!
Amazing!
Hana's breasts.
It feels ticklish, onii-chan.
My breasts are big, right?
Do you prefer big ones?
That's my private part.
It's my first time touching it.
S-So this is Hana's.
A girl's!
Onii-chan, I'm starting to feel weird.
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
Did it hurt?
No, that's not it.
When you touch me there, my mind gets all fuzzy.
Your part down there, your pussy, is a
special part of the body like my dick.
Pus... sy?
My pussy feels happy when it's touched?
Yup. That's great.
Did you become smarter already?
Maybe it's because of your milk?
It feels good.
My breasts and pussy feel good when
you keep touching them, onii-chan.
I'm starting to pee.
It's okay, that's not actually pee.
Your dick is getting big.
Can I drink some milk again?
Oh, okay.
There's another way to make it release milk.
Can you do it?
Yup! I'll do my best to get smarter!
Stop.
She hasn't even masturbated yet, so
fucking her is out of the question.
Oh, then.
Your dick is twitching.
It feels like it's so happy between my breasts.
Alright, try moving your breasts up and down.
Okay!
Give me lots of milk, okay, Mr. Dick?
Yes, just keep that up.
Just press your breasts against it.
Okay.
Oh yeah, Hana.
Try sucking my dick as you do that.
Like this?
This is kinda difficult.
Yes.
You're getting better and better at this, Hana.
Really?
Oh, that feels good.
Hana, you're making such an erotic expression.
Hana, just a bit more... just a bit more vigorously.
Hana, it's about to come out.
It's coming out.
Onii-chan, your milk is really great.
Lots of it came out again.
How does it taste?
Did you not like it?
It's really quite bitter and thick,
but it's so I can become smarter!
I'll do my best, and drink more!
Onii-chan's milk is good and all,
but I love cow's milk better than anything!
Damn, it's still Hana's favorite!
The way the milk came out earlier
made my breasts feel great too.
I'm going to rub my nipples like this.
Wait, stop!
You can't do that in front of other people!
Eh? But it feels good.
This is bad.
Even if she only does that at home, if she
starts playing with herself like that.
Dad will surely kill me.
If you can restrain yourself, I'll teach you
something that feels even better.
Really?
Okay, I'll stop it then.
I want to have sex with her,
but the fact that I completely lied about
her getting smarter with my cum
is something that I really need to correct someday.