It`s so hot!
Just a few more steps until I reach A/C heaven.
No, stay strong, Kouta!
You`re going to win over the temptation
of the convenience store today!
Wait, what?!
I... I`ve never seen such a perfectly tanned slut before!
I mean, wait, she`s in my class. Shiina Chieri.
Her eroticism is off the charts!
Because of what I`m doing right now, I
might be super horny tomorrow, but
At this point, it`s okay for me to keep looking, isn`t it?
Oh crap, our eyes met.
I mean, I know that girls always notice a guy
staring at them with lewd eyes, but...
Wait, are you kidding? You actually looked again?!
You`re gonna get arrested like that.
That`d suck since I came all the way
out here to ask a favor from you.
H-Huh, you need something from me?
You do?
Yeah, I do.
So, the thing is...
She`s the target of every boy`s fantasies in the entire
school and is incredibly popular on top of that.
You`re telling me that the Shiina Chieri
wants something from me?!
I`m glad I`ve always acted like a nice guy.
What should I do if it`s a dirty request?
What if she comes into my room dressed
up like a demon or something?
Geez, Kou-chin, are you listening to me at all?
Oh, sorry. What`d you say again?
I just told you!
Could you...
Help me study?
Hentai Haven Presents
Dumb, but when it comes to sucking dicks,
she`s very talented: Chii-chan
Chii-chan, can you even study?
Muroto Kouta
I did it!
Good job, Shiina-san.
Call me, Chii-chan.
I forgot to ask, but why did you even
agree to help me, Kou-chin?
W-Well...
I just thought that you`re really thinking about
your future seriously and I was impressed.
Oh, nothing else?
Well yeah, being alone together...
Might have made me think that some dirty
things could happen between us...
Yeah, but I have a boyfriend, so I`d never have sex with you.
Huh?! You`re kidding me!
No fricking way...
My best chance to lose my virginity`s gone...
But I do need to do something to thank
you for helping me study, Kou-chin.
S-Something?
You helped me study, so...
As thanks, I`ll stay here and...
I`ll help your dick out for you.
I might be dumb, but when it comes
to sucking dicks, I`m very talented.
No matter how much I lick it, my mouth keeps
getting loads of your thick pre-cum inside it.
It has such a manly smell.
It might make me forget everything we went over today.
Chii-chan, if anything, don`t forget that.
You see, I...
Like seeing the faces of satisfaction people
make when they`re in my mouth-pussy.
Maybe I should start getting serious.
Get serious?
Wow, your dick is so big, it`s filling my mouth up!
You don`t have to hold it in. Shoot
it out whenever you want, okay?
I`ll make sure to empty your balls out, so just keep
shooting everything into my mouth-pussy.
This technique-- I can`t--
Give me your sperm.
Cum inside me!
Chii-chan, you`re too erotic!
Well, this erotic girl is looking forward to working
with you tomorrow as well, Kou-chin.
And as our summer vacation together continued
things between me and her escalated.
Chii-chan, you`ll really show me your boobs?!
Of course!
Look. These are the breasts of your classmate.
Th-These are the legendary boobs of my classmate!
Wh-What is this magic?
Oh, right.
Chii-chan?
Found it!
Today`s tit fuck day!
What a beautiful day.
Uh, okay, Kou-chin, lube up my boobs with the lotion.
Okay.
Oh my god.
You should see the way you`re looking at me. So dirty.
More importantly though, I`ve seen a lot of dicks,
but yours is the most impressive, Kou-chin!
Y-You`re not just saying that?
Yeah, I`m being real.
Your dick is even more amazing than my boyfriend`s.
Alright, I think it`s about time you stuck
your dick through my boobs.
Look, I`m massaging your dick with my boobs.
I`m sandwiching your dick in between them.
Can you hear the dirty sounds I`m making?
Rubbing your wild dick with my boobs...
It`s making me so hot!
Usually, if I lick it all over and rub it with my boobs
like this, most dicks just cum almost immediately.
Y-Yeah, I can see why.
You`re pretty good at holding on, but
are you close to giving in yet?
Chii-chan, I`m gonna--
Okay then, let me swallow the semen you`ve
been trying so hard to keep inside you.
That was so... delicious.
Chii-chan, we shouldn`t... do this here...
Just this one time, please? I`ve always wanted to do this
while everyone around me is hard at work, studying.
Before anyone comes, I`ll...
Make sure to go at full speed to get your dick to cum!
There`s so much pre-cum coming out of your
dick, I feel like I`m gonna get pregnant!
Cum! I`ll drink it all so that it doesn`t get on my uniform.
Chii-chan, I`m cumming!
We`re doing this every day, but there`s still so much!
Kou-chin! Kou-chin!
What do you think? Does this turn you on?
Chii-chan...
You`re a frickin` genius!
This smell, thy dick must be hardened, no?
You really are a dick expert.
So then you know what I want next, don`t you?
Come on, Kou-chin, shove it into my mouth.
H-Here I go.
This hole in the wall idea is the best, Chii-chan!
This feels so good, I don`t care
about anything else anymore!
This is too good! I can`t hold on anymore!
Hey... Do I really have to show you?
Yeah, please.
It`s really embarrassing though.
Hurry up and show me, Chii-chan!
Kou-chin, you big meanie!
Shiina Chieri
I was really trying to get within the top thirty on this test...
I think that might have been aiming a little too high.
But I think you did really well.
I`ve been next to you all the way, watching
over you, so you can take my word for it.
If you keep this up, getting to the top
thirty by next year will be easy.
So don`t worry, I`ll help you make your dream come true.
I guarantee it.
Kou-chin!
You`re not playing fair! You keep saying all these
nice things and making my heart race!
I can`t really do anything about that...
I`ll listen to any favor you want from
me as thanks for encouraging me!
Huh? Really?
Th-Then...
Kou-chin, this is pretty embarrassing...
Why do you have something like this on you, Chii-chan?
I can`t help it. Every time I suck your dick, I get so wet.
You`re such a dirty girl.
We can`t have sex, so don`t take it off, okay?
I`m really going to put it between your cheeks.
Okay, just like that. Rub my butt with your dick.
My butt`s getting soaked from all your pre-cum!
My butt`s holding your dick so tight-- it`s
like my ass has become an onahole!
We re really having sex like this!
Let`s just have real sex! I wanna fuck your pussy so bad!
No, we can`t!
I`ll be cheating on my boyfriend if we do that! We can`t!
Shit! Shit!
My pussy`s twitching with joy because
of your jealousy, Kou-chin!
Chii-chan, I think it`s coming off.
No, you`re kidding!
No, it can`t be off-- No, stop!
Now we`re basically doing it raw!
I`m so close to cheating on him like
this! No! This isn`t right, but...
Chii-chan, I`m about to cum!
Me too! I`m gonna cum too, so cum!
Cover my ass with your semen, Kou-chin!
I`m cumming! I`m cumming with semen
that`s shooting against my pussy!
Geez, Kou-chin, you`re so... perverted.
Whew, that was fun.
But seriously,
I can`t believe my boyfriend stood up
his beautiful girlfriend for work
even though she got all dressed up in a yukata for him.
Oh, so your boyfriend`s an adult?
Yeah, he is. Real trash, isn`t he?
But hey, thanks to you, I had a really fun summer.
The end of my summer was marked by her lonely smile.
HENTAIHAVEN.ORG
TRANSLATOR: HIKARUCON
TIMING: HYAKUPERCENT
TYPESETTING: HYAKUPERCENT
EDITOR: HENTAISENPAI
ENCODER: BAKAPROXY
QUALITY CONTROL: HENTAISENPAI
СОФТСАБ: TFLOATER