The local pool was already jam-packed.
At least here you can play all you want.
Yay!
Good for us to go here!
Here I go!
It's a great place that few know about.
Nobody's gonna come around.
So cold!
There!
Let's get wet together.
You did it, huh.
The water feels great.
Here's more!
That surprised me.
Onii-chan, you're drenched now too.
Both of us, you mean.
Onii-chan, aroused by my boobs already?
Your dick is already big.
Yeah. It'll probably go crazy if you don't extract its milk soon.
Her breasts sure are the best.
I want to drink milk too!
Your dick.
It slipped in very easily.
We're in cold water and yet,
it's so hot.
I love your dick, onii-chan.
I love it so much!
Somebody might come if you moan loudly like that.
But, but!
My nipples and your dick just feel so good.
It can't be helped, then.
Then I'll just have to make you drink my milk sooner.
Hana.
No, don't squeeze my breasts!
Stop... or I'll go crazy.
I'm going to cum while being fucked hard.
I can't hold back anymore.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
Hey, onii-chan.
I want to drink more after we go home.
Can't I have more of your milk?
Of course you can, Hana.
You're going to drink lots.
Okay.
Cosplay Galore! Mitsui Hana.
The one I love the most is onii-chan! Chapter
So cute!
Hey, hey, onii-chan, I wanna buy one!
Well, pets aren't actually allowed in my place.
Besides, you're much cuter than them.
Really?
Am I cute?
Alright, let's get a move on.
O-Okay.
Onii-chan, I want to eat this!
You just ate ice cream earlier, you know.
You're going get a tummy ache with that.
There's lots of cute clothes!
Hey, hey, onii-chan, will these fit me?
Yup. Anything's sure to be a perfect fit,
because you're very cute.
Alright, it's about time.
Good girl.
You really worked hard the entire day
I'm a good girl?
Okay, here's a reward.
Yay, it's your dick!
It went all the way inside!
Why?
You were aroused while everybody watched.
You sure are a pervert, Hana.
Your dick feels very good, onii-chan.
I already said it before, right?
That you shouldn't moan too loudly.
Your dick is so big that it's piercing all the way to the back!
I'm about to cum, Hana.
Ready your mouth.
Just wait!
I want to cum while your dick is still inside me.
It's kind of hard to drink it when you pull it out suddenly.
So please?
Please don't pull it out.
Alright.
I'm going to cum inside, then.
Please cum.
Cum it all, cum all of your milk inside me, onii-chan!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Your very hot milk is about to flow into me from your stiff dick!
I'm still cumming.
I'm sorry, onii-chan.
I'm going to drink it properly next time.
Oh crap!
The parade's almost over!
Hana!
Oh, by the way, onii-chan, this is the girls changing room.
Snacks, snacks.
Onii-chan, what's our snack for today?
Strawberries!
I love strawberries!
I bought them for a bargain.
Now, let's chow down.
Digging in!
So good.
Very sweet.
Eating it normally already tastes good,
but I like to add condiments when possible.
If your milk was this sweet it would have been really perfect.
W-Well, that's.
I've got an idea!
I bet these strawberries would taste better
if I dip them in your cum, onii-chan.
Wait, that doesn't mean you should.
Done!
Digging in!
It tastes good, onii-chan!
Is that so?
G-Good then.
Wanna have some too?
Here, say "ah".
If I do this, then I'll have twice the thing that I love!
So good.
I love delicious stuff like this.
I can lick such a tasty dick all day.
You can squirt all of your milk now.
The mixed taste of all this milk is great!
I'll give you some too, onii-chan.
Our days living together passed by so quickly.
Alright, it's good to go, Hana.
Hey, hey, onii-chan.
No one will scold me even if I'm naked?
It's okay as long as nobody sees you.
You worked quite hard, so this night's special for you.
Yay!
It feels so cool and nice!
Hana is going home tomorrow.
I have one more treat for you.
Close your eyes.
Alright, you can open them now, Hana.
Wow, it looks so beautiful!
What's up with this, onii-chan?
It's from a cheap rental shop, though
I kind of... looked at you that way, you see.
Onii-chan.
My pussy, it's twitching so hard I can't stop it.
Make me
your bride tonight.
Of course, Hana.
Oh no, not there.
Onii-chan, you're amazing right now.
You're, you're really amazing tonight, onii-chan.
So fast!
Hana!
We did it so many times already, bit it's still so stiff.
Onii-chan.
I love you.
– I love you very much!
– Hana.
Hana will someday,
find someone.,
I can't go home.
I want to be with you forever.
Will you be with me forever, onii-chan?
Hana!
Hana, Hana!
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
It's so hot.
My insides feel like they're going to melt.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan?
What's wrong? Did I do something bad?
And as the summer vacation bid goodbye, so did Hana.
This is?
Hello, onii-chan!
Ta-da!
Look, look!
I'll be regularly wearing this uniform starting next month.
Eh? Then that means!
Yup! I was able to properly write my name.
I see. That's my girl!
– I now regularly wear my clothes,
– You're admitted just by writing your name, huh.
– I can also properly use the remote,
– and I can even keep the door locked now!
– Well, that just says a lot about the school's level,
but even so,
she did it on her own.
She took her own single step to the future.
So, I think I'll be able to ride a train on my own pretty soon!
Because you see,
our parents said that they're about to go overseas again!
They went overseas again without even telling me?!
What kind of parents are they?
So during that time,
please take care of me!
I really want to drink some of onii-chan's milk again.