It's summer vacation,
and our parents are on vacation overseas,
so I started living with my sister, Hana.
Did she strip white she was asleep?
I keep telling her that she can't be naked all the time.
For the sake of morals,
and also for the sake of my mental health...
Hey, Hana?
You'll catch a cold if you sleep like that.
"If you drink semen, you'll become smarter..."
The lie I told her in the heat of
the moment was accepted so easily.
Yep, that's right.
My beloved little sister is an incurable idiot!
She's too dumb to be
a functioning member of society.
On that day, I couldn't contain my lust
for Hana's body, and crossed the line.
About that time when the only thing that could
make my stupid sister smart was my XX
I love kitties too!! Mitsui Hana
~ I'm gonna lick that kitty all over! ~ Arc
As if I could just sit back like this.
Well then, let's...
Hana, I'm sorry!
Your brother can't stop himself!
You're not getting away.
Hana!
O-Onii-chan?
Good morning, Hana.
Why is Hana being rubbed by a dick?
It feels good, though...
Then I guess there's no problem...
and if there's no problem, then...
But onii-chan, there is a problem!
What is it, Hana?
Um... Hana's gonna cum!
Okay then, let me give you your morning milk!
Yay, milk! Hana wants to drink milk!
Onii-chan...
What is it, Hana?
Good morning.
Hana actually isn't really an idiot!
Good kid's summer break homework
Onii-chan, how does it look?
Hana thinks she did even better than usual!
I think you might need to try a bit harder.
Huh?!
Well, yeah if drinking cum made you smart,
everyone with siblings would be doing this.
That's weird, Hana's drinking
so much of your semen every day.
It'll take a little longer for
the effects from the milk to kick in.
Oh, really? Then Hana'll drink more
and more of your milk, onii-chan!
Could I actually be the scummiest guy on the planet?
It's so cold!
Onii-chan, Hana wants to drink more!
Yep, it's hot today, so you need to
make sure you're hydrated. Here you go.
Yay!
I'm really weak to Hana's begging.
I never thought that would happen though...
Onii-chan...
We have an emergency.
Oh, you learned a really big word!
Maybe you're getting smarter.
Hana needs to pee.
Crap, I let her drink too much.
Oh, right, there's a public restroom just up ahead.
If Hana doesn't move slowly,
Hana's going to have an accident.
Are you freakin' kidding me?!
Summer Event
So that's the reason?
Hana's at her limit!
Hana's gonna have an accident if she waits any longer!
Park directions
Barbecue Area
Toilets
Manager's office
Off limits
There's no other choice!
This isn't a toilet.
That's because this is an emergency.
We have no other option but to stand outside and pee.
Stand outside and pee?
Come on, before anyone comes here.
Yeah!
Wai...
Hana! Sit down! Sit!
But onii-chan, you said to, stand outside and pee.
That's if you're a guy!
I guess it's too late now.
Ah, Hana feels so much better!
Okay, spread your legs apart a little more.
Okay!
O-Onii-chan, the pee's already gone.
But the more I rub, the more comes out.
But that's not pee, that's...
We have to make sure that everything comes out.
Don't move your finger like that!
Something else is gonna come out! No!
So I should just stop right now?
No! Hana wants to feel more from her pussy!
Then I'll do just that!
It feels good!
Onii-chan...
Hana can't hold on anymore,
Hana wants your dick.
Your dick is inside!
Your dick is going so deep inside Hana's pussy.
Having sex from behind while standing up
like this is called "standing doggy style".
"Standing doggy style?"
It's so good! Your dick is rubbing so deep inside me!
Yeah, that's right. Onii-chan's dick
and Hana's womb are kissing each other.
The kissing feels so good! It feels so good!
Kiss Hana's womb with your dick more!
Okay, here I go!
What's going on? Every spot your dick
hits is making Hana's pussy tingly!
No! No! Hana's gonna cum! Hana's gonna cum
with her womb! She's definitely gonna cum!
I wonder what will happen if
I kiss you even harder than this?
Wow, onii-chan, you're so amazing!
This feels so good!
I love it when you kiss Hana's womb!
No... Any more and Hana will...
Me too! It feels so good, I... Hana, I'm gonna cum!
Hana's gonna cum too!
Onii-chan!
Oh my god! Hana's pussy is being flooded with cum!
Hana couldn't drink your milk again.
If Hana doesn't drink your milk,
she won't become smart.
Then how about we do this?
Here I go.
It's so warm.
It's like hot milk!
Hana likes hot milk too!
Thank you for the milk!
I'm home. Okay, Hana, wear this.
Onii-chan, will this make Hana smarter?
Yeah, cats are really smart, you know?
They can take care of mice,
and even groom themselves.
They know how to go to the
bathroom by themselves, too!
Wow, cats are so cool!
So if Hana copies what cats do,
she'll become smart too, right?
Yeah, exactly!
But onii-chan, this thing in Hana's butt feels weird.
система Станиславского, и всё такое...
You have that because you're a cat.
You need to become the cat!
Okay! Hana will do her best!
First up is cleaning yourself!
You have to make sure
that every part of you is clean.
Like this?
Yeah, just like that! That's just like a cat.
The more Hana does this,
the more she feels funny, onii-chan.
It feels so good that
Hana's head is becoming fuzzy.
Hana's body is also getting hot.
Next is mouse catching practice.
Okay!
Here I go, Mr. Mouse!
Mr. Mouse is really fast.
Do you understand how amazing I am?
At your level, you won't...
Crap!
Hana is becoming even more like a cat!
Hana's gonna get you good, Mr. Mouse!
That's good! Keep it up!
You've got Mr. Mouse on the ropes!
Prepare yourself Mr. Mouse!
Hana did it!
You can't be spitting out the milk like that, Hana.
Looks like you still need some training.
Okay then, next you're going to become
a cat in both mind and body.
The real tail is right here!
Your dick is going inside Hana!
Onii-chan's raw dick is inside Hana's butt!
You can't lose to the dick tail.
Cats know how to move their tails however they want!
It's moving!
The tail's moving around inside Hana!
It feels so good! It feels so good that
it's going to turn Hana into it's idiot!
You need to become the cat, Hana!
If you don't, you won't become a smart girl!
If the dick tail keeps rubbing Hana like that,
she's gonna cum! Hana's gonna cum!
If you can't go to the bathroom correctly,
you won't become a cat.
Hana, I'm gonna cum. I'm cumming!
No! Meow!
Cats really are amazing, aren't they?
Seeing Hana's chest covered in that pearly
white liquid reminds me less of a cat,
and more of a cow, but...
I can't really say that to her.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч