Time passed after I started studying with Chii-chan,
and suddenly... it was the Christmas season.
But our erotic days continued without skipping a beat.
This really warms me up.
It's obvious what you're expecting from dragging a girl
to the boy's bathroom first thing in the morning.
But don't worry, I'll take good care of your
greedy dick as I always do, Kou-chin.
Let's get started...
Your pre-cum's flooding out. It's not stopping!
Chii-chan, you seem pretty used to this.
Because I am.
I've sucked lots of guy's dicks in places where
anyone could walk in on you at any second.
I'm a girl that loves to suck dicks in the boy's bathroom.
You're too sexy, Chii-chan!
Your balls are getting bigger.
They want to cum in my mouth-pussy, don't they?
Yeah! All inside you!
Oh, I see. Yeah?
Then I'll make you cum.
Shoot all your cum from your huge dick inside my mouth!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm so full from your dick milk.
Let's hurry up or else we'll be late, Kou-chin!
Chii-chan, you got pubic hairs on your face.
Dumb, but when it comes to sucking dicks, she's very talented Chii-chan
I'm gonna find my happiness!
I'm so nervous.
You'll be fine.
Chii-chan, look, you're right there.
1. Muroto Kouta
Wow, you're at the top as usual.
Wait, what?!
30. Shiina Chieri
Congrats on reaching your goal, Chii-chan.
No way.
Kou-chin!
Kou-chin! Thank you!
I'm the one who should be thanking you, Chii-chan.
It's already Christmas Eve?
I bet Chii-chan's with her boyfriend right about now...
But seriously,
I can't believe my boyfriend stood up
his beautiful girlfriend for work
even though she got all dressed up in a yukata for him.
I'm not much of a man, am I?
But even so, I...
Her face from then won't leave my head.
Chii-chan?
I got stood up again.
You see, my boyfriend was actually my homeroom
teacher. He even has a wife and kids.
Wait, you're not serious are you?
Yeah, he was having an affair with me.
But even despite that, he helped me think about my
future and then I even got a reason to study harder.
But if he keeps betraying me like this... "our" future and
everything I've built on up until now... everything...
All that's going to become worthless, right?
Listen, is a guy who makes you
feel this bad really a good guy?
If a guy makes the girl he likes sad, shouldn't
that be enough to make him cry?
Wouldn't that make him want to hug her?!
Kou-chin...
How could you like a girl who had an affair?
You're really not too smart.
But thanks to you, I have my answer.
Are you sure?
I've played around a lot.
I don't care about that.
None of that has anything to do with
the fact that I love you, Chii-chan.
Okay then, show me that you're not lying, Kou-chin.
Sure.
I've sucked so many dicks, but this is the first
time I've kissed someone. Funny, isn't it?
Kou-chin...
Your moans are so sexy.
I'm kissing you. How am I supposed to hold myself back?
Okay, open your legs.
Th-That's too sudden...
I haven't taken a shower yet...
But you're licking it so hard!
If you keep licking me so thoroughly like that, I won't
be able to stop my love juices from coming out!
Your tongue... Your tongue's wrapping
around my clitoris and sucking it!
My head's going crazy.
I can't... I can't take it anymore!
Put it in. Put it in! I want you to make me forget!
Kou-chin!
I want you to make my pussy remember
who it belongs to now!
Please. Hurry and put it in!
Alright. I'm putting it in.
Oh my god...
So this is what sex with you is like.
And this is what you feel like inside!
Your dick fits perfectly inside me.
Move! Kou-chin, move!
My wet pussy's getting stirred up by your huge dick!
I'm really having sex with you!
Yeah, it feels so good!
I feel like I'm really gonna lose my mind!
Do it! Lose it! Let's do it together!
Your kiss... so rough!
It really feels like we're having sex like lovers, Kou-chin!
Kou-chin!
Give it to me inside.
Fill my pussy with your cum, Kou-chin!
Give it to me in my womb!
It's coming out. Your dick's coming out!
Your cum's pouring out of my pussy.
Your bed's gonna get dirty.
Geez.
Tissue. Where are the tissues?
How many do I need to use?
My pussy's still basically drooling cum at this point too.
Well I guess I'll have to do something about that.
I was always so frustrated every time
I heard about your boyfriend!
But from now on, you're mine!
I'm gonna let loose all the cum I've
been saving for you in your womb!
No!
This feels too good!
Just say you'll be my woman!
But I'm already your woman, Kou-chin!
My heart, body, and womb...
They're all yours!
Paint the walls of my pussy with your cum!
Mark my dripping wet pussy with your
cum! Make it forget anyone else!
I'm gonna cum inside!
This isn't... fair...
Did I prove my love to you?
Yeah...
I can tell from my pussy that the
way you feel about me is real.
After we revealed our feelings for one
another, we studied a lot together.
We decided that since we liked sex so much that
we'd have sex after we finished studying.
And because of that, our academic level
just kept growing and growing.
So to reward all our hard work, we
decided to go on a bit of a trip.
Let's pretend we're newly wed and have sex.
It's coming inside me!
All of your dick is inside me.
My pussy fits it like a glove.
We study together and eat together...
we're always together.
And then we always have so much sex that it
feels weird not to have your dick inside me.
I love your dick, Kou-chin.
It messes me up so bad.
If you keep moving like that, I'm gonna cum!
I don't mind.
Super Thin MAX
We're gonna run out of condoms at this rate!
Just from one time?
You really are remarkable.
Even with a condom on, my pussy
can't get enough of your dick!
It goes so deep inside me and hits me everywhere!
Kou-chin, let's cum together!
Make my pussy cum with your condom wrapped dick!
Chii-chan, I'm cumming!
Your dick cumming is too amazing!
Super Thin MAX
Hey, Kou-chin, let's do it again.
Cum! Cum!
Make my pussy go crazy with your dick!
Chii-chan! Chii-chan!
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum from your condom wearing dick!
No, I can't...
I haven't even stopped cumming!
Kou-chin, you animal!
You animal!
Keep saying that and I'll take my dick out!
No, don't! You can't! You can't!
I was lying! I wasn't being serious!
I want to have sex with you, Kou-chin!
I'll be honest!
Man, my girlfriend is so cute!
She's so dirty and cute...
And for a dirty girlfriend like her...
Her boyfriend has a duty to show her off
to the entire world with his raw dick!
It's coming inside! Your raw dick's tip is coming inside me!
I'm gonna cum!
Chii-chan, I'm gonna do my best!
Yeah! Yeah!
Marry me!
I'll marry you!
Kou-chin...
I love you...
Kou-chin?
What is it, Chii-chan?
Let's come here next year too.
Good idea.
Let's come here again, Chii-chan.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч