If you can restrain yourself, I'll teach you
something that feels even better.
Really?
Okay, I'll stop it then.
I really want to have sex with her,
but the fact that I completely lied about
her getting smarter with my cum
is something that I really need to fix soon.
Original Animation Disc.
The case of making my stupid sister smart with only my XXX!
I'm Mitsui Hana, and I love ice cream!
I'm gonna stuff my mouth down there too! Chapter
Delicious!
So much jam!
Back at home Mom gets mad at me if I eat that much.
Let's buy groceries later.
I'll buy lots of milk and jam.
Okay!
I love you, onii-chan!
Groceries, groceries!
Lots of milk, lots of jam!
Hey, onii-chan.
I'm properly restraining myself.
That's why.
My pussy is already tingling so much.
I want you to make me feel good already, onii-chan.
I'm sorry, but onii-chan's at his limit!
It's my first time doing this,
but I'll definitely make this feel good for you.
So it's your first time too.
Just like me!
Onii-chan.
The way you lick my pussy.
Yup, I'm licking your pussy just like how you lick my dick.
I think... it feels good.
How about this?
That feels good.
It's licking my pussy's insides.
It's slithering its way in.
The inside of my pussy feels weird.
Your tongue pushing in makes it even more.
It feels so good.
My pussy feels great.
Onii-chan, I'm starting to feel very weird.
Weird?
Are you about to cum?
Where?
Where are we going? Are we going shopping?
It's alright, just relax.
O-Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
Oh no, oh no.
Something's... something's coming!
What's this, onii-chan?
That's what's referred to as "cumming".
It happens when you feel really good.
Really good? I don't get it.
If you cum lots more, it'll start feeling even better.
I... love feeling better.
Then, I want to cum more so I can start feeling better already.
Actually, there's a better way to make
it feel far more pleasurable.
Onii-chan, what should I do now?
It'll hurt quite a bit, so try to endure for a while.
Endure?
Here I go.
Onii-chan, wait.
Sorry, but it only hurts at first.
Onii-chan.
It went in.
I'm relieved.
I was worried that she might have
been tricked by some shady guy,
but she's actually a virgin.
Is the pain gone now?
Yeah, and it feels so good inside you.
Really?
Will I feel good too?
Of course.
Leave it to me.
My breasts feel good,
but my pussy hurts.
I don't want this dick inside me.
It's just temporary.
This is the best way to have sex.
Sex?
I can fully release all of my milk during sex.
Okay, I'll try my best.
I want to drink your milk, so I'll have sex.
Alright, good girl.
Onii-chan, your dick is pushing in.
Are you masturbating?
I'm rubbing my dick inside your pussy to achieve pleasure.
This is what sex is.
So this is sex.
My pussy feels tight.
It hurt so much earlier,
but because it feels good for you as you rub it in.
I'm happy.
That's why... move your dick more, feel good more.
Hana, if you say it like that,
then onii-chan won't be able to hold back!
Onii-chan!
Amazing. Sex is amazing.
The pain is starting to go away,
and something's.
It's starting to feel good for you, right?
Does sex feel good?
It feels full, and it's all tingly.
Does it feel good for you too? Then we're a pair!
Yeah, it feels great.
Let's make ourselves feel even better, okay?
Hana!
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
Ohii-chan,
I'm going to cum again.
Hana, just cum.
Just cum.
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum all over again!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm really cumming.
My pussy feels hot.
Onii-chan, you're squirting lots inside my pussy.
It probably felt too good,
that's why I came so much.
Wow!
So there's this much inside my pussy?
It felt really good for me.
Let's have sex again, okay, onii-chan?
The case of making my stupid sister smart with only my XXX!
Writing reports is such a pain.
Man, I want to play with Hana.
Onii-chan, you can do university-level studies as well? Amazing!
Like hell I'd show how pathetic I am to her!
Onii-chan!
Hey, hey!
I learned something really great!
What are you doing?
Hana.
I found it interesting when it vibrates after pressing a button,
so I tried holding it against my pussy.
You can't ever do that unless you're alone!
That's masturbating!
Masturbating?
But I'm not really touching my pussy or nipples in any way.
No, no.
You're going to be molested if they see you doing that.
I don't want that!
But, I don't want to stop this great feeling.
I won't molest you, so you can keep doing that for a while.
Really?
Can I really masturbate?
So good, it feels so good.
I love my nipples.
Hey, masturbate too, onii-chan.
I want someone to do it too.
You really like doing things together.
Your dick is getting really big!
The way you masturbate is different from me.
Does it feel good for you too?
Yeah, your erotic look is the best.
I want you to do something a bit more intense.
Intense?
Try fondling your breasts.
Also, push the controller a bit harder.
Amazing!
It feels even better than earlier.
That's good, Hana.
You're really erotic.
Onii-chan, I'm...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Me too, I'm about to cum too.
I feel so hot!
Hana, open your mouth.
Stick out your tongue too.
You're completely covered.
I'm going to let you drink it properly next time.
Thanks for the drink.
I'm so sweaty.
Can't I take these off?
No, you can't.
You're going to be molested by weird people if you do that.
Besides, I'll get caught if I let you do that.
You'll get caught?!
I don't want that. I'll just try to hold on.
I'll be a good girl.
I don't want you to go away.
Please be with me forever.
I won't go anywhere as long as you're a good girl.
Okay.
Ice cream!
Onii-chan, there's ice cream!
So cold, and so good.
I'll just go the toilet for a moment.
Just wait on the bench over there.
Okay.
The case of making my stupid sister smart with only my XXX!
Hana?
Oh, onii-chan, welcome back.
Wh-What are you doing?
I feel so hot, so I thought I'd stick it in my pussy to cool it down.
But, though it feels cold,
my body still feels hot.
Y-Yeah. I can see that.
Well, I thought I'd push it in further to make you feel cool.
My pussy feels cold.
It feels good... but my body just keeps feeling hotter.
Why don't we try to make it hotter, then?
Get it hot with something hot.
Whoa, it's your dick!
But, it's hot so I don't want to pull the ice cream out.
Well... then.
What? That's not the right spot!
That's my butthole.
Not there!
Stop... it won't fit!
My butthole is expanding.
Look, it's in.
We can have sex with your butt.
It's really inside.
It's in my butthole, and yet it's like my pussy.
It might hurt a bit, so I'll make it feel good down here too.
So erotic.
My dick is really going in and out of her ass.
This feels embarrassing.
Don't look at my butthole!
My butt feels warm, and yet something's still cold.
So hot... and so cold,
I don't understand it anymore, but it feels good.
All this melted ice cream makes your pussy look delicious.
Can I lick it?
I don't wanna.
Please keep doing that to my butt.
Don't stop making me feel good.
Guess I can't hold back anymore with that request.
It feels so good!
It's squeezing me tightly.
Hana, I'm about to!
No, not yet, I haven't cum yet, onii-chan.
Here!
I think I'm nearly there.
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
Alright, Hana, I'll cum now as well.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
It's not my pussy.
Your milk is being pumped into my pussy, onii-chan.
My pussy feels so hot.
You won't get smart if you don't drink your milk.
Onii-chan, it's amazing.
So there are other places in my body
where you can put your dick into.
I'll drink lots more of your milk,
because I need to become as smart as you, onii-chan.
I love both Mr. Cow and onii-chan's milk!
I'll get even smarter the more I drink your milk, right?
And then... I'll enter the same university onii-chan's attending!
No, I don't really think that's possible.
Onii-chan, I want more milk!
Umm... which milk?
You know already, of course!