hanime.tv
Presents
Chii-chan and I started studying together,
and it's really become…
Christmas season.
We've been friends with benefits for a while.
Wow, this really warms me up!
Sneaking me into the men's room and getting
your expectations up like this…
Kou-chin, your cock is so selfish.
I'll take good care of it today, like usual!
Let's get started.
No matter how much I swallow,
you keep leaking pre-cum!
Chii-chan, you're kind of used
to this now, aren't you?
I am!
In places like this, where anyone could just walk in
I've had sex with many guys before.
I'm the kind of girl who's happy to
give you head in the men's room.
You're so sexy, Chii-chan!
Your balls are getting all heavy with sperm.
You want to cum inside my
mouth pussy, don't you?
I want to cum inside you!
OK! I'll make you cum!
Your thick, throbbing cock is full of semen.
Let it all out inside my mouth pussy!
I can't hold it any longer!
Early in the morning and my stomach's
already full of dick milk.
Let's go! We're going to be late
if you don't hurry, Kou-chin!
Chii-chan, you've got some pubes on your cheeks.
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
Chii-Chan May Be
an Idiot, but at Least
She Gives Good Head!
I'll live happily ever after!
I'm so nervous!
Relax, you'll be fine.
Look, Chii-chan
over there.
Muroto           Kouta
Good job, Kou-chin!
Wait, what?!
Shiina                Chieri
Congratulations. You did it, Chii-chan.
I can't believe it!
Kou-chin!
Kou-chin, thank you!
I should be thanking you, Chii-chan.
It's Christmas Eve…
Chii-chan's probably with
her boyfriend right now…
Even though he's got work
To think he'd cancel on a yukata-clad
beauty like me…
I'm really disappointed in him.
Guess I'm not so manly…
but still
still bothered by that lonely smile she gave me.
Chii-chan?
He stood me up again.
My boyfriend-
He's my homeroom teacher,
and he's married with kids.
Seriously? That means-
Yeah, that makes me his mistress, doesn't it…
But even so, he helped me think about my future.
He gave me a reason to focus on my studies.
But now that he's betrayed me like this
My future and all the effort I've been putting
in… It's all just meaningless now!
Hey
A guy who breaks your heart like this…
Is he really worth it?
If the girl I loved was going though
a hard time, I'd feel sad too!
I'd want to hug and comfort her!
Kou-chin?
Loving a girl like me…
Are you an idiot?
But thanks to you, Kou-chin
I've found an answer!
Is this really OK?
I've been with so many others before.
I don't care about that.
That doesn't change my love for you.
OK
Why don't you try to prove it to me, Kou-chin?
I've given you so many blow jobs, and
yet this is our first time kissing.
That's hilarious!
Kou-chin
You sound so sexy.
Well, it's you who I'm kissing.
Of course it's going to feel good!
OK
Spread your legs.
S-So suddenly!
I haven't bathed yet
but you're eating me out!
You're licking my pussy so thoroughly.
I'm getting so wet!
Your tongue- You're focusing
it on my sensitive clit!
I'm gonna go crazy!
I can't take it any more!
I want you inside me, Kou-chin!
Let me know who my pussy belongs to!
Please, put it in me!
OK, I'm putting it in.
Wow, this is how it feels to have sex with Kou-chin!
This is Chii-chan's pussy!
Kou-chin's dick fits perfectly inside me!
Move inside me, Kou-chin! Please!
His dick is stirring up my pussy!
I'm doing it! I'm having sex with Kou-chin!
This feels so good! If we keep
this up, I'm going to go crazy!
Then do it! Go crazy!
Go as crazy as you want!
You're kissing too hard!
You're the one for me now! Now
we're lovers, Kou-chin!
Kou-chin!
Cum inside me! Fill me up with your semen!
Give it to me in my womb!
You're pulling it out.
You just came, and you're taking it out!
My pussy's overflowing with your semen.
So much for our date…
Where are those tissues?
How many should I use?
My pussy's twitching,
and your semen just keeps flowing out.
W-Well then I'd better fill that hole!
Every time you'd talk about your
boyfriend, I'd feel so helpless!
But starting today, you're mine!
I'm going to give you all the sperm I saved for you!
That- That feels so good!
Say you're my woman!
I'm already yours and only yours!
My mind, body, and womb-
I've given them all to you!
Fill me up with your dick milk!
Fill my dirty pussy, and mark me as yours!
I'm cumming inside you!
Y-You're too good.
Did I prove it?
Yes.
My pussy understood that you really do love me.
We thoroughly understood one another,
and since then, we've studied a lot.
Since we both love having sex, we decided
we'd use it as a daily reward for studying
and so both our academic abilities
kept steadily rising.
As a reward for our regular efforts,
we took a small vacation.
Hey, let's pretend we're newlyweds
and have some intimate sex.
It's going in.
I'm taking your cock all the way down
to the root. It's a perfect fit inside me!
We study and eat with each other.
We're always together.
We keep having sex. It's like it's weird
not to have your cock inside me.
Kou-chin, I love your cock!
It's stirring me up!
If you keep moving like that,
I'm going to cum already!
That's fine, cum!
If I do, we'll be out of condoms in no time!
Even if we have a dozen?
Kou-chin, you've got so much endurance!
Even with that condom, my pussy's
madly in love with your cock!
You're so deep inside me! You're
poking into my womb!
K- Kou-chin, let's cum together.
Make me orgasm with your condom-clad cock!
Chii-chan, I'm cumming!
Your dick's so amazing!
Hey, Kou-chin, can we do this one more time?
Cum, cum! Cum inside my womb!
Chii-chan, Chii-chan! I'm gonna cum again!
Your hard cock is gonna make me cum!
I can't take it any more!
I can't stop cumming!
Kou-chin, you beast!
Call me that and I'll take my cock out!
No, don't do that!
I lied, I lied! I want to keep having
sex with you, Kou-chin! I admit it!
My girlfriend is so cute!
She's so lewd and cute
and sexy and lewd!
It's my duty as her boyfriend to fuck her bareback!
You're inside me without a condom!
The tip is going into my womb!
I'm gonna cum like this. Chii-chan,
I'm hanging in there!
Yes, yes!
Let's…
get married!
Let's get married!
Kou-chin
I love you.
What is it, Chii-chan?
Let's come here again next year.
Good idea.
Let's come again, Chii-chan.
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
Encoding: Dorans
QA: Dorans
Софтсаб: TFloater