If you can hold out, I'll teach you
something that feels even better.
Really? Okay, then Hana will!
I really do want to have sex with Hana,
but first I have to somehow fix that lie I told her
about how she'd get smart from drinking my cum...
About that time when the only thing that could
make my stupid sister smart was my XX
I love ice cream too! Mitsui Hana <3
I'm going to squeeze it out with my mouth down there <3 arc.
That was so yummy! Hana ate so much jam! Mom would
get mad at Hana if she ever saw her eat that much jam.
Ещё и тайминг за ними править...
Let's go food shopping later,
I'll buy you more jam and milk.
Yay! Hana loves you, onii-chan!
Food shopping! Food shopping! Gonna buy lots of jam!
Onii-chan, Hana's been a good girl, hasn't she?
So... Hana's pussy has been feeling weird and hot.
Can you make Hana feel good now?
I'm sorry, onii-chan's at his limit!
Will, what happens next is new territory
for me too, but I promise I'll make you feel good...
So there are things you've never done too?
That means we're the same!
O-Onii-chan! You're licking my pussy...
Yeah... Just like how you'll lick my dick...
Right there! It feels good there!
Right here?
Yeah, that feels good... It feels good
when you lick inside Hana's pussy like that!
Your tongue is going inside!
Hana's pussy feels weird!
Ever since your tongue came inside,
Hana's pussy's been fidgety.
That feels good!
Hana's pussy feels good! So good!
Onii-chan, Hana's starting to feel weird!
Weird? Does that mean you're gonna cum?
Come where? Come to the supermarket with you?
It's okay. Just relax.
Onii-chan! Onii-chan! Onii-chan!
Oh no, something's coming!
Onii-chan, what's just happened?
What you just did, it's called "cumming".
It means you felt really good.
Cumming? Hana doesn't get it.
If you cum a few more times, it'll feel even better.
Hana likes feeling good.
Hana wants to feel even more good!
Actually, there's something we can do
to feel even better, if you're ready...
Onii-chan, what should Hana do?
It's gonna be a little rough at first,
so I need you to try and hold on.
Hold on?
Here I go!
O-Onii-chan, wait!
S-Sorry, but it only hurts at first.
Onii-chan!
Ah, it went in.
Thank god.
I thought she might've been tricked
by some shady guy and lost her virginity,
but it looks like that didn't happen.
No more ouchies?
No more ouchies...
Your insides feel so good, Hana.
Really? Can Hana feel good too?
Of course! Just leave it to me.
It feels good, but Hana's pussy still hurts.
I don't like your dick inside.
It only hurts at first.
Having sex is the best way to feel good.
Sex?
If we have sex, your onii-chan
will be able to give you lots of milk.
Okay, Hana will do her best.
Hana wants to drink milk, so she'll do her best.
All right, good girl.
Onii-chan's dick is moving!
What is it doing?
My dick is rubbing your insides to make you feel good.
That's what sex is.
This is sex? Hana's pussy hurts though.
It hurt a lot before, but since you said that
you'd make Hana feel good, Hana's happy.
So move your dick more
and make yourself feel even better!
Hana, if you say things like that,
your onii-chan won't be able to resist anymore!
Onii-chan?!
Wow! Sex is so amazing! It's so amazing!
The ouchies are starting to go away.
Hana, is it starting to feel good for you?
Does sex feel good?
It feels good. Onii-chan feels good too,
just like Hana! We're the same!
Yeah, I feel good!
Let's feel even better together, okay?
Hana! Hana!
Onii-chan! Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, something's coming again!
Hana, I'm cumming! I'm cumming, Hana!
Hana's cumming! Hana's gonna cum from sex!
Cumming! Hana's cumming!
Hana's cumming!
Hana's pussy's so hot.
Onii-chan, there's so much
of your milk inside Hana's pussy.
Yeah, it just felt so good
that a lot of milk came out.
Wow! All of this was in Hana's pussy?
Hana felt really good too!
Let's have sex again, onii-chan!
I hate reports, I don't wanna finish this...
I wanna play with Hana.
Onii-chan, you're so cool for getting
your studying done for next semester!
I can't let her see my pathetic self!
– Onii-chan!
– Hm?
Um, um, Hana found something really cool!
What are you doing, Hana?!
Pressing the buttons made it vibrate,
so Hana tried putting it against her pussy for fun!
Just because no one's around doesn't mean
you can do that! You're masturbating!
Masturbate? But I'm not touching
my nipples or pussy with my hands.
That doesn't mean it's okay!
If people saw you do this, they'd pounce on you!
That's scary! But this feels so good,
I don't want it to stop.
Don't worry, onii-chan won't pounce on you,
so how about we just leave it at this for today, okay?
Really?
So, I can masturbate?
It feels good! Hana's nipples... Hana likes them!
Onii-chan, why don't you masturbate too?
Hana wants to masturbate with you.
You really like us doing things together, don't you?
Wow, your dick got really big!
So onii-chan's masturbating is different than Hana's?
Does that feel good for you?
Yeah I love looking at your dirty body, Hana.
It'd be even better if you were a bit more rough.
Rough?
Rub your entire boob and push the
controller even deeper inside you.
Wow this feels even better than before!
That's good, Hana. That's so hot.
Omi-chan, Hana's gonna cum! She's gonna cum!
Me too! I'm gonna cum!
Hana, open your mouth and stick out your tongue!
I really covered you in my milk.
Next time I'll make sure you can drink all of it.
Thank you for the meal.
Hana's so stick with sweat.
Is it okay if I get naked?
Of course it isn't! I'm telling you, weird people
are gonna attack you if you get naked in public.
And the worst thing is,
your onii-chan will be arrested.
You will?! Hana doesn't want that. Hana'll be a good girl.
Hana'll be a good girl, so don't go anywhere!
Stay with Hana forever, okay?
As long as you're a good girl, I won't go anywhere.
Okay.
Ice cream! Onii-chan, let's get ice cream!
It's so yummy and cold.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom real quick.
Wait on that bench over there, okay?
Okay!
About that time when the only thing that could
make my stupid sister smart was my XX.
Hana...
Oh, onii-chan, welcome back.
Wh-What the heck are you doing?!
Hana was feeling hot, so she stuck
the ice cream inside her pussy to cool down.
Hana's pussy feels cool now, but Hana's body still feels hot.
That makes sense.
You might feel cooler if I stick it in farther.
Hana's pussy feels weird, but this feels kind of good...
It's starting to feel hot though.
So it's actually making your pussy hot?
Well, you know what they say,
you should have hot things during hot weather.
Yay, your dick!
But it's hot, so I don't want you
to take the ice cream outside of me.
Then how about...
Huh, what are you doing?
That's not where that should go.
That's Hana's butt.
No, not there. It's not gonna fit!
My butt is gonna stretch so wide!
It went in! You can have sex with the butt too.
It's really inside Hana! It's Hana's butt,
but it went in like it did in Hana's pussy.
Looks like it feels good.
I'll help you feel good down here too.
Oh god, this is so hot.
Seeing my dick going in and out of you is so great!
No, this is so embarrassing.
Don't look at Hana's butt!
Hana's butt is so hot, but Hana's pussy is so cold!
Hana can't tell what's hot or cold anymore,
but it feels so good!
The ice cream melting out of your pussy
looks so yummy. Can onii-chan have a taste?
No! Hana wants you in her butt.
Don't stop the good feeling in Hana's butt!
Even if you begged me, I couldn't stop!
It feels so good!
Your butt's getting tighter. Hana, I'm gonna...
No, not yet. Hana's not ready yet.
If that's the case, then...
Hana... Hana thinks she's gonna cum!
Onii-chan, Hana's gonna cum! Onii-chan!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum too, Hana!
Hana's gonna cum! She's gonna cum!
Hana's pussy came!
Onii-chan's milk is in Hana's butt!
It's so hot.
You need to drink your milk or else
you won't become a smart girl.
Onii-chan, that was amazing. Hana didn't know
there were other places you could put your dick in.
I need to drink more milk
and become smart like you, onii-chan!
Hana loves regular milk and onii-chan's milk a lot!
If Hana drinks your cum every day,
Hana'll become smart, right?
When that happens, Hana will go
to the same college as you, onii-chan!
No, I don't think that's gonna happen.
Onii-chan, more milk!
Which one?
Can't you guess?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: akin
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч