Why is your pee-pee getting big, onii-chan?
1 hour earlier.
I guess this is the lonely college student's life, huh?
After being accepted into my first-choice college,
I, Mitsui Yuuishi, am living alone.
I don't have a girlfriend or close friends,
so I just lazed through summer.
This is Hana. I love her more than anything else,
and... I've started seeing her as a woman.
When I realized that,
I knew I had to cut ties with her.
So, I intentionally chose a college
that was two hours away by plane.
All to make sure that we would
barely be able to see each other.
My plan is backfiring, though...
I'm starting to like her even more than before.
Hana-chan, you're so cute! You're an angel!
What the hell am I doing,
thinking about my actual sister like that?
Huh? What now?
Onii-chan!
H-Hana?!
Yep!
Original animation disk.
About that time when the only thing that could
make my stupid sister smart was my XX.
I love milk! Mitsui Hana arc!
I barely recognized you!
You've grown so much since I last saw you.
Really? Is Hana pretty?
Yeah, you've gotten really big.
Hana loves milk!
Hana drinks a lot every day!
Look, they're so bouncy, it's funny right?
So, Hana has a message from Mom and Dad.
Huh? Oh yeah, a message?
Mom and Dad are going abroad for the summer break,
so Hana will be staying with onii-chan
so she can become a little smarter!
Huh? Wait a second, how did you even get here?
There's no way you took the bus or the train, right?
Nope, Mom and Dad dropped Hana off before they left!
For real?!
You came all this way without
saying a word to me about it?!
Do you hate me or something?!
I almost forgot. Though I love my sister a lot,
she's an incurable idiot.
She forgets stuff after taking just three steps.
She can barely read Kanji.
Forget about teaching her how to use
anything with more than three buttons.
My parents spoiled her because they
wanted a daughter, and I did a little, too,
so we ended up raising an idiot.
We worry about if she could
survive in the real world or not.
Now they're telling me to make her smarter?
This is bad...
My sanity might not hold out if
she stays here for the entire break.
My two years' worth of effort would be for nothing!
I'm hot!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Hana is always naked at home!
Wh-What the hell?!
She never did that when I was living with her!
I'm so jealous...
Onii-chan, let's get naked together!
Huh?
Why is your pee-pee getting big, onii-chan?
U-Um...
Because...
It's so that you can drink my milk, Hana.
That's so cool!
Milk comes out of your pee-pee, onii-chan?
You're going to let Hana drink your milk?
Yay! Hana can drink milk forever!
– Yay! Milk! Milk!
– I never thought Hana would be this dumb.
– Hana wants to drink milk!
Huh? Milk isn't coming out.
It doesn't come out that easily.
Your onii-chan's milk is special.
Special?
My milk has nutrients that will make you smarter.
Wow, that's so cool!
Hana wants to drink lots of your milk,
and become a smart person like you!
Aren't I the real idiot here...?
About that time that... idiot... something... smart!
To make the milk come out,
you need to make it feel really good.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Pee-pee!
Try moving your hand up and down.
Um, like this?
Oh wow, your pee-pee is getting bigger and harder!
That means it's ready to start making milk.
It's because you're good at this, Hana.
Hana is getting kind of tired, though.
Then, how about you try using your mouth?
Huh? But, if Hana eats your dick, it'll disappear.
You lick it like you would ice cream.
Ice cream!
Hana likes ice cream too!
Time to dig in!
Your pee-pee made Hana's mouth really full.
Onii-chan, it feels good, doesn't it?
Is the milk going to come out soon?
Yeah, just keep licking it and sucking it like that,
while moving your hand up and down.
Like this?
Hana, you're really good at this.
Really?!
Hm? Your pee-pee is starting to taste funny.
That's proof that it feels good. It's called pre-cum.
It's something that comes before seme...
It's something that comes out before the milk does.
Pre-cum?
I don't understand.
Let's try to remember it, okay?
If you become smarter,
you'll be able to drink the milk even sooner.
Yeah! Hana will do her best!
Hana's gonna be a smart girl!
That feels good!
Does it really feel good?
Are you happy Hana's here?
Yeah, I'm really happy you're here.
It's coming. Put it in your mouth, Hana.
The milk is coming? Is the milk going to come out?
Yeah, it's coming.
A lot will come out, so drink it all, okay?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's milk, Hana. If you don't drink it,
you won't become smart.
S-Sorry. You don't have to drink it,
you can spit it out if you want.
That was nothing!
Oh wow, you're such a good girl, Hana!
You did really well!
Hana did her best!
Onii-chan, your milk is so bitter, though.
It's completely different from regular milk.
I'll make sure to give you lots of milk,
so let's have fun living together, okay?
Yep! Thanks, onii-chan!
I look forward to it!
And so began my summer vacation with Hana.
About that time when the only thing that could
make my stupid sister smart was my XX.
I can't believe she was naked the entire time...
Hana, you can take a bath now, it's ready.
Okay!
Crap... if I keep seeing her naked like this,
one day, my desires will take over and I'll...
No, I'm a nice brother to her!
I need to tell her to stop prancing around naked!
Onii-chan?
What's the matter?
You can turn on the cool water if it's too hot.
Um...
Hana wants to take a bath with you like we used to.
93... 94... 95... 96...
Yay! Hana's taking a bath with onii-chan!
97... 98... 99... 100!
Okay, let your onii-chan wash your body for you.
Okay!
Holy crap, they're soft!
Hana's boobs are amazing!
Onii-chan, that tickles!
Hana's boobs are big right?
You like big boobs, right?
Down there is Hana's special place.
This is my first time touching one!
So this is Hana's... a girl's...
Onii-chan, Hana's feeling kind of weird...
Huh? I'm sorry, does it hurt?
No, when you touch Hana there, I feel light-headed.
Hana's special place, your vagina is
a special place, just like my dick is.
Hana's vagina? So Hana's vagina
likes being touched, just like your pee-pee?
Exactly! You're smarter already!
I wonder if it's because of your milk, onii-chan.
It feels so good! When you touch
Hana's boobs and vagina, it feels so good!
Hana's peeing herself!
Don't worry, that's not pee.
Your pee-pee is getting big.
Can Hana drink your milk again?
Yeah.
There's another way to get it to release milk.
You think you can do it?
Yeah! Hana will do her best to become a smart girl!
She's never even masturbated before.
I can't put it inside her.
So how about...
Your pee-pee is twitching!
It seems happy as a clam between Hana's boobs.
Okay, now move your boobs up and down.
Okay!
Please give Hana a lot of milk, Mr. Pee-pee!
Yeah, just like that.
Keep rubbing your boobs like that.
Okay!
Yeah, that's good Hana.
Now, try putting my dick in your mouth.
Like this?
This is hard.
That's good.
You just keep getting better, Hana.
Really?
Hana feels good too!
Wow, Hana, you're making such a perverted face...
Hana, just a little more. Be a bit more rough.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Onii-chan, your milk sure is amazing.
You let out so much again!
How does it taste? Do you still not want to drink it?
It's still really bitter, but it's all to make
Hana smarter, so Hana will drink it!
Onii-chan's milk is good,
but cow milk is definitely the best!
Shit! I'm being overtaken?!
Making the milk come out like that felt good.
Touching Hana's nipples like that really felt good...
Don't ever do that in front of people!
But it feels so good.
If Dad finds her masturbating, he's gonna kill me.
If you can hold out, I'll teach you
something that feels even better.
Really? Okay, then I will!
I really do want to have sex with Hana,
but first I have to somehow fix that lie I told her
about how she'd get smart from drinking my cum...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: akin
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч