It's so hot...
Just a little more, and I'll be in air conditionad paradise!
Let's go, Kota. You only have to endure a bit more.
Today will be the day I resist the temptation
of the convenience store!
Wow... She's like exhibition
A of a "Tanned Gal Bitch"!
Wait, that's Shiina Chieri from my class
She's so erotic it's overwhelming.
I might be all over the news tomorrow...
But how can I resist!?
Oh, our eyes met.
Hum, they say girls notice when guys give them
perverted looks 100 percent of the time, but.
Oh come on, you can't just go back and look again!
В один присест сожрала!!!
You'll get arrested if you pull that all the time Ko-chin. I came
here because I wanted to ask you for something, you know?
A request for me? From Shiina-san herself?
Yeah, for you. So...
Shiina Chieri aka Chii-chan, the reining Queen of our school's
male masturbation fantasies rankings, has a request for me?
I'm so happy I've been a good boy.
I wonder what the request is?
If it's something perverted.
Late at night, Chii-chan sneaks into
my room wearing a demon outfit.
Hey, Ko-chin! Are you even listening to me?
S-Sorry, what was it again?
Like I've been saying, help me study!
Not Too Bright but at Least She Sucks Dick Like a Pro: Chii-chan
Chii-chan, are you sure you can focus on studying?
I did it!
Good work, Shiina-san.
Call me Chii-chan!
By the way, why'd you help me with such
a bothersome request, Ko-chin?
W-well, it's because I was impressed that you are
seriously thinking about your future, Chii-chan.
You sure it's just that?
Well, of course I'd hope for some perverted
stuff when we're all alone like this.
By the way, I have a boyfriend, so smashing
is out of the question, okay?
I totally thought this was going somewhere!
R.I.P. to the chance to lose my virginity...
But I do have to thank you for
helping me study, don't I?
Th-thanks?
Ko-chin made sure my studying
was properly taken care of.
So I should make sure your dick is
properly taken care of in return.
I might be stupid, but I'm confident
in my fellatio skills, you know?
The more I lick, the more your thick pre-cum
is making my mouth feel hot.
Your manly smell might make
me forget all that studying.
Chii-chan, you should remember at least that.
You know, I love watching people
feel good with my mouth pussy.
Is it about time for me to get serious?
What do you mean serious?
Amazing! My mouth is stuffed
with Ko-chin's penis!
You can let it blow whenever you
can't hold it anymore, okay?
I'll completely empty your balls, so
let it all out into my mouth pussy.
You're too good... I can't hold it anymore!
Let it all out! Pump your cum into me!
You're too erotic, Chii-chan.
Starting tomorrow, you'll be taking care of
this girl who's too erotic, right Ko-chin?
My summer with Chii-chan only
kept escalating after that.
Chii-chan, you're really going
to let me see your tits?
Of course.
Here you go, these are your classmate's
bare tits you've been dying to see.
Th-the legendary "Classmate's Titties!"
They're almost magical!
Oh yeah.
Huh, Chii-chan?
Oh, there it is!
Today is... Titfuck-day!
What a wonderful day.
Come on, Ko-chin... Drench my breasts in lotion.
Y-yeah.
Wow.
Ko-chin, your eyes are so perverted right now.
And I've seen a lot of cocks, but yours
is the best one I've ever seen!
You're not just saying that to
make me happy, are you?
I mean it. Your cock is even more
amazing than my boyfriend's.
Alright, it's time to try sticking
that cock in between my tits.
Look, I'm giving your cock a
massage with my breasts.
When you put it in between like this...
See? It makes such a lewd sound.
If I rub my breasts onto your amazing cock like
this... I'm starting to feel all hot inside.
A normal cock would be done fore when I lick the
tip like this while I massage it with my breasts.
I can see why, this feels crazy good.
Even a stud like you has to be close, right Ko-chin?
Chii-chan, I'm about to.
Here comes the load Ko-chin's
been holding back for so long!
Thanks for the meal.
Chii-chan, we shouldn't be doing this here.
I always wanted to try giving a serious blowjob
where other people are always seriously studying.
Before someone comes, I'm going to
focus everything on sucking you off!
Ko-chin's pre-cum is so thick, I feel like
I'll get pregnant just by drinking it.
Let it out! I don't want to dirty my uniform,
I'll drink it all again like usual!
Chii-chan, I'm cumming!
You let out so much even though
I'm taking care of you everyday.
Ko-chin! How is it, are you turned on?
Chii-chan, you're a genius!
This smell... Thou art erect, are you not?
As expected of the Cock-master. Then you also
already know what I want you to do, right?
Come, ravage me, Ko-chin.
Here I go.
This Chii-chan hole is glorious!
It feels too good, I don't care about anything else!
I can't hold it anymore!
Do I really have to show it?
Yeah, I'm begging you.
But it's so embarrassing.
Hurry up and show me, Chii-chan!
Ko-chin you meanie!
I was aiming to be in the top
30 for the summer test.
I guess that was a little too high.
But Chii-chan, you put in a lot of effort.
It's okay, I always saw how hard you worked.
If you keep working this hard, being in the top
30 by next year should be a piece of cake!
Your dreams will come true, I guarantee it.
Ko-chin!
That's not fair, saying so much stuff that
makes me all happy and fluttery inside!
I don't know how to repond to that.
As thanks for you giving motivation to keep working
hard, I'll listen to any request you have for me!
R-really?
Yup.
Then.
Ko-chin, this is really embarrassing.
Chii-chan, why do you have this erotic sticker on?
It's your fault, it's because my panties always
get drenched when I suck your cock.
You're such a perverted girl.
I can't let you do me, so this has to stay on, okay?
I'm going to rub my cock against you.
Rub your cock against my ass.
Your pre-cum is being soaked
into my ass by your cock.
You're squeezing my ass so hard you're into a pocket
pussy, you're making me give you an ass-job!
I want to fuck you, I want to put
it in Chii-chan's pussy so much!
N-no, you can't! I'd be cheating if you
did that, so you really can't do that!
Damn it, damn it all!
Ko-chin's getting so jealous, my pussy's
so happy it's tightening up!
Chii-chan, the sticker's about to come off.
N-no, if it comes off it'll just be a bare ass-job!
It'll be cheating, it's not okay, but...
Chii-chan, I'm already about to bust!
I'm about to cum too, so let it out on my ass.
Spray your cum all over me, Ko-chin!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming from having
my pussy covered in semen!
You're such a pervert, Ko-chin.
Whew, that was so much fun!
I can't believe my boyfriend cancelled on a
beautiful yukata girl like me just to work.
Oh, so your boyfriend already works.
Yup, isn't it the worst?
But I had a lot of fun this summer
thanks to you, Ko-chin!
Our summer break ended with her smile
that contained a hint of loneliness.
Translation: ShamelessPersimmon
Timing: ShamelessPersimmon
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч