Sorry for the wait.
Miran-senpa—
Erm... Should I have removed my underwear?
No... well...
I was just caught off guard
from how lovely you look.
Really? Thanks...
Every part of Miran-senpai's body is soft.
Shall we proceed?
O-Okay.
Eh,
Wait a second.
This is embarrassing.
Miran-senpai...
Come here.
They're so soft that my fingers sink in them.
Your hands are big, Munetaka-kun.
Miran-senpai!
Please be gentle.
Y-Yes!
I love you, Munetaka.
That's why I want us to have sex.
Let's make a baby together.
M-Munetaka-kun?
It went down.
T-That's because I am very nervous.
I-Is that so? It can't be helped.
I'll make you hard again.
Okay.
S-Sorry.
It's my fault. I selfishly dragged
you along with me here.
Selfishly... that's not-
I am...
I'm going home.
See you again in college!
Miran-senpai!
Goodbye!
At that time, I never had any idea.
That afterwards, I'll end up in a hellish world of sex.
kimi ni tsutaetai ai no 'prologue'
I want to tell you, this prologue of love
tsunai da te dokidoki suru
holding hands makes my heart throb
niji no 'melody' kanadeyou
like a rainbow melody playing
Baku Ane
Otouto
Ippai
Shibocchauzo!
We're gonna squeeze our little brother a lot.
ameagari sora no shita
beneath the sky after a rain
'asphalt' ni tokeru
your running silhouette melts on the asphalt
kakeashi to yokogao
guuzen ubawareta 'heart'
suddenly, my heart has been taken
subete wa 'slow motion'
everything were in slow motion
tokimeki kyuujoushou
but then suddenly got exciting
ushiro muki na jibun tobikoe
I leap while looking behind
hikari mezashite suteki na negai kanaeyou
reaching for the light, granting my lovely wish
kimi ni todoketai amai soyokaze o
I want to give you this sweet and gentle breeze
chikatzukeba furafura shite
when you are near, I feel restless
atama kinkyuu keihou !?
It's 'panic mode' in my head
fui ni terasareta taiyou no 'smile'
the sun suddenly shines its smile over me
mabushikute kirakira suru
dazzlingly shining
koi no 'memory' hajimaru
the memories of love is beginning
This work is brought to you by
a dream-weaving company, Atelier Kaguya
and the publisher of this medium, Pink Pineapple.
I'm coming in, Munetaka.
Hey, it's morning and you're
being sluggish again already.
Good morning.
Don't tell me you're taking
another day off from school?
H-How about you, Ritsuka-neesan?
Are you not going to the law firm today?
I'm on the afternoon shift again for today.
Jeez.
I don't remember raising you
to be such a fragile man.
Seems that I need to discipline you
with some strict training again.
I-I'm alright.
Munetaka, is there something
serious that you're worried about?
You give off an expression,
like you're trapped in something
and that it's making you suffer.
I'm not really... worried...
Here.
Just like in the past,
I'll cuddle you like a good kid
to make you feel at ease
and tell everything, right?
No! I'm not a kid anymore!
Munetaka...
Am I not an unreliable sister for you?
Am I not good enough to help you?
I get it. It's unforgivable.
Yeah... I feel miserable myself.
It's like I'm good for nothing.
That woman's attitude, turning you away
just because you failed at your first time.
Doing things halfheartedly instead of trying harder!
But now I understand.
To make you leave that girl and move on,
I'm gonna cheer you up all I can.
First, take all of your clothes off!
As siblings, there are various issues about this,
But let's not talk about those.
You can use my body and learn
how to make a woman feel good.
However, we're siblings so
we can't do the real thing.
As long as we don't cross that line,
you can do anything else with my body.
Ritsuka... nee-san!
It seems that you're all good up to ejaculation.
Alright, next is intercrural.
Intercrural?
That's it. You can only rub me on the outside.
You can't put it inside me no matter what!
You're doing good, Munetaka!
You're thrusting your hips wildly.
If this goes on, I might also
end up wanting the real thing!
Ritsuka-nee! I can't believe it!
To think how much better than this
it might feel if I slide it inside...
So hot! Munetaka...
That was so good, Munetaka.
If I put it inside, it'll be more...
Good boy...
Ritsuka-neesan won't be home until tomorrow.
What should I do about supper?
It's Mashiro-nee.
She is a very popular newscaster with a
noble aura in her and an outstanding appearance.
Even if we're cousins,
it's like we're a world apart.
When we're kids, I even wrote her a love letter.
Mu-kun!
Mashiro-nee! Why are you here?
Ritsuka-oneechan called me over.
She told me to take care of you. Especially on cooking.
I-I see...
Simmered amberjack with radish is the main dish.
Isn't amberjack a winter season fish?
You're outdated.
Nowadays, they can catch delicious
amberjacks even at summer.
Delicious! The taste is soaked in
and there isn't a hint of fishy taste.
This one's a bonito broth omelet.
Oh, this is something.
The elegant fragrance of bonito fills my mouth.
I need to make delicious and nutritious food
so my husband will be able to work hard.
Husband?
Alright! Answer my question even
though you're still having a meal.
Mu-kun. Can you tell me everything about
what happened you and your girlfriend?
It looks like you're suffering and I can't just ignore it.
Have faith in me. Tell me everything.
This turn of events... I know where this is going...
Do your best, Mu-kun.
If you can hold it in longer
with these tits that you love,
I'm sure that you'll be able to lead better
with your girlfriend on your first time.
Can I have a more practical lesson?
Your hard thing is sandwiched in my butt.
Amazing! You're hip movements are so wild!
This feels so good, but...
Your hot stuff...
It should feel much better inside you, Mashiro-nee.
Inside...
I want to put it inside!
Oh, isn't that Takesaka Wakana?
Oh! The princess of Japanese tennis!
She's cute, strong, and especially that breast!
Ain't she the best!
Wakana-neesan.
She's my second older sister.
That look she gave after leaving the house at that time...
It's been a while since then.
Wakana-neesan.
Eh? The lights are on.
How strange. I knew I turned the TV off.
Today on Sports Watch! We have a sad news.
It's about Takesaka Wakana
who's at the peak of her fame.
Due to a bad knee condition, she's not
going in Wimbledon Championships.
Could it be that...
Wakana-nee is already back?
Gotcha!
Hi, Munetaka.
Wakana-nee!
Why?
What do you mean why?
Of course, I'm here to finally have
sex with the darling that I love.
You still haven't given up on that?!
Give up? No way I will!
I've been always thinking about you
as much as I do about tennis.
So today, let's have the sex we
weren't able to do last time.
I love you, Munetaka.
That's why I want us to have sex.
Let's make a baby together.
I see...
That flashback I had when I tried having sex
for the first time with Miran-senpai is...
Miran? First time?
Hey darling, who's Miran?
Will you have faith in me and tell everything?
Oh.. This turn of events...
Darling's penis which that Miran
couldn't get up is now hard as rock!
This can't be!
Look, your body is so honest.
Rather than that nonsense woman, your body
wants to become one with your true love instead.
That's not true!
Darling, if you make such a face...
Oh, I can't take it anymore!
Even though we're siblings,
let's have a baby-making sex!
Fuck the laws!
This Super-dreadnought class idiot!
Jeez, for siblings to cross that line.
There's no way that you can get away
with such scandalous kind of love.
You're right.
But should you really be the one
talking, Ritsuka-oneechan.
Mashiro, why are you here?
For these.
I brought back these washed clothes from
last time when I had sex lessons with Mu-kun.
Huh?!
W-Wait, Mashiro-chan! What do
you mean with sex lessons?
To make him successfully
have sex with his girlfriend,
we give Mu-kun sex lessons, don't we onee-chan?
You've heard about it?
What's with that?! And you're
the one to scold me about it!
Ritsuka-nee... Mashiro-nee...
Wait, tell them what's in your mind!
Tell them "If they have ulterior motives then let's stop doing it".
They both really give their best for my sake.
Sorry for being a burden.
You three can't stand being alone!
Taking that aside, as the Eldest sister,
I will be the one to provide sex lessons so
Munetaka will be able to have sex properly.
I know what you feel but you are siblings.
So I'm more suited for this since we can cross that line.
C-Cross the line?!
Okay, let's stop it at that.
Everyone already knows it.
This already is a fight between
women for a single man.
Let's settle this once and for all.
Settle?
Each one of us shall give Munetaka a sex lesson,
and let him choose which one of us he wants.
Well then, it's the lover's final decisive battle!
Ain't it harsh?
I'll go wherever and ever, follow you, nii-san.
Wait, what do you mean by decisive battle?
Ritsuka-nee, make her stop.
Excellent!
You think you can take the gallant
eldest daughter of Takesaka household?
I will emerge victorious!
What an annoying bunch of twerps.
What a futile hope on bar exam.
Let's show them the power of elites!
Futile, futile.
Futile!
I'm the the only one who can legally marry Mu-kun!
And so...
The three of us are going in separate rooms.
Munetaka will go in each room
and have a sex lesson with each one of us.
And after that, choose the best one among us.
She will be the only one allowed
to give you further lessons.
Darling, I won't forgive you if you cheat on me.
Everyone's so carefree.
They haven't noticed it yet.
I'm very close to losing control of
my desire to come inside them.
Wakana-nee, what are you wearing?
Isn't this nostalgic?
Don't men love this? Schoolgirl outfits.
Well...
Shall we?
Let's continue from that day...
Inside... feels good... A woman's inside...
Wakana-nee!
Wakana-nee's breasts are soft!
From here on, you're gonna rough me up, right?
You're too rough.
Sorry!
It's okay. Don't hold back and hit me with all your lust.
Suck them.
Bite them if you want.
Do as you please!
Your fingers are so wild!
Give it to me! Unleash all of your lust on me!
Wow, there's something inside that started swelling.
Tell me, why are you so much into me?
That's because, I love you since we're young!
From childhoold, you were my hero!
You already know about it. I was
very timid when we're young.
Yeah.
I was always getting bullied by kid neighbors.
And you always come and save me.
It's alright now, Wakana-nee.
I thought about it.
That I'm a heroine and my destined
prince charming is you, Munetaka.
That's...
Then that means Wakana-nee...
From that time onwards,
she's been living her life loving me.
Hey darling, we're finally here.
I never gave up and kept waiting.
So please take me until the end.
Wakana!
Darling!
You're so tight, I'm stuck deep inside!
Darling... It feels like I'm getting split apart!
If you spread me open that wide...
Say it.
I can't!
Wakana-nee, I want to do it from the back.
Wakana-nee, I can't think of anything else but coming!
Come, darling! I'll take all of it
I feel like I'm breaking apart!
I beg you, Munetaka! Don't hold back and make me yours!
Wakana-nee!
Oh no... I'm already...
Oh no... Amazing!
I love you, I love you! I love you so much!
Wakana-nee!
I can't! Any more of this and I'll come!
So deep! No!
I'm getting filled with your semen...
Wakana-nee...
Munetaka, we're finally bound together.
Yeah...
Okay, now sit over there.
I'll end this by cleaning you as gratitude.
Wakana-nee! You're already dizzy...
I'm coming!
I wonder if my body will last until the end.
I have been waiting for you, Munetaka.
R-Ritsuka-nee, you look so sexy!
Isn't the "Ritsu" in your name
supposed to mean "Law"?
I tried hard doing these to make you happy.
Didn't I tell you? I don't care whatever you do to me.
What I mean is, violate me!
Ritsuka-neesan!
Hey, Munetaka. How long are you gonna do that?
Isn't it time for the next step?
Come here!
Forgive me, Ritsuka-nee!
What the hell?! Not that!
Look on the table!
Table?
T-These are...
Stop getting shocked about everything!
I am the eldest daughter of the Takesaka family!
The most suitable one to give you lessons
is neither Mashiro nor Wakana!
It can only be me!
Is that so?!
I'm currently your lover!
This is a roleplay, so stop hesitating!
You can start anywhere you want on me!
Okay, I got it Ritsuka-nee!
I'll do you anywhere I want!
Oh! You're amazing, Munetaka!
You're hitting me deep inside!
Oh no, this is bad!
If you do me this rough, I'll...
I'm coming!
Munetaka, this is too much!
It's scraping my insides!
I'm coming!
Oh no!
I can't... take anymore...
Ritsuka-nee!
Forgive me! I love you so much
that I couldn't hold back earlier!
You love me...
I love you so much, Ritsuka-nee!
Munetaka, the truth is I also—
Make love with me as a woman, Munetaka!
Good... good!
I love you so much!
Let me hear your lovely moans.
I love you! Your hard thing is sliding inside me!
Ritsuka is in heaven!
Munetaka...
Munetaka, just now...
What's the matter?
It got fertilized.
Munetaka, let's raise this child together
with all kindness and affection.
I see, everyone was able to enjoy
giving lesson to Munetaka.
No one can come between me and darling's bond.
Mu-kun is already captivated on me.
I already have his child in my belly...
Isn't that just your delusion?
So, who would be it?
Munetaka?
Darling?
Mu-kun?
Eh? Well...
Everyone's amazing that I can't decide...
I getting home late.
It's a comet...
How beautiful!
Oh no!
In the cleavage...
"hole-in-one"
As expected from darling!
We're gonna squeeze our little brother a lot.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization