Why doesn't she answer?
That's strange
She usually doesn't miss work without permission.
Is something the matter?
Reisa-san! I haven't been able
to reach Ai since last night.
She just keeps worrying me.
It couldn't be... Not her, too?
That would just be too cruel.
Hello? Ai?
Huh? Segawa-san?
I understand. I'll be there right away!
Yuzu-kun?
He found Ai! I'm going to get her!
Bakunyuu Maid Cari
This is the place.
Excuse me? I'm with Muko-Muko Maid Cafe.
I heard my friend who works there is here right now.
Excuse me.
Ai!
What happened to you? Wake up!
Don't worry, she's just tired.
Who's there?
You must be silenced.
What's this?
Isn't it wonderful?
Welcome to my mansion.
So you're the criminal behind the rape incidents!
Criminal? That's not quite right.
We have fun with our customers.
We grant them pleasures they've never felt before.
As proof of this, no one has filed
a criminal complaint against us.
That's a phony excuse!
You don't know the first thing about how
a girl behaves when she's in pain!
You'll understand that yourself in time.
What do you think you're doing?
Well then, Yuzuki-kun.
Time to have a taste of our ceremony.
Senpai.
Ai! S-Stop it, Ai!
I've always liked you, Senpai.
D-Don't!
Senpai, you're already so wet.
Ai, stop it! I'm begging you!
Senpai, you're cute when you're flustered.
The fun will become ever more intense, Yuzuki-kun.
This is your first time, isn't it?
Senpai, I promise you'll love it.
At first, it might hurt a little.
But eventually, you'll be able to forget the pain.
Please, stop this.
Ai! Ai!
Ai, Where are you?
S-Someone! Call... the police.
Yuzu-kun.
Murasaki-san?
What's happened?
Ai is... Ai is still trapped inside!
Ai?
The headquarters for the Maid Masters
is in the basement of this building!
And they're holding Ai prisoner!
Is that true?
Anyway, we must call the police!
That's not right, Senpai!
Ai?
Sorry to worry you!
That was just an act.
An act? What do you mean?
You see, I asked for their help
in researching my manga.
But what I did to you... I just got carried away.
So please don't call the police.
I see. So that's all it was. You had us scared there.
Now wait a minute!
Those guys admitted that they
were involved in the crimes.
I heard them!
You're mistaken.
But...
Anyway, Ai is safe.
Let's go home, Yuzu-kun.
I still have a meeting with them.
Senpai, see you later.
Don't go! Ai!
Yes. I managed to fool her.
Yes, it should be fine.
Welcome home!
What would you like to order, Master?
I'm done.
Good work.
Thanks.
So Ai got assaulted.
Yeah. But she's denying it.
That's the way it always happen.
They've already brainwashed her.
What do you mean?
You'd better stay on guard.
They'll come after you again.
I've been waiting for this... for this day.
For this time to come!
Who's there!?
What are you doing?
R-Reisa...
It's you, isn't it?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Lowering yourself to this...
You poor man.
Shut up!
Know your place!
You're in my hands now!
I can get away with treating you any way I want.
No! Stop it, Koya!
Never heard of him! Never! That's not my name!
Come on, raise your ass.
Please! Stop it!
You're soaking wet.
I know you like this.
That's not true!
How much longer can you keep that
self-righteous expression on your face?
No. No!
This time... take this!
Very nice!
That's a great look for you!
Reisa! You're actually a very lewd girl!
I like it this way!
Harder. Harder!
I'm almost there!
0-Oh, no!
Wh-What's this?
The ultimate pleasure
on a beautiful night
Who did this?
Oh, no! I'm wet.
Oh. no! I'm wet.
I can't do this. I can't.
Let me help.
Oh, Segawa-san?
Thank you.
Here you go.
Because I told you about that place,
you've had a rough time.
It's not your fault, Segawa-san.
I want you to have faith in me! I'm on your side!
Segawa-san...
If there's anything I can do to
help, I want you to tell me!
Um...
I can't stand seeing you suffer like this!
I've got an idea!
I'll take you for a drive. It'll make you feel better.
Okay.
That injury...
Oh, this?
I accidentally burned myself tossing
away a cigarette butt.
I see. You'd better be more careful.
This way, okay.
Is everything okay?
Welcome home, Master!
See you later.
Wh-What's this?
I'm going to rescue Ai.
Yuzuki-chan!
If I'm gone too long, then please call the police.
But you can't go!
I need to rescue Ai!
Then please don't be so reckless.
We have no idea how sick these guys are.
Welcome to my mansion.
Or perhaps I should say, "Welcome back".
I've come to take Ai home.
Then please do so.
But only if they want to go home.
Take a look!
No!
Too bad. Seems like they don't want to leave.
Ai! Reisa-san!
Snap out of it! Please!
What are you doing? Let go! Let go of me!
Yuzuki-kun, I warned you not to come here.
What are you talking about?
Because you... will no longer
be able to face me again.
Segawa-san?
Segawa-san...
No! Help me!
Segawa-san, that hurts!
You knew all along what you were like.
In fact, you wanted this to happen more than I did.
That's not true!
No!
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen like this?
No. No!
Segawa-san, I'm begging you.
I'm not the Segawa you know anymore.
You're such a slut.
Stop  it!
How about this?
What now?
I want you to become even more beautiful.
P-Please stop this.
Not this. I don't like this.
You'll never be able to escape from this ecstasy.
Reisa-san!
Harder! Harder, please!
Please stop it!
You still don't understand.
You're already soaking wet.
Yuzuki, you really are a slutty woman.
Yes, I am.
I'm almost there!
Yes!
Amazing! How amazing!
Harder. Harder, please!
Yes!
Yes. Yes...
Are you satisfied, Yuzuki-kun?
Thank you very much, Master.