Sorry for the wait.
Miran-senpai...
Um, would it have been better if
I wasn't wearing my underwear?
No, uh...
I was just taken aback by how beautiful you are.
You mean it?
Thank you!
This is Miran-senpai's body.
It's soft all over!
How about we get started?
Y-Yeah.
Huh?
How do I do this?
Wait.
This is so embarrassing.
Miran-senpai...
Come here.
They're so soft.
My fingers are just melting into them.
Munetaka-kun, your hands are pretty big, huh?
Miran-senpai!
Please be gentle.
Y-Yeah!
I love you, Munetaka.
So let's have sex.
Let's make a baby together.
M-Munetaka-kun?
You got small.
Um... I might be a little too nervous.
O-Oh, really?
That's okay. I'll help you get big again.
S-Sorry.
I basically forced this onto you.
It's not your fault.
You didn't force me...
I'm... I'm gonna go home for today.
I'll see you around campus!
Miran-senpai!
Bye!
At the time, I had no idea what was going on.
I never thought that I'd be going through sex hell after that.
I want to tell you.
About this prologue of love.
Our hands together.
Makes my heart beat faster.
Let's play out
this rainbow melody
Baku Ane 2 Otouto Ippai shibbochauzo!
Underneath this sky after the rain,
I see your fading footprints.
And your face on this asphalt.
The heart that you just happened to steal away.
Everything's in slow motion.
My heart is starting to beat so hard.
Leap over your pessimistic past self.
And aim for the light to grant your wonderful wish.
I want to reach you.
With this gentle breeze.
But the closer I get, the more flustered I get.
Danger alarms are sounding off in my head?!
Your sun-like smile caught me by surprise.
It's so blinding, it's twinkling so bright.
Let's start our memories of love.
Munetaka?
I'm coming in.
Hey!
You're lazing around first thing in the morning again!
Morning...
Don't tell me that you're planning
on skipping classes today too?
Wh-What about you, Ritsuka-nee-san?
Aren't you going to the law office today?
My shift starts in the afternoon.
Good grief. I don't have any recollection of
raising you to be such a lazy human being.
I might need to retrain you from scratch, very thoroughly.
I-I'm fine.
Munetaka, are you sure there's nothing big troubling you?
Huh?
You're acting like you're depressed.
Like you're in pain.
I've been getting that feel from you for a while now.
I'm not really... troubled or anything.
Come here.
Just like old times. Good boy.
Doing this always calmed you down enough
for you to talk to me when you were little.
But I'm not a kid anymore!
Munetaka...
Am I really that untrustworthy to you? I'm your big sister!
Am I not enough to help you out?
I see. That's not good.
Yeah, I think I'm pretty pathetic too.
I'm gonna be impotent for the rest of my life.
I can't forgive that woman for her behavior towards
you failing at sex despite that being your first time.
That harlot infuriates me to no end!
But now I understand.
I'll help you out so that you can gain the confidence
to take the lead with her and become happy.
O-Okay.
First, take off all your clothes.
We're siblings, so I've always held
back, but that won't work anymore.
I'll use my body to beat the techniques
of pleasuring a woman into you.
But we're siblings, so we can do everything other than sex.
As long as you can follow that one rule,
you can do with my body as you like.
Ritsuka-nee-san!
It looks like you can still ejaculate just fine.
Good. We'll move on to the test.
Test?
That's good! Just rub against it.
Don't put it inside!
That's very good, Munetaka!
You're moving your hips very intensely.
You might make me lose my mind!
Ritsuka-nee...
I can't believe this!
I can't believe it feels so good just
doing it between your panties!
It's so hot!
Munetaka...
That was very good, Munetaka.
If I put it inside, I can...
There, there.
Ritsuka-nee-san's not going to be back
from her business trip until tomorrow...
What should I do about dinner?
It's Mashiro-nee!
She has a calm air around her and she has an amazing
body. She's one of the most popular casters on air.
She might be my cousin, but it's
almost as if she's out of this world.
I think I even wrote her love letters when I was little.
Mu-kun!
Mashiro-nee?!
What are you doing here?!
Ritsuka-onee-chan called me.
She asked me to look after you while she's gone.
Mainly, she wanted me to make you food.
Oh, I see.
The main dish is yellowtail and daikon cooked in soy sauce!
Wow. Isn't yellowtail usually a winter dish?
That's some old thinking.
It's delicious even in the summer.
Really?
It's good!
The flavor is rich and there's
basically no trace of the fish smell.
But what about these rolled omelets?
I can taste the rich smell of the
skipjack tuna... it's filing my mouth.
I need to be able to make a nutritious
meal for whoever I marry in the future.
Marry?
Alright, now that we're in the
middle of a meal, here's a question.
Mu-kun? Did something happen between you and
your girlfriend? Why don't you tell me everything?
You looked like you were in a lot of pain.
I can't ignore that.
Believe in your big sister and tell me everything.
I can tell where this is going already!
Keep it up, Mu-kun.
If you can hold out against these
breasts that you love so much,
I'm sure you'll be able to take the lead with your girlfriend.
Could we do a more practical lesson instead?
There's something hard in between my butt cheeks.
It's so good! Your thrusting is so intense!
This feels pretty good, but I...
Mu-kun's hot stuff is...
I know it'd feel even better inside you.
Inside...
I wanna put it inside!
Isn't that Takezaka Wakana?
Oh, the princess of Japanese tennis!
She's cute and strong! Not to mention that rack!
They're the best, aren't they?
Wakana-nee-san...
She's my second sister.
Ever since she left the house after that happened...
I haven't seen her since.
Wakana-nee-san...
There was slight rain in the morning,
The lights are on?
but it will practically be raining all
over this area when it hits this time.
What's going on? I definitely turned off the TV too.
Sports watch!
I have some unfortunate news today.
Takesaka Wakana: Dropping out of the All US'Open due to injury
The famous player, Takesaka Wakana,
will be taking a break after a knee injury.
Wait, could it be that...
Wakana-nee is here?!
Gotcha!
Hi, Munetaka.
Wakana-nee!
Why are you...
Why?
Of course I'm here to have sex with my darling.
You still haven't given up on that?
Give up?
Why would I?!
Listen here. I love you just as much as I love tennis.
So let's have the sex that we were never able to have.
I love you, Munetaka.
So let's have sex, okay?
Let's make a baby together.
I get it...
When I was about to have my first time with
Miran-senpai and saw that flashback, that was really...
Huh? Miran? First time?
Hey, Darling, tell me... who's Miran?
Would you mind telling your
onee-chan everything? Just trust me.
I know where this is going!
You might have been limp with that Miran girl,
but you're hard as a rock right now, Darling.
Th-That can't be...
Look, your body's so honest, Darling.
That's because you want to be connected
with your true lover, not some random bimbo.
That can't be true!
Seeing that look on your face...
Nope. I can't wait any longer!
We might be siblings, but let's have some baby making sex!
Who cares about some silly law!
You colossal high level idiot!
Good grief. Were you really thinking of
crossing that line with your brother?
You really think that would be okay?
You have a point, but do you really think
you have the right to be lecturing her?
Mashiro?
Why are you here?
I washed the clothes that got dirty when
I was having a dirty lesson with Mu-kun.
Wa... Wait a second, Mashiro-chan!
Dirty lesson? What are you talking about?
Weren't you teaching him how to have sex after Mu-kun
just couldn't get it up with his girlfriend, Ritsuka-nee-san?
You were listening?
What's up with that?!
You scold me to no end and then do that?!
How dare you!
– Ritsuka-nee...
– Hey, Darling! Tell them off! Tell them that I'm enough for you!
– Mashiro-nee...
You both tried so hard for me, but...
I'm sorry it ended up like this.
Triple commotion!
In any case, it's my duty as the eldest daughter to continue
these lessons to make sure he can properly have sex.
I understand where you're coming
from, but you're his sister.
Crossing that line might be a
problem for you, but if it was me...
C-Crossing the line?!
Okay, okay, everyone stop right there.
Don't you all get it?
This is a battle between all three of us women.
Let's put an end to this feud.
Put an end?
We'll all have one dirty lesson with Munetaka
and he'll choose one of us based off of them.
It's time for the re-ignition of our lovers' war!
It's hard to know the right
direction we should be heading in.
I'll follow you everywhere and anywhere you go, brother!
Wait, what are you talking about?!
Ritsuka-nee, stop Wakana-nee...
So be it then!
This is my duty as the eldest
daughter of the Takesaka family!
They're nothing but little chicks.
They're but failures who can't even pass the
bar exam. I'll show you the power of the elite.
It's futile... so futile!
It's all futile!
The only one who can legally marry Mu-kun is me!
And now...
We will now go into our own separate rooms.
Then you'll go into each of our rooms
and take our sex lessons one by one.
And then afterwards, you'll
choose whoever's lesson was best.
And then you can continue their lesson from there.
Darling, I don't forgive adultery.
They're all so laid back, they don't even realize yet.
They don't know how badly I want
to cum inside someone right now.
Wakana-nee, those clothes...
Yeah, nostalgic, isn't it?
Guys love high school girls, don't they?
Well, yeah...
Okay, how about we pick up where we left off that day?
Inside... feels good...
Inside a girl...
Wakana-nee!
Your boobs are so soft!
You're gonna violate me now, aren't you, Darling?
You're being so rough.
Sorry!
It's okay. Hit me with all of your passion!
Suck it.
Suck it!
You can even bite them if you want.
Do whatever you want with them!
Your fingers are so intense Munetaka!
Hit me... Hit with all your unfulfilled desires!
This is amazing, your insides are so warm and wet.
Why do you like me so much, Wakana-nee?
I've loved you ever since we were little!
You've always been my hero, Munetaka.
I think you know this already, but
I was really timid when I was little.
Yeah, you were.
I was always bullied by the boys in our neighborhood.
But you'd always run to save me.
It's okay now, Wakana-nee.
That's when I knew.
I was the heroine tied to you, the Prince.
Really?
So that means, Wakana-nee...
She's been living her life, always in love with me?
Hey, Darling?
It's finally time. I've believed and waited all this time.
So let's go all the way today.
Wakana!
Darling!
It's so tight! I'm getting caught deep inside!
Darling, it's like you're splitting my body into two!
If you spread me so rough like that, I'm gonna...
Darling?
Wakana-nee?
I want to do it from behind!
Wakana-nee, I can't think about anything except cumming!
Cum, Darling!
I'll take it all in!
I feel like I'm gonna fall apart!
Please, Munetaka! Make every last part of my body all yours!
Wakana-nee!
N-No, I can't... I can't...
This is too good!
I love you! I love you! I love you so much!
Wakana-nee!
No more! Any more than this and I'm gonna cum!
Darling, your cum is...
It's filling up my insides!
Wakana-nee...
Munetaka...
We're finally connected now.
Yeah.
Okay, now sit there.
Okay.
Last but not least...
I'll clean you up.
Wakana-nee?
You look like you're about to keel over...
I'm cumming!!
Is my body going to hold out until the end?
I was getting tired of waiting, Munetaka.
R-Ritsuka-nee!
You're too sexy!
I thought you were supposed to be more modest!
I'm trying my best to get out of my
element so I can make you happy.
Don't you remember? I told you that
you can do anything you want to me.
What I'm saying is... mess me up good!
Ritsuka-nee-san!
Tell me, Munetaka, how long are
you planning to keep doing that for?
Why don't you move it along already?!
R-Right...
Now, come.
Ritsuka-nee, sorry!
Seriously?! You irritate me so much!
What are you doing?! Look at the table.
The table?
Wh... Are those...
Stop getting surprised by every little thing!
I'm the eldest daughter of the Takesaka family!
The one who should be leading you in
these lessons isn't Wakana or Mashiro.
It should be me!
Really?
I'm your lover right now, Munetaka!
That's the setting right now, so stop being indecisive!
Just keep going!
Okay, I got it, Ritsuka-nee!
I'll keep going!
Munetaka, you're so good!
Your dick is piercing into me so deep inside!
Don't be so rough, or I'm gonna...
I'm... I'm...
Munetaka, this is really...
You're stirring up my insides!
I can't...
I can't go on...
Ritsuka-nee!
I'm sorry. I just like you so much, I couldn't help myself!
You... like me?
Yeah, I love you Ritsuka-nee!
Munetaka, I love you too...
Love me as a woman, not your sister, Munetaka!
Munetaka... I love you!
Let me hear your cute moans, Ritsuka-nee!
I love you!
Your hard thing keeps pounding against me!
It's making me so happy!
Munetaka...
Munetaka, right now, I...
What's the matter?
I just got impregnated.
Munetaka, let's raise a kind and
compassionate child together.
What?!
I see. So we all got to have our own
thorough lessons with Munetaka.
No one can come in between my
unbreakable bond with Darling.
I think Mu-kun's completely become my slave though.
I have Munetaka's child inside me.
That's just your own delusion, Ritsuka-nee-san!
So, what do you think, Darling?
So, what do you think,
Munetaka?
Munetaka-kun?
U-Uh...
I think you were all so good that I can't decide.
I'm getting home a lot later than I thought I would.
Huh?
Is that a companion star?
It's so pretty.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Within the valley of boobs.
Hole in one.
Good work, Darling!
We're going to milk our little brother lots!