Please take one!
It's a maid cafe! Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Master.
Please say when.
Well, I'll go take out the trash.
Um...
May I help you?
You're Asana-san from Muko-Muko, aren't you?
Uh, yes.
I'm a huge fan. May I have your autograph?
Is that all?
Bakunyuu Maid Gari
Where am I?
Awake, I see.
Welcome to my mansion, my divine maid, Miss Arsen.
What's this for?
Allow me to introduce the garçons of Maid Masters.
No! Stop it!
Oh,no.
Don't! I'll call the police.
Th-That hurts!
Hey there, you mustn't be too rough.
She's our very valued customer.
S-Stay away!
You're beautiful.
Even more beautiful than when I saw you in the cafe.
No. No...
Amazing. I can't hold back anymore.
Yes. I love it!
Well then, shall we move on?
Bring it to me.
What's that for?
You needn't worry.
Now. for the new students,
there are many different types of people.
Normal and abnormal.
Normal people will do normal sorts of things,
and abnormal people will do abnormal sorts of things.
Manga?
These two types are polar opposites,
And maid fetish manga to boot?
and are very interesting to study.
So a word on the normal people...
Senpai!
Miwako-senpai!
Take a look at this.
I just finished it!
It's my scenario notes for this month's manga.
I thought I wouldn't make it!
I don't want to have to say this,
but you really need to pay more attention in class.
You might be right about that.
It's cool that you're a mangaka,
but you're also a student.
Well...
Hi, Miori speaking.
Huh? A shift?
You mean tomorrow?
But I can't do that!
Yeah. Yeah, I get it. I'll try to work it out.
Senpai, horrible news!
Asuna is quitting the restaurant!
Asuna?
Oh, she's a girl who works where I do.
You have a job on top of everything?
Of course I do!
It helps me with story ideas in any case.
So they need someone to cover her shifts this week.
I've got it! Why don't you cover for her?
I'm sure you'd look great in the uniform!
And your boobs are nice and big.
H-Hold it, AI!
Come on. Consider it a personal favor to me.
But I can't do that.
I can't do it either!
I'll end up flunking out of school!
You're really a handful.
Just for a bit!
I'm begging you!
Then, I guess just for a day.
Hooray! I'm eternally grateful!
I'd better contact the Chief.
By the way, what kind of restaurant is it?
I haven't really had a job before.
It's a maid fetish cafe.
A maid fetish cafe?
So you're a college student?
Yes. I'm a Criminal Psychology major.
That's nice.
I've been looking for someone like you for a while.
But I'm just filling in for today.
Then let's get down to business. Here's your uniform.
Let me know if it's too small.
Wow, Senpai, you look so cute!
Very nice.
And for your name... I was thinking "Yuzuki".
"Yuzuki"?
Yeah. Because you're the rich-girl type.
You have a very dignified air.
Oh, dear.
Good morning.
Ah, Reisa-kun,
this is our new recruit, Shirasaki Miwako-kun.
Please teach her our system.
Okay.
Thanks for the opportunity.
Reisa-san is the number one employee here.
Employee Manual: Service and Manners
For starters, read this. It explains everything.
Um, this is my first time working in service.
Don't get the wrong idea.
This isn't a dingy place like a cabaret bar.
It's a place where men just fantasize about us.
Shirasaki-san... are you...
Huh?
the heir to the Shirasaki Group?
Y-Yes.
You think this is a game.
But going at it half-heartedly will hurt our business.
Коуа, why did you take her on?
I had no choice. We're shorthanded.
Is that all?
Reisa, understand where I'm coming from.
We've been losing business lately.
Are you saying it's my fault?
I apologize.
Asuna quit because those guys fucked her.
Yeah.
You worthless dog.
W-Welcome back, Master.
I like that girl.
She seems so sweet.
And those tits! I can't stand it!
Welcome back, Master.
Goodness. They said it was just for one day.
S-Sorry for the wait, Master.
Are you new here?
Uh, yes.
Your name?
I'm Yuzuki.
Ah! Segawa-san! Nice to see you again!
Hi, Ai-chan.
Segawa-san is the editor of a magazine!
So you're a journalist?
Nothing that important.
He's investigating  a certain crime.
A crime?
The infamous Akihabara maid rape incidents.
You hadn't heard, Senpai?
Maids have been targeted recently.
It's really scary!
The police are looking into it,
but I'd like to catch the criminals myself.
He's our knight in shining armor!
Nice work!
Good night.
Reisa...
What a day.
I was supposed to stay there just for a day.
But, I think it's kind of fun.
Stay calm and behave.
Her body's more amazing than I thought it would be.
But are you sure it's okay?
We didn't get the go-ahead.
I can't wait for that shit!
You! Hold down her shoulders!
I can't hold back anymore!
0-Oh, shit!
Run for it!
Senpai, you were attacked?
Ai. don't shout it out like that.
But Senpai!
Don't worry.
I'm just glad I finally got some use out of
the self-defense techniques i learned.
So you're okay?
But I can't get over it!
Those bastards who attacked you... they'll pay!
Thanks, Ai.
So, what kind of guys were they?
There were three of them.
They were all wearing strange masks,
and they had a knife.
They're the Maid Masters.
The Maid Masters?
They're the guys who target us maids,
After they've finished, they use the knife to cut
off part of the maid uniform as a souvenir.
they're  perverts.
Part of the maid uniform?
If it happens again, let's catch them together!
With our bare hands!
All prepared.
Ai, are you serious?
Yes, I am!
Don't be so reckless.
We should leave this to the police.
No. I can't stand to sit back passively
while you're targeted!
I'm grateful, but how exactly can you help?
Aw, come on, come on!
You can be the bait.
Reisa-san...
What do you mean, "bait"?
What do you mean, "bait"!
Ai will lure them out,
and if things get too dangerous, we'll scream for you.
Then we'll call the police.
I think that might work!
Let's do it, Senpai!
I'll be the bait.
I sense something  abnormal about
the minds of those criminals.
Like how they cut off a part of the maid's uniform,
and how they tried to rape me but failed.
I get the feeling they'll try again.
Very well. I'll also act as bait.
Reisa-san?
Just a disclaimer.
I'm not doing this because I care about you.
I'm doing this to help all the maids.
Senpai, rest easy. Ai is on guard for you!
Um...
Y-Yes?
You're handing out postcards, aren't you?
May I have one?
Oh, sure.
Not so fast! Asshole!
Pardon me! Pardon me!
It was just a misunderstanding!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Something wrong?
Reisa-san!
False alarm. Ai jumped to conclusions.
Where is she?
Ai? Where did she go?
Maybe she went back?
Don't tell me...
Hey! Yuzuki!
Ai! Where are you? Ai?
Ai!
Senpai!
Don't disappear so suddenly!
You scared us!
I'm sorry.
Is there something going on in this building?
Uh, no! Nothing at all!
Welcome back, Mistress Miwako!
The way you address me..
can't be changed, can it?
You're the real thing, after all.
Maid Masters. Based in Akihabara, they are
a rape organization that targets maids."
No one knows their true identities yet,"
but they never let their targets escape."
Disturbingly, their victims never file police
reports and end up joining them."
That is the main reason they are difficult to trace."
That was definitely Asuna.
But why?
Those who fall victim to the Maid Masters
are bewitched by their demonic
allure and end up enslaved.
What did he mean by "demonic allure"?
Did Asuna become their slave?
The manga artist in me can't leave this plot alone!
But...
Listen. You must not act alone.
Senpai...
Miwako-senpai!
I'm sorry!
The basement is suspicious.
It looks like a closet.
Wow! I've never seen or worn
a maid outfit like this before!
They're all yours if you wish.
Welcome to my mansion.
So you finally showed your ugly face! You maid killer!
How impudent.
You like these clothes. Admit it.
You may try them on if you wish.
The police will be here any minute!
Huh? There's no reception here?
Fine, then how about this!
Give them back!
Just as I thought.
She was unable to hold back her curiosity.
Oh, no.
So you woke up.
No, I didn't.
Well then. The forbidden world...
Don't do that!
No! Please stop that!
Very nice.
Don't do it!
It's flowing. All of Ai. All of Ai!
Please. Please...
What? I couldn't hear you.
Please hurry up.
Be more specific.
Please put it in.
Even more specific.
Y-Your cock, Master. Put it into me.
I couldn't hear that.
Your cock, Master. Please put it in my pussy!
If you want it that bad...
then you've been reborn.
Everyone, your turn now.
My turn now!
Bring it out.
Miwako-senpai
Why doesn't she answer?
That's strange
She usually doesn't miss work without permission.
Is something the matter?
Reisa-san! I haven't been able
to reach Ai since last night.
She just keeps worrying me.
It couldn't be... Not her, too?
That would just be too cruel.
Hello? Ai?
Huh? Segawa-san?
I understand. I'll be there right away!
Yuzu-kun?
He found Ai! I'm going to get her!
This is the place.
Excuse me? I'm with Muko-Muko Maid Cafe.
I heard my friend who works there is here right now.
Excuse me.
Ai!
What happened to you? Wake up!
Don't worry, she's just tired.
Who's there?
You must be silenced.
What's this?
Isn't it wonderful?
Welcome to my mansion.
So you're the criminal behind the rape incidents!
Criminal? That's not quite right.
We have fun with our customers.
We grant them pleasures they've never felt before.
As proof of this, no one has filed
a criminal complaint against us.
That's a phony excuse!
You don't know the first thing about how
a girl behaves when she's in pain!
You'll understand that yourself in time.
What do you think you're doing?
Well then, Yuzuki-kun.
Time to have a taste of our ceremony.
Senpai.
Ai! S-Stop it, Ai!
I've always liked you, Senpai.
D-Don't!
Senpai, you're already so wet.
Ai, stop it! I'm begging you!
Senpai, you're cute when you're flustered.
The fun will become ever more intense, Yuzuki-kun.
This is your first time, isn't it?
Senpai, I promise you'll love it.
At first, it might hurt a little.
But eventually, you'll be able to forget the pain.
Please, stop this.
Ai! Ai!
Ai, Where are you?
S-Someone! Call... the police.
Yuzu-kun.
Murasaki-san?
What's happened?
Ai is... Ai is still trapped inside!
Ai?
The headquarters for the Maid Masters
is in the basement of this building!
And they're holding Ai prisoner!
Is that true?
Anyway, we must call the police!
That's not right, Senpai!
Ai?
Sorry to worry you!
That was just an act.
An act? What do you mean?
You see, I asked for their help
in researching my manga.
But what I did to you... I just got carried away.
So please don't call the police.
I see. So that's all it was. You had us scared there.
Now wait a minute!
Those guys admitted that they
were involved in the crimes.
I heard them!
You're mistaken.
But...
Anyway, Ai is safe.
Let's go home, Yuzu-kun.
I still have a meeting with them.
Senpai, see you later.
Don't go! Ai!
Yes. I managed to fool her.
Yes, it should be fine.
Welcome home!
What would you like to order, Master?
I'm done.
Good work.
Thanks.
So Ai got assaulted.
Yeah. But she's denying it.
That's the way it always happen.
They've already brainwashed her.
What do you mean?
You'd better stay on guard.
They'll come after you again.
I've been waiting for this... for this day.
For this time to come!
Who's there!?
What are you doing?
R-Reisa...
It's you, isn't it?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Lowering yourself to this...
You poor man.
Shut up!
Know your place!
You're in my hands now!
I can get away with treating you any way I want.
No! Stop it, Koya!
Never heard of him! Never! That's not my name!
Come on, raise your ass.
Please! Stop it!
You're soaking wet.
I know you like this.
That's not true!
How much longer can you keep that
self-righteous expression on your face?
No. No!
This time... take this!
Very nice!
That's a great look for you!
Reisa! You're actually a very lewd girl!
I like it this way!
Harder. Harder!
I'm almost there!
0-Oh, no!
Wh-What's this?
The ultimate pleasure
on a beautiful night
Who did this?
Oh, no! I'm wet.
Oh. no! I'm wet.
I can't do this. I can't.
Let me help.
Oh, Segawa-san?
Thank you.
Here you go.
Because I told you about that place,
you've had a rough time.
It's not your fault, Segawa-san.
I want you to have faith in me! I'm on your side!
Segawa-san...
If there's anything I can do to
help, I want you to tell me!
Um...
I can't stand seeing you suffer like this!
I've got an idea!
I'll take you for a drive. It'll make you feel better.
Okay.
That injury...
Oh, this?
I accidentally burned myself tossing
away a cigarette butt.
I see. You'd better be more careful.
This way, okay.
Is everything okay?
Welcome home, Master!
See you later.
Wh-What's this?
I'm going to rescue Ai.
Yuzuki-chan!
If I'm gone too long, then please call the police.
But you can't go!
I need to rescue Ai!
Then please don't be so reckless.
We have no idea how sick these guys are.
Welcome to my mansion.
Or perhaps I should say, "Welcome back".
I've come to take Ai home.
Then please do so.
But only if they want to go home.
Take a look!
No!
Too bad. Seems like they don't want to leave.
Ai! Reisa-san!
Snap out of it! Please!
What are you doing? Let go! Let go of me!
Yuzuki-kun, I warned you not to come here.
What are you talking about?
Because you... will no longer
be able to face me again.
Segawa-san?
Segawa-san...
No! Help me!
Segawa-san, that hurts!
You knew all along what you were like.
In fact, you wanted this to happen more than I did.
That's not true!
No!
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen like this?
No. No!
Segawa-san, I'm begging you.
I'm not the Segawa you know anymore.
You're such a slut.
Stop  it!
How about this?
What now?
I want you to become even more beautiful.
P-Please stop this.
Not this. I don't like this.
You'll never be able to escape from this ecstasy.
Reisa-san!
Harder! Harder, please!
Please stop it!
You still don't understand.
You're already soaking wet.
Yuzuki, you really are a slutty woman.
Yes, I am.
I'm almost there!
Yes!
Amazing! How amazing!
Harder. Harder, please!
Yes!
Yes. Yes...
Are you satisfied, Yuzuki-kun?
Thank you very much, Master.