Hey bro, so,
you play soccer or something?
Uh, yes.
I do. But I got a little injured, so I'm
heading home to rehabilitate.
That sounds tough.
Well, slow and steady wins the race they say.
You'll be fine.
It's also nice to rely on your parents
once in a while isn't it?
Unfortunately my parents are abroad on business.
I think my four elder sisters will be waiting for me today.
Oh? So you'll be like the young master
of the house or something?
It's so nostalgic. I haven't been home in a while.
Ryou?
Oh, it's really Ryou!
Ryou-kun!
On one, two...
Welcome back, Ryou-kun!
Welcome back, Ryou!
Baku Ane
We"ll Milk Our Brother!
The second daughter, Yurine.
Second Daughter
Yurine
Gravure idol currently at the height
of her popularity.
My favourite foods are mangoes and bananas!
The first daughter, Noemi.
FIRST DAUGHTER
NOEMI
The H-cupped and biracial doctor.
My bust size is 98.
Fourth daughter Naru,
FOURTH DAUGHTER
NARU
A school-type beauty with
many secret admirers.
my favourite anime is "Pineapple Cake Duet”!
Third dauthter Mio,
THIRD DAUGHTER
MIO
The cool beautiful university student,
Miss Campus of her school.
my s-sensitive spot is... my clitoris...
With four beautiful elder sisters,
Hayasaki Ryoushirou, that is me.
LAST SON
RYOUSHIROU
The youngest brother,
who always feels diffident
surrounded by four sisters
Although I have to come back home to rehabilitate...
Well... I wonder what will happen from here...
I’m back!
Ryou! Can I get you to take out your laundry?
Oh. There's a bag around there, you can just take it.
Geez, such a spoiled child.
E-Eh??
Ryou, why do you have these...
these lolicon mags and perverted videos in your bag?
Eh!? What is that?
Huh? There’s a cute letter in here, too.
Let's see...
I heard that Hayasaki-kun liked younger girls.
I’m quite a lot younger than Hayasaki-kun,
and I wouldn't mind having sex with Hayasaki-kun.
Please go out with me.
Eh?
Ryoushirou-kun, is it true that you like younger sisters?
I'd like to become Ryoushirou-kun's sister.
I'm quite a bit younger, so you don't have to hold back.
Heart...
Wait, wait sis! What is that?
I have no idea what that is or what's going on...
We're having a family meeting!
First off, why do you have these kinds of things?
Please explain.
I don't think there's any explaining needed here.
The reason any boy would have these things... well...
Hmph, how filthy.
What?
Just look at that!
It's all younger sister, younger
sister and younger sister stuffs!
You pedophile!
That’s what makes me sad, too...
That of all things?
Wait, I have to say this again,
but none of these are mine!
Not this DVD “I Love the Perverted Onii-chan"?
Nope.
This comic "There's No Way My Younger
Sister Could be so Sexy", neither?
No!
All these fan letters from juniors insisting
sexual relationships with Ryou-kun, no?
All of them, no!
How unmanly of you.
Eh?
These books and DVDs and letters
are all yours, aren't they?
Just admit it already.
As I've been saying all this time they're not!
Oh, I know.
It must have been the other members
from my club activities.
It's their prank.
See? How unmanly!
You're even lying now.
More importantly, you like younger
sisters while having elder ones?
How can you even get so unmanly like this?
Treasuring these fan letters from
younger girls so carefully,
do you really like younger sisters so much? You pervert.
Who do you mean by pervert?
It's Ryou, of course!
You like younger sisters and younger girls,
You're just a clumsy failure who won't face reality!
That’s enough.
H-hey, Ryou!
Ryou-kun!
It might be best to leave him alone for now.
That's true, but...
I tried sleeping in to avoid facing everyone,
and it's ten already.
They've all gone to school or work, right?
Yuri-nee!
Can I bother you for a sec?
Yeah, come in.
Sorry about yesterday.
I guess we were too rash about it.
Well yeah...
But Yuri-nee, in fact you’re still suspecting me, right?
Ryou is sure sharp.
Well, that stuff did come out from my bag.
But you know Ryou, I really want to trust you.
Yuri-nee... thanks.
Yep.
Hey Ryou, by the way, could you
close the curtains for a sec?
But, why?
Don't worry, just do it!
The lights, too!
Why?
Because!
Alright!
Now with some indirect lighting...
What are you trying to do, Yuri-nee?
Boo!
Hey Ryou...
What do you think of Onee-chan's body?
Eh... very stylish, I think.
Not that, but more like, will you get erect or not?
What are you saying so suddenly!?
What is it?
Ryou...
This isn't sudden at all, you know.
You know, ever since we were kids,
I'd do anything for you.
These are... what my classmates say they jerk off to...
Yuri-nee’s...
To make sure Ryou is no longer a pedophile,
I've got to use my body to help you recover!
Yuri-nee's bare boobs...
The currently incredibly popular gravure model...
Yuri-nee’s bare boobs!
Here. You can do all you want with them.
It's the first time I've shown a guy
my boobs or let him touch them,
But you know,
I'll be giving a lot of firsts to Ryou today, okay?
So then... let Onee-chan have Ryou's first, too...
Wow, your penis is so hard already!
Onee-chan is so happy!
To think that this would...
You didn't think that as a younger brother
you'd have your penis held by me?
Well, we're moving on.
Wow! Ryou's penis is so big.
Ryou's penis is so hot, it's wonderful.
It feels like I'm heating up just from holding it.
The penis is so honest.
Even if you don't say anything, by the way it’s
twitching I instantly know you feel good.
Ryou, focus on Onee-chan's hand.
It feels too good!
How cute!
Be sure to feel real good!
I'll use my mouth, too.
The penis of the Ryou I love...
Yu-Yuri-nee...
What is it?
Are you used to these kinds of things?
Don’t joke around!
Didn't I just tell you it was the
first time I showed my chest?
I was... practicing...
Thinking that...
One day I'd do this for Ryou...
I wanted to use all of my body to serve Ryou...
Stand up, Ryou.
Onee-chan's loves the taste of Ryou.
Give me lots more.
Yuri-nee, amazi...
Ryou, please feel real good from Onee-chan.
No way... every time Ryou's penis rubs
against my throat I get horny...
Now even though they haven't
been touched my nipples are...
Yuri-nee...
It's fine, you don't have to hold back.
You can let it all out!
Let out lots inside Onee-chan's mouth!
Yuri-nee, Yuri-nee...
Cumming!
Amazing... semen won't stop
flowing out of Ryou's penis...
It's wonderful...
I love Ryou's semen!
Ryou's semen was poured deep inside my tummy.
It's still warm even inside me...
Geez, Ryou.
Getting your sister covered in semen like this...
But it's alright.
Until my precious brother is no longer a lolicon,
I won't refrain from serving you with my body!
I'm not a toy...
Eh? What, what’s wrong, Ryou?
I'm not Nee-san's toy!
Eh?? Why? What happened, Ryou!?
Look at that!
Woah, amazing!
What a beauty!
She's exactly my type!
Huh, Ryou?
Why is he here?
Hey mister, would you like to have fun today?
A mountain of boobs!?
What's wrong, Ryou?
Spacing out at a place like this...
I got them.
Th-Thanks.
Sorry about that, having you treating
me and even getting the drinks...
What are you saying?
You're injured, so I'm supposed to do this.
Besides, yesterday... it was my bad.
I'm reflecting on it.
Mio-nee...
But then again, what were you doing
there with nothing on you?
Oh, that was because Yuri-nee had...
Wait, I can't say that...
There's no way I could tell her I did that with Yuri-nee!
Ryou?
You can really be read like a book!
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Phone call, phone call.
Hello?
Ryou?
Yu...
Ryou, I'm sorry about what happened this morning...
Onee-chan won't have those selfish rampages anymore.
I'll be sure to have lots of love and
that Ryou is also satisfied, so...
Wait... not right now...
Ehl? Ryou... could it be that you don't
even want to phone Onee-chan?
I'm so sorry!
No, that's not it...
Too suspicious.
Ryou?
If it's to Ryou, Onee-chan's happy
to give her virginity any time!
If it's for Ryou to recover from being a lolicon,
I can do anything!
This time I'll be gentle to Ryou's penis!
I'll make Ryou learn to appreciate adult woman!
Yuri-neesan...
Yurine-chan, the shoot is about to start!
Where are we going, Mio-nee?
To punish you!
How ridiculous... just be quiet and follow!
Wow, so cute!
Eh!?
Wait, aren't we in the red-light district!?
You're joking, right?
Um, it's kinda hard to work as a joke...
Mio-nee!
Woah, so this is what it's like inside...
What are you planning to do here, Mio-nee?
I-It's... It's, It’s punishment!
First of all take off all your clothes!
If not I'll tell Mom and Dad about everything
you did with Yuri-nee-san!
That's not fair!
Just do it!
They're... in the way..
Move it.
Eh?
Your hands. Don't hide.
I-It's tiny!
Why aren't you hard!?
You're in a hotel with a woman you'd make
your girlfriend and you're naked!
When's the time to get excited?
It's now!
Just get it erect!
I can't get hard. There's no way I could...
See? See!?
You big liar!
Not a single word you say is true!
I understand the situation.
But why is it Yuri-nee-san helping you recover?
Eh?
So do you mean that...
Compared to Yuri-nee-san, I... Um...
You didn't ask me because I wasn't attractive enough?
What are you saying?
Mio-nee is very attractive. You're very cute.
C-Cute?
Yeah. If you weren't my sister I’d want
to have you as my girlfriend,
kind of thing.
Girlfriend!? That's...
You need punishment!
Huh?
You liar, you liar!
Never mind.
Since it's come down to this I'm going
to make you hard no matter what!
I'll make you erect...
Erect...
And I'll make you ejaculate.
Ejaculate!?
That's right! I'll be sure to watch your perverted
loose ahegao when you ejaculate!
I won't forgive you if you don't get hard from this...
Full throttle!
Oh, Ryou!
To think that you'd get so hard
in front of your older sister!
But, you just said you were going to make me erect...
Shut up, you pervert!
Looks like you really need rehabilitation.
It'd be too late If I don't fix you now.
Now come!
Wait...
This way!
Listen.
I've gone all the way to get naked for you,
so take the chance and focus on you rehabilitation.
Mio-nee... how do you know this kind of play?
Do you do it with your boyfriend?
Don’t say something gross like boyfriends!
Gross?
I've never had one before,
and even if I do, there's no way I could
do this with someone so distant!
Eh?
I worked on this in the bathroom at home.
Really?
Yeah!
I was daydreaming that if there ever was a miracle
that I would had sex with Ryou, we'd do this!
Huh?
Mio-nee? Did you always want to have sex with me?
That's... that...
Mio-nee...
I mean...
Mio-nee??
That's, that's right!
You finally get it now?
It's not Ryou that's the pervert, it's me!
I just really, really love my younger brother Ryou...
I'm a perverted sister who just can't
help but want to have sex!
I did everything to hold back and hide it...
I wanted to just take these feelings with me to the grave!
Why aren't you saying anything!?
Uhh...
You just thought I was a gross sister, didn't you!?
You can go ahead and hate me!
You can laugh that I'm a stupid sister who
goes crazy when you say something
like you'd want me as your girlfriend!
I'd never think... that Mio-nee was
thinking of me in this way...
What do I do?
I could just be completely honest...
Please don't come searching for me...
I can't, I can't!
The choices I have now...
Don't be silly.
There's no way I'd dislike Mio-nee.
Huh?
And I won't hide it, I really like Mio-nee, too!
Just as family though.
I see. That's right.
I've said a lot of bad things,
but to be honest I'd never think of
Ryou as a pervert or disgusting...
So we had loved each other all along!
It's more like... uhh...
Well then, let's extend our relationship beyond siblings,
and make it the best love!
I'm so happy, Ryou.
Ryou had always loved Onee-chan, right?
That's why your penis is hard, right?
Uhh...
It's so hard. Ryou's is twitching...
Can you feel my hand? Does it feel good?
Yeah... it does...
Mio-nee...
I can put it in, right?
Eh?
I've always... wanted Ryou's penis...
Always... since we were children...
So, I really can't hold back anymore.
I want Ryou's penis inside me...
It's alright, isn't it? To put it in...
Onee-chan can't wait anymore!
That's... bad! Really bad!
Mio-nee, over here.
I have to make Mio-nee cum first,
and plan it out from there!
Ryou... why...
I want it inside... why don’t you put it inside?
Even though I want Ryou's sturdy thing inside me!
Mio-nee!
Ryou?
No, that's...
Your penis is rubbing against
my clitoris and I'm feeling it!
I'm feeling it too much from around my
pussy, it's getting all messed up!
I'm cumming from just rubbing!
I can't take it anymore, Onee-chan
is cumming! Cumming!
Make me cum, Ryou!
Take me there!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
I can't take this...
Cumming! I'm cumming again...
Onee-chan can come again and again from this!
Stupid Ryou...
Your mind went blank even before you put it in
and just started thrusting without control...
Geez... be patient,
If you had rubbed your penis inside Onee-chan,
It'd feel much, much better!
Could it be that I made the wrong choice...
But we don't have to be in a hurry,
We have lots and lots of chances to have sex from now.
I'm always ready.
For the day I give Ryou my virginity.
Well, let's go home, Ryou.
Yeah...
Ryou?
MENACING
Hey, tell me...
What were you doing with Mio at a place like this, Ryou?
Yuri-nee, this is...
Of course we were sharing love as lovers!
Hey, what are you saying, Mio-nee?
Ryou! Even though you came so much from
my boobs, it was all nothing to you!?
What do you say!?
But just now Ryou was feeling real good
and came lots from my bare legs!
What do your say!?
Just kidding.
Huh?
We are sisters, after all. It's hard to fight the blood.
We had the same feelings...
Nee-san...
If it's come to this, it can't be helped.
Since it's come to this,
we have to have a fair, clean fight and
decide who is more attractive to Ryou!
If it's for Yurine-chan, I'll do my best!
Wait, Yuri-nee, what do you mean, fight?
If you guys work out the misunderstanding,
we should solve the problem, so...
You say something, too, Mio-nee!
Just what I wanted!
Ryou will definitely pick his lover, me!
Yuri-nee will be taken down!
Oh dear, it's hard to put all you
have into such a fight like this.
Well, here we go, Taranosuke.
Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
After that...
Passing the night with nothing happening like this...
Would be simply impossible!
Ryou, it's pointless to pretend to be asleep.
Just face it already.
Guys...
Why are you in your swimsuits?
I already told you!
We're getting Ryou to decide who is more attractive.
We've prepared lots of outfits.
But of course Ryou is going to
choose his lover, me, right?
My heart's racing...
Even though they're my sisters, my mind is going blank!
Eh?
What are you doing? Yuri-nee! Mio-nee!
Be sure to properly decide which one's your favourite!
Of course Ryou is going to choose his lover, me, right?
I can't do this!
If this goes on even my last chastity will be gone!
If it comes to this...
Using my technique, "God Finger”!
I'll make them cum again and again and K.0. them...
And avoid going all the way at all cost!
Ryou, so rough!
No, please, Ryou, I love you!
I want to cum from your penis!
I want the penis, too!
I want to cum from Ryou's penis!
Ryou...
No!
No! I'll cum too much!
I'll cum... if you mess up my pussy like that!
If you rub so hard...
It's just gotten started.
I won't stop until Nee-san can't stand up anymore.
Ryou, so rough!
Ryou's fingers are attacking Onee-chan's
weak spots inside!
No, this is... I can't think straight anymore...
Please stop, Ryou!
It feels so good I'll cum!
Please don’t make Onee-chan cum
from Ryou's fingers anymore!
No more...
Cumming!
My darling Ryou's fingers feel too good!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
Cumming again and again from Ryou...
It feels so good, I’m so happy!
So much blood in my dick, it's hurting.
What's going to happen if I stick
it into that hole right now?
It's gonna be gentle wrapped in soft flesh...
I'm... going in!
Yuri-nee!
Ryou!
No...
It's inside... Ryou's penis is inside!
We're finally connected... Ryou and I...
Ryou...more... my body... you can go even deeper...
Ryou...
Yuri-nee...
It's hitting deep inside...
Ryou's penis is going all the way inside me!
This is Yuri-nee's first...
I'm...
Yuri-nee’s first man...
I don't want to let anyone else have Yuri-nee.
Yuri-nee is all... all mine!
Amazing... amazing, Ryou!
Ryou, I'm...
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
Mio-nee!
I'll cum!
Whenever Ryou rubs his inside
me, I cum again and again!
I think I'm losing my mind...
So Ryou...
Please thrust harder! Drive me crazy!
Ryou's penis is going in and out of me at amazing speed!
I'm so happy!
My dreams came true!
Ryou! Ryou!
Mio-nee...
Ryou...
Ryou I love you... I love you!
Onee-chan loves Ryou!
Grab on!
Ryou!
It's hot! Semen is hot...
Alright, next up, so you'll feel even better when you cum!
W-We'll cosplay for you!
Hayasaki-senpai! Hayasaki-senpai!
Please thrust harder deep into Yurine!
You even break the buttons on your uniform...
These boobs are against school rules!
I'm sorry senpai!
These giant boobs!
Like a cow's!
The man's romance!
Yuri-nee, Yuri-nee, Yuri-nee!
Come, come, come!
So much is coming out...
You felt that good?
I'm so happy...
Boing, boing!
Hey, every time I hop, I can feel you twitching!
Geez, how sloppy of you, Ryou!
No, so rough!
It's too rough, Ryou!
No, boin! I surrender, boin! Please spare me, boin!
No. No, no, no!
I’m cumming! Cumming!
Thank you for the great, tasty meal...
My pleasure, boin...
Go, go, Ryou!
It's almost time for the fifth round!
On your mark, get set...
Go, go, Ryou!
Fight, fight, Ryou!
Ryou!
Squeeze me!
Rub the slutty Yurine who's become an extension
of Ryou's penis, until you're satisfied!
What's with you?
The moment you get behind me
you start thrusting so hard!
You're just like a beast!
How can you even say you're not a pervert with this!
Well... there's no way l could resist after sticking
my dick in a hole that feels so good!
Geez, Ryou, are you saying it's my fault?
Wait, no, Ryou...
Now, tell me who's the real pervert.
It's me!
I'm the pervert!
Mio-nee...
It's coming!
From Ryou's seed bag...
Through the sturdy pipe...
Sperm in swimming towards me!
I'm so happy...
Hey Ryou, less is coming out.
You can do better than that!
Onee-chan's boobs are here to make Ryou feel good!
Ryou can cum all you want with no restraint!
I love this!
Ryou sure makes his mark when he cums!
Spray more, Ryou!
My boobs, too!
Mark them with your thick semen!
No more... my body and soul both belong to Ryou...
The two of us will be sure to bear lots of Ryou's children,
so be sure to give us lots more seed from now!
I give up, give up! Really, no more!
I'm really going to die if I cum again!
No way!
Until your penis has nothing left inside,
you have no right to refuse!
Stop whining and get hard already, you sick pervert!
We'll milk our brother!