It happened during my sophomore year.
I was considering quitting
the college track and field team.
But then...
I had an unforgettable experience
at the empty practise field.
I Pass a Baton to Rena-senpai
(Oh, there's still someone here...)
(It's my senior, Rena...)
"Oh, uhh, you're... Rena, right?"
"...Hm?"
"Oh, it's you. You're a sophomore, right?"
"Getting some free practise in?"
"...Oh, well, I..."
"...Uh, yeah! Yeah, I'm here to practise!"
"That's perfect! I just got here too."
"Hey, let's do some partner stretches. Wanna help we out?"
"Woah! You... you wanna partner stretch with me??"
"...You don't want to?"
"No... I didn't mean...! I'll help! Let's do it!"
"Awesome, thank you. OK, let's get started!"
(Woah... I'm gonna partner stretch with Rena...?)
(...I hope I'm good enough for her...)
One! Two! Three! Four! Five! Six! Seven! Eight!
(At this point, there was probably something wrong with me.)
"Uh, Rena!"
"I've been reading up on the latest training techniques... Do you want to try it?"
"Hmm... I've actually been in a slump recently. The latest techniques, huh?"
"Ok! I'm interested! Let's give it a try."
"Alright... First of all, put this blindfold on."
"You want me to... cover my eyes with this headband...?"
"Yes! You train your senses while blindfolded!"
"You can train all kinds of parts of your body!"
"Huh... OK..."
Once Rena agreed to go along with my idea,
my desires started running wild.
"Have I... got this right?"
"Yes! While blindfolded, you focus more on your muscles!"
"...You don't say...?"
"First, let's test the muscles you don't normally use."
"Huh? OK..."
"Stay like that, on your right side."
"OK!"
"Alright... I'm going to slide the baton under your arm..."
"You have to try and hold on to it, and keep it from getting loose."
"...Got it."
"Alright, here I go."
"Woah, what?! Is this..."
"Is this how a baton feels?"
"Y-Yes. It's definitely a baton."
"Does it feel different with your eyes covered?"
"Uhh... yeah..."
"OK, I'm going to push and pull the baton, so make sure it doesn't get loose."
"I-I'll try..."
"Nng... This... feels kinda... weird..."
"You have to hold it tighter!"
"Don't let it... nngh... get out!"
"O-OK, I'm trying..."
"But, it's starting to get slippery..."
"Oh... hey..."
"Nn... It's... slipping... It's coming out..."
"Angh... Just keep going... a little bit longer..."
"O-OK..."
"Ahh..., this is... too hard..."
"Oh...! Rena... I'm gonna...!"
"Huh? What? What happened?"
(I can't hold it! I'm gonna cum!)
"Um... hey, what? What are you...?"
"Hey... what happened...? Are you alright...??"
"It... It's nothing... I'm fine... haa... haah..."
(I thought she would have noticed for sure... Apparently not...)
"This is pretty tiring... huh..."
"Y-Yeah, I know, right?... Ha ha..."
(...I guess touching her boobs would blow my cover...)
"Alright, so next..."
(What about these tight leggings...?)
(It might work... It's all or nothing!)
"OK, I'm going to give you a massage next."
"I'll start by massaging your thighs!"
"Oh, a massage? OK... so, should I lie like this?"
"Yes. Just rest for now."
"Heh... I might get sleepy, with this blindfold on..."
"That's OK. Alright, I'm going to start."
"Ohh...! What the... what's this??"
"It's baton from before."
"Your lymph system doesn't flow as well under the leggings."
"Oh... really...?"
"If you rub it like this..."
"...it helps the lymph flow better."
"Ah... Hey... This is... kind of... like... Mmm..."
"Is this right...??"
"It seems kind of... nn... weird..."
"Nnn... Hey... did you hear me...?"
"...Hey... come on..."
(Aw man, I'm gonna cum again!)
"Rena... Oh, Rena! ...I'm cumming...!"
"...Huh? What? Coming from where?"
"...Unngh...!!"
"Hey... Uh? Huh? ...What is... Something warm is..."
"uhh... coming out...?"
"No, that's, uh... the, uh..."
"Y-Your blood flow is improving... That's why you're feeling that..."
(Uh... I think... I might've gone too far this time...)
"...Hmm?"
"Hey! What the...!! You jerk! What do you think you're doing?!"
(Oh, crap... It's over... I went too far...)
(Rena finally caught on to what I was doing.
This will probably get me kicked off the team...)
"...God, why did you do... something like that?"
"R-Rena...!"
"Rena, I..."
"I've always loved you!!"
"What??!"
"That's... no reason to... You still shouldn't have done this."
"When I see you, Rena... I start to feel so excited..."
"And I can't... I can't concentrate on practise!"
"I was going to just... quit the team, but..."
"What?"
"...You were that worried... about it?"
(Alright, here I go...! I hope this works!)
"Rena!"
"Huh?! W-What...?"
"Just for today!"
"I just need to get it out of my system, then I can focus on practise!"
"Oh... OK..."
"If you get it out of your system... you won't have to quit the team...?"
"That's right!"
"...Are you sure?"
"Y-Yes!"
"...Mmmm..."
"...OK... Maybe... just a little..."
"You can... do what you like..."
"S-Seriously?!"
"Sure..."
"...And then..."
"...You'll focus on practise, right...?"
"Yes! I will! I can do it!"
"Um... OK... Then, hang on a second..."
That was how I managed to score myself one day
of sexy training with my sexy senior, Rena.
"Woah...! Rena, that uniform..."
"That's the one you wore for the tournament, isn't it?"
"Yeah... I changed, because you got the other one dirty..."
(I can't believe I get to play with Rena in her tourney outfit!)
"...So, what should I do...?"
"First... I want to..."
"...Massage your tits!"
"...When you say massage..."
"You really mean you just want to touch them... right?"
"Heh heh... OK, here I go..."
"Uhn... geez..."
"How is it?"
"...How is what?"
"My... massage..."
"Does it feel good?"
"...shut up..."
"N-No... don't..."
"Rena... you're wearing a sports bra underneath, huh."
"It's hard to..."
"...hard to run..."
"...when they shake... mm..."
"Hey... what are you...?"
"Let me get a better look..."
"...Don't look... It's embarrassing..."
"Would you lie on your back?"
"What... what are you going to do now?"
"I want to use your tits..."
"To get off!"
"Nn... Hurry up... will you?"
"There'll be no time to... uhh... to practice..."
M: "Ohh... Rena... your tits... they're wrapping all around me..."
"Ugh, no... don't say that..."
"Yeah, I like it when you say no... That's more exciting..."
"Gross... you pervert..."
"Be... a little more gentle... please..."
"Ah... no... that's too rough..."
"Ahh... Rena... I'm gonna cum..."
"Ah...! ...I'm coming!!"
"Ugh... Nn..."
"...Get it all out..."
"Huh?? R-Rena??"
"Ugh... you're too rough..."
At first, Rena was overwhelmed by the situation.
But now...
Somewhere along the line, she started getting into it.
"Haah... Geez, you're grinning too much..."
"Now you're already so hard again..."
"When I think about you... No matter how much I cum, it's not enough..."
"How can I think about practise at a time like this?"
"Hmm... well... if it's getting to you this badly..."
"I can understand if you can't think about practise... I guess..."
"Oohh... R-Rena... I'm so happy..."
"Don't be stupid..."
"Happy isn't a word... that one would normally use in this situation..."
"How can I not be happy? My favorite, sweet, Rena is..."
"doing such sexy things for me..."
"You keep talking like you're on top of the world..."
"Maybe you need me to set you straight..."
"Agh...! Rena...! That's too much...!"
"...I won't... let you off the hook so easily..."
"Hahh...! Rena... I'm gonna cum!"
"Oohhh... That felt so good..."
"I couldn't hold on at all..."
"...Huh. It was that good, huh..."
"R-Rena??"
"Woah...! Are you going to give me a blow job?"
"...I told you I wasn't... going to let you off easily, didn't I?"
"How's that...? You like it...?"
"...You dreamed about me..."
"...doing this stuff to you... didn't you...?"
"...You're making such pathetic noises..."
"...You like it, don't you...?"
"OK, maybe I'll..."
"...make if even better for you..."
"...Rena... I can't hold on... You're gonna make me... cum...!"
"That's OK... you can cum... if you want to..."
"Ahhn...! Rena...! I can't... hold on...!"
"I'm gonna blow... right in your mouth...!!"
"How was that? ...Did you get it all out?"
"...That's good."
"Alright... let's get back to training. OK?"
"I think you're got it out of your system by now, haven't you?"
"...Rena..."
"...It's not enough..."
"...Huh? ...What...?"
"I didn't get enough... of you!"
"Ah... Hey, wait..."
"Um... come on..."
"...Please... don't rape me..."
"I only teased you a little bit..."
"Yeah, I... I didn't get enough either, ya know... so..."
"...Rena..."
"I wanna... do it with you..."
"...Be gentle."
"Huh? Rena, you're... totally wet..."
"Ugh... don't tell we that..."
"...Hey, come on..."
"You're so wet... were you really planning on doing any practise?"
"...Don't... tease your senior..."
"Aahn... Hey, don't... pick on me..."
"Aaah... Rena... you're so warm and gooey inside... awesome..."
"Hey, come on... don't say embarrassing stuff like that..."
"Hahn... It's so big... I can feel it going deep inside..."
"All you ever do is practise... you must have been so horny, right?"
"Eww, no... shut up..."
"But look... at how much you're sucking me in down there..."
"And shaking your perfect titties around..."
"...Stop... Don't look..."
"It's better if I nail you like this... Rena..."
"Ahh... No way, this is too much..."
"To think I get to have sex with my senior... with Rena!"
"...I can die happy..."
"What are you... mmmph... talking about?? Once we're finished..."
"uhn... we have to get back to practise..."
"...Hey, that's... too rough...!"
"...Damn... I'm gonna blow my load...!"
"Ohh...! Here it comes...!"
"Rena... I still want more..."
"I get it... it's not enough, yet, huh?"
"Well... I need some more, too..."
"...Ahhnn... It's hitting me deep in the back..."
"You're enjoying it too, Rena... You're so cute..."
"Shut up... Don't say that..."
"Ungh...! Rena... that feels incredible!"
"I'm... mmmm... feeling good too!"
"It turns out you're really pretty freaky..."
"I see you pounding your hips..."
"No, I'm not... Nnn..."
"You're gripping me so tight..."
"No... Hey, come on... Leave me alone..."
"Seeing your face... making that sad expression, makes me wanna..."
"Uhh...! I'm gonna cum again!!"
"...OK... come inside we..."
"I'm gonna cum... inside you...!!"
"Ohh...!!!"
"Did you... blow a big load inside me...??"
"That's good..."
"Hey... I just thought... Do you think..."
"What we just did could be considered training...?"
"Let's do some more training again... OK?"
"But don't tell anyone else in the team know... Promise?"
CV: Phan Masaki
SFX Materials: Shirokuma no Yome
Music: Amacha Music Studio
Production: Amelialtie