No... Takumaru...
Spare me...
It's really embarrassing...
With this Ofuran ability that Akira-sensei gave me,
people around us won't be aware of our presence.
So it's fine to show more of your emotions.
Even if that's the case, it's still embarrassing...
No!
Don't!
Takumaru-kun, doing this in this kind of place...
Narika, it feels good.
Lick me more.
How's this, Takumaru?
I'm cumming.
It's all right. You can cum.
Takumaru, you really came, eh?
Episode 3 : Sennin of the Ancient Times [Edomae & Yui-Nyan Subs]
Haruka, Narika.
Yes!
I'm counting on you.
Jougen Ninja Skill...
Power of the Dragon!
Transform, Heaven Phoenix!
Jougen Ninja Skill...
Power of the Dragon!
Transform, Heaven Phoenix!
Narika-san, we're going.
I'm ready anytime, Haruka-san.
Let's go.
What'll we do?
Let's split up.
A competition, eh?
Yes.
All right. I won't lose to you!
Eat my dust!
Narika, Haruka-san...
Ahead of Haruka-san is the Noroi's barrier!
Haruka, can you hear me?
We've lost Haruka-san!
Dammit! They got ahead of us, huh?
Haruka-san...
Subaru!?
Thank goodness, Subaru!
I've been worried about you all this time.
After the time transcendence ceremony, I was the only person who came to this era.
I thought I wouldn't be able to see you again...
Ow!
Subaru, don't!
What's the matter? Are you aroused?
N-No...
Don't lie.
Your nipples are already hard.
So you are aroused.
S-Subaru, what's happened to you?
I will let you relish the pain that I have suffered!
What do you mean?
No! Stop!
Why would you...
How does it feel?
S-Stop...
Please stop already...
Haruka, your lewd juices are flowing out of your hole.
It's twitching... and begging for a man's dick.
No! Stop it, Subaru...
N-No...
Subaru, I beg you!
It's no use...
Ikusabe, what is it?
I don't know...
I felt that Haruka-san is in danger. But I can't get close to her.
It's the first time this has happened.
A line has been established with Narika-san!
Takumaru! Did something happen?
Narika, Haruka has been captured.
Can you go to her rescue?
Haruka-san was captured?
Haruka, do you want to taste my juices?
Yes, keep this up, and then get enslaved by the Noroi.
Haruka-san!
Where'd she go?
Anyways, I'm glad you're all right.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
No, it's just that the enemy has gotten that much stronger.
Y-Yes...
In any case, Ikusabe...
You also have your own responsibility.
Me too?
Yes. You have to give Haruka more H-power.
That means you need to work harder.
How can I work harder?
Simply put, you just need to become dirtier, right?
Huh!? What are you saying?
Narika is right.
I understand.
I shall work hard.
Eh? H-Haruka-san...?
Even if she says that...
What should I do...
Takumaru-sama.
I'm sorry.
What's the matter, Haruka-san?
I was overwhelmed by my inexcusable feelings towards Subaru.
I failed to fulfill your expectations, Takumaru-sama.
I see. I understand how you feel, Haruka-san.
I believe in you. You should believe in me, too.
Takumaru-sama...
But the next time you're in a pinch, you have to call out my name.
Got it?
Yes.
Tada!
I brought something good!
Ways to Increase Stimulus, number one:
Nurse Cosplay Special Set!
Mr. Patient...
How does it feel?
Not good enough...
You have to do it more intensely or else I won't be able to cum, Ms. Nurse.
That's right, Haruka-san.
Please comfort Mr. Patient better.
Y-Yes.
How about this?
Yes.
Just like that, Haruka-san!
Yes, like that. I'm cumming...
Ms. Nurse...
Yes, please cum a lot.
I'm so glad...
Thank you very much for letting my breasts pleasure you.
It's embarrassing, but...
...this angle is the best!
E-Excuse me.
Haruka-san, you have to make yourself feel better.
Like this!
Narika-san, amazing...
It's going deep inside!
The Ryuurinko is...!
That's right, do this more intensely and it will shine even more!
Haruka-san is so aroused.
Just by stroking her pussy, her juices are flowing out non-stop!
Don't say it out loud! It's embarrassing!
The Ryuurinko is getting stronger.
Haruka-san, keep going!
Yes!
Takumaru-sama!
I'm going to cum too!
It's the Noroitou!
Stop right there!
I shall be the crescent whose moonlight cleanses the endless darkness dyed with sin!
Blade of the Souha Jougenshuu, Haruka is here!
And her comrade, Narika, is here!
Oh dear. You've come for another round?
Please leave her to me.
Understood. Well then, leave the other Noroitou to me.
Subaru! After transcending time, why are you assisting the Noroitou in this era?
I shall put your mentality under trial with my ninja skills!
Right now, the Noroitou are everything to me.
My misery and pain can only be truly understood by the Noroitou!
If you are saying that you are going to commit sins alongside the Noroitou,
then I have absolutely no intention of ever forgiving you!
Here I come!
Come at me, Haruka!
Please, Subaru.
Turn back into the Subaru that I know and love!
It seems that your heart still has its falterings.
Subaru...
You cannot kill me.
Joining the Noroitou together with me is the path that you should take.
I'll make you understand that fact.
O great gods of Noroi! Bestow thine torrential powers upon these fingers!
Entrap mine foe within a bulwark of infinite darkness!
We've lost Haruka-san!
Ikusabe.
Haruka-san... Please answer my call!
A male shaft. This was also given to me by the Noroi.
It's to make you sink into salacity.
Not that!
Stop it, Subaru! Anything but that!
Stop! Please stop!
No!
It's so hard... This big thing...
Is it painful to accept this thing?
It's painful, right?
I'm going to move.
Forgive me...!
No... Let me go...
You cannot escape.
Neither from this web, nor from my right hand.
I pledge my right hand to the root of all evil.
Subaru! Your hand-
Don't be afraid.
This is to send you to the heaven in which perverts dwell.
No! No!
This is... This is so...
Are you in pain?
Spit it out.
I can also feel pleasure in going so deeply inside you.
I'm going to cum soon.
I'll ejaculate my hot seed into you.
Not that!
N-No, Subaru! Not inside!
It's too late. I can't stop now.
Just give up.
No!
I'm getting more and more sensitive inside!
I'm going to become strange!
You're so tight...
Haruka, you're going to cum. Isn't that right!?
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
Great. Then I'm gonna cum too!
Subaru! Subaru!
I beg you! Please stop!
I'm cumming, Haruka. Accept them!
Accept my sperms!
Blade of Souha Jougenshuu, corruption complete.
Takumaru-sama...
Haruka-san, I will cleanse you.
So you called out for me?
Yes.
Sorry I'm late.
No, I'm happy that you came.
Well then, here I go.
Yes!
This light is the Ryuurinko?
S-Stop it! Stop it!
Subaru! Subaru!
Haruka... did we finish off the Noroi that appeared at the ceremony?
S-Subaru...
Welcome back, Subaru!
Haruka...
With this, the seal of the Jougenshuu is broken.
The Noroi will revive and we will rule over the heaven and the earth.
Haruka-san!
Those are...
Byakko, Genbu, and...
Mugenjou!
Mugenjou is the place where all the Noroitou gather, right?
Yes, that's right.
Haruka-san, will we be able to win against them?
Don't worry, Narika-san. No matter what happens, we won't lose!
[Edomae & Yui-Nyan Subs]