Episode 12: Even We Don't Know
If This is Truly The End
S-Splendid...
You've gotten stronger...
F-Father?
Everyone...
L-Leave this to me...
Don't do it!
Wh-What are you doing?
You betrayed us?
This is fate.
You're going to die here.
You've done well to
make it here.  I am God.
Now I shall release the World Seal!
Y-You're wrong, Fighter!
Everyone...
L-Leave this to me...
Don't do it!  Don't!
This is the World Chaos.
All evil is born from here.
Th-This whole thing is too big to believe!
Is this the end?
Not yet!
Don't give up!
Y-You guys!
We've come to help you!
Leave this to us high-level classes!
Hunter!  Valkyrie!
Th-This is the legendary Excalibur?
L-Leave this to me...
Don't!
I am the Dragonlord.
The ultimate creature,
who rules the entire world.
Shut up!  We refuse to accept that!
The world doesn't belong to anyone!
It belongs to everyone!
We'll give everything we have...
Here we go!
Let's fight!
Prepare to die!
Don't think this is the end.
He was the weakest of us.
The world belongs to us.
Is this the end?
Y-You're...!