This is the story of the young, beautiful heroines
who rose to bring back light to the realm.
Episode 1
Bikini Armor is Armor, Not Just a Bikini
Ow!
I-I'll try next!
Episode 1
Bikini Armor is Armor, Not Just a Bikini
So hot!
S-So cold!
My clothes are melting!
Hey, you!
This armor has no defense at all!
We get hurt, burned, and frozen easily!
Well, we have some new armor in stock.
Would you like to try it on?
You look good in it.
Hold on, isn't this the same crap we were just wearing?
This is great!
I've never worn something so wonderful!
I've never known the pleasure of such form-fitting armor.
I love it!
I can tell how fine this armor is just by wearing it.
Its defense values are on another level compared to our earlier drabs.
Um, they're the same.
You all buying?
Yes!
I'm fine.
Ow!
That didn't hurt at all!
The new armor is really working!
You're kidding!
It's not hot at all!
The new armor is really working!
It's not cold at all!
Y-Y-You're kidding!
Please, sir! I need that bikini armor!
Sure thing. Will you be equipping it now?
Is that the famous foursome?
Wow! They're so cool!
They look so strong!
Mommy, I wanna wear that armor, too!
I could get used to this.
I've never had this much attention before!
Now this is armor befitting
adventurers out to save the world.
Bikini armor is awesome!
I'm glad you like them.
By the way, we've got new armor in stock.
Th-These are just swimsuits!
How naughty! Sinful!
Impure!
Indecent!
I-I'm so embarrassed!
What do you think you're doing,
making us wear these skimpy things?
They don't seem any different from what you were wearing before.
Well they are! They're totally different!