Episode 6
Heroines Make the Impossible, Possible
Apparently only women are being attacked in the nearby forest.
Th-That's scary.
The victims have their items stolen and are horribly raped.
I'm so jeal—
I mean, I'm so judiciously mad!
Let us defeat this evil!
I-I'm scared!
This is our job as heroines.
Chin up!
I've been wondering...
Why is this sign board so full of holes?
Th-This forest is really creepy.
There's no telling where an attack might come from.
Be on your guard!
You shall not pass.
You are now victims of my technique.
Damn you!
Wh-What are you doing?
Why only attack there?
Your body tells the truth!
I-I'll turn you into a frog!
Don't worry. I'll make you a cute frog.
Just do it!
Mage!
Damn you!
Th-That's impossible!
How can I lose to a bunch of little girls?
Die!
P-Please!
That's too good!
All right! We beat it!
This feels so nice.
That was a close one, I have to say.
Our enemies are getting stronger.
Even stronger ones will be waiting for us.
But we are heroines.
We shall not fall!
The four of us shall persevere until peace is restored to the land!
Yeah!
All right! Let's go!