Episode 9: What a Hero Should Do When
Betrayed By a Companion They Trusted
Okay, we took care of it.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Die!
Awaah! What?
What was that for?
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you all!
What's wrong?  You seem like
a totally different person!
That's right!  This isn't who I usually am!
I'm being controlled by magic!
You can't hear me?
I'll never forgive you.
Now you will learn the depths of my hatred!
Hatred?  What are you talking about?
Could it be...
Is it because I didn't give you
quite as much stew as everybody else?
Because I secretly tried
to put on your panties,
and broke them?
Because I always leered at your naked body?
You guys were doing that?
You're horrible.
Didn't you realize that was wrong?
What about you?
E-Everybody, that's really mean,
but I'm not mad about it!
Die!
It may be that we were in the wrong.
But...
...that doesn't mean we can die here!
It's sad, but this must be fate.
I'm sorry!
We have a destiny to fulfill!
Forgive us!
Goodbye!
We won't forget you!
Wait!
I'm being controlled!
S-So don't apologize!
Listen to me!
N-No...
Don't!
We'll fight for your part, as well.
Watch over us.
Um... I may be dead,
but if you pay money at the church,
I can come back fairly easily.
D-Do you maybe not know that?
Um... wait... this really isn't funny.
Why those looks of defeat?
Everybody, don't give up on me!
Wait, please!
Don't take me with you!
Revive me!