Episode 11: A Filthy Beast Comes
for the Paladin's Alabaster Skin
Watch out!
Episode 11: A Filthy Beast Comes
for the Paladin's Alabaster Skin
Paladin!
Now! Hurry! Run!
It's all slimy...
Everybody, stay away!
He's strong!
We can't beat him at our current level!
What do we do?
Leave it to me!
What will you do?
You can't...
Adventuring with you guys
has been so much fun...
You idiot... you didn't have to do that!
PALADIN!
What's with that self-sacrifice thing
you've got going on?
I am a paladin. A holy knight of God!
Sacrificing myself for this world
and its people is my mission!
Some day you're really
going to wreck yourself.
I'm the mayor.  Call me "my lord."
If you want to proceed,
one of you must marry me!
W-We can't do that!
Sexual harrasser mayor...
Unforgivable.  Let's kill him.
Wait.  This is the perfect time
to demonstrate self-sacrifice.
I will marry him to help the rest of you!
What?
At last, I'm going to be tainted, aren't I?
That filthy man will have his way with me...
I will offer up my maidenly purity
for this world, its people, and its peace!
This is the ultimate self-sacrifice!
There you are!
Now show me... everything!
Y-Yes, my lord.
That's right.  I'll take good
care of you.  Come over here.
Hold it!
Wh-What's going on?
You're going to pay for trying to
make one of our friends your toy.
Y-You're going to pay!
I'm glad we made it in time!  It didn't feel
right to make you do all the sacrificing.
But you don't look too happy, do you?
It was the perfect chance to sacrifice
myself!  You shouldn't have done that.
But...
Thanks... just a little.