This is the story of
young beautiful heroes
who rose to restore light
to the world...
Episode 1: Bikini Armor is Bikini Armor.
It's Not a Bikini.
Oww!
Episode 1: Bikini Armor is Bikini Armor.
It's Not a Bikini.
I'll try next!
It's so hot!
It's so cold!
My clothes are melting!
Hey!  These things don't protect us at all!
You get hurt!  You get hot!
You get cold!
Okay, then, I just got in
the latest model of armor.
Want to try it?
It looks good on you.
Hey!  This is the exact same thing
we were just wearing!
I'm so happy!  I've never
worn anything so wonderful!
The way it just clings to your skin...
I've never felt anything like it!
It's so wonderful!
When you're as talented as I am,
you can tell just by putting it on.
These will protect us far better
than the last ones we wore.
No, no. They're the same...
You all want to buy them?
Yup!
I'll pass.
Oww!
It doesn't hurt!
And it's thanks to my new armor!
No way!
It's not hot!
And it's thanks to my new armor!
It's not cold at all!
Could it be thanks to my new armor?
W-what? Seriously?
I'm sorry!  Please sell me that bikini armor!
Sure thing.  Will you equip it now?
Are those the four girls
everyone is talking about?
Wow! They're so cool!
They look so strong!
Mommy!  I want to wear that outfit, too!
It's not bad being so popular.
I've never been the
center of attention like this before!
This is the perfect armor for an adventurer
who's going to save the world!
Bikini armor is the best!
Glad you like it.
By the way, I've got another
new item that just came in.
Oh, my.
These are swimsuits!
How filthy!  How naughty!
How indecent!  How perverted!
I... I'm so embarrassed!
What are you thinking,
making us wear these foul things?
I don't think they're that different
from what you were just wearing.
No!  They're totally different!