Episode 2: There's Something Every Hero
Needs at the Start of Their Journey
Welcome, heroes!
Episode 2: There's Something Every Hero
Needs at the Start of Their Journey
Lift your heads.
Episode 2: There's Something Every Hero
Needs at the Start of Their Journey
I've heard tell of you.
Fighter, the daughter of the
legendary hero who saved my country!
I'm so happy you've come.
I'm honored, Your Majesty.
And Paladin, famous for her beauty
and her many victories!
How divine is your countenance!
You're far too kind, Your Majesty.
And the genius who mastered the art
of magic at such a young age, Mage!
I never thought you would come, as well.
Oh, my... you're embarrassing me!
And Dark Elf!
They say you're wise,
and a deadly warrior as well.
So my reputation extends
even to the middle of nowhere.
That's rude!
Now that you four are here,
everything will be fine!
If only I'd had your aid sooner,
this never would've happened...
Your Majesty.
The entire world is in danger!
What should we do?
Don't worry, Your Majesty!
We four are here to save the world!
We won't let them get away with this!
We'll do our absolute best!
Leave everything to us!
I'm so glad to hear it!
I'm counting on you all!
Go, heroes!
Yes, Your Majesty!
Um...
Hmm?  What?  We're done talking.
No, um...
We need to make some preparations
to fight the enemy...
Oh, you're right!
I'll give you some funds for your journey!
Um...
One, two, three, four...
If I'm seeing right,
there are ten gold pieces here.
Now go!
No, um... well...
King!
In other words,
you're telling us to save the world
without enough money
to buy a single herb?
Th-that's rude!
There's no way he would possibly-
That's right.  That's all you get.
Now go!
Your Majesty!  A single night
at an inn costs 12 gold these days!
My grandpa gets a 100 gold
pension every month...
Yes. Now go!
Then at least lend us the
legendary weapon kept in this castle!
Oh, that, well...
No!  There's no such thing!
You just had a "Oh, that?" look on
your face for a second, didn't you?
You're imagining it.  Now go, heroes!
I said, go!
Then first,
sell some of the weapons of
those stupid-looking soldiers
who do nothing but stand there all day,
and get us some money, would you?
You would insult us?
You're insulting me much more,
telling me to sell my body for just 10 gold!
No, nobody's saying that.
Um... I'm pretty sure if we don't fight,
this country is doomed...
Which is more important:
your nation, or your money?
King, make your choice!
Why?
Obviously!
The rope's rubbing me
someplace very personal!
Please don't look at me!