The Ice Staff is so expensive.
Episode 5
Those Things You Save For Later But Never Actually Use
We don't have nearly enough gold.
But without it, we stand no chance against the enemies camped out in that cave.
Guess our only choice is to just take a look at our inventory, sell what we can,
and try to scrape up enough cash.
You mean sell me?!
Shut up, slut.
I can't believe we had this much stuff.
Where were we carrying it?
We've got too many potions.
And we never use the holy water.
There's no point in keeping it.
Hey, this is the Mirror of Light that we only used on the first enemy we fought.
We still had that?
Sell it or drop it, seriously.
W-We just never got around to it.
And when we brought it up,
it felt like such a waste!
Let's get rid of our old armor and weapons first.
This is great!
It's mine!
So some people actually want used bikini armor, huh?
I don't understand.
I don't understand why Mage's sold for the most.
R-Right.
We still don't have enough, though.
We've gotta sell more.
What're these?
We sure have a lot, whatever they are.
Those are elixirs.
They're basically the best potions, restoring both health and mana when you're in a real pinch.
But normally we heal a little at a time so we don't end up in a pinch, right?
So now we've got a whole bunch and never use a drop!
Then let's sell 'em all!
Not like we'll use 'em!
B-But if we do need them...
We haven't yet. That's why we have so many.
We'll be fine.
Come again soon.
W-We bought the Ice Staff!
All right! Let's take down those cave dwellers!
The cave dwellers are right in front of us...
But it's no use!
Does no one have a potion?
W-We just used the last one.
Th-Then someone, cast a Heal...
I'm out of mana.
Oh, if only we had an elixir...
Whose bright idea was it to sell all of them?!
Yours!
We sold everything to buy this Ice Staff!
Now we can't fight!
We have no choice. Let's retreat and regroup.
That's a long walk...
A treasure chest!
Yes!
Come on, elixir!
Or any healing item, really!
Huh?
A-An Ice Staff!