Episode 8: It's Common for New Party Members
to Join Midway Through an Adventure
You want to join our party?
Yeah.
I'm Hunter.
I've never been in a party
with people from the city.
So I'm really nervous.
She's from the middle of nowhere...
I am Valkyrie.
Unlike Fighter,
mine is a high-level class
that shows I've been chosen by God.
I have high-level weapons,
and I can show you an extremely
high-level attack, if you like?
She's kind of irritating.
Shall I kill her?
Wait a second.
Even if we do let them in
our party, I only want one.
Then you'd want a
higher-level class, like me.
What?
I'll be a lot more useful
than this stuck-up girl!
C-Calm down...
First, what exactly can you two do?
This is good!  It's so good!
I'm good at cooking and hunting.
If you let me join your party,
I'll make you delicious food every day!
That would be great!
This really is good!
What's the broth made out of?
Oh.
This is dried slime.
Don't make me eat that!
Why?  It's got a nice, strong flavor.
And the secret ingredient
is harpy brains and basilisk eyes!
Stop...
How barbaric!
A higher-level class like myself
could never do that.
Then, what can you do?
I could do that, too...
What do you think?
This is the power of a woman
born with unique talent.
The power of a high-level class,
chosen by God!
She really does piss me off.
But that was impressive.
Right now, Valkyrie is doing better.
Okay, now that I've worked, I'm tired.
Let's go back to town. Here.
Huh?
Where are our horses?
A carriage will do, as well.
What are you saying?
We don't have those things.
We walk back, obviously.
What?
But that would make it look like I'm poor!
A high-level class like me can't do that!
Get us horses immediately.
What is her problem?
And I want the best room in the inn!
Annoying.
She's incredibly selfish.
And I want the best room in the inn!
I'm a high-level class!
She's incredibly selfish.
She really does upset me.
I'm a high-level class!
Shall I kill her?
They say they can't decide who it should be,
so we'll fight, and they'll take the winner.
Fine with me.
Taste the overwhelming power
of a high-level class!
Here I go!
I won't lose to you!
Shut up, you country hick!
Where are you touching me?
You little...
I can't keep going!
We ended up friends after that fight.
She's pretty cute.
Her strength moved me.
We're going to form our own party!
Right?
O-Oh...
I guess it's a happy ending...
Maybe?