The Boss that rules this territory is at that Crystal Tower!
From now on, the enemies will be considerably stronger!
Everyone, don't let your guard down!
I know that, but why are you acting like you are the leader?
TL note: I don't understand, she is talking about not being able to use recovery magic, acting bossy and stuff
It's not like I can't use it, I'm just bad at it!
Anyway, let's be careful!
I'm more worried about you... de gozaru
It's asleep!
Everyone, stay calm!
Doryaaaaaaaaaaa!!!!
Oi! You are not being careful at all!!!!
T-That place is...
Nooooo~
You are hopeless.
There is nothing here.
I smell a strange scent over there.
As expected from Hunter, we should be more careful here.
It's fine, it's fine! Go! Go!
Hey! Oi!
Huh?
Aaaaaaah
Hyaaa! What the hell is this!?
I-It's all sticky and slippery!
Ahhh! The armor... The armor is dissolving!
That was close... de gozaru
That's not fair!
We finally reached this point.
That was terrible though, thanks to you.
Enemies that are even stronger than before are waiting there.
We need to be really careful.
I understand, leave it to me.
Oh God of War, grant power to our weapons!
Whoa! This is...
It's a reinforcement magic isn't it?
The power is surging in!
Yosh! everything is all set?
Well then, let's go girls!
Don-don-donuts let's go nuts!
Uaaaaaghhhhhh!!!!
You are finished!!!
Uaghh!
We did it!
We finally defeat him!
Hm?
What the hell is that?
It looks really suspicious.
That thing should not be destroyed!
Huh?
If it disappeared, this world will be in great danger!
I-Is that true? Well, it looks like it's acting strange.
I can feel great power... de gozaru
We need to plan this carefully.
Huh?
Yosh! It looks suspicious, so I will just break it!
Stop!!!
Eeeeey!!!
Those girls, finally get caught huh?
It seems a country got destroyed because of them.
Ahh, how horrible. Perhaps it was demons' doing?
As I thought, we should have come sooner.
*sexy noise*
Waaah!
How did we end up like this?
It's all your fault!!!