Episode 3: Even a Hero Needs to Survive
We have no money!
What do we do?
We can't even stay at an inn anymore!
I guess we have no choice.
We'll have to use our last resort!
You mean making money with
your body, like always?
N-No!
I always imagine doing it,
and I get all flushed and excited...
...but I don't actually do it!
So what's our last resort, then?
We are heroes.  The law protects us!
Hello. We are heroes!
As per the Special Hero Dispensation Act,
we will be taking needed items!
As you are aware,
those given the task of saving the world by
the national government are called heroes,
and the Special Hero Dispensation Act
gives them the right to take needed items
from treasure chests and dressers in town.
Okay, let's search this place
from top to bottom.
E-Excuse me.
Is this really okay?
Herb.  Antidote.  10 gold.
That's about it, I guess.
Look at all this gold!
I'll make very good use of this!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
A wizard's staff!
I've always wanted one of these!
Okay, we're getting out of here.
Is it really okay for us to do this?
It's all legal!
We have a higher purpose: to save the world!
And small sacrifices must be made
to achieve that end.
Okay, we're hitting that place next.
Good afternoon.  I'm a hero.
A fighter's steel broadsword!
U-Uh... excuse me...
Oh, my!  A philosopher's stone?  Here?!
Once I save up more money,
I'm gonna buy Daddy a present!
I'm sorry!  This is all to save the world!
Thanks to the Special Hero Dispensation Act,
we're not in danger of going broke anymore!
And we get to stay in such a
wonderful hotel... it's like a dream!
The Special Hero Dispensation Act
is the best, isn't it?
The law is absolute.
As heroes, let's keep doing our best
for our world and its people!
What is this?
They were mad, after all!
I'm sorry!
They're breaking the law... how rude!
Unforgivable!
At least... leave us our clothes...
It's so cold!
I... I'M SORRY!