Episode 4
Heroines Never Ask for Rewards
You'll need a special key to get through the cave leading to the Kingdom of Geldabar.
Episode 4
Heroines Never Ask for Rewards
A key only I have!
If you want it, you gotta do what I say!
Didn't take long for your true colors to show.
Should I kill him?
Wait!
Whatever awaits us, it's still a heroic trial!
We have to do it!
Sh-Shouldn't we help?
Fighter's doing all the work.
She wanted to do it, so let her.
Transporting goods is no heroic task.
Stop!
Catch a runaway dog, he says!
Is this really a job for a heroine?
Huh?
Hey, you!
That tickles.
St-Stop that!
No!
I said no!
This is a new potion the mayor created.
I'm supposed to drink it and see what it does.
A-Are you really going to drink it?
That has bad news written all over it.
That is no heroic task.
No! I must drink it, or we cannot move forward!
This is my job as a heroine!
Down the hatch!
My body's all warm and fuzzy!
I-I'm burning up!
Contain yourself, Fighter!
We're in broad daylight!
But... But...
You sure you want me to stop?
Don't stop!
People are staring.
Do your antics somewhere else.
Th-They really shouldn't do it anywhere!
If I defeat this thing like the mayor requested,
I can finally get the key!
I have to win!
But...
N-No!
No more!
A-Are you okay?
G-Girls...
Our adventure will be over if we're stuck in this town.
You fiend! How dare you monopolize such a pleasurable-looking monster!
I-I wasn't!
That's totally backwards!
It didn't feel good at all...
Whatever.
Let's just finish this.
Right!
Great job completing all my tasks!
You are true heroines!
Then the key we desperately need to move on to the Kingdom of Geldabar...
Indeed.
The key is already in you.
Huh?
By completing my ridiculous tasks, you learned the importance of helping others!
That experience is the most important key a heroine could ask for!
Truly heroic! I am moved to tears!
Don't stop me, girls.
God permits it.
Do it.
J-Just don't kill him.