【Episode 14】
Kunoichi Ninja Arts Chapter  The Drip Honey Secret
We were told to have to share a room...
She's really a cute one.
I'm Cleric.
Nice to meet you!
Cleric?
A clergy and follower of the God of War.
They're rumored to excel in healing magic.
You're really something.
You think too highly of me.
You shouldn't do this.
We're not alone here.
You don't mind at all, right?
I really can't hold back any longer.
This is the right spot, isn't it?
If you keep doing that, I'll...
Your body is being really honest.
I'll attend to you all night.
Who is it?!
I'm Kunoichi.
I am in search of the legendary bikini armor.
Legendary bikini armor?
For what reason?
It's my hobby!
All these collections are for the sake of
obtaining the legendary bikini armor.
I will also seize your bikini armors.
I don't really understand but I'm not going to hand my armor to you.
Then I've got no choice but to take it by force!
That's dangerous!
O God of War, please bestow more power to my weapon.
I-I'm sorry.
A-Are you okay?!
Hey, you're a cleric aren't you?
Cast some healing magic!
Eh?
You could just use your saliva on the wound.
Let's resume the fight!
Could it be that you can't use any healing magic?
That's not true!
I'm just bad at it.
You're useless!
Ninja Arts - Koi Shigure technique.
What a great body.
I want to eat it.
W-What are you doing?
Now isn't the time to be doing this-
I'll definitely crush you!
I swear in the name of the God of War!
The bikini armor will be mine or be destroyed.
I bet you girls had a great time last night, isn't it?
Yes.
Not at all!
The bikini armor that I'm searching for is still out of my reach.