A Hero is One Who Pushes Against
His Limits, and Exceeds Them
It says there's something in the nearby
forest that only attacks women.
A Hero is One Who Pushes Against
His Limits, and Exceeds Them
It says there's something in the nearby
forest that only attacks women.
Th-That's scary.
The women were all stripped of their clothes,
and violently raped.
I'm so jealo-
I mean, I'm so appalled! Let's defeat it!
I-It's scary!
This is a job for a hero! Let's do our best!
Hey, why's this sign got so many holes in it?
Th-This forest is kind of creepy.
We don't know where the enemy is
going to attack from.  Be careful!
You shall not pass!
You shall fall victim to my spells!
Damn it!
What is this?
D-Don't keep touching me there!
Your body says otherwise!
I... I'll turn you into a frog!
Don't worry!  It'll be a cute one.
Just hurry up!
MAGE!
How dare you!?
Th-This can't be!
I can't lose to little girls like this!
This is it!
Not there!
No!
Okay! We beat it!
This feels so good.
That was close, though.
The enemy is getting pretty tough.
The enemies we face after this
will be even stronger.
But we are heroes.  We must not lose.
Until the day the four of us restore
peace to the world, let's do our best!
R-Right!
Okay! Let's go!