Episode 7
Never Trust Strangers You Meet at a Bar
The ultimate swordsman,
but no practical experience.
Acquaintance of the neighbor of the cousin of the friend
of the hero who defeated the Far East Demon King...
We finally decide to add someone to the party,
but all these people are nothing but talk.
Like you're one to talk!
You were the same in the beginning.
You wish to enlist me?
I must admit, you have good taste.
A real dark elf!
Sh-She seems strong!
What are your skills?
Not only am I a master of magic and blade—
we elves live eons longer than humans.
I have seen all that this land has to offer.
Not that I'm bragging.
Yes she is!
But she'd surely be a boon to our party.
Is this really the right way?
No need to worry.
The wind sprites whisper the path to me.
You've been saying that for hours!
Don't worry.
Trust me.
No!
You mustn't!
Not there!
That's one rough customer!
Never fear!
I shall handle him!
Wh-What is that?
I can feel incredible magical energy emanating from it!
Roar of the Thunder God's Cannon!
He's better than I thought.
What are you talking about?
You liar!
Don't worry.
As hundred more shots should take care of the monster.
What are these stones?
I sense a strange power inside them.
Okay! Punch first, ask questions later!
Fool. These are gates that connect to the Dark Realm.
Really?
How rude.
I have the faintest memories of possibly reading about these
in a book maybe thirty years ago.
There's vague, and then there's that!
If memory serves, you just move this stone...
Wh-What's going on?!
Where are we?
Greetings, brave warriors.
I am the Demon King who rules this land, Deathgedd.
You mean the last boss?
W-We have to fight him already?!
N-No way, no way, no way that's happening!
I knew it.
Just as planned.
Liar!
Demon King Deathgedd!
Consider your life forfeit!
Your head shall rest on my blade!
Stop exaggerating!
How amusing.
Let's go!
En garde!