Episode 12
Even We Don't Really Know If This Is the End
Very good.
You've gotten strong.
F-Father?
Everyone!
L-Leave this to me...
No!
What are you doing?
Is this betrayal?
It is as fate wills it.
Now, die!
Congratulations on reaching me.
I am God.
Now, let us undo the seal!
You're wrong, Fighter!
Everyone!
Leave this to me...
Don't do it!
No!
This is the true world.
All evil is born from it.
I-I wasn't prepared for something this epic!
Is this it for us?
Not yet!
You mustn't give up!
You guys!
We came to save yer asses!
Leave this to us, the ultimate pair!
Hunter!
Valkyrie!
It-It's the holy sword of legend!
L-Leave this to me...
No!
I am the Demon King.
I am the supreme ruler of all existence!
Shut your face!
No way we're letting that fly!
The world belongs to no single being.
It's for all!
We're coming at you...
...with all we've got!
I challenge you!
Prepare yourself, fiend!
This is far from over.
You've only defeated our weakest brethren.
The world is ours.
Is this it for us?
Y-You're...