Episode 10: It's Hard to
Get the Items You Want
W-We finally found a treasure chest!
It's been a long dungeon, huh?
My HP and MP are both at their limit!
It would be best if there was some
kind of healing item inside...
No, the enemies in this dungeon are strong.
A powerful weapon would be good too.
Okay, I'm going to open it.
But if it's another trap...
Th-That's right.  All the treasure
chests in this dungeon...
Oh, a treasure chest already!
That's a good omen!
A trap?
Another trap!
Are you okay?
It's digging in... it's digging in!
More!
I'm going to drop you.
My magic will allow me to check the
contents of the chest without opening it.
Then you should've done that
for the first one.
I can see it!  There's something inside!
Okay, I'm opening it!
NO! E-EELS?!
I was right. There was something inside.
"S-Something inside" doesn't help!
Don't go in there...
But it feels strange...
Yeah.  It's been traps up until now.
But that doesn't mean this one's a trap.
I used my magic.
There's definitely something inside.
"Something" doesn't tell us anything!
B-But if it's a weapon or a healing item...
We need to open it!
Okay, let's do rock paper scissors
to decide who'll open it!
Rock, paper...
You guys cheat!
So do you!
Are you in a position to talk?
Oh, fine.  The party lives or dies together.
We'll all open it together!
That's right.
Okay!
We'll just have to see what's inside...
Okay, here I go!
One, two...
I am the Goddess of Truth.
Do you want the Symbol of Courage?
Or the Crest of Justice?
Neither.
What honesty!  I'll give you both!
I said we don't need either of them!
Forget those!  Give us something better!
This is an emergency!
You're a useless goddess, aren't you?
Don't you have anything else?
A sword, or a staff, or even an herb?
What about an elixir?
Wait! Don't run away!
If you're a goddess, do something!
Please!
Help us!