【Episode 15】
This is the appearance of the warriors who obtained the legendary armor
I am God.
You all have done well to finally reach here.
All of you are truly warriors.
In praise of your bravery, I shall bestow you with the ultimate equipment - the legendary bikini armor.
The legendary bikini armor!
Huh?
W-What is this?!
How is this considered as legendary?!
S-Stay calm, everyone.
I'm sure God has a profound reason for this.
Have you deceived us, you bastard?!
Unforgivable!
I'll kill you!
The legendary bikini armor that I had bestowed on all of you cannot be seen by idiots.
Eh?!
Idiots can't see the bikini armor?
T-That's right.
I knew it all along.
I've been able to see them from the start.
M-Me too...
This snug feeling seems like it is tailored especially just for me.
I can't believe I'm receiving such a fine armor.
Just equipping it makes me feel like I have powered up.
Thank you, God.
So this is the legendary bikini armor.
We were given such a great item.
I-I agree.
However...
Why do you think people keep staring at us so lecherously.
I bet it's because our bikini armor is so awesome that they couldn't tear their eyes away from us.
Yes, I'm sure that must be it.
Nailed it! A huge win for me.
You're safe now.
T-Thank you very much.
Somehow I don't feel so comfortable with this bikini armor.
It feels breezy.
It'll be fine once you get used to it.
It is the perfect armor for a high level job class.
W-What's with your appearances?!
Have you girls gone mad?!
Oh dear! Can you not see what we're wearing?
We're wearing the legendary bikini armor.
But, idiots will not be able to see them.
T-The legendary bikini armor?!
And it can't be seen by idiots?!
Of course I can see them.
I can see them very clearly!
Please let me know where you have obtained them.
From the sanctuary over there.
I see.
You have my gratitude.
Hopefully there's more left in stock.
What is it?
It's my act of sympathy because all of you are naked.
Huh?!
How much do you charge, sweetie?
Based on your appearance, it's your trade of work, isn't it?
You're exhibiting your body in such a lascivious way.
Eh?!
Don't move, you perverts!
Perverts?!
Can you guys not see this at all?!
I knew it!
I knew it'll be like this!
In praise of your bravery, I shall also bestow you with the legendary bikini armor.
It'll finally be my very own!