Episode 3
Even Heroines Need to Eat
We're broke!
Wh-What do we do? We can't stay at an inn now.
We have no other choice.
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
Selling your body again, are you?
N-No!
Sure, I fantasize and get hot and bothered at the thought,
but I've never actually done it.
If that isn't the "desperate" measure, then what is?
We are heroines.
The law is on our side!
Good day.
We are heroines.
In accordance with the Hero Special Supply Law,
we will be commandeering our needed supplies.
As you know, those charged with the kingdom's salvation are called heroes and heroines.
The Hero Special Supply Law
allows us to take any useful items we find in treasure chests and storage cabinets.
We'll be searching every nook and cranny of this place!
E-Excuse me.
Is this really legal?
Herbs. An antidote.
Twenty gold coins.
Is that all?
Oh, dear!
Look at all the gold!
Thank you very much for your donation!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
A mage's staff!
I've always wanted one of these!
All right, time to leave.
Are you sure this is legal?
It is all perfectly legal.
Saving the kingdom is our holy mission!
Small sacrifices are unfortunate, but necessary.
Okay! On to the next house!
Good day. We are heroines.
Oh, what a magnificent fighter's steel sword!
S-Sorry for the intrusion.
Oh! Look where I found the Philosopher's Stone!
I'm saving to buy Daddy a present!
I'm sorry! This is all for the kingdom's safety!
That Hero Special Supply Law really saved us from the jaws of poverty.
This hotel is so luxurious! You gotta pinch me!
Truly these are the perks of the Hero Special Supply Law.
The law is absolute!
Let us do our best in service to the realm and its people.
Wh-What's going on?
They were mad!
I'm sorry!
What ruffians, disobeying the law!
This shall not go unpunished!
They could have at least left our clothes.
It's so cold!
I-I'm sorry!