Episode 8
Gaining New Party Members in the Latter Half of an Adventure is Quite Common
You want to join our party?
Ya.
I'm Hunter.
Nevah kep wi' city-folk afore,
so I ain't too sure 'bout this.
She's so from the sticks.
I am Valkyrie.
Unlike Fighter, I am chosen by God and the ultimate warrior.
I can give you a demonstration of my heavenly weapon's ultimate power, if you'd like.
She's pissing me off.
Can I kill her?
Cool it.
We don't necessarily both of them.
One is all we really need.
Then I, the ultimate warrior, am the obvious pick.
What?!
No way dis stuck up beetch is more useful 'n me!
C-Calm down, now.
Would you two mind showing us what you're capable of?
This is good!
Too good!
See? I'm great at bows and cookin'!
Let me in your party, and yeh'll feast like kings every nigh'!
That sure would be useful!
This is so good!
What's in it?
Dried slime carcass.
Don't feed us that crap!
Why?
It's good when you cook it.
Oh, and my secret ingredients were harpy brains and basilisk eyes!
Stop it!
How vulgar.
Even I, beloved by God, could not tread there.
Then what the hell can ya do?!
That ain't no hot shit!
Impressed?
This is the one and only power of God's beloved.
You should expect nothing less from one chosen by Him.
Well, she still pisses me off, but she's strong.
Ms. Valkyrie seems to have the edge right now.
All that work has tired me out.
Let us return to town.
Here.
Excuse me?
Where is my horse?
I also accept carriage rides.
What're you talking about?
We've got nothing of the sort.
We're walking back to town!
What?!
There is no way I, God's beloved,
can walk to town like a peasant!
What's her deal?
Bitch.
She's just demands and demands, doesn't she?
Yeah, she pisses me off.
Can I kill her?
Apparently they can't choose, so we're supposed to duke it out fer the spot.
Very well!
Prepare to taste the power of the ultimate warrior!
Let's go!
I hate jerks like you!
Silence, plebeian!
What'd you say?!
Where do you think you're touching?
No more!
All that fighting really brought us closer together!
Turns out she's a sweet li'l thing!
And I was moved by the strength she showed.
The two of us will make our own party!
Right?
A-All right.
Is this happily ever after?