We did it!
Alright! let's go back to town then
Everyone!?
Are you alright?
Yeah, it was nothing.
What was that magic just now?
Then, where should we spend the night?
W-what's this about?
I-I'm sorry, my body is acting on its own!
D-don't, you can't do this
Not in this place
People will see us
Perverts, think about the place
We're in public!
E-Even if you say that...
My body wont listen to me
D-Don't not in that place
My body is really doing this by itself
I don't wan to do this!
Could it be because of the magic before?
W-What are you doing?
I-I'm sorry but my body is...
Don't touch that place
It's not on purpose
I've heard about this...
In exchange of one's life
The enemies go through  embarrassing moments
A legendary magic called chikate
I can't believe there was someone that could use it
Don't do it! This is wrong!
I know but there's nothing I can do
Mom, what are they doing?
You must not look
Ah, they're watching, this pure body that I've shown to no one
We're exposing ourselves in front of these gentlemen
Such a dirty and vulgar act
But... but... Aah!
Don't! ... Y-You can't do that
I'm sorry, but there's nothing I can...
I'm sorry, there's nothing I can... DO!
I've been defiled
N-No you can't do this
I'm.... Sorry!
They've seen it.
Idiot!
Like I said, it was the magic's fault
Forgive us
I won't
Eh? where's she?
Magician please show yourself
Please use that magic once more
Please I'm begging you!