The Ice Staff is so expensive!
Most Things You Save, You End Up Never Using
We don't have this much money!
But without the Ice Staff,
we can't beat the boss of that cave!
Let's sort through what we have,
and sell what we can to get the money.
Are you going to sell me?
Shut up.
I didn't realize we had so much stuff.
Where were we keeping it all?
We've got too many herbs.
And we never use holy water,
so there's no sense in keeping it.
Huh?
This is the Mirror Light, which we only
ever used to seal away the first enemy.
We still have that thing?
Sell it or throw it away already.
W-Well, for some reason,
we just don't feel like throwing it away.
And when we try to sell it, they say,
"You can't possibly sell this!"
We can start by selling
our old weapons and armor.
This is great!
It fits perfect!
I guess some people
really like used bikini armor.
I wonder what they want it for.
And it's a mystery why Mage's sold
for the most money, too.
Y-Yeah...
But it's still not enough.
We need to sell more stuff.
What are these?
We've got an awful lot of them.
Oh, those are elixirs.
Even if you're near death, using one will
bring your HP and MP back to maximum.
They're the ultimate medicine.
But usually before things get that bad,
we heal little by little, right?
And since we never use them,
they've piled up like this.
Then let's sell them all!
We'll never use them anyway.
B-But if we ever need them...
That's never happened, which is why
we have so many of them, right?
It'll be fine.
Thank you.
W-We got enough money
to buy the Ice Staff!
Okay! Let's go fight that boss in the caves!
The boss is behind that door...
But, I'm too tired to move!
Does anybody have an herb?
I... I just used our last one...
Th-Then, does anybody have a cure spell?
I don't have any MP left.
If only we had an elixir...
What idiot convinced us to sell them all?
It was you!
We sold all that stuff
to buy the Ice Staff,
but we can't fight like this!
I guess we'll have to back out and try again.
That's going to be a pain.
A treasure chest!
All right! Come on, elixir!
Or anything that can heal us!
Huh?
I-It's an Ice Staff!