Episode 7: Never Put Too Much Trust
in Companions You Meet in Taverns
Ultimate warrior.  No combat experience.
Episode 7: Never Put Too Much Trust
in Companions You Meet in Taverns
Related to the hero who defeated
the Demon Lord 70 years ago
by being an acquantance
of his cousin's neighbor.
I was planning on adding
somebody to the party,
but they're all talk.
None of them are any good.
You don't get to say that!
You were like this at first too, right?
You want my help?  You've got good eyes.
Ooh! A real dark elf!
Sh-She looks strong...
What can you do?
I'm skilled with both the sword and magic,
and we elves live longer than humans.
We have knowledge of practically
everything in the world.
Not that I'm bragging.
You're totally bragging!
But if we got her to join our party,
she looks like she'd be a big help!
Is this really the right way?
No need to worry.
The wind spirits will show me the right path.
You've been saying that for
two days, and we're still lost!
It's fine. Leave it to me.
N-No!
No! Not there...
He's tough!
Don't worry.
Leave it to me!
Th-That's...
I feel an incredible magic power!
Thunder King's Slash!
He's more powerful than I thought!
Huh?
What was that?
It doesn't actually do anything?
Don't worry.
If I use it a hundred times or so,
I'll defeat him for sure.
What are these ruins?
I... I feel a strange power...
Okay, let's punch it first and think later.
Fool. This is a gate connecting
our own world and the demon world.
Really?
How rude.
I think I remember reading about it
in some book or another 30 years ago.
Possibly.  Maybe.  Perhaps.
So basically you don't remember at all!
As I recall, if you move this stone...
What is this?
Where are we?
You have done well to come this far!
I am Deathgeddon,
the Demon Lord that rules this land!
Which means you're the last boss?
We have to fight this guy all of a sudden?
N-N-No way!  No way!  No way!
I knew it.  All according to plan!
You're lying!
Demon Lord Deathgeddon,
now that I'm here, you're finished!
Your blood shall rust on my blade!
Waah!  There's no way that's happening!
Interesting.  Here I go!
Come!