We did it!
Alright! Shall we head back to town, then?
Girls?!
Are you alright?
Y-Yeah, it's nothing.
What was that magic just now?
Well then, shall we look for
a place to spend the night?
W-What are you doing all of a sudden?
I-I'm sorry, my body's acting on its own!
N-No! You can't do this,
not out here...
P-People will see us!
How indecent. Think about where we are.
We're in public!
E-Even if you say that...
My body won't listen to me!
D-Don't! I-If you suddenly touch me down there—
M-My body really is moving by itself!
I don't want to do this!
Could it be because of the magic before?
W-What do you think you're doing?
I-I'm so sorry! My body is just...
Please don't touch me there!
I'm not doing it because I want to!
I... I've heard about this before...
In exchange of one's life,
The enemies are subjected to embarrassing situations.
It's a legendary magic called chikate.
I can't believe there was
someone that could still use it!
Don't do it! This is wrong!
I know that, but there's nothing I can do!
Mom, what are they doing?
Don't look at them!
They're watching... they can see my pure body that I've never shown to anyone!
We're exposing ourselves in
front of these good men...
It's such a dirty and vulgar act...
But... but... Aah!
You mustn't! Y-You can't do that!
I'm sorry, but there's nothing I can... do!
I've been so thoroughly defiled...
N-No! D-Don't do that!
I'm... Sorry!
They can see...
You idiot!
Like I said, it was all the magic's doing!
Please forgive us!
I don't know what you mean!
Oh yeah, where'd Paladin go?
Great wizard, please show yourself!
Please cast your magic one more time!
Please, I implore you!