Episode 4: A Hero Must Seek No Reward
You need a special key to get through the
caves that lead to the Kingdom of Geldovar!
Episode 4: A Hero Must Seek No Reward
You need a special key to get through the
caves that lead to the Kingdom of Geldovar!
And only I have it!
If you want it, you have to do what I say!
He's quite rude, isn't he?  Shall I kill him?
Wait.
We don't know what he'll make us do,
but I'm sure it's a trial fit for a hero!
Let's do it!
I-Is it okay to have Fighter-san
do this all by herself?
She said she'd do it.  Why not let her?
Carrying things isn't a job fit for a hero!
Wait!
"Catch a dog that ran away"?
Is this also a hero's job?
Oh, stop!  That tickles!
Hey, stop!
No! Stop! I said stop!
This is supposedly a new medicine
developed by the mayor.
He wants me to drink it and see what it does.
A-Are you going to do that?
Nothing good can come of this.
That's not a hero's job!
No!  If I don't drink it, we cannot progress!
This is also a hero's job!
Here I go!
My body feels so warm...
It's so hot!
Oh, so suddenly?
It's still the middle of the day!
But... but...
You like that?  You like that?
People are watching.
Do that somewhere else.
You like that?  You like that?
D-Don't do it anywhere else, either!
If I defeat this monster
like the mayor said...
...I'll finally get that key...
I can't lose! But...
No!  No more!
Are you all right?
G-Guys...
If we don't get on with it,
our adventure will be over.
Unforgivable!  Having all
that fun by yourself...
N-No... it's not like that!
It doesn't feel good at all.
Whatever.  Let's get this over with.
Right!
Excellent!  You have completed all my tasks!
You are true heroes!
Then... then like you promised,
you'll give us the key we absolutely need
to get to the Kingdom of Geldovar.
Yes... the key is already within you!
Huh?
By obeying my unreasonable commands,
you learned the importance of helping others!
That experience is the key that every
adventurer absolutely requires!
You are true heroes!  I'm so moved!
Hey.  Don't stop me.
I'll allow it.
Do it.
J-Just don't kill him...