Episode 11
The Deviant's Trap Closes in on Paladin's Soft, White Skin
Look out!
Paladin!
Now! Get out of here!
This thing's too dangerous!
All of you, run!
This thing's strong!
We can't beat it at our level!
Wh-What do we do?
Leave this to me!
What can you do?
Don't tell me...
It has been my pleasure to share this adventure with you all.
That idiot!
We could have found another way.
Paladin!
What's with your fondness for self-sacrifice?
I am a paladin—a holy warrior in service to God.
It is my purpose in life to put myself in harm's way for the sake of others and world peace!
One day you're gonna end up in a situation worse than death.
I'm the mayor of this town.
Address me as m'lord.
If you wish to pass through my town,
one of you has to marry me!
N-No way!
What a sick mayor!
He needs to pay. Let's kill him.
Wait!
Now you will see the value of my self-sacrifice.
For your sakes, I shall marry!
What?!
It seems I cannot keep my purity any longer.
That filthy man is going to have his way with me...
For the sake of the people and world peace,
I shall sacrifice my virginity.
Truly the ultimate in self-sacrifice!
Good, you're here!
Now, show me everything you have!
V-Very well.
No need to be shy.
Come!
Stop right there!
Wh-What's going on?
How dare you try to defile our friend!
Y-You'll pay!
Man, lucky timing, huh?
We felt bad letting you sacrifice yourself like that.
But you don't seem very happy about it.
I was finally going to commit the ultimate sacrifice!
Thanks for nothing!
Well...
not nothing, I suppose.