Episode 9
Faced with Betrayal from Within, What Will the Heroines Do?
And that's that!
Let's go.
What's the matter?
Die!
Wh-What the?!
What do you think you're doing?
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you all!
What's gotten into you?
You're like a totally different person!
That's totally right! This isn't the normal me!
I'm being controlled by magic!
Wait, can't you hear me?
You will pay!
You will know my pain!
Pain? Uh, what?
Wait...
Are you mad that you got the smallest portion to eat the other day?
Are you mad that I tried on your underwear in secret
and accidentally ripped them?
Are you mad that I ogle at you lustfully in the bath?
Did you people seriously do all that?!
How horrible. You should be ashamed!
No, you!
You're all terrible, but I'm not mad!
Die!
Perhaps we may have wronged you...
But!
We will not lay down our lives!
Sorry, but we've got destinies to fulfill.
I'm sorry!
We have our quest to finish!
Please forgive us.
Farewell. We won't forget you!
W-Wait!
I-I'm being controlled!
Let's not be hasty here!
Listen to me!
N-No way!
D-Don't!
Stop!
We'll fight in your stead.
Please watch over us.
Um, I know I'm dead, but a donation to the Church will bring me right back to life!
Y-You do know that, right?
W-Wait a minute.
Enough joking around.
Wh-Why do you all look like you've given up?
Don't give up on me!
Please!
Wait!
Don't take me away!
Let me revive!