Episode 2
What Every Good Adventurer Needs
Thank you for coming, heroines!
Raise your heads.
Episode 2
What Every Good Adventurer Needs
The people talk of the Fighter,
daughter of the legendary hero who saved my kingdom.
I am most honored to have you here.
Thank you, sir.
And the Paladin, holy knight with both a beautiful countenance and radiant record of service!
I am humbled.
Your words of praise flatter me so, Your Grace.
And the Mage, young yet peerless in magicks.
You do me great service in coming.
Please, Your Grace. I'm blushing.
Oh, Dark Elf!
I hear you are quite the scholarly soldier.
I see my reputation precedes me.
Watch yourself!
What reliable warriors, all!
If I had known of you earlier,
much tragedy could have been avoided!
Your Grace!
The realm is in grave peril!
I am at a loss!
Rest easy, Your Grace!
The four of us have banded together to stop this foul evil!
We won't let them have their way!
We promise to do our best!
Leave everything to us.
Truly, we are saved!
Go forth, brave heroines!
Your Grace!
Um...
What? That will be all.
Well, we can't just go out and fight without proper preparation and arrangements.
Oh, of course!
Have some gold to finance your quest.
Um...
If my eyes don't deceive me,
this is but ten gold coins.
Go forth, heroines!
Well, um, you see...
King!
Are you telling us to save the realm on only enough coin to buy a single potion?
M-Mind your tongue!
Of course he's not saying that!
You are correct. That is all you get.
Go forth, heroines!
Your Grace!
A single night at an inn currently costs twelve gold coins!
My grandfather gets a hundred coins a month from his pension.
I see.
Go forth, heroines!
Th-Then at least allow us use of the legendary weapons within your treasury!
Oh, those?
They, uh...
We have not what you speak of!
You were totally thinking about them just now!
You imagine things! Go forth, heroines!
Get going already!
Why don't you take the weapons from those useless knights just standing there
and sell them to pay us?
You dare insult us?
These meager ten coins are tantamount to telling me to sell my body for funds!
Yeah, no one's saying that.
Um, your kingdom really will fall if we don't fight.
Your kingdom or your money, Your Grace!
Decide, King!
Wh-Why?!
What'd you expect?!
Ropes don't belong there!
Don't look at me!