Episode 10
The Desire Sensor is Real
W-We've finally found the treasure chest.
That was a long dungeon.
My AP and MP are all used up.
I sure hope there's some sort of recovery item in there.
No. The monsters of this dungeon were fierce.
A great weapon would be nice.
All right, let's open it.
But if it's another trap...
Th-That's right!
The treasure chests in this dungeon...
Oh, a treasure chest already!
Things are looking up!
A-A trap, huh?
It's another trap!
Are you okay?
You're splitting me in two!
Give it to me harder!
I'm gonna drop this bitch.
My magic can check the contents of a chest without having to open it.
You should have mentioned that earlier.
I see!
There's something inside.
Okay, I'm opening it!
No! E-Eels!
There was indeed something inside.
Th-That doesn't help us at all!
That is not a proper place to insert yourself!
B-But what a strange sensation...
True, all the chest so far have been traps.
But that doesn't mean this one will be!
I used my magic to check, and I am certain:
something is inside.
That doesn't help us at all.
B-But if it really is a healing item or a weapon...
We gotta open it!
Okay, we'll decide who opens it with rock-paper-scissors.
Rock, paper, shoot!
That's cheating!
Says the cheater!
Who are you to talk?
Fine! We're all in this together, so we'll all do it!
Good idea.
O-Okay!
Everything is in fate's hands now.
All right, let's do this!
Here goes nothing!
I am the Goddess of Truth.
Is what you desire the Badge of Courage?
Or perhaps the Crest of Justice?
Neither.
How honest!
I shall bestow upon you both.
I said I don't want them!
Give us something better than that junk!
We're in a real bind!
What a useless goddess!
Hey, get back here!
You're a goddess! Help us out!
Please!
Save us!