It's the student council president Ninomiya Ai!
She's always so beautiful!
Of course she is!
She's the daughter of the leader of the Ninomiya Group!
She’s pretty!
So beautiful!
Ai-sama!
As expected from Ai-chan!
She's the number one idol at school!
Of course.
My name is Yoshizawa Atsushi.
Right now I am in serious regret.
Why did I fall in love at first sight of Ninomiya Ai?
Student Council Meeting Room
It's too cold!
All you are is a caddie, and you
can't even make decent tea?
You're a piece of garbage that doesn't
even qualify as a human.
You piece of trash! You moron
that can't even do the basics!
You're really useless!
I didn't know her personality was this horrible...
First off, making tea is the basics of the basics of all work!
If I had only noticed earlier...
When will you be able to do your job properly!?
This hate...
I will definitely avenge myself!
Pick up the slack already!
The Beautiful-Legged Sex Slave President Ai
The Ninomiya Ai Arc
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Student Council Room
This, this is...
I found it in this room.
Kaichou's family,
the Ninomiya group has been bribing
members of parliament.
This hold all the details of those hidden trades.
This is a big case, Prez.
Not only the Ninomiya Group,
but all industries and governments
will be affected by this scandal.
And it is your fault.
You were the one to lose the key to this room.
Don't you think it's interesting?
You're just a caddie here! How much do you want!
I don't need money.
What I want is...
What are you...
Ai... It's your body!
You want me to keep quiet about
the secret trades, right?
Then you'd better do what I say.
Ai... you... belong to me...
I'll leave the best part to the last.
How cold. Let's enjoy ourselves.
What are you expecting me to enjoy?
Look over here.
This time it's your lips.
Don't joke with me!
I'll never kiss you!
Oh really?
Stop! How vulgar of you!
Oh, were your ears a weak spot?
You're quite cute, unexpectedly, Prez.
No, don't... you bastard...
About time I go for the main course.
What is this?
You perverted maniac!
That's quite rude.
I'd prefer you call it a fetish.
Shut up, you pervert!
What are you doing...
The smoothness of the tights on my penis...
And the softness of thigh and calf despite
also being elastic and resilient...
Enjoying something like this... you're abnormal!
It's soft and squishy... it feels incredibly good, Prez.
That's such a disgusting way to put it! You pervert!
That was a compliment.
You think that there'd be a woman who'd be
happy if you told her that her legs were fat?
You stupid chimp who can't even
understand a woman's mind!
Oh, so you were worried about how fat your legs were.
Who would be...
They're not fat at all.
The meat on them just makes them feel even better.
Was that a sarcastic insult?
It's the best compliment I can give.
Prez's legs are sexy.
Stop saying such stupid things...
Well, let me enjoy these beautiful legs!
You pervert! Maniac!
How horrible! You're the worst person
in human history! You...
It's getting sticky, gross!
I feel very good, though.
Of course you are! You're doing all
these perverted things you want!
What was that voice just now?
Could it be that Prez is...
There's no way that's possible!
It's just itchy!
But of course!
There's no way the daughter of the Ninomiya
Group would get aroused from a dick
rubbing at the back of her knee!
Of course!
Amazing...
How filthy! You won't be forgiven for anymore of this!
Listen... listen to what I say!
I'm telling you... to... stop...
I'm... I'm cumming!
What incoming, you say?
There's no way you wouldn't know!
I'll let out lots for you!
What it is, exactly?
Get away from me! Right now!
I'll let It out Lots of it.
I'll ejaculate from Ai's legs!
No!
How dare you spray such filthy fluids...
It's great view, Prez.
Come to think of it, it must be a twist of fate
that I picked up the key to this room.
After sneaking in, I was lucky enough
to fine that account book.
My grudge from those days of being bossed around,
I'll make sure you jay, Prez.
As long as there is that account book,
Ai, you are mine!
No! Don't!
Don't look! Don't look!
You're beautiful, Prez.
You've got such a good look right now.
I'll never forgive you...
In the name of Ninomiya, I won't let you
get away with this! Remember that!
Stop! Go away!
Well then, Prez, no, I mean Ai.
You are about to make a once-in-a-lifetime contract.
With I, the person you called a piece of trash!
Who would do that with you!
I won't accept this! There is no way I'd let it happen!
Don't! No!
How is it? Any thoughts on losing your virginity!?
Thoughts on losing your chastity to
a man you hate blackmailing you?
Don't think you have me in your hands just like this!
Does it hurt?
This is reality.
The reality that your virginity was taken by me!
I'll train it well.
Into my personal hole!
Who'd ever be... your personal...
But don't you look like you feel good there?
Don't joke with me! There's no way I'd...
be aroused by something like this...
Don't put it... so deep inside!
It's all the way inside me...
By such a horrible man... I am...
When attacked, yelled at or shamed, you get aroused.
You're a pervert! Why don’t you admit already?
There's no way that's true!
I'm the daughter of Ninomiya!
Then what's with this soaked pussy!?
No, that's not it, That's not it, it's not, it's not!
You masochist who get excited from
a dick forcefully stuffed inside!
Who would ever...
I’m cumming, inside you. I'll cum lots inside Ai!
No way! The semen of a pervert like
you doesn't deserve to be with me!
Cumming... Take it all, Ai!
I don't want your child!
Such a horrible man's is... flowing inside me...
I'll make you regret right away...
It's because you got too carried away.
Look at that.
Well you've got to put up some fight or it won’t be fun.
I'll make you pay for all the grudges with that body.
Woah! Satsuki senpai's legs wrapped
tightly in stockings...
As expected from her training in gymnastics.
And Mana senpai in white tights!
It's looks so soft and squishy!
Both look so tasty!
What are you looking at?
Ai-chan?
President Ninomiya!
You pervert!
You're the worst to be skipping work and
looking at Satsuki's and Mana’s legs!
There will never be a girl in your
life that'd give her heart to you.
What are you doing?
I just thought that I have to get
the Prez to understand properly.
Understand what?
Our standings in this situation.
Well then, hurry and start, please.
Here? Someone will come.
You don’t care if I expose that account book?
I get it.
It's hard already? What kind of weirdo are you?
Ah, the fine made silk tights, this sensation on the skin...
Prez's tights are the best!
It's great, Prez! More strongly, please!
You pervert!
Who'd be happy from someone's feet...
You're going to stain my feet and tights again...
Such humiliation, over and over again...
I’m cumming, Prez! I'm cumming from your feet!
Don't! It'll get all over me!
No... so much... so much semen got on
me... even though I shouldn't let it...
As expected from a high class lady!
Even the semen looks pretty as if they were accessories!
You idiot!
Staining them like this... I have the inspection
of club activities after this!
Why don't you just go like this?
What did you say?
I get it...
So gross... it’s wet... no...
Well then, Prez, let's go.
Satsuki senpai... the usual purple tights are great,
But you’re wonderful in a leotard, too...
You pervert!
Pervert, you say?
Please endure this.
If anything, you're the daughter of the Ninomiya group.
Prez is a real pervert, too.
Sticking a vibrator in your pussy and getting
excited in front of a crowd like this...
Shut up...
We're birds of a feather.
President Ninomiya!
C'mon, Satsuki senpai is looking.
If you don't say a greeting, they'll find out
about Prez's abnormal sex fetishes.
You... you're the worst of people...
You'd better remember this.
This humiliation... I won't lose to it.
Ai-chan! Welcome back.
Mana? Why are you here?
What are you talking about? This is the
meeting room of the student council,
It's our room!
Oh yeah... I guess so...
Anything wrong, Ai-chan?
Nothing, really. It's nothing...
Ai-chan?
I'm fine.
I'm alright, so... please go back to work.
Caddie over there!
You get to work and tidy up the reports, too!
Oh, understood. As you say.
Ai-chan, please put the seal of approval on these.
Huh? J-Just leave them there...
Are you really alright?
Of course I'm alright.
Are you... done yet?
Aren't you done with it yet?
Let's see... just a little more, Prez.
Hurry up already!
It's not like...
I have all the time in the world... to wait... around...
It's about to come, Prez.
Alright, hurry and come!
Hurry... hurry...
No, no, no... no, no...
Ai-chan!
Are you alright? Let’s go to the nurses office.
Oh? She was able to endure it all?
I wonder if it's the pride from being the
daughter of the Ninomiya Group.
I'll make you feel more and morel Enough
that you'll go mad in agony!
What's wrong? What's that face?
Hurry... and take that out!
I did as you said and did the inspection
with it inside already!
That's not gonna happen yet.
Stop it! Not this position...
Prez's thick and slutty legs!
I’ll be sure to enjoy this!
Stop violating my legs!
If you're going to violate me, then properly...
Properly? What is that?
Don't push your hot and hard thing
up my legs... don't rub...
Prez's leg-pussy is the best!
What do you mean leg-pussy!? Don't joke with me!
Don't rub so much!
It's coming...
Between my legs... my legs are being...
You're squeezing quite hard.
You actually want me to rub it
harder against you, don't you?
There' no way...
It's getting all sticky between my legs...
Just having a dick thrusting between your legs
is getting you so aroused?
You're a real pervert.
You're the pervert... here!
You're so obsessed with legs... and
you're happily violating my legs...
They being violated... my legs, they're being...
It's like your legs are actually genitals!
No! That's no it!
I'm the daughter of the Ninomiya family!
I should be high classed, of surpassing
excellence, and perfect!
There's no way I’m slutty...
No way...
It's hot... it's getting larger between
my legs, and it's twitching...
I'm going to cum!
No, no! You can't cum!
Don’t let out your semen! Don’t spray your hot stuff...
That's just like you're asking for it!
If you cover my body and face with sticky semen... I... I...
Cumming!
No... it's on me... so much semen is on me...
I'm being stained... I...
Sticky and dirty semen is making me...
This is great This smell.
Don't say that...
It went all the way inside at once with no resistance!
No, no, no!
I don't want the penis of a mere caddie!
You're quite stubborn.
My insides are so full... it's being filled by a penis...
It's completely become the shape of my dick!
No way... I don't want the shape
of my pussy to change...
I don't want to be someone's personal...
Cumming... I'm going to cum...
No... I'm cumming from this!
Cumming! I'm sending it all in to Ai's womb!
No! Not inside!
It's hot! It's deep inside my pussy... it's in my womb...
It'll remember...
Inside my pussy... the sensation of semen
is seeping deep into my body...
Where is the president?
I think Ai-chan wasn't feeling well.
Come to think of it, when she came for inspection,
it seemed like she was pacing off...
I wonder if Atsushi-kun is taking care of her properly.
I'll go look.
Me too!
It suits you well. What a slutty bunny here.
No way! This kind of outfit... it's so perverted!
It's more outrageous that I could imagine.
Especially those thighs wrapped in tights!
Don't! Don’t touch my legs...
I can't believe I’m in a bunny suit... me,
the daughter of the Ninomiya family...
If someone sees this, my power, glory and reputation
as the president will be all gone!
They're rubbing the penis...
My feet are rubbing against the penis...
Your penis is hotter than usual...
It's twitching a lot...
Does it feel good?
Do my feet... does being rubbed
by feet in tights feel good?
I feel good, too!
Your penis is violating the palm of my feet!
I'm cumming... I'll cum lots on Ai's slutty tights!
No! I said no! I won't forgive you
for covering me in semen!
Even though I said not!
So much semen... I'm happy... it spurted so much...
This thick semen... where do you want it next?
No... I can't say it...
There’s no way I could say something so embarrassing...
Satsuki-chan, is Ai-chan there?
Satsuki-chan?
Where do you want it?
No! I can't say it!
I can't say such slutty things!
Please, hurry!
You want it here, don't you?
You slut who can cum from rubbing
your feet against a dick!
You tore it... are you putting your
penis through that hole?
Well then, what should I do?
C'mon!
No... just do it already... I can't hold back anymore...
Put it in...
I want your dick!
Well said! Let's give the good girl a reward!
No!
It's inside! It’s all the way inside!
It's pushing through the flesh in my
pussy and spreading the sides...
You dick... it's so hard and hot,
it's filling me up! So much!
Did you cum just from me putting it in?
Geez, what a slutty bunny!
But... I was holding back for so long...
My pussy... my womb was... so lonely...
So lonely, so... amazing... my insides
are so full form your penis...
So full... it's taking the shape of you penis...
I'm so happy... my womb is happy...
from being filled by your penis...
It feels good... more...
I'm going to cum... I’ll cum inside you like this!
Give it to me! Give your semen to me inside my womb!
Cumming!
Hot stuff is inside! It's inside my womb!
Cumming, I’m cumming from
semen coming in my womb!!