That's Council President, Ninomiya Ai.
She's wonderful as always.
Of course she is.
She's the daughter of the Ninomiya group of companies.
She's beautiful.
Ai-sama!
That's Ai-chan for you,
the number one idol in this school.
But of course.
My name is Yoshizawa Atsushi.
Currently I'm filled with regret...
Regretting that became enamored with her.
Student Council Meeting Room
This is not even half good.
Your only job here is to do minor stuff,
and yet you can't even make good tea.
What a piece of trash human you are.
Trash!
A bird brain with no learning capability whatsoever.
You're such a useless man.
I should have realized how horrible she was from the start.
Besides, preparing tea is the most basic of all minor tasks!
How can I even expect you to work properly then?
I'm definitely going to make her pay.
Clean up your act already!
Beautiful Legged
Ai
Sex Slave President
Ninomiy Ai Charapter
Student Council Room
Th-This is...
I found it in this room.
Your family's corporation, the Ninomiya group of companies,
and the secret funds obtained by some
of the National Diet members.
The exact details of these hidden records are in there.
This is a big deal, President.
The Ninomiya group involved in an illegal
affair, a scandal on a grand scale.
And the only reason I found out,
was because you carelessly dropped the key to this room.
Don't you find this turn of events interesting?
You're just an underling!
How much do you want?
I have no need of your money.
What I want is...
Wh-What are you...?
Is none other than your body, Ai!
You want me to stay silent about the missing funds, right?
Then do as I say.
Ai, you are now mine.
I'm going to save the best for last.
How cold of you.
Let's just enjoy this.
How am I supposed to enjoy this?
First the cheek.
Next, the lips.
Stop fooling around!
I'm definitely not kissing you.
I see...
S-Stop this, it's filthy!
Oh, your ears are a sensitive spot?
That's surprisingly cute, President.
Don't... Stop you scum...
How about we skip to our main course already?
W-What are you doing?
You deviant!
How rude of you to call me that.
Please properly call it fetishism.
Silence, you pervert!
W-What are you doing...?
The silky sensation as I rub my penis onto your stocking-fitted legs.
The tenderness of its shape is just as good.
Even the softness of the leg itself.
This is just too abnormal.
It's a meat-filled pleasure, President.
I don't want you to speak of it like that, you pervert!
Those are all words of admiration.
You think girls would love being told that their legs are big?
You don't even know a maiden's heart you lowly monkey!
Are you worried by the size of your legs?
I never said anything about...
They're not big.
It is simply a meat-filled to goodness.
What are you really trying to say?
It's the best praise that I can give you.
In other words, your legs are very sexy.
W-What foolish things are you saying?
Now then, let me have a taste of these gorgeous legs.
Y-You pervert! Deviant!
The lowest of the low with a weird foot fetish!
It feels a bit slimy and gross.
Oh, but it feels quite great for me.
Of course it would for you.
Only you would like this perverted act.
What was that moan?
Could you be...?
No way!
It just tickled a bit.
I see.
The daughter of the Ninomiya group of companies,
couldn't possibly be aroused by a penis
that's being rubbed on her leg.
O-Of course...
It's squeezing me.
How filthy.
I won't let you do this any longer.
Listen, hey listen to me!
I said stop...!
I'm about to cum.
Huh? What is about to come out?
You already know that of course.
I'm going to cum lots.
Idiot, what are you...
Let me go right now!
Yeah, I'm going to let it all out.
I'm going to cum between your legs.
No!
How dare you squirt that filthy stuff on me!
What a great sight President.
It's probably the will of fate that I was able
to obtain the key to this room by accident.
I was rummaging through the things inside,
and I found the hidden records.
I’m going to make you pay,
for all of the days that you have humiliated me.
As long as that record exists, Ai,
you are mine.
No, don't!
Don't look, don't look!
It looks beautiful president.
You're positioned quite nicely there.
I definitely won't forgive you.
In the name of the Ninomiya family,
I'm not going to let you get away with this!
Stop, let me go!
Now president...
No, Ai,
let's partake in our everlasting bond.
A bond with a trash of a human such as myself!
And just who would want you?!
I won't accept this.
I definitely Won't!
No, don't!
Well?
How does it feel to get your virginity torn apart?
How does it feel to have it taken from you
by a man whom you're not even close to?
Don't you dare think that you already own me because of this!
Does it hurt? This is reality, you know.
I have just taken your virginity.
Soon I'm going to mold you,
and your pussy to become my own!
W-Who would want to be your...
It looks like you're feeling quite good there.
Stop messing around with me!
I'm not... I'm not a single bit aroused from this.
Don't go so deep inside.
I'm being penetrated up to that point...
So you're a pervert who gets horny
by being shamed and humiliated.
Why don't you just accept that side of yours?
I'm not like that!
I'm the Ninomiya family's daughter!
Then how do you explain this wetness?
No, no, no, no, no!
Cum, and go crazy with this dick!
You masochistic perverted bitch!
I'm not a pervert!
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum lots inside you.
Don't...
I don't want any of your perverted cum!
But, take all of it Ai.
I don't want to bear your child!
F-F-For me to be impregnated by a lowly man such as you...
I'm going to report this soon...!
You've gone too far with your cockiness.
Serves you right.
I guess there's no point in this without a little resistance.
You're going to pay back all that you've
done to me with your body.
Wow, Satsuki-senpai's firm legs.
As expected of someone who does gymnastics.
Mana-senpai's wearing white pantyhose!
It looks very soft and tender!
Both look very delicious.
What are you looking at?
Ai-chan?
President Ninomiya.
You pervert.
Ditching work and ogling at Satsuki and Mana's legs is the worst.
There's no woman that would ever accept you.
Understand that?
What do you want?
Well, I just want to make sure you truly understand.
About what?
The real situation at hand.
Now, start doing it already.
In here? Someone might come.
Do you want me to expose those records?
I get it already.
It's already getting stiff.
What kind of nerves does this thing have?
These smooth and silky stockings,
it's making it nice and stiff.
Your stockings are the best.
That feels great President.
Do it faster.
You pervert, feeling pleasure with this footjob thing...
My feet and stockings are going to get soiled again.
And I'm going to experience this many times...
I'm cumming president.
I'm going to cum on you!
No, you can’t, it will stick...!
Oh no, lots of it sprayed on me.
I can't be seen like this.
As expected from a top-class lady.
Even my cum serves as an accessory to
make you look even more beautiful.
You idiot!
You soiled me when I'm about to do club activities!
Then just go like that.
What?
I get it already.
This feels gross.
It's all sticky...
Now president, let's go.
Satsuki-senpai.
Her purple stockings are good,
but her leotard is also quite nice.
Your pervert.
A pervert, eh?
Do your best.
You're the Ninomiya group's lady, right?
President, you sure are a big pervert.
Feeling aroused by having a vibrator inserted into you in public.
Shut up.
We're in the same boat then.
President Ninomiya.
Look, Satsuki-senpai is looking at us.
She'll find out if you don't greet her properly.
You really are the worst person ever.
Remember this.
I’m not giving in to this humiliation.
Ai-chan, welcome back.
M-Mana, w-why are you here?
What are you saying?
This is the student council meeting room.
It's our room, right?
Y-Yes, you're right.
It is indeed.
Is there something wrong, Ai-chan?
N-Nothing really.
It's nothing.
Ai-chan?
I-I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Just go back to work.
You there, miscellaneous.
Arrange all the reports.
Okay, as you say.
Ai-chan, can you sign these papers for me?
Huh? J-Just leave them there.
Are you really okay?
Of course l am.
Are you still not done yet?
Isn't it done yet?
Well, just a little bit more, President.
Hurry up and finish it.
I don't have all day to wait for...
Here I go now, President.
Okay, just hurry up.
Hurry it up.
Oh no, oh no, oh no...!
Ai-chan, are you alright?
Do you want to go to the infirmary?
So you were able to endure it, eh?
Still prioritizing your family, I see.
Then I'll just have to make you hornier,
so much that you'll no longer be able to live without it.
What's wrong? You don't look good.
Hurry and pull it out already.
I already tried working with it inside as you told me.
Not just yet.
Stop!
This position is...!
Your lewd and meaty legs,
let me have some fun with them!
Don't violate my legs!
If you intend to rape me, then properly..
Properly? Are you trying to say something?
This hot and thick thing is rubbing between them.
I don't want you to rub it like that!
Your leg pussy is the best!
Leg pussy? What are you talking about?
Stop making a fool of me!
Please don't rub it on me anymore.
It's going in and out... just like last time.
It seems to have fit in between quite well.
You really want it to be rubbed some more, right?
No way...
It's starting to feel sticky in between.
I never thought that you'd get horny just
by rubbing my dick against your legs.
You really are a pervert.
P-Pervert? That's you.
Sticking your dick between my legs like this,
and feeling pleasure while violating them with it.
I-I'm being raped.
It's my leg that's being raped.
It's as if your legs are your sexual organs!
No! That's not true.
I'm the daughter of the Ninomiya family.
Elite, excellent, perfect,
not in any way perverted.
Not in any way!
It's getting hot and twitchy now.
I'm about to cum.
No! Don't cum!
It's going to spray it all over me again.
Absolutely don't!
Then it'd be like you want them inside you instead.
For my face, my body, to be sprayed over by cum...
I-I'm cumming!
Oh no, it's all over me.
There's lots of cum on me.
I'm soiled now.
I want it now.
This thick and sticky cum...
This looks good.
This strong scent.
Don't look...
It went all the way in smoothly!
No, no, no!
I don't want some minor member fucking me like this!
Still holding onto your pride, eh?
My insides are getting filled by your dick.
Its shape has become the same as my dick.
No, it just can't change its shape like that.
This can't be, it actually did become exclusively for you...
I'm about to cum, I'm cumming.
Oh no, I'm really cumming.
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to pour everything I've go in your womb.
No, don't cum inside!
It feels hot!
It's pouring in my womb!
I'm too full with semen.
Some of it is even going deep inside my pussy
that it feels like it's part of my body now.
I'm impregnated now...
Where is the president?
Ai-chan doesn't seem to be feeling well.
Oh yes, earlier at the gym she also seemed to be spacing out.
I wonder if Atsushi-kun took care of her properly.
I'm going to take a look.
Oh, I'm coming too.
It looks great on you.
You look like a very horny rabbit.
N-No, these clothes just make me look like a pervert.
It looks even more lewd than I thought.
Especially your healthy and plump legs.
No, if you touch my legs like that...
For me to be a bunny girl,
I, the daughter of the Ninomiya family is...
If someone ever sees this,
my position and reputation as the council president is over.
I'm rubbing your dick.
My feet are making it all sticky.
Your dick feels hotter than normal.
And it's very twitchy too.
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good to be rubbed by these
smooth feet covered in silky stockings?
It feels good for me too.
The underside of my foot feels like it's being raped by this dick.
I'm going to cum lots on your stockings.
No, you can't.
I'm not going to forgive you if you do that.
I already told you not to...
There's lots of cum...
You squirted it all on me.
This sticky cum, where do you want me to pour it next?
No, I can't say it.
I can't say such embarrassing thing.
Satsuki-chan, is Ai-chan there?
Satsuki-chan?
Where do you want me to release it?
No, I can't say it.
I can't say such an embarrassing thing.
Please, hurry.
You want it here, right?
You already came just from rubbing my dick, you obscene woman!
It's torn now.
Are you going to fuck me there now?
Well, how shall I do it then?
N-No way...
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm at my limit now.
Put it in.
I want your dick.
Well said and this is your reward.
It's in, it's going deep inside me!
It's stirring up the insides of my pussy.
It's getting stretched and widened.
It's filled with your thick and hard dick.
You already came right after I put it in?
Jeez! You really are a horny rabbit!
That's because I've’been waiting for it already!
And my pussy is lewdly twitching now because of it.
Oh wow, your dick is really filling my pussy.
It's really become the shape of your dick.
I'm happy, and my womb is glad as well.
Give me more of your dick!
It feels really good.
Just a little more and...
I'm going to cum.
And I'll let it all out inside your pussy.
Please, give it all to my pussy.
I'm cumming!
It's hot inside me!
I can feel it in my womb!
My womb is cumming!
I'm cumming!