Thank you very much.
It's prospering again today.
Thank you Kouji-san.
Oh... Uhm... that's no problem...
I'll help you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's ok.
Don't be like that.
Are you done?
Arisa, sleep early or else you'll be late for class tomorrow.
It's all right.
W-Wait, Arisa-chan...
Hey, can I go to your house this Sunday?
Hey, don't be irresponsible.
I can go right?
Arisa-chan, even if you go there, there's nothing fun there.
You can live here any way.
There's an open room too...
Arisa!
Arisa-chan, that room is for your father who just passed away.
Yes it is, but...
Arisa-chan, your father who went out to sea and had an accident, the 1st anniversary of his death is fast approaching.
He might be sad in heaven.
Good night.
SubDesuーH Presents
Beautiful
land
lady.
Mie
Mourning
Wife
Just what I expect from Kouji-san, it's delicious.
It's not a big deal.
Hm?
I want you to teach me how to cook.
I want to help my mom.
It's better to study it.
I've studied it so there's no need.
The store is not that prospering, but it is not narrow so it's all right.
I just wanted to be with you guys, but am I disturbing?
Uhm, I love you Kouji-san.
Do you hate me, Kouji-san?
I don't hate you.
Hug me, Kouji-san.
No... It's embarrassing...
Don't...
Don't!
Kouji-san, please be gentle...
I-It hurts.
It hurts.
Kouji-san...
Thank you, Arisa-chan.
Don't look around so much.
Oh, ok.
I'll bring some tea.
Thank you.
Please don't touch the things around.
Small Restaurant
Megumi
Oh I'm sorry.
No problem.
Don't be like that.
Did it catch your attention?
Kouji-san, could it be that you like my mom?
I-It's not like that.
Really? I can trust you, right?
I was born when my mom was 20.
This is me.
You have been cute for a long time.
Say it again.
You're cute.
I'm happy.
Hey Kouji-san,
Hm?
Lets have sex again.
I'm going to suck this?
Y-Yes.
Use your mouth to suck this.
Okay. I'll do my best to suck it
Relax a bit more.
You're putting too much strength in your hand.
Good. That's good.
Something bitter like a juice came out.
Continue licking it.
Arisa-chan.
Put it in your mouth and continue sucking it.
A-Arisa-chan, I'm sorry.
I went a bit too far.
No, you did not.
Arisa will do her best.
I'll suck Kouji-san's dick with my best.
It's good. It's so good.
I-I'm at my limit!
Drink the semen which comes out from my dick!
It's bitter.
I drank something so bitter.
You drank a lot, Arisa-chan.
So I must give you a reward.
The big one is entering...
Good...  It feels so good.
Does it hurt? Are you ok?
Yes. It doesn't hurt, it feels so good.
I.. I...
I-I'm cumming!!!
Kouji-san, it was so good.
It was good for me too.
Do you love me?
O-Of course!
Then say "I love you" many times.
I love you so much.
Kouji-san...
Kouji-san, I have something important to tell you.
Hm? What is it, Arisa-chan?
Please come with me.
W-What's the meaning of this, Arisa-chan?!
Mom said she is lonely...
Eh?
Since the time my father had an accident at sea,
she has been bearing it all by herself.
W-What are you saying?!
My mom imagines you as she masturbates.
Kouji-san, you like my mom, right?
A-Arisa-chan.
If so then it's ok with me,
if you're with my mom.
Kouji-san... Arisa... please...
It entered! Kouji-san's-
Good. Do it harder!
Kouji-san, from now on let the three of us have a lot of sex together.
It's hot! It came out inside!
Mom, you want to cum some more, right?
Good! It's better than before!
No... I'm cumming!!
Konno
Family
Tomb