She'll soon be going back from studying abroad.
Look at this, Hakkun!
I'm going to come from craving your semen!
Mao-nee...
I-I'm coming! I'm coming—!
We'll have lots of sex when she gets home!
Bitch Gakuen ga Seijun na Hazu ga Nai!!?
There's no way for that bitch school to be pristine!!?
First Volume
Bitch Gakuen ga Seijun na Hazu ga Nai!!?
There's no way for that bitch school to be pristine!!?
First Volume
Hey, what are you dreaming about?
Huh?
Huh?!
Th-This is bad...
My mind spontaneously drifted
from reality while in this situation...
Okay then, it's the usual doodle time now.
So, it'll be your cock today, Amami-kun.
Arisu-chan, stop this already.
Am I not the only male student left here?
Our father founded the Amami Holy Mother's Academy.
It started to become a co-ed this school year,
and male students have enrolled.
But Arisu-chan and her companions started to mob them.
They bullied them by doodling on their cocks,
making all the other guys drop out of school.
Then, it means that you're dropping out of school.
It is my responsibility as a son to protect this school!
My little sister Airi is here as well,
and Mao-nee will be going
back from studying overseas.
There is no way that I'll quit.
The current principal is my mother.
You siblings aren't needed here.
Isn't my late mother the principal's elder sister?
Why is there a need for us relatives to have a feud?
Seriously, you bark a lot for a mere dog.
Our chatter ends here.
I'll be playing with that lowly and puny
cock of yours, so prepare yourself!
Th-This is...
Arisu-chan?
I wonder what you are doing
to our Hassaku there?
Mao-san!
Mao-nee!
You two may now leave.
O-Okay...
Okay.
I have a few questions for you.
It seems that you need some
punishment, Arisu-chan.
Wait, stop that!
Come on, show us some smile there!
This is the dick of Hakkun,
the boy who you played with a lot!
Isn't that nice of you? So, you consider
this as lowly and puny!
Just how loose your pussy could be to say that.
I-It's so hard! So, this is how Amami-kun's penis is.
M-Mao-nee...
I-If you keep stroking it that much...
If I keep stroking it, what's gonna happen?
Wh-What, you ask?
H-His precum...
It has Amami-kun's scent in it!
Come on, don't you love doing this?
Coming on her hair and having your
semen hang on it... That's so lewd!
Th-This sensation...
This is bad! C-Coming! It's coming out!
You can shoot it out.
Spray it on Arisu-chan's face until it's all white!
C-Coming!
Alright, plunge it into her mouth!
It's so hot! H-His semen is incredible!
Something with a fishy smell is coming out!
I was only gone for a short while
and things became like this.
Our aunt treats you as a nuisance...
Your dick is all sticky now...
Mao-nee, aren't you supposed
to return next month?
I wanted to see you as soon as I can so I went back!
It's been a while since I smelled your semen!
I can't take it anymore!
Mao-nee!
I'll drink the remaining semen that's still
in your urethra so it won't go to waste.
Mao-nee, I just came, so the tip is still sensitive...
I'm glad to see that your cock is still hard!
Mao-nee, I've been longing for you
to suck my cock all this time!
You only want me to suck it?
Is there nothing else you want me to do?
Huh? Oh...
It's so stiff!
It's so big... It feels so good!
Hakkun, both your cock and my panties
are digging into my pussy!
Th-They're rubbing against me!
M-Mao-nee... This is bad,
you're rubbing the tip!
No, you shouldn't come again! Hold it in!
I want to have your enduring cock inside me!
It's alright, put it in!
I-It went inside!
The tip went in my pussy!
Deeper... Push it deeper inside me!
Mao-nee!
I-Inside me... Go deep inside me!
Your cock is amazing! It feels good!
No... I-I'm coming!
Hakkun, your enduring cock is so huge!
You'll tear my womb open!
Mao-nee, your pussy is squeezing
me so hard! It's so tight!
That's because you're making me feel too good!
This is bad, I'm already about to come!
I-It's alright...
I want to come from having your semen, Hakkun!
Give it to me, squirt it out and give me a creampie!
C-Coming!
Let's do it more, I haven't had enough yet!
I want a whole year's worth of your cock!
I want it... I want plenty more of your cock juice!
I want a lot of it!
I love it...
I love it when you're grinding deep in my pussy!
Make an even bigger mess of it...
You can do as you wish, Hakkun!
My pussy belongs to you!
I'm coming! I'm coming—!
Me too...
I want to shoot a lot of semen
in your pussy, Mao-nee!
Shoot it in! I want you to soak my womb
with plenty of your piping hot juice!
It's gushing into me...
It feels hot and there's so much!
No...
I-I feel something coming out... No way!
I'm coming—!
It won't stop... I can't make it stop!
M-My pee won't stop...
Whoa! Hakkun, you're amazing!
You deliriously keep on pounding me!
I'll end up peeing myself again!
Wh-What's this?
I-I'm coming!
H-Huh?
No, my pee is leaking out...
A-Amami-kun...
A-And Mao-san are...
N-No way!
Arisu-chan...
Y-You two... What do you
think you're doing...
It's just as you can see.
I'm enjoying having Hakkun's humongous
cock after missing it for a whole year!
N-No way...
A-Amami-kun, didn't you tell me back then...
You said that you love me!
Huh, are you talking about that time
in our first year of grade school?
Even if you bring up something from long ago...
Hmm? So, you actually do like Hakkun...
Hakkun, I want you to fuck Arisu-chan!
Huh?!
Wh-What are you talking about?
I-I don't want to, not a situation like this!
Both you and your mother
need to fully understand this.
The one at the top of this school's hierarchy
is none other than the founder's son, Hakkun.
I never thought that Arisu-chan wears
such prim and pure white panties.
But her dew won't seem to stop flowing, so you can see through them!
And moreover, you actually
have inverted nipples!
Look, my fingers went in!
Sh-Shut up! That's none of your concern!
Come on, Hakkun.
She won't stop dripping unless you hurry up
and give her pussy some sperm.
Huh? That's... H-He can't!
O-Okay, I'll give your pussy
some sperm, Arisu-chan.
Arisu-chan, you have to relax your body.
No, stop!
Arisu-chan, here I go!
I-It's so big!
Don't put it in my pussy, it'll get disfigured!
Ouch, it hurts! It's too big!
You're tearing my body in half!
It feels so hot in my belly! I'm burning!
Th-This is too much for me!
N-No, don't move!
I'm begging you, you'll scrape it off!
So, this is your first time, Arisu-chan.
It's alright, you'll get used to it in time.
I-I can't! It really hurts, after all!
Stop!
Oh yeah, don't you love doodling, Arisu-chan?
No, this is embarrassing!
But your inverted nipples are now
gradually getting erect, Arisu-chan.
No, this is embarrassing!
If you like them that much,
I'll write plenty more on you!
Should I pull your nipples out for you?
N-No, don't touch them right now!
Arisu-chan, you're just like a dirty sow!
My pussy feels so hot!
Your cock is burning me!
Amami-kun, your cock is so hard and big!
It's scraping me inside!
I want more of it! Give me your cock!
My once virgin pussy is feeling good!
Keep thrusting, make a mess of me!
You're so tight!
This is bad, it's coming out!
I'm coming!
Hakkun's cock won't be done
just from this much, you know!
No!
No more!
Th-The pleasure is too much!
I don't care anymore!
No... Your cock is scraping my pussy
walls, it's starting to get bruised!
I love your cock!
I wanna have more of your cock, Amami-kun!
Arisu-chan, you're now Hakkun's slave.
From now on, you'll address him as "master".
Yes...
M-Master, allow me to
have your cock inside me!
Amami Hassaku...
He secretly is just like that man...
How despicable!
Good! Good!
I'm coming—!
Amami siblings...
It won't be over yet just from that...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization