Damn, I have to hurry up and go home,
or else Mao-nee will get in a bad mood!
Nii-san...
Airi, what's the matter?
I actually want to ask you about something.
Ask me?
Umm, my chest has been aching lately.
It happens whenever I see you and nee-san together...
I wonder why?
That is an illness, Airi-san!
Sensei, am I sick?
That is called being lovesick.
Both you two siblings have been alone
together until your older sister came back.
It's a feeling that Amami-kun
is being taken away from you.
Huh?!
H-Hey... Sensei, what are you doing?
You're the only one who can
cure this illness, Amami-kun.
Bitch Gakuen ga Seijun na Hazu ga Nai!!?
There's no way for that bitch school to be pristine!!?
Final Volume
Bitch Gakuen ga Seijun na Hazu ga Nai!!?
There's no way for that bitch school to be pristine!!?
Final Volume
We'll go with oral medicine first.
We'll squeeze it from Amami-kun's cock.
Why does it have to be that way?
Th-This is nii-san's dick...
That's right, start by slowly licking it.
O-Okay.
Like this?
Nii-san, your dick became so hard!
Gobble it up to the base and suck it just like that.
O-Okay!
The medicine keeps on trickling out.
I love how it tastes!
More of it will come out if you'll
narrow your mouth while sucking.
Oh, it's delicious...
It's spreading in my mouth!
I'll let myself loose as well.
Nii-san, I somehow feel dizzy...
Airi-san...
Come here!
Sensei...
Amami-kun,
You have to inoculate Airi-san
using your meat injection.
Put it in, nii-san! Hurry up and treat my illness!
Airi, will this be alright?
H-Hurry!
Administer this inoculation!
It hurts!
Haven't people been saying
that good medicine tastes bitter?
You'll have to bear with it.
You're tearing my groin apart!
It's filling me up inside!
I-It hurts inside my belly!
My groin stopped hurting.
It's starting to feel good...
My breasts are throbbing!
N-Nii-san, keep sucking it more!
My belly feels warm... It feels good!
How is it? Isn't the medicine taking effect?
Yes, I want more of this injection!
Nii-san, I give me a lot more!
It appears that I caught the illness as well.
I want an injection!
In that case, I'll have to treat
you both at the same time!
Amami-kun, there's no need to hold back.
Shove the whole thing in up to my deepest parts!
You're so stiff!
H-Hurry up with that thick and long injection!
S-Sensei, your pussy is so sopping wet.
Stop teasing me.
I-It went inside!
You're ripping me up!
I-I can't get enough of this!
I-It's so deep! It's already driving me crazy!
This fat meat injection is the best!
Ugh... Your pussy suddenly tightened!
I never felt this extreme pleasure before!
Nii-san... G-Give me the injection as well!
You're inside me!
Your hot thing is going deep inside me!
My womb is throbbing in awe!
The heat is gradually spreading all over!
Airi-san, the medicine is taking effect!
I'm already about to come!
I almost forgot...
Amami-kun, the principal is calling you over.
My aunt?
Hassaku-kun, you're going to be expelled.
I can't allow such indecent deeds in this school!
I wonder if it's alright
for you to talk that way?
Wh-Why are these...
Everything that you did
was being recorded, auntie.
Did you think that I just left to
study abroad without any plans?
Oh, it's you.
I know all about it.
About the fact that you are our father's lover...
And that he chose our mother, which is
your younger sister, and casted you aside.
No, stop!
And after our parents died from an accident,
you took revenge by taking over this school.
That's also the reason why you
forced me to study abroad.
That's why I worked my way
through the School Board
and had this school become co-ed.
It's all for the purpose of enrolling
Hakkun here and protecting the school.
Does this cock resemble our father's?
Weren't you actually craving for it?
Hakkun, your cock is the best!
It's the most delicious thing in the whole world!
Be honest and admit it.
Don't you want this thing, auntie?
I want it... L-Let me suck it!
Let me suck that meat rod as well!
W-Wow, it's filling up my mouth!
Even the taste is the same as that man's!
Hey, auntie... Don't you want to
put it inside you now?
Yes, I want to have this inside my pussy!
Then, you'll have to beg for it.
Say "Put your cock inside my pussy"!
P-Please put your dick inside me!
Use that huge thing of yours
to ravage my sopping wet pussy!
My pussy is getting stretched wide!
Your whole dick went inside...
Th-They're the same... You're hitting
the same spots as that man!
Oh... That's right!
Make a broken mess out
of my pussy just like he did!
Th-This is bad... I'm about to come!
I'm coming too!
Your thick meat rod is making me come!
I-I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
Do you understand now? Everything
in this school belongs to Hakkun.
Hakkun, how about letting auntie enjoy
some anal sex while you're at it?
A-Anal? I never did that before!
Then, isn't it about time?
After all, our father already
had your pussy all worn out.
Give your anal virginity to Hakkun.
D-Don't! Something that
thick won't fit inside me.
D-Don't!
N-No!
M-My asshole is getting stretched wide! S-Stop!
Wow, this is incredible!
It feels like I'm being strangled.
My rectal walls are clinging to your dick!
How does it feel?
Aren't you glad to be deflowered on both holes
by the two men of the Amami household?
My gut is being stirred into a mushy mess...
I'll really go crazy...
Then, we'll have to make you
more accustomed to this.
Hakkun, move even harder.
Th-That's too intense!
If this goes on, even my asshole will get
molded to the shape of Amami-kun's dick!
C-Coming!
No—!
It's gushing in! Your semen is pouring into me!
I-It's flowing back from inside my belly!
N-No!
I can't take this anymore, it feels good!
I-I'm coming!
It's in my ass again!
The virginities of my two holes were
stolen by both father and son.
Auntie, you'll address Hakkun
as "master" from now on.
Yes... Master...
Please use both of my two holes any time you wish.
Both of you, mother and daughter,
are Hakkun's cumdumps forever.
Hakkun, give me more!
Yes!
I'm coming again! I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
I-I-I'm gonna leak!
It's leaking out!
My pee came out!
Nii-san, use my pussy whenever you want!
Fill my naughty pussy to the brim as well!
Do it, make an even bigger
broken mess out of my asshole!
The future of this school will be reversed now.
And what sits at the top is Hakkun's cock!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji