Saki...
She was killed!
She was killed! Same as Naoya!
By that woman!
Killed! By that woman!
We're all going to be killed!
Jun!
We're going to die!
Stop!
Stop! Stop it, Jun!
Jun. Jun!
Wakamiya... Do you know what happened to Wakamiya?
Seiya, too... by that woman!
Jun! Jun! Why did Naoya...
That woman...
White room... White room...
Jun! Where is that room?
Killed!
Stay away!
Akira...
You!
l don't know you. l don't remember meeting you.
Those women are in my way!
That's why you're killing us?
Kill you?
l showed the shame of those women.
Behind their proper faces, l revealed their true colors.
Then, why did you kill Naoya?
Selfish and snobby Saki,
high-maintenance Yukari,
and the happy one who loves to cook... Sayaka?
l can't stand any of them.
Wait! Please wait!
Wakamiya... Wakamiya...
Give her back!
Seiya...
Yukimura!
Shit! Those guys again?
Soft... So soft.
Seiya...
Shit!
Everybody... by those guys!
Wakamiya's diary?
Oh, yeah. This is built exactly like Wakamiya's room.
Maybe even on the inside?
July 19th.
We all went to the pool, but Sayaka got all the attention with this bikini with lace on it. lt pisses me off! She likes Akira, too. Always so pitiful.
ls that what that woman wrote?
She even knows we went to the pool.
Stop it, Jun! Please!
Wakamiya?
No!
Don't!
Wakamiya!
Are you all right?
Jun, no!
B-Beautiful...
Seiya!
Don't, Jun!
Jun, stop!
So soft... Seiya's tits.
Jun, l don't want this!
Seiya, we're all going to be killed by that woman.
So...
Look how it is already.
No!
How terrible. You detest it that much?
No... No... No...
What do you think you're doing, Jun?
Stop, already.
lt's all that woman's fault.
No!
-Jun, stop it right now!
No, Jun!
No, stop it!
lt's in.
No, no...
lt's so warm inside you, Seiya.
l'm so happy to have some memories with you.
Seiya... Seiya... l'm already...
Don't! No!
Seiya... Seiya...
Don't! No! No!
No!
Seiya...
Se... Seiya...
Jun! What happened?
Jun!
Wakamiya!
He laid hands on me.
That's it. Open this door, Wakamiya.
Wherever Seiya goes, acting like a honor student...
But l've had it.
l won't let it go Seiya's way.
Wakamiya.
l'm Maya.
l'm not Seiya.
Wakamiya!
What are you saying?
The other personality that lies inside Seiya.
Other personality?
The oppressed Seiya...
The deep envious true color or something like that.
Wakamiya has...
a split personality?
l've been waiting for you, Akira.
To lure me into this mansion...
This trip was all planned by Wakamiya.
To have you in my hands.
But why do that to everyone else?
So you wouldn't suspect me.
But to do those things...
What are you doing? Akira!
Yukimura! This isn't Wakamiya!
What are you saying?
Help! Sayaka! Akira is...
Maya! That's enough, already!
What's wrong with you, Akira?
Putting you and everyone else through all this pain...
was all her doing!
Don't!
There's no way Seiya would do such a thing!
That's right, Sayaka.
What's so funny, Seiya?
You.
You're always acting like a princess,
and to see you take on two guys you don't even know...
Seiya! Why would you say something like that?
Yukimura! l'm telling you, that's not Wakamiya!
How debauched, getting it from whomever you can.
She's from inside Wakamiya.
She's a different personality, called Maya.
l'm the one who lured everyone here.
Wakamiya has a split personality.
l wanted to blow off steam at you guys.
lt's a lie.
She killed Naoya, and just now killed Jun in front of me!
Seiya, it's a lie, right?
You're an eyesore!
ln front of the guys, you sell yourself as cute.
l don't do that.
lt's such an act for you to say you like cooking.
You're terrible, Seiya.
Spiteful bitch.
Distorted and ugly... l like that expression on you.
Seiya.
Good... all messed up with tears.
Don't touch me!
Saki, who did whatever she wanted...
Maya!
Yukari, who got whatever she wanted...
Stop, already. No more.
Akira... You...
Let Wakamiya free.
l want you.
Akira.
Maya.
Akira. Touch me, too.
Wakamiya.
Please.
Please...
Come on, Akira. Please.
Maya...
Akira.
lt's inside.
l've been waiting.
lt's inside. Akira.
The women who tempted you... l hated them all.
Stop all this, Maya.
lf you stop now, Seiya's headed for prison.
What?
Locked up in a mental institution, if she's lucky.
Damn it.
Help me, Akira.
Please, Akira.
Let Wakamiya free.
Akira.
Stop, Jun!
Maya, let Wakamiya free.
Akira!
Maya, please.
No! l...
Let Wakamiya free!
No... l'm Seiya!
Maya.
No... Akira!
No... Akira... No...
Here, sit down there.
Do you remember anything?
Don't push yourself too hard.
Just let me know if you remember anything.
Do you think it's something in this room, Doctor?
When l brought her to this room yesterday, too...