We have to go back soon and help out with dinner.
lt's okay. They have five people. lt's too much trouble.
No, Naoya and Jun are helping out, too.
Don't talk about guys. lt's just the two of us here.
But...
l wonder how deep this lake is.
Well, it's a dam, so there must be all kinds of things at the bottom.
Maybe a town at the bottom?
Maybe a sunken corpse? There had to be graves around here.
Please stop it.
Hey, is the bread toasted?
Just about.
The jam's ready. Look.
The blackberries you picked this afternoon.
We picked up some firewood.
This should be enough.
Welcome back.
Yeah, you saved us.
Sorry we're late.
Oh, Yukari.
Hey, how was it?
lt was a good atmosphere... all creepy.
What do you mean, creepy?
Naoya, l left the boat there, so move it later.
Okay, okay.
Then l'll go bring the boat before dinner.
Jun, let's go.
lt's like a movie.
"Stand by Me..." wasn't it?
But there's no train coming. lt's off-track.
D-Don't... lt's a story about going to see a corpse.
ldiot! lt'd be great if there were a dead body!
Ouch!
There's no limit to your cowardice!
Sayaka, don't fall and hurt yourself!
l'm okay.
l don't want to carry you on the walk back.
Fine. Akira will carry me, then.
What are you, a little kid?
There... lsn't that a train station?
lt's pretty run-down.
What's the matter? Wakamiya...
Never mind. lt's nothing.
All right. We should go soon.
l'm thirsty!
Don't, Shindoh.
lf you're going to drink from it, we should go further upstream.
Yes, that's a better idea.
Yeah?
Let's go.
What road is this?
Shindoh! lt's spring water.
Move it! Move it!
Hey, don't push. That's dangerous.
The climb was worth it!
Wish we had a water bottle.
To do what?
lf you make coffee with mineral water, it's really good.
There are a lot of minerals here, like from the Adirondacks.
You're well-informed.
We'll come get some tomorrow.
lf Naoya is drinking it, it might as well be tap water!
lt's only water.
We should go back soon.
Shut up.
Ouch!
Yeah, we should go down. We've climbed up pretty far.
Let's go.
Hey, the sun is going down quite a bit.
Wow, great! A waterfall!
We didn't pass any place like this.
Are we lost?
The direction should be right.
lt's getting cold.
That's mountain weather.
We should hurry.
You say hurry, but we're lost!
Don't get scared all the time!
Ouch!
Knock it off, Naoya! This isn't the time!
You don't have to yell all of a sudden.
Rain. This is seriously starting to suck.
Well, all we can do is head down. Let's go.
What's the matter?
There.
A light!
A light?
Let's go.
l'll go ahead and check it out.
Wow! What a big house.
Let's ask for directions inside.
Hey, the gate's open.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Hurry up!
Wow. ls this building a hotel, or what?
Let's go and ask.
lt's open.
Excuse me.
We'd like to ask for some directions.
ls anybody home?
Why don't we go in for a bit?
lsn't anyone home?
You should check it out!
Who, me?
Yes, you.
All right, l'll go check it out a little bit.
Jun, you come along.
l'm going, too?
Wait a minute.
What are you going to do?
lt's okay. We already announced ourselves.
Excuse me!
l'll look around, too.
ls anybody here?
lt's like a restaurant.
Wow, a row of knives!
What?
The heat's on! There's someone here!
Don't panic! We're looking for that someone!
Sorry.
What is your problem?
Excuse me, is anybody home?
Somethings funny.
This is a sign that someone's here.
Sayaka.
Huh?
Check the second floor.
Huh? Why bother? lt looks like nobody's home.
lt's raining. And those guys aren't back yet.
Seiya...
l'm going to have a look. Let's go.
ls anybody home?
lt's locked.
Where are Wakamiya and the others?
They went to check the second floor.
We shouldn't all roam around.
Let's leave once Naoya gets back.
Seems no one's here.
Seriously? How are we going to get back to the camp site?
lt's still raining, too.
What are they doing, anyway?
Wakamiya?
Akira!
Why are you in a panic?
Where's Sayaka?
She's not with you?
We came upstairs together, but... it suddenly... got dark.
When l came to... l was in my room.
Your room... Wakamiya? What are you saying?
lt's built exactly like my room!
Really?
Who did this?
Where's Sayaka?
Shindoh said she was with you.
lt's Sayaka!
ls that you, Sayaka? Sayaka!
What's the matter? ls that you, Sayaka?
Yukimura!
Hold on!
No! Don't look!
Sayaka!
Sayaka... Sayaka!
Who? Who did this?
A woman...
Woman?
Akira!
Sayaka? What happened?
We're locked in this house.
The doors and windows are locked.
The windows are barred from the outside.
What?
Take care of Yukimura. l'm going to check it out a bit.
What's going on?
lt's not opening, right?
What's going on? What's the matter with this house?
We broke in, but we don't deserve this.
What are they accomplishing by locking us in?
To do that to Yukimura...
Naoya isn't back yet.
So, we have to look for him, too?
Ouch.
What a bad joke. Come on. Take this off.
We called out, but no one responded.
No, we didn't come in to steal anything.
l have something for you guys to help out with.
What? Don't scare us.
Just put that dangerous thing away.
So, what do we have to do?
Come on. Take this thing off.
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
You live here, right?
What? lf that's what you want, you don't need Jun.
So, take this thing off.
Oh! Hey!
l can satisfy you all by myself.
You like this kind of thing? You have good taste.
You're good.
lf you take this off, l'm good to go.
You know, if you do that much...
Yeah! l can let it go?
Yeah... l'm just about to...
Hey!
Oh, come on. Let me cum.
l'll let you take care of the ladies you came with.
You'd never be able to tell you're like this by your looks.
Then, you'll wait right here?
So, if it's gonna be like that, there's that chick in pigtails.
Her name is Seiya.
Let me do it with her!
She's always putting on the valedictorian princess look.
She even yelled at me today.
l want to see the look on her face when l jam this thing in.
But before that... Aren't you digging it, too?
Don't get embarrassed. Let's have fun.
Shut up!
Barbaric, sloppy, and vulgar! You're always like this!
Always?
Don't! Hey! Hey!
l can't let you go home alive.
But l'll let you have a good time.
Where did those guys go?
What are these residents planning?
Shindoh! Chikami!
ls that Shindoh?
What happened?
Naoya is...
Naoya?
Nao...
Naoya...
Naoya.
Who did this?
Sayaka!
They didn't have to kill him.
What's going to happen to us?
Naoya! Shit! Why...
lf we stay on the second floor, something bad is going to happen.
Sayaka locked herself in that room.
Man, you're heavy. Naoya.
Walk yourself, damn it!
Seiya... Seiya...
lt's okay. Sayaka, calm down.
l'm going to go look for Jun.
Wakamiya? Wakamiya, l'm coming in.
Yukimura?
What happened to Wakamiya?
Seiya is... Help. Seiya is...
-Yukimura...
Seiya is...
Maybe... Wakamiya.
Help... Seiya is... Seiya is... Help...
Princess...
You own three dogs that cost a few thousand dollars each?
You always take care of them. You can be pampered today.
No, a spoiled princess can't be pleased so easily.
Come.
Don't be scared. He's a good dog.
Here, lick it thoroughly.
lf Princess is not in the mood, she will not take you on.
Princess...
There's no point being proper at a time like this.
So, lick her breasts, too.
This dogie doesn't know the female body yet.
Can you teach him for me?
lt's magnificent.
Now, get on.
No!
lt's no use screaming.
The maid who always takes care of you isn't here.
Loosen up a bit!
l told you so.
Satisfied?
Princess...
You can't help it. lt's your first time.
Let's go!
Come on!
Wakamiya!
Not here either.
Wakamiya...
Where did everybody go?
The light's on.
Wakamiya?
Chikami? How? What happened?
Hold on, l'll let you loose.
Sorry! Are you okay?
Almost there...
l'm embarrassed. Please don't look.
Chikami...
Chikami... Weren't you with Shindoh?
Akira. After you stepped out,
l fell unconscious and when l woke up, l was blindfolded here.
Then where's Shindoh?
Shit! Why all these horrible things...
Who the hell...
lt was a woman...
A woman's doing. Just like Yukimura said.
She brought a big dog. And l...
To let you go through such a terrible thing...
Chikami... Can you get up?
l'm worried about Shindoh, too.
Could you go with Yukimura on the second floor?
Take care of Saki, please...
Are you all right? Wait for a bit.
Naoya...
l'm definitely getting out of this house.
Hold on, Naoya.
Shit! l'm definitely getting out of here!
Sorry.
We should go.
Why is this happening?
Yukimura, we're coming in.
Yukimura...
Sayaka?
lt's Saki!
Shindoh?
Saki!
Stop! What's the point of this?
Shindoh!
Please don't... Saki is...
lt's a re-enactment.
Welcome to my bondage mansion.
You're this house's...
You! How did you know about Saki?
How did you know about us?
l had to do this much to calm her personality.
What do you plan to do with us?
She orders others around, but doesn't do anything for herself...
A woman like that won't understand unless it happens to her again.
How do you know something like that?
She finally got better.
She's still not good with men, but... Please, don't!
You've never even met us.
l'm glad you fell into my trap.
Why did you kill Naoya? What's your plan?
A man like that has no value, even as a tool.
There's no reason to keep him alive.
That's not for you to decide!
What did you do with Wakamiya and Jun?
We can't get out of here alive.
What are you saying, Jun?
We're going to be killed.
Like Naoya? Stabbed?
What did you do to Jun?
Disappeared?