Workshop
Master, you summoned me?
Hahaha...
It is done.
Body
Jack
Sublime Separation
OX-Subs Presents...
Not for sale, rent, or eBay!
Let s rinisn tnisi
Okay!
Here I go!
Okay.
Not again
Hey, you have to concentrate
more when receiving.
Oh well, let's call it a day.
Yes! Finally!
We're done.
Really! You're only enthisuastic
about the end of practice.
Can you rub my back?
I'm totally exhausted.
Should we go somewhere later?
Come on, no dilly-dallying.
Okay!
I'll be going.
She slides, she's safe!
Komaba
Shoes
Prohibited
From Asagaya?
How intriguing.
Stand.
Bow!
Hey, wanna go
to the pool this Sunday?
Huh?
The pool?
There's a cheap public pool
near my house.
But, I don't have the figure for it.
Hey, hey. I'm talking about going
swimming, okay? Swimming!
Oh, is that so?
Ouch, ouch!
Nakano, let me borrow your
Modern Japanese textbook?
Will ya?
Again!?
Komaba, how are you?
I'm fine. But you
shouldn't trouble Nakano
by borrowing her things all the time.
Well, you should use the time
you spend sorting love letters
to make it to class on time.
Here you GO!
Let's go to the restroom!
Ouchie.
Fight! Give'em hell!
Here I go!
Nakano!
There!
Na~ka~no !
Na-ka no!
Got it!
Over there!
Okay!
Nice one!
Na~ka~no...
Aw, let go.
Ma'am?
Oh?
Good morning.
Mornin'.
Hi.
Yo!
How cute.
Oh dear!
What the...
Hey, hey...
It's you!
They're coming this way!
Oh crap...
It's you!
Only you will do!
Help me!
Wait a minute!
Don't let him escape!
Oh my god!
Go!
What the hell's this?
They're here!
It's you!
Yes, you.
You mean me?
Absolutely.
I knew at first sight!
It has to be none other than you!
What the heck was
that supposed to be?
What the hell do you want!?
What I want is right beside you. Miss.
It would take too long to explain...
So make it short!
Um m, it ts kind of a long story...
I said short!
Well, briefly speaking,
this machine will give you an
out-of-body experience.
What?
Unbelievable, isn't it?
I finally completed it yesterday,
after many years of study and research.
All tests have been successful.
So it's quite likely...
that this is the only
one of its kind in Japan.
That's right. This machine, the
only one of its kind on Earth...
can be yours for
a special discount price!
Bought!
Sold!
Wait a minute!
About that discount price...
...it is ? 5,000, right?
? 5,000 it is!
H-Hey, wait1 Didn't you say
you'd help me choose a swimsuit!?
Wait, Asagaya? ASAGAYA!
Forget you!
Damn idiot Asagaya?
He buys that bogus shit,
then leaves me here alone...
Feel free to try on anything.
...oh, but we might not have
sizes for your height...
All right, I'll try it.
Let's do this!
Here I go!
Father, Mother, please forgive me
for going to the other side before you.
How convenient; where I'm going...
...I don't need doors!
So long door, I won't be
using you anymore! Heh heh.
I'm flying, I can fly!
There's only one thing for a
man to do in this situation.
Komaba!
That's the 1,600th one.
Komaba, I'm "coming in"...
I did it!
We've combined
Whoa, Komabas panties.
Let's use this opportunity to explain.
You might be wondering what happened
to Komabas consciousness.
In this case, Asagaya's
consciousness is stronger.
So Komaba's is in a sleep-like state.
In other words,
Im free do to anything I want.
Damn, I wanna jerk off.
Man, but Komaba is really pretty.
It's touching time!
How dirty...
A woman's body is really amazing!
Let's go to the pool!
Today looks like another hot one.
That dumb idiot...
I guess he really is hopeless.
R...right.
"Right"?
Just imagine him.
But surely Asagaya has his own
way of thinking, doesn't he?
He's not thinking about anything!
No fucking way!
I mean, I don't think so!
Listen...
The only things he can think of are...
...how he can sneak a peak
at a cute girls panties...
...how he can get laid...
...or how he could get
closer to you. Nothing else.
If you thought anything else was on his
mind, you've got another think coming.
You goddamn...
Uh, I mean, he's kind of a good guy...
What?
You're not taking his side, are you?
Not really.
Wait, don't tell me
you like Asagaya!?
Not really.
You can't do that.
We ve known each other
since we were kids.
Anyway, it's not fair to do that now.
Not fair?
What? Didn't you say
you'd help me out?
You know...getting me and him...
sort of...in other words...
Public Pool
Ah, right... I guess... right?
What? What's she talking about!?
In other words...
Is that so?
Come on!
Sweet!
Komaba, what are you doing over there?
Lets change already!
Changing. What a wonderful word!
You know, I had to go shopping
for a swimsuit all by myself.
So I got this one in the shop.
High leg?!
That's right
That stupid saleswoman said:
"For someone of your stature,
we have nothing but this".
Ah, well. I kinda like it though.
Check this out.
Look!
I got rid of it.
I shaved earlier at home, see?
Sha...Shaved?!
Damn, it's all Asagaya's fault.
Shaved...
Aw, your boobs are so big, Komaba.
No!
Nooo~...
I can see all.
Stop it.
Over here!
I'm exhausted.
Not half bad...
What?
Your breasts are cute.
You're cute here, too.
Stop it, Komaba.
Hey, what are you two doing?
N-nothing!
Its lifesaving practice, right?
Uhh, yeah...
Strange, it doesn't...
...looks like that to me!
Hey, wanna come
to my house after this?
S-sure?
Stop it.
Hey, that tickles!
Will you...Komaba?
I won't, Nakano.
No!
Not there...
Hot!
Don't, that's embarrassing.
Nakano, can I please see
all of your pretty body?
When I look at you like that,
you're surprisingly...
...beautiful?
No, sexy!
No, sexy
Noo...
You re acting
so strange today, Komaba...
How so?
But we've...
...never done something like this.
It s because you were
so lovely at the pool.
No...
Th there...
Nakano?
Do you love...Asagaya?
You can't... ask me now...
Do you want to do something
like this with Asagaya, too?
Don t ask... while I'm doing this...
So, do you want to?
Or, don't you?
I want to...
So it's just as I thought.
Looks like I really do have people skills.
Don't stop now!
Maybe I should stop.
No...
But it's not fair to Asagaya, isn't it?
Please don't stop.
Even if I do something like this?
There.
Like this?
Even something like this...
Is it okay if I do this
before Asagaya does?
It's okay, its okay.
Maybe I should tell Asagaya...
No... please don't...
You'll say it.
Asagaya...
"I want him!"
Try and say it.
Say it.
If you don't say it...
I'll stop.
Asagaya... Asagaya...
I want him!
I'm home!
But I guess no one else is.
"Dear Komaba,
Mom and Dad have to go see Grandpa.
Dinner is in the fridge.
Just heat it up in the microwave
and eat it with your brother.
Love, Mom & Dad."
I'm starting to feel strange.
Still...
I need something to put in there.
Who's there?!
Yo, Ko m aba. Don't you think
you've warmed up enough?
As your brother, I haven't given
you much attention lately.
I'm really sorry!
Komaba's stepbrother?
Isn't this incest?!
H-hey!
Let go! This is disgusting! This... this...
...this... feels really good...
What the...
Her bo-body is ju just
do doing as it pleases.
This feels so gooood...
More!
I brought you a present today, Komaba.
Wha...?
Hey, Komaba, we're here again.
Also, here's the guy you liked
at first sight, Hamada.
Hi there.
What the...?! Two menl
No way!
Hamada, your turn.
But... this is my
first time with a woman.
Here goes nothing!
This is my first time with a man, too!
I mean... No! Go away! Shoo!
"Virgin Hamada", launching!
No, no, no!
Komaba, Hamada is over there!
Komaba! How unladylike!
It's not about being greedy!
If people saw this, wouldn't they think
I was a bad brother who couldn't
satisfy his sister?
Isn't it the other way around?!
Don't be so angry.
Let's try a rape scenario today.
How wonderful, Komaba.
You're playing your role so realistically!
I shee You alwaysh wanted to do
shomeshing like shish, Komaba.
Oh, what the... hell no.
How can I get
my consciousness out of here?
So this is how a woman feels!
It's my turn now.
Can't
Show
What the fuck was that just now?!
Oh, the pain!!!
What d I do...?
What will you be building this time?
This time?
What I'm building this time...
...is still a secret.
It's for me to know,
and for you to find out.
Morning! What happened
to you, Mummy Man?
That machine
from yesterday "happened"...
See? I knew that thing was trouble
from the moment I saw it.
Nakano.
Yes?
Say, we've known each other
for a long time, right?
What are you talking about?
It's just that it always
makes me feel happy
to see you growing into a woman.
And what is that supposed to mean?!
Well, anyway, lets try
to get along well, okay?
Is something wrong
with your head, again?
For example, sex, and stuff like that.
What are you, stupid?
But aren t you only fooling around
with Komaba these days?
Cut the crap!
All right, let's see that Student ID!
umi ni me wo fusete
I close my eyes upon the sea
utsumuku anata
and hang my head in shame to you
yatto se wo mukete
When you finally turned away
kakedasu watashi
I set off at a run
il soko no mama de
If I fall all the way
och ite yuketara
down to the deepest depths
donna ni ka shiawase
I will find my own kind of joy
I'm a lady always a lady
I'm a lady, always a lady
Tell me your name
Tell me your name.
tell me your telephone!
Aaah, ima wa
Aaah, right now
koi mo inochi mo
all of my life and my loves
namida mo somete
are soaking in my tears
dakara anata
So, then will you
Ah, anata
ah, you my love
aishite kuremasu ka
will you still be loving me
kanashh hodo ni
until you hurt like I do?