Lecture 1
lchijyo-san, you're not the only
one who's afraid of surgery.
Easier said then done!
Fine, l'll prove to you by letting you
know how fast my heart is beating.
Put your hands and ears on my....chest...!
l can hear...
l can tell that your heart is beating really fast...
No....Dai-chan, stop this.
This wasn't on the script.
The script...
lf we go by the script, how can l
judge your ability as a nurse, Nao.
Here's the real test.
No, l can't hold in my moan.
How can l resist this when it's Dai-chan...
Dai-chan, wait...
lt's hard to notice my heartbeat
over this clothing so...
A, amazing!
So this is Nao's boobs.
Yes, l'm not flat like when l was young anymore.
Nao, you like it?
l, l don't know.
You are stubborn.
No...stop Dai-chan!
Don't concentrate on the nipples...!!
See, your nipples are hard.
Because...you keep touching them....
Dai-chan, this is embarrassing...very embarrassing...
Nao...
Dai-chan...come inside...me.....
Nao?
Dai-chan...does it feel good inside?
Yes, it does...
lt's so warm and tight inside.
l'm so happy...
Please make yourself feel good, Dai-chan.
Nao, you're a...!?
lt's ok, don't stop Dai-chan.
l...l always had a crush on you, Dai-chan.
l was saving this for you all the time...
Nao.
So amazing...all of you is inside me!
That big, hard thing is rubbing inside me!
lt got bigger!!
lt's because of your erotic moaning.
That's because you're making me feel good....!
Going to cum, alright Nao?
Cuming inside you!
lnside me...?
That's right, inside!
l feel something coming!
Coming, coming!
Nao, here l cum!
l think...l am cuming too, cuming!
Nao!
Cuming, no....!
(Sign: Teacher's Lounge)
lchijyo-sensei, how did the career dramatic practice go?
W, well, l think it went well.
That's good news.
Yeah, it is.
There's no way l can tell her l had sex with Nao.
These are the script for your next one.
Huh, it's not Nao?
She is Mitsugiu Tsukushino.
l don't know why but she strongly insisted that
she should try this career dramatic practice.
l am Daisuke lchijyo.
l recently started teaching at this school.
Besides teaching my class, l am also responsible for
the school's program Career Dramatic Practice.
This program allows the students to experience
their career choice through role playing.
She is Nao lihara, a student body and also my cousin.
And the next student for the practice is...
Daisuke-sama....
Daisuke-sama, l knew that we were meant to be.
Mitsugu-kun, remember that you are a temple
maiden listening to other's problems.
Please follow the script.
Of course, anything you say Daisuke-sama.
M, Mitsugu-kun, what are you...!?
l sense an evil spirit inside you.
l have to give you some remedy to rid this spirit.
M, Mitsugu-kun....
Please enjoy this and let it all out...
You're not cuming.
Does my mouth not pleasure you enough?
l, l think if you work on a bit more, it'll explode.
l will do anything to fulfill your wish.
Amazing, your tits are so soft.
This is so embarrassing...
But looks like your enjoying this.
See?
Y, you're making me even more turned on...
Please, do anything you want to me.
N, no!
lf you continuing licking me, l...!
You're so wet down here.
lt's so embarrassing!
Dear God, please forgive me.
l'm going too...!
You're going to make me cum!
P, please, please, give me...!
What do you want?
l, l really...
Want you to stick that hard thing inside me!!
Sure thing, Maiden.
Your inside is so warm and tight...feels incredible.
No...please don't say such things.
No, l'm starting to feel good...
You're going to cum?
Y, yes...
How about you, does it feel good?
l'm going to explode soon too.
P, please cum!!
P, please! Unload every drop inside me!
Almost...l'm almost there!
No, l...l....!
Cuming, l'm going to cum inside!
Me too....cuming!!!
Your evil spirit has now left your body.
What kind of report is this!?
lt looks like an essay written by a kid.
Can't you even write a report?
l'm sorry...
Looks like l expected too much out of you, lchijyo-sensei.
Alright, l will need to see what you do in this program.
You, Touko-sensei?
Oh, is there a problem?
O, of course not.
Yes, l would be delighted.
Um, so this scenario is to see what a teacher would
do when a student reveals her love for him?
This is just practice, right?
Teacher, l realize l do love you.
l just can't hold in my feelings any more.
Teacher, please hold me in your arms as a lover.
Touko-sensei...don't joke around.
Touko-sensei?
Touko-kun...
Alright, l'm a man...
As a teacher, l will answer to your needs.
Thank you, lchijyo-sensei.
Teacher, l've never shown my body to any man...
Touko-kun, you're so cute.
No, Teacher...it's embarrassing, very embarrassing.
Touko-kun, you must get turned
on when you're embarrassed.
Your nipples are hard.
No, Teacher...Teacher...!
Hey Touko-kun, do you really like me?
Y, yes...
Then, can you show me yourself masturbating?
l want you to show me...
Your feelings for me physically.
Um, Teacher, you really want...
Yes, masturbate.
Ok, you may start.
Understood, anything for you.
l will...
Touko-kun, how does it feel?
l, it feels as if you're touching me.
lt feels different than usual.
So it feels good?
Yes, better than always.
See Touko-kun, you get turned
on when you're embarrassed.
Teacher, you're going to make me.....cum!!!!
l know, Touko-kun...
However, l won't be pleased if you do.
ls your love for me that cheap?
lf you keep touching my breasts, l...!
Going to cum?
l, l'll hold it, but...
But l'm about to cum!!
You sure are sensitive...fine.
Go ahead, you can cum.
OK, cuming...cuming!
N, no!!
Teacher, Teacher, Teacher!!!!
Touko, you came while thinking about me...
l'll answer to your feelings now.
Touko-kun, it feels great!
lt's so warm inside!
Teacher, l never felt like this before!
lt feels like something out of this world!!
Touko-kun, you're getting tighter by the second...!
Touko-kun!
l'm so happy, you're deep inside me...!
lt's because you're so wet down there.
l can go in deep as l want!
Teacher, if you keep thrusting in so deep...!
Teacher.
Cuming, l'm cuming!
Not yet.
lt feels great to me too, but l'm not at the peak yet.
But you're deep inside me and if
you continue, l won't be able to hold it!
Touko-kun, almost...almost!
Yes, cum...please cum!
Cuming, cuming, l'm going to cum!
Touko-kun, l'm going to cum too!
Teacher, please spray it all over me!!
lchijyo-sensei, your cum is delicious.
lchijyo-sensei.
Please keep this kind of 'practice' between us only.
And this concludes today's lesson as a teacher.
However, this was merely just the beginning.
Who would of thought there would be more.