Lecture 2
l'm so pooped...
l'm going straight to bed after the shower.
Huh, did l forget to turn off the lights?
Welcome back, Dai-chan.
Nao, what are you doing here?
N, Nao, why are you dressed like that!?
l wanted to make you dinner so l was waiting for you.
But it took you a while so l started cleaning and l found this in the closet.
That's!
A prize l won from last year's....
l found this inside.
A, anyway, why are you dressed like that!?
This.
T, that's...!
l...skimmed through it.
Then l saw girls with aprons only.
W, well a naked girl in apron is every man's...?
And so l thought this is what you like.
l want you to be happy.
l'll have dinner ready soon.
Nao...
No, Dai-chan...
Nao, l'm going to give you a massage to show you my appreciation.
Your nipples are getting harder...
D, don't, Dai-chan...
Dai-chan, something hard is touching my butt....
Nao, it's your fault for having a great body...
See?
lt's...
No, Dai-chan, not....there.....
l see you like it..
See?
lf you admit you like it, l'll make you feel better.
l don't like...don't like...!
Dai-chan, l want it...l want yours.
My what?
Dai-chan, don't be so mean!
Dai-chan, that's!!!
Yeah and l'm sure you know what to do with it.
No, that's too big to fit!
lt'll be fine.
See, you're already really wet.
lt goes in deep with ease.
Dai-chan...it's moving...inside....
lf you continue, l'm going too!!!
Going to cum?
No, l don't want too!
l want to cum with yours.
Dai-chan, h, hurry!
Please Dai-chan, don't make me beg...
Dai-chan, please...
Nao, it feels great...
l'm so happy you feel that way Dai-chan...
Nao, l'll make you feel even better!
Wow, she gets tighter when l fondle her breast!
Deeper, deeper, push it in deeper!
l'm about to cum...Nao, l'm going to cum inside you!!
Yes, please shoot your seeds inside me!!!
Dai-chan, love, l love you!
l'm going...
Nao, l love you too...
No, Dai-chan, l'm cu, cuming!!!
Nao!
Dai-chan...
Daisuke-sama, are you home!?
Why is Mitsugu here!?
But of course.
Daisuke-sama and l were destine to be the world's greatest couple.
What!?
He promised me that he'll make me his bride!
l'm sure you just forced that on him when you guys were young.
What did you say!?
Daisuke-sama, please pick me for today's lesson.
No, it's going to be with me!
Stop it you two!
But!
Don't worry, l'll have both of you attend today's lesson.
You are going to be a great maid.
You are good at serving.
P, please don't make our passenger do that.
You're a hostage as well, yet you rebel against me.
You are a great stewardess.
l just want a great time until l get to my destination.
Unless, if you want to substitute for her?
l understand, please do what you want with me but don't harm the passengers.
Mitsugu-kun, you did a great job l'll come back to you later.
Daisuke-sama....
You asked for it, now you're getting it.
lf you don't stay put, l'll ignite the bombs l placed.
l told you to stay put!
You want me to go back to the passengers?
Not..there....
Wow, you're going to serve me some juice?
Dai-chan, l want it, l want it now!
You are one horny stewardess!
So you weren't trying to save the hostages, you actually wanted it!
No, Dai-chan...stop picking on me!
Fine, come over here then!
Come, sit on top of me.
Now, move your hips.
lt's hitting deep inside!!
Hey Stewardess, your boobs are bouncing all over!
Dai-chan, Dai-chan, great, great!
You...you like it when it hits deep inside you!?
Yes, right there, l like it right there!
Dai-chan, more, give me more!
lt feels so good...l'm going to, going to....
Hey stewardess, don't tell me you're going to cum before l do.
But!
lf you do, the hostages will die...
Dai-chan, you're going to make...me cum!
Me too, l'm going to cum!
Cuming...cum with me!
Cuming...now!
H, hurry...!
l'm going...to...cum!
Nao-chan, did you have an orgasm?
Daisuke-sama, next is my turn.
l can do it better than Nao-chan.
Mitsugu-kun...you're good.
lt feels really good.
And your hard thing is very delicious, Master.
Master, l'm sorry but can you please stand up?
l can do better than Nao-chan.
l'll please you using everything l have to offer.
l'm not going to let you win!
Your nipples...
lt's rubbing mine...and l like it...
Mitsugu...
Nao-chan...
Mitsugu-kun...
Feels great!
Thank you very much, Master.
But doing this in front of Nao-chan is embarrassing!!
Mitsugu, you're very cute when you're horny.
Nao-chan...
l'm going to make you feel better.
Nao-chan, if you keep going, l'm going too...!
You're such a bad maid for enjoying this more than your master.
Mitsugu-kun, you're so wet!
You're just as wet, Nao!
Daisuke-sama, l'm going to!!!
Alright Mitsugu-kun, l'll make you cum first.
D, Dai-chan...
l'm cuming, cuming...
No, cuming, cuming!!!
Mitsugu...
Dai-chan...!
Nao, get ready, l'm going to cum!
Yes, Dai-chan...cum, cum!
Nao..cuming, cuming!
Dai-chan promised me that we will get married ever since we were little!
That's probably just your imagination!
People everywhere know that Daisuke-sama and l are meant to be!
What are you talking about!
Not surprised, just as l expected.
No, Daisuke-sama!
Dai-chan, get away from her!
Over here!
And as you can see, l currently spend time with these three girls.
Obviously, there's no way l can pick just one.
This heavenly situation continues on...
But that's a story for another time.