Listen, Mio...
I'm thinking about going to a medical school.
Oh... I see...
Your grades are top-notch after all, Takuya...
Then, you're gonna succeed
in your family's profession.
Yeah, but...
I want to open up my own clinic
someday as a pediatrician...
M-Mio?
H-Huh?
A-A nurse?
Takuya...
Takuya!
Are you alright, Takuya?
Yeah...
Oh, that's right.
I fell down the stairs.
I, Shirosawa Takuya,
graduated with a medical degree
and am now working here in Amagi
University Hospital for residency training.
Hey, wait!
Yay!
That naughty kid...
Huh?
T-Takuya!
Who are you?
Wh-"Who?", you say...
It's... It's me!
Akagi Mio.
We're childhood friends who've been
together from grade school to high school.
She's ended up becoming a nurse in this hospital.
M-Mio?!
You took too long to recognize me!
And here I recognized you immediately!
Heheh... You can never be too careful, Mio-chan!
So you're wearing white today...
H-H-H—
Hey there!
You shouldn't be doing stuff like these!
You're getting all bashful
because your boyfriend is here!
Boyfriend...
Th-That's dangerous!
O-Ouch...
Takuya...
Wait... Are you alright?
Takuya, Takuya...
Takuya!
I ended up confined in this hospital
not as a residency trainee, but as a patient.
Here you go!
Say "aah", Takuya.
What are you even thinking, Mio?
Th-That's because...
Your dominant arm got fractured.
It's the same for your left leg...
You got injured shielding me from the fall.
Or could it be that you hate being fed by me?
It's not that I hate it...
Strange as it seems,
Mio's presence makes me feel so conscious.
Hey, Takuya...
I want to do anything I can for you.
I already got permission from
the head nurse, so... okay?
But, well...
Please, Takuya!
O-Okay, then...
Alright!
And just like that, the accounts
of our residency training began.
My Accounts of Training with My Girlfriend
Nurse
Was it delicious?
Well...
It tasted like a hospital food.
We're in a hospital, after all.
Is there anything else you want me to do?
Well...
Then, I'll apologize for the trouble...
But may I ask you to bring me to the restroom?
Oh, that's right...
Could it be that you haven't been there yet?
I don't think that I can when I'm in this state.
I think that you shouldn't be walking around yet.
We have urinal bottles for situations like this.
Oh, I'm sorry. Do you need to pee a huge amount?
Well, it should be just a little...
Then, I think the urinal bottle will do.
No, that's...
Oh, I see.
Then, I'll be assisting you!
Oh, I can't... right now...
What's wrong, are you embarrassed?
It's alright. I'm a nurse, after all.
I've been taking care of everyone,
from children to the elderly.
Just... Wait, Mio!
Hey, I said wait!
T-Takuya...
You got big down there for some reason...
This is nothing more than a physiological response.
B-But...
It won't fit in the urinal bottle
unless it shrinks down.
Even if you tell me that... What's
the protocol when this happens?
I've only been assigned to children
and the elderly until now...
Then...
Will it shrink down when you ejaculate?
Huh? No...
J-Just wait for a second, Mio!
This somehow is embarrassing for me.
Your dick feels so hot,
it's big and as hard as a rock.
I've never seen anything like it before.
Takuya...
It'll end up spraying all over
if I keep doing it like this, so...
You can come whenever you want, okay?
M-Mio...
I'm already gonna...
It's alright, shoot lots of it out.
I'm sorry, Mio!
Why?
Well... I got some of it on your face...
That's okay.
Wait... Takuya!
It got big again, for some reason...
Uh, well... This is nothing more than...
Gosh...
It's not gonna fit into the urinal bottle now!
This is bad, I can't look straight at Mio eyes now!
Are you not hurting anywhere?
Ah, yeah.
I'm alright.
Feel free to ask me for anything, okay?
Mio's breasts have been pushing
against me this whole time.
Th-This is bad!
Alright then, I'll wash your front next.
Uhh, no... That's...
T-Takuya, is that a...
I-I can't help it in this kind of situation, can I?
But if we leave it stiff just like that,
won't it feel distressing for you?
Huh?
Wow, it's rock hard!
M-Mio...
It feels hot and it's pulsating...
It feels good on this wrapped up part, right?
Just let it out like this.
Leaving it stiff like this feels bad, right?
I-I'm already...
W-Wow, it's throbbing in my hands!
It's alright, shoot lots of it out.
I'm sorry.
I-It won't stop!
You came a lot, Takuya.
Then, shall I wash your front now?
O-Okay... Please do so.
What the hell is up with Mio?
Is she possibly doing the same to other patients...
Takuya...
Mio...
Are you having any troubles?
A-Are you getting backed up down there?
Wh-What are you talking about, Mio?
Do you even understand what you're saying?
Yes...
You see...
I love you, Takuya!
Huh?
Takuya, do you dislike me?
Is that why you don't want to do it with me?
Mio...
Me too...
I love you as well, Mio.
Hey, Takuya...
Let's keep going all the way!
Alright then, I'm putting it in.
The tip went inside!
O-Ouch!
You... Don't tell me that this is your first time...
That's because I've been
in love with you all this time!
Mio...
Are you not hurting anywhere?
Is it alright for me to start moving now?
How about you, are you feeling alright?
Yes, I'm alright.
T-Takuya!
Takuya!
I-I feel like coming already!
Yes, It's okay! Come!
If you keep doing that, I'll end up coming inside!
Me too, I'm about come!
I'll pull it out at that moment.
Just a little bit longer... Just a little bit longer!
I-I'm coming—!
You came a lot
of hot stuff...
Did that make you feel good, Takuya?
Yeah, it felt very good, Mio.
Mio's intensive nursing started after that night.
Linen Room
No... This is embarrassing.
It's very gorgeous...
D-Don't stare at it so much...
Your finger...
Don't put your finger in!
You keep on overflowing down here.
That's because...
I'm putting it it.
Do it, please!
I came just from being penetrated by his dick!
I'll start moving.
Wow...
It got even bigger than before!
Takuya, no!
It's reverberating deep in my belly!
I'm... Already... I'm already...
Coming! I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
M-Me too, I'm already...
I'm coming!
Your hot stuff is overflowing from inside me!
T-Takuya...
Are you not hurting anywhere?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Or rather, I got dirty down here...
Mio?
It's all clean now.
M-Mio...
It won't settle down again.
Huh? Even though I just got it all cleaned up...
Takuya, how is it? Feels good?
Yeah... It feels very good!
Really? I'm glad!
Then, how about when I do this?
Something's overflowing from the tip.
M-Mio, this is bad!
Takuya... You're still good to go, right?
I'm overflowing down there as well, so...
Okay?
I'm putting it in, okay?
T-Takuya...
Kiss... Kiss me!
Takuya, your dick feels good...
Your insides as well, they're
warm and they feel good...
You're hitting my deepest parts!
You're sucking my tits...
M-My nipple...
Your dick is so hard and huge...
I can't take it anymore.
It feels so good that it's making me feel strange.
I'm about to come!
Let's come... together at the same time!
Shoot a lot of it!
Shoot a lot of it deep inside me!
C-Coming...
I'm coming... I'm coming... I'm coming!
Takuya... I love you so much!
Ohh... I'm finally free from those plaster casts!
I'll work harder on my injury rehab
and catch up with my postgraduate training here.
Am I right, Mio?
What's the matter, Mio?
I guess you don't need my help anymore.
Huh?
It's nothing.
When I thought that you don't need
me taking care of you anymore,
it made me feel a little said...
What are you talking about?
Aren't there a lot of patients that need you?
Yeah... You're right, but...
Hey...
Mio, why did you choose to become a nurse?
"Why?" you ask...
Takuya...
That's because you wanted to be a pediatrician...
You see, that's because...
Someday, I'm going to be your...
Mio!
Takuya?
I want to become a pediatrician someday,
and then open up my own clinic.
That's why I need to have you with me!
So, would you like to be together with me?
Takuya...
Let's get married.
Am I good enough?
I'd have a problem if it's anyone else but you.
Takuya... I want to do it!
So do I...
I'm putting it in, Mio!
Okay... Do it...
Wow, your dick feels good!
You're stirring me up deep inside!
You're so intense!
Gouge me up inside!
Good!
It feels good!
I can't take it anymore, It's coming!
Something intense is coming!
I-I'm coming already!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
Takuya...
You too... Let's come together!
Shoot a lot of your semen inside me!
Inside my pussy...
Shoot it inside—!
Takuya... I love you so much!
Well...
Your fever still isn't going down...
I'm sorry, Takuya.
Even though it's a long holiday...
What are you saying?
Didn't you take lots of care
of me when I was hospitalized?
Now it's my turn.
Takuya...
Hey, that's right...
I got a really potent suppository here
so you'll feel better in no time.
Huh?
S-Suppository...
You mean I'll take that in?
It's gonna be alright.
I'm still under training, but I'm a doctor.
It'll go in easily. Alright, I'll take these off.
I-I'm not talking about how easy it'll go in...
This is embarrassing!
Just wait... Wait!
M-Mio... You're somehow wet down here...
Shirosawa-sensei, I think inoculation
will be much more effective!
Oh... I've been too hasty and was about to proceed.
We have to give the prescription at once!
No!
The needle is too thick!
If it's like this, then it's super effective!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization