This is my girlfriend, Takigawa Hina.
Yep, see you tomorrow.
She's a student at a very famous all-girls school in this area.
Park
But she has a secret.
On weekdays after school,
she goes to the deserted park, and in the cover of the grass,
she does things like this, that, and even this!
She did these things over and over again every day.
And since I've stumbled on her secret,
we've started having sex outside, and it was really hot!
That's when it dawned on me.
She's not the only pervert... We're both perverts.
This is the start of how we shared this dirty secret
And even today, we're...
My perverted girlfriend More
Yo-Yonetsu-kun...
Is this a...
Yeah.
I kinda bought it...
Do you have any interest in this kind of stuff at all?
I might be a little interested, yeah, but...
Then wanna try it out?
B-But...
This is really something.
It's vibrating even more than I thought it would.
What do you think?
I'm not really sure yet.
I guess it's starting to make me feel a little hot.
How about instead of putting it on your underwear,
you try putting it right on your skin?
What? But that's so embarrassing.
Don't worry, I'll make sure I watch every second.
But...
Hina-chan's masturbating with a vibrator.
And I get to see it up close and personal!
H-Hina-chan, it might feel better if
you put it against your lower parts.
Huh? I don't want to.
Come on, Hina-chan.
H-Hey, wait...
W-What is this...
Stop... Seriously.
Hina-chan's getting so wet down here!
I bet it's because I'm watching.
Stop! No!
I'm gonna...
Th-This is... No! Don't!
Stop!
What's wrong?
Wait, does it hurt?
It's not fair if I'm the only one going through this.
You get what I'm saying?
Huh?
N-No, you're going so deep...
M-My stomach's...
N-No...
Wow, there's so much coming out.
That feels too good!
H-Hina-chan... W-Wai...
P-Please just wait a second!
D-Do you wanna try this out next?
Sure...
Hina-chan's so hot and wet down here.
It went in all at once!
I'm getting to see so many of
the dirty faces that she makes!
It's hitting me so deep...
I know that Hina-chan wants to be looked at more.
She wants me to do even more perverted things to her!
That has to be it!
Hey, Hina-chan?
You're fine with me using this too, right?
Huh?
Wh-What do you mean by that?
N-No! Don't! Stop it!
Wow, look at how happy she is.
She really is a pervert.
Also, I've always wanted to try this.
I've always wanted to try using two vibrators at once!
D-Don't do that...
N-No!
Don't! Don't!
I want to see more of her face lit up in ecstasy!
Y-Yonetsu-kun... I... I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
That's fine. Just cum.
Show me how you cum.
Let me see all of it!
N-No!
No, not like this.
Together...
I want to cum together with you, Yonetsu-kun.
Please, hurry. Your dick... give it to me.
Hurry, put it in me!
Hina-chan!
Hina-chan, your insides are so warm...
They feel like they're on fire... It feels so good!
It feels good!
Yonetsu-kun, your dick is so hot and so big...
It feels... It feels so good!
Hina-chan!
Th-This position...
More! Feel even more pleasure!
Show me, and just me, more of your dirty expressions!
Oh God, this is so good.
I shouldn't...
I shouldn't be feeling this way, but...
I can't stop! It feels so good!
I... I...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
N-No... D-Don't...
I can't handle both that and your dick at the same time!
No!
Don't!
Crap, this is amazing. I can feel it vibrating with my dick!
My dick's really starting to feel it!
No.
D-Don't move it like that
It's vibrating and rubbing against me...
I-I'm gonna...
Hina-chan!
Does it feel good?
Where? Where does it feel good?!
I-I can't say that...
My pussy... My pussy feels good!
So good!
More! Do my pussy harder!
I love it! I love it! I love your dick so much!
Hina-chan!
I... I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna cum!
Please! Please cum with me!
Hina-chan!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
After finding a new fetish of Hina-chan's,
she started to stop acting so reserved in front of me.
She lets me do all kinds of things,
and lets me look at all of her body.
But...
Oh, it's this late already?
I need to get home.
Yonetsu-kun, I'm gonna use your bathroom real quick, okay?
Oh, really? Then maybe I'll come with you.
Just kidding.
Wh-What are you saying?!
You can't do that!
It'd be so embarrassing!
This should be something that she'd love...
but she still won't let me watch when she's peeing.
Really? But haven't we done even
more embarrassing things than that?
This is different!
I don't want to pee in front of somebody else.
Don't you like peeing outside?
It's hard to tell where exactly she draws the line.
But one of the reasons I came to love here even more
than I already had is because I saw her like that.
It'd be great if she could give me my
own little private pee show, but...
Yonetsu-kun... Look at me pee.
I've got no choice. This is my last resort.
If thy won't reveal,
If thy won't reveal, thy must hold it.
Until thy are incapable of holding it anymore!
thy must hold it.
until thy are incapable of holding it anymore!
End verse.
Yonetsu-kun?
Actually, sorry, the toilet here is broken.
Would you mind using the one at the train station?
Huh? Really?
Wow, it must be pretty rough on you and your parents.
What caused it?
Oh, uh...
Oh, look at the time! We should hurry!
I bet that Hina-chan really does want me to watch,
but she's just too shy to take that step forward.
I'm pretty sure that as long as
there's a reason, she'll let me watch.
And that's because...
We're both perverts.
Yonetsu
I'm a genius!
Hey, this isn't the way we usually go, is it?
Oh, uh, yeah.
The path we usually go is closed
right now due to construction.
Sorry.
Didn't mean to make you walk this far.
Oh, I see...
Yeah, that's good.
Keep holding it in. Keep doing it. Keep it up.
Oh, oopsie, I think we might be lost.
Y-Yonetsu-kun, are there...
Are there any convenience stores or parks around here?
Something wrong?
I... I might not be able to hold it anymore.
Now's my chance!
H-How about instead of a park...
A-Are you about to pee yourself?
Wh-What... Huh?!
So how about you just do it here?!
Huh?!
Wh-What are you say...
I'll use my body to hide yours.
Also, nobody really comes this way, so it'll be fine!
W-Wait! I don't want to pee out here.
I know that you actually want me to watch.
I know you do!
Right?!
Hey... Wait!
I'll make sure I watch every last second.
N-No!
Knock it off!
I...
I can't...
I told you no. I said I didn't want to!
I...
Hina-chan?
That girl is peeing herself!
Look! She's peeing...
She's peeing herself!
Look, she's peeing herself!
Hey, why? Hey, Mama, why? Why?
It doesn't matter. Let's just go home.
Hina-chan, I'm sorry!
Sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry!
I misunderstood what I thought you wanted...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
And after that, she didn't talk to
me even once for an entire week.
I am really so sorry!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч