To protect my step-brother,
who changed me both mentally and physically,
I gave Hebizuka Jouji my body.
However, I, Nijihara Yayoi,
was taught exactly how naive I was being.
The humiliation of being cummed inside of.
The disgrace I felt, having sex
while talking to Hiro on the phone...
I'm so sorry, Hiro...
I've become a slave to Hebizuka's cock!
It feels so good, I can't restrain myself anymore!
After the pleasure and immorality was drilled into my body,
I felt myself sinking deeper and deeper
into the puddle of disgrace at my feet.
My Yayoi-san 04
Thank you very much, Hebizuka-san.
It was nothing. I just happened to be passing by.
Thanks for scaring the dog away.
It was just coincidence, nothing more.
Yayoi-san, I'm going to cram school now, so I'll see you later.
How does it feel to climax just by hearing your name?
Get ready, we're changing places.
No! No!
You're violating my ass while the dildo is in my pussy!
My head's becoming completely messed up!
It's so good that you're about to cum, though, aren't you?
No, stop! This doesn't feel good at all!
I love it when your dick cums in me!
If you do it again I might die from the pleasure!
You look so happy, though.
You want me to finish this up, don't you, Yayoi?
Yes, I want it! I want your hot cum shooting into me!
All right get a good taste of it, Yayoi!
It's going in! Your cum is flowing into my pussy!
I can't live without this! My pussy needs this to live!
It was like nothing I'd ever experienced before.
It wasn't something that I could handle!
I'm so sorry, Hiro! I'm sorry for being so weak!
It really doesn't have any bad side-effects, right?
Are you getting scared after giving
your little brother a sleeping pill?
I'll drink it!
I'm a real human toilet.
When did I doze off?
Please let my womb suck your cock!
What's going on?
Yeah, sure. Knock yourself out.
This can't be real.
You want to suck on my cock with
your womb after letting all that stuff out?
You're too hooked for your first time.
Good! It feels so good...
This... This has to be a dream.
I'm...
You came just from having it put inside you?
Looks like the ecstasy's kicking in hard.
That's the spot!
There... Right there!
Rub it hard, with the tip of your cock.
I'm dreaming...
You're fucking me so hard!
Your dick is hitting me in all the right places!
You're too good at fucking my ass!
Your cock!
My Yayoi-san is...
Here I go, Yayoi!
Do it! Give me your cum!
I'll finish off in your pussy!
My pussy is... No...
All right, come here.
Y-Yes...
I can't hold on anymore! Hurry up and cum inside me!
I'll give you what you want!
Here!
It's here!
Give me and the guy back there
a better view of your cumming pussy!
Huh?
Hi... ro...
My life was flipped, turned upside down.
A stranger was playing with something that was mine.
He would play with her body, all day and all night.
In the hallways... At the front door...
In the kitchen and in the living room...
Every spot in the house was slowly
covered with the odor of sex.
No... I'm cumming!
I couldn't do anything but sit and watch as it happened.
Aren't you quick tonight?
It's just because we're doing it outside.
Haven't you noticed?
Noticed what?
Hey, hide and seek is over.
Hold up. Keep your right hand where it is.
Hi... ro?
I thought we were dating.
Yeah, I used you as leverage so I could fuck her.
You're her boyfriend. You are.
I thought I could protect you!
I thought as long as I kept doing
this I'd be able to protect you!
Now, tell him how you feel.
This guy's thick cock just feels too good,
so I became his slave, and...
And...
I'm pregnant with your child!
I'm so sorry, Hiro. I'm sorry I'm such a weak woman!
You actually came to your sister's confession?
Hirocchi, today's a special day,
so I'll let you do it here.
You've never used her ass before, have you?
Yayoi-san, your asshole is so soft, just like your pussy!
The dick that I love so much is...
How about it, Yayoi? Satisfied?
No, not at all!
I want your thick, slimy cum inside me as a reward!
Get a good taste of it, then!
It's going inside me!
Come on, Yayoi. Say something to your boyfriend.
Hiro, I love you,
but you're not good enough.
I can't stop loving this guy's huge, amazing dick!
No way. You're not serious!
I knew it! Your cum is the best!
It's flowing into my womb!
It feels so good, it's making my insides so sticky!
You're done now, right, Yayoi?
Your training is finished.
After that, Hebizuka never showed his face again.
Five months later,
all that was left was this child in my belly,
and the memories of rough sex he carved into my body.
Everything that happened was my responsibility.
He was the one who stopped me,
and told me to stay and not take my ring off.
Mother's Nutrition Diary
Good night, Yayoi-san.
I'll use the rest of my life to atone for what I've done.
Because I have such a kind, loving person
like you by my side, I know I can do that.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч