six years after my husband died.
I, Nijihara Yayoi,
have crossed the line,
with his younger brother, Hiro, whom I've been living with.
It was a sensual relationship, that I can never tell anyone about.
I was overwhelmed by the secret,
it was like a dangerous rose, alluring due to its sweet scent.
However, one day...
Long time no see, miss.
Y-You're...!
The man who suddenly greeted me was
none other than Hebizuka Jouji.
The man whom my husband and I used to just order around.
He was also,
the despicable jerk that caused that bloody
incident over eight years ago.
BOKU NO YAYOI-SAN
This is our firs time to meeting together after a long time.
What a very cold, and distant welcome.
The perfect greeting for someone who indiscriminately
drugged and raped the gang's girl.
You're really uptight as always.
And here I thought you were in trouble, so I came right away.
Hmph, who, you?
I heard that boss already died.
If I recall correctly, it was over six years ago.
What are you laughing for?
I was kicked out of the gang by boss,
and it's had an effect on my life too.
I've never felt this thrilled before.
Besides,
my long-held dream will finally be realized.
That high hole that I could never reach before,
is now right within my grasp.
I knew it.
You're as despicable as always.
Go on now, rape fiend.
Before I call everyone that would love to smack you down.
Actually, I've brought something interesting with me.
Boss' younger brother... he's quit the docile type, isn't he?
Hiro-kun~
You couldn't have...!
Limited time product wholesale bargain items secured!
Yayoi-san and I are going to have a feast tonight.
I just have to do it with you, right?
I've even brought you to a love hotel, so duh.
Why don't we get started already?
I don't really like waiting, you know.
Okay already.
I can't believe he already knew Hiro.
My first priority is Hiro's safety.
I have to protect him no matter what.
You can stop now if you want to.
I-I'll do it already!
Well?
How's the taste of a dick after such a long time?
Tastes great, right?
It's so stinky, I'm about to puke!
I'm always sucking a younger, cleaner dick, you know.
Far too different from this grotesque and dirty thing.
And what's with his tip?
Feels so gross.
It's not filthy, and it's actually quite valuable.
I even spent money just so women can
pleasure themselves more with it.
How stupid.
Just means it's a wimpy dick that can do
nothing without getting a makeover.
I'll listen to your snarky remarks once you've
sucked the entirety of my dick.
Hey, suck it properly.
Man, drinking beer while getting a blowjob really is the best.
And the one doing it is the women of my former gang's boss!
Moreover, its the cheeky Yayoi-san that's sucking my dick!
This is like a dream.
I can't breathe!
I can't...
...breathe!
I'm going to suffocate!
Alright, I'm gonna cum.
He's cumming!
Stand up.
Take your clothes off.
My heart won't stop throbbing.
I have to calm down!
Wait up.
Face here.
I was smelling something stinky a while earlier.
This isn't pussy juice, right?
This is piss, right?
You even pissed yourself back there?
Your insides are pretty wet and tight.
The sensation on my fingers feels very nice.
My head feels light...
I'm getting stimulated more and more by the second.
Pissing, while letting out that cum-stinky breath...
The queen looks pretty miserable now without her king.
My mind has completely blank.
Now for the main course.
First of all, try straddling me backwards.
It feels tight!
It's just the tip. What's with this monstrous thing?
I'm scared to push it further in.
Hey, you stopped.
Getting scared now?
I'm going to push it further in.
This is nothing to me.
It's in!
It's gone way up to my deepest spots.
I never thought it'd feel this great by just inserting it.
Did you just come?
I... I did not!
I didn't cum!
My body just reacted to it!
I'm getting excited now for the rest of the trip.
I will never cum,
with a dick from someone like you!
Threatening me? that's good.
Because you've just taken in the most
wonderful dick you could ever find.
No, this is... this is for him!
Why would I... want a filthy and rotten dick such as...
Why would I... why would I...!
That's a nice expression you've got there.
That face clearly tells me that you've already come.
I-I did not!
I haven't come yet!
What an obstinate woman you are.
Even though your hole down here is already telling me the truth.
No, not there!
Don't kiss it... please don't kiss my womb!
Hey,
I'm going to mark you with my cum,
so why don't you tell your ring what's happening right now.
I can't just do that!
If you don't, I won't let you go home.
No...
... I can't get out of this.
I hate this man with every fiber of my being,
in a short while,
I'll get cummed in, by Hebizuka!
The man I hated the most before,
is now having sex with me.
Even now, I'm already about to take in,
his gross and filthy cum.
His dirty cum is about to be pumped inside my womb!
I'm going impregnate you with it.
Take this!
It's not safe day, and yet he pumped a whole lot inside me!
I'm really going to get pregnant.
I want to go home already.
I want to go head home.
I want to go back to the place where Hiro's waiting for me.
Yayoi-san's been overtime these past few days.
She's a caretaker, so i guess it can't be helped... right?
I haven't used it yet.
It probably won't be again tonight.
Yayoi-san
Hello, Yayoi-san?
What's wrong? Calling at this hour.
Something happened?
No, I'm actually on break... right now...
We haven't had much time together as of late.
We weren't able to chat much, right?
Hiro
So I just wanted to hear your voice.
Thanks!
A also wanted to hear yours.
Oh yeah, I think I can go home early today.
What do you want for dinner?
Well, let's see...
I just finished eating lunch right now though.
Don't push my womb like that!
I won't be able to talk properly!
How about carry?
You love curry, right?
How about I make some of my special curry?
I've lost It!
It's trying to push through my womb!
I love that!
Your curry is indeed very delicious.
There's also some vegetables left from yesterday.
Would our meat here be enough?
Oh, we only have beef here.
But we're also going to mix some pork, right?
End this already...
Hiro's listening to me, and yet I can't stop myself from cumming!
Huh? Yayoi-san?
Can you hear me?
I have to end the call,
before he makes me cum!
Hello?
Yayoi-san?
I-I can... hear you.
I'm... alright.
What's wrong?
You're panting.
I-I was jogging.
I made the call while running.
Huh? At a hospital?
Yeah!
I'm on a diet you see.
My words are fragmented, I can't breathe well,
this is just too hard!
Your g-spots is wide open!
Yayoi-san?
He just hit my g-spot right mow.
Are you alright, Yayoi-san?
I'm okay, a dog just came running at me,
all of this is the dog's fault.
A dog, eh.
Then I'm going to let you howl some more then!
Yayoi-san?
Hey, Yayoi-san?
I can't stop moaning.
He's going to hear me moan!
Your breathing sounds rough.
Are you on the way back? Call the health care center right away!
I can't stop.
Anything but that!
I'm already very stimulated,
but I'm okay.
It's just too big and srudy.
I can cum anytime now.
I want to end the call, I really want to cut it off!
How cute.
Alright, I'm going to...
No, don't... don't...!
I'm cumming!
His cum is starting to pump in!
His filthy semen is flowing in!
I'm...cumming!
Was that some sort of fight or flight response?
You really shook my arms vigorously
just as you were about to cum.
I guess the aftereffect of cumming won't
help you think up a proper excuse now.
Your pussy seems really pleased with it.
The sight of it peeing as it cums is really nice from here.
Suck out the remaining cum left inside my dick,
and clean it up too.
What in the world am I doing?
Getting both my holes filled with this jerk's cum...
See you tonight then.
I'm going to fetch you sometime later after your shift.
See ya.
My head's completely blank now.
Everything's so wrong right now.
Oh, it's raining.
I wonder if Yayoi-san brought an umbrella.
Hiro, who I should have protected,
fell victim to my betrayal twice already.
And in the near future,
shall be my third...
I'm sorry, Hiro.
I'm... now a slave of Hebizuka's dick.
It felt so good, I can't escape anymore.
I'm really sorry...