BOKU NO YAYOI-SAN
Yayoi... -san!
Hiro, you're always masturbating there.
And you're always using me to jerk off.
It's all your fault, Yayoi-san.
The way I masturbate now,
the fact that I'm longer interested in other women,
everything... all of is your fault, Yayoi-san!
Okay then, I'll take responsibility for it.
But big bro will...
That person is no longer here.
He already went on a bike tour to heaven.
Could it be that the reason you're still with me after losing him is...?
By all means, as a guardian.
Until you become an adult that is.
Come, Hiro.
leave it all to Nee-san.
A dream... huh.
I never thought I'd dream about going
to a hot spring with Yayoi-san.
And it was also quit erotic.
Wait, these are Yayoi-san's panties!
I experienced tingly sensations whenever
I touched her crotch and breasts.
Then I'd snatch her panties while she
was bathing to jerk off with them.
What the...!
This is bad.
I have to clean this immediately!
What exactly is bad?
Whoa!
Ah! Yayoi-san!
I saw you sleeping when I tried to peek in your room.
Tried a lot of things while watching your sleeping face.
Wait! Those are my porn mags!
You took them out without asking me again!
This is breach of privacy!
I see that your fetishes are quite specific.
The new ones are also about nurses.
Could it be because I'm a caretaker?
Of course not.
It's just a coincidence, it really is.
Oh, just a coincidence, huh.
That's too bad.
I thought it'd be normal with you.
I'm not wearing anything under this bathrobe, you know.
Just kidding.
Of course not.
I'm really wearing a bra underneath.
Of course, that includes undies.
Oh? Maybe I teased you too much?
Sorry about that.
You don't understand, Yayoi-san.
You don't understand my feelings at all.
Hiro?
I'm a guy too, you know.
I may be just a kid now,
but I'm really serious here!
Hiro.
Was that your first kiss?
Yeah.
You're the first.
I see.
I'm going to teach you everything, just like I said.
But, this will only be for tonight.
We'll return to being just family when dawn arrives.
Is that clear?
Alright, well then...
We're going to have to close his eyes for a bit.
Take off your clothes first,
and take off mine as well.
We're both going to be in our birthday suits.
This really feels quite awkward.
We always casually see each other everyday.
I see, you're quite the nervous type.
It's alright.
Just leave it to me.
Yayoi-san is carefully licking my thing.
It feels good.
It's covered a bit in smegma.
Hey, you have to clean this properly, you know.
I'm sorry! Then I'll go to the bathroom to...
This is tonight's special service.
I'll be the one to clean it... every last inch.
Thank you, Yayoi-san.
It feels like I'm in a dream.
Ya-Yayoi-san...
I just came...
It's okay.
I'm going to drink it all.
She's licking off every last drop.
Well? Did that feel good?
Yeah. very.
You really are young after all.
It's still very lively.
Yayoi-san, I want to put it in now.
Don't you want to take a closer look before that?
At your big sis' hole that you're about to fuck.
A-Amazing.
It looks really wet, and the secretions are reflecting light off.
It looks really delicious, Yayoi-san.
I can't hold back anymore.
Come.
Don't rush.
Go a bit lower.
Keep touching the vagina as you try to check for the hole.
That's the spot.
Then just keep pushing it gently inside.
Put it in little by little.
Good, you're doing well.
Just keep up that pace.
Yayoi-san, your insides feel warm.
I'm now one with you, right?
You're now an adult, Hiro.
It feels good, Yayoi-san.
So sex feels this good, huh.
It feels good for me too.
Maybe... because it's been a long while since I've had a dick in me.
It feels really good.
There, just keep it up, Hiro.
Make sure it's rubbing inside me well,
as you push it in!
If this continues, I'll...
I'll cum!
You're... going to cum?
I want to make you cum.
I want to make you cum, Yayoi-san!
I'm going to do it as many times if that's what I have to do.
I want to always make you cum, to always make you satisfied!
You're getting more lively.
No, don't bite my nipples softly.
Oh, wow, it's...
I'm going to cum first!
Please, Hiro, cum with me.
I'll try to hold out till then,
so please cum already.
My insides feel like they're going to melt!
I'll cum, Yayoi-san.
Let's, let's both cum together!
It's okay, cum then.
Let out all of your feeling into me.
I'm cumming!
Nurse Station
How many days in a row has it been?
Two hours of sleep... well of course I'd get sleepy.
My, how unusual.
I've never seen you yawn before, Njihara-san.
Chief!
I'm sorry, that was rude of me!
No need to be so uptight.
It can't be helped really.
It's been a long time since you had one, right?
It's the 7th anniversary, right?
Of your husband's death.
We all get really stressed when interacting with relatives
we don't have much contact with, right?
W-Well... it was really quite troublesome.
I got flustered and thought it was something about Hiro.
That's right.
Yesterday was another year after the sixth year my husband died.
Despite that, I...
It's been six years since that accident, eh.
We really can't attribute it to anything else but fate.
Yes, and he was quite the unusual man as well.
You're right.
We can't do this now.
Our relatives will notice.
It's okay, everyone's too busy thinking about Nii-san.
So, about your career lately...
What's wrong, Yayoi-san?
Are you unable to stand anymore?
You can't do this in front of everyone!
I have to tell him properly as his guardian.
I have to tell him to stop!
Well, Hiro-kun sure grew quite splendidly.
I'm sure your brother will be relieved to see you.
Isn't that right, Yayoi-san?
Don't come over here, talk somewhere over there, please.
It's all thanks to Yayoi-san,
she's been taking care of me up until now.
You're still the mischief-loving delinquent brat.
Hiro-kun's a delinquent brat?
Even though he's this well-behaved?
Skipped....
You're right. It's a bit perplexing actually.
Don't! Stop playing with both my pussy and clit!
Getting both of them fondled by him right in front of them...
And it's getting totally wet from it!
Oh no... this feels too good.
No...!
I'm... cummmg...
I'm, cummmg.
Everyone will hear if you moan loudly.
I know.
I'm putting in, Yayoi-san.
Okay.
Many of our relatives are m the other rooms.
But I'm here having sex with his younger brother.
This feels really great,
I'm getting so horny.
It's the same sensation like when going fast on a bike.
My heart won't stop throbbing!
Oh no, I'm starting to moan!
What are you trying to do?
It's safer this way, right?
Hiro...
Yayoi-san, does it feel good?
Your dick feels good.
I want to cum inside all the way.
I can do it, right?
My day is getting closer, so please cum outside.
But I can't stop anymore.
Yayoi-san, take it all.
Don't... you can't!
I'm, I'm cumming!
I can't resist it anymore.
I won't be able to live without this dick now.
I can't tell them.
I can t tell that my lack of sleep is due to having
hardcore sex with my brother-in-law.
I absolutely cannot!
Nijihara-san, you have a guest.
Welcome!
If you really care about me, then you need to use a condom starting tomorrow, okay?
Alright then.
Buying stuff like this without getting embarrassed...
I'm sure this is love, yeah, love.
Long time no see, miss.
You're...!