It shouldn't be just once or twice,
since it will be passed off as coincidence.
However, if he keeps doing it this much,
he won't be able to talk his way out of this!
Yes, he's taking pictures.
Is that how much you like my ass?
What a cute boy!
Look, I'm wearing black lace today.
Take a good look.
You'll also show yours to me soon,
cute Boku-chan...
Guidance Office
What's your reason for doing this?
Well, there's no need to ask about that.
Which class are you in?
I-I'm Aizawa.
I-I'm a first-year in class F...
Of course, I know you... Aizawa Subaru-kun!
Is your parent at home or work right now?
N-Not my parents...
Yes, that face looks so good!
I'm joking. I'll keep quiet about this.
In exchange...
Are you embarrassed?
Doesn't this finally make us even though?
That's because you've been taking
lots of candid shots of me.
Y-Yes...
I-It's so tiny and it's covered with foreskin!
How cute!
What the hell? You're not getting hard.
You're being reprimanded right now!
Do you understand your situation?
I-I'm sorry!
B-But sensei, you are...
How is my thigh?
Doesn't its smoothness make you feel good?
I-I-It's gonna come out!
Oh... This cute boy ejaculated.
He did while he's trembling on my chest!
Just one more push...
I'll definitely make him my very own puppet!
The Next Day
How is it?
Isn't seeing the real thing way better
than just some pictures?
Y-Yes! It looks very erotic!
Alright then, pull your dick out.
Hey, do it already!
O-Okay!
What do you think of this 98-centimeter butt?
But first, we should do something
about that foreskin.
Haven't you fantasized about
me down here all this time?
Fine, I'll let you have a look.
U-Umm, sensei?
That's right, I've been fantasizing all this time
about sitting on a pretty boy's face!
What do you think? Is it just as you imagined?
His breath is blowing through my entire pussy!
I can feel his gaze as well!
You're looking...
...at my asshole.
You're looking at each and every fold, aren't you?
But just looking won't be enough, right?
Y-You may do anything just
like how you imagined before.
Yes, that's it! You're such a good pupil!
His tongue went inside my pussy!
Alright, I'm going to treat myself as well!
It's slippery! It's so tiny and stiff!
Here, isn't this the spot?
The tip of the glans is oozing a bit.
Doesn't it feel good when I stroke the opening?
You're about to come, aren't you? That's okay.
Ejaculate while your face is buried in my ass!
Sensei!
I peeled it off.
It's reddish and it looks pretty, just like a gemstone!
You can put it back in the foreskin if it hurts,
but you should retract it when possible.
And one more thing...
Be sure to think about the things you want to do.
I understand! I'll think about it myself!
That's when my "Puppet Scheme" began.
You're not taking candid photos anymore, right?
Yes, I don't, since you're doing all of this for me.
I also think about you at home, and I do it myself...
Right...
I don't like the idea that he's ejaculating
without my permission.
Hey, Aizawa-kun!
Shall we do something different for today?
Huh?
We'll put your dick in my pussy.
W-Will that be alright?
But in exchange, you won't be
masturbating anymore.
Huh!?
Doing that by yourself is bad for your health.
You'll end up with weird ideas again.
Hey, what are you going to do?
It's squishy and sopping wet.
It's warm and it feels good!
Stay still just like that.
Leave it all to me.
I was planning to save this fun
for later, but it can't be helped.
Look, it went in!
Yes, this is great!
Your virgin cock is mine now, Boku-chan!
What do you think? Doesn't it feel
a lot better than masturbating?
He only pulled his foreskin back recently,
so his glans is clinging to my vaginal wall!
Oh, looks like you're about to come.
Y-Yes!
He's adorable! I want to tease him!
You can't come inside!
I'll end up getting pregnant!
It's gonna come out! Pull it out, sensei!
Don't! I'll have a baby!
I'll end up having a baby!
No, don't shoot it inside me!
You can't—!
How does your first creampie feel?
You're such a bad boy, coming inside me!
I-I'm sorry!
But, sensei was...
It's a safe day for me, though.
You really are no good.
I'll have to do something
about your strong sex drive.
I'll make you feel more intense...
An even more intense pleasure!
Sensei, I just came earlier!
Silence!
Bear with it! You'll have to endure this!
If you come inside, I'll get pregnant!
That means a baby!
Here, I'll keep rubbing your dick that's
still sensitive from ejaculating earlier!
You came inside me again, didn't you!?
You're a bad boy!
I-I'm sorry!
That's right! You won't get hard
from anyone's body except mine.
Become a puppet that is submissive to me!
My, my... To think that you'll dare
piss yourself inside my pussy...
You truly are a bad boy.
I never thought about it at this time...
...about the fact that our roles will be reversed.
Guidance Office
Yes, it's the usual amount.
You didn't masturbate just like I told you.
You're a good pupil.
Then, I'll let you inside me as a reward.
Ah, I have to go home now.
Oh? That's earlier than usual.
Uhh... The exams are...
Ahh, the exams will be a week from now.
Then, we'll hold this off until after the exams.
Ah, but if it's the same time as today...
No way, you'll have to hold yourself back.
I'll take you to a good place after the exams.
A-A good place?
At a hotel.
I'll let you do more amazing things there.
And a day after the exams,
To perfectly turn this pretty boy into my own puppet,
I took action.
What do you think about this
latex suit? Isn't it very erotic?
His reaction exceeded my expectations.
The young boy started to make the face of a man.
But there's more!
I need to turn him more into my very own puppet...
Here! It's alright!
You can do anything that
you fantasized about.
Ahh! Are you making me do this embarrassing pose?
The "Puppet Scheme" is successful!
Now I can use this boy as I please...
Did he pull the hood off my clit and start licking?
I-Isn't that enough already!?
Th-That was a close call...
Don't you want to put it inside
my slippery pussy already?
Yes, I want to put it inside you down there, sensei!
There, now you may put it inside me.
I'm sorry but I have no plans to show
myself being haggard to a man.
Wh-What's the matter?
I-I've been holding myself back from
masturbating for the whole exam period!
I can keep going on!
Wh-What did he just say!?
He didn't masturbate all this time!?
I know that I told him not to masturbate,
but that was for a totally different thing!
Hey... Wait... S-Stop!
I-I'm tired so let me take a break!
Please take a break, sensei!
I'll do the moving on my own!
Th-That's not the issue!
This is bad! If this goes on...
I'm always the only one being taken care of.
I want you to feel good too!
I already do! This feels good!
I'm about to come!
No, I'm being brought to orgasm!
By this puppet... By this child...
I went through... I managed to hold it in...
I ended up coming again...
But I still can keep going on!
Ahh...
I'm already done for...
I'm coming—!
Coming?
Sensei, did you just come?
Y-Yes!
I made her come!
Stop!
I-I came! I came, so...
More! Keep coming more, sensei!
I want you to feel good!
What? What's up with this!?
A huge volume of sperm
has accumulated inside the rubber!
No! No—!
I-It's gonna burst if you keep moving that hard!
This can't be! It's pouring out!?
It's all pouring out from my pussy!
N-No way! I-It's a risky day for me...
I-I need to hurry and rinse it off...
Stop!
Stop pushing it in!
Stop pushing your sperm deeper inside!
Ahh! This is too much... Ahh, it feels good!
There's no way I can hold back from
sex while being smeared by semen!
I couldn't go against him...
And I never intended to do so...
I made up my mind...
...to become a puppet of this young boy.
Sensei! I love you, sensei!
Me too! I love you too!
Yes!
Your hard cock feels great!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm gonna come too!
Shoot it out! Shoot it out!
Right into my climaxing pussy!
Make it spurt!
Sensei, you also peed!
You're a bad girl!
Y-Yeah...
Guidance Office
I'm coming in.
Hey, sensei... What kind of things
have you fantasized about today?
Gosh... You already know it!
And thus, I became this young boy's puppet.
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji