I have a person I admire.
No, this isn't at that level, it's love.
Admiration, love, misery... I've never had so many
emotions towards someone in my life.
I sit alone in my room and stare at the
star-lit sky and all I can do is sigh.
Pranks
forbidden
Pranks are forbidden, okay?
How cute is she?!
She’s so sweet!
She's so sexy!
With a woman like her, one day I'm just gonna lose myself and...
My libido's gonna explode and take over!
Misaki-sensei and me
Misaki-sensei and me.
Coming!
Kazama-kun?
What's the matter? Why are you here so late at night?
Sensei, the female body... the female body...
T-Teach me about the female body please!
I beg you.
Apple juice...
Do you want some apple juice?
Or maybe you'd like a shower?
Y-Yes, I'll gladly take a shower!
Take it off for me.
Look, this is what a female body looks like.
Don't rush now.
My underwear's still on.
Boobs... boobs... boobs... boobs...
Not yet. We need to take a shower first.
Be gentle, okay?
Kazama-kun, this is a woman's most precious place.
Take a good look.
Sensei, I can't see it well unless you spread a little wider.
Th-This is pretty embarrassing for me, so...
Wider!
Try touching it.
It's getting really slimy.
It's getting... ready... to... take in... a man.
It's so big.
Does it feel good?
Come here.
Here?
Yes, right there.
Do it slowly.
It's inside!
Try moving it slowly, okay?
It's so warm!
So this is a pussy?
That's the warmth from the deepest parts of my body.
Your dick is really warm too, Kazama-kun.
It almost feels hot!
It feels so good! My dick is starting to feel weird!
Don’t!
I'm cumming!
Not inside!
Don't!
I'm cumming!
Hey, can we do it one more time?
Did it feel good?
Yeah! It felt really good!
Alright, but this time cum outside, okay?
It's... inside me.
Kazama-kun! Kazama-kun!!
Sensei, I'm cumming!
Misaki-sensei,
why did you let me have sex with you?
You see me getting pranked all the time, don't you?
Seeing you trying to join in with everyone else was just so cute.
And so,
my secret relationship with MisaKi-sensei began.
You really wore it, Misaki-sensei!
It looks so good on you! So sexy!
This is from back when I was still a student, so it's really tight.
I wore it because you asked me to,
but this is really embarrassing.
Don't lick there.
Wait, sensei, are you also wearing a swimsuit?
I thought you'd like it.
I have a lot of confidence in my proportions.
What do you think, Yuu-kun?
Taste good?
It's so good!
Put it in.
Oof.
Misaki-sensei, I’m going to do some more foreplay, okay?
No!
Sorry for the wait. I'll put it in now.
Please give if to me hard.
Give me your dick, Yuu-kun.
It feels so good!
Your dick is so amazing, Yuu-kun!
My dick feels so good!
It feels so good!
I'm cumming!
I dressed up as a bunny today.
You always just get right into it.
Misaki-sensei, can I use some rope?
Rope?
Are you done yet, Yuu-kun?
It kind of hurts.
I don't really like this kind of thing too much.
This is necessary for me to enjoy both your butt
and your boobs to their maximum potential!
We're going with this today.
It looks really good, sensei!
I can't hold myself back!
Take this!
Take that!
Crap!
Take this!
And this! And that!
How's that?! Take this! And this!
Feels good, doesn't it? You like it, don't you? You little...
If it feels good, say it out loud already!
Let's do this in a more fun position, okay?
I don't like this, Yuu-kun!
Misaki-sensei! I'm so sorry.
It feels so good!
Cum! Cum a lot!
I-I'm cumming!
Did it feel good?
Yeah, it felt amazing!
I love you.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч