There's someone I admire.
No, I don't admire, I love.
I never thought that in my life would appear
a person that would make me feel this way.
I picture myself with her when I'm
alone in my room looking at the sky.
NO
PRANKS
OR WILL BE
PUNISHED
Pranks is forbidden.
How beautiful! How pure! How sexy!
I can't stand just looking at her anymore.
My libido will explode!
Me and Misaki-sensei
I'm going.
Kazama-kun?
What's the problem?
It's late now.
Sensei, teach me… teach me about a woman's body, please!
I beg.
A-Apple juice…
So, do you want apple juice?
Or would you rather take a shower?
Yes, I'll take a shower!
Take off my clothes.
Look, this is a woman's body.
Don't hurry. I'm still wearing underwear.
Boobs, boobs, boobs, boobs!
You can't! Let's take a bath.
Be kind, right?
Kazama-kun, this is the most special girl's place.
Look with… attention.
Sensei, open more your legs, I can't see.
Sensei… is a little embarrassed.
More…!
Try to touch it.
It's wet…
It's… getting ready… to receive a boy…
It's big.
Is good…?
Come.
Here?
Yeah, right there.
Put it slowly…
Came in.
Try to move slowly.
It's so hot…
The inside of my body is also hot…
Kazama-kun's penis is also hot.
It's very hot!
Delicious! My penis is moving like crazy!
You can't!
I'm coming!
Don't cum inside!
You can't!
Hey, can we do it again?
Was it good for you?
Yes, was very good!
So, next time, cum out.
Came in…
Kazama-kun! Kazama-kun!
Sensei, I'm coming!
Why did Misaki-sensei have sex with me?
Everyone plays tricks on me.
You always noticed, right?
It's great to take care of these cute kids.
And so, my secret relationship with Misaki-sensei began.
So you're wearing it! You look amazing
in it, Misaki-sensei! This is very erotic!
This is from when I was a high school student.
Now it gets too small.
I dressed because you asked me to,
but this is very embarrassing.
Don't lick there.
Sensei, are you wearing bikini?
I dressed him thinking you'd like it.
Besides, I've a lot of
confidence in what I planned.
What did you think, Yuu-kun?
It's good?
P-Put it in.
Let's see…
Misaki-sensei, I'm going to masturbate you a little more.
No!
Sorry for the delay. I'll put it on.
Please, put it all at once… your penis, Yuu-kun.
H-How delicious!
Your penis… It's amazing!
Ah… Again! Very Tasty! Very Tasty!
I'm a bunny today.
You get very excited!
Misaki-sensei, can I tie you?
Tie me up?
Enough, Yuu-kun.
That hurts a little. This isn't something I like.
This is necessary for me to enjoy your huge boobs and ass.
Today we will use that.
That looks really good on you, sensei! I can't control myself!
Go, go!
Damn it!
Bang! Bang!
Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
You feel good, huh!? Are you liking it, huh!?
Are you having fun, huh!? Come on, say it!
Let's have fun having sex. I don't like it, Yuu-kun.
Misaki-sensei, I'm sorry.
– I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
– So good! This is amazing!
Come! Come a lot!
I-I-I'm coming!
Did you have fun?
Yes it was really good.
I love you.
Me and
Misaki-sensei
www.xanimeporn.com