There's one person I really admire.
No, this isn't admiration.
This is love!
For someone to be this dear to me,
this beloved to me, this precious to me...
I look up to a window to the starry night,
sighing, and sighing.
No
Teasing
Teasing isn't allowed.
She's so cute!
She so lovely!
She's so sexy!
Just looking at her makes me want to cry out with joy.
My libido's about to completely explode.
Misaki-sensei and I.
Coming!
Kazama-kun?
What's wrong? It's quite late already.
Sensei, I want to...
I want you to...
I want you to teach me about a girl's body!
Please.
A-Apple juice.
Umm... would you like to have some apple juice?
Or, maybe a shower?
O-Okay! I'll have a shower, please!
Take my clothes off.
Look. This is a girl's body.
No need to rush.
There's still two undergarments left.
Breasts.
Breasts...
Breasts... breasts...
Stop, we need to shower first.
Gently, okay?
Kazama-kun,
this is a girl's sensitive spot.
Take a look.
Sensei, please part your legs. I can't see.
I'm quite embarrassed, so...
More!
Try touching it.
It's sticky.
It's lubricating,
lubricating itself... to take a man...
inside.
It's big.
Does it feel good?
Come.
In here?
That's right.
That spot.
Slowly...
It's in.
Try moving slowly.
So warm.
So this is a pussy.
My warmth is emanating from deep inside me.
Your dick feels warm, too.
It's almost burning me.
It feels so good, my peepee's going crazy.
Oh no...!
It's coming out!
No, not inside!
Stop!
It's coming out!
Hey, can we do it again?
Did it feel good?
Yeah, it was amazing!
You need to cum outside then, okay?
It's... in.
Kazama-kun, Kazama-kun!
Sensei, I'm about to cum!
Misaki-sensei,
why did you let me have sex with you?
You were always watching me closely whenever
I got teased by your classmates, right?
Your eager expression that yearned to join in looked very cute.
And so,
that was the start of my secret relationship with Misaki-sensei.
So you really wore it!
It's so erotic, and it looks good on you, Misaki-sensei!
It's something from my old school,
so it's quite tight already.
I tried it on because you requested it.
But it really feels embarrassing.
Please don't lick me there.
Sensei, are you wearing a swimsuit?
I thought it might make you happy.
I'm quite confident about my proportions, you know.
Well, Yuu-kun?
Does it taste good?
Yummy.
P-Put... it in.
Oopsie.
Misaki-sensei, I need to nibble just a bit longer.
Sorry for the wait. I'll put it in now.
Please... push your dick all the way in.
So good.
Your dick is amazing.
My peepee feels so good again.
It feels fantastic!
– I'm going to cum.
– I'm cumming!
I'm your bunny-chan today!
You're getting horny way too quick.
Misaki-sensei, can I use strings?
Strings?
It's fine now, Yuu-kun.
It hurts a bit.
I don't like this too much.
It's necessary to fully enjoy your butt and boobs,
so we're using it today.
It looks really good, sensei.
I can't restrain myself anymore.
Here...
and here!
Damn!
Here... have some of this...
and some more!
How's this for you?
Here, and here!
It feels good, right? You're getting horny, right?
If you are, then say it out loud!
Let's make this sex act more enjoyable.
I don't like this at all, Yuu-kun.
I'm sorry, Misaki-sensei.
– Oh yes. That's good.
– I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Cum. Just cum lots.
I'm... I'm cumming!
Did it feel good?
Yup.
I love you.