Cicada from the past
Look at her! So hot, right?
This is what a woman looks like naked.
Look at her tits!
Holy crap!
How'd you get your hands on these adult magazines all at once?
I'm just really lucky today!
It was really hard to take all of these from the dumpster
all the way here without anyone spotting me.
Okay guys, let's store everything we have
here and share it among all of us!
We're gonna keep if a secret from everyone and never look
at them except for when we're all together, got it?
Shit, boobs are amazing. I wanna try licking them.
I wonder what a real girl's like?
It feels like all the blood in my body's
going straight to my dick and head!
I feel like my hips are just gonna start
moving on their own at any second.
Shinpei, my dick is so hard right now.
Y-Yeah, me too!
I'm like a rock down here and kinda wet too.
This is too good!
Oh, Akio! This is where you were?
Mom said that she's cutting a watermelon, so
you should bring everyone over for some.
What? Why are you all acting so surprised?
Shut up, sis! You're so ugly!
We're not surprised at all.
Oh, hi Tomoko-san.
Oh, hi Shinpei-kun. You want to eat some watermelon too, right?
What are you guys doing? Did you just hide something?
Huh? No, nothing...
Whatever, let's go already ugly!
What are you doing, Akio?!
Woah there.
Fine, let's go.
You guys should hurry up too.
The next day...
It's so hot.
Who's there?!
Sh-Shinpei-kun?
Tomoko-san? I...
You don't need to be so scared, Shinpei-kun.
Hey, Shinpei-kun, do you wanna go
somewhere a little more private?
You guys are the ones who hid those
adult magazines there, right?
Yes...
I'll be honest. I overheard you guys talking about it yesterday.
You came by yourself to look at them, didn't you?
Y-Yeah.
Shinpei-kun, how about this? If you do
as I say, I'll let you look at me naked.
Huh?!
You want to see me naked, don't you?
Then let me see your dick, Shinpei-kun.
Huh?!
L-Like this?
Yeah, that's good.
This is such a cute dick.
T-Tomoko-san, you can't...
Tomoko-san, if you keep doing that, I...
Something's going to come out!
Hey, don't forget your promise!
You need to take your clothes off.
So, what do you think?
This is what real boobs look like?
You're too close to me. Your breath is tickling my boobs.
Can I touch them?
They're so soft!
So this is what real boobs feel like?
Tomoko-san... your nipples are getting really hard.
Hey, Shinpei-kun, I'll show you even more.
Look, Shinpei-kun.
So this is what a woman looks like down there.
You're so wet, Tomoko-san.
Your dick's pretty wet too. There's
something dripping out from it.
Do you wanna try having sex?
Yes...
You need to keep this a secret from
Akio and everyone else, okay?
Okay.
Shinpei-kun, your dick is hitting me down there.
Here I go.
It feels so good!
Tomoko-san!
I'm going to move.
My dick is getting so wet.
Your dirty juices just keep pouring out from your pussy.
Tomoko-san, your pussy is wrapping around my dick!
It feels so good!
It's so hot!
My dick is inside your pussy!
It feels like it's on fire!
It's like I'm one with you now, Tomoko-san!
But seriously, where the heck is Shinpei?
He wasn't at his house.
I thought he'd be here, but he's not.
Geez.
We promised not to look at the magazines
unless it was with everyone.
But, eh, whatever. Let's just take a peek.
He might drop by.
Oh man, naked women really are the best.
What do boobs feel like when you rub them?
They've gotta be so soft.
I wonder what pussies are like.
I wanna see one.
I wonder what it would feel like to put my dick inside one.
I bet it'd feel the best to just stick it in straight up.
I wanna cuddle with a woman when we're both naked.
I wanna try kissing one.
I wanna have sex so bad!
<Part 2>
Visiting the den of the spider
You're here again, sensei.
I let you go home the other day because you said
you had other house visits you needed to do.
I didn't think you'd come again,
but here you are, I guess you really liked my technique.
What are you saying?!
You really think I could leave the home visit on that note?!
Oh, wait, are you mad, sensei?
But seeing you angry isn't too bad.
It makes me want to try tying you up again.
I'm not the same person I was yesterday!
Today I'm going to finally have a real talk with your father!
But... I got tied up again instead.
I'm such a weak woman. Seriously.
When's all said and done with, I really
like you when you're tied up, sensei.
Master, how did I do?
Yes, that is a remarkable pose.
If she tries to beg for forgiveness, the cloth
will fall and the world will see her pussy.
But at a certain point, her mouth will get tired
and she won't be able to hold it anymore.
Oh, we can see it.
How embarrassing.
And you're even wet.
N-No!
It's your fault for not holding onto it with your mouth.
You're a really bad teacher to get wet
from your student tying you up.
I'll tie you up all day to punish you.
Thank you for helping me out today as well.
Indian style Knot
Indian style Knot.
Sleeping Raccoon
Sleeping Raccoon.
Open Legged M
Open Legged M.
Caltrop Rope Knot
Caltrop Rope Knot.
No...
Human Flower Vase
Human Flower Vase.
Tortoise Shell Knot
Tortoise Shell Knot.
I lose track of time when I'm tying you up, sensei.
Well then...
I have a prior engagement, so I'll
leave you in charge of the house.
Master, thank you very much.
Janome-kun?
Sensei...
Please, do me.
I've been this hard all this time.
It's amazing.
So good!
Janome-kun, your dick is so amazing!
Your pussy's really amazing too, sensei.
I feel so good, my mind's going blank!
Not yet! I'm not done tying you up just yet!
This is such a beautiful, huge ass.
You've made so many guys at school go crazy with this huge ass.
You're such a dirty teacher!
Don't say that to me.
You're everyone's masturbation pet idol, you know that?
No!
Shake your ass! Take my dick in deep!
Sensei, my dick is really deep inside you.
Aren't you in an embarrassing position.
Usually you have a cool face on while you teach class.
But right now, you just look like a run of the mill whore!
You're just a tied up piece of meat!
No!
I can't anymore!
Then just cum.
But say that you're a perverted teacher
that loves being tied up, first!
That's an order.
Now, say it to my face!
I can't! I'm gonna cum!
I love being tied up...
I'm a perverted teacher!!
Janome-kun?!
I couldn't properly talk to your father yesterday either!
I-I... I'm not going over to your house
to do that kind of thing, you know?
Today I'll be coming over to properly speak with your father.
So just be a good kid and wait, okay?
Sure. I'll gladly wait for you, sensei.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality check: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч