This is a famous all-girls school around these parts.
See you later.
Bye bye.
– See you tomorrow.
– The students there not only have a great academic record,
– Let's go home together!
but they also have an air around them that makes
it hard for any guy to get close to them.
A characteristic of any all-girls school.
– And this girl is one of those girls, Takigawa Hina.
– Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Park
And I know her secret.
At first I thought it was just because
she couldn't find a bathroom.
But every day after school, Takigawa Hina would
come to this empty park to do various things.
She really is a rich girl. She's actually
throwing away her tissues.
I guess she's done for the day.
She's leaving the park... with such
an innocent took on her face.
Oh, crap I need to hurry!
Hello.
Thanks for coming.
What's the matter? You seem out of breath.
U-Uh, I had to stay after to help clean the classroom.
I practically ran back home after that.
Oh, really? Sorry for making you rush back.
No, no, you're fine.
Come on in.
Thanks.
Thanks for having me.
That's right, Takigawa Hina is my girlfriend.
My perverted girlfriend
Hey, is it really okay that we're here instead of the library?
Oh, yeah.
It just so happens that my parents aren't
back until later tonight anyway.
Oh, really?
L-Let's get our homework and review for tomorrow done.
Y-Yeah, let's.
I met Hina-chan half a year ago at the library.
I always thought rich girls were people in
a completely different world than me.
But after studying together, we kind of hit it off and
now we've been dating for almost three months.
And just one month ago...
I found out about her secret.
No, we...
We can't do this.
And when I found her, she was looking at a magazine that
no rich girl should be looking at, while masturbating.
No, we can't, but...
And after that, every week...
I made sure to stop by the park to
see her exhibitionist behavior.
This park that she'd always be in.
N-No, I can't...
Hina-chan!
No...
Wow, look at this.
It's so...
I... I...
No, I...
But I can't...
And even now I can't bring myself to ask her
about the things she does in the park.
Something wrong?
N-No, I... Uh...
– S-So in the par... par... part I'm thinking about, I was
doing some training... muscle training, that is.
– Do it! Ask her! No I shouldn't! I really want to
ask though! Would she be okay if I asked her?
I'm always winded after working out, so I was told
to do something to increase my lung capacity,
– but after I started to catch my breath, I...
– U-Um...
Wh-What am I even saying?
U-Um!
I-If your parents really aren't coming
back until later tonight, then...
I don't mind.
Wait, don...
They're getting harder.
This is so embarrassing.
Hina-chan?
Oh no, I can't hold my voice back.
I've seen her embarrassed face so many times.
It means that it feels good for her.
But compared to the expression she makes
when she's alone in that park...
W-Wow, so intense!
She never shows me that side of her!
I... I'm gonna... No!
No...
I want her to look at me that way.
H-Hina-chan?
Yonetsu-kun?
Why are you here?
Th-This isn't what you think! I just couldn't hold it in, so I...
I know about everything.
I know about everything you've done here.
I've known about all this for so long.
But, it wasn't really that easy to bring up.
Please don't tell anyone...
You can hate me all you want, but please don't tell anyone.
I won't.
I won't tell anyone, so...
Let's do what you did here by yourself, together.
Yonetsu-kun?
D-Don't, it's not clean.
Sto...
Please...
Stop...
Not there...
I'm gonna...
U-Uh, this is...
I guess it's my turn now.
It feels so good!
Hina-chan, I...
I'm about to...
How about we do it?
So big.
It's coming inside me.
Being inside Hina-chan feels completely different.
Her insides are so wet and twitchy...
I can tell how turned on she is.
It... It feels so good!
This is so good, I can't hold my voice back. I can't!
Hina-chan!
No, don't take my boobs out here. It's so embarrassing.
Don't worry, just be as loud as you want, Hina-chan!
This is bad. If anyone sees us having
sex outside, I'm gonna...
Wow, it feels so good!
We shouldn't be doing this but it just feels so good!
His dick feels so good!
It feels so good.
I-It's making me go crazy.
I'm gonna lose my mind!
More...
Hina-chan, what do you like more. Doing it
by yourself here or doing it together here?
Both... I like both.
This is it! This is the face I wanted to see all this time!
This is the what she really looks like!
His dick... It's getting bigger.
Oh my god, it feels so good!
This'll be our secret from now on.
Hina-chan, if you keep squeezing me like that, I'm gonna...
I'm not. I don't know what you're talking about.
I-I'm gonna...
Please, let's cum together.
Hina-chan!
No, this is... this is so...
Oh god, oh god...
Oh god...
It's been half a year since I met Hina-chan.
I feel like I've come to understand her a little
more now even though we're worlds apart.
Okay, let's go home.
Yeah, let's do that.
I'll walk you home.
Okay.
I'm the only one who knows the secret that we share.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч