I thought no one would be here
since it's supposed to rain this afternoon.
I'm surprised you keep coming here every day, Takeshi-kun.
What's the problem? I like the pool.
You don't like playing video games
and stuff like the other kids?
My family's poor, so we don't have any.
– Really? That doesn't really make it okay
for you to be here every day thought.
– Truth be told, I'm here just because I want to see her.
But Kagari-san somehow feels different today.
Shadow of Summer
NATSUNOKAGEROU
Take that!
Kagari-san used to have long hair
– and would always wear a sports swim suit up until just last week.
– You! I know you can hear me! Don't shove people's
heads under the water even as a joke!
– She was working as a lifeguard.
– She was strict, frightening, and never took
her eyes off of the pool even for one second.
But now she has short hair, isn't even looking at the pool.
and is wearing a different swimsuit than usual.
She's exposing herself more now, but the biggest thing
is that her tan lines are so white, it really turns me on.
Takeshi-kun, you're gonna catch a cold.
Go to the locker room.
All right!
So it really did end up raining.
Yeah.
Geez, this really sucks.
Takeshi-kun, aren't you cold?
Huh? No.
You'll feel warmer like this.
Kagari-san...
You're so warm, Takeshi-kun.
Th-That's...
I'm gonna cum!
What's gonna cum?
Th-That's...
What's the matter?
Kagari-san, I...
I'm sorry.
It's so hot. It smells like a guy.
Your cum is all over me now.
I-I'll wash it and give it back to you.
No, don't worry about it.
But...
You got turned on by looking
at my body, right, Takeshi-kun?
Uh, I...
I'm getting really turned on from the smell of your cum.
I'll let you do what you want to me.
You can do whatever you want to me until the rain stops.
Look. Take a good look. This is a vagina.
This is your...
I can't believe I can see it this close in person!
But this is really embarrassing.
You can lick it if you want to.
It has a strange taste to it.
Just like that, Takeshi-kun...
That's good!
Right there!
Try licking the entrance. Try licking the clitoris too.
That feels really good!
Yes!
My mind's going numb!
I'm gonna put it in.
Okay!
Kagari-san!
Your insides feel so good, Kagari-san!
To tell you the truth,
something really bad happened to me yesterday.
I was crying all night last night.
I was even thinking about skipping lifeguard duty today.
But after seeing you get hard from looking at my body,
I just got so happy!
When I thought about you seeing me as an attractive
woman, I was able to forget the bad things a little bit.
And then I began to really want to have sex with you.
So I want to make you feel good!
Use my body!
Kagari-san!
Hm?
I don't want to be on the bottom the entire time.
That's fine.
Okay, put it in.
I want to make you feel good too!
You're so strong!
It feels so good!
You're such a rough kid.
Make my body more of a mess!
Kagari-san!
More... stir me up inside even more!
Mess me up even more!
Break me to bits!
Takeshi-kun, your dick is rubbing inside me...
It's so hot!
Bigger...
It's gonna explode!
Your pussy's so wet, it feels amazing!
That's because... your dick feels so good!
I can't stop getting wet!
Kagari-san!
Your pussy's the best, Kagari-san!
Thank you.
Kagari-san, I'm gonna cum!
I want to cum while looking at your face.
Huh?
That's good, Kagari-san!
Don't!
I love you!
You're exaggerating.
But thanks.
Takeshi-kun!
I... I'm gonna cum!
Cum! Cum lots in my pussy!
I'm about to cum too!
Oh, the rain stopped.
Wow, it really did.
Takeshi-kun?
Thank you.
Maybe I'll take a dip now too.
Is this the right house for the teacher visit?
I didn't see a nameplate or anything.
I'm so glad I found the house.
All right then.
Visiting the den of the spider
I'm the homeroom teacher of Janome Koichi-kun.
My name is Nanase Saori.
I do apologize for being late.
No, don't worry about it.
I'm his father, Janome Ichirou.
Welcome, sensei.
I've heard about you from my son,
but you're even more beautiful than he described.
My son's been really excited
about you coming since this morning.
Master, that's embarrassing.
Master?
Well, please come inside.
Come this way, sensei.
Oh, of course. Please excuse me.
Please sit on this chair over here.
Um, what's going on here?!
Are you surprised?
Well, please have a seat.
I thought that it'd be a good idea to decorate
the room special today since you were coming over.
Oh, so this isn't normal then?
It's not always like this then, right?
I feel a little bit more comfortable hearing that.
But, while you are free to your
own hobbies, this kind of... um...
This isn't, um... I don't think
it's befitting for a place of learning.
Wouldn't it be better for this to be
in a place where Koichi-kun can't see it?
Indeed.
My job is binding, you see.
And this is my home.
Usually I rent out a studio for this.
We make adult videos especially those of S&M, daily.
That's why I decided to greet you with the same
scenery that my son is used to seeing every day.
But Koichi's entering a really
important part of his life right now...
What are you saying?
He's already begun training under me as a student.
What?
My son tied those three up.
He put in even more effort than usual
because he wanted to show it to you.
So, what do you think?
Take a good look.
I don't know much about this.
So you're not into S&M?
I don't know.
But I've never thought about it
being a part of my life even once.
Is that right?
But my son told me something.
He said that you definitely have the potential for it.
I do?!
I've never even given it a thought.
I felt the same thing as my son
when you walked in through that door.
And I can still feel it strongly.
I've been enthralled with you since I first saw you!
I have a favor to ask of you today!
Would you be kind enough to let me tie you up today?
Huh?!
What are you saying out of the blue, Koichi-kun?!
I really think it'll suit you!
I want to be as good as my master in the future, but...
I still have so much more training to do.
It was then that I found you, sensei.
I want to tie up the best material I can find.
– Sensei, I'm begging you.
– No... Stop!
– I don't think I'll get another chance like this in my life!
– Don't beg me!
– Just think about this as part of helping
me choose my path for the future!
– I'm a big pushover when it comes to begging!
– Sensei, please!
Stop!
– Sensei!
Don't make it hurt, okay?
Of course.
I've been taking great care with this rope just for you
to make sure that it won't hurt you in the slightest.
Oh god, what am I even doing?
I'm really letting my student put me
in an embarrassing position tike this?
If you tie it so tightly,
you're going to make my boobs pop out.
Sensei, your boobs are such a beautiful shape.
Don't say that. You're making me so embarrassed.
My... My nipples are getting hard!
Sensei, I'm going to lift up your skirt.
Huh?!
What's happening to me?
My student is lifting up my skirt and touching me
all over and I'm not even resisting in the slightest.
I just wanted to help him out a little as a teacher
to make him figure out his future path.
But I'm being swallowed by this strange
atmosphere and my head's going crazy...
I can't form a single rational thought!
Or maybe...
You're doing it there too?!
Sensei, your butt is a really good shape.
It's splendid.
Stop saying stuff like that!
It hurts!
But it still feels so gentle.
What's this feeling?
You're so beautiful, sensei.
I knew you'd look good in ropes.
This is strange.
Being bound makes me lose my freedom,
but now I feel my body more than ever.
Every time I feel pain, I feel my soul.
Koichi-kun, let's stop here, okay?
Sensei, I...
I can't hold back any longer.
I'm sorry!
Don't look!
I'm going to use my tying to make you
awaken to your masochistic nature!
No, stop, Koichi-kun!
I'll make you beautiful, sensei!
So just leave your body to me.
Koichi-kun? You're really going to do that for me?
What am I supposed to do?!
No! I don't like this position!
Everyone's watching.
Everyone's looking at your shameful figure.
No!
Look at how widely spread your beautiful legs are.
You can't close them, right?
At school you hide them so well,
but I can see your panties and tits so easily now.
No! Don't look!
The rope is digging into those parts of you now.
Your nipples are getting hard.
Stop, Koichi-kun!
I thought we agreed on just tying me up.
Please, stop!
No.
If I let this chance slip away, I'll never get another one!
Right now, you can't do anything.
You're my little plaything now.
Why am I getting so hot down there
from being tied up like this?
You're such a liar, Koichi-kun.
Sensei, are you sure you want to be talking to me like that?
Ow!
Stop!
Sensei, your face right now is beautiful too.
There's a huge stain on your stockings right now.
You're getting excited, aren't you?
I'm not!
Don't make things up!
But your nipples are already this rock hard.
That hurts! Stop!
Then how about we take a closer look, sensei?
No!
See? Look at how soaking wet you are.
You're already bursting out over here.
It's easy to see that even through your underwear.
Don't touch me there!
So this is your pussy, Saori-sensei?
I can see all of it.
Don't look!
It's so beautiful. All the juices coming
out of it are making it sparkle.
That's so embarrassing! Don't say that!
That's surprising. You've got a pretty big clitoris, sensei.
No! Stop!
Okay, now show me more of your insides!
You're wet inside too. It's because you're
turned on from being tied up, right?
That makes me so happy!
There's so much love juice flowing out of your pussy.
You're already a wet mess.
Stop!
I'll play with your clit and pussy!
How is it?
Feel like you're gonna cum yet?
S-Something is... I-I'm gonna pee!
Stop! Stop moving your hand! No!
Stop!
That's not pee.
So don't hold back and cum a lot, sensei!
No, I don't want to!
I don't want to cum with so many people watching me!
No! No!
I'm cumming!
So, Koichi?
Yes.
As I thought, sensei was a wonderful material.
She's one I'd like to take my time
polishing into the perfect material.
What do you say about that, sensei?
Did my son's techniques please you?
That being said, I can't let you go home cumming
after only tasting what a novice could do.
Huh?
The real fun starts now.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч