To protect my step-brother,
who changed me both mentally and physically,
I gave Hebizuka Jouji my body.
However, I, Nijihara Yayoi,
was taught exactly how naive I was being.
The humiliation of being cummed inside of...
The disgrace I felt, having sex
while talking to Hiro on the phone...
I'm so sorry, Hiro...
I've become a slave to Hebizuka's cock!
It feels so good, I can't restrain myself anymore!
After the pleasure and immorality was drilled into my body,
I felt myself sinking deeper and deeper
into the puddle of disgrace at my feet.
My Yayoi-san 03
I'm home...
Yayoi-san, welcome back!
Were you okay this afternoon?
The call cut all of a sudden...
Y-Yeah...
Hebizuka-san just happened to
be passing by, so he helped me out.
Yup, and as thanks, she promised to let me
have some of her world-famous curry.
Oh, so that's what happened.
Sorry I couldn't get in touch with you sooner.
I was just completely soaked.
It's fine. I'm just glad that you're okay, Yayoi-san.
Thank you so much, Hebizuka-san.
I didn't do anything special.
What a shameless bastard.
He followed me all the way home, and even... He even...
Yayoi-san?
Oh, it's nothing. You have cram school, don't you?
Oh, you're right! I'm going to be late!
Stay as long as you want, Hebizuka-san.
Okay, I'll see you guys later!
You knew that he had cram school, didn't you?
So? What now?
Bastard! How far does he intend
to toy with people... with women?!
Please, I'm begging you.
Let me take it out! It's making me cum
and cum, like something will happen to me!
Looks like you're ready.
All right, then.
I'll take it out, just like you asked.
Look, you got a new stain on this.
I'll use your body to replace the old stains
with new ones, every day from now on!
I'm already cumming,
just from his semen dripping out of me!
I'm losing it!
I tease you just a little and your asshole gets this loose.
Am I wrong?
Is it because after your husband died,
you've been doing it nonstop with that kid?
I'll do something real nice to your clit, you slut.
This guy is way too good at fingering girls!
The way he plays with the holes like they're
nothing just makes me want even more!
That's all it took?
All that's left is to put this back where it belongs.
Why'd you put it back inside me?!
Listen up, the next thing to have cum pumped into it,
will be this nice, juicy asshole over here.
Remember the feeling of it throbbing inside you as I cum!
It went in.
Hey, can you tell?
My dick is going all the way inside you. Doesn't it feel good?
Now you're ready for more anal sex!
This is really going to make me go crazy!
My womb's already really weak from earlier,
but now I'm being fucked by both the dildo and his cock!
The dildo's making me feel even more sensitive than usual!
It's making his dick feel ever better, too!
We can use toys like this, too.
Like it? An anal virgin like you shouldn't
be able to handle this kind of pleasure.
Especially since your womb is so sensitive!
Please! Please, stop! I can't take it anymore!
No, there's no way I can take this anymore!
The dildo's...
The dildo and your dick are... I'm gonna die!
Save me, Hiro. I don't think I can hold on any longer!
Something really incredible's gonna happen now.
After it happens, you'll never be the same again.
It's coming inside!
I can feel something really amazing starting inside me!
Now, it's the moment you've been waiting for...
The moment I cum inside you.
No, don't cum!
Please! Please don't cum,
I'm begging you! Please, don't cum!
If you cum now, I'm gonna explode and I'll... I'll...
That's all you have to say?
Cum from this, bitch!
I'm dead!
I'm so dead! I died!
I'm completery dead!
Hey, it's too early for you to pass out.
You have something to let out, don't you?
Spread it yourself, and let it flow.
If you do, lim sure something great will come out.
I'm sorry Hiro, but my body can't resist pleasure...
It can't resist his body anymore!
I'm really sorry.
Peeing feels so good! It feels so good!
Now, what do you say after you cum?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming by peeing!
I'm cumming with my piss!
Looks like we've made another big stain.
You're never going to make another
stain with that brat again, got it?
Yes...
I won't...
I won't do it with Hiro, ever again...
I'm back!
Did Hebizuka-san go home?
Yayoi-san!
Hiro? W-Welcome back. That was quick.
I guess so. This is around the time
I usually get back, though.
Come on, the dick inside you
is more important than that kid.
I'll cum inside your womb just
like you want, so move your ass!
No, if you cum inside me now, Hiro will...
Don't move!
Don't you want semen in your womb?
Who was the one who said
"finish me off by pumping my womb full of cum"?
Y-Yayoi-san?
I was wondering if it'd be okay if I came inside with you...
That's not possible. I'm already inside her.
I'm coming in.
Don't!
S-Sorry...
Yeah, taking a bath together's pretty embarrassing, isn't it?
Okay, I'm going to sleep then.
Smart thinking, using the sound of the shower to trick him.
Though, it doesn't look like you could do
anything other than scream and pass out.
Your orgasms are just as depraved as an animal's,
so I guess it's not that hard
to conceal with just the shower.
Huh?
You're peeing again?
Now we can't stay in the bath because of your pee.
You begged me for this cum.
Better be able to savor it all.
Have a good day.
Yep. I'll see you later.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Bye!
Ever since Hebizuka came into our house, I...
I've been violated countless times, in my own home.
All behind Hiro's back!
We even did it in front of him, while he was asleep!
Please, stop! I'm going to cum! I'm gonna cum!
Then, if you don't want me to cum
so hard that he wakes up.
You need to get your clit and nipples pierced. Got that?
I will! I'll pierce them, so please...
You're not gonna beg?
Please shoot your cum into the slut
who cheated on her husband and boyfriend!
I'm going to have my body pierced...
If I do that, I'll never be able to embrace Hiro again!
Even though I know that... Why am I getting excited?!
If this doesn't stop, one day I'm going to forget about Hiro!
But...
Never thought you'd be the one to call me out.
Finally in the mood, huh?
Take off your clothes. I'm going to make
you unable to live without my cock.
Sorry, but no thanks.
Hey, hey!
Who the hell are you guys?!
They're people from your past, and they want to kill you.
Yayoi, you bitch!
Shut the hell up!
This is for what you did back then!
That's a good look on you, you bastard.
Let me carve this into your body!
You start shit again,
and I'll crush your other ball. Remember that.
It's all over now.
You think it's over?
What are you saying, missy?
We're still here.
Huh?
You don't mean...
Yeah, you're next!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Let go of me! This wasn't part of the deal!
Let go of me! What are you doing to me?!
What do you think were doing?
You're just a traitorous bitch!
Who's a bitch? Who do you think you're
calling a traitor?! Try saying that again!
You're the traitor, Yayoi-san.
Hiro?!
You went behind my back with Hebizuka-san.
Am I wrong?
H-Hiro... Are you saying that...
I know you've been coming back
with him ever since that night.
I know about your bath together.
I know about what happened in the living room.
I even know what you did in my room.
When you called me that one time,
you were with him too, weren't you?
That's why I got these guys to do me a favor.
This is your punishment for playing with my feelings.
Take your time and repent, okay?
My sin? Hiro... you...
No! Make them stop, Hiro!
You got it all wrong! I never betrayed you, Hiro!
Shut the hell up, you fucking pig!
No!
No, not again! Someone who isn't Hiro is...
Oh man, your pussy is so tight, Yayoi!
Hi... ro...
Her face is already twisted in ecstasy. What a pig.
I'm not! I'm not a pig!
Stop letting out those disgusting moans!
People will find out you're just a cock-loving pig!
Cock!
Why? Even in a situation like this,
why am I getting turned on?
Why is my body...
I knew it. You get turned on
no matter who's having sex with you.
I guess that's just how you are.
No, that's not true! I...
Please shoot your cum into the slut
who cheated on her husband and boyfriend!
Hiro... you...
Suck it already!
You drank Hebizuka's piss,
so whatever you say doesn't matter anymore!
Did she suck Hebizuka off like
a vacuum cleaner or something?
My hips are...
Oh, finally admitting it, huh? You fucking slut!
I can't wait any more! I'm gonna use these huge ass tits!
Hey, give me a hand job!
I'm gonna cum! Drink it all, okay?
Your cocks! They're so amazing! So good!
How's this?!
– It's good! It feels so good!
– You get off from this hole too, don't you?!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming, so give me your semen!
I'll give you what you want, you fucking slut. Here you go!
I'm gonna cum, Yayoi!
C-C-Cumming! I'm gonna cum!
The bitch just pissed again. Now it reeks of semen and piss.
Hi... ro...
Don't think you're off the hook just yet.
Hiro... Please, forgive me!
I'm... I'm...
Have you thought about what you've done,
after being fucked all night by those guys,
and being left alone like this for an entire day?
I have!
So please! I want that!
I want that huge, hard cock inside me!
I guess I was right. You don't care whose
cock you have in you, do you, Yayoi-san?
That's not true!
If you're mine, then swear to this picture of me,
and of my brother as well.
Say that you're mine now.
You're mine, aren't you?
I'll accept your dick, Hiro.
I'll become your woman.
I'm sorry for becoming the woman
of the child you left me to raise.
I'm going to forget about you
and live oh as Hiro's woman.
Goodbye.
Now you're my woman, Yayoi-san, no, Yayoi!
Thanks to what I did,
it's so easy for my dick to hit your womb now!
Yayoi, my dick is going to kiss your womb every day!
Yes, I'll make sure my womb is always like this for you!
Yayoi, you're mine. Your womb, your boobs,
your body... everything about you is mine!
Shit! I have to go deeper!
I have to go deep enough that my dick goes into her womb!
It feels so good! Your dick rubbing
against my womb feels so good!
My womb's spreading out
and your dick's trying to get inside!
I'm gonna be cummed inside of!
I'm gonna cum!
Yayoi, you're going to cum with me!
You're going to cum when I cum inside you!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
P-Peeing feels so good! It feels so good!
I'm going to cum from peeing!
After you finish cleaning it, I'll put it inside you again.
I'll keep cumming inside you all night.
It's been two months since I swore to be Hiro's woman.
Hebizuka never dared show his face again,
and I hear that after losing the function in his balls,
he's become a completely different person.
Hebizuka wasn't the only one that changed, though.
Perhaps due to him,
Hiro and I both changed quite a lot.
Yayoi, it's breakfast time!
Okay then, eat up.
Woof!
Yayoi, you're such a good girl.
Yep, you're welcome.
Is your pussy wet?
Woof! Woof!
Okay then, roll over.
Woof!
Woof! Woof!
Hurry up and bear my child, okay?
Bear my child, and not that bastard's!
I'm cumming! Get pregnant, Yayoi! You got it?!
Woof! Woof! Woof! Woof! Woof! Woof! Woof!
I'm cumming!
Get pregnant! Get pregnant!
I love you, Yayoi.
Woof!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч