Master Renji...
The package from the auction has been delivered.
lt took a while...
lt might now be enough time till the next game...
l don't want to make any excuses to Jinkurou, but...
Leave.
Yes, Master Renji.
You smell.
lt was a long journey, but is your body odor just normally stronger?
Your name is?
l... l am...
Yu...
l've been taught it's just Yu.
Oh, yeah, you've lost your memories.
lt's small...
That's right...
l've been sent to this mansion...
Seems like no one has played with you yet.
Come out.
l'll teach you the slave's greeting!
Don't forget it!
Yes!
l, Yu, take an oath to never disobey the master as a sexual slave.
Forget you were a human.
l'm going to train every inch of your body...
...into a dirty sex slave's body.
Yes, master.
Master...
l-lt's at its limit...
lt's going to rip...
No!
Hot!
Hot! lt's coming in!
lt's hot! lt's hot!
My anus!
Seems like it's hardened.
Please...
Don't get rid of me, Master...
Suffer.
l'll pull the whole thing out including the rectum!
My... My stomach!
Please forgive... Please forgive me!
No!
Thank you very much, Master...
Master...
ls...
...this something a person should be treated like?
lt's horrible...
My night at the mansion has started.
l was shocked by the abnormal scene...
...and couldn't get any words out.
l thought...
...what meaning is there for me to be here...
...but there also was the reality for an orphan like myself not having any...
...way of living in the outside world.
Am l going to be...
...treated like that too?
Your anus...
Yes.
This is my first job...
Let me see your indecent spot.
l can't see too well.
Show it to me more.
Suck it.
Yes.
lt smells...
l didn't clean it just for you.
Clean it.
He's making me suck on something this disgusting...
Use the back of your throat more.
lt won't go in any farther...
lt's hot...
So indecent... My pussy...
N-No, my anus is totally turned on!
lt's hot!
lt's a gift from Master. Ask for it the right way.
Please put it in my mouth...
He's going to come.
Twist your tongue.
What... am l...
What?
You can't hold it in anymore?
Then do it here.
Don't touch me with that filth!
Release me from those filthy hands!
What!
What are you going to do?
You think you'll get away with doing such things to me?
lt's cold!
Just because you're the daughter doesn't mean it matters to us.
What is it? Stop it!
No! Stop!
Stop!
No!
l'm... being licked by someone this disgusting...
Stop it!
Shut up!
No...
You know what you have to do, right?
Yes...
Suck it. Show the customer your shameful self.
l heard you're still a virgin.
lt's going to be gone with training anyway...
Why don't you give it to the customer, right, Misuzu?
You are the one treasure l found within the riches of Asahina.
You have to dress up nicely...
That's an idiotic thing!
She is the daughter of the Asahina company...
Then who... am l?
This is once in a life time.
lf you're going to hold a grudge, hold it on your father who fell.
No...
Really, l see...
This spot turns you on so much, huh?
Stop it!
Even if you touch that spot, it's not turning me on!
No, don't look! lt's coming out!
So you're turned on...
You're so wet.
No, it's not like that! You've got it all wrong!
No!
lt's tight. lt's so good.
lt hurts! lt hurts!
lt hurts!
Use your hips more, you female pig!
No! lt's coming!
lt keeps on coming into my pussy!
Forgive me, please!
My stomach...
Suck on this, Misuzu.
Get that dirty thing out of my way.
Make more dirty sounds!
You've got to use your tongue!
Miss Misuzu is getting that many horrible things done...
...but she's so pretty...
l'm the master's slave.
l'll serve you for the rest of my life.
Thank you very much...
...Master...
Miss... Sachie?
What are you going to make me do now...
Please stop...
No!
Master...
Please forgive me...
My nipples...
No, not my clitoris. Not there. Please forgive me. l'm going crazy!
My indecent spot turned into this...
No, don't rub it!
Please forgive me...
No, my clitoris!
No, don't hang it!
Miss... Sachie?
W-Why...
She's accepting Master's love.
No!
Yu, feed Sachie her food.
lt's an order!
Miss Sachie...
No...
Miss Sachie is eating my poop like it's really delicious...
Why!
Why is he like this to Miss Sachie...
Master Renji, why aren't you more...
Master Renji!
No, l'm not!
l'm not Yu!
l am!
No!
Why!
Don't!
Yu...
You are still pretty...
Miss Sachie...
No!
This is horrible. Why...
Why is it...
Why...
Master Renji!
To Be Continued