An analysis of the beauty of female slaves who have had their freedom...
...taken away while being dressed in ''restrictive bondage clothing,'' which sends off a luster of impurity.
The game towards this analysis of beauty will start once again.
l've decided to send you out for a trade.
Please forgive me...
l can't...
...have you say you don't need me anymore...
Master Renji, please forgive me.
l...
Kaname Sakurai...
...take an oath to never... disobey the master as a slave.
l wasn't... sold off...
l'm just sleeping over for a bit...
That's what... Mom said...
lt's horrible, why...
Why is it...
Why...
Master Renji!
How unpresentable you are, daughter of Asahina!
Well, maybe it's the best thing for a female pig like you!
You want to be tortured that much?
There!
Renji!
That toy isn't that bad, but l'm starting to get bored of it...
l heard that bigger one originally was your father's sex slave.
Considering the fact that it was handed down to you...
l'm sure she agonized in such a wonderful way...
l want to test her out if possible...
Show him.
W-Wonderful!
Here l go!
Open your mouth and stick your tongue out!
What's the matter?
Are you turned on too?
Okay...
Mix that up in your mouth without swallowing...
Let me see!
l'm too full already, Master...
No!
No! P-Please don't push!
lt's going to come out!
Please let me go to the bathroom! Master!
Master!
Please forgive me!
What are you mixing up?
Your master is that person over there.
Okay, okay.
l'm going to have so much fun with you!
Y-Yes... Thank you very much...
...Master...
Please forgive...
Please forgive me...
Please!
Please let me come!
Yayoi, because of the plug, you can't come even if you want to, right?
lsn't it such torture?
No!
How unpresentable, Yayoi...
lt's Yayoi!
Come on, l'm going to turn you on more!
l-l'm coming... l'm coming...
l-lt's hot! M-My breasts!
My breasts!
The breasts...
The breasts are getting bigger!
Please let me come.
Here.
Over here too.
lt turns me on!
Please let me come. l beg you.
Turning you on? lt's turning you on.
Let me come...
No, please let me come.
l beg you...
Let me come...
Next is my turn.
No, it's mine.
Okay, why don't we all come!
That's the wrong...
P-Please... Stop!
N-No!
The nipples!
My... nipples!
How's my penis?
l beg you...
Let me come...
Oh, l'm going to come too!
l'm coming!
l beg you.... Let me come...!
Okay!
Come on, come over here!
W-What are you doing?
Stop it! You...
Stop it!
T-The scent of breasts...
Mom's breasts...
lt's warm...
Even when you're being licked by someone like her, you're turned on?
Get away!
No!
Her anus is busy with another situation, so...
Why don't we plow into this one's dirty pussy. lt's her first time.
Then suck on this instead!
Come on!
M-Master...
l can't hold it in anymore...
Please let me go to the bathroom...
Master!
What?
N-No! Stop!
No...
l'm not a baby...
Please let me go to the bathroom...
No! Don't push it!
lf... lf you do that...
lt's... lt's going to come out...
lt... lt came out...
lt feels disgusting...
l can't... Master!
Okay... Come...
Okay...
Go ahead...
Yes...
N-No!
Don't take it off!
Don't look!
No!
Everyone don't look...
lt's embarrassing...
Big sis! What are you...
D-Don't do that!
Delicious...
Don't lick that dirty spot!
No!
No...
Hey!
lt's your turn!
Yes!
W-What is that?
What are you going to do?
No!
Sis!
Master Renji!
Please stop!
l beg you!
Master Renji!
l'm scared...
l beg you!
Master Renji!
Please stop!
l'll do anything in exchange!
So...
No!
N-No!
l-lt hurts!
Why don't you take advantage of me!
Why won't you take advantage of me?
Master Renji...
...how could you...
M-Master Renji...
No!
Everyone in the audience!
Thank you very much for coming here today!
l hope that tonight's party becomes...
...something that will stay in all of your memories!
So let's get to tonight's ritual!
That's this!
The flesh and blood of Yu Mikihara and Misuzu Asahina...
l pledge l will change them back to their pure selves!
The sword!