Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: Anon | TS & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Ayanami
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat c irc.rizon.net
KORO
Bouken Shite mo Ii Koro
No!
Hurry, hurry!
Hi, Junpei here again.
Hero:
Koganei Junpei
My first encounter with the
major motion picture industry ended in success.
And now, our AV film company is doing
unrehearsed filming on a train.
No! Stop it!
Cut!
Apollo Productions Director:
Wakaba Miwa
Okay.
We're gonna do another take inside the train car.
This time, run all the way to the front,
chased by the rapist the whole time.
We're going without a camera test this time.
Naturally, we have no budget or backers
or anything, so it's all guerrilla filming.
At least it's going well for now.
Action!
Why you!
No!
Hey! What the hell are you
guys doing in my train?
...Or not.
Oh crap, get the Chief!
Wait for me, guys!
Hey, Junpei! To me! To me!
Throw me the tripod.
U-Uh, sure!
Good!
Nice catch.
This can't be happening!
This can't be happening...
H-How cruel!
Invasion of the Apollo Productions
Guerrilla Film Squad!
For the millionth time,
I was working on filming a new movie,
"The Romance of Subway Travel."
"The Romance of Subway
Travel" is a tourist video.
Explain to me why there's a
naked girl in a tourist video.
Well, you see...
We thought it would be more popular
if it had a pretty girl in it. Right?
I admit, I'd be more likely to enjoy
it with a pretty girl in it.
But a bare-breasted naked
woman is going too far!
And you didn't even get a filming
permit to film on my trains.
You did just about everything wrong.
Excuse me, sir...
Okay?
You said you were with
Apollo Productions, right?
Yes.
They say they've never heard of you.
Koganei Junpei?
No, we don't have an employee by that name.
Th-That can't be!
Why don't you just tell us the truth, son.
This will be over much faster.
Hey, you! Jackass!
I'm fucking pissed!
Chief!
You're horrible!
I was prepared to take the fall for everyone!
"Koganei Junpei?"
"No, we don't have an
employee by that name.”
If you're going to be like that, all my hard
work for you has been pointless!
Huh? He went home already?
They're all so cold to me.
Ch-Chief!
Good evening, Koganei-kun.
Huh? You're Director Shibuya's secretary.
What are you doing here so late?
I... I came here to ask a favor of you, Koganei-kun.
Secretary:
Ogawa Masako
Junpei-kun is probably really mad right now.
Junpei-kun, nice work!
Sorry we abandoned you today.
Sorr... What!?
You horny, hard-on pervert!
I let you out of my sight for a second,
and this is how you act?
It's not what you think!
Oh, you're...
I'm sorry about that.
I told you it wasn't what you thought!
I'm sorry.
Looks like I caused a big problem.
But I need your help, too, Wakaba-san.
Please let me be in your next adult video.
I'm... I'm still a virgin at age 20.
Isn't that strange?
I have problems with men.
Something traumatic happened
to me when I was little.
And ever since then... I've been
uncomfortable around men.
So I was hoping that perhaps Koganei-kun...
could help me finally lose my virginity.
That's why you want to be in an adult video?
Yes.
I wonder if Ogawa-san will be any good.
Don't worry.
She's got pretty big boobs, and she
does seem to have passion.
I'm sure the Chief will like her.
Right?
But I was really flattered.
About what?
About you coming back for me.
Don't get me wrong.
I just came back to collect something I forgot.
How cold of you.
I endured hours of lecturing
in that stationmaster's office
for you, you know.
Can't you at least thank me?
Just kidding.
Everyone is really grateful to you, Junpei-kun.
I mean, if you hadn't taken
the fall for everyone,
our tape might've been confiscated,
and we would've lost everything.
But our tape is safe.
Miwa-san!
So you’re saying the tape is
more important than me.
I am. It's a fact of life.
Miwa-san!
Keep up the good work, okay?
Junpei-kun.
Hurry, get inside me.
Junpei-kun, hurry.
Miwa-san!
Hey!
You never learn, do you!?
I'm sorry!
You see, adult videos are sort of like fruit.
Apollo Productions CEO:
Ujiki Masami
The girls should be fresh and appealing.
Like, for example, Girls that are fresh as
Video Engineer:
Ishikawa
Kiwi and the Papaya Mangoes!
Like that, Chief?
Um, yeah, that's right.
This is where you come in, Koganei.
Yes?
Your duty for today is to find Apollo's next star.
That's right!
In Harajuku, Shibuya, and Roppongi,
we'll be scouting out young,
fresh, and exciting girls!
Y-Yes, that's exactly right.
U-Um, Chief...
Actually, Miwa-san and I have
already found a perfect girl.
What the fuck? You already found her?
Well, if you already did, then I guess
you can't take it back, you horndog.
Horndog! Fucking pimp!
Hey, asshole!
You're stealing everything I wanted to say!
Just shut your mouth for a while!
Koganei, you've done it!
You've done well!
With praise like that, I'm starting to believe it.
Lighting Designer:
Tanaka
Junpei-chan,
when did you trick her into joining?
Introduce her to me, will ya?
Cameraman:
Ujitani
I'd like to meet her too!
Well? What's she like?
If she's anything like Diane Day,
I'll die a happy man!
I guess she looks like her or something.
Maybe just a little, Junpei-kun.
Are you serious? Where is she?
Where is my Japanese Diane Day?
Oh! Sexy legs!
Oh! Swaying hips!
Shit! Those boobs are unreal!
And the most crucial point, her face...
...looks just like Diane Day!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ogawa Masako.
Koganei, she's no good.
Wh-Why?
Because she doesn't look like Diane Day.
B-But she does sorta look like her, right?
Like her hair...
No, she doesn't!
S-Still, that's no reason to turn her down!
He's right!
You're being too hard on her!
This is my job.
There's no such thing as being
too hard in this business.
Uh, um... am I really that unappealing?
Am I really no good?
Ogawa-san!
Come back here!
Allow me to tell you why you're no good.
Try fucking Koganei right here.
Come. Lie down.
Restrain yourself, restrain yourself.
This is all part of the job, right, Miwa-chan?
She's acting, totally.
She's not really turned on at all.
That hurts!
Stop there!
I'm sorry!
I guess... I'm just... I'm no good!
Your name is Ogawa-kun, right?
Yes.
And you're a virgin, right?
But how did you know?
By your smell.
Ah, stop.
That's not the sort of smell I meant!
Lemme see.
Virgins used to be sought for
magazines all the time...
and I still don't oppose that.
Then Chief!
What about Miwa-san?
Leave me out of this!
There was one other.
One other?
You should know the answer
better than anyone else.
But then, Chief, don't you think you
should give Ogawa her wish?
She wants her first time filmed.
The moment a girl changes into a woman is
the most beautiful her body will ever be!
Then why won't you allow it?
If I say no, that's final.
Oh, come on!
That's not a real reason!
That's okay.
Koganei-san, Miwa-san,
you've done enough.
Thanks for trying.
Ogawa-san!
Why did you say that, Chief!?
Explain yourself!
I admit, she has something special.
Then why won't you use her!?
Because she's too gloomy.
I want to film the vibrant,
contemporary youth of today.
We don't need the moody type
in Apollo Productions!
Is that the only reason
why you won't take her?
I hate that about you.
Don't go!
Try not to go outside with
your dick hanging out.
Ah, g-good idea!
La la la, where are you?
Where are you? Are you okay?
Kumamoto-san?
Kumamoto-san, where are you?
Senpai, those raccoons were really big.
And the parents were shot with a gun.
Look at it, cook it, eat it,
and I'm gonna try and draw it all.
Forget about it.
You're not the same Masako that gets
depressed about that anymore.
Come on. Let's go for it!
Welcome, sir.
The usual.
I didn't ask for that.
It's from that lady.
Are you here alone?
No. I'm meeting someone here.
"Meeting someone"?
Then you must not be sure
if he's showing up.
Not exactly.
The one I'm meeting is sitting
next to me right now.
I've been waiting for you, President Ujiki.
How did you know my name?
You still don't get it?
Now do you remember? We met yesterday.
I-It's you?
I had no idea!
What are you doing here?
I'm seducing you.
What?
I mean, you told me I have no appeal.
So I came here to seduce you.
Is that funny?
You think an amateur like you can seduce
a pro like me? I've seen it all.
What if I  succeed?
You won't.
Is that so?
S-Stop it. Stop it.
Would you like to bet?
Bet?
F-For what?
If I win, you use me in your next video.
And if I win?
I'll dance around naked in Shibuya.
Very well.
But I doubt you'll be able to seduce me.
I'll show you otherwise.
Driver, please go to the first point.
Very well, miss.
Where are you taking me?
My apartment.
Shit. She says she's gonna seduce me,
and now she's making me
wait outside forever?
Sorry for the wait.
Oh, wow!
Please come in.
Th-This is the home-cooked aroma
that makes all bachelors cry!
I hope you like it.
I'll bring you the pickles soon.
Oh, my?
Chief?
What are you doing?
Let's end this charade!
And let's have a fun night together!
Then I win the bet.
The bet?
I never went all the way.
I figured you'd say something like that.
Wh-What's this!?
Let me down! Let me down!
Let's me down!
We got it all down on film.
Now we have video proof.
Now I get it.
You were all in cahoots! You tricked me!
And that’s how Masako's virgin
graduation video was scheduled.
I was assigned to write the script.
It's a love story, and I know the location.
Work hard, okay?
I live for these trivial moments.
Masako-san, you seem in high spirits.
Did something nice happen to you recently?
Not telling.
I'm going out for a bit.
Can you take care of the phone for me?
Sure.
Bye, thanks.
Okay. Take your time.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Ah, this warmth!
Oh! Masako-san's smell!
Chief Assistent Director:
Gondo
B-Bad news, sir!
Film Director:
Shibuya Shozo
It's Koganei!
It's that bastard Koganei!
He's putting my secretary in a porno?
I won't let him.
I won't fucking let him!
Yes?
Ogawa-kun, do you have a minute?
Excuse me.
Help me! Koganei-kun...
Help me!
So zoom in there.
Okay.
That's strange.
She definitely should've left by now.
Something must be up.
She's not the type of girl who'd flake out.
I hope she didn't get in an accident.
I'll go have a look around.
Hello.
Is anyone here?
That's strange. They shouldn't
be taking today off.
Gondo was acting weird.
Could it be...
I... I knew it!
Junpei-san!
What a horrible thing to do!
I'll come help you right now!
Koganei!
You bastard, what are you doing!?
What am I doing?
I should ask you!
Why is Masako like this?
Fuck you!
You'd never... You'd never
understand how I feel!
Ow!
Junpei-san! Watch out!
What the hell is going on, Director?
A Kidnapping, just like it seems.
Kidnapping?
Listen, Koganei, I'll never let my sweet
secretary star in your cheap porno.
Do you get it?
Gondo, keep close watch on them both.
What's up, Koganei?
Wanna eat some pie?
What’s wrong? You keep fidgeting like that.
You have to take a piss or something?
How bout now?
Masako-san!
Wait for me!
I promise I'll come back for you!
Wh-What?
They've kidnapped Ogawa?
How horrible!
Let's kick their asses!
But I don't understand...
Why would a man like Shibuya be
so possessive about his secretary?
Look who's talking, Chief.
You fell for her sexy charm.
Sh-Shut-up!
But if she's being held captive,
Apollo Productions can't make
any progress on its next film.
In tnat case, chief...
To the Secret Locker!
"Secret Locker"?
Sound off!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
U-Um, Chief, what are we going to do exactly?
Captain! Call me Captain!
Well invade Shibuya's home...
and liberate his prisoner, Ogawa Masako!
But if we do that, Shibuya will
just get more pissed off at us.
And then we really won't be able
to make the movie with...
Don't misunderstand me!
Our filming has already started!
We'll abandon our former plans
and do guerrilla filming!
"Guerrilla filming"?
Some pretty freaky stuff happens
when there's no script.
Let's go!
My fearless soldiers of Apollo!
Sir, yes, sir!
Jimpei-kun, hurry!
Yes, sir!
Masako-san, you'd better eat
something eventually.
You've been holding in your
pee this whole time, too.
Can't you just wet your-
How dare you.
You're a horrible man!
It's not like I want to be doing this.
Masako-san, I don't want Koganei to have you!
I don't want you to be in their dirty porno!
That’s for me to decide, not you.
Masako-san, ever since the first day you
joined the company, I've wanted you!
I love you.
But you're going to be in a dirty porno
with that stupid hard-on freak.
F-Fucking Koganei. Unforgivable!
If you wanna be in a porno so bad,
I'll shoot one, and it'll be amazing!
Hell no.
Your world view is too dark.
I'm drawn to Koganei's brightness.
He might be able to make me...
He might be able to make you what?
You're just a normal woman, after all.
You probably just want to fuck Koganei!
Sex!
If that's the kind of woman you are,
then here's a solution.
Stop it! Stop it!
I'll fuck... I'll fuck you!
What are you doing?
Why? Why won't you be more understanding?
And here I love you so much.
Let's make the most of this.
Who the fuck are you guys?
The Apollo Productions Guerrilla
Warfare Filming Squad!
You bastards.
Fire! Fire, fire, fire!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
I'll get you back someday!
Ogawa-san, are you okay?
Yes.
I'll untie you now.
Hey, Junpei-kun, could you help me?
Wh-Why you...
dirty-ass pervert!
Why only me?
Ogawa-san, don't worry.
It's all over now.
Koganei-san! I was so scared.
Okay! Now we'll film the crucial
virgin graduation scene.
Miwa-san, you're so...
But I'm still not ready yet.
You'll be fine.
If you leave everything to me,
I'll turn you into a beautiful princess,
just like Cinderella.
Thanks.
Junpei-kun, you pervert!
How dare you say such cheesy
lines all cool like that.
So you’re here at last, dogs of Apollo.
Setsuko-san, your daughter is growing up
so fast that I can't reach her anymore.
But, Setsuko, I haven't
forgotten my promise to you.
Scenario Transform!
Koganei, you'd better show
me something good.
This is impressive.
I never thought I'd be
filming this inside a cage,
but I think it'll end up
looking very picturesque.
We'll make the most of it.
Wh-What's that?
Wh-Whoa.
What the hell?
This part wasn't in the manga!
How naive you are.
Deviating from the manga is what anime does.
Changing the plot of a story
is a director's prerogative.
I won't let you have Masako.
Prepare to die!
My tackle will fold that wall like paper!
Chief!
We'll be fine.
This wall is sturdy.
It's made of a special alloy.
It's go time, Gondo.
Yes, sir.
Oh, this hurts!
Director! Director!
Oh, how horrible!
He's having a heart attack!
My heart is... stopping!
Oh, no! Just like during the
filming of the last movie.
His pills!
Where are his pills?
Over there.
Unlock the gate.
And release only Gondo.
We'll let him take care of Shibuya.
Miwa-san!
Now the score is even.
We're one-to-one, bitches.
But you fought dirty!
Chief! What about Miwa-san?
Shut up!
Now's no time for personal
feelings to get in the way.
You have to fuck Ogawa-kun.
For the success of our operation,
there will be sacrifices.
Oh, no!
Oh, Ujiki, it seems you
understand where this is going.
In that case, I won't waste your time.
Miwa-san!
Chief! If we don't do anything, Miwa will...
Don’t falter!
Shibuya is a good man!
He would never rape Miwa!
That's not true!
He cani't be trusted.
He has a secret trick for violating a woman...
without even laying a finger on her!
I wish I could do that.
Will you teach me your
trick, Director Shibuya?
It's not a good thing at all!
He hypnotizes the woman,
and she begins to masturbate.
Then she has an orgasm far
beyond anything tolerable.
It's a truly frightening trick!
So you're saying she will be
a slave to him forever?
Then Miwa-san will...
I, Shibuya Shozo, master hypnotist, will
transform you into the whore you really are!
Miwa-san!
Junpei-kun, I'll be okay.
Enjoy saying that while you still can.
Awaken, whorish blood!
Miwa-san!
Ow!
Wh-What was that?
My hypnosis beam was deflected!
Come! Do it now, Koganei!
Fuck her! Fuck her now!
No! Koganei-kun, look only at me.
Fuck only me!
I will.
Here I go.
Junpei-kun...
What's wrong with you, Koganei!?
I can't do it.
Oh, no!
This is no ordinary woman.
She should be well under my spell by now.
What's going on?
Masako-san...
Masako-san!
Dammit!
My spell hit Gondo!
No! Get away from me!
Ogawa-san, watch out!
Move it! Give me Masako!
No way! I'm not budging!
If you don't move, this will happen.
Yikes! The iron melted!
Shit!
Wait! Koganei, can't you see it?
It's the legend of the red thread!
Masako-san...
No! Stop it!
What are you doing?
This looks like it'll be the first real
fuck I've seen in a long time.
What's happening to me?
I've resisted men for so long,
but now the tension is melting out of my body.
Gondo, you're dead!
This is how you repay my kindness?
Director, it's okay now.
I know that you did a lot to help me as a child
because of my traumatic experience.
Senpai, those raccoons were really big.
And the parents were shot with a gun.
Look at it, cook it, eat it,
and I'm gonna try and draw it all.
What is this? This soft, gentle,
and nostalgic feeling...
That’s it!
It's love! It's love!
Ogawa-kun, you kids taught me something.
It's about love.
Without love, real sex cannot take place!
M-Miwa-san!
Miwa-san! Are you okay?
Miwa-san...
You feel great.
What are you doing?
Miwa-san! You're awake?
Thank God! I was worried about you!
Get your lower half out of my way!
Jeez! I lower my guard for a second,
and this is hat happens.
Why you... dirty hard-on horndog!
It's... It's not what you think!
And it was this video, that brought
the two of them together.
Watching it deeply moved me.
Masako's mother was an associate of mine
when I used to be an assistant director.
I finally was able to fulfill my promise to her.
I truly believe this.
In the end,
that guerrilla video became a big hit.
Because of it, Gondo and Ogawa got married.
This is my first time attending a wedding.
I wonder if Miwa and I will ever get married?
Yeah, right.
Koganei Junpei
Hey, Koganei!
There's a time and a place
to get hard, numbskull!
asphalt kodoku no building
Asphalt, the lonely building,
tachi sukumu minareta machi
The still streets so familiar to me.
Kochi no nagare ni senaka osae
Going with it, leaning back,
ikiru no mo waruku wa nai sa
Isn't a bad way to live.
dakedo tsukuri warai no warui face.
But I don't want a face with a bad fake smile.
sugoshitakunai dake na no sa
That's not how I want to live my life.
kami naru kanene no ude o
These strong, powerful arms of mine
nawa tsukarete kondo anuite miru
Won't be bound this time as I walk forward.
ato sukoshi de
And in just a little while,
teenware to wakitai nukedaseru kedo
I'll be able to escape my false hopes.
deguchi wa nai sa
But there is no escape.
warui baby
Sorry, baby.
tori ashitake mukau
Our first steps face each other.
just a puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle.
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
Never say love
Never say love.
tsekuri warai no warui face
I don't want a face with a bad fake smile.
sogoshitakunai kara sa
That's not how I want to live my life.
puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
Never say
Never say...
puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle.
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
never say love
Never say love.