KORO
Bouken Shite mo Ii Koro
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: Squiggy | TS & Enrode: ShocWave | QC: Ayanami
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
So this is the place.
Rainbow Mansion 5055
First Challenge!! Into the World of Adult Films!!
Apollo Productions
So I've finally made it.
You flipping moron!
College is so yesterday. Just quit it.
It's the era of talent now!
Come work for me!
We're currently seeking new staff.
Pornos are great, man.
After all, you'll get to see them
for free if you work for me.
Ishikawa-senpai's speech
sounded too good to be true.
But I actually quit the college entrance exams
to work for a porno video company.
If my mom heard about that,
she'd probably get mad.
Is this okay? Is this okay?
This is so lewd!
My innocent dream was to become
a world famous movie guy, not this!
I'd talk business with Coppola.
Shake Spielberg's hand!
And make plans for a new
movie with George Lucas!
To make movies with all those
geniuses was my dream!
Guess I'll go home.
Sexy!
S-Sorry!
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
She's beautiful.
Th -These papers...
Apollo Productions
U-Um...
Thanks!
Apollo Productions?
But that's Ishikawa's porno film company.
That girl is a porn star? No way!
It can't be.
I'm back.
It's not like one decision dictates
your entire life anyway!
Even if it's a winding or thorny path!
Koganei Junpei, age 19!
Hero
Koganei Junpei
It's about time I had an adventure!
Oh, hi.
Um!
Oh, I see. You're Koganei-san,
here for the interview.
H-How did you know?
Come on in.
Mr. Ishikawa told me a lot about you.
"A lot"?
Wow, it's really clean in here.
All the company members are gone now,
but they should be back soon.
O-Oh, thanks.
No bra!
Is something the matter?
No! Um, I mean, sorry if this is a
rude question, but who are you?
Oh, sorry, I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Wakaba Miwa.
Apollo Productions Director: Wakaba Miwa.
I'm an actress for this company.
Which means that...
this sweet looking girl...
looks like this...
and does that...
This can't be!
F-From that angle too!
Oh, no!
Junpei-san! You're too good!
Is something wrong?
You're covered in sweat.
Uh, no! It's nothing.
Don't worry about me.
Hey, Koganei-san, do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
Hey, Koganei-san, are you a virgin?
Aw, come on. Gimme a break.
You're not?
Um, well... It's more like, "Do I look like one"?
Guess so.
What are you doing, Wakaba-san?
Boys mustn't be shy.
Come on. Let me see.
W-We shouldn't be doing this! Not here!
Wow, you're pretty big.
But you've got hair.
How cute.
Th-That's not right!
I tweeze it out.
Hair everywhere!
See? See?
You're funny.
Ha ha, you liked my bad rhyme.
Listen, I'm a bad girl.
I can't hold back anymore!
Oh shit!
Accept my love!
Where are you putting your dick!?
Don't worry!
I'll take full responsibility
for the consequences!
No!
You just came here for an interview!
Like I give a shit!
I don't care about a stupid interview anymore!
Cut!
"C-Cut"?
'sup, Koganei?
I-Ishikawa-senpai!
What's going on? What's going on?
What's going on!?
This is your interview.
This is the way we haze newcomers at Apollo.
A-An interview?
That was?
I suppose so.
What do you think, Chief?
Wouldn't he make a good co-star?
Isn't he your type? Don t you think so?
Koganei, let me introduce you.
This is the company president, Ujiki-san.
Apollo Productions CEO:
Ujiki Masami
And the cameraman, Ujitani-san.
Cameraman:
Ujitani
What a relief.
We're short on staff.
Our lighting designer, Tanaka-san.
Lighting Designer
Tanaka
Nice to meet you, Mr. Pubic Hair.
W-Wait a minute!
I'm the video engineer, Ishikawa.
Video Engineer:
Ishikawa.
And this is our very talented director,
Wakaba Miwa-chan.
"D-Director”?
Welcome to Apollo Productions.
N-No way!
I guess we could try him out.
You pass!
Koganei, I'm proud of you.
W-Wait just a minute!
First you spring this bullshit "interview" on me,
and now you're making up my mind for me?
This wasn't what you told me!
I didn't come here to audition to be in a porno!
You may say that, but you were
pretty into it just now.
W-Well! That was just...
Well, I think it's all good.
Just don't embarrass me.
Newbies need to get all the
experience they can.
After a while, I'll let you get
behind the camera too. Got it?
Stop making up my mind for me!
Even I have a sense of morality!
I dreamed of leaving behind
my humble upbringings in a hick town
to be a world famous movie director.
I proudly proclaimed that when I left home!
But if I appear full-frontal in front of a camera,
how am I gonna explain myself to everyone
who has high expectations of me?
Don't say "full frontal,'' please.
Oops. Sorry.
Hey there!
You snot-faced boy!
Don't be so fucking cocky!
Let me tell you something about porno videos.
They're like the martial arts
of the film industry!
They're not like the cushy corporate
films in the mainstream!
I can't breathe!
Ch-Chief, Chief, easy, easy.
He had it coming!
Those who look down on pornos...
have no right to be in the film industry!
Get the fuck out!
I-I'll be glad to get the fuck out.
Hey! Koganei!
Can't you move it, jackass?
Boss Kanekura!
Ujiki, I came for your answer.
A heartless investor:
Kanekura
You do know what I mean.
Yes! Just another twenty days!
No! Just two weeks!
I should have everything handled by then!
I didn't come here to bargain.
I came here to find out if I'm smashing Apollo
Productions or not. It's one or the other.
Well, I...
Wait!
If you do that, we won't be able to film!
Miwa-chan!
No! No!
I don't intend to trick you.
Got it, Ujiki? It's in your hands.
Yes! Just give me two weeks!
Shut the fuck up!
Do it!
What? A love hotel?
I'm a girl. Please don't make me ask twice.
To put it in simple terms...
I wanna do it with you.
N-No way! This is all so sudden!
R-Really?
Come on.
Oh, no, Miwa-san!
Not right here!
This is no good!
I don't mind being watched.
Are you sure you want to?
Are you sure you want someone like me?
We're a man and woman.
We don't need an excuse to have sex.
W-Wow. So this is hat it looks like.
Stop staring at it.
Just do it quick.
You're right.
In these circumstances, we must shrug
off our insecurities and shame.
Miwa-san!
Ah, just a dream.
But what a realistic dream it was!
She had such an innocent-looking
face at the interview,
but she didn't even blush
at the sight of my dick.
I guess she's used to it.
She's probably got a boyfriend,
but maybe she'll let me fuck her if I beg.
Ah! My right hand seized up!
Damm it!
I wanna fuck Miwa-san!
Let me fuck her!
Ah, that felt good.
Y-Yes? It’s open! Come in!
Good morning.
M-Miwa! Director Miwa!
If you scream as loudly as that,
you'll disturb the neighbors.
Ishikawa gave me a map of where you live.
He's just really pushy.
And here I was about to give up on you.
W-Wait a minute!
Wh-What are you doing here?
You want to fuck me, don't you?
That must've scared you yesterday.
Guess so.
That's not an unusual
occurrence in our line of work.
Don't hold back. Eat up, Koganei-kun.
Well... I-I m really honored to be
out with you, Ms. Director,
but I'm not sure about being in a porno.
We're just eating hamburgers, dear.
I intended to go to film school and
make something of myself,
but all I've done so far is
8mm stuff on the farm.
I would like to be on the staff, though.
I'll help out with anything!
You'll do anything for me?
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious!
Then I'd like you to appear in my next film.
You see, Apollo Productions will probably
go under if our next project fails.
Unlike mainstream projects, independent
films are very difficult to produce.
Even the talented people suffer.
In order to really communicate a
moving experience to the viewer,
the acting and the directing must be good.
But more than anything, the
characters must be very appealing.
I'm sorry. I guess I should just give this up.
I shouldn't be telling you this,
but our CEO is broke.
And he's borrowed money
from a notorious jerk.
In other words, he's in debt to Kanekura.
And because of that, Kanekura
makes us change the script.
He talks back to us.
And to me...
He did something to you?
That asshole keeps pressuring the CEO
to make a porno starring him and me.
N-No way!
We had been secretly planning a different
production starring Shinohara Chie.
We'd hoped it would be a big hit
so we could pay him back, but...
Whoa! The Shinohara Chie?
We were going to pay her later.
But she refuses to participate unless
she approves of her costar.
When I saw you, Koganei-kun, it hit
me hard that you'd be perfect.
It's hitting me hard too.
I'm a huge fan!
If it will save you from your crisis,
I will fuck Chie with all my might!
Koganei-kun?
Miwa-san, could you stop
calling me "Koganei-kun"?
You can call me Junpei.
W-Walking like this m-makes
me feel like we're lovers.
Then let's go someplace where lovers go.
Th-This hotel?
Yup. To scope out the location.
We're going in?
Of course we are.
This film mostly takes place in a love hotel.
Awesome.
This room fits my image perfectly.
Let's turn on the video.
M-Miwa-san...
Miwa-san, I can't hold out anymore!
We can't!
A director mustn't get involved with her actor!
Then let's get involved as man and woman!
No! Stop it!
Ah, help me!
What a great view, babe.
I can totally see all the dirty stuff.
Don't fight back, bitch!
It was your choice to come in here.
P-Please stop it!
You were planning this all along!
I didn't know you were like this.
It was your fault for coming to this
kind of place with a guy, babe.
You know you want it too.
That's not true at all!
I'll fuck you up, bitch!
Hey, is mumbling to the video that much fun?
Well, as long as we're here, let's
make use of the facilities.
Will you put this on?
Miwa-san, you don't mean...
Too late to discover my identity now.
Call me "Queen"!
Scream out "Queen"!
You are my dog!
It's falling down!
What’s wrong?
Come on. Hurry.
Are we really gonna do this?
Miwa-san! Let me go!
No, dear.
Miwa-san! You really don't trust me?
No, I don't.
Weren't you the guy screaming from inside
his apartment that he wanted to fuck me?
I paid for the room, after all.
I'd better at least use the shower, right?
This is torture!
Porn star:
Shinohara Chie
Shinohara-san.
We did it, Junpei-kun!
She likes the script, and she likes you!
R-Really?
But I'm kinda nervous.
Don't worry.
You're the type of guy who can turn into
a superhero when put under pressure.
Next, we're going to do the flashback scene.
Um, am I doing it for real in this take?
I was just thinking that I can't do
it unless there's love involved.
What's wrong, Junpei-kun?
It won't get hard?
Um...
Let me see.
You don't need to worry.
Th-That's not the issue!
What is?
I can't have sex with another woman
while the girl I like watches!
I didn't think I could say that.
And besides...
No! Stop it!
Okay, here we go. Start the VTR.
The camera's rolling.
5... 4...
3... 2...
I've gotta pee!
What's his problem?
He's slow!
Junpei! What'cha doing in there?
Wh-What the hell?
Where are you calling from?
I-I'm sorry.
But I can't...
You think "I'm sorry" will make
everything better, you shit!?
Explain yourself!
I-I'm sorry... but is Miwa-san there?
No, don't put her on the line.
You're in love with the director?
And you "can't give up your virginity
in front of the woman you love"?
Wake up, you fucker!
Fuck my life.
Junpei-kun?
M-Miwa-san?
Thanks.
I'm very flattered.
But you see, the job has already started.
Everyone has already
invested quite a lot into it.
I guess I said something wrong.
No. It's not your fault at all.
But I'm very disappointed in
you for bailing on us now.
Where are you right now?
Th-The telephone booth in the second block.
Stay there.
What a pathetic wimp!
I had no idea he was like that.
Director, what should we do?
Get him back.
Just be gentle with him, okay?
He's your future husband, after all.
Don't make a joke out of this.
Just a minute.
I was the one who was stood up.
Miwa-
Chie-san?
You'll catch a cold like that.
I’ve got clothes for you in the car.
U-Um...
Get in.
U-Um, we're going the opposite
direction of the hotel.
Of course we are.
You can't work in your condition.
I'm sorry.
And the poor director cried.
Girls don't know how to take a confession
of love that is so sudden and awkward.
And what's more, at a time when her
head is full of her director's duties.
She's very talented.
And you love her.
D-Don't say that.
It seems like she actually
has a thing for you too.
How do you know!?
Woman's instinct.
This is my true form.
We're having some personal time today.
Ch-Chie-san?
Of course, this will also help
tomorrow's rehearsal.
I'll make a man out of you.
There's no director and no camera in here.
Just the two of us alone.
Ch-Chie-san!
We really shouldn't be doing this!
That attitude of yours is putting
Miwa-chan in a tough spot.
B-But I...
Let's end the talk there.
If... If you do that, I'll...
Come here.
O-Okay.
You're really big.
Wow!
You're hitting all the way inside!
I can't hold back anymore!
That was very nice.
What you just did.
Cut!
Okay, that's good!
That was fucking intense!
See? You can do it!
Good work! Here you go.
It's all thanks to Shinohara-san.
What a relief.
You were amazing.
It's a wrap!
Good work, Shinohara-san.
D-Director!
Yes?
Did you get some good shots?
Yes, I did.
Was it emotionally moving?
I tried my best.
I need to do some editing now,
so I'm heading out.
Huh? She's leaving already?
Leaving?
We're starting the shoot at 6:00 tomorrow.
See you then.
Director...
Ujiki Masami, legendary producer,
will now sing you a song.
Oh, gross, Chief. That's your eighth song!
Miwa-san...
Will it sell well?
Most likely.
I think it will be known as one of Chie's best.
Then why aren't you smiling more?
Maybe I'm coming down with something.
A-A cold? That's horrible!
Ujitani-san, drink up!
It's a big party tonight!
Yeah, we got some great shots.
This will revive Apollo Productions for sure.
A toast to you, Miwa-chan.
Let's do the next one!
Hey! What are you guys doing over there!?
Retreat!
Hey! Wait up!
Come back here!
It's been a long time since I've run this much.
Looks like we lost the others.
Huh? This is close to your apartment, isn't it?
Should we just go back?
No way. I'm too drunk to walk any further.
C-Could it be her way of seducing me?
Miwa-san...
She's asleep.
She was heavy!
Heay, Miwa-san, wake-up?
You'll catch cold.
U-Um, Miwa-san... your panties are showing!
Miwa... san?
No!
Showing me your colors like that!
It's your fault, bitch!
No! Don't!
You Slut!
How d'ya like this?
Fucking awesome!
At least I wish that would happen,
but I don't have the balls.
Junpei-kun?
Miwa-san...
Fully
awake
You filthy man!
Wh-What was that for?
You're the worst!
Stealing my body when I was drunk!
W-Wait a minute!
Let go of me, you pervert!
You just don't listen to people, do you!?
What are you gonna do?
Hit me?
Mornin'.
You motherfucker.
You and Miwa-chan did
something good, didn't ya?
Good morning.
Oh, here she is.
They came here together.
Miwa's face looks serious.
And Miwa-chan's wearing the
same clothes as yesterday.
U-Um...
Damn you, Koganei!
How dare you treat our poster girl like that!
I didn't do anything.
Oh yes, he did.
I keep telling you, I didn't!
If I'd realized you'd accuse me like
this anyway, I would've done it!
Now you're trying to put the blame on me.
I'll bet you did do it!
Are you guys still fighting?
Yeah.
Do I really look like I'd do
something perverted like that?
Well, it’s hard to deny when I
see that face on the screen.
Ah! But that was just acting!
Really?
Director, he's actually cumming, isn't he?
Good point.
And the fact that he showed that lewd face
to me last night really pisses me off.
J-Just a minute, Director!
Listen to me, okay?
M-Miwa-san...
Senpai, I just don't understand Miwa anymore.
And if things keep up like this,
it'll be like I really did violate her.
You really didn't do anything that night?
Of course I didn't!
Miwa-san simply jumped to
the conclusion that I did!
Why didn't you?
Wh-Why didn't I?
I mean, I just...
She does have strange opinions
of men here and there.
She slapped me once too.
Well, don't worry.
I'll smooth things over for ya.
Senpai!
Well, you take this.
I’ve gotta go.
It's an honor to have you mooch off of me!
Yeah, whatever.
Thank you for helping me!
So you were up here?
Where are the others?
Still in the studio.
And Koganei is still in low spirits.
Ishikawa-san!
Can I ask a favor?
Will you give Junpei a message for me?
I've been thinking.
My panties weren't stretched, and I
don't feel like I've been penetrated.
I have a feeling I made a mistake.
Ah, I see. Yeah.
But for some reason, I can't seem to stop
acting awkward around Junpei.
And that stupid boy... he slept away
from me under just a thin blanket.
He's sweet and quite a gentleman.
And in comparison, I'm just...
Wh-What the hell?
This is turning into a fucking romance novel!
What about me?
Sorry! I was gonna keep quiet about this,
but seeing you like this, I
can't hold back anymore!
He said, "Oh, she was amazing!"
"I couldn't let go of her."
Th-That can't be true!
What are you talking about?
You really don't remember?
He said you were really freaky.
N-No way.
He's fucking dead!
And here I almost forgave the bastard!
Thank you.
I can count on you to tell me the truth!
No matter what happens,
I'm on your side, Miwa-chan.
He's still in the studio, right?
W-Wait...
Maybe I went a little too far?
Well, if I don't go to these extremes,
there's no chance for me.
Are you sure, Senpai?
Yeah, you're welcome.
I cleared up the misunderstanding,
but she's actually kind of pissed now.
She was like, "Why did he take me back
to his place and not do anything to me?"
Most girls would have that expectation.
Men are like that, after all.
And she sort of expected it, you retard.
But she was really mad,
and I don't really know why.
You re really a nitwit.
Lemme tell ya about women.
They act the exact opposite
of the way they feel.
She’s only acting embarrassed and mad.
Actually, it's the opposite. Opposite!
Women sure are complicated.
Miwa-san!
Miwa-san, um, I...
I just didn't understand how you felt.
How can you grin at me like
a hungry five-year-old?
You're even worse than I thought.
You say I was the one who
came on to you? You suck!
When did I come on to you?
I don't ever want to see your face again!
U-Um, I don't really
understand what you're saying.
Um, is that also the opposite?
What do you mean?
I mean, like, that you want to sleep with me.
You dirty worm!
Gee, was I stupid.
I really shouldn't trust men.
I don't get it!
I really don't get women!
With cheap money, you tried
to change our video?
Wh-Where did all this money come from?
Thanks to Koganei Junpei and Director
Miwa, "Love Angel" was a big success.
Did you see the look on that octopus’s face?
Hey, Miwa-chan!
The octopus of the adult film
industry was just here.
Resignation notice
Resignation?
Why are you doing this?
I'm quitting Apollo Productions after today.
Why?
Is it something I did?
No.
I thought I could keep my personal
life and work separate,
but I can't work with someone
I don't respect as a human being.
Bye.
And thanks.
Excuse me.
M-Miwa-san!
Wait a minute!
I'm so sorry, sir!
Move it.
I’m going home.
I'm not letting you get away.
Let's both have some fun while we're in here.
Wh-What are you saying?
I see no problem with it.
We've already done it once before, after all.
Do you realize what you're saying?
It won't make a difference
if we fuck a few more times.
What a horrible man!
Oops.
I don't think you'll win in a fight against a man.
Someone help!
This is just right.
It feels right.
You monster!
I don't need lectures from you, bitch.
I'm gonna fuck your brains out!
No!
Miwa-san. Miwa-san?
Um, please be disgusted with me.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Sorry for holding you down.
There's no way a weak-willed guy like me
could force a girl to have sex with me.
Even that night... when you
were passed out drunk...
I couldn't do it.
I especially can't do it to someone I love.
Please believe me.
Junpei-kun...
Ah, that felt good.
Now I can quit with no regrets.
I'll take responsibility for what happened
and quit this company tomorrow.
You won't have to see me ever again.
I didn't get to know you for very long,
but it was fun while it lasted.
Don't do it!
Please don't quit!
Junpei-kun! Junpei-kun.
Miwa-san?
I'm sorry!
It was my mistake!
Please forgive me!
Miwa-san, don't cry.
So you'll forgive me?
Of course I will!
Go for it!
Hey, cut it out!
What are you doing?
asphalt kodoku no building
Asphalt, the lonely building,
tachi sukumu minareta machi
The still streets so familiar to me.
Kochi no nagare ni senaka osae
Going with it, leaning back,
ikiru no mo waruku wa nai sa
Isn't a bad way to live.
dakedo tsukuri warai no warui face.
But I don't want a face with a bad fake smile.
sugoshitakunai dake na no sa
That's not how I want to live my life.
kami naru kanene no ude o
These strong, powerful arms of mine
nawa tsukarete kondo anuite miru
Won't be bound this time as I walk forward.
ato sukoshi de
And in just a little while,
teenware to wakitai nukedaseru kedo
I'll be able to escape my false hopes.
deguchi wa nai sa
But there is no escape.
warui baby
Sorry, baby.
tori ashitake mukau
Our first steps face each other.
just a puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle.
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
Never say love
Never say love.
tsekuri warai no warui face
I don't want a face with a bad fake smile.
sogoshitakunai kara sa
That's not how I want to live my life.
puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
Never say
Never say...
puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle.
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
never say love
Never say love.