Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: Anon | TS & Enrode: ShocWave | QC: Ayanami
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
KORO
Bouken Shite mo Ii Koro
Hero:
Koganei Junpei
As a man who dreams of becoming
the next world-famous movie director...
This is Koganei Junpei,
on his second adventure!
Ready?
Start!
Crank Into the Burning Love of Youth
Junpei-kun, let's swim!
Here I go!
Junpei-kun...
Miwa-san...
Hurry!
I think we're okay now.
Lucky!
Wanna have some fun now
that it's just the two of us?
Meaning, are you asking for a do-over?
A dream?
Dammit! Fucking shark!
Why'd he have to show up when
things were getting good!?
Moron. Moron.
Good morning.
Ribbit, ribbit.
Oh, crap.
Chief! It's finished!
Apollo Productions CEO:
Ujiki Masami
Shut the fuck up. It's morning!
Sorry about that. I'm just grumpy.
So?
This is the script for the next project!
A script, huh.
Chief, what's wrong?
Koganei, we're putting the
next project on hold.
"﻿On hold"?
I wonder if bunnies on the
mountain taste good.
But why are we putting it on-
We've got no money! No money!
N-No way.
But didn't we make a huge
profit on the last one?
All the profits went to paying off our debt.
Apollo Productions Director:
Wakaba Miwa
So how are we gonna move on now?
We're discussing that right now!
Keep your shirt on.
Guess I wasted an all-night writing session.
Junpei, looks like you'd better think
of an alternative source of income.
That's a bit harsh, even for you.
 ﻿Good morning.
Hey, guys!
Sir? Sir, please use this.
There's not much in there, but use all of it.
Awesome. Kick ass!
At least I wish it were that simple.
But I don't want it.
Sir!
Miwa, I appreciate the gesture, but no thanks.
But...
Don't worry.
Apollo Productions won't go under so easily.
But do you have funding for the next project?
We do.
You're lying.
Everyone, gather round!
Friends. As you're well aware,
Apollo Productions is facing a crisis.
In order to overcome this crisis,
I'm going to need your help. ﻿
Our help? What sort of help?
I need all of you to get side
jobs to provide funding.
Side jobs?
Host Club
Hercules
Ta-da! ﻿
You sure are cute.
Hey! Whoa! Wait!
Someone! Help!
Welcome, Miss.
Take care of my car, please.
Actress:
Mina Yoshiko
Yeah! Shake it!
Go! Go!
Welcome, Miss.
Have a drink.
Go! Go!
So sexy.
It's not much.
Thanks.
Whoa, stop it! I'm getting too excited!
Like this.
You really are a funny boy.
I'm Koganei Junpei.
Miss, you're the actress Mina
Yoshiko, aren't you?
Lucky!
I've seen all of your movies!
I had no idea college students liked my films.
I'm flattered.
I'm not in college.
I'm training to be a film director.
You're a director-hopeful?
I like you.
Want to dance?
Working at a host club to raise money.
Look what we've stooped to.
I'm satisfied.
Because you got to meet Mina Yoshiko?
Bingo! Correct!
Woo-hoo.
 ﻿I got her autographed handkerchief
and business card.
And she also says she'll introduce
me to her film industry friends.
Idiot.
She was just being polite.
Chief, pull yourself together!
I know you're trying to earn money,
but you don't need to be so reckless.
You think I can do this sort
of degrading thing sober?
No matter what, Apollo won't be crushed.
But for my precious company...
I've caused everyone else so much distress.
I'm sorry.
Awesome! Miwa-san...
Junpei-kun, how was your first day at work?
I hope you like this midnight snack.
I'm starting to plan our next film
using your script as a base.
My script, huh.
If you want to be a director,
that means writing scripts.
I'll introduce you to one of my film friends.
That's it!
Where was it?
Not there.
Okay! I'll fix this up and send
it to Mina Yoshiko.
Okay! Time to go hardcore on this!
Fly high above the world, Koganei Junpei!
I'll talk business with Coppola.
Shake Spielberg's hand!
And make plans for a new
movie with George Lucas!
Yeah, I wish.
Three million!
No, two million would be okay.
Anything.
But that's...
I see. No good.
I thought so.
Who might you be?
I called you yesterday. I'm Koganei Junpei.
Please wait just a moment.
Unfortunately, Madam is currently at her villa.
I see.
Well, when she comes back,
will you give her this?
I most certainly will.
Thanks!
Yahoo!
Go!
Go, go!
What are you doing? Stop it!
Let go of me.
That hurts!
She's got a cute ass.
Stop it!
You little punk.
Get him!
Asshole!
Bastard!
Oh shit, it's the cops.
Fuck.
This ain't over!
Are you okay?
What about you?
Hey! Wake up!
Mr. Superman?
Pop Idol:
Mikami Shoko
Oh, shit!
Don't tell me I'm in someone else's room?
You pervert...
Excuse me!
Wait a minute.
I could swear this is my...
That means...
Good morning.
It's you!!
I took you home last night
when you were drunk.
You had a cracked rib, you know?
Don't tell me you...
You don't remember at all?
Not at all.
Then you don't remember what
happened between us either?
"﻿What happened between us"?
Don't tell me.
I made a huge mistake with you?
Oh, shit.
No way!
It was my first time.
If I get pregnant, what will you do?
I... I was drunk,
so I don't remember.
I was lying.
Well then.
By the way, are you friends
with Mina Yoshiko?
Why do you ask?
Well, you have her number.
I sort of met her at work.
Did you know she's married to the
big film director, Shibuya Shozo?
Shibuya Shozo?
They have a child, too, I think.
Oh, so that means she's a divorcee.
And also, the mistress of a different
film director, Nanto Daigo.
Oh, I see.
Nanto Daigo and Mina Yoshiko, huh.
Hey, wanna have lunch?
Oh, so you want to be a film director.
Guess so.
But it's not easy.
But you're reaching for your dreams.
I think that's awesome!
By the way, what's your name?
Shoko.
Mikami Shoko.
Nice to meet you, Koganei-kun.
Huh? How'd you know my name?
I saw your business card.
Oh, crap! I have a meeting!
Uh, wait...
Well, bye!
Shoko-san, huh?
She's like a good fairy.
Junpei-kun?
M-Miwa-san!
Since when have you been friends
with pop idol Mikami Shoko?
She's an idol?
Yup. Though she's in a bit
of a slump right now.
Oh? So you rescued Shoko.
Then she took me back to my apartment.
Then she spent the night, I suppose.
B-But nothing happened!
You can't prove anything anyway.
P-Please believe me!
I-I would never do anything
to anyone besides you!
Well, guess I'll believe you.
Lucky!
What? You want me to star in a movie?
Yes. Nakama Toru and I will be costarring.
Call my agency for more details.
I look forward to working with you.
Junpei.
Mina Yoshiko called.
She says she's got a producer
to introduce to you.
Hey, Junpei, stop flying solo, okay?
You're defecting to Mina Yoshiko?
I didn't want to do that at all!
And use us as a stepping stone?
That’s a really rotten thing to say!
Junpei.
You can quit Apollo Productions if you want.
Even you're talking like that?
Excuse me.
Doing what you did is a huge slap
in the face to Apollo Productions.
Yes, but I'm going to turn down Mina!
You're turning down your big chance?
Though I'm not confident it's legit yet.
They may be angry now, but they'll
send you off with smiles if you quit.
How can you say that?
I don't intend to quit Apollo Productions at all!
Don't hold back on my account.
It's pretty common in our profession.
People join the porn industry as
a stepping stone to make it big.
But I'm not like those people.
You don't need to hold back, Junpei.
You should go after your dreams.
But I love you, Miwa-san.
I'd like to keep working with you forever!
What do you think you're saying...
Miwa-san!
I'm serious.
But you're always so vague with me!
You never show me how you're feeling!
I'm not vague.
Then show me ho you really are!
Junpei-kun.
I'm gonna go talk to Mina Yoshiko.
Don't go!
You'll regret it!
I'll be fine.
You're turning it down?
Yes.
But Ujiki-chan said it was okay.
He did?
And also, I'm going to be making a film soon.
I intend on hiring on the staff
of Apollo to help me.
Are you serious?
And in exchange, I m going to do a guest
starring role in Apollo's next film.
Ujiki-chan and I go back a long ways.
He's currently involved in TV, but back
in the old days of film, he was the best.
I'm very grateful for the opportunity.
Don't thank me yet.
My boss hasn't given me permission yet.
Oh, you mean Mr. Daigo.
Yes. So you know about him?
This whole plan hinges on getting
Nanto Daigo's permission.
Come with me.
W-Wait a minute.
Are you an idiot?
You think you can really
pull in young viewers?
And I don't care if he is a veteran
director. I don't like Shibuya.
You're saying we're outdated?
Exactly.
Nanto Conzel CEO:
Nanto Daigo
Your era has passed.
Our audience is changing gradually.
But it doesn't have to be that way!
We can lure in younger viewers by
casting Makami Shoko as the star.
And for our staff, we'll hire young
and passionate people.
You still don't get it?
You no longer have the sex appeal
for attracting young viewers.
You can make such a declaration so easily?
Are you suggesting you do have the
power to arouse a young man?
I do.
Then prove it to me.
And if you convince me
you're right, I'll fund you.
Very well.
I will make this young man have an erection.
No way!
Very well.
Give it a try.
Keep your eyes on me.
Yes, ma'am.
What's wrong?
He's not aroused in the slightest!
I'm just warming up.
Be patient.
See? Well?
How's this?
Junpei-kun! What's wrong with you?
I'am deeply moved by your nakedness,
but it isn't arousing at all.
I understand.
You felt it all through your body.
That means that I can turn
your entire body on.
I think you're fooling yourself.
You just have no appeal.
You're wrong, Nanto-san!
Mina is very sexy and pretty!
She's plenty appealing!
Then why aren't you aroused?
It's just because... somethings missing.
I think something is missing.
Something...
What are you doing?
Now!
Everyone in the other
building can see you naked!
Are you trying to embarrass me?
I won't let you!
Come on!
Give them all a good long look at your body.
Hey! Stop that!
No, just stay quiet and watch.
Stop it!
Go! Go!
Hey! Can't you cut it out?
What are you doing?
Stop it! ﻿ ﻿
Sex at an open window is awesome.
He's supporting Yoshiko's entire
body weight on his erection!
What amazing power!
Stop it!
That's enough!
When you're not acting,
your natural body is beautiful.
Your rod also has tremendous power.
I lose.
I will give you 1.5 billion for the production.
Darling!
Mina-san!
Junpei-kun, thank you!
I think I need to say thank you as well.
It's been a bit sleepy lately, but it sprang
back to life from that. See?
Whoa! What a hard-on!
That's wonderful, darling!
Yoshiko!
Hurry up!
I'll leave you kids alone.
Oh, that's nice!
Oh, darling!
So we've got the money taken care of.
Now things are getting interesting!
Moron. Moron. Moron!
What the hell?
The new film will be called,
"﻿Who Saw the Tears"?
Press Conference: Who Saw the Tears?
It will star Mikami Shoko,
with Mina Yoshiko and
Takamura Toru as costars.
The director will be  Shibuya Shozo.
Apollo Productions will handle the technical
positions, and we will start in the summer.
Miwa will assist Shibuya
with the storyboarding,
while I will also be on hand
in the studio as the "Third"!
And in honor of this new
film, let's have a toast!
Cheers!
Production Chief:
Gondo
I'm surprised that Shibuya
Would lower himself to use a pop idol in his film.
It makes the veterans and true
professionals of this world cry.
How dare they say that!
Just let it slide.
We're moving up, aren't we?
We really are.
Hi, Koganei-kun.
I'm Shibuya Shozo's chief, Gondo.
And I'm Nakajima, the first assistant.
This is my first time doing this,
so I hope we can work well together.
I think suddenly being a third assistant
is a bit too much for a rookie like you.
It took me eight years.
I'm saying that even an assistant
director walks a thorny path.
Just a little advice as your superior,
but real films are different from pornos.
Well, I hope we get along.
Junpei-kun!
What's wrong? Why are you so quiet?
Can I really work in these conditions?
I don't know anything about making movies.
I don't think I can do it!
Don't worry.
I know you'll do well.
If you start sprinting at the start of
the race, you'll run out of breath.
So let them take the lead!
Miwa-san...
Let's show those jerks just what
we AV people are made of!
Be strong. You're a man, right?
Yes.
And so, "Who Saw The Tears?"
began production.
The story is about a female teacher
and her daughter, Hitomi.
Film Director:
Shibuya Shozo
It's a tale of love and hatred.
Let's do a take.
Ready? Action!﻿
Hey, cutie. Wanna play with us?
How 'bout you take off your panties?
I should have known you were like this.
No, no, not like that.
Don't you have any feelings?
Don't you have any sense of virgin shame?
But isn't Hitomi okay with taking off her panties?
No one is fully okay with taking off her panties.
Come on. One more take!
Okay.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no!
No good, cut, cut, cut, cut.
Let's take a break, everyone.
Should we go to my room?
But...
Come on. You need a break.
Just relax.
Understand?
Just pretend I'm one of the actors.
No!
Come on.
Because it was both Miwa's and Shoko's first
time experimenting with another woman,
they both showed some very sweet
and vulnerable expressions.
You're really sweet, Shoko-chan.
Don't forget how that felt.
Ready. Action!
Fucking brat!
Shit, you're just a little brat!
Who you calling "brat"!?
Cut, cut, cut, cut!
Oops. Did you see my naked crotch?
That was great, that was great! Okay! Good!
It was so much better when
you put your feelings into it!
You sure are a sweet thing.
That was great, that was great! Okay! Good!
The next day, we began filming with the scene
where Hitomi's mother is beaten
up at school by her students.
Ready. Action!
Well, time to let it all out.
Well, what do you think? You like it, right?
Stop it, please.
What are you...
You don't get it, do you?
You re just too small.
It doesn't scare me.
My what is too small?
Shit!
Mina Yoshiko decided that I, Koganei Junpei,
would replace Takamura Toru.
Oh, my!
No...
Nice!
Cut!
Oops...
What's his condition?
He had a stroke.
He's relaxing now.
We'll get another director to finish the film.
Shoko. Do your best for me until the end.
I will.
By the way, Miwa.
Yes?
Would you be the director in my place?
Me?
Because you helped me with the storyboards,
I'm sure you understand my vision
better than anyone else.
Please. Accept the position.
But...
Being a film director, whether it's for
a porno or a major motion picture,
means communicating well with your staff,
getting the best performances
out of your actors,
and having the passion to carry it all out.
What's most important of all
is a love for the project.
You have that love, Miwa-san.
Miwa-san, please do it!
I'm asking too. Please do it!
Miwa-san!
Director Shibuya, I'll give it a try.
Thank you.
Stay calm and do it, Miwa.
I will!
Good.
Show them what an AV director is made of.
Shit!
He's ignoring me and hiring some
fucking rookie porn director!
Well, Gondo-san, she still can't
film anything without our help.
Y-You're right!
Let's just see her try!
How much power does the
director have, anyway!?
Bad news, people!
A boycott?
The cameraman and the chief are walking out.
How could they?
I'll go beg them to come back!
Please, gentlemen.
Please help us!
We need you.
No fucking way!
Gondo-san!
Why are you asking me?
Why doesn't Wakaba Miwa
face me personally? Well?
It's protocol.
It's because she doesn't follow proper
film protocol that we're ignoring her.
You fucking rookie.
Please help us.
Gondo-san, please participate.
I'm begging you.
Y-You assholes!
Do you even like movies!?
What?
You're just fucking cowards with no balls!
Junpei-kun!
You asshole...
Now you've done it.
Junpei-kun!
Fucking bastard!
Let go!
Sto...
Stop it!
Junpei, stop it.
Miwa, leave those who don't
want to help behind.
I'll take over as chief.
Director, let's get to work.
This scene is a big turning point in the film.
She's about to be raped on the vaulting horse.
But a certain teacher, her mother,
comes in just in time to rescue her.
She's just a porno director.
Actor:
Takamura Toru
She thinks she's all hot shit.
Fuck. What's supposed to be
wrong with me anyway?
Fuckers, just you watch!
I'll fuck you up!
Hey, guys, I'll let'cha in on a little secret.
Get closer.
What? You're fucking Shoko?
Shh! They'll hear you!
During the take, I'm gonna
put my real dick into her!
It's a take, people!
Ready. Action!
No! Stop it!
Don't!
No. Stop it.
Shut the fuck up.
My pan-
What are you doing?
You boys. What are you doing?
Shaddup! And stay back!
Stop this now!
Shut up!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Stop struggling!
No!
Stop-
F-Feels nice.
Oh, crap!
Wh-What the fuck?
This nice?
You fucking grandma!
Let go! Leggo my dick!
S-Stop it, bitch!
How is it?
Go, go, go!
This is the way you scare people!
Well?
You like it?
To save my beloved daughter, I'd even
become a vampire if I had to.
Mom...
Hitomi!
Mom!
Cut!
Thanks to Miwa and the staff at Apollo
Productions, we finished filming.
It will be released around New Years.
Even though Miwa took over from Shibuya
as the director, it was a big hit.
Shoko was able to climb the wall to stardom.
Everything turned out well.
Congratulations.
Well then,
it's about time for Apollo Productions to
make its first major motion picture.
With Mina Yoshiko as a supporting actress.
Thank you, everyone.
Our film was number one at
the box office on New Years.
Thanks to that, Mikami Shoko's
popularity has risen dramatically.
Hopefully we can repay Shoko with this.
The truth is, Shoko is my
daughter with Shibuya.
We divorced when she was in grade
school, so we sent her away.
So that's what it is!
Good thing nothing happened between
you two after all, Junpei-kun.
I'm going to quit acting after
this and become a producer.
I hope to work with you again in the future.
She's retiring?
What a waste!
So the shadow-helper of Apollo
Productions is Mikami Shoko, I guess.
Guess so.
And my knight in shining armor is Junpei-kun.
Just kidding!
It's so cold and refreshing!
Miwa-san, you're showing me
how you really feel!
Come on, let's race!
Miwa-san!
I'll always be with you!
What? You'll always be what?
I can be so cheesy sometimes.
Jeez! Where are you hiding?
And so...
my second adventure was also a crazy circus!
And with that, everyone... have a nice day!
asphalt kodoku no building
Asphalt, the lonely building,
tachi sukumu minareta machi
The still streets so familiar to me.
Kochi no nagare ni senaka osae
Going with it, leaning back,
ikiru no mo waruku wa nai sa
Isn't a bad way to live.
dakedo tsukuri warai no warui face.
But I don't want a face with a bad fake smile.
sugoshitakunai dake na no sa
That's not how I want to live my life.
kami naru kanene no ude o
These strong, powerful arms of mine
nawa tsukarete kondo anuite miru
Won't be bound this time as I walk forward.
ato sukoshi de
And in just a little while,
teenware to wakitai nukedaseru kedo
I'll be able to escape my false hopes.
deguchi wa nai sa
But there is no escape.
warui baby
Sorry, baby.
tori ashitake mukau
Our first steps face each other.
just a puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle.
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
Never say love
Never say love.
tsekuri warai no warui face
I don't want a face with a bad fake smile.
sogoshitakunai kara sa
That's not how I want to live my life.
puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle
risky na mama ikiteku shika nai
The only choice we have is to live with risk
genjitsu ni
And reality.
Never say
Never say...
puzzle awasu you ni
It's just like facing a puzzle.