Thank you very much for flying with us today.
The plane will ascend to 10,000 meters shortly.
I'm back, Shindo-kun.
Sorry about the long wait.
I just got the medicine just now.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Sorry for all the trouble.
Don't worry about it.
We will be arriving in about two hours.
Okay.
I ended up showing my sloppy side to Sensei...
Please fasten your seat belts and prepare for impact!
Kana-chan, I'm scared!
Mo-Momoka...
Naoki-kun...
Sensei...
Your attention please,
Due to troubles occurring in the engine,
the plane is falling towards the sea.
My last memory with Sensei... is so...
Sensei!
No!
Even though you can't...
No...
No, not there...
Shindo-kun...
Shindo-kun!
Sensei!
The plane we flew on crashed to the sea,
and sank in an instant.
I got it!
Wow! He got it with just one shot again!
Even though we haven't even caught one yet!
We've always been relying on you ever since we got here.
Holding tight onto the luggage that fell into
the sea, we finally got to this place,
but it turns out that it was...
An uninhabited island.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon net
Translation Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
A Southern Island Harem
Amazing!
No...
Geez, Momoka...
I'm sorry, Kana-chan.
Geez...
I got too excited because Naoki-kun
caught so many large fish...
It's, it's nothing...
That's not true.
With that much, we even have enough for tomorrow.
It's really true that we've been relying
all on Naoki-kun after coming here.
Thank you.
No-no... I've just been a boy scout
since I was young... so...
Naoki-kun is... hard...
Huh?
I'm sorry! This is...
It's fine...
It's a natural physiological occurrence
for boys. Don't worry.
Guys, I've prepared the fire!
Let's have lunch.
This relaxing feeling is actually really good!
But then again...
Sensei is...
When you look at it like this...
Huh?
Your boobs are amazing!
Huh? No!
Sensei...
I'm so sorry for peeping on you...
But, I... just can't hold back...
When I'm with everyone, I can't even masturbate...
Sensei's body is just too erotic!
When Sensei is naked in water just past these bushes...
I can't hold back no matter how wrong it is!
I'm sorry... Sensei...
I see...
Naoki-kun's is surprisingly large.
Oh, don't panic.
You don't want Sensei to find out you're peeking, right?
Good.
But then again, such a naughty child you are, Naoki-kun.
Hiding and masturbating like that.
Why didn't you tell me?
Asami-san...
You can just leave these things
to me, you know, Naoki-kun.
Wait, it's dirty! I just came...
It's fine.
Thick semen... is one of my favourite foods.
Amazing...
Naoki-kun's is... getting hard...
It's getting larger...
It's so large...
And tasty!
Cumming!
I'm sorry...
It's fine. You were storing up, right?
Everyone was getting frustrated.
See?
Kana-chan's nipples... they're really hard...
No, no... don't say that.
Momoka is, too...
So stiff...
If you rub it so hard, my pussy...
It'll get hotter and hotter...
No... no!
That expression of Momoka... I love it!
Kana-chan is so mean!
Together, Kana-chan...
Yes... yes!
It's good, Momoka!
I'll cum!
Gumming!
Cumming, cumming... together!
Yes, yes!
Miyamura and Kiriyama are...
Amazing... I really do have to do it again.
It's just too much for me alone.
This... this can't be helped...
It's a physiological occurrence...
It's an instinct to maintain a species...
Under these kinds of circumstances... by instinct...
Anyone will become aroused!
Naoki-kun...
No... I'm the teacher...
I have to hold back and just masturbate...
Naoki-kun... I'm cumming!
So this is... a penis...
It's hot... and hard!
Why...
Why did it turn out like this?
It's twitching and getting harder!
Let me do it, too, Momoka!
You guys... are you really okay?
Yeah... masturbating and doing
it with a girl is good, too...
But I do have interest in actual sex...
And if you see something so hard,
it's just impossible to resist.
If you're that rough...
If you're...
I'm... going to...
It's fine... let it out like you want.
Amazing... this is...
Such an amazing amount...
From the looks of this, there's still much to enjoy.
Wh-What... What is everyone doing?
Sen-Sensei!
What, you ask?
Like you can see, we are treating our sexual desires.
See?
Naoki-kun was peeking on the Sensei he
loves, and secretly masturbating to it.
Don't you think he's a poor kid?
Or would Sensei prefer to do this instead of me?
Taking care of his urges.
Naoki-kun's urges... I...
I get it.
I'll do it.
Sen-Sensei!
This... this isn't something perverted.
That's right.
I am just helping Naoki-kun with his sexual desires.
No way...
To think that Sensei is...
Sucking on my penis...
Right now... Naoki-kun's penis...
I'm... I'm sucking on it, aren't I?
It's getting larger!
It almost won't fit...
But... more....
Deeper inside...
Naoki-kun... does it feel good?
Sensei... too... rough...
Naoki-kun...
Sensei is... I can't...
I can't hold back anymore...
It's okay, right, Naoki-kun?
Yes...
I'm putting it in...
Sensei...
Could this have been... your first?
That's right...
I've been keeping it... for the Naoki-kun I love...
Sensei!
I love Sensei, too!
Naoki-kun... amazing!
Naokl-kun’s is... getting larger and larger...
I'm so happy!
Oh... so a pussy can be spread so much...
It's so perverted...
I'm being watched...
Everyone's watching me... as I'm
having sex with my student!
I'm glad it turned out well, Naoki-kun.
Let me help you out a bit more.
Naoki-kun’s anus!
Take this to your prostate gland!
Your penis is... twitching... it's getting larger again!
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Yes, I'm...
Naoki-kun...
Just like this... inside Sensei's pussy...
I want it... I'm cumming, so...
Let out your semen... inside me!
There's so much... of Naoki-kun...
Well then, Naoki-kun.
Put it inside us, too.
There's the second round.
We've all been as well.
Be sure to be our partners, too!
Huh, but, but...
I don't really mind.
Although I am a bit jealous...
But if you always see Sensei as your favourite...
Yes!
You can violate us in any order and as much as you want.
C'mon, don't tease us.
Don't stare like that.
You've gotten so large already... I hope it'll fit inside...
Kiryama, here I go...
It's my first time, too...
So please be gentle...
Hurry...
Does it hurt?
No... It's going all the way inside...
Amazing... it's good!
Kiriyama's body is so soft, it feels good!
Me too... even though it's my first time...
Sex with Naoki-kun...
It's good!
Next, Miyamura...
May I?
Yes... but please start slowly...
I told you to slow down...
Sorry, I just can't hold back...
You stupid...
It's tight...
Miyamura's is so tight... it's just too good!
If you do it so much, I'll break!
Me too... isn't it about time...
Y-Yes!
G-Great! Naoki-kun... start moving...
C'mon, more. Shake your hips more!
Yes... Thrust at me... harder!
Great... it's great!
Rub them harder...
This isn't enough...
More, more... that's right!
Your penis... thrust it deeper inside!
It's really... that's right... it's... good...
More, more... thrust more!
Yes...
Yes!
Naoki-kun... you're even better than before!
It feels even better!
Sensei feels so good!
Deeper inside... mess me up!
Your penis feels so good...
Sensei... I'm... cumming again!
It's fine... don't spill anything...
Let it all out inside my pussy!
I can fuck you as much as I want, right, Asami-san?
I did say that... but not so...
Hurry... give it to me, too...
I just can't wait!
No...
My pussy is so soaked...
If you do that, I'll cum right away!
You're messing me up so much...
Yes... yes...
Wow... amazing!
Even though... you've let out so
much in everyone already...
Your penis is still... so hard...
Naoki-kun...
Your hot stuff... spray it all overt!
Two weeks after the accident.
We were rescued.
And since those things happened,
even after going back, we...
Hey, Naoki-kun. What are your
plans for the winter break?
Eh?
To make up for the school trip, we should
traveling abroad or something.
Seems like the conversation was going around in class.
No... I think I've had enough of planes.
So maybe I'll go skiing in the mountains
near my hometown.
Mountains, huh...
Hopefully we won't run into a snowstorm or something...
Please don't say that.
But... if that does happen...
I'll warm your body with my boobs.
Sensei...
That's right.
Skin contact is the best for warming up.
Well then, it's about time we start round two.
We've given you so much time with Sensei already,
so it's our turn next, right?
Yes...
Amazing, amazing!
I'm...
I'm cumming! Cumming!
Let it out! Let it all out inside!
The next vacation,
It's just me and Naoki-kun that are free.
This time I'll be alone with Naoki-kun for sure.
No one will get in our way.
We're going abroad!