Man, I'm beat.
It's impossible for a guy to have his
personal needs met with all this overtime.
There's not a single girl in my department either. I wish
Reika from design was my boss. That would be so hot.
How can you say that? It's not like I want to be working
so late! Some work just came up all of a sudden.
Ok... Ok...
I just called one of my junior staff members.
I think I can if he takes over for me.
I think it takes about an hour to get out
here from her place too.
You can wait a little longer! You always
get off without me. It's not fair.
I just can't right now. I'm hanging up!
I want to get laid too!
She just doesn't understand!
Oh, no, it's not what it looks like... I didn't
mean to overhear your conversation...
Please forgive me!
Hey you. Let's do it. It's boring just waiting around here.
Huh? What? R-Reika? Do... what?
Because of my stupid slutty sister I've been unsatisfied lately.
Huh? Wha!? What are you talking about?
You're done with your work an way right? What's the problem?
What? Are you telling me that you have
a problem with having sex with me?
What? You cant be serious!
Doesn't that make it even better? Doesn't it turn you
on thinking about doing it right here. It makes me wet.
Have you ever jerked off while thinking about me?
Uh, well uh... Um, y-yeah...
Really? You masturbated while thinking about me? Hahahaha!
I love how you're so honest.
Your body can't tell a lie either.
Wow, I can see your rock-hard dick
from the outside of your pants.
So, how many times did you pleasure
yourself while thinking about me?
Did you dream about having your
way with me every time you did it?
Beautiful, a dick just the way I like it.
It looks so good I want to lick it.
Wait! This is dangerous!
Why are you holding back all your pent-up desire?
Don't you want to feel good? You
should just let yourself go unleashed.
When you were jerking off you thought about
thrusting this cock deep inside me didn't you?
Maybe tonight I should have my way with you.
You never imagined that I would turn the tables
and take advantage of you, now did you?
But this isn't the time. Please, Reika.
Aaah! I never bought you would give me a blowjob!
Ohh!
Hm? You sound like you're already
about to cum. Does it feel that good?
Yeah. Reika, you're amazing!
I know. So you do get turned on when a co-worker
takes advantage of you. You really are a dirty boy.
I love this. It makes me so hot. I want to go even farther.
Ohh! I can't hold bask are longer!
You don't have to hold back. Give me all your cum.
Yeah! Hurry! Make me dirty with your hot cum!
Ohh. I'm sorry! I can't stop myself!
Ahh, I love hot cum.
You must have had lot of pent-up desire too.
Your cum is so thick, it tastes so good...
There's so much. It's overflowing.
You must have had lot of pent-up desire too.
Your cum is so thick, it tastes so good...
Now you can do the same for me right?
Whoa! Why aren't you wearing any underwear?
Because I get wet so much I have to change
underwear all the time if I do wear them.
And this way I can have sex anytime anywhere.
All a guy has to do is look at me to get me wet. One
dirty look like the one on your face and I'm soaked.
Why don't you look at me a little closer.
Hey, don't you want to do more than look?
Right now...
You can touch me all you want.
Ahhh, that's it! Mmmm, my clit feels so
good, I can't help but sway my hips.
All it took was sucking your dick to
make my clit bigger. Can you tell?
Yeah. You really have a kinky clitoris.
Ohh, if you pull the skin back like that I'll lose control!
Ahhh! It feels so good on my clit!
Use your tongue too. Make me clit even wetter.
Lick me. Make my pussy even wetter! Lick every part of my clit.
Yeah, that's it. My pussy is overflowing. I'm going
to squirt everywhere. I want to be soaked!
Yes, yes! Ohh! Having my pussy licked at work is so hot!
It feels so good my hips can't help but sway!
Hey, kiss me and play rough with my pussy.
Don't just tease me, put your fingers deep inside me!
Ahh, it feels good inside. I"m going to
overflow! My pussy is getting so wet!
Ahhh! That's it, you can be even rougher.
That's it, all the way inside me.
Aaaaah! It's making a dirty sucking sound!
It feels so good! It's driving me wild!
I can't stop myself! I'm gonna cum!
Ahhhh, I'm cumming!
Reika, you're too much.
Ohh, you really have a nice cock.
It makes me want to worry with it.
Wow! I can't believe you can do this!
You've never done this before?
No, never. Oh Reika, that feels so good!
I love your reactions. They're turning me on.
Reika! I'm about to cum again!
No, you can't cum yet!
I can't help it! I'm gonna blow!
Then how about if I do this?
Wow, you can suck me off too!
It's so hard. I love your cock.
It's ok, shower me with all your cum!
Ooooh, it's so warm. It smells like sex. Cum is so sexy.
Fill my mouth with all your cum!!
Mmm, it's so good. I love your thick hot cum.
Okay, it's about time for you to let me have some fun.
About time? I think you've been
enjoying yourself all along.
I've been wet all this time.
Look at my pussy with those dirty eyes.
Yeah, that's it. I love it. Look even closer.
Oh, I can't wait any longer!
Oooooh! I can feel your hand cock. It's amazing.
You're going to give it to my pussy as hard as
you can right? I can't resist it any longer.
Well, your want to be inside me right?
Yeah, I want you so bad. I want to give it
to you right now! Let me give it to you!
Heh-heh. You're so cute. Is that what you say to all the girls?
Reika, don't be such a cock tease!
You really are a cute one. I can't resist you
anymore. Let me feel you deep inside.
Ooh, that's it. I can feel you all the way inside!
It feels incredible when you come up from below.
Your cock puts me in ecstasy. How does it feel inside me?
Oh Reika, you feel so amazing. You're so hot and tight.
Oooh. Ohh. Your cock makes me wild! It feels so good.
It's so hard. I can feel you hitting my womb! It feels incredible!
Reika, I can't control myself any longer!
I'm gonna cum! It feels too good!
It's fine, don't pull out I want you to cum
inside me! Fill my pussy with all your cum!
Fill me up with loads of cum!
Give me that hot thick cum right now!
I can't hold back! I'm sorry! I'm cumming!
Yes! Give it to me! Give me all that cum right now!!
Ohhhhh, I can feel it inside me. I'm overflowing with cum.
You squirted so much inside me, it was incredible!
Ohh, it drives me wild when my pussy is wet and full of cum.
Give it to me even more. I need more.
Yeah, give it to my horny pussy. Harder!
Ohhhhh, wow, you're still so hard! Your cock is amazing!!
Ohhh, having sex at work is so wrong! It makes me so horny!
Ooooooh, you're thrusting so deep. I can feel you
banging at my womb and it's making me crazy!
Ohh oooh, I love it! I'm about to orgasm!
Aaah, I'm about to cum again!
That's ok, get it all out. This time squirt sum all over my pussy!
Aaaaaah, your cum feels so good! I'm cumming
too!! Make me dirty with your cum!!!
Wow, it's so warm. It feels wonderful to
be covered, inside and out with cum.
Mmm, you're not done yet. I haven't had
enough. I want you to give it to me harder.
Ride me rough from the back.
Give it to me rougher than you ever have before!
That's it, keep hitting my womb
with your dick. It drives me wild!
Yes! Make me your sex toy!! Stretch me apart!
Ahhh! I love big cocks! My pussy is
tingling from taking your huge cock.
I don't ever want you to stop! Just keep filling me full of cum!
Aaaaaah! This looks so dirty. My pussy is dripping all over!!
Yeah, look at me! Give me a dirty look
as you give me that big cock of yours!
Look at how much I want it!
Oooh-aaah-aah-ahhh! Do you...
want to... cum inside me this time?
Yes. Please let me cum inside you Reika!
Ahhhh! Fine! Cum inside me! Ahh, I'm
getting screwed by a subordinate!
My pussy is covered in cum. It feels
so good. I love big cocks inside me!
Ohhhh! Yes! Me too! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumminnnng!!
No! Not there!!!
What's wrong? Doesn't it feel good?
Oooh... Not there... It's just too much for me...
Nooo!!!
Aaaaah! I came! Anal makes me lose control.
I just can't take that much of it.
Wow, you're really sensitive. Now I can return the favor to you.
Let me have a rest. I... really... can't... take it.
Aaaaaaaaaaaah. No! I'm gonna cum!
That's driving me wild! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!!
But you like it in the ass don't you?
Ahh-aaahh! Yes! I love it!
So you get off on anal sex? Reika, you're such a dirty girl.
Don't make me embarrassed, it makes me even hotter!
Then you want me to stop?
No. No. I want you to screw my ass hard!
I'm a dirty girl, so I need you to hit my ass hard!
No problem!
Aaaah! Ohhhh! Wow! I can feel each stroke
all the way from my ass to my womb!
Oh yeah. Ohhh. I'm in ecstasy now!
I'm about to cum in your ass!
Ohhh. Yes. Shoot loads of cum in my ass!!!
Oh wow! Oh wow! I'm about to orgasm in
my pussy and my ass at the same time!
I'm cumminnng! I'm cumming! Oh my God I'm
cumming! Aaaaaaah!! I'm cumming everywhere!!
Ahhh, sometimes it's good to be stuck at work late.
What are you talking about? Don't you
still have more work to do Reika?
Oh, speaking of that, the kid I called is late. I'd like
him to take over for me soon so I can go home too.
Well if you don't mind I think I'll head home first.
Hey, why don't you wait just a bit and some home with me.
What?
I think you have a nice body, and we're good for
each other, so I'd like you to meet my big sister.
Big sister?
Yeah, she's such a slut she makes me look like a nun.
Let's pick up where we left off with a
threesome tonight and have even more fun.
Uh, I don't know if I have anything more left in me...
Big sister Halka.
It doesn't end at night...
I told you not to give it to me in the ass!
But it felt good didn't it?
Don't be stupid! I don't like it because it makes me lose control!
Haha, sorry.
I still have work left and now I'm totally exhausted.
I'll have to take it out on the kid who's
replacing me. I'll really lay into him.
(You're... seriously going to keep going?)
Okay, I'll be leaving first then...
Oh, it's you. You're from design right... Oh, I get
it, you're the one Reika's been waiting for.
Be careful with her, she's really pissed.
I'm a little tired... so I... fell asleep in the elevator.
WHAT? IN THE ELEVATOR!?
Why? You do look pretty tired though...
W-well, good luck. Later.
All right. Have a good night.
(Oh, so he's the one who's going
to get it from Reika. Poor guy...)
Man, overtime here really does get tiring.
And all that sex doesn't help either.
Wha? Reika?
Did you just get off?
Софтсаб, ретайминг – торрент иваниваныч
It doesn't end at night...