What a piece of cake!
What a pathetic planet this is.
Their so called ultimate weapons are pitiful.
Now then, we just have to destroy their
headquarters, and victory will be ours!
Giga Gillum!?
Sorry you think this planet is pathetic,
but you're going to lose to us.
I'm scared!
Destroyed in an instant? Impossible!
Nobody said anything about this planet being so strong!
You're the last one standing.
Will you not surrender?
Remaining battle capability at 32.8%.
Fool! You think you can hide? We will
find you, and we will eliminate you!
We've located the enemy commander.
War Maiden Troupe: Blade Briders, deploy!
Show the world what you can do!
I don't care who you think you
are, Blade Briders or whatever.
No one can survive my super-destruction beam!
Too slow!
Burst Laser!
Go, Kumataro!
You're hurt.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Even if you think so, get yourself checked at the infirmary.
Is that an order?
It's an order.
Don't make me worry so much.
I won't.
War Maiden Troupe:
Blade Briders.
Both the Redians and the Caramelians have failed.
So I'm up next, huh?
I would like to say that is the case. However,
it seems there are rebels hiding on Earth.
What's up with that?
You better take care of them.
Shall we exterminate them?
I don't care, as long as you don't get in my way.
You're not planning to, are you?
It seems they are intelligent enough to
know not to make an enemy of us.
That's all I needed to know.
I might be able to get the assistance of the Gyozians, too.
Get it done quick, alright? I need to use them next.
I don't mind.
We're married, aren't we?
Yeah... how'd that happen?
Jeez, what are you thinking, Ryuusei-san?
Can't be helped. I'm a bit disappointed
about my life decisions.
I'm happy.
After that incident, nothing happened so I thought
maybe you only saved me because you had to.
You think things would be how they are
now if it was just because I had to?
Don't! It's embarrassing! Turn the lights on.
No!
Does it hurt?
I'm fine. Do me as you like.
Then...
I'm not sure on how to do it well, though...
Like this?
Yeah, just like that.
Ryuusei-san, if you do that, I'll...
Your breasts aren't moving.
I know...
Honoka...
It's in so deep!
Well, well. I thought I'd check up on her
because her body temperature suddenly
shot up, but this is the reason?
This is splendid.
Do more of these perverted things!
Ryuusei's...
His thing is...
Inside... Honoka...
Ryuusei-san, I'm going to...
Yeah, me too.
Ryuusei...
It has been nearly a year since the
Human Defense Task Force began
repelling extraterrestrial invaders.
Areas around the world that were affected
have begun reconstruction...
It's only been a year, huh?
Only!? You mean "already"!
Natsumi-san?
Nothing's changed in a year.
Why aren't we deployed more often?
That's a problem with our effective range.
Our effective battle capacity is within 40 km of this base.
The wormholes that the enemy uses to invade
are far and out of our combat range.
They're appearing where we can't get them.
It's a war of attrition.
Then should we not figure out ways
to deal with them besides fighting?
Are you saying we should try to talk to them?
Depending on the situation...
No way that's happening.
Have you already forgotten what happened a year ago?
Either win, or lose. We don't have any other options.
Sorry...
I'm sorry. I haven't had the time to
get flowers or wash the grave.
But, if I remember right, you don't like
chrysanthemums do you, Riruka.
That would make mom and dad so much happier.
But in the language of flowers,
doesn't a chrysanthemum symbolize heart break?
Huh? But...
It'll be fine.
That said, we'll have a bouquet of chrysanthemums, please!
Sheesh, Riruka.
That's what I was thinking at the time, but...
They symbolize good things too. Trust,
a noble heart,
and even love.
I was wrong for hating them so much.
Riruka, why won't you complain more?
Don't leave me alone!
I'm going to end up hating myself
for not being able to save you.
If only I had this power back then, I...
They're here. The mechanized weapons,
Apharos and the NK Gidogabucha!
They're so cool!
Our Briders will make quick work of them.
What happened to Natsumi-kun?
I haven't seen her since this afternoon.
This is bad! Natsumi-san isn't in the base!
What?!
From the readings, she's approximately 50 km away.
She's at Tanizawa Cemetery!
This is the day that Natsumi's little sister died, isn't it?
The one who died a year ago?
What do you mean she's 50 km away?
That's within the Kuugen Kafuka's boundaries.
What!?
Captain.
It'll be tough not having you on the front lines,
but you need to get her back here.
By himself?! It's too dangerous!
It'll be fine.
Even if most people can't fight outside
our base's range, he can.
You'll all just be dead weight to him.
I'm useless...
You all have the important duty
of eliminating the enemy here.
Yes!
I need to get back soon.
I'm sure they've already noticed.
I wonder if they're angry?
Well, whatever. That's fine.
Riruka, your big sister is going back to get scolded, okay?
If this was a year ago, I'd be dead.
I have to get within the base's range, otherwise...
Where do you think you're going?
It's pointless. You're going to be killed, right here.
Who'd die to you?
I won't die until I get revenge for my sister!
How comical.
Don't laugh, you monster.
None of your kind have the right to.
Monster?
Know your place.
Fine. Just die!
Looks like I made it in time.
Ryuusei? Why?
Oh? You're not bad.
But don't think you can beat me in just numbers.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Stand back.
Stand back? You're being reckless!
We have to think of how to get away.
I have no intention of retreating.
Ryuusei...
Awaken, my blade!
Corporal War Ultimate Technique:
Limit Release
Limit release!
No way!
You're kidding!
Limit release:
A technique that allows the user to
increase his power by sixty times.
It is said that this technique has the
power to split warships in two.
However, the price to pay for grossly
surpassing one's limits isn't cheap.
A proportionate amount of stress is placed
on the user's body as a result.
Is this guy really a human?
Are you okay, Natsumi?
Yeah, I'm fine.
R-Ryuusei?
Ryuusei, are you okay?
Sorry. The stress from using that ability
has taken a toll on my body.
You're an idiot for pushing yourself so hard just to save me.
It's a cheap price to pay if it means I can save you.
What are you acting so cool for?
You're all beaten up.
Even if you saved me, I'm not happy at all.
What? Why did you laugh?
I just thought, you're acting like yourself again.
Sh-Shut up, stupid!
– Sayoko-san!
– Sayoko!
Gidogabucha!!
We... made it.
How dare you!!
Shit!!
I'm counting on you, Kumataro!
Sayoko-san!
Enemy reinforcements?
I can't hold out much longer!
Stop!!
She's strong.
What?
Looks like she'll take them on for us.
All of you, take this chance and help Sayoko!
Sayoko-chan!                   Sayoko!                          Sayoko!
Sayoko... Sorry!
I can't...!
Now's our chance!
Achemy Impact!
This is the end.
For our planet's future!!
Natsumi-san!!
Sorry.
I put you guys in danger because I went off on my own.
You said it.
When we get back, you're getting punished.
Uh, um, you had your reasons though, didn't you?
For now, lets head back to the base.
Yeah, let's go back.
Back to our home.
"Our?"
Thanks for your help. Appreciate it.
This was merely punishment for those who broke the rules.
Who are you?
I'm Fine.
I'm your enemy.
– Ryuusei-san!
– Ryuusei!
So after that, I...
Riruka... Ryuusei...
Ryuusei? Thank goodness, I thought you were going to die!
Sorry I made you worry.
That's my soft spot!
It's my first time, so be gentle.
Looks like you're starting to feel good.
No, your finger is...
Natsumi...
He wants to do it with me?
I'm going to have sex? With Ryuusei?
Ow... My stomach is filled with Ryuusei's dick...
It's going into my womb!
No, not there...
You're being too rough!
Does it feel good?
Ryuusei?
Cum inside me.
Take responsibility, okay?
Now you have THREE wives??
I fucking hate guys like you!
So shameless!
Are you ok with this?
Listen here!
Well I kind of already knew what I was getting
into after seeing you two with him,
I don't know who you think you are, but
in my day, people only had on wife!
so I gave him the okay.
This is exactly what I wanted.
Ryuusei, let's build a huge harem!
You guys got it tough.
Now I'm the only one not in the harem.
I don't really know how to act.
Well, in any case, now that you're
a fellow woman in the harem,
I'll call Natsumi, Nacchi from now on.
What the heck?
That's so cute!
Can I call you that too?
D-Do what you want.
Then, Nacchi!!
Yeah...
Nacchi, your, face is red.
What did you just call me?
Are you okay!?
Should we take him to the infirmary?
Riruka, your big sis found out who were important to her.
Ryuusei-san!!
I'll keep doing my best, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: bis | punk4real
encoder: punk4real
После титров перевода нет :(.