A LITTLE STINK
MAKES IT
MORE DELICIOUS
RIGHT?
Episode 03
What the hell is happening here?
Yano hasn't shown up for a week.
She hasn't disappeared or anything you know.
She's supposed to have gone back home due to an urgent matter.
She looked like she didn't want to go back though.
Sender: Yano Megumi
Igawa-kun Save me
Does she have any idea how worried I was?
In the end, she just went back home to help in a funeral ceremony.
And that message was actually meant
for her online game character.
Igawa-kun, that's cute.
It's alright.
There's no way I'd disappear on you.
I love you very much.
My body and soul are all yours.
Yano...
Conversely,
if you every try to forsake me,
I'm going to slash off your dick and mount it on a wall.
And so, I'm having this clear secretion first.
Yano, I'm about to cum!
That was a bit quicker than normal,
but it was delicious, so I'll forgive you.
Thanks, I guess.
Today, I'm going to do it for you.
Just stay put and lay down there, okay?
It's going in!
What’s wrong?
Are you okay?
It's been quite a while, I was a bit overwhelmed.
If I just rest for a bit I'll...
I'll move then.
No...
Don’t!
Wow, Yano's cumming really hard.
Yeah, I'm cumming, but that's terrible for you to say!
I'm telling you it isn't.
Your pussy, and even your asshole,
are feeling completely ecstatic.
No, I can't hold it anymore.
I'm cumming so much that my mind's going blank!
It's okay, I'm going to take good care of you.
Together, forever...
Igawa-kun, I love you.
I love you!
Amazing, it's overflowing.
Oh no, your dick is still twitching wildly inside.
I can't stop cumming.
This girl came really hard, huh?
I'm envious Megumegu, it looks like it feels so good.
Why are you two here?
Didn't you two go home already?
We thought we'd be considerate today
and leave you two alone, but...
But it felt like we were really missing out on something.
W-What do you mean?
A Pu~nish~ment!
You had all us here worried, you know.
And we just can't let you have all the fun, you know.
Okay, what shall we do first?
How about like this?
It's a high quality imported item.
Wait, I'm the one being punished?!
Oh wow.
It already came a lot, but it's still stiff.
Your dick is very delicious.
Give some to me too.
Nope.
No fair!
I'm envious.
I'm going to play with Megumegu instead.
Sensei, please pull this out.
Do you like it?
Oh look, Igawa's cum is flowing out of Megumegu's pussy.
No...
Don't shove it in so much...
It looks delicious...
Su-chan... no...
My cum...
My, Megumegu looks so cute when she cums!
And it's been a long time since we were alone together.
You say that, but you also like doing this, right?
But...
If you have something to complain about say it to him.
To me?
Because you love all of us equally, right?
Well...
Then you have to service all three of us equally, or it won't work.
And so,
from now on, you'll have to satisfy the three of us everyday, okay?
Every day, and to the three of you?!
I'm going first.
W-Wait...
My pussy feels great, right?
More than four-eyes otaku Megumi.
More than an older, cosplay-loving teacher.
I'm the only one who can really make you feel good.
Those who say arrogant things like that...
It's this hole, right?
Tada!
Here's Super Dildo!
Sensei, no way!
I was just kidding so please forgive me.
Why does she have that thing?
Here, I'll put it here like this.
No complaints.
It's going in.
No way...
Your asshole is really tight.
I'm going to remove the cuffs so move freely, okay Igawa-kun?
Sensei... no...!
I'm going to cum!
Where will you cum first? From your pussy or asshole?
From both!
I'm going to cum from both!
Good girl.
I'm cumming!
I'm happy.
I'd like to do this again some other time.
Wait, Igawa-kun?
Don't, don't!
Not my ass please!
It's not fair if you don't get your share, Su-san.
There it is, his sadist mode.
Su-san, your asshole is really tight.
Because...
Because I haven't used it yet...
Sensei, don't move.
I'm going to cum again.
Me too, my asshole is being fucked.
I'm cumming!
Hey!
What is it?
Don't just leave me here and have fun all by yourselves!
Besides, Shinobu-chan and Suzie-sensei
are now the ones getting punished!
Then what do you want me to do?
What I'm saying, is that I want to be punished too.
That's a no go.
What?
Besides, I really can't get it up anymore.
That's mean.
I'm already wet in anticipation for it, you know.
Oh, it stood up again.
How simple of you.
Igawa-kun.
Hey, don't just fuck Megumi.
Well, that's...
As an educator, I don't think that is proper.
Though, I think you already fail as an educator at this point.
No matter what happens,
it looks like I'm still your number one.
What did you say?
Well, his first time was with me.
I'm also the one who has had the most sex with him.
I'm just going to catch up from now on, you know.
And I'm after quality over quantity.
No matter, I'm still his number one.
Aw geez!
Every day?
All three of you?
Okay, I'm going to deal with all of you!
Igawa-kun, more...
Do it more, harder...
I'm cumming...
No...
Oh no...
I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum!
No., no...
Igawa-kun.
No...
Ah no...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Here? Does it feel good here?
Are you about to cum?
It's okay, just cum.
I love you.
Igawa-kun...
I love you very much.
Minister. Minister.
Prime Minister Igawa.
You seem tired sir.
Not really.
I was just remembering the old days.
The cabinet meeting is about to commence soon.
I understand, let's go then.
Also, you had a phone call from your wife earlier.
My wife?
Which wife are you referring to?
And so, the Shinsei Galactic Empire was established!
It conquered all of the territories formerly
occupied by the old empire.
No way that's possible.
A first lady, huh?
Oh, he's seems to be awake now.
Jeez, don't just leave your girls and sleep there.
It's an epic failure for you as my darling
if you sleep first before your honey.
Good morning. It's morning already, dear.
No, I wasn't sleeping, I was actually knocked unconscious.
Oh? It's getting big again.
Wait, ow!
Don't pull it!
If won't learn if it doesn't feel pain!
Hey, it's my turn next!
No!
Hey I'm going to...!