Fansub by http://shin-hentai.com *X-Death
Hey!
It's Igawa, from your class.
Hey! Yano if you're there could you come out.
Hey! Yano!
Is there something I can do for you?
Yeah~
Ya, I brought all the handouts that piled up while you were absent.
In that case, It's fine to just put them in the mailbox, so...
Hmm... While we're at it, there were some announcement that included info about next week test too.
Sorry, but could you let me intrude for just a little while?
Please give me a minute.
Come in.
Oh... It looks like you're relatively healty, doesn't it.
You'll be able to come back to school pretty soon, wont you?
Sensei and our classmates are worried you know.
Is that so...
Oh... Aura telling me to get out...
As usual, that girl doesn't want to be around people, does she...
She's shy, socially awkward and it seems like she doesn't have any friends either.
Is that so.
If she acted normally, she'd be pretty cute, wouldn't she.
Though If possible, I wouldn't mind if she talked a little more...
It'd be a bad idea to stay long, so I'm going to head home, Okay.
But before that, would you mind if I used your Bathroom?
Here?
Not that room...!!
T-This is...
W-What...!!
What is THISSSSSSSSSSSS!?
Um... This is not what you think!!
AWESOME!!
Are these DVDs of the entire Tiger Series in order!?
And these are the Green Barrel figures...
aren't they the shop limited edition ones!?
U-um, Igawa-kun, do you know a lot about these sort of things...?
Yeah~
Wouldn't it be kinda cool if you let me talk with you about Anime and Manga?
By the way, did you watch yesterday's Tiger Sheet?
I Did watch it, it was amazing!!
Even though yesterday the Character Disgner Hoshino-san made sure as Director that it was well animated.
More than that, the Animation of the fight scene where he told them to have it at the perspective had the quality of an average movie production, It was trully devine...
Ooh... that Yano is getting excited!!
And after that the fore-shadowing that the main character Shin Hiyama and Rihiro from the rival Red Star were actually brothers was unbelievably MOE~
Ooh... I... What should I do...
Right... Shin Hiyama with this... isn't it!?
I see...
So this is Yano's real face.
Ah... Sorry...! I... for some reason I'm getting all worked up by myself...
I'm embarrassed.
No, actually I don't know a lot about the production,
so if you don't mind, let me hear more about it.
She's a lot cuter than I thought, Isn't she.
Eh, It's already this late?
I'm sorry, even though you're still recovering, I'm staying for so long...
Um... If it's alright, can't we talk for a little while longer...?
I don't mind but ...you're fine not resting?
Eh?
Ah... that's not a problem.
Well then... I'm gonna go start making some tea okay?
Okay~ Thank you.
Since a little while ago, something's been bothering me.... that's a sketchbook, Isn't it.
By some chance, could she be drawing pictures...?
As expected, It'd be awkward if I just looked at it without asking...
But, maybe If I just take a little peek.
DON'T!!
These are fellow male "YAOI" characters?
Don't~
Ooh... is this him putting it in? ne~ ne~ are they connected?
By the way, which hole is this?
The Yaoi hole...
He saw it...!
I've made him despise me... ABSOLUTELY...!!
These are amazing Yano!!
Huh!?
No, I'm serious, I'm a little amazed.
Even though I also love anime and whatnot too, I can't draw pictures at all.
So I really respect a person who can draw.
You're lying... that's...!!
Not going to school and drawing pictures like these...
You must think I'm a disgusting female OTAKU...!!
Nope, not at all.
Ah! I apologize for stealing a look.
I'm verry sorry.
Huh... but you know even though I don't think this is something that's embarrassing enough to hide...
Everyone gets wild ideas, It'd be strange if they didn't, right?
Don't men think about Erotic things 24 hours a day?
Forget about if it's Erotic or Yaoi.
Being good at expressing images in your head with pictures...
is an amazing ability, right.
Th-Thank you very much...
Wait a minute... you said you weren't going to school because you were drawing?
Ah!
You weren't absent because you were sick!?
Actually... that is...
After I started drawing, I fell into a trance....
That's certainly a kind of illness.
In any case, draw porn in moderation.
Still, when I look at it again, it sure is awfully funny, this.
Is it strange... As I thought...
Ah... that's not what I meant, the shape...
I guess you could say it's weird.
The S-H-A-P-E...?
Look... this... the shape of the guy's thing...
The real thing doesn't taper off to a point like this... and isn't relatively grotesque?
But.. that's because I've never had the chance to see one...
So I'm just drawing from my Imagination.
Yo~ Yo~ Yano-kun~
Were you thinking about nothing but dicks while you weren't going to school?
Jeez!! You're so mean, Igawa-kun!!
Well then, how about I show you mine for reference?
Just kidding.
Nah, I'm just joking...
What's with those gleaming eyes!
This isn't the kind of thing you randomly show to others...
If it were you Yano, you wouldn't want to show me, right?
Well then... How about I show you.
Wait... Yano!?
W-Wait...
Now then!!
What the hell do you mean "Now then"!?
It's fine, put your clothes back on!!
I've already exposed everything... I'm literally naked.
I've already got nothing to be afraid of!
Besides... Who exactly was it that decided to look at my SKETCHBOOK without asking?
Is an OTAKU who's become defiant scary...?
Here... See.
It's different from Manga, It's not very good looking, right?
Amazing...
It's twitching and pulsing, It almost looks as if it's alive...
That's because it's alive!!
It's so masculine... and strong...
But the tip has a pink color, and it's so soft and cute...
How should I say it... It's LOVELY~
W-Wai... Yan!?
A-ah... Yano...!
S-Stop, I'm gonna... cum~
I drank it... Igawa-kun's cum...
Yano... Why...
W-What's wrong Yano...?
Are you... Okay...?
No...! Don't touch me...!!
You... You're not cumming by any chance, are you?
Y-You're wrong! There's no way that sort of...
Open your legs for a minute.
Don't...!!
N-No... Don't...!
Really, You can't just mess around with a person's thing and expect that to be it, right... So!
Don't...!!
Yano... You're getting all sticky...?
Amazing~
Don't...! Don't touch that...
I-It... It's filthy...
No... It's Beautiful.
N-No... S-Stop...
I-I'm going...
Um, Yano... I know it was bad for it to be a place stepped in memories but...
Aaah!! Even though this book is already out of print!!
You're awful Igawa-kun!!
I'm awful... You reap what you sow, right!?
What!?
Normally in this situation shouldn't you be drinking it for me!?
No... I... That sort of thing is a little abnormal...
Didn't I drink yours Igawa-kun!?
Jeez~ I don't care anymore...
Instead... If you do even more for me, I'll forgive you...
You really are... way too Erotic...
That's...
T-The whole thing went in...
Yano...?
You... Even though all I did was put it in...
Aren't you cumming a little bit too much...
With this, aren't you going beyond Erotic into becoming Indecent?
You're Wro... You're Wrong...!
You were doing nothing but Masturbating while you weren't going to school, weren't you...?
I wasn't...! That sort of...
If you're going to lie, then maybe I'll just stop?
No... D-Don't...
I have been doing it... Everyday, so many times...
I look at Doujinshi... and play with my... Clitoris with my fingers...
And imagine... Penises...
Yano, you really love Dicks don't you.
I love them... I... Love... Penises...
Yano... I'm already gonna!!
Please Cum...
In the deepest part of my Pussy~
Do it~ Do it~
It's leaking out~
Your cum... is leaking out~
As I thought... Igawa-kun, you are mean!
Cruelly calling a person Erotic and a Pervert and Indecent...
Even though you have a look of a "Bottom"!
A "Bottom"...
You're a terrible Sadist!!
Well, If you say so, then Yano, you're a...
"Indecent Masochist Girl"
or something like that.
That's... well I... Don't deny it, but...
She's not denying it!?
But... It's thanks to Igawa-kun.
Thanks to you, from here on... I can...
I can draw more... more realistic Penises!!
That's it!?