My dear prince, Emilio...
For him to be with that barbaric woman...
Why was it not me?
The prideful princess knight, Henrietta.
Use your mouth.
Who would suck the dick of some mountain thief?
I hope you're not forgetting that this is a challenge.
The one who makes us cum first is the winner.
In other words, it's a contest to see who is better at satisfying men.
It's too big, I can't take it in.
I feel like my chin's about to be dislocated.
But compared to this...
my prince's dick looks so adorable.
I can't reach it, it's just too small.
I'm sorry for being an unsuitable partner.
Watch your words, Helga!
I just said the truth, it can't be done.
That dick of the bandit group boss you're sucking is a lot better.
I shall not accept such words of humiliation toward my prince!
Suck it already.
It doesn't feel good at all.
Suck it harder, put some effort into it!
What a nice expression for a blowjob.
You look like some wild boar with all that hard sucking.
This is amazing, Helga-san.
It feels like your breasts are eating my dick.
It's all right, prince.
Just let yourself go.
The prince has such an ecstatic expression.
My dear...
No slacking!
That won't do at all.
You shitty princess knight!
We're going to go all the way.
Prepare yourself.
Okay.
It's sucking me really hard!
It feels like it's going to be pulled out and sucked into her mouth!
Are you okay getting left behind like this, my princess knight?
Even if you're of higher rank, you're still falling behind as a woman.
Helga-san, please do it with your breasts before it ends!
I'm cumming!
Emilio...
My name is Henrietta.
The eldest daughter of the royal family.
It is the tradition of this country to appoint princesses as knights
in order protect the kingdom?
I vowed to protect my younger brother, Emilio, until the very end.
But the peaceful days soon came to an end.
Forces opposing the kingdom soon converged.
The citizens fell into chaos, and the entire country fell.
The one who saved us from utter annihilation,
was a female warrior named Helga.
However, in the end, we fell into the hands
of a team of mountain bandits.
We were captured and imprisoned,
and made to pleasure these swine.
The one who made her partner cum faster
was the female warrior. *oink*
So she wins. *oink*
It seems the female warrior has the better worth as a woman.
Your title as a princess knight is nothing but a name.
You can't even satisfy a single man, how pathetic.
Hey.
Don't touch my body!
Let me go!
She really looks like a pig now!
Boss, why don't we make her wear this too!
That's right.
Even if she's a swine, she's still a female.
We have to at least make her look stylish.
It suits her! *oink*
Henrietta-chan, the female swine.
Alright, do her.
Stop!
Don't just touch me like that.
You bunch of swine!
I really wanted to fondle her breasts hard. *oink*
It feels even softer than I imagined. *oink*
They're going to fall apart if you fondle them too hard.
We're going to shape them any way we want to. *oink*
This is amazing. *oink*
Her nipples stretch really long. *oink*
Hey, stop pulling so hard.
They're not just some toys.
Something's leaking out. *oink*
She's lactating! *oink*
It means she's getting aroused from this. *oink*
Not love juices, but milk?
What a perverted princess knight.
You insolent...!
Take that back!
I'm not really threatened by some bitch with
her nose clipped that wears pig ears.
It's starting to leak out more. *oink*
What a waste. *oink*
Let's all have a taste. *oink*
No, stop!
Stop sucking them...
It's coming out.
My milk's coming out!
It feels good...
I'm cumming while secreting milk!
Cumming while lactating,
it seems you really have the potential to become a bitch.
Silence, I am the prestigious princess knight of my kingdom.
Not some bitch.
It seems you really can satisfy men after all, my princess knight.
I didn't even break a sweat!
Then clean everything up for me.
Clean?
We want you to clean every last drop of cum in our dicks. *oink*
Stop!
Stop, that part of mine is delicate.
There's someone I want to give my virginity to!
It's tight.
It's going to get ripped apart.
Clean it up well with your ass.
My ass isn't for cleaning your cum!
No way... it feels... good....?
I can't believe this.
I told you that you have the potential to become a bitch.
It feels, it feels so good!
Yeah, just go crazy with your first time having anal sex!
I'm going to cum anally.
I'm going to cum while getting cummed inside my ass!
I'm having cum poured inside!
I'm getting cummed in my ass.
And I'm cumming with it!
She really did come.
I did protect your chastity, though.
We survived that somehow.
What's wrong?
Well, I just thought that angels are still to
be found even in the worst of places.
It's nothing.
You're also tired after today, right?
We're sleeping.
Good night.
Your nipples are hard, and it feels good, Helga.
Your breasts also feel very tender, Hentrietta.
I'm going to 'drown' in them.
These big breasts feel good.
They're warm and are enveloping me.
These two...
Are nothing but big breasted swine bitches.
Ain't that right, my prince?
Oh, Emilio...
Don't look at me like that.
This is a tribulation given by the gods.
We only have to endure it until the end, Emilio.
My ass!
My butt!
This feels good.
I love how our breasts rub together as we get fucked in the ass.
It's coming.
Something's coming out from my breasts!
Me too, I'm about to lactate!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out, it's coming out,
it's coming out!
You two just came while squirting milk all over the place.
It seems there's no turning back for these two now.
My dear Emilio,
we're going to get out of this swine den someday,
and start to rebuild our country.
I promise.
I believe you.
No matter how much these bandits harm you,
my heart shall never waver in your favor.
Emilio.
Would that be alright, Helga?
I know, my prince.
Emilio wasn't talking to me!
What's going on?
Has his heart been stolen by this lowly woman?
His pure, innocent heart?
This cannot be.
Something's wrong.
My prince, would you be so kind as to rape that princess knight?
Henri-neesama is my sister!
Are you out of your mind?
She's now a sex swine.
Soiled by the love juices of lust.
This is an act of mercy.
Become her first.
Give it to me, Emilio.
Nee-sama?
If they're just going to take my purity anyway,
then at least, I want you to be...
But...
I beg of you, Emilio!
Listen to my first and final plea.
If it means salvation for your heart, then...
I shall take Henrietta-neesama's, my sister's virginity!
Thank you, my dear Emilio.
Just wait.
Who said anything about fucking her pussy?
You'll be fucking...
This.
That's not possible!
It's not where you impregnate a woman!
Not doing it, eh?
It can't be helped then.
Then we'll stop this forbidden lovey dovey sex right here.
Wait, Emilio, I'm alright with this.
Henri-neesama.
Now, hurry!
Nee-sama, forgive me!
That just won't do.
It won't fit no matter how small your dick is, my prince!
It's in.
Emilio's dick is now inside...
Her nipples can really take his dick in!
Congratulations! *oink*
You're now one with your brother.
Come on keep moving, you sibling swines!
Remember this!
I will never forget how you pushed us into doing this!
Shut up!
Just get on with the show. *oink*
You said it. *oink*
Move faster. *oink*
Your dick feels good.
It's coming out.
My milk's about to squirt.
It feels good!
It feels good when my milk comes out...
My nipples are being violated by Emilio's dick.
And I came while squirting my milk.
I'm cumming!
How does it feel to be changed by your brother's dick?
Shut up!
It's something you'll never be able to experience.
I see.
Then at least teach me how to do it properly.
No, no, no, it can't...!
That big thing won't fit it!
It won't fit!
Just stay put!
Keep your breasts as they are!
No!
This is amazing!
It's wrapping my dick very differently!
And it's so soft!
Breasts are not supposed to be fucked!
I'm literally going to break down!
I won't be able to raise a child anymore.
Wh-What is it?
Wait... me too...?
Stop, I said stop!
*oink* We can also insert it. *oink*
Hey, that's just not possible.
Don't, you can't add any more!
You just can't!
It feels so warm, and the wrapping sensation is really nice. *oink*
Feels like we're being squeezed really softly. *oink*
I think I'm starting to like this.
My breasts are also getting fondled at the same time.
It feels good.
Nee-sama, if you fondle your breasts any harder,
I'll also feel it in my dick, and cum!
Just cum.
I'll take your cum inside of me.
Nee-san, I'm going to cum!
Me too, I'm cumming too.
Take it all!
It’s seeping inside.
Their cum is seeping inside my breasts!
My breasts felt it so much that they squirted milk again.
I'm squirting milk too.
And it feels really good!
I'm cumming while squirting milk.
It's squirting out!
I'm cumming while squirting milk too!
My dear Emilio...
Give me more of your cum.
Pour all of your cum into me.
How cute.
You're like an infant.
That's not true.
I'm already an adult.
You're an adult alright, but you're still breastfeeding.
That's because your breasts taste really good, Helga-san.
I'm embarrassed, but I'm also glad, prince.
Can I drink some more?
Of course.
My milk is all for you to drink, my prince.
Helga-san, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Just cum.
Helga-san, be at my side forever.
We'll never be separated, my prince.
I was defeated?
Defeated by this barbaric woman?
I'll give you another reason to live.
Our dear princess knight.