Welcome!
Have you decided what you'd like yet?
Um... one blend, one cafe latte, and a bagel sandwich.
Okay...
Two coffees and a bagel sandwich, right?
Understood...
Excuse me!
Please wait just a moment.
M-Ma-kun.
Please let me stop this...
You're making a perverted face.
You really want to stop this?
This is embarrassing... even if only you know about it, Ma-kun.
No! Not here...
No, if this keeps up, I'll..
There sure are a lot of people here today.
It must be because of you two.
Right, Nanami?
Nanami?
Huh? Oh, Ma-kun, what are you saying? Haha.
Good afternoon, Ijuuin-kun.
It's always been my dream to go on a date with Nanami-chan.
How about it?
What do you mean, Ijuuin-kun?
I just need a pick-me-up from time to time.
We'll take care of that here won't we, Nanami?
l-Id better get this stuff tidied up!
Just stay and chat a little bit.
Oh? How sensitive of you.
Geez. Ijuuin-kun, you're such a joker...
Oh no, he's gonna notice...
He'll hear the sound...
Hmm? Nanami-chan, your face is a little red.
Do you have a cold? Maybe I should nurse you back to health.
Huh? If you did that, I think I'd get even worse.
Aww, that hurt.
Oh no, I can't take much more...
Cafe Junkie
[Translator: Ershin | Editor/QC: Raze | Timer: VGuy]
[Encode/Hardsub -> Softsub/Styling: SimpleX]
I'll give you lots... of love...
Because I'm... the one for you...
Am I making you... feel good?
With me...
Well then...
That's... embarassing...
So deep...
You don't want it?
I want Ma-kun to do this to me...
It's okay, I want you to look at me...
Only me!
Your dick...
It's filling me!
You're so perverted, Nanami.
That's... because Ma-kun...
... has made me this perverted!
No, even though I'm better...
Even though my pussy belongs only to Ma-kun...
Coming... I'm coming...!
Ma-kun, I'm gonna...
No, it's gonna leak out, oh no, oh no!
Ijuuin-san, you keep looking at Nanami even though I'm here too.
K-Kurumi-chan?
Kurumi, you're in the middle of a shift.
Y-Yes, I'm sorry.
Nanami, go check the inventory.
Why... even though I said not to, that Ma-kun...
He's so pushy. Up until now he wasn't listening to me at all.
Ah, it's all soaked...
My favorite panties...
Huh? Did you say something, Kurumi?
N-Nothing, Nanami-chan.
Should I help too?
That's alright, today's my turn. Take it easy, okay?
With Ma-kun...
Oh no, Nanami-chan's gonna find out!
I want to see you so I've decided to come home tomorrow. ♥ I'll be sure to tell you my feelings at that time. I should show up around 8pm so look forward to it, 'kay?
E-mail Draft
Ma-kun
Send
Select
Func
Back
So look forward to... it.
Send
Connecting
Sending
I sent it...
Ahh, now I've done it.
But, it was so sudden.
Kaede-san, I like... you.
Ma-kun... umm...
It's okay not to answer right now, but I'd like you to seriously consider it.
Sheesh. I had originally planned to call about the job,
but I ended up sending that mail instead.
I always thought of him as a little brother, but...
To make me realize how I really felt only after we'd been separated...
It's unfair.
No. just by thinking about him I'm already this wet...
Ohh... Ma-kun
I'm becoming so perverted... I can't stop...
Ma-kun!
Even though Nanami and Kurumi both feel the same way...
But, me too, me too!
Oh no, it felt so much better than usual...
I'll sit right here.
Hey... then I can't watch the TV, Kurumi.
Here is just fine.
Kurumi...
Once I finish this up everything will be ready, guys.
About ten more minutes.
She said about ten more minutes.
His dick, it's going inside me!
Amazing, it's filling my pussy...
Oh no, I can't stop... I'm gonna come just like this!
Ma-kun too, fill me up, please!
It's all ready!
Y-Yeah. I'll be right there.
Geez... I could totally hear the two of you.
Here's an order!
Ah, alright.
So, what were you asking?
Ma-kun! hurry up okay?
What? I didn't ask anything
About what?
Ma-kun, you're going shopping with me today, right?
Oh yeah, I said that this morning, didn't I.
Geez, don't forget it!
Also, tomorrow's a holiday so we're going out.
Ah, I get it now.
Well, looks like you two are doing fine.
Nanami... chan?
See you again, Ijuuin-kun
If you ever have a problem, I'm here for you.
So don't hold back, ok?
Thank you.
Kurumi...
Don't come yet...
Come inside me, okay?
Nanami-chan said she had errands to do, so she went back home. It's just the two of us.
Ma-kun, you're so big!
My pussy's... completely filled up!
Ma-kun, you're so rough!
It's going all the way inside me...
Ma-kun, please!
Shoot out all your thick come inside my womb, please!
No, I'm gonna...!
Ma-kun, I love you.
Such an unfaithful cock.
If you don't hold still, it'll hurt.
Such a painful face.
But I wont forgive you yet.
Just this much punishment isn't quite enough.
Squeezed.
Stroked.
Yet still hard as a rock, you pervert.
You look like you're enjoying this...
I can feel it pulsing against the soles of my feet.
So lewd...
Even though it's so hard, it's also soft...
I can feel it welling up...
Not yet, don't come just yet.
You're not allowed to come so quickly.
It's so hot, I...
Oh no, I'm so wet...
By playing with his dick, I'm really feeling it...
His dick... It's kinda cute.
Does it feel good?
But you cant come until I tell you to.
What? Even if you make that face, too bad.
I won't forgive you.
Hey! Wait, no-!
There's so much...
Ma-kun...
Don't stare so much.
Looks like my fingers made it happy again.
More...
Ma-kun...
It went in...
Ma-kun... you're my first...
No, don't move...
You're not allowed to come... this is punishment!
It's so big, it's filling me up...
Ah, no... it feels so good!
No...
It's going all the way inside...
No, this is so... embarrassing!
No, this is supposed to be your punishment, but...
I... can't...
It's... filling me up...
Now that I think about it..
Onee-chan, no fair!
W-Why are you naked?
I was...
... punishing Ma-kun.
"Punishing"?
Isn't that the complete opposite!
What's this all about?
This.
Thanks for explaining things to me.
O-Onee-chan?
You and Kurumi have both grown to be pretty cute...
... though quite perverted.
Sorry, we broke our promise not to steal from each other.
That's okay, I was kinda expecting it to happen, but...
But we still have to punish the boss a bit.
O-Onee-chan...
Don't worry.
We can count on Kurumi.
We're sisters, right?
The two of you are my adorable sisters after all.
Onee-chan...
Ahh, Masaru gets all the love...
If it weren't for you, Ijuuin-kun, I wouldn't be able to talk like this with Nanami.
Yeah, you really helped us out.
To be able to talk to Onee-chan...
The three of us, together with Ma-kun...
It's our first time doing this together, so be careful not to be too absorbed into it...
Think about his feelings!
Me too...
I don't really get what's going on but...
This is embarrassing...
I'm embarrassed too...
I mean, we are facing each other, so...
Let's just make him feel good...
You're surrounded by so much love!
I love you! x 3