Ma-kun, are you supporting it properly?
Uh, yeah...
Ma~kun!
Hey, watch it!
Hold the ladder properly, it's dangerous!
Sorry!
I'll be done in a bit, so...
Kurumi, that's dangerous you know?
Yeah, I'm sorry!
Ahh, Ma-kun, you have this perverted look on your face.
All done!
Ma-kun, Why are you staring right up my skirt?
J-Job well done?
Ugh...
Ma-kun you pervert!
Read message
Back
Menu
MSGs
To Ma-kun:
I was so surprised yesterday... but, I was happy. I actually intended to talk to you over the phone, but I got kinda nervous so... I'll just send a message.
I did say it was a part-time job, but this week my parents had to leave the house for a meeting, so while I'm doing my part-time job I wonder if I can stay at home like I always have.
Actually, dad and mom already left... Seems like they forgot about what I asked of them.
I don't mind you staying with Nanami and Kurumi, it's kinda sudden but please take care of them. m(_ _)m
I'll come back this weekend... Okay?
I'll thank you this weekend or something. As usual, please take care of the shop, okay? Just do the breaks as usual... Heh, you know what I mean, right?
Well then, we'll talk on the phone next time.
Good luck, Ma-kun ♥
Sorry for leaving all of a sudden!
But in return, you can use anything you like.
It's okay, Nanami and Kurumi are here too.
Yeah, thanks.
Ahh, if only I was there too, then we wouldn't have to...
Well, you're graduating next month right?
You'll be able to come back then.
I'm looking forward to it. Kaede-san.
Ma-kun...
As I thought, when you guys aren't here with me I'm...
Kaede-san...
Me too, when you're not here, Kaede-san it feels as if something is missing.
Right, Ma-kun. But...
I heard all you've been doing is taking advantage of the girls.
That... that's...
I learned that from Nanami's messages.
Ohh, my cute little Ma-kun is now a....
That's not true!
Kaede-san, about you, I've always L...
L-? Uh. Ma-kun?
Umm, liked your sweetness.
Hahah, what are you trying to say!
Oh well, why don't you tell me everything that's happened once I get back, okay?
G-Go easy on me...
Cafe Junkie
[Translator: KEI | Editor/QC: Raze | Timer: Bob64]
[Encode/Hardsub -> Softsub/Styling: SimpleX]
Onee-chan said?
Yeah, she said she's sorry for all the trouble she's caused..
Hmm...
So Onee-chan is coming back next month huh.
Just when I could be alone like this with Ma-kun...
Huh?
Uh, it's nothing.
Come to think of it, I wonder where Kurumi went...
I-I sent her out to pick up a few things...
She should be back soon I think.
I see, she sure is taking a while.
It's throbbing...
Hmm? What's wrong, Ma-kun?
Nothing, my hand just slipped. I'm fine, I'm fine.
Gosh, hehe.
It's that time of day when there's nothing to do, isn't it?
And there aren't many customers.
I'm so glad I get to be alone like this with you, Ma-kun.
Once Onee-chan comes back, I wonder if all of us can hang out together again.
Y-Yeah. Kaede-san is also really looking forward to it.
You must be happy Onee-chan's coming back. She's always spoiled you.
But, don't Kurumi and you also stick to me like younger sisters do?
That's true, but it's different...
Ma-kun. are you gonna come, are you gonna come?
It's okay, come, spray your thick come all over me!
Wow, Kurumi's really taking her time.
I... guess.
Well, I guess I'll take care of dinner today, so please clean up the store.
Sure.
Kurumi.
Ah. Ma-kun!
No, d-don't...
Nanami-chan's gonna hear us!
M-Ma-kun, your phone's ringing.
Huh, Kaede-san?
Sorry, I'll be back in a bit.
Ma-kun, you alright? Were you busy?
Sorry, I was in the middle of something.
Actually. I just wanted to let you know that I might be able to come back.
Really? Uh, when?
Well, the internship program gave us one week off.
I see, it's been a while.
Yup, I'm really looking forward to seeing all three of you!
As I thought, he hasn't been able to forget about her...
Oh by the way, how's your friend, Ijuuin-kun? Is he doing well?
Huh? Kaede-san, you know Ijuuin?
Didn't you introduce him to me?
He's an interesting person, left me quite an impression.
Is that so...
Ah sorry. I gotta go. I'll call again!
Ah, Kaede-san?!
Ijuuin?
No, you're so rough...
Nanami-chan is...
gonna notice...
G-Go ahead, please feel even better...
Ma-kun!
Three days ago
Ma-kun, I can't hold it in anymore.
I'm in love with you.
Kurumi...
It's okay, even if the only one you can think of is Onee-chan
Onee-chan is...
Even so, I still wanna get closer to you.
I....
It's okay if I don't come first in your heart.
Even if it's just a little...
Look at me, please!
Ma-kun. you don't have to hold back
You can do whatever you want with me.
Kurumi.
It's embarrassing, Ma-kun...
No, you're feeling up... my body...
Don't, Ma-kun, not there-!
Ahhh, it's feels good!
You're cute, Kurumi.
Ma-kun, I'm so happy! Come...
Ma-kun, Ma-kun!
You're going inside me, Ma-kun!
It's okay, just like that Ma-kun, give it all to me!
It's all in, Ma-kun!
Ma-kun, you can try moving, please feel good!
Amazing...
You're going all the way inside me!
Ma-kun, go ahead...
You're stretching my pussy, my pussy's overflowing!
You're rubbing me!
My pussy and my nipples, they feel so good, I'm gonna go crazy!
Kurumi, your pussy is squeezing me so hard...
I'm so happy I'm able to make you feel good...
Do it, do whatever you want!
Ma-kun, go ahead, fill up my womb with your sperm!
Just like this, okay?
Make my pussy overflow with your sperm, Ma-kun!
Kaede-san said she's coming back here for an internship.
I see...
You can finally see her again after so long.
You must be happy.
Kurumi, I guess I
Ma-kun, don't worry
I understand.
Kaede-san said she's coming back!
Huh? Who'd you hear that from?
I got a call from Kaede-san.
Kaede-san's such a great girl!
Hmm, so you're into Kaede-san?
I can't control where my heart takes me.
Ahh, what a bother.
I see, via the phone, huh...
Did she say anything else?
Nope, aside from that, not really...
Oh, she said she misses
Misses you?!
No, everyone.
Hey!
Watcha daydreaming about?
Ma-kun, breaktime's over!
Uwahhh!!
O-Ouch...
Sorry!
Gosh...
Hey, can I ask you something?
Are you in love with Onee-chan?
H-Hang on Ma-kun, wait!
Please don't look. Ma-kun...
No...
Ma-kun you pervert.....
Kurumi, that's so hot.
No, stop it... everything you say is weird...
Ma-kun, looks like you're turned on too.
Ma-kun, be honest with me.
You're in love with Onee-chan right?
What are you saying?
Stop pretending!
I'm summoning all my courage to ask you this right now.
So the least you can do is tell me the truth, Ma-kun!
I do indeed long for her...
But whether to call that love or not, is something I haven't quite figured out either.
R-Really...
So does that mean I still have a chance with you?
Nanami?
Ma-kun, I...
For a long time, I've always liked you...
These feelings for you won't lose, to either Onee-chan's or Kurumi's!
I'm sorry, how embarrassing...
I also... won't lose.
No, Ma-kun!
Wait a second...
You're totally overflowing.
Nanami, you're such a horny girl.
No. Ma-kun, we shouldn't do this...
I-I don't...
I've always thought you were cute, Nanami.
But if I don't embrace you, I won't be able to see how cute you really are.
N-No...
Think of the situation, Ma-kun, let's not do it right here...
Ahh, no... your tongue is... going... in!
Is this alright?
Nanami. you sure about this?
It's not like I can say no anyway.
Ah!  Ma-kun. don't be too... rough.
Ma-kun...!
It's going in!
S-Stop, it hur-! Ma-kun!
It went in...
I'm inside you, Nanami.
Ma-kun, you dummy...
But I'm glad my first time was with you, Ma-kun...
Nanami.
Your penis just throbbed, is holding back painful?
Hey, you can move, I don't mind...
It's so deep, your dick is going all the way inside!
Nanami, your pussy is wrapped around my dick...
Stop it, it's embarrassing....
Ma-kun, no...
No, Ma-kun, your dick just got bigger inside me!
It's okay, Ma-kun, fill me up inside, please...
Inside, all the way inside, shoot your sperm inside me!
I'm coming!
Ma... kun...
L-Like this?
Your pussy, it's inviting me in...
Ma-kun, don't tease me... okay?
It went in, your dick has filled up my insides!
No, Ma-kun, move a bit, come on, don't be mean...
Ahh, you're so rough...
Don't, or else... they'll hear us outside...
Don't, no.... I'm... coming, I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
Hello?
Ma-kun?
Sorry, do you have a moment right now?
Yeah, what's up?
Did something happen?
We haven't been able to properly talk recently, so...
It's kinda bothering me...
Oh, don't worry about that at all. Though...
Kaede-san, did you talk to Ijuuin over the phone?
Eh? You heard from Ijuuin?
Yeah, he knew that you're coming back.
Oh, is that so, ah..
I dialed the wrong number last time, haha...