Ayame! I love you!
I love you too!
I had a feeling the
first time I met you...
Believing in Mayumi's fortune...
I went and told her how I felt.
I'm flattered but I'm sorry.
I can't accept something like this.
I explained to her about the
dream and the fortune.
That's how Ayame and I started dating.
Ayame, that feels wonderful!
Oh, no! I'm gonna come!
I'm sorry.
Takakage, I'm so happy with you.
I love you so much.
Ayame...
Oh, yeah!
I can't believe how amazing this feels.
Ayame...
I'm gonna come.
OK.
Genshiro...
Ayame?
It can't be...
UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
CAFETERIA
So that's the story.
What do you think, Mayumi?
Are you listening, Mayumi?
After thinking about what
you said happened...
I think it's best left
between you and Ayame.
I didn't say it was with her.
It's just an example. An example...
Oh, just an example...
But more importantly...
In regards to this kind of weird stuff...
Where am I supposed to turn for help?
It was just a coincidence, right?
You think so?
No matter what happens...
it's still hard for me to hear about
your relationship with her.
After all, I was in love with you.
I'm sorry.
Ah, ha! Then you were
talking about her!
You're so see-through.
I'm please to meet you.
I'm Ayame Ikeyanagi.
Nice to meet you too.
What was that feeling earlier...
When I shook her hand?
Maiko? The water's boiling.
Would you like some help?
No, I'm fine.
She looks just like her.
Like the girl in my dream.
No! I can't even look at them.
You've been studying up on it?
Yeah. It's been bothering me.
Takakage, you believe you were a solider
named Genshiro in your past life, no?
And the Ayame in your dream
and the real Ayame look alike.
The name Ayame comes up often
in the history of that shrine.
All the way back to the Sengoku Era.
I know Genshiro will return
for me. He gave me his word.
I can't die until then.
Here...
Ayame...
Genshiro!
Genshiro! Are you alright?
Ayame... I'm...
Genshiro! Don't die! We
have to be together!
There's a legend about that shrine that...
...the family that lived there knew
the secret of immortality.
So if Ayame was blessed with
this gift of eternal life...
That means that you're now dating
your girlfriend from the past.
No!
NOO!!
I can see it now.
You told me that in the past I
was in service at a shrine...
Yes, you were. I can
see you praying.
You mean, like a shrine attendant.
Yeah, you're right. That's
exactly what you were doing.
Just like Takakage's girlfriend.
Around what era?
The Sengoku Era...
The Sengoku Era?
No, the Edo Period. No,
Meiji. Uh... Showa.
This is weird. It can't be
that you never died.
I mean I'm reading your past.
I never died?
Don't take it so seriously.
Fortune telling is not
scientific fact or anything.
That feels good!
Wow! Your pussy is so wet!
You don't have to tell me that.
Here. See for yourself.
No!
So good! Oh, Takakage!
How is it, Ayame?
Wow! I can feel your dick
deep inside me, Takakage!
deep inside me, Genshiro!
... deep inside me, Genshiro!
Amazing! I'm tingling!
Just a coincidence...
or something unnatural?
Please reconsider what you are doing.
Are you even listening to what I'm saying?
I love him.
I want to have a life with Takakage.
And I want to get old with him.
Ayame, you should not rush into this.
You have to make the right decision.
You know there is no turning
back once you have decided.
I've lived long enough.
He will accept me for whoever I am now.
Otherwise, I will stay young
and have to watch him die.
No! I can't bear to go through that.
I'm going to spend time with him and...
With him, I'm going to die.
Ayame! Stop this!
You've already made a
mistake once before.
If you make the same mistake again...
But even if you succeed this time....
...your body will not be able to handle...
... the process a second time.
You will die and turn to dust.
I'll try at the next full moon.
I can't wait any longer.
Maiko? What's the matter?
You screamed out in your sleep.
I heard it from my room.
It was nothing.
Don't say it was nothing.
Tell me. Is something bothering you?
Me or Ayame...
Who's more important to you?
Why would you ask
something so stupid?
You're my younger sister.
Ayame can't compare to you.
Brother!
Brother...
What?
Ayame is going to die tonight.
But you might still have time.
Please! Go and save her!
Maiko! What are you talking about?
Don't worry! Just go! Quickly!
I'm not sure what's going on.
But I know something odd is happening.
Please be safe, Ayame.
Ma'am, where's Ayame?
Takakage, Ayame is not here.
Please go home.
I can hear Ayame's voice.
Ma'am, she's inside, isn't she?
Takakage! Don't go in there!
Don't go any farther!
Why? What's she doing in there?
Ayame is conducting a
very sacred ceremony.
No one can enter until it is finished.
If you intrude upon it, something
terrible will happen.
Something terrible?
Total chaos...
....and death!
Ayame!
Maiko!
Please don't go in!
Ayame, I won't let you die!
The flames... went out.
Maiko?
I'm alright.
But...
Ayame?! Are you alright? Say something!
Genshiro?
Genshiro, I'm so happy that
you are a part of my life.
You mean so much to me and
I love you.
I have no regrets in life.
Ayame...
Thank you.
Ayame!
AYAME!
Hey, is Takakage still sick?
Looks that way.
Maiko too, huh?
I'm not to worried about
Takakage, but I miss her.
You wanna go see them?
Leave them alone!
They'll be fine. We'll go and
see them when they feel better.
You're right. It's nice being here alone with you.
What are you talking about?!
Maiko, how did you know Ayame
was going to die that day.
I had a dream.
A dream?
Ayame's old boyfriend was a soldier
named Genshiro in the Sengoku Era.
That was me in my dream.
Genshiro is your past life, right?
Ayame tried to save Genshiro,
by using a spell of immortality.
But she cast the spell
on herself by mistake.
That's why she was still
alive up until now.
You are the reincarnation of Genshiro...
...and she fell in love with you.
She wanted to get old with you.
That's what she was
trying to do that night.
Reverse her immortality.
But she failed.
No, she succeeded.
The truth is, she freed herself.
...so she could finally die.
Then there's no point to what she did.
If we can't be together,
her death was all for nothing.
Brother?
What's up?
You may not believe this but...
I'm the Ayame in your dream.
I'm the reincarnation of Ayame.
That's ridiculous.
We've been through some weird things but...
The same person can't live
two lives at the same time.
I don't know how it's possible...
But I was born 19 years ago as
the reincarnation of Ayame.
It's a paradox, but we shared the same
spirit between our two bodies at the same time.
But you have to consider that as time moves
forward, it can also move backwards.
Anything could happen.
I guess it's possible.
It's the truth.
There's no other explanation.
C'mon... Don't cry.
I'm sorry for saying such unbelievable things.
I believe you.
I do believe you.
That night, in my dream...
I saw Ayame and I die.
There was a full moon...
Just like that night.
Wait a minute!
If she didn't complete the
ceremony, she would have lived?
And if she had lived...
...you might have ceased to exist, Maiko?
But still, even at the
cost of your own life...
You tried your best to save her.
I knew what she was going to
do but I couldn't let her.
I didn't want to live if I...
That's why you asked me that night.
Me or Ayame...
Who's more important to you?
I didn't know what to do.
That's why I wanted you to decide...
Who was most important to you.
Maiko...
No one would believe us...
But we know we are the reincarnations
of Genshiro and Ayame.
So we'll keep the promise made
over 400 years ago.
We'll be together.
I don't think my father had this
in mind with his last request.
Maiko...
Takakage...
If you're not used to this,
we don't have to.
Brother!
Oh my god!
That feels great!
Don't hold back...
Maiko!
Maiko...
Brother, I want to be one with you.
Maiko, I'm going to put it in now.
I'm ready.
Does it hurt?
It's alright.
Do whatever you want to me.
You got it, Maiko.
How does it feel?
It feels a little weird.
But my blood is boiling!
I'm so hot I'm going to melt!
More! More! Push harder!
No! No! No! I think I'm losing my mind!
Oh, brother! I'm...
I'm gonna come too.
I think I'm gonna die!
Maiko!
Maiko, look!