Their support troops will not arrive in time.
The West really has no chance anymore.
They can surrender or die!
Those are their only two choices.
So the final battle is set for tomorrow?
Yes. Most likely. As soon
as the sun rises, we'll attack.
Ayame...
Yes?
I will not die! I'll be back.
I'll return here, where you'll be waiting.
Genshiro!
A soldier's wife should not cry.
Wife? Did you say wife?
Tonight, you and I shall
become husband and wife.
If you agree, that is.
Of course I agree.
Don't worry. I'll be gentle.
OK.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm going to become Genshiro's wife.
Genshiro!
Ayame, how is it? How does it feel?
I'm so happy that you
love me like this, Genshiro.
Wow! I can feel your dick
deep inside me, Genshiro!
So deep inside...
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm gonna come soon.
Go ahead. Do as you please.
Ayame! I love you more than anyone else.
I love you too, Genshiro.
I'm gonna come!
A dream?
My name is Takakage Takasaka.
I'm a junior in college.
Today, my little sister Maiko
starts classes at the same college.
Our parents died in an accident
six years ago.
I've become almost a parent to her.
Take care of your sister.
You're the only one she has left.
My father's last request is
something I'll never forget.
What's the matter?
Oh... It's nothing.
UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
SOCCER CLUB
BASKETBALL TEAM
MAC CLUB
DEBATE CLUB
Takakage...
Mayumi!
You made it, neighbor! Come on in.
That's Mayumi Hiragi. She lives in our
neighborhood and we grew up together.
She's nice.. but she's quite the loudmouth.
Maiko, don't bother with that.
There's lots more to see.
Oh, shut up! Let me explain this to her.
Fortune Telling? It looks interesting.
Don't be stupid.
Your sister is really cute!
Does she have a boyfriend?
Shogo?
I don't know, but she'd never
date a horndog like you.
Whatever you say...
You thinking of putting the
moves on her yourself?
Idiot! I would never even think of it!
But Shogo has good reason to think that...
Maiko is actually only my half-sister.
There is no actual blood relation.
We were brought up together
since we were young.
But I've never ever thought
of her in that way.
Brother! Come here!
Nice to meet you. My name's Tateno.
I'm a good friend of your brother.
I'm his younger sister, Maiko.
Watch out, Maiko.
You have to be careful. There are perverts
like him roaming all over campus.
That's not true! Just
because you're like that...
Don't lie! I'm as honest as
they come! You know that!
Sometimes I wonder.
SSHH! Be quiet!
I can see it now... Maiko's past life.
Really?
She served in some capacity at a shrine.
What's the matter, Maiko?
It's nothing. It's just that I had
a dream like that recently.
It surprised me.
Dream?
Your next, Takakage.
Have her read you.
Not me. I don't believe in fortune telling.
Jerk! I'm the real deal.
Why don't you go?
I've already had my fortune told before.
I was a ''kappa''.
(Legendary Japanese monster)
That's enough! Get over here!
Alright already!
You're going to fall deeply in love with
a woman who you'll meet in the next few days.
That's awesome, Takakage!
And what about his past?
A demon? A rat?
Mayumi, what about my brother's past?
Sorry.
He was a soldier during the Sengoku Era.
But he died young.
What a coincidence...
But fortune telling is just a scam.
You don't believe it, do you?
Of course not.
I just had a dream about
something similar. That's all.
But your sister had the same dream, didn't she?
Can that be coincidence?
So whose side are you on anyway?
Do you believe in fortune tellers or not?
Hey! Don't move!
You should only believe in the
good things they tell you.
She really didn't tell you
anything bad, did she?
She said you were going to fall
in love with a woman, right?
I hope it comes true.
But we already know each other...
...so it's not you.
That's too bad, eh?
Don't you have to paint?
I'm done for today.
I've had enough.
That's awesome. More! Do it more!
What a little slut, you are.
Uh-oh! Look how hard your clit is!
That's your fault, you pervert!
So are you about ready for the real thing?
I want it!
It feels so good!
That's good! You're pushing all my buttons!
Awesome!
That's great!
I'm about to come!
Come! Come!
Still not yet?
Takakage...
I've never told you how I really feel.
CAFETERIA
Excuse me...
She's really cute!
Which way is the library?
I'm new here and don't really
know my way around yet.
I'll take you over. I've got time.
Now where is it again?
I don't really use the library
so I forget where it is.
It's alright.
I'm sorry I couldn't get you there.
I really didn't want to go
to the library anyway.
I just made that up because
I wanted to talk to you.
What are you talking about?
Don't think I'm weird just because
I'd do something like this.
I've been watching you since I started here.
Takakage... I like you!
Please go out with me.
Could this be the girl from my fortune?
What's wrong, Maiko?
What are you so pissed about?
You're going out with someone you just met!
You have to meet everyone
for the first time once.
I'm not sure exactly what you mean.
Oh, I get it. Don't worry. I'll introduce you.
You can judge her for yourself.
Forget it!
What's bothering you, Maiko?
Hey guys!
Hey, Mayumi. Come on in.
Welcome.
I heard you have a new
girlfriend, Takakage.
I guess...
See? My fortune was on the money.
It was pure chance.
What? You still don't believe in it?!
So tell me... what's she like?
Is she cute?
Don't hold out on me.
What's wrong, Maiko?
Well, I thought Mayumi liked you so...
I'm just a little surprised.
What are you talking about?!
It's not like that!
Do you think I'd fall for him?
Give me a break!
Whatever you say...
I have a new girlfriend a hundred
times prettier than you.
What was that?
UNIVERSITY OF THE ARTS
OCCUPIED
Takakage's so lucky. He's dating
a cute, new freshman.
And here I am, stuck
with only older women.
Did you say something?
No. It was nothing.
Looking for a job gets me all stressed out.
Help me forget all my troubles.
You're finally hard.
You can do it now, right?
Alright.
More! More!
You're too loud!
Don't get any on my suit.
I have another interview tomorrow.
I know. So I can come
inside you, right?
That feels great!
I'm about to come.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
SAKURA NAMIKI SHOPPING CENTER
I've been at this school
for over two years...
But I never knew there was a classic
kind of place like this around here.
It's like something out of the movie ''Tora-san''.
You're right.
SAKURAGI SHRINE
A shrine?
Looks like it. Let's check it out.
SAKURAGI SHRINE
OK.
Whoa! This looks pretty old.
Yeah, it's pretty classy.
How cute!
Stop, Shiro!
I'm sorry. He's just not used to people.
As a guard dog, he's doing a good job.
I've seen her somewhere before.
Ayame!
I thought I heard the dog barking.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing to worry about. It's fine.
Ayame.
I can't hold it anymore! I'm gonna come soon.
Go ahead. Do as you please.
Ayame! I love you more than anyone else.
I love you too, Genshiro.
I'm gonna come
Huh? That same dream again.
I'm so bad...
What's come over me?
Right about now...
My brother's on a date with that new girl.
Chisato, you're lovely.
Thank you.
No! Not down there!
Don't worry. It's feels good, doesn't it?
It tickles!
You're really wet!
You're getting really turned on, Chisato!
Don't say that.
You like it like that?
Yeah. You're pretty good.
But there's no need to rush.
Enjoy it, like you would a sweet lollipop.
Like a lollipop?
Awesome! You're great with your tongue.
Oh, no! I'm gonna come!
You came a lot!
Because you're so good!
But I'm still good to go!
Then let's move to the other room.
Does that feel good?
Yeah. But it's different from
when you give me head.
You keep that up and I'm
gonna come again soon.
I'm gonna come!
Come as many times as you want.
I'm coming!
Let's keep going!
Alright. Here we go.
OK.
Feels great!
Your pussy feels so nice!
Don't say things like that!
I'm tingling! I can't feel my legs!
Not just yet.
It feels so good!
I'm about to come!
Oh, yeah! Me too. I'm in heaven!
That was refreshing.
Takakage...
There's something I have to tell you.
What? You have another
boyfriend or something?
That would be a problem.
Mayumi?!
What's going on?
I've liked you since we were kids.
But I could never tell you.
That's why I had to pretend
to be someone else.
Mayumi...
I'm sorry. I know what I did was wrong.
But my feelings for you are real!
I'm so happy to hear that. But Mayumi...
I think it's better if we stay just friends.
I've known you longer than Maiko.
I just can't see you as my girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
It's alright. I was wrong
in trying to trick you.
And you lied about my
fortune too, didn't you?
That was true! I wasn't lying
when I told you that.
To tell the truth, I see Maiko
as my rival for you.
When I found out you would
fall for someone new...
I tried to use that to my advantage.
Don't be stupid! There's nothing
between Maiko and I.
We're brother and sister.
I'm sorry.
But your fortune was true, right?
You're thinking about that girl
at the shrine, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Fortunes... Fate...
I don't believe in things like that.