Year 158, in the New Common Era,
on the continent of Synapse,
the conflict known as the 'Holy Demon Wars' has lasted for many years.
Two hundred years have passed since the first conflict,
and on the side fighting for a bright future, a single hero has appeared.
Retreat! Retreat!
Hold out, we'll soon be able to reach the ally's battlefield and relax!
The general's head is mine!
Who the hell?
Hewie!
The Hermit Dragon, Diana Section, Hewie Elzand! I change with my moods!
Just kidding!
The same, Hannah Hamilton!
Aria Gadland here.
Esmeral kumeihamilos tororuquen de gomia, astoro!
Of course! To control the specialized magic it takes myself, Cecil Forward.
Retreat!
Concentrate your forces! Let's get them all in one shot! Go!
SubDESU-H Presents
Holy Demon Wars
Chapter One
I'm glad you came back.
Thanks for taking care of Carraway.
What of it. It was just by coincidence that I passed by.
The executive branch keeps giving out these reckless orders.
To get a magical cannon with no injuries... Easier said than done.
Don't say things like that.
If we mess up this plan, our army here will suddenly change and lose its chance of winning.
To get this magical cannon, we have to make the invincible Boleblade fortress fall.
Why don't we sign a peace treaty instead of doing something so reckless?
After all, we went to the trouble of offering help to the other side.
We don't have infinite resources, either.
Hewie...
It would only make sense to sign a treaty when we have the upper-hand.
Besides, that's not something we get to decide.
I wonder if I should have become a civil official?
That useless role? Carraway, would you explain the escorting to Hewie?
Yes, sir!
Good work on defeating the fort commandant by yourself.
I just don’t like sitting still all day.
Besides, this Elran cannon or magical cannon or whatever it is, I hate it.
You have to fight whether you like it or hate it.
As firepower against the enemy, thanks to this we have a means of withstanding anything.
By the way, Julie, did you think about what I mentioned earlier?
Having dinner with you?
We eat together all the time, don't we?
Nah, nah, not with this unromantic Julie,
I mean with a Julie who's sparkling and in a frilly dress.
Impossible.
What the heck?
I've never worn clothes like that even once.
I'll make you wear them for sure!
The problem is the magical cannon.
We have to take the fort before the magical cannon is loaded.
That's not necessary.
Do you have some kind of plan or something?
I guess so.
Why don't we prepare a backup plan?
I don't particularly mind.
What will we do?
Wouldn't it be most efficient to get the cannon to shoot?
I object!
The magical cannon would be helpless,
but it would be extremely dangerous to all of our troops concentrated in the fort!
I propose that we reconsider the plan!
There's no such thing as a safe fight.
But!
Aria!
It's already been decided.
Somehow, the commander is scary today...
Always that devil-may-care attitude on the surface...
I am going to give a full report to Ducis-sama suggesting we reconsider the plan!
Hey, wait, Aria!
Come now, Hannah, let's go to the hot springs.
What? Oh... okay...
Do you disapprove?
Having accepted Hewie's plan.
Even if I were to have another chance, I want to see it fall this time!
There is no way that the might of our military will diminish from now on.
Such a thing is impossible for me!
That's the official stance, but really, I don't want to let anything dangerous happen to you.
Ducis-sama.
So good!
Carraway!
Du-cis...
It feels good, doesn't it?
Makes you really feel alive!
I wonder if Aria is okay?
Good grief... you're like a child who always takes on everyone else's worries.
What does that mean?
Do you not understand the meaning behind what Hewie plans to do?
What the commander... plans to do?
You're just not ready yet, are you?
Now, then!
Cecil, you have such a nice figure!
I'm jealous.
Oh, my, it's not something to make such a fuss about!
I'm normal, really!
Am I interrupting your studying?
Why don't you do something besides reading books and looking up at the sky once in a while?
It feels so good.
Did Ducis say something?
He said he had entrusted it to the commander.
I can tell, you're still not happy.
Aria, what do you think the art of war is?
What? Um... that is... I guess...
Using the basics of tactics, in whatever way makes the most efficient use of the army.
Bzzt! In-cor-rect!
Well then, what do you think, Commander?
In the most efficient way possible, killing both enemies and allies.
You can't mean that! I understand the enemy, but... killing allies?
You are mistaken!
Yes. I am mistaken.
War itself is an insane concept to begin with.
That's why, even little by little, I want to put an end to war.
Hypothetically, in any possible form.
Even if we lose?
I suppose so.
It would be nice if both sides could nicely shake hands with as little animosity as possible, but...
Now that several hundred years have passed, we've both gone too far to back out,
and because of that, it has become necessary to use these tactics.
That's why, Commander, instead of peace, you want to defeat Boleblade fortress...
I don't care about this mutual countries thing.
But in order for this operation to be a success,
I've been wondering if we can get by with no deaths, neither enemies nor allies.
You thought that far ahead, Commander...
I'm a complete hypocrite.
Tomorrow's maneuvers will inevitably involve immense bloodshed.
Sorry for making you listen to such a trivial conversation.
If you've got free time to read up on the arts of war,
books on the arts of romance would be much more fitting to you.
All troops, attack!
Hewie, I'm counting on you.
Right, we should get going soon, too.
Their movements are unusual.
Are they luring us out, or something else?
Argh, I can't think with their jumbled movements!
I'll go out and find out what they're doing!
Going out from the fort by yourself?
At least take one battalion with you.
Right now this is a one-on-one battle between commanders!
Gaiyaku, I don't hate the you that does things like this.
Usually people use the word 'like.' 'I like that.'
If we both survive this, I will.
Right! I'm definitely going to make you say it!
Which one of us is stronger? Push, push, push them down!
Now! Release the signal!
Attack!
An ambush?!
They're splitting up... We can't shoot the Elran cannon this way...
This should be their entire military strength.
If there are reinforcements, would annihilation be possible?
Reinforcements...
Reinforcements...?
Right, the reinforcements have come out. Cecil, it's up to you.
Ha! Those vulgar ramparts will become nothing but paper scraps in the face of my magical power.
Esmeral kumeru hamiaosu toruruquen de gomia, astoro!
Now! Charge!
I thought it would be something like this.
Annihilate them!
It's an order! Whatever it takes, take the fort!
Go!
I was just about to!
Pitiful excuse for an army! Prepare to die!
Ducis-sama!
You're not bad!
Is it okay for you to pick a fight in a place like this?
Your strength might give out.
What did you say?
P-Protect the fort at all costs!
All forces, attack!
Really, there's simply no end!
The commander and Aria have disappeared!
Commander! Commander, where are you?
You're not bad.
That's my line.
I thought you were just a wannabe hero, but you're not bad.
Why not be reasonable and surrender?
Your group has nowhere to run.
Unfortunately, I'm bad at giving up.
I've got you!
Commander!
Hewie-sama, Hewie-sama!
It ends here.
J-Julie is...
Julie!
Commander, please hang in there. Commander!
R-Report on the battle's progress.
With Ciruela-sama's reinforcements, it's a victory for our troops.
I see. Ciruela... was able to come...
Don't speak! Your wounds will open!
Persistent bastards!
They're coming from in front of us, too.
Leave it to me!
G-Gaiyaku!!
Gaiyaku!
Gaiyaku! Gaiyaku, hang in there!
J-Julie...
Gai, didn't you want to have dinner with me?
I hate people who break their promises!
I-In the end, I have one favor to ask.
What is it?
Would you have sex with me on my way to Heaven?
Really, you are ridiculous...
You're beautiful.
Don't stare at me like that, you idiot!
Ow-w-w-w.
S-Sorry!
It's nothing...
Let me make you feel more...
G-Gaiyaku!
Julie...
This should do it.
Thanks a lot.
This looks... like a hidden room?
Commander!
What is it, Aria?
I thought you were going to die, so...
I’m not that weak.
C-Commander!
Boo! Just kidding, I was faking it!
Commander, you idiot!
I...
I'm sorry. My mistake.
Commander...
Commander!
No!
If you don't like it, we can stop.
T-That is...
I don’t want to continue any further if you end up hating me.
Please...
Hm?
P-Please continue!
C-Commander!
Commander!
No... that place...
No, don't! It's dirty!
C-Commander!
I can't... can't... Commander!
Do you want it?
Are you afraid?
Just... a little...
It's okay. You'll get used to it soon.
Um... Commander...
Yes?
Is it true... that it hurts?
Hurts?
Well, I'll do my best to make sure it doesn't.
Please.
I'm entering.
Okay.
Aria. I'm going!
It'll feel good soon.
Really?
I'm... I'm... I'm cumming!
Commander, your operation was a superb success!
I would never have thought of that plan
Though the plans changed a little at the end.
Aria, Hannah, Ciruela, Cecil...
You all did a fantastic job. Thank you.
Boleblade Fortress has, after 141 years, returned to its original masters.
The time is the year 358, New Common Era, an August event.