Year 158 of the New Common Era.
On Synapse Continent, the conflict known as the Holy Demon Wars has broken out again, but...
according to legends passed down,
it is not just a conflict of demons and people.
Two hundred years have passed since war broke out, and on the side fighting for a bright future, a single hero has appeared.
This story takes place during the time of this hero and tells also of the many dead.
SubDESU-H Presents
Holy Demon Wars
Chapter Three
The victorious Ingela Army was at Eberuzado, the largest field of battle in the Holy Demon Wars, but,
due to heavy casualties, they postponed further advancement for a while.
Reinforcements from unit 8 were sent to the fortress at Arubidabu, to protect it.
I suppose this is our only choice, then.
Ducis, Hewie, just now, for a little while...
could you go along with this selfish, doddering old man?
That is all.
The number four unit on the front line will advance as they are.
The number one unit will return to Parumira.
The number seven unit will, together with the newly-formed number eight unit,
encircle Arubidabur fort's defensive outpost and assume responsibility for subjugating them.
Yes, sir.
We will faithfully carry out the imperial orders.
That is all. Do your best.
Yes, sir!
Somia.
I have great hopes for you, Somia.
All right.
Leed, your daughter has grown into a strong adult.
I will definitely keep my promise.
I will show you Somia rising above all others as a fine holy knight.
Come back alive, and let's go drinking.
Of course. Take care of yourself on the way.
Oh, yes. Watch out for the number eight unit.
There have been various dark rumors about them.
It's fine. You, too, take care of your new wife, Carraway.
Right.
What?
Ducis-sama is going?
Mm, yeah, he had imperial orders...
He's leaving tomorrow, I think.
I-I-I-I'm going to go pay him my respects! Renoir, you come with me, too!
Even so, pulling the number one unit from the front line
and leaving just the number four unit, capturing Kurikara and Estancion?
I've had it! On top of that, left together with that shady unit!
They are an established unit fighting for the same side. You shouldn't be that prejudiced.
Commander!
It’s THE number eight unit!
Number eight, the 'massacre' unit. Rumors are spreading among the commoners.
It's just a baseless rumor.
Besides, for tomorrow's operation to be a success,
we've been ordered to deal with the remnants of Luciole's garrison,
who appear to be hiding out in a small village.
First thing tomorrow morning, meet with the tactician over there.
Commander, does it feel good?
Yeah, really good.
Then, next, stand up, Commander.
That's very...
Sorry... it just felt too good...
You're delicious...
Could you make sure everything goes well with the number eight unit?
If it matters that much to you, Commander...
Thank you.
Hewie-sama.
You'll catch a cold.
The stars were just too pretty, so I accidentally...
Yeah.
Tonight's Ciruela is very pretty.
The coming military action is becoming far too unpredictable.
Even though the enemy is right before our eyes, it's as if their intentions are shrouded in fog.
The return of the number one unit's desperate effort.
If would be nice if our infiltrator behind the scenes could find something, but...
Oh, Hewie-sama, more, more, stronger!
The commander is... in me!
Ciruela...
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
No!
I'm counting on you to look after the place tomorrow.
Will I not be of use?
It's not like that.
To the extent that all other units are ordered forth, you won't take part in this operation.
Besides, I want to leave this task to the most trustworthy subordinate.
Is that bad?
It's no problem at all.
Because you have so much faith in me, I will do my absolute best.
Thank you.
Finally, huh?
The resistance was a lot more violent than we were expecting, wasn't it?
Commander! We've got trouble! Trouble!
What is it?
C-C-Cecile is...
Hey, hey, Ciruela, what's a 'secret unit'?
'Secret unit'?
I heard it mentioned over there. They said that Somia was a 'secret unit'.
A secret unit is a military tactic where someone infiltrates the enemy forces and gathers information,
assassinating important people if necessary.
It's a special unit under orders from military headquarters.
Really? That's amazing.
That's not all.
They collude with the enemy and inflict punishment on traitors as emergency measures.
But that's strange.
If you become part of a secret unit, you supposedly can't stop until you're dead.
She's a holy knight, and what's more, a commanding officer...
Move! Don't get in the way!
I refuse. What did you say these people did?
They are all victims of the war!
Hiding enemy weapons is a serious crime!
That's why we're going to sentence them here and now!
So the rumors were actually true, then.
Rumors?
Unit eight, a 'massacre' unit.
These are all traitors!
Traitors must... traitors must...
Die!
Wait!
Don't kill the commoners!
That's not in your orders!
The battle is already over!
Are you okay, Cecile?
Yeah.
It's unusual to see you so flustered.
N-Not particularly.
It's just that I didn't want to see people not involved in the war die.
Oh, so that's what you're like underneath.
Wh-What are you saying?
You have such a pretty smile, so why do you wear sunglasses?
It has nothing to do with you.
I'm going to ensure the safety of the injured commoners and then leave!
Removing me from command?
Are you dissatisfied?
Of course I am!
I was only thinking about punishing traitors!
And that I have to be punished for that...
HE is the one who should be discharged!
Idiot!
Raising your sword against civilians is an act of heresy!
You should be grateful to Hewie!
You have no grounds to criticize!
Heresy, you say.
Somia!
As I thought, I'm no substitute for a father.
What have you come to do?
To look at the stars.
The stars?
Looking at the stars, I can feel humanity's insignificance.
What do you live for? Why do you keep on going?
From before we're born, until after we're dead and gone, the stars continue to shine.
Don't force yourself.
Mind your own business.
I thought you’d say that.
Well, I'm going to take a bath and wash away the day's sweat.
Take care of yourself.
Mind... your own business...
Huh?
Cecile.
You're nice no matter who it is, aren't you?
Not like you, Cecile.
I was just...
I was just...?
Involving the innocent people of that village in the battle...
Your eyes were beautiful then, too.
Very clear, and a little scary.
That's...
I think deep down you have undeniable strength... and purity.
I'm really glad I have subordinates like you.
Commander...
How far were you planning to follow me?
I was planning on taking my bath alone, but...
do you want to come in with me?
Yes! As you wish!
Are you okay? You're not scared?
J-Just... be gentle, please.
I understand.
No!
You get aroused pretty easily.
No! Don't look...!
This embarrassing pose...
That's why it's okay.
No!
I was just given this.
Oh, it's finally come.
We will conduct a formal sentencing. Have Somia come quickly.
Yes, sir
Want to get on top?
U-Um, t-that is...
I can’t go any further...
Hewie-sama...
Amazing... Amazing...
Ama...
This... What on earth is the King thinking?
Forming an alliance with those demons?
Oh dear, you learned the secret.
That old man is so careless.
Wh-Who's that?
My imagination?
If you butt in too far, you might get hurt!
Look!
I'm coming in!
What happened?
Somia...
Hang in there!
My daughter...
Why did my father...?
For your father, become a fine holy knight.
What's going on?
Commander!
You did this to the Commander!
N-No, it wasn't me!
Capture her!
It wasn't me! He was dead when I came in! I'm not lying!
Shut up!
It's true!
You lie. Didn't you have an argument with the general?
Just the sort of thing a beginner in the secret troops would do.
You even went so far as to kill your commanding officer.
You just sit there quietly and think about your punishment.
On top of being deprived of your command, the death penalty is more than likely.
Father... did I... make a mistake?
How're you? Feeling well?
Idiot. I've been imprisoned on a false charge. How the hell could I be feeling well?
Of course... You think I did this, too, don't you?
I wonder about that.
There's circumstantial evidence from the place of the crime, but there's no physical evidence.
The weapon used for the murder is too heavy for a woman.
You...
How about it? I brought this.
You really are something...
I see.
It's to protect your dead father's honor.
The only thing I was able to get from my father was his blood as a knight.
As a daughter in a job I couldn't abandon, with just my blood to rely on, I couldn't match my father.
That's a big sense of duty.
It's not that big of a deal.
I’m just obsessed with it.
Those of us in the secret unit, no matter how hard we work, are never recognized.
We continue to take on jobs that the other units despise.
As a result, by mistake you've become known as the 'massacre' unit.
Your sentence has been decided.
Death.
Of course.
I supposedly murdered my father’s best friend.
I'm sorry.
The council of the military court didn't allow for a formal trial, and made their decision arbitrarily.
And I was appointed the executioner.
You?
Of course, I plan to refuse. The decision was a mistake.
Why are you angry about it? You're a strange person.
Besides, it's funny, but I think it would feel good to have you do it.
Somia.
It's just... If there was one thing I’d regret...
What would you regret?
... It would be to die without knowing the feel of lying with a man.
Would I do?
Are you being honest?
Yes.
I suppose. Lying with an interesting guy like you wouldn't be half bad.
All right. I'll leave it to you.
It's fine, don't worry.
It's impossible!
H-Hewie!
Just a little more, lower your voice.
But I'm...
You’re so…
It's so pretty.
No...
Oh, I see. Somia, you're getting aroused here.
Down there is...
No!
... Thrusting
Hewie.
What is it?
It's my first time, so be gentle...
Don't worry. You have good instincts, so it'll be fine.
Th-That...
Yes... Oh, yes!
I'm... almost there...
Hewie!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
She's escaped!
Search over there!
Could she have gone there...
Is she there?
No!
Having done that, I truly am sorry.
But I really couldn't kill Somia.
As the time came closer, I felt doubts about this country's justice.
The powerful people are naturally running roughshod over the laws I've held since I was born.
It's something I simply cannot allow.
That's why I can't throw away lives fighting for this country.
And for the same reason, I cannot order my subordinates to do so either.
You must be wondering why I left you girls behind.
That's because, as regular soldiers, you form a private army.
Hewie-sama.
If we're lucky, we might be able to meet again sometime. Take care.
Are you really okay with this?
Doing something like this for my sake?
No matter what I do, I'm unfit to be a holy knight.
It was a perfect chance.
What are you going to do after this?
Are you just running away without thinking?
Hewie, you're going to marry me, and we'll have children,
and you'll make your own country, right, Hue-ba?
Country, you say?
What a child you are! And besides, having a child is not that easy a thing to do.
It's time for the second queen to be quiet.
S-Second queen?
My, my, you must be half asleep. The first queen is myself!
If you wish to become one of my followers, I may be so good as to allow it.
What did you say?
What do you want?
Oh, that's right.
That’s not a bad idea.
Let's make a country. With our own hands. The ideal country.
Let's go!
Giddyup!