Year 158 of the New Common Era.
On Synapse Continent, the conflict known as the Holy Demon Wars has broken out again.
It has been two hundred years since war broke out. On the side of the bright future, a single hero has appeared.
The Ingela Army has taken the Southern Faction's Boleblade Fortress, with no resistance from the Luciela Army.
That momentum has taken them forward as far as Isfart.
However, the Luciela Army without breaking through the last line of defense on the opposite side,
Leinga has gathered their forces at the strategic point of the Arubidabu.
They await the arrival of the Ingela Army with increasing tension.
SubDESU-H Presents
Holy Demon Wars
Second chapter
This time with you is fantastic, Julie.
G-Gaiyaku!
Julie!
But this weather is pretty crappy! Looks like it's going to keep us from getting to Albia anytime soon.
It's not the fault of the rain.
Julie, you're actually pretty lonely without everyone else around, aren't you?
Y-You idiot.
I'm going on ahead.
W-Wait up!
Seria-sama.
Ciruela, are you in there?
Yes, p-please come in.
Hewie-sama.
Is that... Seria's?
Yes.
It's Seria's only memento of the battle.
I'm sorry; I made you remember something painful.
No, it's fine.
If I don’t keep this sword with me at all times, I'll quickly forget my own purpose.
Purpose?
Taking revenge for Seria-sama.
Ciruela...
And? Was there something you wanted from me?
No... not really.
A messenger? Me?
They are planning to invade the enemy while their guard is down from a messenger of ours.
Right.
Whether the plan is a success or a failure, the messenger will most likely die.
What do you think? It's okay if you refuse.
There's no need for you to be drawn into such a foolish conflict.
I'll go refuse directly for you.
Hewie-sama.
Yes?
Please wait. I... I will go.
Ciruela!
It's enough that you care about me, Hewie-sama.
Ciruela...
Se-Seria-sama!
Seria-sama!
Seria-sama, I will definitely avenge you.
Good morning, Commander!
Aria, did you see Ciruela?
She was supposed to be in her tent, but she's not there.
She left early this morning.
What?
I thought for sure you'd know, Commander...
Ciruela...
My, my, if it isn't a messenger.
Thank you for coming all this way in this rain.
First we'll have to warm up your cold body.
We can think about things after that.
According to the report, this messenger has arrived in Arubida.
Give this message to the troops
Attack the enemy while they are distracted by our messenger.
Prepare for battle!
Yes
Gather the weapons!
Hey, stop messing around!
Are you worried about Ciruela-san?
Well, she's a valuable subordinate.
That's... all?
Yes, that's all.
Commander, let's go rescue Ciruela-san.
Aria!
Commander!
That's right, I'm sure Ciruela is waiting for her Commander to rescue her!
Hannah.
Really, I have to keep taking care of you children.
Cecil...
Okay, let's go!
If this fails, the Lucielle army will crumble.
If that happens, then surely Seria-sama will be happy...
Who's there?
May I join you, Madame Messenger.
Th-This is a problem! Please leave!
Come here, there's no reason to flinch away.
I know your true plan, “messenger”.
You were sent here to seduce me and to make Albida fall, weren’t you.
No, stop!
My body... can't move!
It's useless. We burn a very special incense in this bathhouse.
Once you inhale the smoke, your body goes numb.
Don't!
Luckily, I’m immune to it.
Oh, young girls have such beautiful skin!
It's been such a long time!
Oh, that's right, that's right.
There was an aphrodisiac in the smoke as well.
It should be increasing your sensitivity many times over about now.
You should be really starting to feel it, right?
Overflowing like this means you must be feeling good, eh?
I wonder what you taste like?
Let me taste you...
Oh, it's gotten all red.
Let's open it up nice and wide here.
It's the best!
Messenger?
At a time like this... it's suspicious.
So? Where is the messenger?
Well...
She should be ready by now. Right? Good girl. Coming in!
Who is?
Gaiyaku, from Boleblade. I thought to warm my cold body here.
What's this? Looks like I'm barging in on something. Do pardon me.
And? This woman is?
You are...
So... who might you be?
You're...!
Gaiyaku-san...
Hewie-sama and his troops have left to rescue Ciruela.
I see. I understand.
Shall we call them back to us?
No, we won’t.
Man, what were you thinking?
A woman messenger coming into a bathhouse like this? Isn’t it obvious what would happen to you?
I was just thinking of Seria-sama
Huh? You were thinking of taking revenge for that crazy woman?
I told you already, I'll take care of it for you!
As a young woman you could so easily be kidnapped! Or die!
I don't care.
You idiot!
Who in this world would be fine with dying?
You need to treasure yourself a little more.
Um, where are you going?
I'm going to war, of course.
Since they sent you here as a messenger,
it’s obvious that they plan on having a surprise attack while our guard is down.
So I’ve gotta go face ‘em!
Um...
Ah yes, almost forgot, this room has no key.
Well, it can't be helped, we'll leave it like this.
Don't let any thieves or anything come in!
Gaiyaku-san
You're just as crazy a person as ever.
I think that myself, sometimes.
It's no good.
The rains are too heavy, and the river is flowing too rapidly for us to cross.
Shit. With them unprepared, this was the perfect chance.
There aren't that many guards at the lookout.
Don’t tell me they actually fell for our plan?
With their bridge almost submerged as well, they seem overly confident.
Commander, someone's coming out.
Oh, it's Shireula!
Okay, let's go!
Commander!
I'm sorry we're late.
I...
No need to say anything.
More importantly, there's trouble!
It seems they're confined by the high waters.
Or is that their main platoon?
Shit.
This long rain has really taken its toll.
With this, Elsbard's remaining decoy military power can't attack from both sides.
What should we do?
A chance like this will never come again.
Let's commence.
Is that okay?
I don't think we can wait any longer for another chance.
They're unprepared, so we'll go in through the rear in one move.
Gaiyaku, is that the stronghold over there?
Sorry, Julie. I had you come along with me on this boring trip.
Just like always.
Coming at us from that cliff?
From there we can get at the stronghold around the back!
Can we make it?
Invasion! Invasion!
Shoot, shoot! Don't hold back, the battle is now!
Before they have a chance to regroup, everyone attack!
It's an invasion, a night attack!
What did you say?
Oh, that's...
Shit, we're too late!
It's fine, leave us! Go take care of the wounded!
Yes, sir!
Where is Ducis?
He feinted regrouping the troops and sent them towards the stronghold.
They’re on their way to the water now!
Ducis said that?
Yes, sir. He said to use Leinga to completely annihilate the enemy's weapons.
That idiot!
What is it?
He's getting impatient for a win.
At this rate... We'll lose!
Right. The enemy is has entered the battle ring.
Your target is the enemy's central platoon! Have all troops charge in!
Yes, ma'am!
Aria, tell this to all troops.
When the enemy begins to reach the innermost area, remove the front line.
We'll take the enemy's rear.
And the right wing?
The right wing will steadily and surely move to meet the rear.
When they show up, they should appear as a separate force.
When they reach the innermost area, we'll take the rear.
Are you abandoning the center?
We're heading for the stronghold! Don't slow us down!
The encirclement is also complete now.
What is it? You look unhappy.
Nothing.
Well, never mind.
All troops, form an arc
What's that sound?
It's the enemy, from over here!
A reserve corps?
They weren't supposed to have such resources!
They're not reserve. This was their plan from the beginning.
So they had only pretended to fall for our plan.
Our only remaining choice now is to put our faith in Hewie.
Ducis-sama!
Nothing more to be said! All troops stand firm!
Attack the enemy from a different formation!
Fire at will!
Carraway!
Ducis-sama!
Ducis!
Hewie?
I'm sorry I couldn't do anything...
Cecil, Ciruela's magic?
Don't mind me, continue the pursuit!
Don't let our chance for victory escape!
I don’t mind...
I have this one here.
What?
I get it.
Commander!
Let's go.
Yes!
Is that you, Gaiyaku? The enemy's response was faster than I expected.
They started moving so suddenly.
No, it wasn’t sudden.
From the beginning, they had an unpredictably powerful guy who foresaw what would happen.
And therefore, they retreated.
Retreat?
When it's like this, there's no way to win.
Run away quickly.
Understood. Then, I will also--
Julie, before the main forces are completely finished,
you will collect the remaining troops and retreat.
I will take care of the attack.
You idiot!
Do you understand what you're saying?
I completely understand.
Then!
For your sake, I can die.
Let me at least say a heroic line for once!
I get it.
Right, I'm leaving it to you, then.
Absolutely don't die, because I'll be waiting for you.
Right, this is my last duty.
There's no end!
Again? These are persistent bastards!
Maybe Julie should have
It's the young lady!
Gaiyaku... san!
I guess you're my final opponent, young lady.
Please put down your weapon!
Sorry, but I just can't do that.
I've got a lot to manage here.
Gaiyaku-san.
I'm not going to go easy on you!
Gaiyaku-san!
This is as far... as it goes... looks like... I got stabbed first...
Please surrender.
If we don't get you medical treatment soon
Don't joke around. If I were to surrender...
Gaiyaku-san!
Why? And you told me to live on!
Well, yeah, I said that...
Despite that, why?
Well, it's because... I decided... to become... a soldier...
To be held by... a beautiful... young lady... as I die...
Gaiyaku-san
You're called... Ciruela... right?
Y-Yes.
P-Please... don't hate... me...
Gaiyaku-san!
Hey, woman, how many times do I have to ask?
If you don't eat, you'll die!
I don't mind dying.
It would have been better if I'd died in place of Seria-sama.
Die, die, stop saying that, you fool!
Are you an idiot?
W-what did you say?
You're an idiot, so I called you an idiot.
You're helpless, you just worry.
And how is that insignificant?
Are you going to keep being like that forever?
Are you going to continue carrying the burden of a dead woman on your back? That’s what I’m asking.
Th-That is...
There's no way you can.
We're in a war.
You have to take it all day by day and take care of yourself.
But!
You don't have to forget.
The people you killed, the people who died for you...
Their faces... remember them always.
If you do that, they'll keep living on inside of you.
While we're living, they'll always be together with us.
That's nice, isn't it?
Always... be together?
That ends our conversation. Make sure to eat properly, okay, young lady?
Um...
I have a name: Ciruela.
Young lady is young lady.
If I hadn't met that person, I may have lost myself in Seria-sama's death.
That's why...
That's why... I'm no longer going to carry around the burden of her death.
Ciruela...
This... this is for the best.
It's fine, right, Seria-sama?
Hewie-sama, I've decided.
From here on, I'm going to live life to the extent that it covers the portions of those already dead as well.
Live for myself.
Always, always, I’ve admired you so... May I satisfy you?
Ciruela...
Hewie-sama...
I never would have imagined that I could do something like this with you.
I was aiming to be with you like this, Hewie-sama.
This is embarrassing.
You're so pretty, Ciruela.
Hewie-sama!
Does it hurt?
It's bearable. I'm okay. Please continue.
It hurts?
I'm fine... You may move.
I... Hewie-sama...
Ciruela!
Having won the Elisaber Garrison, the Ingela Army waited until the river died down to complete their invasion.
Having lost most of their power, the Luciela army was unable to hold them back.
After a mere four days, the Albida defense forces fell silent.
With the fall of the strategic location of Arubidabur,
the fight, increasing in intensity, approaches its closure.