And then, his dick is so
teeny-weeny it's easy to suck!
If you keep licking the tip even
right after he came, he'll squirt!
My classes are
over. When do you
want to meet?
I'm almost done
in here as well.
How does 5 PM
sound?
Okay, where
will it be?
Eh, seriously? So boys squirt too...
Yeah, it's fun! How about trying it too, Erena?
Hmm... Maybe if there's someone
I want to give that much of a service...
Sorry for the wait!
Oh, Ria.
Huh? Erena, are you free today?
Wanna hang around home with us?
Ah, good idea! Let's all come together!
Uhm... I'd love to but you see,
this month's kinda difficult for me.
I'm gonna work for some pocket money!
Cherry and gals.
...or so I said, but I kind of envy them both.
Oh, that kid is cute...
Isn't Ria's brother that young?
Or was he a little older?
His legs are so thin! It's even more slender than mine.
He has a fair skin, and his cheeks look so squishy!
Maybe I should tease him a little.
He's looking! He's ogling upfront at my panties!
He's so cute!
Huh? Is he not here yet?
I wonder what kind of guy will it be...
Now I'm getting nervous!
If it's a creepy guy or has no money and want
to do it in the restroom, I'll just go home.
H-Hello...
Huh?
Huh? You're that kid from earlier...
U-Uhm... Are you by any chance...
...meeting someone at 5 PM?
Eh? Ehh?!
You mean this was you?
Y-Yes... I'm sorry.
Woah... is this for real? No matter how
you look at it, this kid got no money.
And even if he had some,
It'd feel awkward for me to take.
I-I brought this.
Huh? What's that?
H-here's the strawberry. I bought them
'coz you told me not to forget about it.
ichigo (苺) = strawberry / ichigo (一五) = One-Five
Okay!
15k excluding hotel fee,
don't forget about it.
In compensated dating, ichigo means 15 000 yen.
e.g. one (ten-thousand) + five (thousand)
Take those strawberries home and eat them.
Whatever, this kid is adorable.
Gotta have a good taste of him!
I'm broke today so we have
to make do with this place.
O-Okay!
What's your name?
R-Ryouma.
Isn't this gonna be your first?
Are you sure about this?
Yes... please!
What a precocious kid! Even I had my first just last year.
Alright, get naked first.
Huh?
Take everything off. Let me see you naked.
B-But...
You don't want to? Then I'm going home.
Ah... I'll take them off!
I-Is this good enough?
Yeah, that's good!
You have such a fair skin,
your body is slender as well.
And you also don't have any muscle at all.
You look so fragile.
Oh well, you are cute so it's fine.
Th-This is embarrassing.
Eh... So you become like this when embarrassed.
Your thing got so stiff.
You're a pervert, Ryouma-kun.
Wh-Whenever I look at girls,
My pee pee gets hard right away... then...
So, you look at girls with those lustful eyes.
It's alright, you don't have to hold back today.
Well then...
Here, you can stare as much as you want!
Wow...
What's the matter, you don't like tits?
I love... them...
You can touch them.
O-Okay!
Wow, they're plumpy and bouncy!
They're soft!
Here, you don't have to hold back.
Don't you want to do this on my tits?
Suck on them just like a baby, okay?
Okay...
Yes, just like that!
That's good! More, suck them more.
Make my tits feel good!
That's my...
My pee pee...
Can you feel it? Your pee pee...
It's rubbing against my very important place!
Doesn't it feel very good when I do this?
Isn't it exhilarating?
Yes! It's good... It feels good!
This kid surely is adorable!
It feels... good!
You're getting better at it... That's good!
I'll enjoy this to the fullest!
Eh? What...
I'm gonna make you feel good using my mouth next.
Eh, with your mouth?
Yes, it's gonna feel very good!
It's so...
It's just like Ruruna said. Teeny-weenie dicks are easy to suck.
Do you use your hands
when you do this by yourself?
Y-Yes...
Which one feels better, using your hands or this?
T-This one!
N-No... It's gonna come out!
Not yet!
I'm gonna lick your balls next, okay?
This kid's dick and balls,
I can put his whole genitals in my mouth!
Coming... It's coming already!
Not yet!
That's...
Oh... You look troubled!
Your making such a cute face! Well...
Making you come that easily would be boring.
I'm gonna tease you more and more!
C-Coming... I'm coming!
Try to hold it in a little more!
A little more? I'm already so close...
It'll feel the best if you hold it
long enough before you squirt it out!
Boys are amazing creatures.
They can feel good on a blowjob
even from a girl they just met.
Please, let me come already!
Really... he's so naive, or rather a silly kid.
Well, that makes him cute.
I-It's coming out!
He should be at his limit already.
Alright, pour everything into my mouth.
Wh-What is this?! It's so incredible! He's coming like crazy!
He's been holding this much in him.
How is it? Does coming a lot feel good?
Y-Yes...
Then, I'll do something that
feels even more amazing!
Th-That's my butthole!
I just heard this from a friend.
She said that boys will squirt
when the tip is stimulated right after he came!
No...
Does it feel that good? Your dick is twitching.
S-Stop... Not that!
So it's ticklish for you...
I wonder how long will I take
before I make you squirt.
N-No more! Please!
It's driving me crazy!
He looks like he's suffering a lot.
But he looks cute like this as well!
It's alright. Come, come!
Show me how a boy like you squirts like a girl!
Something's coming again,
something's gonna come!
It's coming out!
Wow, he's coming! It really is true!
He's really squirting despite being a boy!
I'm sorry. Did that hurt?
N-No... It felt good.
I knew it, this boy really is a masochist.
I see, so it felt that much good.
Then, I'd love it if you use your pee pee
and make me feel good this time...
B-But I'm already...
Eh... we're already done?
Other boys are still okay after doing it three times...
If we're gonna end it now,
I won't be playing with you
ever again. You want that?
Huh?! I don't want that!
Then, here... come here!
Put your pee pee in here, okay?
Don't you want to try fucking my gooey pussy?
It will feel like heaven!
Hurry up... put it in!
O-Okay...
That's it, do it slowly... Put it in!
Can you feel it? This is what a girl's pussy is like!
My pee pee kind of feels ticklish...
I see, that's 'coz you just came earlier.
And that was his second time.
Wow... It feels so hot and slippery,
and it's squeezing me!
Hey, do your best! Keep on humping me more!
Use your pee pee to make
my pussy feel good a lot more!
O-Okay!
Your legs are shaking! You're funny! And cute!
Aww... What's with this? His dick is puny like a finger...
And he's barely moving at all...
But it feels so good!
Just like that... Plunge your dick deep inside me!
L-Like this?
Yes... Yes... There, right there!
That spot that the tip of your pee pee is hitting...
That's the spot that feels the best for girls!
If you'll squirt your semen right there,
I'll end up falling in love with you.
Will you do it?
Y-Yes!
Alright! Then, there... more!
Do your best and screw my pussy intensely!
Wait... If you keep doing that,
I'm gonna come again. I'm gonna shoot!
Alright, you're doing great.
Don't hold back, okay?
You don't have to do the moving by yourself.
You can come anytime you want!
B-But that's...
No... Oh no!
It's coming! It's coming out!
Incredible! It's such a tiny dick, but it really feels good!
I've never felt this aroused in sex before!
Stop it... stop!
No... Onee-chan!
I'm sorry! Just bear with me a little.
I'm gonna come as well!
Let me use your pee pee!
No! My pee pee is gonna turn weird!
Just a little more...
Onee-chan, I'm coming!
Let's come together, Ryouma-kun! Shoot it in my deepest parts!
Look, Ryouma-kun. These are my friends.
Should I let them join us and have sex with you?
Okay...
Then, we'll be doing it next time in my house.
I'm gonna make you feel good a lot, okay?
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization