And so, like, his dick was tiny.
It was so easy to suck.
Even after he came, all I had to do was keep
sucking and the cum just kept coming out.
Just got out. What time are we meeting up?
Don't worry. I just got out too. So how does 5 o'clock sound for you?
OK. Where should I meet you?
I didn't know guys could cum like that.
Yeah, it was pretty fun to watch.
You should try it too someday, Elena.
Just need to find a guy who I'd want to go that hard on to.
Sorry. Wait long?
Oh, Ria.
Elena? You free today?
Wanna come over?
That'd be fun!
Come with us!
Sorry, I'd love to, but I'm kinda pinched for cash.
I'm gonna go get some money.
Cherry and Gal's.
I wish I could've gone with them though.
Oh, that boy's cute.
Isn't Ria's little brother about the same age?
Or was he a little older?
His legs are so thin.
Thinner than mine.
His skin's so light and his cheeks seem so squishy.
Let's play with him a little.
He can't keep his eyes off of me!
He's fixated on my panties.
He's so cute!
What? Where is he?
What kind of guy is it gonna be today?
Pretty nerve wracking.
If he's even a little gross or can't pay up
immediately I'm just gonna go home.
U-Um...
Huh? You're from the bus.
Are you maybe the person I'm
supposed to be meeting here at five?
Huh? Huh?!
Wait, so this is you?!
Y-Yes.
Sorry.
Wow, you serious?
There's no way he has the money for this.
I'd feel pretty bad taking money from him too.
I-I brought them as promised!
Huh? Brought what?
S-Strawberries.
You told me to remember to bring them.
Okay. We'll hotel it up. Don't forget to
sweeten the deal. Fifteen should do it.
Why don't you take those strawberries
home and eat them yourself?
Well, whatever. He's cute.
I'm gonna eat him up.
I don't have any money, so we're gonna have to do it here.
O-Okay.
What's your name?
R-Ryoma.
You're a virgin, right?
Are you sure about this?
Y-Yes!
L-Let's get started.
Could wait a little longer, kid.
My first time was just last year.
Okay, then. Get naked.
Take everything off.
Show me your body.
B-But...
You don't want to?
Then I'm leaving.
I-I'll get naked!
I-Is this okay?
Yep, very good.
Your skin's so light.
And your body's so slender.
Don't got any muscles on you at all.
So delicate.
Not that it's a bad thing though, because you're cute.
Th-This is really embarrassing.
So why's it like this if you're so embarrassed?
Look, you're already hard.
You're a pervert, Ryoma-kun.
My dick gets hard really quick whenever I look at a girl.
I...
So you're looking at girls with dirty eyes then, huh?
Well don't worry, you don't have to hold back today.
Okay.
You can look all you want.
What's the matter? Don't like boobs?
No, I... like them!
Go ahead. Touch them.
O-Okay!
They're so smooth and squishy!
They're so soft!
Come on. Don't be shy.
You wanted to do this to my boobs, didn't you?
Just suck them like a baby.
Okay?
O-Okay...
Yeah, good. Just like that.
That's good!
More... Suck them more!
Make my boobs feel good!
Th-That's...
My dick's...
Can you tell? Your dick is rubbing against my special parts.
It feels really good doesn't it?
Really turns you on, doesn't it?
Y-Yes! It feels good! It feels really good!
This kid, he's so frickin' cute!
It feels so good!
You... You've gotten really good at this.
I need to make sure I get my fill of the fun.
Huh? Um...
Now I'll make you feel good with my mouth.
Huh? With your mouth?
Yep. It's gonna feel really good.
Ruruna knew what she was talking about.
It's so easy to suck smaller dicks.
Do you use your hands when you do it alone?
What feels better? This or your hands?
This does!
N-No! I'm gonna cum!
Not yet.
I'm gonna suck your balls next.
I can fit his dick and his balls in my mouth with no problem.
I... I'm gonna cum!
Not yet.
P-Please!
Oh my, you look so sad.
That look on your face is so cute.
Well, then...
It'd be boring to let you cum so easily.
I'm gonna play with you more and more.
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!!
Hold on just a little longer.
Longer? But I'm so close!
It feels even better if you hold it in before cumming.
Boys sure are something.
He's getting turned on from being
sucked off by a person he just met.
Please! Let me cum!
Not sure whether to call him innocent or stupid.
But I guess that's what makes him cute.
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I guess he's at his limit.
Go ahead. I'll take everything in my mouth.
What's going on?! There's so much!
He had this much saved up?
So? You came a lot. Did it feel good?
Y-Yes.
Then I guess I'll do something even better for you.
M-My butthole!
See, I heard from a friend that if you stimulate a guy
right after he cums, they just cum over and over.
S-Stop!
Does it really feel that good?
Your clicks twitching a lot.
S-Stop! Don't...
Does it tickle? I wonder what I need
to do to get that cum flowing.
S-Stop! No more!
I-I'm gonna lose my mind!
He looks like he's really enjoying it.
But that's just really cute!
It's okay. Cum! Cum!
Squirt on me like a girl!
No... I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Wow he did it... He really came!
He really squirted even though he's a guy!
Sorry, was that tough on you?
N-No, it felt good.
This kid's really a masochist.
Oh, really. It felt that good, huh?
Okay then, how about you make me
feel good with your dick this time?
B-But, I don't think I can...
Huh? You're done already?
Normally, guys have no problem going at least three times.
If you can't even do this much, I'm never
gonna hang out with you again, Ryoma-kun.
Is that what you want?
N-No!
Then come on. Come here.
Put your dick in here.
Okay?
Don't you want to know what sex feels like?
It feels really good!
Put it in already.
O-Okay!
Good. Slowly.
It's going in!
Can you feel it? This is a girl's pussy!
My dick feels kinda weak.
I guess that makes sense since you just came.
Especially after cumming twice.
Wow, it's so wet and it's so tight!
Come on, try moving more. You can do it!
Make my pussy feel even better with your dick!
O-Okay!
You're trying so hard! So cute!
What is it about this dick that's as slender as a finger?
It's barely moving at all, but it feel so good!
Keep going! Shove your dick deep inside me!
Like this?
Yeah! Yeah! Right there!
The thing the tip of your dick is touching right now...
It's the spot that girls like the most.
If you shoot your cum right there, I'll love you, Ryoma-kun.
Will you do it for me?
Y-Yes!
Yay! Now shove your dick in me harder!
If you keep doing it like that, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
That's okay. Don't worry.
When you want to cum... just do it, okay?
B-But, I...
I... I...
I came! I came!!
Shit! His dick's so small, but it feels so good!
I've never been this turned on in my life!
Stop! Stop!!
Stop! Stop! Please!
Sorry!
But bear with it. I'm about to cum!
Let me use your dick to cum!
No! My dick is starting to feel really weird!
A little more...
I'm cumming!
Cum with me, Ryoma-kun!
Look. These are my friends.
How about we all do something dirty together next time?
Let's do this at my house next time.
I'll make sure you feel really really good.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч