So like, I heard that Sasamoto's dick is, like, totally thick.
Huh? Aren't you dating Yuuki?
Huh? Yeah, but...
It's just sex. Nothing serious.
So you're saying it'd be okay for
me to do it with Yuuki then?
Go ahead. But let me tell you, he's not that good or that big.
Huh? You serious?
So what? He's hot and that's it?
Yeah, everything but his face sucks.
I can't do this anymore. I'm totally in the wrong group.
Why?
All they do is talk about sex. I've got nothing to say.
I envy you, Ria.
You don't have to say anything to fit in.
You think so?
I get so depressed every lunch period.
Wait, so, have you never had sex, Ruruna?
Wh-What about you, Ria?
Of course. Basically every day.
Huh? Every day?
You don't have to pretend.
Who would you even be having sex with every day?
My little brother.
Why don't you try fucking my little brother too, Ruruna?
I bet if you have sex, you'll be able
to join in the conversation.
H-Her little brother? Really? W-Well,
she's probably kidding...
Cherry and gal's.
Kei-chan?
I'm coming in.
O-Oh, welcome home, nee-chan.
I brought Ruruna over.
Yo, how've you been?
Ruruna-chan?
You've really grown.
Why are you acting like an aunt talking to her nephew?
I haven't changed at all.
Kei-chan, it's sex time. Strip.
Huh?
B-But...
I already told Ruruna.
Just take 'em off.
Nee-chan? What do you mean, you told her?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Get naked.
She wasn't joking!
Okay, Ruruna, you can touch him.
B-But...
It's fine. I've trained him.
He knows if he tattles I'll crush his balls.
S-Stop...
Fun, right?
You play with his balls here and his dick
gets bigger. Why don't you try, Ruruna?
You're sure it's okay?
Of course. This is all about the experience.
It's so soft.
So this is what it feels like!
Ruruna-chan...
Try massaging around here a little harder.
L-Like this?
Wow, the ball's moving around in my hand!
It's starting to twitch!
This is so fun!
Right?
There's something coming out of the tip.
Kei-chan, does it hurt at all?
What? He ejaculated?
Cool, right?
I've been able to get him to cum just by touching
his balls ever since about a week ago.
Maybe you played with him too much
and now his dicks really messed up.
Hm, maybe.
It's pretty fun to make him cum about three times
before having sex... it'll really turn you on.
So what should I do?
So he apparently likes it when you shove your tits
in his face and stroke his dick at the same time.
He cums so quick.
Okay then, I'll do it too!
Kei-chan, your dick's gotten really hard.
Good for you. You have so many boobs today.
He's so cute... he's like a baby!
Your dick must be really sensitive.
He's being drowned by boobs.
Looks rough.
But Kei-chan's a pervert, so pain feels good, doesn't it?
Look at how your dick is bulging.
You're such a perverted baby.
N-No, go slower...
Huh? Are you gonna cum?
Not yet. Hold it in longer.
I-I can't!
S-Stop! Stop it!
Oh god, it's getting so hot.
It's twitching a lot too!
Come on, you can do it.
You can do it!
N-No I can't! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum again!
You came even more than usual, huh?
It can really shoot that far?
It's because he got really turned on from you doing it.
What a perverted baby.
Hey, it's still twitching.
Then let's move on to the main course.
Are you sure?
He has only cummed twice.
It's fine, I'll make him cum with my pussy.
After that, we'll switch off.
W-Wait...
N-Nee-chan, I think I'm done for today.
No you're not.
N-No, I...
Maybe it's because the second time was pretty rough.
You're usually fine even after cumming twice.
You look like you're in pain.
Y-Yeah, he really does.
Are you sure he's going to be okay?
He'll be fine. This is fun.
I'll have you make him cum next.
Come on, Kei-chan, you can see it, can't you? Your
dick is so happy inside your big sister's raw pussy.
You don't have to hold anything back.
Just shoot out your cum like you always do.
N-No... W-Wait!
Please!
Hey, Kei-chan...
You're not getting away until you cum.
Your dick's really twitching.
Gonna cum?
That's fine. Go ahead.
Shoot it out.
N-No... D-Don't... Don't be so rough!
Please! Stop!
Oh, right, you needed more boobs, didn't you?
Do my boobs feel good?
Your dick's getting even harder in
this position. Do you like this?
Tell me. Do you?
Do you?!
It feels too good! I-I'm gonna cum! N-No!
That's okay. Just cum.
Just fill me up with your cum like you always do!
Don't grip me like that! No!
Does it really feel that good? You're
such a pervert, Kei-chan!
You can't hold it in, can you? Come on! Come on!
Don't hold it in. Just shoot it out!
I'm cumming!!
I can feel the warmth deep in my pussy!
He's really shooting it out!
Keep cumming until you're done, okay?
W-Wow.
This is his third time, but he came so much!
Don't worry, he's still good to go.
N-No, I'm not!
P-Please, stop!
Kei-chan, sorry.
Do me a little too, okay?
N-No, Ruruna-chan!
C-Calm down.
Th-This is my first time.
Ruruna, how's your first dick feel?
It hurts a little, but it's not a problem.
It's so warm, it's making me feel kind of weird.
Ruruna-chan, stop squeezing me so tightly.
Wow, even a kid dick like this feels good!
Tight! So tight!
No... Stop moving so much!
Th-This might feel good now.
I-It feels good!
N-No, stop moving!
It feels so good!
N-No more!
Don't move!
Wh-What?
Are you disobeying me?
Stop moving. I-I can't...
I-If you keep moving like that, it's gonna come out!
You say that, but you're already
moving your hips by yourself.
P-Please, take it out! Take it out, Ruruna-chan!
Seriously, it's gonna come out if you keep moving like that!
Just kidding!
Now it's all inside.
Th-This is bad... It's too tight inside you, Ruruna-chan!
Okay, I'll move this tight pussy of mine then.
I think my pussy's getting really hot.
It feels really good!
Ruruna-chan, s-stop!
Stop!
After I'm finished with my first time,
I can have sex as much as I want!
I love having sex!
And you do this every day?
I'm so jealous.
I wish I had a little brother too!
It's really going in me!
Ruruna-chan, you're really getting tight!
No!
Feels good, doesn't it? But he's my little brother,
so you can't keep him for yourself.
Let me join in the fun.
N-Nee-chan? What are you...
Okay, now make your big sister's pussy feel good too.
Oh god, his dick's twitching and it's getting hotter.
So this is what turns him on?
Is this rough? But you have a pussy on your
mouth and your dick. You're so lucky.
What should I do? I think I'm about to cum!
His dick might make me cum!
Ruruna, I think he wants to cum really badly too.
He's really turned on!
Really? Wow.
This'll be my first time getting cummed in.
Hurry! Hurry up and give it to me, Kei-chan!
Fill me with your cum! Cum! Cum!
In my pussy...
Cum in my pussy!!
I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!
It's so hot!
His cum's filling up my pussy!
There's so much... I might get pregnant!
So, Ruruna?
How do you feel about your first time?
Yeah, it was amazing!
I thing I kinda get why everyone
loves talking about sex so much.
So Mom and Dad aren't coming home tonight
because of work. Wanna stay the night?
You sure?
I-I'm done!
He ran away!
Hey, wait!
No! Stop!
Don't step on it, Ruruna-chan!
Your balls are so sticky and slimy from all your cum.
It feels good!
Wh-Why are you suing your foot? You're so mean!
But your dick's really hard, Kei-chan.
Look how hard you are!
You like this, don't you?
N-No, I don't!
Th-This is...
N-No! P-Please stop!
Hey now, look over here.
I'll get a good video of your lewdness, Kei-chan.
N-No!
Nee-chan, please don't!
This is so embarrassing!
You get turned on from being watched.
Maybe I should upload this so everyone can watch.
No! Stop!
Please don't do that!
Your dick just got even bigger.
How dirty. You're about to cum from
being stepped on, aren't you?
No! Stop!
Don't rub it around so much like that!
I need to make sure I get a good shot of him cumming.
No!
I shouldn't be cumming from this, but...
I can't hold it in any longer!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Go ahead. You want to cum a lot, don't you?
You wanna shoot it out, don't you? Come on! Come on!
You don't have to hold it in.
Cover my foot in your cum!
There it is!
Wow, he's still shooting out this much!
This could be a new record.
And we haven't even gotten started yet.
You're gonna make us cum a lot.
All night long... 'kay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч