As I was saying, Sasamoto's dick is so thick!
Wait, weren't you with Yuuki last time?
Eh... Yeah, I was. But fucking other
guys around a little should just be fine.
Then, it's fine if I do it with Yuuki?
I'm fine with it, but he sucks on bed and he's small.
Eh, seriously? Even when he's that handsome?
Everything about him sucks except for his face!
This isn't working out. I surely
joined the wrong social group.
Why?
They only talk about sex and I
can't join with the conversation.
You have it better, Ria. You can stay silent and it will fit your personality.
You think so?
Jeez, I feel lonely on every break times because of it.
Could it be that you never had sex yet, Ruruna?
Huh?!
H-How about you, Ria?
I do it, like everyday.
Huh? Everyday? You're kidding.
And saying you do it everyday... with who?
My little brother.
Want to try fucking my brother too, Ruruna?
If you'll have sex, you'll be able to
join in everyone's conversation.
W-With his little brother...
I-I'm sure she's just kidding.
Cherry and gals's.
Kei-chan!
I'm coming in.
Ah, w-welcome home, nee-chan.
I brought Ruruna-chan with me.
Yo, it's been a while!
Ruruna-chan!
You've grown up, Kei-chan!
Why are you talking like a grandma?
And you say it like that's the only change you see in me.
Kei-chan, we're gonna have sex. Take your clothes off.
Eh?
But...
I already told Ruruna about it,
so you can take your clothes off.
Nee-chan... You told her?
Don't make me repeat myself. Come on, get naked.
Whoa... These siblings really were...
Go on, Ruruna. You can touch him.
But...
It's alright. I already groomed him.
I drilled in his head that if he tattled about this, I'll be crushing his balls.
D-Don't...
See? Looks cool, right?
He gets hard when you squeeze his balls.
Can I really?
It's alright, it'll all be for your experience.
Wow... How soft! So it feels like this...
Ruruna-chan...
Do it more like this, try to press them like a rubber.
L-Like this?
Amazing... The balls inside are rolling around!
He's trembling, this is cool!
I told you!
Something's dripping out at the tip.
Does it hurt, Kei-chan?
Huh?
Eh? It can't be... Did he ejaculate?
Isn't it amazing?
I've been kneading his balls for a week now
and he started to be able to shoot semen out.
Maybe you made his penis weird
from playing with it so much?
Maybe.
I first make him ejaculate around
three times before fucking him.
Then his body starts trembling, and it's fun to watch!
What? What are you doing?
You do it like this...
He loves it when you shove him your tits while
stroking his dick, and he'll come in no time.
I'll do the same then!
Kei-chan, your dick got hard already!
Isn't that great? We'll give you a lot of tits today!
How cute, just like a baby!
You're hard as a rock, Kei-chan!
You're drowning in tits!
Looks like he's in pain!
You're a pervert so you feel
pleasure from the pain, right?
Having your pee pee stroked...
You're such a perverted baby!
D-Don't! Slow it down!
Wait, are you gonna come?
Not yet, try to hold it in longer!
I can't! Stop... Stop!
Oh my, it's so hot and it's twitching!
Come on. Do your best, do your best!
I can't anymore... It's coming out!
It's coming out again!
Wow...
You shot out further than you usually do.
He's able to shoot that far?
He got so excited because you stroked him.
What a perverted baby.
Hey, he's still twitching.
Let's get to the real thing, then.
Already? He only came twice though.
It's okay, I'll use my pussy to make him come.
After that, you can have your turn.
Eh, that's... Oh... Nee-chan!
I had enough for today!
No way...
No, I'm already...
I think the second round was too intense for you.
You usually are still fine after coming
twice, but you look so worn out now.
H-Hey... He really looks like he's
in pain. Will he really be fine?
It's fine because it's gonna be fun.
I'll let you come later too, Ruruna. Okay?
Look, Kei-chan! Can you see it?
Your dick is feeling good
from onee-chan's raw pussy!
You don't have to hold yourself back.
Squirt your semen in me just like you always do!
No, don't...
W-Wait... I beg you!
Jeez, your hand's in the way!
Oops!
See? Now I won't let you go until you come!
Your dick is twitching.
Are you gonna come? It's okay!
You can come! Squirt it out!
No... Spare me... Don't be so rough on me!
Please... Stop this already!
You never had enough tits yet, right?
Do my tits feel great?
Your dick got harder now that we're in this position.
Do you like this? How is it?
Good? Is this good?
You're moving too much! I'm coming... No...
It's alright, shoot a lot of it out,
inside me like you always do.
Nee-chan... Don't squeeze me so hard! Don't!
Does it feel good? You really
are a pervert, Kei-chan!
You can't bear it anymore, right?
You don't have to hold it in,
shoot everything into me!
It's coming out!
He's squirting warm stuff deep into my pussy.
Pour it all out until the last drop.
It's incredible...
He came that much even on his third time.
It's alright, he still can go on.
N-No more! I can't anymore! I-I beg you...
Forgive me, Kei-chan.
Let me do it a little as well.
I don't want to, Ruruna-chan...
Wait, quit struggling! It's my first time, you see.
Ruruna, how does having your first dick feel?
It hurts a little, but I'm okay!
I feel warm in my belly, I feel somehow strange!
Ruruna-chan, don't...
Don't hump me that much!
Wonderfull!
You have such a little dick,
but it still feels good.
Tight... It's so tight! No!
Don't move that much!
This actually feels amazing!
Somehow... I'm loving this!
No... Don't! Please stop moving!
So... good!
N-No... I can't take it anymore, please stop moving!
Wait... What, are you trying to push me away?
Stop moving, I can't... Anymore...
Your dick's gonna come out of me
if you push me away like that!
You talk like that, but you're
already shaking your hips!
I beg you, pull it out! Pull it out, Ruruna-chan!
No, if you keep on resisting your
dick will be pulled out of me!
Just kidding!
The whole thing went inside.
No... You're so tight, Ruruna-chan!
Well then, I'll start moving this tight pussy!
It's like my pussy...
is burning hot, and it feels good!
Ruruna-chan... No... Stop!
After getting on it just once, I'm already hooked!
Sex is so much fun!
Are you doing something
like this everyday, Ria?
That's wonderful, I want to have a little brother too!
This really feels good!
Ruruna-chan... You're squeezing me so hard... Oh no...
Okay then. He's my little brother
so I shouldn't have him selfishly.
Let me join in as well.
N-Nee-chan? What are you—
Here you go, make my pussy feel good too.
Oh my, his dick is twitching
and it got even hotter!
He's feeling good from all this.
Are you getting worn out, Kei-chan?
Aren't you glad to get pussies both up and down?
What should I do? I think I'm gonna come soon!
His dick is gonna make me come!
It looks like Kei-chan can't hold it in
anymore and is gonna come too, Ruruna!
He got so aroused!
Really, I'm in for a treat!
I'm gonna have my first creampie too!
Hurry, hurry up and give it to me! Your semen...
Come on, come on! Come! Come! Inside my pussy...
Squirt it deep inside me!
I'm coming!
Oh no... I'm coming!
I-It's so hot!
The creampie is gushing... It's spilling out!
I might get pregnant with this much!
Ruruna, how is it? Any thought about your first sex?
Yeah, it's the best!
I think I now understand why
everyone loves talking about sex!
Hey, our parents won't come home from
work today. Want to have a sleep over?
Can I?
I-I can't do it anymore!
He's running away!
Hey, wait for me!
S-Stop! Don't step on it, Ruruna-chan!
Kei-chan's balls are sticky and slippery
with semen, they feel awesome!
T-That's... Doing this to me with your foot... You're so cruel...
But look, your dick got hard again, Kei-chan.
You're hard as a rock. Having this done
to you doesn't really feel that bad, right?
T-That's not true! This is...
No! S-Spare me already!
Come on, look over here!
I'll get good shots of your lewd thing.
N-No, nee-chan! Stop recording this!
It's embarrassing!
Even though you get so aroused while being watched.
I might as well upload these online.
Stop... stop!
Please, don't do that!
Your dick got big again, how lewd!
You're gonna come from a footjob.
No... no! Don't rub me that much!
I have to record the moment Kei-chan's dick squirts.
No... I-I shouldn't come...
But I can't take it anymore! Coming! It's coming out!
It's alright, don't you want to shoot a lot?
Don't you want to come? Here you go! Here!
You don't have to hold back!
Shoot it on my foot!
He came!
Incredible! He could still shoot this
much. Isn't this a new record?
We still have a long way to go before the real deal!
You'll still have to make both of us come...
a lot until the morning, okay?
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization