Petite Tummies
I'm Inoue Emi.
I'm quite the anemic girl,
so my body is actually kind of weak.
Sensei has saved me so many times from collapsing.
That made me so happy.
Sensei.
Emi, that feels good.
Push it in further.
Which is why I restrained myself, when
sensei asked me to have sex with him.
It hurt a bit, but...
Emi?
Did you just cum?
Sensei hasn't cum yet, though.
I'm doing it from behind.
Sensei.
It feels good.
It really does feel good when you do it from behind.
He held me tightly after doing it.
Patted my head.
He was so nice to me.
Since then,
sensei and I have been.
Doing it everyday in the morning
and after school at the infirmary.
But, it's been weird as of late.
Whenever we have sex,
my chest suddenly throbs, and it feels so hot.
I'm going to cum, Emi.
Okay.
Emi, that felt very good.
After school again, okay?
I wonder what this is.
"You know, Emi-chan..."
~After school~
Emi-chan!
Emi-chan.
Hey, Emi-chan!
Let's go home.
Let's.
Oh, ah... well.
Umm.
I-I have something else to do today.
Th-That's why.
What, again?
You've been like that lately.
Come on, let's go home together!
What exactly were you doing?
Se-Sensei's... well.
Being sensei's assistant, I guess.
You know, Emi-chan,
could actually be.
Emi.
You've gotten better at this since you sucked it for the first time.
I've been doing it... regularly.
I really can't get used to sucking a dick, though.
But sensei is just so happy when I do it.
That's good.
I'm about to cum.
Oh, you swallowed it properly.
Good girl.
Emi,
try putting it in by yourself.
Okay.
Sensei's thing is... big!
Sensei!
I can't push it in any further.
We're almost halfway there.
Sensei becomes a bit of a meanie when we have sex.
You can still push it in, right?
No, I can't!
Sensei!
No, no.
It's going to completely fill my insides!
It's reached my very depths!
Sensei, stop!
No!
There it is again.
My chest is yet again,
throbbing wildly.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
Ready? I'm going to go faster right before I cum.
Sensei, sensei!
Sensei, no!
Sensei, sensei, sensei.
Sensei!
Whenever I think of him,
my chest feels very tight.
I'm already.
My thoughts are already...
focused entirely on sensei!
Emi, Emi.
Emi, that felt good.
Emi, let's go home!
W-Well.
U-Umm...
I need to do something with sensei again today.
Figures.
You're going to be with sensei today again, right?
Tell us all about it next time, okay?
I wonder how far they've gone already.