MIKA
Don't Just Enter As You Please!
What a sweet smell...
Mika run away without so much money
and without clothes for change, but...
Without bringing so much it'll be dangerous for her...
Dangerous place...
This girl doesn't have any place to go to...
Could you mister help us?
Hey mika smile a bit more... they'll soon
gonna make you feel amazing!
It's better without condom, right?
The night is still long. I'll come all out inside
you until you became a mother, Mika-chan!
It can't be that...
I'm sure she's probably within Misaka.
But she's so defenseless.
Just thinking of that makes my reasoning go crazy.
ahh I'm so irritated!
I thought that he's the dumbest person but...
How in the world did that happen!! dumb-ass brother!
This is really the worst...
What are you doing there? You'll gonna catch cold.
Why did you come here for?
I'm looking for you... so let's go home.
Go home with yourself... there's no way I'll sleep
under the same roof as you.. PERVERT!
You... now that it comes to this... then...
could that be my...
I'll be a pervert for real!
Give that back to me!
Get off me... I know you hate me, right?
Recently, even on our home, your distant
from me and you abandoned me.
Well about that...
Don't confuse me anymore... how much
more of a pervert could you be...
You don't even care about me...
Come closer to me...
What the heck is happening with me?
This is kinda swollen... because I touched it?
kiss me...
or...
Try to compare us... me and Sayaka-chan.
You can do whatever you like... Onii-chan!
Why did you?
When we were still children... When I can't
make friends and just cried all the time...
That time you said I'll be your wife so...
Its embarrassing... if you continue doing that...
No... not there... I said not there...
you're focusing too much on my breasts...
Its over now... that's all for today...
No! I don't want to!
Onii-chan...
Your touching them lasciviously...
I want to come with your boobs...
With this Position...
This is so lewd... what if someone sees us...
Hey, that's enough...
I... haven't taken a bath since yesterday...
This is embarrassing...
That's enough... not there..
I mean it we shouldn't...
Stop it already...
If were seen doing this... they'll think that were both perverts...
Don't do it too much... I can't control my voice...
and someone might hear me...
Oh no... I'm being turned-on...
oh no...
No... don't look... this is so embarrassing!
What.. I did it with Onii-chan in raw...
And you even did It on me... you're such a pervert Onii-chan...
I cant hold back since I'm a pervert!
And I've seen your cute parts...
No...
I can't stop myself from wanting you...
Your dick... its completely inside me...
Just stay like this for a while...
Its fine... you can now move, Onii-chan.
Amazing... Its so slimy inside you..
Oh no... I'm getting fucked and I'm letting out lewd sounds...
Someone might hear my embarrassing moans...
No... if you do more of that I'll moan more!
Its getting more bigger... Onii-chan come on deep inside me...
Aside from hearing your lewd voices I also
want to see your naughty expression...
Such thing...
No... if we continue... I'll be a pervert for real...
Onii-chan come over here...
More!
Onii-chan, I want to be pleasured more!
More! Give me more!
No!
No...
NO!
Onii-chan, I now know what it feels. I'm twitching a lot...
Cum a lot... cum a lot inside me!
I don't care...
Mika, I'll make you mine!
That's so good. Penetrate me deeper!
No...
I love you... I love you...
You can come on me... I want to be yours...
I'm cumming... Cumming... Cumming!
Say Onii-chan... In comparison with Sayaka-chan..
what do you think of me?
what?
oh what's with the comparison.. I certainly
want to know the details about that...
don't enter as you please!
we're on the same boat... we both entered here right!
You PERVERT!!!