I drank too much tea!
Just three more stations.
Hold it in, hold it in.
Huh? Konoka-chan?
Se-Sensei!
Good morning. You're quite early today.
It's Kaneko-sensei.
He's really cool, so he's quite popular with the female students.
I-I'm assigned on morning duties today.
Oh, I see.
But, why now of all times...
So, morning duties start this early.
Looks quite difficult.
Yeah, it really is.
There's quite a lot of things to do.
Do you always do this alone?
Hold it in. Hold it in.
Y-Yes.
Which is why it's usually only assigned once every month.
Oh please, please don't shake too much!
Next stop, Morino University, Morino University.
She's fidgeting around.
Could she be...?
Konoka-chan, could you be...
This station starts to get really packed at this hour.
Are you all right, Konoka-chan?
I kind of knocked you over earlier.
I-I'm not all right at all!
I really can't hold it in anymore.
Please get there already.
Sensei's leg is pressing against it!
Oh no...
Stop, don't move!
Hold it, hold it in!
It's just a little more before I reach the station.
Should I suddenly get a leak here, I'll...
We'll soon be crossing over an elevated area.
The train will experience a slight bump, so please be careful.
That was quite a bump.
Konoka-chan, are you alri—
Huh?
Sensei...
My knees kind of feel warm... and wet...
Could this be...?
Keep
this
a secret ,
okay ?
Sensei...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sensei.
Don't worry, it'll be okay.
It was partly my fault, anyway.
You might catch a cold if we don't wipe it properly.
Don't you feel cold?
Yes.
I'm not a kid anymore, but I still had a leak.
She really peed earlier.
She was all fidgety earlier, but...
...it does look really smooth.
I want to look a bit more inside.
I've wiped off most of it,
but we still need to clean it more thoroughly.
Can you sit at the toilet seat for a bit?
Okay.
My butt feels cold.
Can you... part your legs a bit more?
Oh, like this?
Yeah. That's right.
This position feels embarrassing.
Th-This is...
It's more than I imagined...
Sensei?
Oh, I'm sorry!
Looks like it really needs some more wiping.
See? Over this spot.
It feels kind of weird.
Sensei!
It feels really tender.
Sensei...!
It tickles!
Just hold on a bit more.
She's not yet aroused at this point, I think.
Then, I'll just have to directly...
Sensei?
We have to wipe the inside properly, too.
That tingled a bit...
Sensei,
that part isn't wet!
You might get sick if we don't clean it properly.
Huh? It's getting a bit wet.
Sensei...
It's embarrassing for me down there.
Is she getting aroused already?
Sensei, please stop!
Something feels weird...
How does it feel here?
Her clit is also quite covered.
I'll open it here, and...
There, that tingling sensation again!
Sensei!
No, no...
Sensei—
Oh no, if this continues...
Stop, something's coming out!
She just suddenly came.
Also...
I can't possibly hold back anymore after seeing that.
We've reached this point already, so I'll do it till the end.
Sensei?
Sensei...!
Stop, don't lick me down there!
Don't suck!
Such a tiny clit.
She seems to get more aroused at this point,
so I'll have to thoroughly caress it.
Wh-What is this?
Her pussy is small.
Will my finger fit inside?
Sensei, stop!
Sensei, please don't put your finger inside!
My insides feel all tingly.
Oh no...
Sensei, sensei!
No, it came out again.
My entire body feels weak.
Sensei?
Konoka-chan, I'll gently put it in, okay?
Sensei...
It's okay, you're already this wet.
It's pushing itself inside.
It's so tight, yet so soft.
Sensei...
Whoa, this is quite something!
Her pussy is trying to squeeze my dick!
No, not there...
His dick is hitting deep inside me.
Sensei...
Her body's soft and light.
It feels like I'm holding a doll.
No, it's going to come out again.
Sensei, stop. I'm going to get soiled even more!
I'm... I'm actually having sex with sensei!
Oh no, this feels too good!
So these tiny, tight and soft pussies feel this good?
Sensei, please stop. I'm already about to...
Sensei!
I can't hold it in anymore!
If you keep pushing it in even further, I'll...
Your pussy feels so good!
I also can't hold back anymore!
Stop...
Stop, not there!
Please, don't!
My body's completely tingly now.
Konoka, your insides are wrapping me tight!
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum inside!
Konoka... Konoka, Konoka...!
Sensei...!
I'm cumming!
It's going to come out!
It's pouring inside me...
Your pussy is small,
so my cum easily overflowed.
Se-Sensei!
Y-Yes?!
C-Can you keep what happened a secret between us?
O-Of course I will.
It'd be embarrassing if everyone knew I leaked.