small insides
I drank a little too much tea!
Only three more stations. Need to hold it in...
Hold it in, hold it in!
Huh? Konoka-chan?
S-Sensei!
Good morning. You're early today.
It's Kaneko-sensei.
The girls love him because he's really cool.
I-I'm on duty today, so...
I see.
But why now, of all times?
You need to get up early if you're on duty, huh?
Must be rough.
Ah, yeah! There's a lot to be done, after all.
– Is it always a one-man job?
– Just hold it in.
Y-Yes. It takes around a month for a full rotation.
Oh train, don't shake so much!
Next stop, Morinodai. Morinodai.
She's fidgeting a lot. Is she...
Konoka-chan, are you...
The train starts getting packed around this time, doesn't it?
Konoka-chan, are you okay?
I kinda bumped you...
Y-Yeah!
I'm okay!
I can't hold it in anymore!
Please get there soon!
Sense's leg is pressing on it too!
No, don't move!
Hang in there.
We're almost at the station. I can't just let it out now.
Next stop, Suginooka. Suginooka.
The train will shake momentarily. Please exercise caution.
Phew. That was something.
Konoka-chan, are you...
H-Huh?
Sensei...
My knee feels kinda warm.
Did she...
it's a secret
Sensei, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Sensei, I'm so sorry!
It's fine, it's fine.
I mean, it was partly my fault.
You'll catch a cold if we don't wipe you dry.
Do you feel chilly?
No.
I can't believe I peed myself, I'm not a 2-year old.
She was fidgeting a lot, but I didn't
expect her to pee herself.
It's so smooth, damn.
I want to take a closer look.
I-I'm almost done, but I'll have to wipe the inside too.
Could you sit down for a bit?
Okay.
My butt feels cold.
Spread your legs some more.
Like this?
Yeah.
This is kinda embarrassing.
W-Woah. This is a lot better than expected.
Sensei?
Uh, sorry, sorry!
Yeah, it's still wet around here. See?
I'm feeling... strange.
Sensei.
It's so soft.
It tickles.
Just hang in there.
I guess this isn't enough to turn her on.
Guess I'll kick it up a notch.
Sensei?
We have to wipe the inside too.
I-It feels tingly...
Sensei...
I-It's not even wet there!
You'll get sick if we don't wipe it.
Oh? It's starting to get wet.
Sensei.
Not there. It's embarrassing!
Is she... getting turned on?
Sensei, please stop!
It feels strange.
How does it feel around here?
Her clit is completely hidden.
If I flip this here...
It's that tingling sensation again!
Sensei.
It feels amazing...
S-Stop, sensei...
Oh, no. At this rate...
No. I'm gonna pee again!
Wow, all in one go.
But, damn.
After seeing something like this,
I can't control myself.
I've taken it this far, so I may as well...
Sensei?
Sensei!
No, don't lick it!
Don't suck on it!
Her clit is tiny.
She seems sensitive here so I'll focus on it.
W-What are you...
It's so small!
Would my finger even fit?
Sensei, don't!
Don't stick your finger inside!
It feels tingly inside.
No, sensei, stop!
Oh, no. I did it again.
I'm exhausted.
Sensei?
Konoka-chan, I'll put it in slowly, okay?
Sensei.
Since you're this wet, it'll be fine.
It went inside me!
It's soft, even though it's tight.
Sensei!
This is amazing.
Her pussy is wrapping around my dick.
No, not there!
His dick is thrusting in so deep.
Her body is so soft and light...
It's almost like she's a doll.
No, sensei. Don't move so much!
I'm having sex with Sensei!
Holy shit! It feels amazing!
Do soft, tight pussies always feel this good?
Sensei...
Sensei! No more, please!
If you keep thrusting...
Your pussy feels so fucking good!
I can't hold back anymore!
No, don't.
N-No! Not there!
I can't! I can't!
My body's going numb.
It's so tight. I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna let it all out inside you!
Konoka... Konoka, Konoka!
Sensei.
Here it goes. I'm cumming!
It's coming out... inside me.
There's no space inside your vagina,
my semen's flowing out.
S-Sensei!
Y-Yes?
Can you please keep what happened today a secret?
O-Of course.
It'd be embarrassing if everyone found out I peed myself.
it's a secret
translator: nyanpasu
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent