small insides
Every summer, I go over to my cousin's to hang out.
Hey, how are you?
Dad seems to always have a lot of fun because
he can drink as much as he wants, but...
Since I can't drink, I don't really
get what's so great about it.
Even so, I do have something to look forward to.
And that's hanging out with my cousin, Ta-kun.
Hey, Naho-chan.
Nice to see you.
Not only does he help me with my homework,..
It's hot today, huh?
Looks like you worked up quite a sweat,
why don't you take a bath first?
...but he's also a really nice guy.
Tatsuya-kun, as always, thanks for playing with her.
It really helps out.
Mom! Stop treating me like a child!
It's no problem at all. Please enjoy yourself.
He's a really nice guy.
So, Naho-chan, let's enjoy ourselves too.
it's a secret
Really?
I can't believe it.
Ta-kun...
Don't be so rough...
Sorry, did it hurt?
No, but...
It just feels kinda weird.
That's just proof you're becoming
more and more of a pervert.
I'm not that perverted!
It doesn't look like you've realized it,
but your nipples are getting more sensitive.
They're so soft and springy.
Not to mention, that sweet smell of a
girl you have, fresh out of the shower.
Ta-kun...
This is great!
Now, I've played with your nipples enough.
Next up is your pussy.
Ta-kun, are we doing that again?
Don't you like being licked, Naho?
Well...
Come on, open your legs.
Spread your pussy.
Naho, your pussy's small and pink, it's so cute!
No matter how many times I look at it, it's always beautiful.
D-Don't look at it so much...
I'm actually not good at handling it when he's licking me.
It's already getting wet.
Whenever he licks me, I start feeling really weird.
I don't know what to do with this weird feeling.
Your clitoris is really small too!
Looks like you get aroused with your clit,
but not so much from your actual pussy.
Ta-kun... that's...
I'm starting to lose control of myself too!
Naho, could you lick mine too?
I can't hold on any longer.
Yeah, just like that. Point your ass this way.
What a great view!
Ta-kun's dick is so big!
I can barely fit all of it in my mouth.
It feels really good, Naho.
And then,
when I lick the... tip?
His dick starts to throb like crazy.
I guess it feels good?
I'll make you feel good too, Naho.
Ta-kun!
You're dripping wet already!
No, don't be... so rough...
Naho, aren't you forgetting something?
I feel so weak...
No, don't...
Your pussy seems like it's wet enough. That means...
No, I'm going to cum!
You came so much.
Wow, you've gotten so wet.
No more...
Well, this is good enough, I guess.
How I about I keep going for a bit?
I just came again!
Ta-kun... No... Don't...
You're cumming again. I can tell
from how your body is shaking.
No...
Your pussy's so tight!
No... Don't...
Now that you're this wet, it should be okay, right?
Hey, Naho-chan, let's do something
even more amazing today.
More amazing?
I'm going to put my dick inside you.
This way, we can both play.
There's no way your dick will fit!
Don't worry, it's fine!
You're so wet that it'll just slide right in.
His dick is throbbing like crazy!
If it hurts, will you take it out?
Of course! I promise.
Looking again, it really is small, isn't it.
Will it really fit?
Do it gently, okay?
First, get it all lubed up.
Shit.
I really don't think it'll fit.
I'll do it, even if I have to be rough...
Make sure that I get it right at the entrance, then...
It's going in.
Then push it in all at once, and...
It went in!
No...
Don't worry. The more I move, the
sooner you'll get used to it.
Don't mo...
Ta-kun...
Every time I move, my dick keeps gets wetter.
This feels amazing!
So this is what her pussy feels like?
His dick is going into my stomach!
I'm starting to feel tingty down there!
It's coming into my stomach...
At first, I didn't like playing with him...
Ta-kun, this is embarrassing!
Naho, don't you like being stared at?
See? You're wetter than usual.
Don't touch it...
Ta-kun...
It's so big and it's going in so deep! No...
Sometimes, we'll have sex in the park at night
and he'll put a collar, or handcuffs, on me.
You're getting tighter, so I guess you're feeling good, huh?
I started looking forward to our summer play dates.
I like it deep inside me!
I love it!
If you like this then you've become quite
the perverted girl, haven't you?
It's not my fault! It's all because of you!
It's reaching in deep inside me...
I always look forward to what kind of things we'll do next.
Maybe next week we'll try anal.
A-Anal?
N-No, it's so hot...
No...
It feels so good!
My clit and my ass are going crazy...
See? You feel good with your ass now too, right?
My ass is...
No...
Don't be so rough!
I wonder how were going to play next week.
You guys got here late!
Sorry, there was just so much traffic.
We've been waiting forever.
Hey, there.
So, what should we play today?
it's a secret
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: bis | punk4real