On Weekends, I usually hang out at cousin's place.
It looks quite fun with Dad and the others merrily drinking,
but for someone who can't drink, I won't really know.
However,
there is something fun for me to enjoy here as well.
It's to always be able to meet with my cousin Ta-kun.
Come on in, Naho-chan.
H-hello.
He looks after me with my studies.
Quite hot, isn't it?
You look sweaty, why don't you take a bath first?
He is a very nice person.
Tatsuya-kun, thank you for always getting along with her.
It's a big help for us.
M-mom!
I told you not to treat me like a kid!
Oh, it's nothing
Just make yourselves comfortable.
He's a very nice person.
Now, Naho-chan,
why don't we play as well?
Secret
♥
Play
Secret
♥
Play
Ta-kun...
Stop sucking on me like that.
Oh, sorry about that.
Did it hurt?
It doesn't hurt... but...
It feels somewhat weird.
That's the sign of you slowly loving sex.
I'm... I'm not a sex lover!
She may not be aware of it,
but her nipples are slowly becoming more sensitive.
It feels great to touch and pinch!
Plus, with her body's feminine tenderness and sweet scent...
I'm loving this!
Alright, that's enough for your breasts.
Why don't we play 'lick' on your pussy next, then?
Ta-kun... are we doing that again?
You like being licked too, right?
Well...
Alright, spread your legs,
and open your pussy.
Naho's pussy looks so petite and pink, it's very cute!
It looks so beautiful no matter how many times I gaze at it.
D-don't stare so much.
I'm actually not too comfy with being licked, though.
It's already so wet.
I start to feel very weird whenever he starts licking me there.
This very weird feeling is what I'm not comfy about.
Her clit is also very small.
Looks like she's getting aroused normally at her clit.
I wonder if she's starting to get aroused inside yet.
Ta-kun... that's...
Now I can't hold back any longer.
Naho, can you lick mine too?
I can't hold it any longer...
Yes, that's right.
Position your butt here.
What a great view!
Ta-kun's dick is so big.
It completely fills my entire mouth.
That feels so great, Naho.
If I lick the base of its head...
will it feel good?
It starts to twitch.
Is it feeling good?
I'm going to make you feel good too, Naho.
Ta-Ta-kun!
It's completely drenched now.
Oh no...
Please... don't suck it that way...
Naho, you must continue licking.
I'm feeling weak.
S-Stop...
Looks like it's about loose enough already.
Well then...
D-Don't!
It's coming!
She actually ejaculated vaginally.
She really made it wetter than wet.
No more... please...
This is already enough... but...
H-he's done it!
Stop... Ta-kun!
She came again.
Her entire body is twitching.
No...
She's wrapping really tight.
S-stop...
Stop...
If she's this wet, then I guess it's okay, right?
Naho-chan,
why don't we do something even more amazing today?
Amazing?
I'll put my dick inside your pussy.
In other words, we'll play 'fuck'.
Your dick can't fit inside!
It's okay, don't worry!
It's already this wet, so it will go in smoothly.
His dick is pulsating.
Will you stop if it hurts?
Yup! I promise.
It really is small, looking at it again like this.
I wonder if I can put it in.
Do it gently.
Lubricate it well.
Damn!
It really won't fit.
Might have to push it a bit.
Line it properly with the opening...
It's... going in...
And then give it a sudden push!
It went in!
It's alright, you'll soon get used to it once we get moving.
Stop moving!
Ta-kun...
It gets even more slippery inside as I move!
It feels so good!
So this is how Naho's pussy feels like.
His dick, it's moving in and out of me!
I'm starting to feel tingly all over.
It's pumping inside me...
It started as a game at first.
Ta-kun... this is embarrassing.
You like being exposed, right?
See you're a lot wetter than usual.
No... touching!
Ta-kun...
Please don't push it so deep inside me.
Now we're having sex with me wearing only cuffs or collars at the park at night.
Looks like you're starting to feel aroused inside as well.
I eventually started longing for weekends.
I love it deep.
I love it deep inside!
Getting horny by being fucked at the entrance of your womb,
You really have become a naughty girl, Naho.
It's not my fault.
It's your fault!
It's pumping deep inside me.
I wonder how we're going to do it next?
Why don't we try some anal next week?
Anal?
Not both my clit and my butt!
Naho-chan, you can also get aroused with your butt now?
That's not true, pull it out already!
What are we going to play next week?
Come on in.
Now then,
what are we going to play today?
Secret
♥
Play
Secret
♥
Play