I always go to my cousin's house to play during the weekends.
My parents seem to have a lot of fun because they can drink as much as they want.
As someone who can't drink alcohol yet, I don't know what's so fun about that.
But, there's one thing I always look forward to.
It's that I can meet my cousin Taa-kun.
Come in, Naho-chan.
H-hello.
He also helps me with my homework.
It sure is hot.
You've sweat a bit, want to take a bath together first?
Taa-kun is super kind.
Thanks for always taking care of her, Tatsuya-kun.
You're a great help.
M-mom! Don't treat me like a child!
Don't even mention it. Please have fun.
He's super kind.
Well then, Naho-chan.
Let's go have some fun.
T-Taa-kun
If you suck it like that-
Oh sorry, does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt but...
It feels strange.
That's the proof that you're slowly becoming a lewd girl, Naho-chan.
I'm not that lewd.
She doesn't realize it herself but, it seems that she's become able to feel it through her nipples a bit.
All squishy and stiff.
And the girl-exclusive softness and faint sweet scent.
T-Taa-kun.
I can't get enough of this!
Let's leave your tits aside and move on to pussy licking play.
Taa-kun...
Are you going to do that again?
You like being licked, don't you Naho.
U-Uhm.
Come on, spread your legs.
Open your pussy.
Naho's pussy is so small and pink, it's super cute!
No matter how many times I see it, it sure is pretty!
D-don't look so much.
Actually I'm bad at being licked.
It's already a bit wet!
I start feeling really strange when I'm being licked.
I don't know how to handle this strange feeling!
Her clitoris is also really small.
She seems to be feeling it through her clit, but I wonder how it is on the inside.
Seems like I can't hold myself in any more either.
Naho, could you lick mine too?
I just can't wait anymore.
Like that.
Point your butt towards me.
What a great view!
Taa-kun's penis is so big...
It's filling up my entire mouth.
It feels great, Naho.
If I lick this "head" part...
His penis goes up and down.
I wonder if it feels good.
I'll make yours feel good too, Naho.
T-taa-kun.
She's soaking wet!
Naho, don't stop licking.
I can barely move my body.
The inside is a lot less tight now, so...
N-no, I'm going to cum.
Wow, she squirted a bit.
N-no way.
This should be sufficient, but..
Let's loosen it up a little bit more!
I came!
N-no
Taa-kun
She's cumming again, her body is shaking.
No...
It's so tight!
If she's this wet, it should be fine right.
Naho-chan, let's try something even more amazing this time.
Something amazing?
I'm going to put my penis in your pussy.
It's never going to fit!
Don't worry! If you're this wet, it'll fit easily!
His penis is bouncing up and down.
If it hurts, you'll stop right?
Yeah, I promise!
Looking at it again like this, it's really small!
I wonder whether it'll fit?
Go slowly...
Properly lube it up..
Shit.
It won't fit!
I'll have to force it a bit.
Line it up with the hole.
And then in one go...
It went in!
No.
Don't worry.
You'll get used to it after I move a bit.
It feels more wet every time I move!
This feels amazing!
So this is Naho's pussy!
His penis is inside of me!
It makes my pussy feel all tingly.
Something's coming out...
I didn't like it at first but...
Taa-kun, this is embarrassing.
You love it when I put it in like?
Look, you're more wet than usual.
Don't touch it...
Taa-kun...
Something deep inside me.
At the park during the night, we had sex using things like collars or handcuffs..
You seem to be completely feeling it on the inside now too.
And like that I started looking forward to the weekends.
Deep.
I like it deep.
Feeling it through your womb, you've really become a dirty girl, Naho-chan.
It's not my fault, this is because of you!
I wonder what we're going to do next time.
Let's try it with your butt next week.
My butt?
My butt and my clit, n-no.
You're able to feel it through your butt now too? Naho-chan.
I wonder how we are going to play next week?
Come in!
Well then, how do you want to play this time?