We're back!
That Takashi, he never changes.
This time it was Sayama-sensei, a trainee teacher.
I can't believe he confessed to an engaged woman.
Everyone's grown up within a blink of an eye.
Seems like he's desperate.
Even my childhood friends have grown up
so well that I can't keep my eyes off them.
To be honest, I can't even count how
many times I've wanted to do them.
Those sweet "little sisters" of mine.
I'm gradually losing my self control because of them.
So it was all about her enormous breasts?
This pervy idiot brother!
My little friend is already at his limits!
And now, I'm finally going to...
...cross the line!
Milk White Moan
Leave a man's mark on my childhood friend
No...
Stop...
Don't be so rough.
Don't...
Your tits are so lewd.
How rude!
I'm not a pervert!
Geez...
You were only supposed to touch them a little.
Ok, enough of this.
You only told me to help you practise a little
because you had never touched ti...
...that you had never touched a woman's breasts.
I pitied you a bit since you had been rejected, so...
Tiiits!
I guess a little fondling will be ok.
H-Hey!
S-Stop it!
Don't take it off, you idiot!
H-Hey...
I told you to stop.
Don't tease me there!
No, don't...
Stop licking me there.
No, not the nipples...
Don't bite them!
Stop!
H-Hey...
They are hard now, so if you keep licking them...
No, don’t...
Your voice...
It'd be bad if Mikami heard us.
Hey, it's all your fault!
Stop teasing me, you idiot!
M-My nipples...
They...
Don't touch them so much.
My tits, my nipples, they...
S-Stop it.
I'm starting... I'm really starting to lose it!
I wonder if she's consoling him.
Idiot brother.
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Show me yours too!
It isn't fair that the only thing being played with are my boobs!
Besides, don't drag a girl to bed if you just want to relieve yourself!
Am I really this pathetic?
Well, I don't see you as a man, anyway.
You... You're nothing special.
You're not really athletic.
Your grades aren't that good.
And you're not even kind.
Plus you're quite the womanizer.
What are you looking at, you pervert?
It's payback time.
You think you can just tease someone's nipples like that?
Show some repentance at least.
If you like breasts so much then I'll do it like this!
Don't misunderstand me.
It's not like I like you or something.
Sayaka!
You're letting out such a pitiful voice.
Does it feel this good?
Idiot brother!
I'm entering!
Sayaka-chan, are you still...
Mi-Mika-chan!
Hey, don't take them off!
You're so wet, Sayaka.
Don't tell me swallowing it got you that excited?
It's not like that, you idiot!
No, don't...
But you're so hard up here.
Hey...
Stop it.
This one's also hard.
My pussy...
Take it out already!
But it feels so good inside you, Sayaka.
Don't thrust it so violently.
Stop it already or I'm really going to...
Hey, don't do it so fast.
Oh God, it's hitting me so deeper.
Hey, what's with this position?!
I've told you to stop, haven't I?
You're being too rough!
I'm really going to get you back for it later!
No!
No, not there!
Wh-What are you doing!
You've already come inside me.
What I am doing right now is...
You're still pouring it into my pussy!
Don't!
I've decided!
What?
I'll make you belong only to me, Sayaka!
What the hell are you talking about?!
No, stop! Don't plunge it into me anymore!
At this rate I'm also going to cum!
If you cum so much inside me...
...I'm really going to become pregnant!
I'm cumming!
Oh no!
Sorry.
Sayaka, I...
Don't try to apologise now, you idiot.
No, not that...
Shall we do it one more time?
What?!
Geez...
I can't believe we ended up doing it until morning.
You idiot.