Mika
Don't
Enter
Without
permission!
That sweet scent...
Mika's still out after she ran away, huh.
She says she's still at a delicate growing age.
But things might get perilous if she keeps roaming around looking like that.
Wait, perilous? Delicate age...?
She says she doesn't have a home that she can go to.
Misters, take care of her please?
Hey Mika, why don't you smile some more?
It'll feel good soon, you know.
It feels better without the condom, right?
The night is still young,
I'll make sure to keep cumming until I impregnate you, Mika-chan.
Nah, that can't be.
True, I was also quite tactless at the time,
but it's her fault for being so defenseless!
Just how many times has she unwittingly swayed my morality, huh?!
Milk Withe Moan
Chichiiro Toiki
Part 2: Dear brother, show your sister your dignity!
Aw jeez! I'm really pissed off!
I've always thought of him as the worst fool, but...
Impossible! My idiot brother!
This is really the worst.
What are you doing out there? You'll catch a cold.
W-Why are you here?
I was searching for you. Let's go home.
Then go home by yourself.
I refuse to accept that I'm living under the same roof as some pervert!
Hey now...
If... If that's how it's going to be...
W-Wait, are those my...?
Then I shall really become a pervert!
Give them back to me!
Let me go!
You also hate me too, right?
You've been avoiding me at home lately, haven't you?
Well, that's...
W-What?
Because you're about to lose your sense of reason if you didn't?
How big of a pervert are you really?
And because of that, I...
Come a bit closer.
What am I even getting mad about?
It's gotten a hit hard.
Is it because I touched it?
Kiss me.
Huh?!
Or...
Maybe you want to try and compare?
Mine and Sayaka-chans...
Do whatever you want.
Onii-chan...
Why are you...?
You see, even as a kid I've never been the type to make friends at school.
But back then, you were there, right?
You even said you'd take me as your wife, so...
Jeez, it feels embarrassing when you do that.
No, not there...
I already said no...
Don't just keep on sucking my breasts.
Stop, this is enough already for today.
Wait, I said no...
Onii-chan...
Jeez, the way you fondle them is very erotic.
I want to cum with your breasts.
T-This position...
This is really lewd.
If this continues, I...
Hey, stop that already.
I...
I didn't take a bath yesterday.
This is really embarrassing.
Jeez,no...
Not there!
Really, I really don't want this.
Stop this already.
The two of us will be thought of as perverts.
Don't suck too strongly, I'm starting to moan loudly.
Someone might come!
Oh no, I'm starting to feel really horny.
No...!!
No, don't look!
This is realty embarrassing!
No...
I just... peed in front of you.
Even then, your thing is still...
You really are a pervert, Onii-chan.
I am, and that's exactly why I can't hold myself back anymore.
Because I've now seen your cute side.
No!
And I'm craving to see it more.
It's... It's all the way inside.
My head's starting to go blank.
Let's stay like this for a while.
It's okay.
Just move, Onii-chan.
Wow, your insides are really wet, and it's sucking me in!
Oh no, I can hear the loud sloshing sounds.
Someone might hear these embarrassing sounds!
No...
It's going really deep inside.
Your thing is starting to get even bigger.
Please try to go in even deeper!
Not just these lewd sounds...
I want to see your lewd face as well.
No...!
Oh no, I think I'm really starting to become perverted.
Onii-chan, come inside.
More...
I want to feel even more pleasure, Onii-chan!
Make a mess of me more!
Oh no...
Onii-chan, you just came and yet...
Amazing, it's twitching wildly.
Are you cumming again?
Are you about to cum inside again?
You can't, if we don't use a condom...
We don't need it.
Because I'm going to make you mine!
There... Amazing...
Onii-chan, it's going really deep.
I love you.
I love you very much.
It's Okay, just cum.
I want to become yours completely.
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum too.
Hey Onii-chan, so how was it really?
Did it feel better with me or Sayaka-chan?
What?
Oh, so what is it that we are comparing?
I would really love to hear about it.
Why did you just...?
You are the one who just barged in here, you know!
You pervert!
Onii-chan, are you alright?