I still have to finish my shift, and yet...
My fingers just won't stop.
I'm a nurse, and an emergency might spring up any minute.
Why...? I have to go already.
Im... about to cum!
I'm going to cum!
Something big's welling up inside!
Oh no, I'm about to cum during work!
I'm cumming!
Yoshimoto-kun from the electronics store?
Why are you here at this hour?
Laying off your important job of handling
emergencies for some quick schlicks?
Toyomori Ayase.
Th-This is...
Hey, what did you just take a picture of?
Erase that!
Stop that ruckus.
Well, I could erase it.
On one condition.
C-Condition?
You're kidding, right?
With just one search, anyone will be able to
find your masturbating wonder online.
So you'd better obediently do as I say.
And what would that be?
What are you planning to do?
Why sex, of course.
Are you serious?
I am.
If you know that much already, then just give me your pussy.
I can't just do that, you know.
Stop fooling around and just erase that image!
Here, take a look.
You understand now how serious I am, yes?
I see.
I had a good impression of you before.
I never knew you were such a demon.
I'm disappointed.
Finally giving up, eh.
If you ever do something weird,
you can be sure that this image will
be all over the entire hospital.
I-I would have to quit working here if that happens.
I see you already get it.
Now spread your legs and gimme your pussy.
Why is this trash.
Alright, but...
Put this on.
I really can't have you refuse this one.
Alright already.
Jeez, this is the worst.
For our masturbating nurse to actually put a
condom she's been carrying around on me.
This really makes me happy.
There's no telling what will happen in the wards.
But you, out of all possible people.
Is this okay?
Now, tear off your stockings and straddle me.
Put it in and fuck yourself.
You pervert.
So this is how my virginity ends, huh.
It hurts, it hurts!
Good for you, having lost your virginity with my great dick.
You trash!
As expected of your virgin pussy, it's so tight.
It's like it's sucking in my dick each time it moves.
It feels the worst here.
It hurts so much, that I'm about to faint.
Just cum and end this already.
With your pussy squeezing me like this? Not just yet.
Let's enjoy this all night.
It'd never feel good with someone whom I don't even like.
It's only physiological reactions.
You even got your nipples so hard here.
You sure loved playing with your pussy.
Don't just ignore what I said.
You're letting out such tender moans now.
I see, being fucked feels a lot better.
It hurts! My wound is being pierced!
It feels so good even with the condom on.
I might just cum right away.
Then just cum already.
Just release your cum!
You don't have to tell me to cum.
Oh no, it's squirting hard inside.
Here's your much awaited cum.
I'm not done yet!
So hot.
The condom might just rip open with this much cum.
Stop, no, please, pull it out!
It's over.
The condom?
What's with this amount?
Good, it's not torn open.
It's different than earlier.
You're not wearing a condom!
No, pull it out!
So this is your raw pussy, Aya.
It's on a completely different level.
It's bigger than earlier, and it's getting even bigger!
What in the world is this? I've never felt a dick like this before.
Finish it already.
My thing down there is starting to lose it.
You don't have to tell me to cum!
It feels so good... that I'm about to squirt it all inside!
So big, this is impossible!
No, not inside.
You mustn't cum inside me!
You mustn't!
Then I'll cum it all inside as you wanted!
No!
No... it's still pumping into me.
My womb will get completely filled,
if you continue to cum like this.
What will happen to me now?
Hello there.
I've come for the regular inspection of the air conditioners.
Umm... Suzuki-san.
How do you feel?
Hey, don't fuck me too hard.
Will I be able to go home earlier if I do it like this?
It's poking through my throat.
You really do normally cum this much, huh.
Hey, your job is over there, you know.
He's been cumming inside me every single day.
So I've gotten used to this, huh.
Jeez, why do I have to wear something like this?
Whoa, the way you open it like that doubles
the erotic levels of that two piece.
Hey. That's dirty.
No, I'm unable to resist.
We're going to have lots of anal sex this time,
so I need to properly loosen it up.
Why are you licking it like that?
Don't wriggle your tongue like that.
My asshole's going to get penetrated.
He's only been licking my ass.
I'm starting to feel all tingly with his teasing.
Are you really going to put it in my ass?
No, this dick is giving me an enema.
More! Squeeze my dick more!
Your dick feels good.
It's fast.
I'll lose it if you keep drilling it in like that.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming with my ass.
Why?
Why did you pull it out?
Now I'm really itching to cum.
Please, put it in alraady.
Aya,
if you really want to feel even better,
then you'll have to become my private nurse.
P-Private?
Yes.
You'll become my slave,
and will keep on having sex with me even if you get pregnant.
You can't live without a dick anymore
at this point anyway, right?
I'm...
I'm not just about to be.
I will!
Please impregnate me with your dick!
Master!
Well said!
Feels good, right?
Women feel the happiest when they're being fucked!
I'm happy, so happy that even my
brain is acclimating to your dick!
I can't survive without having your cum!
Your dick, your dick!
I love your dick, I really love your dick!
I totally love your dick!
Pleasure my pussy more with your dick!
I'll make sure my pussy rubs it really well!
Let's make a healthy baby.
I'll bear your child for you.
I'll wear whatever you want me to wear.
So, are you going to cum inside?
Cum inside me.
Make my pussy cum with your cum
I'm going to cum lots inside you.
So become pregnant!
I'm going to cum!
I'm about to cum as I get cummed inside!
Fill every gap of my womb with your seed!
Oh wow.
I'm going to lose my mind with this.
Cumming as your slave is the best.
Please release your rich seed for me, Master.
Give your hot cum to me, okay?
Your dick is getting really stiff.
Please cum lots.
Share it properly now.