I know I need to get ready for my shift,
but my fingers just won't stop!
There's an emergency case, but I'm masturbating.
I need to hurry up and cum!
I can feel it! I'm gonna cum!
It's coming! I'm gonna cum so hard!
Oh no, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum at work!
I'm cumming!
Uniform of Disgrau
02 The Third Prey
Aren't you Yoshimoto-kun, the electrician?
Why are you here at this hour?
Toyomori Aya-san, your patient is dying,
and yet, you're masturbating?
Th-This is...
Hey, you took a picture of me?! Delete it!
Don't make a fuss! I don't mind deleting it,
but I have some conditions.
C-Conditions? You're kidding, right?
Well, if you don't play along,
I could just upload this picture onto the internet.
I think it’d be better if you listened to me.
What are you planning on doing to me?
Sex!
Are you serious?
Yeah, I am! If you understand,
then be a good girl and show me your pussy!
You really think I would?
Stop messing around and delete it already!
Here, look. Now you know I'm serious, right?
I see. I always thought you were a good person,
but you're just a perverted freak.
I'm disappointed in you.
Finally giving up?
If you try anything funny,
I'll send this picture to every single person here.
I-If you do that, I'll have to quit.
If you can think about the consequences,
then you better spread your legs.
Why do I have to have sex with scum like you?
Fine, I get it. You'll have to wear this, though.
I won't let you do it otherwise.
Okay, okay.
Geez, this guy is the worst!
I'm so happy a nurse who masturbates
at work is putting a condom on for me.
You don't know what could happen at a hospital.
I can't believe I'm doing it with
such a disgusting person like this.
Is this good?
Well then, tear your stockings and get on top of me.
You're gonna put it in and move by yourself.
You perverted freak.
This will be how I lose my virginity?
It hurts! It hurts so much!
You have a nice, juicy cock
to take your virginity, how nice!
You perverted piece of shit!
The tightness from your virgin pussy is amazing!
Every time you move,
it feels like you’re gonna take my cock with you!
I hate it! It hurts so much I could faint!
Hurry up and get it over with! Cum!
Should you be saying that when
your pussy is gripping my cock so tightly?
Let's play until the sun rises.
There's no way I'd feel good from
doing it with a guy I don't even like.
It's just a normal reaction from the human body.
Your nipples are getting so hard, too.
Your pussy feels so soft. It feels great!
Listen to what I'm saying!
Oh? What a sweet moan you just let out.
So that's how it is. You like being attacked.
That hurts! You're gonna make it worse!
Even with a condom on, it feels so good,
I think I'm gonna cum already!
Hurry up and cum, then! Let out your cum, jerk!
If you're gonna be like that, then I'll cum for you!
No, I can feel it gushing out inside of me!
Take that! It's the semen you
wanted so badly. I'm not done yet!
It’s so hot! If you keep cumming this much,
the condom's gonna break!
Stop! No, take it out!
It's over. What are you going to do with the condom?
What? There's so much.
Thank goodness, it didn't break.
No!
It feels so different! Wait, stop!
Put a condom on! Take it out!
This is what your raw pussy feels like, Aya?
Doing you raw is so much better!
It's even bigger than before! It's still growing, too!
What is this?! I've never seen a penis like this!
Hurry up and finish! You're gonna break my pussy!
You don't have to tell me that.
I'm gonna cum very soon!
It feels too good! I'm gonna cum in your pussy!
You're kidding! You're kidding, right?!
You can't, you can't cum inside me! No!
I'll flood your pussy with my cum,
just how you want it!
No!
You're still cumming! If you cum so much in me,
I'm gonna... My womb is flooding!
What's going to become of me?
Good afternoon.
I came to check up on the air conditioning system.
Suzuki-san... how are you... feeling?
Hey, don't be so rough.
You can get this hard so quickly?
You're shoving it so deep down my throat!
You always cum so much.
Hey, palpation is part of my job.
I'm so used to letting him cum inside me every day.
Hey, why am I in this outfit?
If you spread your pussy,
the outfit is a million times sexier.
No, that place is dirty!
No, I feel so weak!
I'm going to play with your ass today,
so I need to make sure to loosen it up.
What do you mean by that?
What are you going to do?
Don't move your tongue like that!
You're gonna split my ass in two!
He's focusing on my ass. It's like he's teasing me
and it's making me feel weird.
It's really going to go in my ass.
No! You're examining my ass with your dick!
More! Squeeze my dick and make me feel even better!
Your dick feels so good!
You're moving so fast! I'm going to lose to your dick!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum with my ass!
Why? Why did you take it out?
You just made me want your dick more!
Hurry up and put it back in!
If you want me to keep fucking you,
then you'll have to become my personal nurse.
P-Personal?
That's right. You'll become my slave.
We'll have lots of sex, and you'll get pregnant.
You're already at the point where
you can't live without my cock, right?
I...
I won't become your slave...
I'll do it! Impregnate me with your seed, Master!
Well said!
Feels good, right? Having a dick shoved
into their pussy is a woman's happiness!
I'm so happy! It feels like my mind is being
filled with nothing but your dick!
I can't think of anything but your semen! Dick! Dick!
I love it! I love your dick! I love your dick so much!
Make a mess of my pussy!
I'll take the whole length of your cock!
Let's make a healthy baby!
I'll get pregnant for you.
I'll service you with my pussy,
so cum inside, okay? Make me orgasm from it!
I'll let out lots of cum inside you! Get ready!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum from being impregnated!
Fill me up with your semen!
Oh my god, this is amazing.
I’m gonna lose my mind. I love being a sex slave.
Please cum for me soon, Master.
Please give me your hot semen!
Your dick is getting so hard.
Give me lots of your semen!
Be good girls and share, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч