I'll be coming home late today.
Be sure to keep the doors firmly locked, Akemi.
I understand.
Oh, Yoshimoto-san.
Good morning.
G-Good... morn.
You're still in your jersey's at this late hour?
You really are such a creep.
Seiji-san, you shouldn't say things like that to our neighbor.
Well, sorry if my husband was rude.
No, it's nothing.
Listen up.
Don't you dare do something weird to Akemi.
I'm really sorry about him.
I'll just have to
"apologize" to you lots later.
Thank you very much.
Oh, Yoshimoto-san!
Hello.
Thanks for fixing my TV the other day.
Don't mention it.
How is it working now?
In perfect condition.
It also helped that you sweetened the pot for me.
No, it was my pleasure as well.
And, oh yes.
I need to talk to you about something in private.
Nobody's coming here at this hour.
So, what was it that you wanted to talk about?
I want you to look at this.
No, why do you have that?
It's easy to install one of these in your TV.
No way.
You actually recorded me doing this.
I never thought someone who looks pure
like you could have such a hobby.
Your co-workers would surely be shocked.
Please don't, anything but that, please.
I beg of you!
If you're willing to do my bidding, then
I can simply forget all about it.
What do you say?
I-I... understand.
N-No, not there.
Please don't expose it like that.
You went to work not wearing any panties at all.
Even now you're a totally aroused bitch as I force you to do this.
Isn't that right?
No... your tongue is.
This isn't.
It's starting to get even wetter, see?
Do you usually masturbate while this drenched?
That's not true.
I don't even love you and yet.
Stop.
Please don't be too rough.
Don't lick me inside too much.
What? Did you really just cum with what I said earlier?
Stop, no more, please.
My mouth feels gross.
Please stop.
It'd be weird if I don't take the opportunity
to fuck this very delicious hole over here.
It's hitting my throat.
I can't breathe.
If you don't want that image to further taint your mind,
you'll have to do your best to rub my dick with your throat.
It feels tighter and tighter with every thrust!
My breath... please, no more!
If you agree to drink all of my thick cum,
I'll let your pussy off the hook today.
I'll... I'll drink it.
So please, cum already.
Here I come.
Be sure to drink every last drop, Kasumi.
It stinks.
I drank it all.
If you don't go home right away, or if you
even attempt to remove the camera,
this image will instantly be distributed.
Understood?
Yes.
I've been waiting for you, Master.
Oh, Akemi.
Looks like you're getting the hang of being
my slave now, naked apron and all.
Indeed.
My dear husband was really quite rude earlier this morning,
so I wanted to service you lots.
Please, put your dick inside my mouth pussy, Master.
So big.
So thick, so stiff, and so manly.
It also smells different than usual.
Did you do it with another woman today?
What exactly did you do?
Yeah, I've made another slave like you, Akemi.
I'll introduce you to her sometime.
For me to no longer be able to hog Master's cum for myself,
please always leave enough for me, okay?
My balls aren't as impotent as Seiji-san's, so don't worry.
Oh how wonderful.
Please mark this slave with all of your cum.
I'll make sure to squeeze every last drop out of it.
It feels great, Akemi.
I'm about to cum in your mouth!
Cum. Just cum it all inside my mouth pussy!
There's so much of your dick's love juices.
I'm home, Akemi.
Did she go out for groceries?
Oh yes, oh yes!
Your dick is just too amazing, Master!
My pussy feels really happy.
You have a husband, and yet you crave for another man's dick.
Such a slutty pussy.
I'm sorry, please forgive me for having such a slutty pussy!
Forgive me, dear.
I'm nothing but a slutty sex slave,
and I'm having immoral sex right now!
You weren't satisfied with your husband's
ministrations last night at all.
I'm really sorry, dear.
My pussy just didn't feel satisfied with your dick.
Please forgive my adulterous pussy.
I can't go back anymore.
Once I got a taste of Master's dick, I could
no longer live without his demands!
It's hard to get pregnant with your husband's dick, right?
You're going to have to bear my child!
I will.
I'm going to get pregnant with Master's child!
I'm sorry for succumbing to such a great dick.
I'm cumming, my slave pussy's about to cum!
Get pregnant!
Akemi!
So much cum.
Your husband is right over there in the other
room, and is waiting for you to come home.
Now this is a marvelous sight.
My pussy feels great.
After being sexually assualted by Yoshimoto-san,
after seeing a real dick for the first time.
My pussy just kept throbbing,
I know I mustn't, and yet I can't help but masturbate.
I want it... I want to be fucked!
Masturbating with the door completely unlocked, and
knowing that there's a hidden camera in the TV, eh.
Yoshimoto-san, th-this is... well.
You wanted this, right?
Just be honest with yourself already, Kasumi.
Your dick is really stinky.
So thick... and.
If you agree to become my sex slave,
I'll be glad to fuck that slutty pussy of yours.
I've always wanted someone to rape me.
So please, take my slutty pussy's virginity.
Please make me into your sex slave, Master.
This is the best, Kasumi.
Then I shall grant you your wish.
I'm going to rape you.
Your dick is entering me.
I've always had the hots for you.
For your virginity.
Me too, I've always wanted someone to rape me,
so I always play with my pussy every single day.
Oh wow, so this is what sex really feels like.
Your dick is completely penetrating my pussy.
It's fucking my pussy deeply.
It violates my very womb as it keeps on rubbing my clit.
Don't just move your own ass, learn
to pleasure your Master too!
Okay.
How is this, Master?
Is my pussy properly pleasuring you?
Your pussy is the best, Kasumi.
I can't believe that you were a virgin just a while ago.
Thank you very much.
My pussy is overflowing with pleasure.
This is amazing.
I'm really being violated.
It's rubbing very deep inside.
It feels better and better as it keeps fucking me.
As a reward for being honest, I'm going
to cum everything inside you.
If I get cummed inside now,
I'll definitely cum.
I'm going to get pregnant.
That's good. Be sure to give birth to a healthy baby.
Yes. I will.
Oh no, my pussy's about to climax!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm at my limit.
I'm going to cum!
It's coming.
Please, pump all your impregnating cum into my pussy!
My womb is filling with cum.
Sex feels good.
I'm expecting you to entertain me as my sex slave from now on.
Yes... Master.