Ogawa Kasumi
I'll be back late today, so be sure to
lock the doors and everything, okay?
I know.
Oh, Yoshimoto-san. Good morning.
Oh, goo... good morning.
Wearing a tracksuit at this time of day?
What a creepy guy.
Seiji-san, don't be rude to our neighbor.
Um, I apologize for my husband's rude comments.
I-It's fine.
Listen up. Don't try anything with Akemi, you got me?
I really do apologize for his behavior.
I'll be sure make it up to you later.
Uniform of Disgrau
01 Akemi and Kasumi
Thank you very much.
Oh, Yoshimoto-san, good afternoon.
Thank you very much for helping me fix my TV.
Oh no, don't mention it.
Has if been working properly?
It's been perfectly fine. You didn't even
charge me that much. Seriously, thank you.
No need to thank me, it was enjoyable.
Oh, there's something I want
to talk to you about, in private.
Okay.
Nobody's here around this time.
What did you need to talk to me about?
I'd like you to take a look at this.
Wait, how did you get this?
It's child's play to set up a miniature camera like this.
To have someone... see me like this...
It's hard to believe someone as pure
as you does these things in private.
I bet your coworkers would be surprised.
N-No, please! Anything but that! I'm begging you!
If you do what I say, then we'll have a deal.
Okay?
I will.
No, not there. Please, not there.
Please stop.
You didn't even wear panties to work. You're just
a dirty slut who gets wet from being blackmailed.
Right?!
No! Your tongue's going inside me!
Th-This can't be...
You're getting wetter and wetter.
Do you like being in this kind of situation?
No, that's not it! I don't like this at all!
No...
Stop! Don't be so rough!
Don't lick me there!
Hm? Did you just cum from being verbally abused?
Please, stop. Please don't go any further than this...
It feels really disgusting...
Please take it out of my mouth.
I'd be stupid if I didn't want to put
my dick in such a pleasurable hole.
It's hitting my throat! I can't breathe!
If you want those images kept a secret,
you'll take it down your throat!
It's hitting the back of my throat! It's going so deep!
No... Don't push it in any further!
If you drink my cum,
I'll leave your pussy alone for today.
I'll drink it, so please, hurry.
Here I go! Drink it up, Kasumi!
It stinks so much.
I drank it all.
If you go home and try to get rid of the camera,
I'll leak these pictures right away.
Understand?
Y-Yes.
I've been awaiting your arrival, master!
Oh, hey there, Akemi.
Greeting me in nothing but an apron...
you must have gotten used to being my slave.
Indeed. That man was very rude to you this morning,
so I want to service you as well as I can,
to make you feel better.
Please push your dick into my mouth-pussy, Master!
It's so hard!
It's so hot, hard and tasty.
It tastes completely different than it normally does.
Could it be that you found yourself a new woman?
You're going to make me jealous!
Yeah, I made a new slave today.
I'll introduce you to her next time.
Now I won't have all of your cum for myself.
Please leave some for me, okay?
Don't worry, my balls aren't as impotent as your husband's.
How wonderful! Please, mark me with your semen!
I'll squeeze all of it out for you!
That feels great, Akemi!
Take it all in like this!
Please cum in me! Let all of it out in my mouth-pussy!
There's so much of your dick juice.
Akemi, I'm home.
Is she out shopping?
That's good! It feels so good!
Master, your dick is so amazing!
My pussy is overjoyed!
Your slutty pussy is getting this wet from
my dick even though you have a husband!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry for having a dirty pussy!
Dear, please forgive me.
I'm a dirty bitch who loves to fuck! I'm a sex slave!
Your husband couldn't satisfy you at all last night, huh?
I'm sorry, dear! Your cock doesn't satisfy me!
Forgive this cheating pussy!
Since I've had a taste of your dick,
I can't live without it or your orders anymore!
Your husband can't get you pregnant, right?
I'll impregnate you, and you'll have my child!
I will! I'll bear your child!
I want to get pregnant from your semen, Master!
I'm sorry for losing myself to this amazing dick!
I'm cumming!
My slave-pussy is going to cum!
Get pregnant, Akemi!
There's so much semen!
Your husband is already waiting for you to come home.
Oh? What do we have here?
My pussy feels so good.
After Yoshimoto-san showed me a real cock
for the first time, I've been so horny.
I know this is bad, but I can't stop playing with it!
My pussy wants, it so badly!
You were masturbating even though
you knew I was watching, huh?
Y-Yoshimoto-san... This isn't... Um...
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
Just be honest, Kasumi.
A raw dick smells so bad.
And it's so hard.
If you become my sex slave, I'll put my dick in you.
I've always wanted to be fucked by someone.
Please take my dirty pussy's virginity!
Please make me your sex slave, Master!
You're the best, Kasumi!
I'll give you just what you want.
I'll fuck you good.
Your dick's inside me!
I've been gunning for this forever.
I've wanted your virginity all this time.
I've wanted someone to fuck me like this too,
so I play with my pussy every day.
Amazing! This is what sex feels like?
Your dick is sliding in and out of my pussy!
It's making me so wet!
It's playing with my clitoris, and
hitting the entrance to my womb!
How come it's only you feeling good?
Pleasure your master too!
Yes. How's this, Master?
Is my pussy stimulating you correctly?
Yeah, your pussy's the best, Kasumi!
I can hardly believe that you were a virgin just now!
Thank you very much!
My pussy's so happy, it's pulsing like crazy!
Being fucked feels so good!
My deepest parts are being rubbed so hard!
It feels so good every time you move!
As a reward for being honest,
I'll fill your pussy up with cum.
You're going to cum inside me?
I'm going to get pregnant.
I'm definitely going to have a baby!
Bear me a healthy child!
Yes, I'll bear a healthy child!
Oh God, my pussy's going to explode!
Cum! I'm going to cum!
I'm at my limit! I'm gonna cum!
It's coming! You're going to cum inside me!
Please let it all out inside me!
There's so much cum... in my womb...
Sex feels so good.
From now on, you're going to act
like a slave and entertain me.
Yes, Master...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч