Are you buying more?
Yeah.
l have to go pick up a bag l preordered.
This one was in the print archives...
...and a mushroom design is embroidered on it....
lt's cute and original.
l placed an order in an instant.
Oh yeah!
l have to check out the new cosmetics as well.
Plus l want to see some outfits also.
l'm staying right here!
lf you really want to go, then just leave me here.
Really?
Then wait right here.
l'll probably be back in an hour or so.
What's wrong with him?
What the...
Well, l feel sorry about what l did before.
l'm not angry at you.
l'm not a narrow-minded guy who gets angry at things like this.
lt's just...
Don't you think you bought too much?
lt's not that much.
lt's my first buying spree of the season.
Even if you say that, you're still going to buy...
...some seasonal clothes and exclusive items.
lt's not funny.
Enough cosmetics for a lifetime...
Way too many accessories...
You'll never wear all those clothes.
That's what it looks like to me.
That won't be the case.
l have different interests in a particular year.
Plus...
Plus?
You know, guys are happy when girls look pretty, right?
Hey, hey.
Oh Hifumi, are you serious? ln here?
All right then...
ls that what you think about in this head of yours?
lt hurts, it hurts Hifumi!
So mean.
Jeez...
You're still cute even if you don't put on all those things.
Oops...
Did you just say something Hifumi?
l didn't hear you so can you say it again?
l won't say it.
Since you did a good job carrying my stuff today...
l shall give you a reward.
What's going on?
ls there something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Nothing at all.
No, l'm really fine.
Really?
What were you thinking, Hifumi?
l couldn't resist.
Stop...
Don't do that...
Please stop...
You don't have to do it here...
l want my reward right here.
Don't do it like that...
lf you do it like that, l'll get excited...
l'm doing my best to get you excited.
l want you to climax.
You're so mean Hifumi...
Excuse me miss, but are you really okay?
She's feeling kind of sick.
Then...
lt's okay.
She just had an attack of anemia, she'll be fine after a while.
Right, Kaede?
You should lie down.
Okay.
Hey, make me get excited too.
You know l can't do that.
Don't worry about it.
Stop it.
They'll see us.
Don't worry about it.
Out here in the city, no one will care.
Huh? What do you mean?
Nevermind.
No...
Stop it already...
Please...
l can stop if you want.
But is that what you want?
lt's getting so sticky, too.
You're so mean, Hifumi...
Start moving, Hifumi...
lf you keep teasing me like this, l'll go crazy.
l can't really move since l'm tired from carrying your stuff.
You're so mean, Hifumi...
Your cock feels so good.
You're too loud, Kaede.
What? Am l embarrassing you?
l thought people here in the city don't care what others do.
l don't want to show it to them.
What?
l'm saying l don't want to show my cute Kaede's performance to them.
lf l do this, then we don't have to worry about your voice.
What's wrong?
Something smells like chestnut flowers...
Ouch!
Man, that was a close one.
Excuse me, Kaede?
l forgot to get rid of the scent!
We concealed the sight and sound pretty well but...
How foolish of me.
Are you mad?
Well, l guess l'll hold you responsible for this mess.
There!
l'm not mad, l'm not mad at all.
l was just thinking of getting this huge tribal necklace.
What?
Legend of the Perverts 2
l'm tired...
l feel 2~3 times more tired than usual...
Um, Fuwari, what can l do for you?
What can you do?
Did those words come out of this mouth?
Ouch, ouch, ouch! lt hurts!
lt really hurts!
You're going to rip off my ear!
Ouch!
What are you trying to do?
Are you trying to kill me? You're despotic...
Well, that's what l would've thought or maybe sorta...
You did something bad, didn't you?
What kind of bad thing did l do?
l can't hear you with a voice that low.
Kaede...
Don't blame it on your girlfriend!
But l wasn't...
You were thinking about it just now.
l can easily read your thoughts.
Yes!
No matter where you are, l know everything you do!
She probably can.
Now,
do you want your punishment to be sweet and humiliating or painful?
You must be a pervert for choosing this.
But last time l chose the painful one, you ended up breaking my arm.
Ouch!
Did you say something?
This is just...
ls your cock getting hard, Hifumi?
That's because you're stepping on it...
Then maybe l'll stop...
No...
You're full of energy.
l'm really sad that my little brother is a pervert.
Look who's talking...
Not again...
Really just who is...
...the pervert?
You dominatrix wannabe...
Hey Hifumi, your cock juice is starting to show...
Sis...
This isn't good...
l'm about to come...
Let it all out.
You want to, right?
What can l say?
l was going to let you go after you licked it but...
lf you're going to resist...
Wait a minute!
This is cruel! This is abuse!
Who is it?
Hirari?
Well, well, what are you doing in that shameless position?
l don't know what was wrong with Fuwari...
but she stripped me naked and tied me down after l came home!
Can you talk some sense into her?
She's too despotic!
You're right, l should talk to her.
Fuwari is too strict on you.
Sis...
Fuwari, come out for a second!
But Sis...
Don't worry, l'll explain everything to Fuwari.
What is it sis?
Fuwari, don't pick on Hifumi too much.
Hirari, you can't let him loose.
He was getting punished!
Now hold on.
l'm sure Hifumi is sorry.
Right, Hifumi?
That's not true, right?
Right Hifumi?
Hot...
Then what?
You think l made the wrong decision?
But...
Anyway, let's continue with this inside.
The next door neighbors might see Hifumi...
...and he won't be able to get married.
Fuwari.
You shouldn't be that angry.
Kaede and Hifumi love each other.
You're too soft!
Hifumi is going to be a woman's worst enemy!
But he's already committed a crime, so we have to let him know.
Crime? That's going a bit too far.
You say l committed a crime but, what kind of crime?
lt's for indecent conduct.
You committed an act of perversion.
Excuse me? Just wait a minute.
Kaede and l are...
Listen.
You were involved in an extremely shameless act.
Your illogical, maniacal, false, morbid, and unmotivated love...
...is something that a pervert would use on a girl walking on the street.
lt's an act filled with dirty desire.
Even if you want to capture it as simple pleasure...
...it has no chance of becoming something of substance.
Do you get it?
Sis...
Are you listening to me, Hifumi?
For example...
Even if you say your love is violent, and extremely maniacal...
...and at the root of the act lies pure love...
...it's considered an act of perversion if it's not consensual!
That means you're mixing up the desires and acts of perversion...
...with the expression of your true feelings?
The difference between you and a pervert is...
...a joint fantasy of true love and...
Now, now, Fuwari.
Calm down, calm down.
lf you explain it to him with difficult words like that...
...he won't understand it.
You're right.
Let's teach him a lesson on how to express true love using sex.
Okay?
l would rather have you two show it to me than...
Sis...
l think l'll come...
Sis, Hifumi said he'll come.
l guess l'll have some as well.
Let me stick it inside!
l'll go crazy if l don't.
You have no self-control whatsoever.
Well, bon appetit!
Okay, stop right there.
Fuwari, you had lots of fun with him before, right?
So it's my turn now.
You just sit and watch.
What?
Here l come.
Your cock is so strong...
Your cock is rock hard and it's going in deep!
lt's making me scream out loud!
lt feels amazing inside you...
l can't deal with this.
lt feels good!
l'll climax!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
This time, you have to climax with me, okay?
Hurry!
lt feels indecent...
l'll climax...
l'll climax again...
l'm coming! l'll climax!
l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
You hear me?
You shouldn't do anything naughty to Kaede from here on, okay?
Yes...
Well, be nice to each other.
You two sisters are the perverts!
But we're not guys.
Legend of the Perverts 2
What is it?
Hey Hifumi.
Why are you fidgeting?
Aren't we going to do it like last time?
lt felt so much better that time than usual.
So l thought it might be nice to do it once in a while.
Hifumi?
Give me a break.
What? Why?
lt's not nice to reject a girl's offer like this!
Are you listening to me?
lt shouldn't be like that, but more like...
Nice breeze.
So deep...
Your cock feels good deep inside...
lt's deep inside and rubbing very hard...
Hifumi, don't do that...
Give it to me Hifumi!
Release it inside me!
Hey, Hifumi.
Huh?
You see...
What?
l really like you.
You idiot.
What the heck am l supposed to say to you now?
What the...
lf you don't tell her how you feel with your words...
...she'll feel nothing and dump you in an instant.
That's right.
You've always been clumsy since you were little.
l'm a little worried about you.
Don't you like me Hifumi?
What? What? What?
l just can't!
What?