Suzu, is something bothering you?
Oh, it's nothing.
l see...
But if there is, don't be afraid to talk to me about it.
Since l've been living longer than you have, l think l can be of great help.
Okay, thanks brother.
By the way, you're not going with that lady friend of yours?
Ah, yeah...
She doesn't like us to be seen in public together.
l see.
l guess it's a complicated time for you.
By the way, brother...
lt must be really hard for you to go to work early these days.
You think so?
Well it's like this.
l'm finally beginning to realize that l'm a hard-working individual.
You know, l never thought l'd hear those words from you, brother.
As your younger brother, l'm a bit relieved.
Why you...
Oh, look at the time.
Sorry...
...but if l don't catch the train at the 45th minute, l won't make it on time.
Have a nice day, brother!
ls this your bed? l don't think so.
This isn't naptime is it?
Am l right?
Or are you really so stupid that you can't even figure that out?
Of course not.
l'm sorry...
Ouch!
Go to the bathroom and wash your face!
Also these documents have errors, so make sure to fix them!
Your bed?
What do you have to say about your behavior?
My nipples are getting hard.
l'm getting my nipples hard in a place like this.
Chief Nanakase is...
...masturbating again in the office early in the morning.
My hand won't stop...
lt's moving fast...
Why do l enjoy this?
l found out about this like a month ago.
Oh man.
Why did l go home last night without finishing up my work?
The Chief is going to smack me again.
ls someone here?
Chief Nanakase...
lt feels good...
Why...
l can't stop...
l know that...
l know that l'm strict on my subordinates...
...but l'm a shameful girl that gets excited like this.
lt's coming out! lt's coming out!
Maybe l have lots of stress.
That's my tea cup...
Hey Akagane-kun, do you want to go to a bar with us after this?
Yeah, sure.
Ouch!
These are full of errors.
Work overtime and fix them!
But...
Stop complaining and do it!
Well, maybe next time, Akagane-kun.
What?
She's keeping an eye on me?
Give me a break.
Oh no!
He's such a restless loser.
Looks like he'll make more mistakes.
But...
lt's getting pretty late.
lf l have him redo all the documents, he won't make the last train.
l guess l'm being a bit too harsh.
What the hell.
You were masturbating early in the morning.
What?
How does he know?
Was he watching me?
What should l do?
What can l do?
Maybe l heard it wrong.
l'll just have to confirm that and...
Akagane-kun.
Were you watching me?
Oh, l see.
You're trying to scare me like that.
Then l'll play along.
lf you think l'm a woman who cares only about work,
...you're totally wrong.
l'll show you.
She fell asleep.
That's just great.
Well, it is early in the morning now and l did keep her here all this time.
Oh well.
You just wait.
Wait a minute...
This is bad.
l can't even get my work done like this!
Amazing.
lt's hard to believe that she's the bossy woman l see everyday.
lf someone sees me like this, then they'll think l'm a pervert.
Come on and do it.
When you do, l'll just...
She's got really nice legs...
Do l need to guide him a little further?
Go on and play with my thing more...
Keep looking at it...
Amazing!
lf she resists, then l'll just remind her of that incident.
Hurry up already!
The moment you come and attack me...
l'll take a picture of you with my cell phone and l'll make you suffer!
Just you wait, Akagane.
Everyone, throw yourselves at my feet!
Yes, Nanami-sama!
What do you think about that Akagane?
Chief Nanakase.
l haven't done this in a while.
l was dumped on graduation day...
...and nothing has happened for about 6 months.
l haven't done this in a while.
This is bad!
lt's a good thing he's stupid.
But l should go forward with the plan...
Not that big... but l like the shape of her boobs.
But then again, l guess l could enjoy this a little more.
Oh no! Did he notice?
l didn't know cute girls can feel good even in their sleep.
Stupid.
He's such a stupid novice.
Hold on...
Did he just say l'm a cute girl?
That's not fair.
l can't trick him if he says things like that.
No...
lf you do that to me...
l'll get really excited...
l'll climax, l'll climax!
Chief Nanakase?
There's a reason for all this...
What kind of reason?
How long were you awake?
From the very beginning.
You tricked me?
That's right.
That's not fair.
And don't call me chief in this kind of situation, call me by my name.
lf you don't...
Ouch!
l think we're ready now.
Did you come already?
Boys who say that kind of thing are vulgar.
Sorry.
lt's okay.
Yes, yes!
Your cock is just perfect for me!
Chief...
l mean Nanami-san...
You're really cute.
Akagane-kun, you said something similar before...
lt's just not fair...
Yes!
You know what?
You called me a cute girl before, right?
l was very happy.
Nanami-san...
l can't take it anymore!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
Are you angry?
About what?
l use your cup to catch my urine after masturbating...
...and l usually never wash it.
Sorry, it's nothing.
Just forget about it.
Allez, arrête ca...
Pas question ! Fais comme je te dis et dépêche-toi d'avoir la trique !
Mais... dans un endroit pareil, c'est impossible !
Ah bon ? Suzu-chan, tu manques un peu de motivation... Dans ce cas là, que dis-tu d'un petit coup de main ?!
Laisse-toi faire, tu vas te sentir mieux...
Je te le garantie.
Arrête, Natsune-chan !
Je arrêterai quand elle sera bien longue, là tu te branleras tout seul.
Alors laisse-toi aller complètement.
Je crois que ca vient là!
Alors, qu'est-ce qu'il y a mon petit puceau ? Tu as envie de voir ma culotte ?
Regarde, regarde...
Natsune-chan...
Qu'est-ce qui ne va pas Suzu, tu as déjà fini ?
Ce n'est pourtant que le début.
Natsune-chan n'était pas comme ca avant. Mais mes sentiments demeurent inchangés pour elle.
Peu importe ce qu'elle me fera, ca ne changera pas.
Euh... J'aimerais votre attention...
Cause toujours !
Bouffonne !
Et si la déléguée nous faisait un strip ?
Bonne idée !
Hé la déléguée, tu écoutes ?
J'étais sérieuse je te signale, allez grouille !
Arrête-toi maintenant.
Ne bouge pas d'ici, attends un peu.
Ah, j'y repense. Ne pense pas à t'échapper, j'ai ton pantalon en otage.
Ah ! Attends, Natsune-chan !
Je ne trouve pas Natsune-chan... Est-elle partie ?
Je dois récupérer mon pantalon à tout prix.
Se pourrait-il que ..?
Oui... Suzu...
C'est pas vrai...
Natsune-chan ?
Euh... Natsune-chan, je te cherchais partout. Et...
Quoi, tu peux pas regarder ailleurs ? Pourquoi fallait-il que tu me vois dans cette position ?
Euh... pardon, mais c'est que tu ne revenais pas et...
Suzu, fous le camp ! Sale lâche, tu n'as jamais rien fait pour moi alors que j'avais besoin de toi.
Attends ! Quelqu'un approche.
Non mais... ils pourraient faire attention d'éteindre les lumières quand même.
Pardon !
Suzu, sale ..!
J'avais peur qu'il nous trouve.
Evidemment!
Attends ..!
Non ! Pas ca !
Suzu, je mouille... Non ! Suzu, arrête ca !
Je sens que je vais... je vais...
Ca sort ! Ca sort !!!
Tu me fais mal ! Tu me fais mal, crétin de Suzu !
Arrête, arrête bordel !
Elle est dedans.
Je... Je me sens toute bizarre.
Ca fait mal, j'aime pas ca.
Suzu, oui ! C'est la première que je vais jouir avec un garcon.
Encore, vas-y encore plus fort !
Pardon.
Ce n'est pas grave, Suzu.
Quoi qu'il en soit, Suzu je suis désolée.
Si tu veux que je fasse quelque chose pour me faire pardonner demain...
Pardon, je n'arrive plus à te regarder en face...
Suzu...
Tout va bien, le coeur de Natsune-chan a cicatrisé ses blessures.
C'est tout ce qui m'importe.
lt's been a while since we left the house together in the morning.
Yeah, you're right.
Natsune-chan is busy today, so...
You two started going out?
What?
lt's not like that.
Oh, l see.
And how far did you get?
You can tell your brother.
Did you hold hands? How about a kiss?
Or maybe...
Are you kidding me?
l can't believe you.
Then we have to ask mom to make you some rice with red beans.
We need to celebrate you getting a girlfriend.
No, no!
Please don't do that!
l shouldn't be the only one to know about it.
You shouldn't be talking loud to your girlfriend on the phone at night.
What was her name? Nanami-san?
Suzu, you punk!
Brother, you're going to be late for work.
Then Nanami-san will scold you again.