The High School Girl
Who Was Groped, and
the Pure, Indulgent Love
They Shared After.
The High School Girl
Who Was Groped, and
the Pure, Indulgent Love
They Shared After.
part.1
This wasn't planned.
It's rush hour on the subway.
This girl always shows up at the same time.
She's cute, but...
She's a well-developed high school girl with a real sexy body.
Her tits are as huge as ever...
She's got them childbearing hips too... I want to fuck her from behind.
If she were my wife, coming home would be a real treat every day...
I'd want to rush home and make her moan every night...
I hate my job, and I'm always exhausted when I get home, but this little period of time soothes my soul...
Oops...
Wha!?
Whoa! C-Crap, my hand's touching her...
It's so soft!
I need to remove my hand!
Ah, this is insane!
This high schooler's ass... It's so freaking soft!
I'm being molested again...
How far will they go today...?
I hope he doesn't take too long... I need to hurry and get dinner ready...
Fuck. My hand's got a mind of its own...
Whoa! It's like mochi!
Wait... Huh? She's not trying to stop me?
She couldn't be a pervert, could she? No, no, of course not...
No way a cute, sweet girl like this could be...
But... but... her ass is so soft... and she smells so good.
Fuck, I can't stop myself...!
Whoa!! I grabbed her boobs!
She's getting groped by some strange office worker in the train...
And she's still just a high schooler! I-I can't make any excuses anymore...
Ah... huge... her tits are huge!
Her boobs are bulging out between my fingers...
Kids grow up so fast these days...
These are... huh? They've got to be a J-cup!
How can a teenager have tits like these!?
Wh-What the...? Why isn't she yelling?
This one isn't rough...
He's not hurting me...
And down here... Her butt's so soft and smooth.
What? This is... it's like a flood down there...
Huh? Did she just go "ahn"?
I feel a lot... stranger today than usual...
It feels... kinda good?
I'm... I'm actually having sex!
I'm having sex with the girl I'm always ogling on the train!
And she's at least a generation younger than me!
It's rape, but... Her crotch is wet, so it should be fine.
Not like I can stop now, anyway!
Th-This feels so damn good!
I'm doing it bareback! And her juices are pouring out!
This is so much better than a fuck toy!
Sh-She's so cute, but...
Her pussy is glued to my dick!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Shit! I can't cum inside her!
Wh-What's with this girl?
I can't believe she's acting like this even though it's her first time with me...
She's so cute it's erotic!
She's so sexy!
I'm so sorry!
Fuck! Fuck! What the hell did I do!? I committed rape!
I'm a criminal! Rape! I raped a high schooler! And I did it bareback!
If she gets pregnant, I'm gonna be in such a world of hurt!
It's okay.
Huh?
Well, I mean... it's not okay to force yourself onto a girl, but...
How do I say this...
I've always been an easy target. Maybe I was born under a bad star?
This sort of thing happens all the time.
People have done all sorts of awful things to me.
One time I was raped on video...
I normally don't report it, and I don't intend to today either.
Today actually... felt pretty good...
If anyone can do it with her, isn't it just sex...?
What kind of sex has she had before now?
I raped you.
Are you forgiving me!?
You really shouldn't do stuff like this though...
She's such a great girl!
Her tits are huge!
Her skin is so smooth!
She's so voluptuous!
And she's still just a schoolgirl!
I'm falling deeper in love with her!
I'm fucking her!
I'm actually fucking this amazing girl!
So cute!
Her voice is sweeter than it was before. Is she cumming again!?
She's clamping down on me...
Even slick with juices, her pussy's stroking my cock!
I can feel the sensations of her pussy walls! Is this what a high-class pussy's like!?
The volumes of her ass is amazing! It's so plump!
I'm getting an assjob!
I can't believe I assaulted a high school girl...
I guess she really was born under a bad star...
She's bewitching inside and out...
I actually brought a high school girl to a love hotel...
But this is wrong.
I raped her.
I should end this here. I'm satisfied, right?
The only people who can get a girl like this are big company men or really handsome guys... right?
Or so I thought.
Oh, hello.
Hey...
She greeted me? Why? I raped you!
Are you making something?
I'm good at cooking.
Um... so you...
want to pick up where we left off before...?
I'll be gentle again.
What the hell am I saying!?
If that's the case...
Whoa... her lips are so soft.
Well, she's soft everywhere!
Th-This is my first normal kiss...
Incredible... I-I'm melting...
Um... I didn't know kisses were so amazing...
So cute! So cute! So cute!
I feel like I've struck by lightning...
I... I can't keep standing...
Whoa, she's already like this...
This is... weird!
The others didn't do it like this! This is different!
It feels good.
It feels so good!
It's much better than when I do it myself!
Did she just cum? Already?
Just from this!?
I-I also need to make him feel good...
Would you like... a blowjob?
Oh... yeah.
Seriously!? She's offering!?
Oh, the ice cream must be melting...
But... my body aches for this man...
Dicks used to scare me, but... now I'm starting to like them.
Wh-What is this!?
She's sucking me right up to the base!
But she's so young...
Is it because she was forced to do it?
I was trained in fellatio...
This feels so good! Her tongue is wrapping around me!
Sh-Should I cum? Inside her mouth?
Idiot! I can't do that during her first blowjob....
...but I want to do it!
So good...
I feel like my legs are losing strength...
I-I'm sorry!
I remember I'm supposed to...
...show him.
I want more... I want to make this girl... feel even better!
What is this girl!? Her body's out of this world!
My dick feels so good!
It's so good... This really is different!
He feels so good! He's so gentle!
It feels... It feelsh sho good when it goesh deeep!
What's thiiis!?
No! No! I'm already gonna...
Shit! I'm gonna...!
So deep! Sho deeep...!
It's so good! It's sho goood...!!
How would you feel... about us dating?
If we do that, we can have sex as many times as you want, you know?
Ah... I'm falling for this man.
Sex is... a wonderful thing.
I... think I might be getting addicted...
I want her even more...
I want to indulge in her more!
I want to make her moan more!
I want to make her cum more!
I want his dick in me more!
I want him to fuck me more!
He's cumming inside me!
I can't believe sex is so good and fulfilling...
I can't... I can't stop.
You're gonna do it from behind now?
I can't stop fucking her!
I brought a high school girl to my place to do this!
But we're lovers, so it's fine, right?
Right!?
It just feel so good...
I just can't stop!
It feels so good. I'm so happy.
It's amazing to have such a gentle man as my boyfriend...
I'm gonna cum again.
I'm cumming! Cumming!
She cums so easily...
I want to make her feel even better!
And her body is so honest.
After cumming inside this much, there's no doubt she'll get pregnant!
I actually think I want her to have my child!
I've been dating a teenage girl for a few hours...
What the hell am I thinking!?
I see. So you live alone, Okata-san?
Yeah.
I work at a company nearby.
Ah. I'll fold these up.
Oh, sure. Thank you.
She's a great girl. The family type.
So her name is Yui-chan, huh?
She's so kind... and sexy... and erotic...
I-I can't fold these!
Just do your best!
My beloved's dick is in again.
My body is making him feel good again!
I'm so happy! I'm so glad you fuck me so much!
I love you!
So, how about a movie tomorrow? Though 5 AM is...
I just want to be with you as much as I can...
Well, I should get home soon...
I don't want dad to worry...
I just want one more k-kiss...
She's so cute...
I don't want her to go home.
I'm so hard even though we did it so much.
I'm gonna be away from this body until tomorrow...
God damn it! Her tits are huge!
I just can't stop myself!
Ah, my curfew... dad's gonna get worried...
Ah, but just a little longer... a little longer...
More... more...!
I really need to go back now. Sorry...
Th-That's fine, it is pretty late...
We really need to go on a date!
Let's go on one tomorrow!
I feel like just being close to her will make me want to fuck her...
I just want tomorrow to hurry up and get here so I can have her in my arms again...