The High School Girl
Who Was Groped, and
the Pure, Indulgent Love
They Shared After.
The High School Girl
Who Was Groped, and
the Pure, Indulgent Love
They Shared After.
part.2
Good morning.
That outfit...
I tried to pick up something men would like.
H-How is it?
It's super sexy...
She really is kind of a naughty girl...
She is in great shape...
Her body is built for childbearing!
A bunch of guys started talking to me and I had to shake them off to get here.
So, once again, today I want to...
She's so sexy-cute!
I love her!
Her submissive personality is wonderful!
And so is the feeling and smell when I hug her!
I can tell she's turned on.
There, there.
I-I can't take it any longer...
Huh...? Did you... cum?
Yes...
I've been kinda feeling good constantly since last night...
No matter where you touch me, it feels amazing, Okata-san...
I feel like I'm gonna break...
Take me somewhere...
...and fuck me, please.
Quickly...
I-I did want to fuck her, but...
Doing it right at the start of our date...?
There's no mistaking it. This girl...
This good, sweet girl...
Is an irredeemable slut!
No matter how many times I fuck her, Yui-chan's pussy feels so good!
Today is as amazing as before...
The fragrance of her shampoo...
Every time I thrust, her moans slip out...
Every little thing is turning her on... that's so cute!
I-I want to make her cum more!
Her pussy feels like it's twisting around me even more than yesterday.
It keeps squeezing my dick...
Her whole body is incredible soft!
Okata-san... I can't... hold in my voice...
I thought that we'd both calm down after doing it a few times, but...
It's causing us to heat up even more.
Everyone's eyes are glued to her...
I guess it's not unreasonable. We did just stop having sex, after all.
Yui-chan's absolutely oozing with sex appeal.
I wiped myself off, but my juices are still overflowing...
Ah, we need to hurry and find a hotel...
I want it... hurry...
Do you want it that badly, Yui-chan?
Ah... I'm... I'm sorry.
You're really a perverted girl, aren't you, Yui-chan?
Probably. I do masturbate a lot.
Do you... dislike perverted girls?
Nah, I love 'em.
To be honest, she should really be going out with a high-class guy instead of me...
But, bad men have always been attracted to her.
Is it because of her overflowing pheromones?
I'm sure that just loving her normally...
Will make her love me unconditionally!
That bed looks great for sex...
Once we get on it... his big, hard dick will...
...penetrate me and make a sopping mess out of my insides again!
Is she fantasizing about sex? Well then...
I'll fuck you so hard you won't be able to stand...
O-Okay...
I'm... I'm cumming! My head is... going blank...
I want to make her feel as good as possible!
Such a gentle kiss...
I'm gonna... die.
Go ahead. Get turned on even more.
I want to have normal, great-feeling sex with her again and again.
She's experienced nothing except rape until now!
Wow, she's quite a sight in her panties...
Ah, she's lightly cumming again.
I want to make her body and heart mine forever!
I love you... I love you.
Okata-san, I love you!
Yui-chan's doing that without being told...
P-Please don't tease me...
I can't wait anymore...
I want to slam it in right now, but... I want to make her feel better first.
You're cumming a lot, Yui-chan.
No! Shtoop! Ah'm gonna diee!
You're really enjoying this, right? You're pretty backed up...
It's coming out! I'm cumming!!
O-Okata-san...
I want you to... feel good too.
My pussy is all fired up right now...
It'll feel really good...
So... please...
Put your dick in, and... cum lots inside me!
Use my pussy as much as you want!
I am... your girlfriend, Okata-san!
Oh... Fuck, I can't hold back any longer either!
She's overflowing with all the sperm I pumped into her on the net cafe.
This feeling! High schooler pussies are amazing!
My girlfriend's pussy is out of this world!
All the sperm I pumped into her is leaking out!
Your baby juice... what a waste...
I'm pouring more right now!
Amaaashing! He keeps filling up my pussy over and over again!
I'm so happy!
I love him... I love him so much...
I want to come here every daaay!
Just how many times have I cum inside her high schooler pussy?
She's still in her teens, and her skin is so smooth.
Her tits are huge and her body is so soft...
I want to impregnate... my beloved girlfriend!
Ah! I've cum so much that my eyes are losing focus!
It feels so good!
Yui! Yui!!
Whew! I came 23 times...
We never did see that movie.
Yeah...
Still, how can you still be so energetic after cumming so much, Yui-chan?
I'm pretty resilient, you know?
I rarely even catch colds.
Yeah, I figured.
Oh, want to stop by a restroom first?
Yeah.
Wait a sec... This isn't what I came here to do!
Yes! We're having sex again!
How many times are we going to fuck today?
But... if we end up somewhere we think we can get away with it...
I get so horny that I have to do it with my girlfriend!
A-Amashiiing!
We're having such amazing sex in a public toilet stand!
It's shooo good!
I-It's completely different from when I was gangraped by bad people!
He's not tearing up my clothes, he's not sticking his dick in my butt...
He just has proper sex with me...
I love him sooo much!
How many times has he made me cum today...?
Too many to count.
I love him... I love him so much...
I want to make him feel even better...
I'm about to piss myself!
Hurry it up.
People are here. We've got to be quiet for a bit...
Did you see that 16 year old gravure idol's video?
Okay...
Oh yeah, Ayasa!
Yu... i...
Man, she's fucking hot...
Isn't she a G-cup? Her tits are huge!
I know, right?
If she made that face while sucking my dick I'd blow in five seconds!
My dick's being sucked by someone even hotter than that gravure idol...
And I'm fucking her mouth like this!
Yui-cha―! I'm cumming...
Okata-san's shooting so much into my throat...
Give me more. Let my mouth make you feel even better...
Can't you wait just a bit?
But, you make me feel so good, Okata-san...
I just want to return the favor.
I want to make you feel as good as you make me...
Ah... She's such a good girl.
She's so lovable...
Um, so...
P-Please make me pregnant...
Well... as much as you've come inside me I'm probably pregnant already.
Is that okay?
I'll... quit school and start working!
I'll convince my parents too!
I won't be a bother, so please make pregnant, Okata-san...
Let's get married and raise it together.
I love you... I love you.
Okata-san, I love you!
I want to have sex...
I want to have more sex!
I'm still young so I can bear you lots of children!
You're the best girl in the world, Yui!
I'll really do it! I'll cum deeper than ever before!
Making children was all the thirty year old man had in his mind―
Bearing the man's child was all the young high school girl had in her mind―
The pure, animalistic sex a couple has when they decide to aim for pregnancy―
Both of them longing for each other―
And slamming their sweat-covered bodies into one another!
Cum gushing like a fountain―
Pussy squeezing like a vice―
Both giving and receiving...
That kind of sex!
Amazing how we did it in the bathroom all night long...
You're too sexy, Yui-chan.
To tell the truth, I could keep going.
Where should we do it next?
Let's see... Maybe at your house?
Or an empty movie theater?
Or in the bath?
Oh, I'd like to try cosplay sex.
Gosh, Okata-san, you perv...
Let's do all of those.
Geez...
Haven't you touched me enough, Okata-san?
Your butt's so buxom I always want to squeeze it.
I'm so happy...
It's green... The light's green.
Yeah...
You still haven't given me enough sperm to make a baby.
I'm dying to give you a child, so...
L-Let's hurry and get home so we can do it again...
Oh... Oh!
She's so sexy and cute!
My girlfriend is way too sexy and cute!