It was a new pair, too...
A nurse?
What's Tokiko-san doing out at this hour?
Is her patient in trouble?
How dare you ditch your duties and treat me that way.
It's too quiet to be an emergency.
What's going on?
Tokiko-san, you really are my dick slave, aren't you?
Yes!
Wh-What are they doing?
You've gotten really good.
Next time, try it without your hands.
Okay.
This time, with my breasts.
How do you like it? Do my breasts feel good?
Can I put it between my breasts?
Why?
Why, Tokiko-san?
Here ya go.
It's so hard... and hot.
She's being so lewd.
Hurry. Shoot out your hot cum.
Shower me with your cum!
Please. I want your cum!
Okay, where should I put it?
On my face. On my face! Cover it with hot cum!
You're about to cum, right?
Cum... So much cum.
Takumi-kun, in here too.
Yes!
Yes... Takumi-kun...
your dick is so wonderful!
Yes!
Yes...
Deep... It's hitting deep inside.
Yes!
Come on, move your hips more, you dick slave.
Yes! I'm your dick slave!
I can't live without your dick!
You dirty slut.
Your clitoris is getting bigger and bigger.
You're squeezing my clitoris!
Yes, I love it. Please tease me!
Harder!
More...
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Takumi-kun, that was amazing.
Isn't it about time?
Did you say something?
Isn't it about time you left?
You don't need to come back tomorrow.
Why are you saying that?
I mean...
I'm tired of you.
No! I won't have it! Reconsider, Takumi-kun!
I'll do anything for you! So please don't talk like that!
You're really annoying.
I'm already done, so just leave.
But I...
Ah, yes.
Make Shiori-san my nurse again.
I prefer her.
Aw, what the hell is this? It's so funny!
It's really funny!
Hey, look, it's Doctor Mamiya!
Who's that?
Huh? You don't know?
She's a doctor here. She's the Chief of Medicine.
She's been on TV a lot lately.
She's young and beautiful, quite a woman.
No one is permitted up here.
And what's more, if you smoke,
you'll only prolong your recovery.
Though I guess it doesn't apply in your case,
since you've been faking your illness all along.
Would a doctor usually say that to a patient?
You aren't my patient, though.
Kitagawa Takumi-kun, I won't go easy on you.
Your father put you in here to prevent you from
spattering mud on his sparkling clean image.
Those must be the circumstances, right?
Impressive!
Your really are as good as the media makes
you out to be, Doctor Mamiya.
I guess you plan on leaking your
findings to the morning shows.
Oh dear, did I anger you?
I'm sorry.
Anger?
Which one of us?
What do you mean, "Which one of us"?
You think I'm angry?
Doctor Mamiya, you're too easy to read.
What an impudent little brat.
Yes? This is the 3rd floor ward.
This is Mamiya. Is Shiori-san there?
Ah, she's with a patient right now.
I See. Then could you tell her to
bring Kitagawa Takumi-san here?
Yes. I'll do that.
What is this? What's going on?
That kid's evil laughter is still echoing in my ears.
And besides, why did Tokiko-san
reduce herself to that?
Why is my body getting so...
Why is it throbbing?
Not here. I can't do this here!
But..
I can't stop!
More...
Oh, no.
A survey? For what?
It's just something I'm doing for research.
You shouldn't read too much into it.
A survey of boys, eh?
You thought up a pretty clever excuse.
Excuse?
Yup, an excuse. To call me in here.
You're interested in me, aren't you, Doctor Mamiya?
You sure think highly of yourself,
but I'm not interested in you personally.
Sorry to tell you that.
Huh? But I'm interested in you.
Like the color f your panties.
I have an idea.
I'll fill out your survey if you answer
some of my questions in return.
What are you saying?
This is just for research, not for play
Doctor Mamiya,
what's your favorite body type?
You're supposed to answer my
Did you masturbate yesterday?
That's none of your business.
What's your most sensitive area?
Just cut it out already!
Then here's my final question.
During all the previous questions,
did your panties get wetter?
This is ridiculous.
I don't have time to waste on your silly game.
Should I investigate directly then?
Shiori-san.
Yes, sir.
Shiori-san, don't tell me you...
I was sure the contents of that
shot would work on you.
/It couldn't be... a sedative?
I'm sorry, Doctor Mamiya,
but I can't go against my Master.
It won't put your life in danger, though.
So don't worry.
So even Shiori-san is under Takumi-kun's control?
Wow, what a big crotch,
filled with horny things.
Oh, shut up.
Huh? Even though you let us tie you
up so easily, you're being defiant.
Are you pissed?
Of course I am.
Drugging me with a sedative to
have your way with me is low.
A sedative? What do you mean?
Don't play dumb! I know what you injected me with!
But that was just a vitamin shot.
Oh, please, don't think we'd carry
around something that dangerous.
Or did you want us to inject you with that?
Jeez, what are you expecting from this?
In that case...
Here you go.
Wh-What are you doing?
I've always wanted to try this at least once.
St-Stop it!
You've had enough already, haven't you?
If you stop now, I'll let it go.
So please..
You're behaving foolishly. You need to stay still.
Shiori-san, stop it!
No, stop it! Please!
Stay still. Otherwise I might slip.
Can't you hear me? Stop it!
I can totally see your clitoris.
Please, stop it.
Not that... that important a place.
Don't touch it with that!
Oops, did that scare you?
Don't worry, I didn't cut you.
Takumi-kun, I think you went too far.
Sorry about that.
Looks like I scared you too much.
So I guess even distinguished  adults
like you can piss themselves.
How cute.
No. Don't say that!
But I guess it really is different.
A celebrity pussy.
It's the same. Are you an idiot?
Fine. I guess I'll have to investigate this further.
Wh-What are you trying to do?
Stop playing around and listen to me!
Hey, Shiori-san...
You need this thing, right?
Wait, they couldn't be...
Yes. that's what I want!
Wow, this really is "playing doctor".
Shiori-san, just think about what you're doing.
It's a bit cold. Just hold on.
It's getting spread out.
Wow, I really can see deep inside.
No! Don't look!
I can see your membranes moving.
Don't look at that!
He's looking at me.
This little brat is peeping deep inside of me!
You're so happy to be seen on TV all the time.
So what's the problem?
No!
What's happening to me?
What a lovely, horny scream that was.
You're getting wet too.
You've got such a slutty pussy.
Doesn't it embarrass you?
I'm so embarrassed I feel like I'm going to die!
He's looking at me,
but I'm getting off on it!
Oh, dear.
I'm really hard.
Hey, what should I do about this?
He intends to have me suck him off.
Shiori-san, help me please.
Yes, sir.
Why?
Why is she doing this?
Shiori-san loves my dick.
Yes, I love it. I love your cock.
Do it the way you always do, Shiori-san.
Yes.
How is it, Takumi-kun?
Great as always. I love your boobs.
I love this too.
That serious girl, Shiori-san, is...
being so slutty.
I'd never have imagined her sucking a dic before.
How lewd.
But she looks so happy.
I'm sure he's almost there.
He's probably going to cum soon.
The white... white cum...
is coming.
Hot.. and young... dick milk.
It's coming.
Well, I'd like to be cleaned now.
Yes, sir!
Shiori-san, show me your butt.
Yes, sir. Please put it in.
Shiori, you're already soaking wet from
the blowjob and the boob job.
Yes!
Takumi-kun, I want your cock.
Let me check first.
She's so wet.
How lewd.
Yes! Takumi-kun! Yes!
Takumi-kun... Takumi-kun...
I can't hold back!
Shiori-san, you're much rougher than usual.
Does it excite you to be watched?
Yes! It's wonderful.
Oh no! I'm cumming!
Not until I cum first.
It's no use. I'm cumming! I'm cumming soon!
Already? But there's still more.
It's no use. I... can't...
Hurry!
Takumi-kun just heard me.
Did you just say, "Hurry and do me instead"?
No! I said, "Hurry and get this stupid thing over with!"
You're such a bad liar, Doctor Mamiya.
There are gallons of juice flowing from your pussy.
But... But that's just..
Be honest.
You're overflowing down here.
Doctor, it's been a while, hasn't it?
B-But I don't...
No, not that.
I can't hold back anymore!
Doctor Mamiya, why don't you just ask him?
Your dick! Bury your dick in me!
Your big, your very big dick!
Bury it in my pussy.
Very well said.
I'll take my time tasting your pussy.
Please.
Hurry and put it in. I want it.
It's in, it's in. His dick is in me!
This is... This is what I wanted!
No!
My nipples... My nipples... I'm sensitive there!
Yes! Deeper... deeper! It's hitting my womb!
It's touching... Yes!
My clitoris feels so good!
It's turning me on.
My boobs and my pussy are in paradise!
This is... This is the first time I've felt this!
No! It's so hard and wonderful!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm sorry, Doctor Mamiya.
I can't hold back anymore.
Shiori-san, that's too much.
Doctor Mamiya won't be able to breathe.
Lick me harder, Doctor!
Thrust harder! Deeper and rougher!
Inside of me, please!
I want your hot juice inside my pussy!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Me too! I'm cumming!
Look at me more!
I want you to look deep into my pussy!
Then this time spread your own legs, Doctor Mamiya.
Yes. I'll spread my legs for you,
so please look inside my pussy!
Look, please, look deep.
It's full of juice.
Hey, Shiori-san, take a look at this too.
At this slutty vagina.
No! Not that.
Amazing. It's turning me on.
Shiori-san, you want to see what it looks
like to enter a pussy, don't you?
Yes.
I want to see it.
I want to see your cock enter her lewd pussy.
No! Don't watch me... while he puts his dick in.
Wow!
Amazing. So slutty, Doctor Mamiya...
N-No!
Yes! Amazing!
I'm cumming!
Yes! Me too! While being watched...
I'm gonna cum!
Hurry. Hurry and release your cum.
Just like you released it onto Shiori-san.
I'm gonna cum. I'm cumming!
Me too! Yes! Yes! I'm cumming! Here I come!
I'm cumming!!
Wow, so you've been hospitalized forever.
Yes, so it's been very boring for me
Ouch!
I-I'm sorry. I'm not very good at this yet.
Don't worry. I'll help you practice.
You really will?
But in exchange, could you teach me a few things?
Huh? "A few things"?
I'm a little behind in school.
I'm embarrassed to admit this,
but I haven't had much practice talking to girls before.
I was hoping you could help me get used to it.
I don't mind.
I'll talk to you about all sorts of things.
Thank you!
Then, could you come to my room tonight?
Sure!
Looks like something fun... is about to start again.