Do it more. Do it harder!
Stop it. You're too loud.
You don't want Takumi-kun to hear, do you?
No! Don't tease me!
What'll you do about it?
Hurry up!
Wow! Yes! I love it!
Right there! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
That's it.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Kimura-san, Takumi-kun, I have a...
Oh. shit!
I'm leaving!
I can't believe those two! Doing that
when you're right here, Takumi-kun.
T-Takumi-kun, should I take your temperature?
Hello? Takumi-kun?
Can you hear me?
Shiori-san.
So you see, the last enemy was really strong.
Aw, Takumi-kun.
He was so engrossed with his game that he
didn't even notice the two next to him.
Oh, that reminds me, Shiori-san.
What is it?
I heard Kimura-san was being discharged tomorrow.
Is that true?
Yes. At least that's what's scheduled.
I see.
But Kimura-san taught me so much.
That's too bad.
So he was helping you with your homework.
In that case, tomorrow I'll take over
where he left off and help you.
Really?
Long ago, I used to be a tutor.
Wow, that's cool.
It'll be pretty lonely in here.
Hey, look at this.
I bought it today. Let's use this to study.
I'm sorry, but I don't think that will help.
What I need help with...
is this.
What are you doing?
Takumi-kun, put it away!
I'm sorry, Shiori-san, but Kimura-san taught me.
a woman's mouth on it than my own hands.
He said that it felt much better to have
Ever since I heard that, I was hoping you'd...
Because of me? Th-That's why he wants to?
That's why he's so hard?
I-I'm sorry!
I guess you think it's gross, Shiori-san.
I guess today, I'll...
I'll...
I'll use just my hands.
I'm a nurse,
and my patient is in pain.
I have to help him out somehow.
This is for my patient.. for my patient's well being.
Just today, okay?
It must be difficult for you. I'll make it go away soon.
It's so big.
Takumi-kun, you really feel it, don't you?
Yes. Shiori-san, this feels great.
You can cum if you want to.
Don't hold back.
Wow. It's getting so big just from being stroked.
He's secreting so much fluid
that my hands are slippery.
Wow, that's pretty lewd.
And also, this smell...
I... I can't hold back anymore.
Shiori-san, you're licking me.
Takumi-kun, does it feel good?
It's so big. You must've had a difficult time.
It's okay. Cum whenever you want.
Suck it in deeper. Suck it harder!
Am I really sucking on this underage boy's cock?
Put it in deeper. Just with your mouth.
Oh, I know full well this is inappropriate.
But...
I can't ignore Takumi-kun's words.
Suck it harder.
Touch my balls too...
I wish his cock was in here.
Shiori-san, I'm cumming!
Drink my cum!
Wow, he's releasing a lot!
Seriously, what a long ejaculation.
My mouth is getting completely filled with nasty cum!
Oh, no.
I was just about to cum myself.
Takumi-kun, was that enough?
It wasn't enough.
Shiori-san, you still aren't done yet.
Y-You don't need to...
Shiori-san, if I make you cum,
will you have sex with me?
No! We can't! You're in no condition for that anyway.
Why is he saying that?
H-How can he talk about "sex"?
Okay. I promise I'll make you cum.
Don't do it, Takumi-kun!
Oh, no! Not my nipples. They're so sensitive!
You shouldn't hold back.
You're almost there, aren't you?
See? Your panties are wet already.
H-He's good. Why is he so good at this?
Now I'll take them off.
No! Don't look, Takumi-kun! Don't!
Wow, soaking wet. And it's throbbing a little.
A pussy looks completely different
from the way I'd imagined.
No! Don't look at me!
No. Takumi-kun!
Just enjoy it. You let me cum earlier.
B-But...
That's...
I found your clitoris!
If I stroke this...
Not there! No! No!
No!
Stop it!
I'm gonna cum!
I-I-I'm cumming. I'm cumming now!
I came.
With a younger guy.
Shiori-san, a deal's a deal.
Don't!
Not that! Takumi-kun, forgive me!
I won't. We made a deal, didn't we?
And besides, this is something I want as well.
No, but... I... just came.
Still, in I go.
Don't!
Oh, no!
Don't! Takumi-kun!
Not so rough!
You're right.
I'm an invalid. Why don't you try moving for me?
Yes!
My nipples... Not my nipples. Not my nipples!
This is the first time...
Even though I usually hate it...
Even though I usually hate that..
But when I do this, it feels better for you, doesn't it?
Not my nipples! More! You'll make me cum more!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
This feels too good. Your pussy feels great.
It's no good. I can't think of anything else.
It feels... It feels so great!
More! I want more!
No! No! I'll cum again! I'll cum... even more!
Then cum! Cum again, Shiori-san!
Just like last time. Shower me with your cum!
Let me go! I... I can't hold out anymore!
No! Not again! I'm cumming again. Not again!
Then cum!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!!
No more!
You don't really mean that.
Your pussy says differently.
I can't think of anything else.
More, I want more!
More. Inside of me more.
I want his cock in my pussy again!
Yes! Yes! Harder! Harder!
Plow me harder! Plow me deeper!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Yeah, you're running out of breath.
Harder. Harder!
Let me cum!
Let's study again tomorrow, Shiori.
Okay.
What?
You don't want to be Takumi-kun's nurse anymore?
I'm sorry, Tokiko-san. I hope this isn't a problem.
I don't mind trading patients with you.
But why this time?
I probably shouldn't tell you this, but...
Doing it in here is called "anal sex," right?
Stop it, Takumi-kun!
It's not meant for that!
It feels strange!
Takumi-kun!
But I hear anal feels really good. Is that true?
No! Don't touch me down there!
Ah! Your anus just closed up a bit.
I see, again.
I guess it does feel good. It's throbbing now.
Ah. what should I do?
I don't want my butthole to turn me on!
If he keeps doing that,
it'll only make me want more!
Guess you're ready. I'm coming in.
Wow! I'm really in!
Your muscles are really grasping me.
Oh crap, it's tight.
I had no idea it could feel so good in my ass.
My pussy's throbbing too!
Oh, no! Don't cum in my ass!
No! Not that!
Hey, Takumi-kun, in here too.
I can't hold back anymore.
What did you say?
Shiori, you really are a pervert.
Your pussy is all slippery and clotted.
What were you expecting from me?
I was just...
She's not feeling well.
She isn't?
But don't worry, I'll be your nurse now.
Huh? You don't like it?
N-No, I've always admired you for working so hard.
I'm actually very honored to have you as my nurse!
Really?
Thank you very much, Tokiko-san.
Okay.
What the hell? He's just a sweet kid.
I wonder why she's scared of such a nice boy?
Shiori-San's the strange one.
Takumi-kun?
Is something wrong?
I... feel strange.
Strange? In what way?
This...
My dick is swollen, and I've got a fever.
Oh, I see. That's all it was.
Don't worry. It's normal.
He's got such an innocent face, but he's so big.
And see, if I do this..
Doesn't it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
It feels great, Tokiko-San!
This must be his first time. How cute.
I'll make him feel all better soon.
Oh, no! That's dirty!
Don't worry, it's fine.
Does it feel good? Takumi-kun, do you like it?
It feels almost too good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I think somethings coming out.
That's okay. Cum. Let it come out.
My pee is white.
That's semen.
Didn't you learn about that in health class?
No, I didn't. I've been hospitalized my whole life.
Tokiko-san, teach me more!
Don't!
Well? Doesn't this feel great?
No!
Tease me! Tease me more!
Then will you become my slave?
If you do, I'll tease you every day.
Perfect! I'll become your slave.
Please make me your slave!
Then from this point on, you're my personal slave.
Yes! Yes!
Harder! Harder!
Yes!
Oh, no, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! Here I come! I'm cumming!
Cumming!!
Your cum... inside of me. Yes!
Even though you just came, you've still got more?
No! Stop it!
No more. Stop!
Why did Shiori-san really quit?
Because she said you made her feel weird!
It's my fault? But she's the one who started it!
What a rotten thing to say.
Who does she think she is?
Cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Hot...
That really made me mad. Tokiko-san?
Yes?
If I ask you something, you'll do it for me, right?
Yes. You want to go for another round?
I do, right now.
So Tokiko-san, you'll do anything for me, right?
Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been freed from Takumi-kun.
But something doesn't feel right.
Shiori, you're a pervert.
Takumi-kun's right, I am a pervert.
No, that was Takumi-kun's fault.
No way.
My panties are gone?
Oh, no. What should I do?
I'm not wearing panties.
Shiori-san,
Tanaka-san in Room 513 is calling you.
Go as quickly as you can.
Okay.
It's your fault, Shiori-san.
That's what you get for deserting Takumi-kun.
Let them have their fun with you.
Sorry to call you, Shiori-san.
My drip tube is hurting me. Can you fix it?
Sure.
Ah, that's right.
I also dropped a thermometer under that bed.
Will you get it for me?
Sure.
I'd better be careful not to let Him see under my skirt.
Urn, I don't see anything.
Well, it's really far under there.
Okay.
Wow! She's really not wearing panties?
So, Shiori-san, you're like that.
No! I'm not like that!
I think we'd better give her a
checkup just to make sure.
No! Don't do this!
Don't look!
Wow, she's already wet!
Is her clit erect?
Let me give you a breast examination.
Damn! They're huge!
If they fondle me hard like this...
Oh. no!
I can't contain myself!
This is fun! She's really reacting to all of this!
You're right!
After all, she's the type who works with no
panties on. She must be freaking sick!
No. Stop...
No! You're embarrassing me!
Oh, no. Not that!
If you keep doing that I won't be able to hold back!
I had no idea the sophisticated
Shiori-san was such a slut.
I guess we'd better give it to her.
I'm...
...cumming!
That right, Tokiko-san said she also does anal.
For real?
Is that true, Shiori-san?
No, it's not! I'm not that slutty.
You must be lying.
I can tell this hole has known a dick before.
You like anal, don't you?
No!
Just answer us honestly.
Yes! I wanna... do it! In my ass..
Please stick your cock inside!
I really am a pervert.
After all of that, I feel so good.
But..
Oh, crap. I'm gonna cum. I'm cumming!
What I really want is..
Takumi-kun, here are your belongings.
Ah, Shiori-san.
Ah! These things. I've been expecting these.
And I'm glad you're back with me, Shiori.
With this thing, I can tease you even better.
No. I must restrain myself.
B-But, my pussy is throbbing. I can't stop!
Yes, Takumi-sama.