Hey guys, we're going to collect your urine samples now!
If the boys would bring them to me,
and the girls would bring them to Oizumi-san, that would be great!
Yes!
Here.
There you go.
Okay then, everyone's given them to us, right?
Then we're done collecting!
SubDESU-H
Choisuji
Yo-chan, that coat suits you!
That's not true...
You really look like a top student!
Being an infirmary representative sure is bothersome.
Yeah, it is.
What's wrong? You seem kinda ill.
It's not that, but...
We're coming in!
Excuse us.
Thanks for collecting those.
Was there anyone who had forgotten?
Nope! We got everyones-!
Yes, I've forgotten...
What?! Are you serious?
For such a top student as Yo-chan to forget her u-urine sample...
isn't that a catastrophe?
Don't worry. We've got spare packets, so it's fine.
Just remember to hand it in later.
Yes...
Then how about we do it here?
What? What?!
You have to pee in front of me, it's your penalty for not bringing yours!
W-Why?!
I want to see you, my best friend, pee!
No way!
I can't do that!
It's fine, it's fine!
It's your penalty for forgetting, so it can't be helped!
C'mon! If we go behind the curtain then sensei won't see us.
I-It's embarrassing!
C'mon, take it off!
Huh? What...?
T-This is embarrassing!
It's embarrassing for me to be staring at you there!
So we're even.
C'mon, move your hands!
Whoa! Yo-chan, you're like an adult!
Even though it's not much, you're growing hairs down here!
T-That's not true, I'm just at the stage of growing up!
Everyone goes through it, I'm just a bit early!
Well whatever, hurry up and pee!
No...
No, I really can't...
It won't come out.
What? Then how about if I do this?
Don't fiddle with me!
No, you have to hurry up and pee!
Oh! It's coming out!
N-No...
That's not nearly enough!
Let out more!
What? It's too embarrassing...
And it's harder if you do that!
But we don't have enough!
If we don't hurry, first period will start.
I'll try my best too, okay?
Yo-chan, could you kneel down and face the other way?
Yo-chan, I can see it all. I can see everything down here!
What?!
I don't like this kind of pose!
It's way too embarrassing!
Please, forgive me already!
It's so cute! Yo-chan, you're so cute down here!
Don't spread it!
N-No~!!
What's wrong? It's not coming out!
C'mon, c'mon!
Hurry up and pee!
No! Don't!
No~!!
D-Don't! Don't!
I'm gonna cum!!
Huh? This isn't urine!
I guess I'll ask sensei to help us out!
What?
It's finally my turn, huh?
U-Um...
When you're taking a pee, this is the best position.
You're still quivering here, Yo-chan!
No~!!
No!
Your clitoris is getting hard!
No~!
You're so cute down here, Yo-chan!
No! Not there! Really! No!
I'll make you feel good again!
Stop it!
I-I'll cum again!
Stop!!
It looks like it feels good, so I'm not gonna stop!
How is it? Are you gonna pee?
Lots of something that isn't urine is coming out!
No! Really, no!
I'm, I'm gonna feel something different!
Something different? Like what?
L-Like what...?
No! I'm gonna cum again! I'm cumming!
Yo-chan, you came!
You came from my fingers!
I made you cum!
Um...
Umph...
Let's take it off too, Yo-chan!
W-Weren't we going to take urine samples?
Don't worry about that Yo-chan, you're a top student!
Takako-chan! First period is about to start!
It's fine, it's fine!
Umph...
Sensei, come play with us!
Oh, sensei is troubled now!
Then how about we get started?
Here we go-!
A-Amazing!
Yo-chan, this feels good, I'm feeling so good!
Me too! It feels incredible!
I'm about to cum~!
Then go on, cum!
I'm about to as well!
I can't hold back!
I-I'm cumming!!
Sensei... I want to cum again!
I guess we'll have to give it another shot!
So then, I'm gonna put something incredible in.
Sensei...
It's so large! It's coming into me!
I can't hold back anymore! Sensei, I'm gonna cum!
Please, cum!
I'm about to cum too!
I'm cumming!!
It's coming out-!
Right, it's coming out!
Oizumi, you sure let out a lot!
It's a nice color, it should be a good sample.
Yes...
It's done.
Now we've got the samples for the whole class.
Yes! We've got them all now!
Um...
Actually...
I forgot too!
What?!
Eh?! That's not possible!
Saying that after we've gone this far?
Now it's Takako-chan's turn!
Right then, let's let a lot out!
W-Wait you two! We can't! We just finished!
How is it, Takako-chan? Can you pee?
N-No, it doesn't feel like it! I feel something else!
You'll let it out when you feel good!
Let out a lot, okay?
A lot?! I'm gonna let out a lot?
Yep! You're gonna cum a lot!
No-!
Don't do it at the same time!
You gotta cum and pee!
If I do this, maybe you'll let it out.
Huh? What? What are you doing?
No-! Your finger! Don't put it in my ass!
It's unpleasant! Take it out! Don't move your finger!
No-!
No!! I'm gonna cum!
Now you can let it out.
Takako-chan!
Is that all of them?
Yep! We've got all of them now!