Even though it's for work, will it matter if I don't write in this?
Today sure is hot.
Isn't that Aikawa?
Why is she here on the weekend?
Naked?!
A-Aikawa!
Hey you!
Huh?
W-W-W-What's this?! Why?!
Hello sensei!
Hello...
That's not what I mean! Why are you dressed like that?
The hose nozzle broke, and I got all wet.
E-Even though you say that...
Since today is really hot, I figured my clothes would dry quickly!
Wait!
Ouch~!
SubDESU-H
Choisuji
I'm sorry~!
You sure like plants, Aikawa.
Yes, I love them!
Aren't plants great?
Y-Yeah...
Just looking at this natural green is soothing!
I planted some sunflowers in that flower bed over there with the gym teacher.
They've grown so large already, so they should flower a beautiful yellow by mid-July!
I hope there will be lots of seeds by autumn...
Sensei?
I-I guess you're right.
Anyway, are you planning to go to the World Expo, Aikawa?
Yes, I'll be going?
I'm looking forward to it!
Hey there, Aikawa Moe-chan. How are you doing?
Ko-n-ni-chi-wa.
TL Note = This fluffy green creature "Morisuke" is a parody of "Morizo," one of the mascots of 2005's World Expo in Japan
Whoa! It's Morisuke!
Morisuke, Morisuke, Morisuke!
B-By the way, do you know how us plants make more of ourselves, Moe-chan?
Eh?!
Umm... Seeds?
and root division...
and branch separation?
You're too good.
It's easy!
Then do you know how seeds are created?
Yes, I do! They are created by the pistils and stamens!
Then what about humans and other animals?
I like plants but I'm no good at biology!
Actually, humans, animals, and plants are theoretically the same!
Humans also have stamens and pistils, it's amazing!
Wanna look? Have a look!
You want to know about it, right?
I'll show you...
Here it is!
This is the human's stamen!
P-Pen...is...
No no! This is a stamen!
Let's learn a lot about plants, okay?
It's okay to touch!
Whoa, amazing!
It suddenly got large, I'm so surprised!
How is it? Isn't it cool?
The baby seeds come out of the tip of this!
Eh? Sees come out?
Do you plant them in the flower bed?
N-No, we'll show you that soon, but try holding the stamen first.
Like this?
Yes, that's good!
L-Let's try rubbing it gently!
That's it, do it more!
Is... Is this good?
That's it, you're doing great!
That's right! Rub the tip too! Rub it~!
I'm burning up! You're too good!
T-That's good, you're amazing!
Are these the baby seeds?
They're white and slippery...
How was it? You learned a lot right?
Huh? What? What are you doing, sensei?
I'm not sensei, I'm Morisuke.
So then, could you show us your cute pistil?
P-Pistil?
Girls have their pistils here.
W-What?
You don't need to be scared.
No~! It tickles!
It tickles!
Stop it-!
It tickles, huh?
Then how about here?
No, stop it!
Stop! No, stop it already!
N-No Morisuke, not there!
No, no!
Doesn't it feel good?
Aren't pistils amazing?
No, no! No no~!
Don't look~!
Moe-chan,
can you revive the stamen?
Now, try gently licking the stamen...
The things good for your health are usually bitter.
Vegetable juice is bitter, right?
But you'll soon start to like it!
To make the stamen happy, gently lick it and stroke it at the same time.
Whoa! Amazing, you're very good!
The stamen is getting happy!
The stamen nearly let it out again...
Okay, let's get ready to plant the seeds!
No, no! Don't take it off!
No!
Don't look~!
You're overflowing...
I have to make sure the pistil is happy, too.
D-Don't lick it~!
Something will happen again!
I-It's coming inside!
I-It's gone inside me!
I-It's moving around inside!
It's going in~!
I'll overflow, no~!
This is going better than I expected!
I think I can put it in...
It's okay, right Moe-chan?
No...
Now we're going to put the stamen inside the pistil!
No more...
No more!
C'mon, lift your butt.
I'm tired, can we not continue?
It's not scary, make sure you relax.
Okay, it's going in, it's gonna go in! Ready?
Can you tell?
The stamen and the pistil have combined!
It's... It's hitting me deeply!
It's hitting your deepest spots!
It's knocking against the end!
No, it's hitting the end!
Don't come in!
Don't be so rough~!
Noo!
You're being too rough!
No!!
Does it feel good?
The stamen feels good!!
Hey, what does it feel like?
I-I'm about to overflow, it's coming in waves!
No-!
Oh, it's good, it feels good!
Morisuke is about to cum!
I'm about to-!
No-!
I'm cumming!!
My tummy is so hot!!
It sure feels good making more nature...
It sure does, it's an amazing thing...
Although I get exhausted
I'm totally worn out...
Let's treat this beautiful plant preciously, okay?