He only saw hell spread out
before his eyes.
Eyes filled with regret and repent
are staring out.
No one can resist the fate
that befell them.
When he controlled all,
he thought he was immortal.
However, on that unforgettable day...
the major catastrophe
deprived people of everything.
The chaos caused him
to become mortal once again.
As the gears grind into a new era...
will their ignorance
be proven?
Master Kyosuke...
there are forty-eight.
As you suspected...
the NMW seems to be
the most vulnerable.
We'll step in.
That's obviously something
they have not overlooked.
I advise you to reconsider.
It's what's called
"statistical planning".
If it is indeed so, it proves
that they still think like mortals.
Then I still have a chance.
Hello, Kyosuke.
I have something I want to ask you.
Do you have a minute?
There are poor men
who save themselves...
by praying to keep their
sole personality.
There are also imbeciles
who learn nothing...
from killing thousands of people.
I will become the one
to judge their values.
But I cannot promise
to be fair to them.
There's no turning back,
you know that, Suzu?
I do not mind. My brother died,
and I accepted my fate to be the same.
Even plants die without water,
but I lived on.
Allow me to go, Master Ooga.
Direct me to my path.
It's just as he said...
they were drugging people
with words.
Drugged people can do anything
and get off with it.
But I don't want to stoop
to that level.
Then tell us
what this Kaiser stone is!
No lies. Tell us word for word
without twisting the truth!
Stop fighting, guys!
Okay, I'll tell you, but it may
be difficult to understand.
I don't think you should listen.
Too much knowledge will deprive you
of your beauty.
Too much knowledge?
My family's heritage is music.
My father and mother were both
well-known composers.
And I inherited their skill.
But I was bored.
With just one stroke
of an instrument...
people around me applauded
till their hands swelled.
My life was set
from the time I was born.
I wondered why we had the ability
to think.
I know it's childish.
I met him then.
Oosaki?
He was going by the name of Ooga.
Ooga?
And he gave me
the Kaiser stone crystal.
He told me that I can be reborn
with it.
I thought that it was foolish
at the time...
but it was beautiful,
so I kept it.
That was the birth
of Hell-stinger, my counterpart.
I liked it.
There were rumors of a dark night.
I wanted to keep dreaming about it.
But I was immediately
awakened to reality.
I hate reality,
but at least it wakes me.
I finally found you.
I'm the death you've been
waiting for.
Say your prayers Ooga.
You can't satisfy me
with that little toy.
All I want is you.
All you want is me.
Let's go for it.
Fool!
I don't know what you're trying
to do...
but you can't threaten me
with such illusions.
What was that?
Tell me!
That was the end.
We don't have much time.
Do what you must do,
even if you have to kill me.
My theory is that within him
is another him.
You mean a double personality?
I think it's a doppelganger.
I don't know about that.
I think you're on the right track,
but it's not that simple.
- Look who's talking?
- Who does he think he is?
Do you know why it's red?
- Don't ask me.
- The Kaiser stone is made from blood.
That doesn't mean it's made
from actual blood.
He is constantly fighting
with this other self.
It may sound ridiculous,
but it's stained with blood.
This is Ooga's scream.
It's the leftover energy
that flows out...
from his will to survive.
- I have no idea what you mean.
- Me neither.
I didn't think you would.
Let's put it in layman's terms.
Let's compare it to swords.
When a sword smith
creates a masterpiece...
he always creates another sword
of the same shape.
It's the yin and the yang,
the black and the white.
In order to create a sword
with good powers...
he must create another sword
to absorb the evil powers.
And at the time of completion...
the evil sword
will be condemned forever.
This is how a good sword is born.
The Kaiser stone works the same way.
As the negative energy within Ooga
expands...
the positive energy
starts to flow out.
That is, the good energy
has the same amount of power as Ooga.
And that is the positive power
of the Kaiser stone.
I'm begging to get what this little
Kaiser stone is all about.
But why is this negative energy
trying to destroy the Earth?
I would like to ask
the same question.
Stop playing ignorant.
Well, we can laugh about it
all we want...
but there is definitely
something going on.
You're blabbing again.
But I guess we just
have to do it.
Do what?
Stop Ooga.
I knew you were going to say that.
I probably would have been
against it before...
but I saw your Asahina-Twins.
I have to give you credit
for your powers.
Don't be cynical.
As long as I know the truth...
it's not my style
to keep calm about it.
You're not going to lose, either!
It's our duty to save this planet.
This planet's in danger...
because the principal
is taken over...
by some evil force, right?
This is my big chance
to save the world!
I'm amazed that you figured it out all
right.
No way!
Why not!
We're not talking about humans here.
We're fighting against
an impenetrable power.
It's crazy even for us who have the
ability to counter it.
All you've got as a weapon
is that lousy stick.
That's suicide
as far as I'm concerned.
Well, that settles it. You just quietly
wait it out right here.
We'll invite you to the victory party
when it's all over.
But, I want to go!
Huh?
I wanta go! I wanta go!
Even my parents always said I'd never
measure up.
I've worked all my life
to prove them wrong...!
Oh well, I guess
everyone's got some kind of situation.
Set me right if I'm wrong about you
Ohga.
Like Indian warriors fighting on foot
against the cavalry.
Or the long swim of an army of ants
joining together in a torrent.
Even so...
Could my life as
determined by will have any meaning?
Come on over to my place.
It's right near here.
Really...
Come'on.
Area E West, Kanmon district, 100%
deployed.
120% penetration rate.
150% control of sector.
No indeterminate factors.
Standby until further orders. Standby
limit is 128 minutes. Over and out.
Gamon.
It's not going to work at the Gamon gate
no matter how hard we try.
What should we do.
Master Kyosuke?
I will use the divine sword.
You mustn't!
You mustn't use your ultimate weapon
at this early stage!
You will loose all of your energy!
Don't worry about it.
I've worked it out.
I've been measuring
his strength all along.
Using the divine sword now
will not adversely affect me.
Get out of the way, Kubira.
I will not!
You are lying to me,
Master Kyosuke.
You think nothing of it even when your
flesh torn.
You rise up to fight even when your
bones are crushed.
I have witnessed
your relentless spirit
for all of this time.
Now is the time...
Please use my body
as much as you have to.
I will let myself be destroyed.
You can't.
If he sees your spirit rising up from
your body, that will be the end of it.
But...
Hi! You there...
You seem to be having trouble
with that gate not opening.
Not to worry now that I, Misty Shaia,
has arrived on the scene!
Lt'll be as easy as pie!
Hishizaki?
Hey, come on. Why can't you play along?
I am Misty Shaia,
the mystery princess of the school.
Hey, come on. Don't ignore me!
Miss Shaia, maybe we should get going.
You are embarrassing yourself.
Miss...
What is this all about.
You know, even I have my reasons.
Boys shouldn't be so nosy about such
little details.
If you feel obliged
to lend me a hand...
after that talk we had this
afternoon, you're not welcome.
Leave now.
I merely ran into you
at an outdoor concert. That's all.
Don't be so vain!
Ball Boy!
Let's go, Boy!
Yes, Miss Shaia.
Shining Triangle!
The gate has opened!
Master Kyosuke!
You did it this time.
Kubira.
Yes?
Take her to a safe place.
Master Kyosuke...
That's an order.
To watch over my Master Kyosuke is the
most important duty of my existence!
Please let me go along!
No.
Master Kyosuke!
On Kirikiara
Haraharatsuta Yariaura Hila Hon Souka.
Seal!
Please open the door Master Kyosuke!
I will come with you!
Master Kyosuke! Master Kyosuke!
Is this the end? Is this the end of all
that we've been through together!
Is this the end?
Forgive me, Kubira.
If he sees your rising spirit...
He'll be given spellbinding power strong
enough to destroy with one glance.
I can no longer bear to see the face of
one who follows my path.
I don't want to see it.
Well, well. So it is you...
Kyosuke!
My dear friend,
you're not acting like yourself.
You will never be happy with this silly
game you are playing.
You don't seem to have much patience.
Well, well. Are we afraid? As the sands
continue to flow, slowly burying you?
If there was a little more time, with
you I can...
No, I will not say it.
The sands that fill up my ears must be
cleared away first.
Then we can go our separate ways.
It is not only sand...
The fire and water
will also support life.
All of it plays a part.
Do not worry.
As long as divine providence is not
defied...
life shall be reborn.
Come in closer.
Fake beasts.
I'll destroy you all.
I think I have spoken too much
about what happened.
I said a lot of things, without any
regard for your feelings.
I was selfish.
I'm sorry.
But...
But that's not right.
Besides... it's revenge, against your
brother.
My sister...
carried half of my burden.
Happiness and despair, all of my
feelings were for my sister.
It has been seething within me.
Do you think a person can live missing
half their body?
That's right.
This is something that I myself must
take back, even if for my own sake.
If that's the case...
that half you are looking for...
can come from me.
Sister!
Kyosuke...
There's something I want you to keep for
me.
An earring?
It's a keepsake from my sister.
Keep it, no...
I want you to have it.
I can't take it.
It's too important to you.
It's all right.
I may be going to where my sister is.
If I wore something like this,
I'd be laughed at.
Kyosuke.
Could you put it on for me?
Sure.
Like this?
What a fool I am.
Have I not learned anything.
I must never have those
thoughts again.
I apologize.
Forgive me.
Kyosuke.
I'm glad you have awoken, Miss Shaia.
Ball Boy.
You're awake.
Did you bring me here?
Don't get me wrong.
I saved you...
only because Master Kyosuke
ordered me to.
Otherwise you would have been left
abandoned in the cold.
Moreover...
those were his final words and I could
not ignore them.
Then...
Kyosuke...
Master Kyosuke...
will not return.
No!
Hm?
Shadow Run!
Higher Slash!
It looks like my warning
meant nothing.
That's not true.
It's because of what you told me...
that I've been able to direct my powers
for the purposes intended.
Compared to the timewhen all I thought
about was you...
it's quite a step.
How clever.
Whatever...
I don't think there's any time to think
about it now.
I'm sorry but you're
getting in the way.
I can even feel his presence
within you.
The perverted power...
The hypocrisy of your devotion...
It's all very unsavory.
Come on, don't be picking on him.
Only I have that right as his partner in
crime.
Who are you?
You seem to be under
his spell as well.
Leave now. This is no place for low-rent
mercenaries.
I suppose you can always skip out on the
rent.
I might have to pay interest.
Anyway, don't come after me.
Having him confuse me
with you two would be regrettable.
He sure likes to be dramatic.
All right, we should get going too.
I'm sure he'll be fine alone.
Yeah.
Retreat! Retreat now!
What are these
creatures!?
The most advanced weaponry
of the UN has no effect on them!
Wha... What is this young girl!?
Even I will not loose against guys like
these.
I'm not in a very good mood today!
Prepare yourselves!
What is this place?
It looks like some kind of theme park
I went to as a kid.
I guess Ohga built himself a nice little
playground.
She looks like the
Princess of the land.
Uh... It's you!
This is your day of reckoning...
Isato Kaiza!
Ever since you destroyed
my other half...
it's a struggle even
to breathe.
But this is where it
all ends.
Just wait a minute!
Do you remember what my brother
told you?
Whether you can fully utilize
the Caizer stone's power...
depends on your psychological
strength.
And it is when you have to protect
the one you love...
that you are at your strongest.
That's right. My brother was
always right.
By accepting this
Caizer stone into my body
I've come to understand.
The time has come to show you
the power of love!
Metamol Slave!
Kash!
Stay out of this one!
Die! Isato Kaiza!
Graviton...
Fraber!
Together they fought...
in the spirit of youthful camaraderie.
Isato Kaiza...
In the spirit of his own jubilant
re-awakening...
he seeks to make amends for
a wrong he committed.
He faces his vengeful foe, haunted like
a criminal.
Kash Mizutani...
Trapped within the society he so
despised...
and which he understood would soon meet
its own demise...
he strives to unshackle himself from the
burdens of his childhood.
Kyosuke Shigure...
The scent of revenge permeating his
body.
Fighting to prove his own worth as a
human...
setting up the confrontation.
Deep within his conscience...
he was seeking to wipe out the memory
of his own brother.
Also...
there is a man who continues
to wait in the dark.
What is it that he is waiting for?
Is it a creation... or is it utter
destruction?
The moment is at hand.
The final chapter of this legend...
is about to begin.
The Voltage Fighter: Gowcaizer 3
They haven't learned a thing.
Then again... neither have I.
Isato...
Oh no!
Ball Boy!
That can only mean...
Miss Shaia!
Hey!
Let's get 'em, Karin!
Let's do it!
Shining Cluster! Shoot!
The ultimate...
Kaen Henpou!
That's perfection!
We did it! Yet again!
I'm going to rub you out.
Die, Gowcaizer!
No, Isato Kaiza!
Get out of the way, Kash.
It is certainly not
my intention to kill you.
You should know.
I've recently considered doing volunteer
work.
Well I see that you're going to
volunteer your life this time.
Graviton Knuckle!
Beated Needle!
On Bazaragini Harachihataya Souka.
Ha!
It is not easy to be laying in wait.
I've been held in an unchanging state
over the past 3 years, Kyosuke.
I can see right through you.
Anger will reduce your powers by half.
Have you forgotten
what I've taught you.
Ozaki...
I have one last question for you.
What is it?
Why did you have to harm my sister.
Was it because you needed me!
Was it because you needed my power!
That's right.
I needed Mia so that I could give you a
special power.
And once you were re-born
with your new power...
I needed to increase the strength
of that power...
And Mia had to die.
It was my intention all along.
Is that so...
Do you remember, Kyosuke?
Day in and day out...
late into dusk,
I taught you how to use your powers.
And you responded very well in every
way.
A most excellent ability.
Just as I expected.
Everything seemed to be proceeding just
as I wanted it to.
However...
I sensed that I miscalculated
something.
And that was the love that you began to
show me.
Perhaps you saw me as a father figure.
I didn't expect it at all.
So in order to break
that relationship...
although premature, I took the life of
Mia.
However...
It seemed that I'd made another
miscalculation.
Shut up!
That is, the love she had for me was
deeper than I could have imagined.
Even when I sentenced her
to her death...
she stepped forward
and offered her neck.
What was necessary...
were the anguished cries...
Kyosuke, it was the neck of Mia
as she cried for your help.
It weighed heavily on me.
Shut up!
You were siblings hungering for love.
It's really a question of disposition,
but it's so sad.
Shut up!
Don't rush it, Kyosuke...
Now is the time...
that I will reveal the other half
of my soul...
that of the providence of god.
What?
The judgment...
Stop it!
You had to but in, huh?
Just stay out of this, it'll end
quickly.
Shut your mouth!
You want this to end in another
meaningless sacrifice!?
Do what you want then.
But let me warn you first
that she no longer has a human soul.
Your cheap humanistic approach will land
you in a grave.
I don't think it's the time to be
bickering.
Or do you think I'm a pushover.
What's wrong?
You afraid?
Or are you merely plotting your response
to my attack?
Come and get me.
The Soul Gear! That's suicide!
Isato!
I don't know what you've got in mind...
but you fool yourself if you think you
can stand up to me without Soul Gear!
Suzu Asahina!
If your goal is to kill me pure and
simple...
then I'm not going to stop you!
Come!
Look. You are human after all.
When you cause harm to another person...
you will surely be hurting
your own soul.
However much you want to kill that
person.
No matter what happens, I will protect
you.
I love you, Suzu.
My dear brother...
I'm sorry.
Kash! Kash!
Hey hey, don't be
taking advantage of me.
I don't like being called
only when it's convenient.
Come on. I'm sorry about before.
Just try to save her somehow.
There's something weird going on.
Oh no...
The energy of the Caizer is building up
within her.
If it ruptures, that's the end of her.
Stop kidding around! Do something!
You're the authority on the Caizer!
What authority?
Kash.
I'll take my Caizer...
and align it against hers
to neutralize its power.
If it fails, then I suppose we go to
heaven.
You go on ahead.
You've got other things
to take care of.
Don't worry, I won't kill her.
Yeah. All right.
I'm counting on you, Kash.
Don't get lost.
He can run already.
He sure can recover quickly.
Well, just as you wished...
I am volunteering to risk my life
on account of you.
How did I develop such a
self-sacrificing character like this.
Maybe I was railing against all that
uptight society from my childhood.
Listen carefully, Kash.
Since you've been born into this
family...
you will lead a life in which your
performances yield $10,000 per minute...
10 minutes will yield you $100,000.
Ignore all distractions and never waver.
Don't let anyone take your genius
away from you.
You must live your life for yourself.
Only for yourself.
Well, so much for that.
Master Kyosuke.
Penetrate! Kamikabura!
Fire Dance!
Your body breaking apart already?
You mere human.
When not in a group, you cannot stand up
alone.
You are foolish indeed.
You bastard!
That's right. I am not the man you used
to know.
At least on the surface.
I am myself, and you,
and your friend...
A great many people
are embodied within me.
What? What are you saying?
Don't you understand?
Well, I'll forgive you.
I suppose it's beyond the understanding
of a dying man such as you.
To think that you are the one
they await.
Like Pygmalions worshipping the statue
they created...
Pathetic humans.
It will be but a flash.
Master Kyosuke.
Kubira! Is that you?
You can reprimand me later.
The dog!
Kubira!
Forgive me, Kubira.
Die!
Kubira!
Congratulations on your victory.
Why did you...
Kubira.
I've always considered this to be my
final duty.
In order for you to carry out
that duty...
I would have had to return to you.
But I am now all alone.
Master Kyosuke...
Please do not fear.
I will always be near you.
And besides...
You are no longer alone.
Kubira.
Kubira!
Kyosuke!
Kaiza?
Kyosuke! Behind you!
Kyosuke!
This can't be what Kash was talking
about!
This is JG02. There is a mysterious
energy emitting from...!
Who the hell are you anyway!
What did you do with Kyosuke!
I am the will of all creation...
Omni Exist.
What? Omni Exist!?
The embodiment of all thought existing
in nature.
I have absorbed within me all of the
desires of humankind.
That is why I came into being.
What?
I have until now only existed as
thought.
But Shizuru Ozaki...
His desires had reached the level
of my own.
And through him...
I was first able to begin to carry out
my destiny.
You humans are despised...
by all of existence.
Bound by the rules you created...
an insane humanity bent on destroying
everything.
The recklessness of disposing into outer
space that which you cannot process...
The people who live on a planet bathed
in ultraviolet rays...
that reach every corner of the surface.
That is what you are.
The destruction of earth...
It is the desire of all humankind, and I
am the one who will carry it out.
What the hell are you talking about!
That's not what I want!
Is that so...
I'm sure that you've feared the future
at least at one time in your life.
The good things and the bad.
It is surely frightening to look at the
future no matter what your position.
A world that does not progress...
That is something that's certain to
bring relief.
Even the one you refer to as Kyosuke
desires this.
Even you wish it deep in your
subconscious.
The end of everything.
You're wrong! I'm not like that!
Is that so...
But eventually, my powers will destroy
the earth.
Then all will end.
I'm not going to let you.
Then you will have to try and stop me.
You can only succeed if either
your energy exceeds mine...
or if all of existence can be
persuaded...
and cause me to completely loose
my will.
Both seem preposterous at this point.
Sounds interesting...
Well I'm not much
of a pursuasive talker...
but to exceed your power is something
I can give a shot at.
Caizer Go!
Caizer Strike!
Burny Samona!
Miss Shaia.
I hope Isato and them are gonna be all
right.
Don't worry about it...
There're not going to loose that easily.
You're right!
They're not gonna loose.
Kyosuke.
Shit. I can't let it end like this.
No way, Isato! It's not in your nature
to give up like this.
Come on, Isato!
You fool.
Shit!
Kash!
Knowing the kind of guy you are...
I figured you'd be playing up
that high drama yours.
And I was right.
Hey, what did you do with the girl?
Don't worry. I delivered the princess to
her castle.
Hyper Voltage...!
Transform Hellstinger!
Heh! And what did you come here for?
Huh?
Haven't you heard?
I came to round up the finale.
Knowing you, this might never
come to an end.
I don't need any of that at a time like
this.
As I suspected, to band together...
is a human tendency.
I suppose that can't be helped.
Here she comes!
Yeah. I'll set up a decoy.
You go straight for the attack.
All right!
Lineck Singer!
Now's your chance, Isato!
Isato!
You're doing very well.
You have my praise.
I will now give you your reward!
Are you sleepy, Kyosuke?
Yes.
I'm sleepy, dear brother.
Very sleepy.
No Kyosuke. You mustn't sleep yet.
My sister!
It is now that we need your strength the
most.
Kubira is here too.
I cannot see anything.
Besides... I'm no longer...
Take my hand, Kyosuke...
I will show you the way.
It is my final wish.
Brother!
Kyosuke.
Quite amazing...
To think that the human will can be so
sublime...
You haven't seen nothing yet.
We can be foolish and we often fail.
We can also think evil thoughts.
But on the other hand...
only humans will sacrifice their lives
to help save those close to them.
Heh! Well I'm just the kind of fool
that'll fall for that.
Using your power to save everyone isn't
something that hasn't crossed my mind.
I'll show you what it's all about...!
The unlimited possibilities of human
beings!
You've got quite an attitude.
It is time that I show you the eternal
agony of nothingness.
This doesn't look good...
These forces are like no other we've
felt yet.
Isato!
Foolish one...
Wha...!
What's going on!?
Kyosuke!
How could you, my friend?
Forgive me...
but I am human after all.
Now's the time. Come Kaiza!
But... But Kyosuke!
Die!
Come!
Kash!
OK!
Kyosuke!
I've paid my debt.
Die!
Here me well, humankind...
I have not given up.
And I have not died.
Just a momentary lapse of direction.
I will return at anytime that you
desire.
Anytime.
Isato...!
Welcome back.
Good to be here.
That's right.
I did not want to kill you.
I just wanted to bring you back.