Together they fought...
in the spirit of youthful camaraderie.
Isato Kaiza...
In the spirit of his own jubilant
re-awakening...
he seeks to make amends for
a wrong he committed.
He faces his vengeful foe, haunted like
a criminal.
Kash Mizutani...
Trapped within the society he so
despised...
and which he understood would soon meet
its own demise...
he strives to unshackle himself from the
burdens of his childhood.
Kyosuke Shigure...
The scent of revenge permeating his
body.
Fighting to prove his own worth as a
human...
setting up the confrontation.
Deep within his conscience...
he was seeking to wipe out the memory
of his own brother.
Also...
there is a man who continues
to wait in the dark.
What is it that he is waiting for?
Is it a creation... or is it utter
destruction?
The moment is at hand.
The final chapter of this legend...
is about to begin.
The Voltage Fighter: Gowcaizer 3
They haven't learned a thing.
Then again... neither have I.
Isato...
Oh no!
Ball Boy!
That can only mean...
Miss Shaia!
Hey!
Let's get 'em, Karin!
Let's do it!
Shining Cluster! Shoot!
The ultimate...
Kaen Henpou!
That's perfection!
We did it! Yet again!
I'm going to rub you out.
Die, Gowcaizer!
No, Isato Kaiza!
Get out of the way, Kash.
It is certainly not
my intention to kill you.
You should know.
I've recently considered doing volunteer
work.
Well I see that you're going to
volunteer your life this time.
Graviton Knuckle!
Beated Needle!
On Bazaragini Harachihataya Souka.
Ha!
It is not easy to be laying in wait.
I've been held in an unchanging state
over the past 3 years, Kyosuke.
I can see right through you.
Anger will reduce your powers by half.
Have you forgotten
what I've taught you.
Ozaki...
I have one last question for you.
What is it?
Why did you have to harm my sister.
Was it because you needed me!
Was it because you needed my power!
That's right.
I needed Mia so that I could give you a
special power.
And once you were re-born
with your new power...
I needed to increase the strength
of that power...
And Mia had to die.
It was my intention all along.
Is that so...
Do you remember, Kyosuke?
Day in and day out...
late into dusk,
I taught you how to use your powers.
And you responded very well in every
way.
A most excellent ability.
Just as I expected.
Everything seemed to be proceeding just
as I wanted it to.
However...
I sensed that I miscalculated
something.
And that was the love that you began to
show me.
Perhaps you saw me as a father figure.
I didn't expect it at all.
So in order to break
that relationship...
although premature, I took the life of
Mia.
However...
It seemed that I'd made another
miscalculation.
Shut up!
That is, the love she had for me was
deeper than I could have imagined.
Even when I sentenced her
to her death...
she stepped forward
and offered her neck.
What was necessary...
were the anguished cries...
Kyosuke, it was the neck of Mia
as she cried for your help.
It weighed heavily on me.
Shut up!
You were siblings hungering for love.
It's really a question of disposition,
but it's so sad.
Shut up!
Don't rush it, Kyosuke...
Now is the time...
that I will reveal the other half
of my soul...
that of the providence of god.
What?
The judgment...
Stop it!
You had to but in, huh?
Just stay out of this, it'll end
quickly.
Shut your mouth!
You want this to end in another
meaningless sacrifice!?
Do what you want then.
But let me warn you first
that she no longer has a human soul.
Your cheap humanistic approach will land
you in a grave.
I don't think it's the time to be
bickering.
Or do you think I'm a pushover.
What's wrong?
You afraid?
Or are you merely plotting your response
to my attack?
Come and get me.
The Soul Gear! That's suicide!
Isato!
I don't know what you've got in mind...
but you fool yourself if you think you
can stand up to me without Soul Gear!
Suzu Asahina!
If your goal is to kill me pure and
simple...
then I'm not going to stop you!
Come!
Look. You are human after all.
When you cause harm to another person...
you will surely be hurting
your own soul.
However much you want to kill that
person.
No matter what happens, I will protect
you.
I love you, Suzu.
My dear brother...
I'm sorry.
Kash! Kash!
Hey hey, don't be
taking advantage of me.
I don't like being called
only when it's convenient.
Come on. I'm sorry about before.
Just try to save her somehow.
There's something weird going on.
Oh no...
The energy of the Caizer is building up
within her.
If it ruptures, that's the end of her.
Stop kidding around! Do something!
You're the authority on the Caizer!
What authority?
Kash.
I'll take my Caizer...
and align it against hers
to neutralize its power.
If it fails, then I suppose we go to
heaven.
You go on ahead.
You've got other things
to take care of.
Don't worry, I won't kill her.
Yeah. All right.
I'm counting on you, Kash.
Don't get lost.
He can run already.
He sure can recover quickly.
Well, just as you wished...
I am volunteering to risk my life
on account of you.
How did I develop such a
self-sacrificing character like this.
Maybe I was railing against all that
uptight society from my childhood.
Listen carefully, Kash.
Since you've been born into this
family...
you will lead a life in which your
performances yield $10,000 per minute...
10 minutes will yield you $100,000.
Ignore all distractions and never waver.
Don't let anyone take your genius
away from you.
You must live your life for yourself.
Only for yourself.
Well, so much for that.
Master Kyosuke.
Penetrate! Kamikabura!
Fire Dance!
Your body breaking apart already?
You mere human.
When not in a group, you cannot stand up
alone.
You are foolish indeed.
You bastard!
That's right. I am not the man you used
to know.
At least on the surface.
I am myself, and you,
and your friend...
A great many people
are embodied within me.
What? What are you saying?
Don't you understand?
Well, I'll forgive you.
I suppose it's beyond the understanding
of a dying man such as you.
To think that you are the one
they await.
Like Pygmalions worshipping the statue
they created...
Pathetic humans.
It will be but a flash.
Master Kyosuke.
Kubira! Is that you?
You can reprimand me later.
The dog!
Kubira!
Forgive me, Kubira.
Die!
Kubira!
Congratulations on your victory.
Why did you...
Kubira.
I've always considered this to be my
final duty.
In order for you to carry out
that duty...
I would have had to return to you.
But I am now all alone.
Master Kyosuke...
Please do not fear.
I will always be near you.
And besides...
You are no longer alone.
Kubira.
Kubira!
Kyosuke!
Kaiza?
Kyosuke! Behind you!
Kyosuke!
This can't be what Kash was talking
about!
This is JG02. There is a mysterious
energy emitting from...!
Who the hell are you anyway!
What did you do with Kyosuke!
I am the will of all creation...
Omni Exist.
What? Omni Exist!?
The embodiment of all thought existing
in nature.
I have absorbed within me all of the
desires of humankind.
That is why I came into being.
What?
I have until now only existed as
thought.
But Shizuru Ozaki...
His desires had reached the level
of my own.
And through him...
I was first able to begin to carry out
my destiny.
You humans are despised...
by all of existence.
Bound by the rules you created...
an insane humanity bent on destroying
everything.
The recklessness of disposing into outer
space that which you cannot process...
The people who live on a planet bathed
in ultraviolet rays...
that reach every corner of the surface.
That is what you are.
The destruction of earth...
It is the desire of all humankind, and I
am the one who will carry it out.
What the hell are you talking about!
That's not what I want!
Is that so...
I'm sure that you've feared the future
at least at one time in your life.
The good things and the bad.
It is surely frightening to look at the
future no matter what your position.
A world that does not progress...
That is something that's certain to
bring relief.
Even the one you refer to as Kyosuke
desires this.
Even you wish it deep in your
subconscious.
The end of everything.
You're wrong! I'm not like that!
Is that so...
But eventually, my powers will destroy
the earth.
Then all will end.
I'm not going to let you.
Then you will have to try and stop me.
You can only succeed if either
your energy exceeds mine...
or if all of existence can be
persuaded...
and cause me to completely loose
my will.
Both seem preposterous at this point.
Sounds interesting...
Well I'm not much
of a pursuasive talker...
but to exceed your power is something
I can give a shot at.
Caizer Go!
Caizer Strike!
Burny Samona!
Miss Shaia.
I hope Isato and them are gonna be all
right.
Don't worry about it...
There're not going to loose that easily.
You're right!
They're not gonna loose.
Kyosuke.
Shit. I can't let it end like this.
No way, Isato! It's not in your nature
to give up like this.
Come on, Isato!
You fool.
Shit!
Kash!
Knowing the kind of guy you are...
I figured you'd be playing up
that high drama yours.
And I was right.
Hey, what did you do with the girl?
Don't worry. I delivered the princess to
her castle.
Hyper Voltage...!
Transform Hellstinger!
Heh! And what did you come here for?
Huh?
Haven't you heard?
I came to round up the finale.
Knowing you, this might never
come to an end.
I don't need any of that at a time like
this.
As I suspected, to band together...
is a human tendency.
I suppose that can't be helped.
Here she comes!
Yeah. I'll set up a decoy.
You go straight for the attack.
All right!
Lineck Singer!
Now's your chance, Isato!
Isato!
You're doing very well.
You have my praise.
I will now give you your reward!
Are you sleepy, Kyosuke?
Yes.
I'm sleepy, dear brother.
Very sleepy.
No Kyosuke. You mustn't sleep yet.
My sister!
It is now that we need your strength the
most.
Kubira is here too.
I cannot see anything.
Besides... I'm no longer...
Take my hand, Kyosuke...
I will show you the way.
It is my final wish.
Brother!
Kyosuke.
Quite amazing...
To think that the human will can be so
sublime...
You haven't seen nothing yet.
We can be foolish and we often fail.
We can also think evil thoughts.
But on the other hand...
only humans will sacrifice their lives
to help save those close to them.
Heh! Well I'm just the kind of fool
that'll fall for that.
Using your power to save everyone isn't
something that hasn't crossed my mind.
I'll show you what it's all about...!
The unlimited possibilities of human
beings!
You've got quite an attitude.
It is time that I show you the eternal
agony of nothingness.
This doesn't look good...
These forces are like no other we've
felt yet.
Isato!
Foolish one...
Wha...!
What's going on!?
Kyosuke!
How could you, my friend?
Forgive me...
but I am human after all.
Now's the time. Come Kaiza!
But... But Kyosuke!
Die!
Come!
Kash!
OK!
Kyosuke!
I've paid my debt.
Die!
Here me well, humankind...
I have not given up.
And I have not died.
Just a momentary lapse of direction.
I will return at anytime that you
desire.
Anytime.
Isato...!
Welcome back.
Good to be here.
That's right.
I did not want to kill you.
I just wanted to bring you back.