"However great a civilization may be...
there will come a time
when it will all end."
The words uttered by someone long past.
Over the course of a half century...
Tokyo, then the largest megalopolis of
Asia...
witnessed its own demise.
In the year 1999...
devastating the entire Kanto region
was a great earthquake often thought of
as the final sign of doom.
Those who arose out of the ruins, wiped
away their tears
and proceeded to rebuild the city.
Eventually...
out of the ashes emerged a 22,000
hectare man-made island...
called Tron City.
The people whose lives returned to the
peaceful state of former times
did not take any significant notice
to the true purposes of the giant
educational facility
built in the center of the new city.
All personnel!
Weapons safety off!
Give it your all!
Eat this!
Did we hit?
Shit!
All personnel! Withdrawal immediately!
Commander Simmons!
What about the survivors!
I'm going in! Cover me!
What do you mean? You'll be killed!
Commander!
What is it!?
A motorcycle has broken through the
barrier...
and is headed this way!
What kind of idiot goes joyriding at a
time like this!?
Hey you! You're going to be killed!
Who the hell is that?
No! I can't be!
That can't be him!?
Yes.
That's the Gowcaizer.
He's going all out.
Isato...
Come back alive. Kaiza, Kash,
Kyosuke.
Fight for the glory.
Now is the time to settle it, dear
Brother.
That's right.
The dice has been thrown.
Let's get started, Mr. Batman.
Gowcaizer - The Voltage Fighters
Well, Good Morning!
Several tremors have struck the Burgundy
region of France since last night,
the largest of which reached a magnitude
of 6.5.
It occurred at a location quite far
from any faults...
and as such is considered to be
very unusual.
Next on the news...
The girl that is missing...
Yes, embedded in that bracelet I gave
you, there is a Caizer stone.
You can say that it's the last hope for
humankind.
Use it well.
Isato Kaiza!
Boo!!
I am the ghost of one who was beaten to
death by you in a Karate match...
I will haunt you. I will haunt you...
In order to appease my haunting spirit,
I will need 100 shrimp dumplings...
Let's see...
It would be better with a nice hot cup
of tea.
And also, let's see, I want...
I want... uh, forget the pork buns, and
uh... no egg soup...
Yes, that's right!
I want shark fin soup!!!
Stop kidding around!
I've never ever killed anyone in a
match!
Good Morning, Isato!
Cut it out!
Are you trying to destroy my image this
morning!?
I came to pick you up! Let's go to
school!
This is too much...
What did you think, did you see that?
Huh? Perfect score?
Miss Shaia!
Good Morning!
Good morning Miss Karin Son.
Hey, Hishizaki!
I see you're once again driving that
dumpy-looking thing.
Oh, good morning Kaiza...
You think that silly retro bike is any
better?
Well, well.
Good-bye Miss Shaia!
I can't take it anymore. Ball Boy,
overtake them. Hurry!
That's impossible, Miss.
Why? You have the same horsepower as
that retro bike, don't you?
We have the same horsepower, but there's
a difference in the load weight.
Load weight?
In other words, the difference between
yours and Karin's weight.
Oh no...
You had to say it didn't you, you stupid
Ball Boy!
I'm sorry, please...
With this drink, we will start the day,
huh?
You think it's the time to be waxing
poetically like that?
We're going to be late.
Hey Sabu, good morning!
She's all bright and sweet as usual.
Yeah, she's quite a babe.
Well, one day she'll be mine. Oopps.
Hey, Sabu. Don't get me wrong.
I just want her in my clique, if you
know what I mean.
Are you sure about that?
You had that look in your eye.
Shut up!
Ouch.
All right, we made it just in time.
Thank goodness!
You stupid idiot!
This isn't New York! Watch where you're
going!
Yeah, that's right! Isato was watching
where he was going!
I saw how it happened!
My apologies.
Come on Isato! The chimes are ringing!
Uh, oh yeah...
Hey, Isato?
You have a bad attitude. Don't you know
the chimes have already rung?
You think I'm a fool to take seriously
what a nerd like you has to say?
You think you can do anything you want
as long as the teacher isn't here?
We're in the 11th grade now.
In order to develop oneself for future
leadership in large and powerful
organizations,
I think graduation is a good thing.
Why don't you just
keep your mouth shut!
Besides, all you need to get into this
school is a special personal skill.
I've got myself covered
with my physical prowess.
I'll leave it to you to sit at a desk
and study the books.
If that's your way of saying that I
should help you cheat on your tests,
I'll have to refuse.
No matter how hard I try, you only get
half my answers, so that's 50% for you.
Huh. It sounds like you're looking for a
fight, you little twerp.
You idiot!
Even if heaven itself were
to permit you...
I, Rampou Fudo will not allow it
such impertinence!
That couldn't be...
Professor Fudo?
Alas, your advisor and lecturer in the
study of the classics...
Professor Rampou Fudo!
Kaiza. I am punishing you for bad
behavior.
You will write out pages 40 to 50 from
the textbook!
The deadline for your work is tomorrow
morning. Understand!
Huh! The weirdo circus-freak of a Prof.
All right, I'm taking the attendance
roll...
Alilia Eisweig!
Here!
Yuichiro Irie!
Julius Wellfire!
Here!
Levy Eliphes!
Isato Kaiza!
Here!
Shaia Hishizaki!
Here, teacher!
I'm right over here. Good morning!
Miss Shaia, please return to your desk
quickly.
Randy Riggs!
Here!
That's all.
Before we begin today, I'd like to make
an announcement.
The first transfer
student in 2 months.
His name is Kyosuke Shigure.
Once in grade 12, you're not likely be
studying with him.
Passed all of his admissions exams,
and Randy...
he did better than you in science and
classics.
Uh.
So, Kyosuke Shigure's his name.
Huh, It would be nice if we got along.
And as such, Mr. Shigure
attained excellent...
scores on the admissions exams.
Perfect scores in several subjects...
Isn't he so cool?
Yeah...
He is a brilliant student that the
members of the admissions commitee...
felt without reserve
to accept into this school.
Well well, he's getting quite the
mention on his very first day even.
This might just compromise my policy
about
not picking on the weaker students.
Huh?
Hey come on, Shaia. What are you peeking
at?
Wake up Tachibana! I heard about the new
transfer student.
Thought I'd check it out.
I've got no problem with that.
But look at what you're wearing.
Isn't today the date of your concert?
I thought I'd just play a little hooky.
What the hell.
Is that him?
He's pretty good-looking!
Huh! It's not the fact that counts...
I've known lots of guys,
so I know but...
You'll find that those kind of guys are
cowards, running at the drop of a hat.
Well, I can't imagine a coward looking
the way he does.
Hey Miss Shaia?
What are you doing, silly? You're
supposed to be in homeroom. You'd better
get back.
No problem.
Son! Is Karin Son here today?
I'm here!
And, are you here because you wanted to
check out the new student as well?
Yes. Well, I hear that he's really
smart.
I thought he could help me
with my studies.
Don't be silly.
You're in the advanced level martial
arts program, aren't you?
Surely you don't expect him to help you
with that kind of material?
But, Randy teaches me all kinds of
things.
That's because he has other motives.
Other motives?
Wow!!
Hey! Keep it quiet! Don't you know that
we could get into serious trouble?
He's the guy who jumped out in front of
the bike this morning.
What are you talking about?
Hey, new guy! Nice threads you got
there!
I like them.
Professor Fudo...
We'll be arriving at the UN building
shortly.
The UN secretariat, the sublime guardian
of the world.
Huh. Amazing how we've come to follow
their lead.
Unacceptable!
The equator is shifting!? It can only be
a miscalculation!
It has to be!
To suggest that this is the chief cause
of recent abnormal global occurrences.
I was assuming that all the reports
received here...
were submitted by each section upon
official approval, without any delay.
"Plan and Construction of Meteorological
Weapons"?
"The Propensity of Human Effects on the
Earth's Crust".
Huh! It wasn't my intention to come here
to discuss science fiction!
We understand that!
It is precisely because of the abnormal
nature of the matter...
that we have called upon you learned
scholars to debate the issue!
Silence!
Now, I'd like to take this opportunity
to introduce someone.
Assigned by the Japanese government, he
is Special Intelligence Officer,
Professor Fudo.
The information contained in these
reports
was checked and corroborated by him upon
our request.
Let him in.
Thank you for coming all this way to
attend, Professor Fudo.
Not at all.
According to your report...
you know, the one about the big
earthquake in Japan.
"The Second Great Tokai Earthquake".
Yes. You suggested that it was caused by
man?
Yes indeed.
Well, who precisely? Perhaps a band of
mysterious giant dragons?
The president of the Belnar Institute,
Shizuru Ozaki.
You mean 'the' Belnar Institute, that
gigantic high school
set by the Japanese government to
educate an elite cadre of experts.
And this Ozaki, who is he?
To explain simply who he is beyond what
can be expected of any man.
Superhuman, no, rather a Messiah.
Messiah.
Yes indeed. Forging his strength from
all of his being...
One day, he achieved
a power beyond all.
So, who is he?
Shizuru Ozaki.
Yes, are you saying that this Ozaki has
reached some sort of enlightenment?
That's correct. But there's more than
that.
Ozaki currently is incapable of human
reason.
He wields his power according to the
will of a distant force.
The will of a distant force? Vague
terms, don't you think?
The will of a force beyond this world
imposed upon earth.
Well, it plays against all sense of
understanding.
If we base our judgment honestly
on what you say...
it seems what you're saying is that
Ozaki possesses a power
that is beyond this world.
You could say that.
What sort of evidence do have to make
such outlandish claims!
I have seen it...
That night of the moon.
Uh... It's near!
Wha... what is that!?
Are you asking us to believe that?
I believe you Professor Fudo.
But Secretary-General...
I don't think we have enough information
to pursue this.
I'm not sure this is something we can
work with on an international level.
As far as I'm concerned,
until we can verify and analyze what
Professor Fudo has just told us...
get as much information on this person
as possible.
It is true that we have had earthquakes
on a worldwide scale in recent years.
We cannot ignore such a clue.
That is all. Adjourned.
Ozaki submits to the unfathomable
forces intent on denying the existence
of this planet called earth.
A plan destined to eventually destroy
the world...
We must stop him.
Enter.
Excuse us.
President Ozaki, Ryo Asahina
Suzu Asahina.
We have come.
It is a beautiful thing.
Indestructible. Hard to think it can be
used as an instrument of tyranny.
Moveover...
as something that can bring to an end
the whole of human history.
Don't you think so?
I have granted this Caizer stone to
many.
However, there have only been a few
candidates sympathetic to our cause.
As for those who have been granted the
stone and have metamorphosed...
There have been only a handful including
you two.
There is Ryo...
who holds the stone
for the both of you.
The one carrying the burden
All for the sake of love.
You are quite a man.
I am counting on you Ryo
It is an honor, Master Ohga.
I am now Ozaki, my dear Ryo
I apologize.
Not to worry.
In this inner sanctum are allowed only
those
whose have been chosen by the haunting
stone.
Oh well. I guess he sees through
everything.
That's it for me. The crazy fool who
missed the show...
shall quietly leave the room.
Are you allowing him to walk out of
here?
To let him be free?
He's a tougher man than meets the eye.
Everything he is is in my hands.
Excuse my insolence.
And?
It concerns the UN conference the other
day.
Due to a lack of information,
no motion was passed.
However, Professor Rampou Fudo,
a faculty member at this school...
was present as an
intelligence officer.
Don't worry about him.
He can't do anything.
Is there anything else?
Yes.
It's about that Isato Kaiza
who happened to be granted the Caizer
stone.
Although we are concerned that he's more
of a physical type,
through our investigation,
we also feel
that he has not attained...
the psychological
maturity to use the Caizer stone.
Don't worry. Ryo Asahina...
Suzu...
I want the both of you to try to
undermine his spirit.
I'll leave the details to you.
His life?
I have no regard.
If that is what it comes to,
I have no use for him.
I understand.
Is that all?
No, one more thing.
A recent arrival at this school
is a transfer student who possesses
a superior psychological power.
Oh? His name?
Kyosuke Shigure.
Do not get involved with him.
I know of him.
You may leave now.
Excuse us.
I see...
A peculiar power shifting in time has
been mocking me.
Although I did make precautions to keep
him from entering.
So it was you, Kyosuke...
Kubira! Enter!
Kubira!
I'm all right Master Kyosuke.
I cannot make sense of the currents
of this dimension.
Yes, I felt the same way as well.
This is something only he could
orchestrate. I'm sure of it.
What will we do Master Kyosuke?
Let's go into town.
Huh?
He is human after all.
A person will always prove his worth
within the company of other people.
He's probably left a trail.
Take human form.
Right away Master.
What are you trying to do?
I am going out on the town with you.
And besides, if I stayed as a dog,
I'd stand out.
Do what you will.
All right.
Miss Shaia, I have brought you a towel.
I will put it in the basket.
Uh... I've brought you a towel.
Oh no, it can't be!
Are you all right!?
Perhaps you have fainted?
Don't you know that silence means
everything's all right? Huh, Ball Boy?
I'm terribly sorry. It'll never happen
again.
Hey, Ball Boy?
Uh, yes Miss Shaia.
Do you know anything about white school
uniforms?
Uh yes. Well, according to my library.
It is known as a "White Orchid".
It was a uniform worn as a symbol of
strength
among juvenile delinquents
at the turn of the century.
A symbol of strength...
I don't think it's anything so shallow
as that...
Uh, does this have to do with anything?
No, no. It's nothing.
No, it's nothing really.
Master Kyosuke!
Yes, I know...
We're shifting into
the devil's quarter dimension.
This is a trap!
I knew it!
It's coming!
I'm ready!
Kyosuke.
Kyosuke! It's been a long time.
My, you've grown!
Master Kyosuke! It's an illusion!
I know that! Don't say anything!
How cute. Looking at me so seriously.
Oh that earring!
You kept it all these years!
I'm so happy!
My sister!
No it can't be. My sister's...
Oh, what's wrong.
Now Kyosuke, you shouldn't wave around
something so dangerous like that.
You're scaring me.
Give it to me.
Well, well...
I'm quite surprised with you.
You have certainly matured well from
a psychological point of view.
But...
what about your physical strength?
You've scored well so far.
Give it your best. Don't disappoint me.
Ozaki!
Die!
You fool!
How dare you get in the way. Die!
Wait!
Evil beast! In this feast of passion,
I'll take back the honor of my sister!
Oh?
Pay your respects to this divine sword!
What!?
Perfect score, Kyosuke. Here's your
prize.
Shit!
Master Kyosuke!
You have matured well over the years,
Kyosuke.
It brings me joy.
The gears are already in motion.
Hurry, my soldiers.
Look over there Suzu.
When that sun sets...
We will fall into an eternal sleep.
And then...
there will be nothing
to break us apart.
That's right. We'll
always be together.
Ryo...
I'm all right.
Be careful Ryo...
you'll get blood on you.
My dear Ryo.
Why do you not accept me?
It's you again. Making fools of us. You
don't know anything about us.
All your talk about Caizer stones...!
It's not something that's going to cure
Suzu's sickness!
Just leave us alone.
I know about it...
I know a lot about you two.
Even about the forbidden love that you
share.
And about Suzu's sad,
incurable illness.
And the grief you suffer as you come
to face imminent death.
I am not like any other man you know.
I will not punish you, and I will not
hurt you.
That's right...
I possess nothing that
will even bind you.
I understand you.
Above all, I do like you both.
I am envious of the pure love
that you have.
Do you think a friend
can stand idly by as...
the final desperate chapter of your
lives comes to a close.
You must believe in me.
I understand.
Dear Brother...
There are more wounds on your body.
It's nothing to make a big deal about.
I'm all right.
No, these wounds appear solely because
of me.
You were granted the Caizer stone for
the both of us.
It is through bearing this strain for
both of us
that you're body is weakening.
It is because of me that your body is
destroying itself.
If that is my destiny...
I am willing to give up everything.
That's all. I'm not afraid.
My dear Brother!
That's right. Whatever happens, I will
protect you.
Who could it be at this time of night.
Hey! You all right man?
You're that rude transfer student from
this morning!
Well, I can't just leave him sitting out
here.
Hey.
You're awake, street fighter.
This is my special apple-garlic tea.
It does the trick.
Is this your home?
Well, you could say that.
Do you remember?
I'm the guy you jumped out in front of
this morning.
I remember. I apologize.
I'm Kyosuke Shigure.
I owe you for this.
Well, don't worry about it.
I get the feeling you have some kind
of deep, secretive past. Am I right?
The look in your eyes this morning said
it all.
And it sure doesn't look like you got
those
wounds from some bar brawl.
They say that I'm a wild and crazy kind
of guy, but the way I feel now...
It's like I just stepped on to
a strange new ship.
You seem to be a curious
kind of guy as well.
Maybe I can help you out,
as long as you're not asking for money.
I lost the most important person in my
life.
I have been fighting...
to get her back.
Was she kidnapped?
No, she's dead now.
She was my older sister.
What I want to bring
back is her honor.
Sounds like revenge.
Yes, I won't deny it.
That's basically my situation.
You're not up against the Mafia
or some corrupt politician, right?
I mean, I understand the kind of people
you're up against.
So tell me, who are you fighting
against.
The president of the Belnar Institute,
Shizuru Ozaki.
Hey hey, come on. Don't be kidding
around.
I mean I've never actually seen the
guy...
but isn't he just some old man?
This isn't some Kung Fu movie,
he can't be very strong.
Why don't you check it out yourself?
There's something I know about you.
If you want to be a real soldier,
do not depend any weapons.
I followed that path as hard
as I could, but it is nothing more...
than a drug and did not
give me any real power against him.
What are you talking about?
I can sense his presence through you as
well.
You must possess it.
You have a gift from him.
You must throw it away.
You tell me the whole story.
Always keep that on your body no matter
what.
When I'm careless sometimes,
I lose my sense of bearings.
For someone like you.
You'll need a passion strong enough
to seduce even the most devout nun.
Hey!
What did you just say?
What on earth could this be?
Huh!? No way!
It's true.
I saw Kaiza leave with Kash.
Aww... that's too bad. I even brought
him a Chinese lunch today.
You should've seen the looks in their
eyes.
Maybe it's some kind of showdown.
Of no. Oh, Isato...
Hey! I never thought you were
so old-fashioned...
about these things,
coming to a place like this.
This kind of setting that the badass
Tachibana would really appreciate.
Don't you want
to make this dramatic?
I figured it would at least make you
respect the formalities.
Keep shooting your mouth off like that,
Mr. Guitarist...
And you'll never be able to stand
on a stage again.
Make no mistake.
This is not a contest.
It's a practice.
Or perhaps, a recreation.
You know, so we can better get along.
Heh!
Let's do it.
Come on.
Hey, come on! That's fighting a bit
dirty don't you think!
But hey. Haven't you gotten
all psyched up now?
Oh yeah, sure. I just have this sudden
need to bash in that nose of yours...
or I think I might just get some kind
of an ulcer.
Don't you think it's time we savor
the main event?
You do know how to use your Soul Gear,
don't you?
You just have to apply those emotions
to the Caizer stone.
It's easy.
Or...
Perhaps you're afraid?
No problem, man. Let's do it!
A showdown of the superhuman!
Come on Caizer stone.
Take me to the realm of the superhuman!
Let's go! Caizer Go!
Well, how about it!
I think I can get into this gig.
There's no encore. Give it your all.
No need to tell me. That's my plan!
Look out!
Backfire Elbow!
Lineck Singer!
Caizer Strike!
Better run away.
I guess that's about it.
It's not over yet.
Isn't this fun?
Absolutely.
Compared to this, my usual fights...
are nothing more than child's play!
That the spirit.
Shit!
Wait! Kash!
What you were just doing is our job.
We will evaluate you on the basis of his
metamorphosis.
Leave the rest to us and back away.
Of course this is Master Ohga's wish.
Sure, do what you want.
But let me just warn you first.
This guy here...
is a genuine one.
Oh yeah?
Just as you heard, they will now play
with you.
Hey hey, wait a minute. We haven't
settled anything here yet!
Settled?
You don't understand, do you?
Give these guys a good going over.
They'll give you more fun than you can
imagine.
Who the hell are they anyway?
What's the matter with you?
Don't you know the president and vice
president of the Student Council.
Student Council!?
In the spirit of friendship and honor,
I will tell you who they are.
They have the power of two Caizer
stones.
You should now know what that means. I'm
not kidding you.
Kash.
All right... All right...
Well, shall we begin Mr. Kaiza.
What for?
I've got no reason to fight you two.
You'll have no choice once I take the
initiative.
You really want to force it, huh?
Kaiza...
You might have already heard from Kash,
but...
whether you can fully utilize
the Caizer stone's power
depends significantly on your
psychological maturity level.
So I have a question for you...
What do you consider the most powerful
psychological state in human beings?
Who knows?
The main purpose in life of all living
creatures is to reproduce and leave
descendants.
It is to love someone
and to have a child with them.
The process basically repeats itself.
The one you love becomes the most
important thing to you.
It follows that in order to protect
the one you love...
it is necessary to
exercise an ultimate power.
Don't you think?
It doesn't seem like you understand.
Not to worry. That is why we're here.
We'll show you what the power
of love is all about.
Wha...? What is this!?
Metamol Twins!
Isn't it beautiful? Kaiza, this is the
form of our love.
Well, as we promised, we will show you
the power of love.
Higher Slash!
Shit!
Is that it?
You don't seem to measure up to the
standards of Master Ohga.
We'll have to take back
the Caizer stone.
Sleep well.
They won with just two moves.
Good-bye Isato Kaiza.
133rd generation Priestess of Heaven,
Karin Son...
Here to the rescue!
Hey Kash.
Were you making fun of Isato just now?
Don't you have the decency to stand by
him...?
Oh no!
Well uh... Is that the Ninin Baoli?
You fool! Run away Karin!
Here I come!
And now for the deathblow!
Kaen Henpou!
Gotccha!
Let me go!
Stop it!
If you hurt her at all...
I'll kill you even if it means
my own death!
This could be interesting.
They say that people are strongest when
they are forced to protect a loved one.
I think we can make you truly
understand what that means.
Although I don't think you can even
stand in that shape.
Karin!
Is that Isato? Isato...
I'll kill you!
What!? His fury cannot be...?
No!
Suzu.
Ryo.
Isato.
Thank you.
I've always known that...
I was everything to you, my dear
Brother.
Just as you were everything to me.
But now, I no longer have anything.
But... But I thought...
If we never got involved with you.
If only you didn't
come into our lives.
If only you never appeared.
Master Ohga!
We will meet again. One day, without a
doubt!
No!
I didn't mean to kill them.
Isato...
I... I never meant to...
How pathetic.
Not really.
It's merely the result of their final
conclusion.
If anything, it will lead to their next
death.
When people, no, when all living
things...
are met with death. There is nothing
afterwards.
Existence is not to be measured by you.
Well, I'll let that go...
Well, my dear friend...
Let's begin what we are here
to accomplish.
You can't mean...!
Once again, you seem to be against it.
However...
I have concluded that it is the way
that the humans most prefer.
I will not tolerate any excuses this
time.
It's getting worse.
What is that!
Isato?
I sense a danger.
What is it that's about to happen?
Sister... Show me the way.
Now, there is not a moment to spare.
Anyone, come and stop me!
I beg you!
He only saw hell spread out
before his eyes.
Eyes filled with regret and repent
are staring out.
No one can resist the fate
that befell them.
When he controlled all,
he thought he was immortal.
However, on that unforgettable day...
the major catastrophe
deprived people of everything.
The chaos caused him
to become mortal once again.
As the gears grind into a new era...
will their ignorance
be proven?
Master Kyosuke...
there are forty-eight.
As you suspected...
the NMW seems to be
the most vulnerable.
We'll step in.
That's obviously something
they have not overlooked.
I advise you to reconsider.
It's what's called
"statistical planning".
If it is indeed so, it proves
that they still think like mortals.
Then I still have a chance.
Hello, Kyosuke.
I have something I want to ask you.
Do you have a minute?
There are poor men
who save themselves...
by praying to keep their
sole personality.
There are also imbeciles
who learn nothing...
from killing thousands of people.
I will become the one
to judge their values.
But I cannot promise
to be fair to them.
There's no turning back,
you know that, Suzu?
I do not mind. My brother died,
and I accepted my fate to be the same.
Even plants die without water,
but I lived on.
Allow me to go, Master Ooga.
Direct me to my path.
It's just as he said...
they were drugging people
with words.
Drugged people can do anything
and get off with it.
But I don't want to stoop
to that level.
Then tell us
what this Kaiser stone is!
No lies. Tell us word for word
without twisting the truth!
Stop fighting, guys!
Okay, I'll tell you, but it may
be difficult to understand.
I don't think you should listen.
Too much knowledge will deprive you
of your beauty.
Too much knowledge?
My family's heritage is music.
My father and mother were both
well-known composers.
And I inherited their skill.
But I was bored.
With just one stroke
of an instrument...
people around me applauded
till their hands swelled.
My life was set
from the time I was born.
I wondered why we had the ability
to think.
I know it's childish.
I met him then.
Oosaki?
He was going by the name of Ooga.
Ooga?
And he gave me
the Kaiser stone crystal.
He told me that I can be reborn
with it.
I thought that it was foolish
at the time...
but it was beautiful,
so I kept it.
That was the birth
of Hell-stinger, my counterpart.
I liked it.
There were rumors of a dark night.
I wanted to keep dreaming about it.
But I was immediately
awakened to reality.
I hate reality,
but at least it wakes me.
I finally found you.
I'm the death you've been
waiting for.
Say your prayers Ooga.
You can't satisfy me
with that little toy.
All I want is you.
All you want is me.
Let's go for it.
Fool!
I don't know what you're trying
to do...
but you can't threaten me
with such illusions.
What was that?
Tell me!
That was the end.
We don't have much time.
Do what you must do,
even if you have to kill me.
My theory is that within him
is another him.
You mean a double personality?
I think it's a doppelganger.
I don't know about that.
I think you're on the right track,
but it's not that simple.
- Look who's talking?
- Who does he think he is?
Do you know why it's red?
- Don't ask me.
- The Kaiser stone is made from blood.
That doesn't mean it's made
from actual blood.
He is constantly fighting
with this other self.
It may sound ridiculous,
but it's stained with blood.
This is Ooga's scream.
It's the leftover energy
that flows out...
from his will to survive.
- I have no idea what you mean.
- Me neither.
I didn't think you would.
Let's put it in layman's terms.
Let's compare it to swords.
When a sword smith
creates a masterpiece...
he always creates another sword
of the same shape.
It's the yin and the yang,
the black and the white.
In order to create a sword
with good powers...
he must create another sword
to absorb the evil powers.
And at the time of completion...
the evil sword
will be condemned forever.
This is how a good sword is born.
The Kaiser stone works the same way.
As the negative energy within Ooga
expands...
the positive energy
starts to flow out.
That is, the good energy
has the same amount of power as Ooga.
And that is the positive power
of the Kaiser stone.
I'm begging to get what this little
Kaiser stone is all about.
But why is this negative energy
trying to destroy the Earth?
I would like to ask
the same question.
Stop playing ignorant.
Well, we can laugh about it
all we want...
but there is definitely
something going on.
You're blabbing again.
But I guess we just
have to do it.
Do what?
Stop Ooga.
I knew you were going to say that.
I probably would have been
against it before...
but I saw your Asahina-Twins.
I have to give you credit
for your powers.
Don't be cynical.
As long as I know the truth...
it's not my style
to keep calm about it.
You're not going to lose, either!
It's our duty to save this planet.
This planet's in danger...
because the principal
is taken over...
by some evil force, right?
This is my big chance
to save the world!
I'm amazed that you figured it out all
right.
No way!
Why not!
We're not talking about humans here.
We're fighting against
an impenetrable power.
It's crazy even for us who have the
ability to counter it.
All you've got as a weapon
is that lousy stick.
That's suicide
as far as I'm concerned.
Well, that settles it. You just quietly
wait it out right here.
We'll invite you to the victory party
when it's all over.
But, I want to go!
Huh?
I wanta go! I wanta go!
Even my parents always said I'd never
measure up.
I've worked all my life
to prove them wrong...!
Oh well, I guess
everyone's got some kind of situation.
Set me right if I'm wrong about you
Ohga.
Like Indian warriors fighting on foot
against the cavalry.
Or the long swim of an army of ants
joining together in a torrent.
Even so...
Could my life as
determined by will have any meaning?
Come on over to my place.
It's right near here.
Really...
Come'on.
Area E West, Kanmon district, 100%
deployed.
120% penetration rate.
150% control of sector.
No indeterminate factors.
Standby until further orders. Standby
limit is 128 minutes. Over and out.
Gamon.
It's not going to work at the Gamon gate
no matter how hard we try.
What should we do.
Master Kyosuke?
I will use the divine sword.
You mustn't!
You mustn't use your ultimate weapon
at this early stage!
You will loose all of your energy!
Don't worry about it.
I've worked it out.
I've been measuring
his strength all along.
Using the divine sword now
will not adversely affect me.
Get out of the way, Kubira.
I will not!
You are lying to me,
Master Kyosuke.
You think nothing of it even when your
flesh torn.
You rise up to fight even when your
bones are crushed.
I have witnessed
your relentless spirit
for all of this time.
Now is the time...
Please use my body
as much as you have to.
I will let myself be destroyed.
You can't.
If he sees your spirit rising up from
your body, that will be the end of it.
But...
Hi! You there...
You seem to be having trouble
with that gate not opening.
Not to worry now that I, Misty Shaia,
has arrived on the scene!
Lt'll be as easy as pie!
Hishizaki?
Hey, come on. Why can't you play along?
I am Misty Shaia,
the mystery princess of the school.
Hey, come on. Don't ignore me!
Miss Shaia, maybe we should get going.
You are embarrassing yourself.
Miss...
What is this all about.
You know, even I have my reasons.
Boys shouldn't be so nosy about such
little details.
If you feel obliged
to lend me a hand...
after that talk we had this
afternoon, you're not welcome.
Leave now.
I merely ran into you
at an outdoor concert. That's all.
Don't be so vain!
Ball Boy!
Let's go, Boy!
Yes, Miss Shaia.
Shining Triangle!
The gate has opened!
Master Kyosuke!
You did it this time.
Kubira.
Yes?
Take her to a safe place.
Master Kyosuke...
That's an order.
To watch over my Master Kyosuke is the
most important duty of my existence!
Please let me go along!
No.
Master Kyosuke!
On Kirikiara
Haraharatsuta Yariaura Hila Hon Souka.
Seal!
Please open the door Master Kyosuke!
I will come with you!
Master Kyosuke! Master Kyosuke!
Is this the end? Is this the end of all
that we've been through together!
Is this the end?
Forgive me, Kubira.
If he sees your rising spirit...
He'll be given spellbinding power strong
enough to destroy with one glance.
I can no longer bear to see the face of
one who follows my path.
I don't want to see it.
Well, well. So it is you...
Kyosuke!
My dear friend,
you're not acting like yourself.
You will never be happy with this silly
game you are playing.
You don't seem to have much patience.
Well, well. Are we afraid? As the sands
continue to flow, slowly burying you?
If there was a little more time, with
you I can...
No, I will not say it.
The sands that fill up my ears must be
cleared away first.
Then we can go our separate ways.
It is not only sand...
The fire and water
will also support life.
All of it plays a part.
Do not worry.
As long as divine providence is not
defied...
life shall be reborn.
Come in closer.
Fake beasts.
I'll destroy you all.
I think I have spoken too much
about what happened.
I said a lot of things, without any
regard for your feelings.
I was selfish.
I'm sorry.
But...
But that's not right.
Besides... it's revenge, against your
brother.
My sister...
carried half of my burden.
Happiness and despair, all of my
feelings were for my sister.
It has been seething within me.
Do you think a person can live missing
half their body?
That's right.
This is something that I myself must
take back, even if for my own sake.
If that's the case...
that half you are looking for...
can come from me.
Sister!
Kyosuke...
There's something I want you to keep for
me.
An earring?
It's a keepsake from my sister.
Keep it, no...
I want you to have it.
I can't take it.
It's too important to you.
It's all right.
I may be going to where my sister is.
If I wore something like this,
I'd be laughed at.
Kyosuke.
Could you put it on for me?
Sure.
Like this?
What a fool I am.
Have I not learned anything.
I must never have those
thoughts again.
I apologize.
Forgive me.
Kyosuke.
I'm glad you have awoken, Miss Shaia.
Ball Boy.
You're awake.
Did you bring me here?
Don't get me wrong.
I saved you...
only because Master Kyosuke
ordered me to.
Otherwise you would have been left
abandoned in the cold.
Moreover...
those were his final words and I could
not ignore them.
Then...
Kyosuke...
Master Kyosuke...
will not return.
No!
Hm?
Shadow Run!
Higher Slash!
It looks like my warning
meant nothing.
That's not true.
It's because of what you told me...
that I've been able to direct my powers
for the purposes intended.
Compared to the timewhen all I thought
about was you...
it's quite a step.
How clever.
Whatever...
I don't think there's any time to think
about it now.
I'm sorry but you're
getting in the way.
I can even feel his presence
within you.
The perverted power...
The hypocrisy of your devotion...
It's all very unsavory.
Come on, don't be picking on him.
Only I have that right as his partner in
crime.
Who are you?
You seem to be under
his spell as well.
Leave now. This is no place for low-rent
mercenaries.
I suppose you can always skip out on the
rent.
I might have to pay interest.
Anyway, don't come after me.
Having him confuse me
with you two would be regrettable.
He sure likes to be dramatic.
All right, we should get going too.
I'm sure he'll be fine alone.
Yeah.
Retreat! Retreat now!
What are these
creatures!?
The most advanced weaponry
of the UN has no effect on them!
Wha... What is this young girl!?
Even I will not loose against guys like
these.
I'm not in a very good mood today!
Prepare yourselves!
What is this place?
It looks like some kind of theme park
I went to as a kid.
I guess Ohga built himself a nice little
playground.
She looks like the
Princess of the land.
Uh... It's you!
This is your day of reckoning...
Isato Kaiza!
Ever since you destroyed
my other half...
it's a struggle even
to breathe.
But this is where it
all ends.
Just wait a minute!
Do you remember what my brother
told you?
Whether you can fully utilize
the Caizer stone's power...
depends on your psychological
strength.
And it is when you have to protect
the one you love...
that you are at your strongest.
That's right. My brother was
always right.
By accepting this
Caizer stone into my body
I've come to understand.
The time has come to show you
the power of love!
Metamol Slave!
Kash!
Stay out of this one!
Die! Isato Kaiza!
Graviton...
Fraber!
Together they fought...
in the spirit of youthful camaraderie.
Isato Kaiza...
In the spirit of his own jubilant
re-awakening...
he seeks to make amends for
a wrong he committed.
He faces his vengeful foe, haunted like
a criminal.
Kash Mizutani...
Trapped within the society he so
despised...
and which he understood would soon meet
its own demise...
he strives to unshackle himself from the
burdens of his childhood.
Kyosuke Shigure...
The scent of revenge permeating his
body.
Fighting to prove his own worth as a
human...
setting up the confrontation.
Deep within his conscience...
he was seeking to wipe out the memory
of his own brother.
Also...
there is a man who continues
to wait in the dark.
What is it that he is waiting for?
Is it a creation... or is it utter
destruction?
The moment is at hand.
The final chapter of this legend...
is about to begin.
The Voltage Fighter: Gowcaizer 3
They haven't learned a thing.
Then again... neither have I.
Isato...
Oh no!
Ball Boy!
That can only mean...
Miss Shaia!
Hey!
Let's get 'em, Karin!
Let's do it!
Shining Cluster! Shoot!
The ultimate...
Kaen Henpou!
That's perfection!
We did it! Yet again!
I'm going to rub you out.
Die, Gowcaizer!
No, Isato Kaiza!
Get out of the way, Kash.
It is certainly not
my intention to kill you.
You should know.
I've recently considered doing volunteer
work.
Well I see that you're going to
volunteer your life this time.
Graviton Knuckle!
Beated Needle!
On Bazaragini Harachihataya Souka.
Ha!
It is not easy to be laying in wait.
I've been held in an unchanging state
over the past 3 years, Kyosuke.
I can see right through you.
Anger will reduce your powers by half.
Have you forgotten
what I've taught you.
Ozaki...
I have one last question for you.
What is it?
Why did you have to harm my sister.
Was it because you needed me!
Was it because you needed my power!
That's right.
I needed Mia so that I could give you a
special power.
And once you were re-born
with your new power...
I needed to increase the strength
of that power...
And Mia had to die.
It was my intention all along.
Is that so...
Do you remember, Kyosuke?
Day in and day out...
late into dusk,
I taught you how to use your powers.
And you responded very well in every
way.
A most excellent ability.
Just as I expected.
Everything seemed to be proceeding just
as I wanted it to.
However...
I sensed that I miscalculated
something.
And that was the love that you began to
show me.
Perhaps you saw me as a father figure.
I didn't expect it at all.
So in order to break
that relationship...
although premature, I took the life of
Mia.
However...
It seemed that I'd made another
miscalculation.
Shut up!
That is, the love she had for me was
deeper than I could have imagined.
Even when I sentenced her
to her death...
she stepped forward
and offered her neck.
What was necessary...
were the anguished cries...
Kyosuke, it was the neck of Mia
as she cried for your help.
It weighed heavily on me.
Shut up!
You were siblings hungering for love.
It's really a question of disposition,
but it's so sad.
Shut up!
Don't rush it, Kyosuke...
Now is the time...
that I will reveal the other half
of my soul...
that of the providence of god.
What?
The judgment...
Stop it!
You had to but in, huh?
Just stay out of this, it'll end
quickly.
Shut your mouth!
You want this to end in another
meaningless sacrifice!?
Do what you want then.
But let me warn you first
that she no longer has a human soul.
Your cheap humanistic approach will land
you in a grave.
I don't think it's the time to be
bickering.
Or do you think I'm a pushover.
What's wrong?
You afraid?
Or are you merely plotting your response
to my attack?
Come and get me.
The Soul Gear! That's suicide!
Isato!
I don't know what you've got in mind...
but you fool yourself if you think you
can stand up to me without Soul Gear!
Suzu Asahina!
If your goal is to kill me pure and
simple...
then I'm not going to stop you!
Come!
Look. You are human after all.
When you cause harm to another person...
you will surely be hurting
your own soul.
However much you want to kill that
person.
No matter what happens, I will protect
you.
I love you, Suzu.
My dear brother...
I'm sorry.
Kash! Kash!
Hey hey, don't be
taking advantage of me.
I don't like being called
only when it's convenient.
Come on. I'm sorry about before.
Just try to save her somehow.
There's something weird going on.
Oh no...
The energy of the Caizer is building up
within her.
If it ruptures, that's the end of her.
Stop kidding around! Do something!
You're the authority on the Caizer!
What authority?
Kash.
I'll take my Caizer...
and align it against hers
to neutralize its power.
If it fails, then I suppose we go to
heaven.
You go on ahead.
You've got other things
to take care of.
Don't worry, I won't kill her.
Yeah. All right.
I'm counting on you, Kash.
Don't get lost.
He can run already.
He sure can recover quickly.
Well, just as you wished...
I am volunteering to risk my life
on account of you.
How did I develop such a
self-sacrificing character like this.
Maybe I was railing against all that
uptight society from my childhood.
Listen carefully, Kash.
Since you've been born into this
family...
you will lead a life in which your
performances yield $10,000 per minute...
10 minutes will yield you $100,000.
Ignore all distractions and never waver.
Don't let anyone take your genius
away from you.
You must live your life for yourself.
Only for yourself.
Well, so much for that.
Master Kyosuke.
Penetrate! Kamikabura!
Fire Dance!
Your body breaking apart already?
You mere human.
When not in a group, you cannot stand up
alone.
You are foolish indeed.
You bastard!
That's right. I am not the man you used
to know.
At least on the surface.
I am myself, and you,
and your friend...
A great many people
are embodied within me.
What? What are you saying?
Don't you understand?
Well, I'll forgive you.
I suppose it's beyond the understanding
of a dying man such as you.
To think that you are the one
they await.
Like Pygmalions worshipping the statue
they created...
Pathetic humans.
It will be but a flash.
Master Kyosuke.
Kubira! Is that you?
You can reprimand me later.
The dog!
Kubira!
Forgive me, Kubira.
Die!
Kubira!
Congratulations on your victory.
Why did you...
Kubira.
I've always considered this to be my
final duty.
In order for you to carry out
that duty...
I would have had to return to you.
But I am now all alone.
Master Kyosuke...
Please do not fear.
I will always be near you.
And besides...
You are no longer alone.
Kubira.
Kubira!
Kyosuke!
Kaiza?
Kyosuke! Behind you!
Kyosuke!
This can't be what Kash was talking
about!
This is JG02. There is a mysterious
energy emitting from...!
Who the hell are you anyway!
What did you do with Kyosuke!
I am the will of all creation...
Omni Exist.
What? Omni Exist!?
The embodiment of all thought existing
in nature.
I have absorbed within me all of the
desires of humankind.
That is why I came into being.
What?
I have until now only existed as
thought.
But Shizuru Ozaki...
His desires had reached the level
of my own.
And through him...
I was first able to begin to carry out
my destiny.
You humans are despised...
by all of existence.
Bound by the rules you created...
an insane humanity bent on destroying
everything.
The recklessness of disposing into outer
space that which you cannot process...
The people who live on a planet bathed
in ultraviolet rays...
that reach every corner of the surface.
That is what you are.
The destruction of earth...
It is the desire of all humankind, and I
am the one who will carry it out.
What the hell are you talking about!
That's not what I want!
Is that so...
I'm sure that you've feared the future
at least at one time in your life.
The good things and the bad.
It is surely frightening to look at the
future no matter what your position.
A world that does not progress...
That is something that's certain to
bring relief.
Even the one you refer to as Kyosuke
desires this.
Even you wish it deep in your
subconscious.
The end of everything.
You're wrong! I'm not like that!
Is that so...
But eventually, my powers will destroy
the earth.
Then all will end.
I'm not going to let you.
Then you will have to try and stop me.
You can only succeed if either
your energy exceeds mine...
or if all of existence can be
persuaded...
and cause me to completely loose
my will.
Both seem preposterous at this point.
Sounds interesting...
Well I'm not much
of a pursuasive talker...
but to exceed your power is something
I can give a shot at.
Caizer Go!
Caizer Strike!
Burny Samona!
Miss Shaia.
I hope Isato and them are gonna be all
right.
Don't worry about it...
There're not going to loose that easily.
You're right!
They're not gonna loose.
Kyosuke.
Shit. I can't let it end like this.
No way, Isato! It's not in your nature
to give up like this.
Come on, Isato!
You fool.
Shit!
Kash!
Knowing the kind of guy you are...
I figured you'd be playing up
that high drama yours.
And I was right.
Hey, what did you do with the girl?
Don't worry. I delivered the princess to
her castle.
Hyper Voltage...!
Transform Hellstinger!
Heh! And what did you come here for?
Huh?
Haven't you heard?
I came to round up the finale.
Knowing you, this might never
come to an end.
I don't need any of that at a time like
this.
As I suspected, to band together...
is a human tendency.
I suppose that can't be helped.
Here she comes!
Yeah. I'll set up a decoy.
You go straight for the attack.
All right!
Lineck Singer!
Now's your chance, Isato!
Isato!
You're doing very well.
You have my praise.
I will now give you your reward!
Are you sleepy, Kyosuke?
Yes.
I'm sleepy, dear brother.
Very sleepy.
No Kyosuke. You mustn't sleep yet.
My sister!
It is now that we need your strength the
most.
Kubira is here too.
I cannot see anything.
Besides... I'm no longer...
Take my hand, Kyosuke...
I will show you the way.
It is my final wish.
Brother!
Kyosuke.
Quite amazing...
To think that the human will can be so
sublime...
You haven't seen nothing yet.
We can be foolish and we often fail.
We can also think evil thoughts.
But on the other hand...
only humans will sacrifice their lives
to help save those close to them.
Heh! Well I'm just the kind of fool
that'll fall for that.
Using your power to save everyone isn't
something that hasn't crossed my mind.
I'll show you what it's all about...!
The unlimited possibilities of human
beings!
You've got quite an attitude.
It is time that I show you the eternal
agony of nothingness.
This doesn't look good...
These forces are like no other we've
felt yet.
Isato!
Foolish one...
Wha...!
What's going on!?
Kyosuke!
How could you, my friend?
Forgive me...
but I am human after all.
Now's the time. Come Kaiza!
But... But Kyosuke!
Die!
Come!
Kash!
OK!
Kyosuke!
I've paid my debt.
Die!
Here me well, humankind...
I have not given up.
And I have not died.
Just a momentary lapse of direction.
I will return at anytime that you
desire.
Anytime.
Isato...!
Welcome back.
Good to be here.
That's right.
I did not want to kill you.
I just wanted to bring you back.