www.SubDESU-H.net
Wait a sec...
Wait– Huh?
Akira-chan, I wonder what you would like to have for snack  this evening?
My, my...
Hey, hey, Akira-chan...
This person... Doesn't she kinda resemble me?
No she doesn't. Yuu-nee isn't...
Oh is that so? Oh, yeah!
Listen up, Akira-chan.
You can't be watching this.
If you watch these kinds of things over and over again,
you'll become a pervert.
W-Well, that belongs to a friend of mine.
I'll be confiscating this,
and I will return this to your friend, okay?
Yuu-nee, don't!
You can't do that!
You are a guy alright, Akira-chan.
It's gotten so big.
Yuu-nee, what are you...?
You don't really need pornos like these.
If only you had asked me...
Akira-chan...
Is this your first time masturbating?
Yes.
I see.
Then...
I'll help you out.
I really should have taught you this earlier,
but you didn't seem interested in things like that.
Amazing, Akira-chan.
Yuu-nee, why are you doing something like this...?
For me, as long as you become a fine man,
I'll do anything for you.
If I rub it like this, it'd feel a lot better than when you do it yourself, right?
Yuu-nee, it's weird.
I'm feeling weird.
My, my... It looks like you are in pain.
Akira-chan, no need to hold back.
I'm going to make you cum.
Now, Akira-chan, cum while I stroke it with my hands.
It's okay to let it all out.
Wow.
Everything that was built up inside you is coming out.
You came a lot, didn't you?
Yuu-nee, what are you...?
I'm cleaning it up.
That thing is dirty!
Akira-chan, you musn't say those things.
There's nothing dirty about you at all.
It already released a lot earlier...
... but it's still this lively.
I'm really happy.
You, who I treat as a real younger brother, has now become quite the stud.
It's stiff, and it's twitching again.
Akira-chan, are you starting to feel aroused again?
Yeah.
You're still not satisfied yet, are you?
I'll have to turn the pleasure up a notch then.
I'll use my breasts this time.
Are you ready, Akira-chan?
Don't move.
I'll do it like this.
I'll be positioning it between my breasts, okay?
Well, Akira-chan? Does it feel good?
Yeah.
I am glad.
I'll start moving slowly then, okay?
I can feel...
... the twitching of your cock.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
You want to cum, right?
Onee-chan will let you cum this way.
Delicious...
It's a bit difficult and scary for me to shove it in completely.
But I will still show you.
Is that okay?
What a lively cock this is!
Can you feel it?
Here, here!
By the way, are you worried about something at the moment?
No, it's really nothing, but...
Really?
I'm responsible for you while Akino-san is away.
I'll listen to whatever it is on your mind.
Yuu-nee, to tell you the truth...
W
I'll give you a healing kiss
The intruding lady's
shameful
sexual cure
Original Animation
The carnivorous glasses
doctoress, Kimika~
The over-indulgent lab
coat fallen angel
Well then, please take it out.
"Akira-kun", is it?
The one Yuu mentioned.
Yes!
If you don't let me examine the affected part,
I won't be able to diagnose the problem properly, now would I?
I understand.
Is that so?
For me not to have noticed you worrying about it...
I'm a failure as an elder sister.
Do you know something about this, Yuu-nee?
I'm sorry.
I don't know much about males.
What should I do?
Akira-chan's really troubled.
Oh, I know! Senpai!
It's going to be okay, Akira-chan.
We'll just have an expert doctor take a look at it!
A doctor?
Leave it to me.
So you don't have pubic hair... yet.
I don't see any physical abnormalities either.
I see.
You have started going through puberty, right?
Do you experience wetting your pants in the morning if you don't masturbate?
Yes.
So you really are through with your childhood stage.
Umm... Yesterday was my first time masturbating.
Is that so?
So you masturbated for the first time yesterday.
Your face is all red.
It's normal for someone your age to masturbate.
No need to be conscious about it.
R-Really?
I thought I'd grow body hair faster if I started masturbating.
That's not true.
Even if you masturbate, you won't necessarily grow pubic hair any faster.
You're an interesting one.
So you really don't know anything.
That's okay.
We'll surely find the cause of your problem.
Please do.
That's good.
That's very good.
Let's have a closer look, shall we?
Were you expecting something to happen?
No, actually...
You understand what hospitals are for, right?
I wonder if Akira-chan's okay.
Senpai's looking after him so he should be just fine, right?
Getting a boner in a hospital, huh?
So I guess it feels good to have someone touch your cock, right?
Answer me honestly.
Your cock grew big when it was touched, right?
What a helpless lad.
Umm, well...
You're really cute.
Do you feel embarrassed?
Shall I do something more embarrassing then?
Yesterday was your first time masturbating, right?
Yes.
Then, is it your first time experiencing something like this, too?
Are you hiding something?
Answer me honestly.
Yuu-nee, umm...
She did it for you, right?
She is excessively caring when it comes to you.
So?
What did she do for you?
She used her breasts a bit...
She used her hands, and even her breasts.
Not bad Yuu.
It's at the very base...
This is...
Tell me if you're about to cum.
It's twitching.
Are you about to cum?
It's okay.
Let it out.
How cute.
You're cute, Akira-kun.
My switch  got turned on.
I'll have you take responsibility for this.
Maybe I should take your virginity?
Is it your first time seeing a pussy?
My...
Seems you have already seen one.
But you haven't seen inside it, right?
If you gaze at it so intently, I'll end up getting horny.
I'm sorry.
This is the labia part.
It's thin, and it's twitching.
And inside this, you insert the penis.
Do you see how mine's also getting wet like yours?
You want to insert it now, right?
It's going in.
Look carefully, Akira-kun.
It's entering.
It's all the way in.
You're no longer a virgin.
Congratulations, Akira-kun.
How cute.
When I look at your face...
It's like I'm raping you, and I feel aroused.
I'm...
Not yet.
Don't cum yet.
Keep it up just a little more.
This is good.
Your cock feels good.
About to cum?
You're about to cum, aren't you?
You can't though. You are still young.
Hold it in a bit more.
If Yuu comes in and sees us doing this...
Your cock is getting bigger.
Your troubled face looks great.
I'm thrilled to see it.
I'm about to...!
It's okay now.
You've held it in long enough, so I will now reward you.
You can...
You can cum inside me.
It's okay.
I-I'm cumming!
It's coming out.
The hot thing's coming out.
I guess cumming this much is already enough.
Umm, so was this part of the treatment?
Do you think it was?
You're really cute.
www.SubDESU-H.net
I'm going to give you my diagnosis now.
This is a very special medical case.
This is also the first time that I've witnessed a case such as this.
I'll try to do something with the treatment and medication, so...
This is something that cannot be simply treated by medicine as this is quite the rare case.
So what should we do?
Well, to put it simply,
in order for him to balance out his hormones,
he needs to continually have intercourse with women.
Intercourse?
If he fails to engage sexually on a regular basis,
his penis might become dysfunctional, or it might even grow smaller.
Umm... Kimika-senpai, by intercourse, you mean...
You'd understand better if I used the word "fucking" or "sex", right?
It's okay.
I'm here for you.
So Akira-chan needs to have sex in order for him to be treated, correct?
Like how I saw Kimika-senpai do such a thing for him when she came here.
Getting big like this...
Kimika-senpai and I are going to stay over tonight.
We'll do our best to help you, okay?
In order for Akira-chan to completely recover from his illness,
we had Kimika-senpai stay overnight for this, but...
This is to help Akira-chan recover...
Akira-chan...
Oh, no...
I'm not able endure anymore.
I can hear sloppy lewd sounds.
Akira-chan.
Akira-chan...
Your Onee-chan is...
Akira-chan?
My my, what are you doing there?
I heard your voice and it sounded like you were in pain.
Umm, are you sick?
Are you worried about me?
That's right.
I'm really in pain right now.
I'll do anything for you, Yuu-nee.
Come here.
Akira-chan...
I'm going show you everything that is me.
Akira-chan, l-look here.
I want you to lick this part.
Okay, I understand.
That small pea-like thing over here.
Pea... You mean the clitoris?
Seems like you already know about it.
Did you hear it from Kimika-senpai?
I see.
I'm getting quite jealous now.
Your tongue...
Your tongue!
Keep it up and lick inside my pussy.
I'm getting completely licked by you...
Wow.
I can sense how wet I am.
Just a little more over there...
Akira-chan, inside that is...!
No...
I think I don't want it this way after all.
Akira-chan.
Come.
Inside me.
Get inside me.
Does it hurt?
Are you okay?
I'm okay, so put it in.
Huh?
Continue going in.
It's okay to hit the womb.
I'm going to be fine.
So, keep going, okay?
Inject me with your cock.
I'm fine, Akira-chan.
I'm just a bit surprised because it's my first time to receive an injection that deep.
I'm happy.
I was able to give you my first time.
You can move now.
My insides are comfortable with you inside now.
I'm now one with you, aren't I?
How is it?
Do you feel good inside me?
It really feels good.
I'm happy that I've made you happy.
Don't hold back.
Just move as you want to.
Akira-chan, try grinding your cock inside me.
Angle it upward a bit more.
Akira-chan, that's good.
I feel you inside me.
I can feel you in me.
I'm filled with you, Akira-chan.
My insides are filled!
Akira-chan, it's alright.
You can cum and release it inside me anytime you want Akira-chan.
Release it.
Release it!
It's coming out.
Akira-chan's cumming inside me...
I'm glad that you're my first time.
Seems like we both received treatment, huh?
Well then, Akira-chan.
The job today is temporary one only, so I think I will return home early.
Going to school?
Okay.
Take care!
My, my.
Quite bold there, Akira-kun.
I-I'm sorry...
And now you try to escape after I thought you were daring enough.
Isn't that mean?
Umm...
I made a mistake, so...
Do you want to see me pee?
Imagining you watching me pee kinda makes me kinda horny.
Wai–!
Kimika-sensei!
Can you feel it?
This is where females urinate from.
I'm taking a pee, but it feels like I'll end up releasing another kind of fluid instead.
Amazing.
For peeing to feel this good...
Akira-kun's cock is also getting really stiff.
Shall we do the treatment here?
Wow.
Akira-kun's thing is...!
Your stiff cock is rubbing against the inside of my wet pussy.
It's so intense. Your cock has started to fit perfectly inside my pussy.
I'm starting to lose it as you thrust into me so aggressively.
Your cock's amazing.
It's so hard and pulsating.
There... It feels great there.
Thrust it in more!
That's good.
You're hitting my sweet spots.
It feels good.
This is the treatment that Senpai uses to treat Akira-chan...
Senpai is also doing her best to treat him.
So I should also....
Yuu-san, have you found it yet?
I'm sorry, Sana-chan.
I couldn't find it.
It's fine.
I'll search for it when I drop by later tonight.
Okay.
By the way, where's Akira?
Akira-chan seems to be still asleep.
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
Do it more! More intensely!
Yes!
My pussy is being used roughly.
It feels like it's being punished by your stiff and large cock.
That's great, Akira-kun.
You're getting better at this.
Just continue until I...
www.SubDESU-H.net