My, my, Akira-chan.
Just wait for a bit, okay?
After I finish cleaning.
I'll prepare a meal after I finish cleaning.
Akira-chan, is something bothering you?
Well, umm...
How about we do our "treatment" already?
My breasts are now wrapped in your hands.
They have a weird shape now because of your hands.
Yuu-nee's breasts feel tender.
Your thing is already getting big.
It looks very stiff, and it seems tight in there.
Just you wait.
I'm going to help you out.
It looks very lively.
It's really stiff.
I'm doing this while you're fondling my breasts.
Akira-chan, you can cum anytime you want.
Want to do something more perverted?
Umm...
I said "more perverted" but...
This pose feels a bit too embarrassing for me.
For you to want to do it from behind,
you've really become a lot perverted, Akira-chan.
Akira-chan, I'm a little scared.
This is...
Akira-chan, my pussy feels full.
It's teasing me deep inside.
I feel like losing it with your cock.
So Kimika-senpai taught you a lot of things.
Yuu-nee, let's go to the sofa.
Huh?
Akira-chan, your cock is still inside me.
No way...
Yuu-neesan and Akira are...
I called out earlier and no one responded.
The door wasn't locked, so I just entered.
You're still deep inside me...
It's intense, and it feels very good.
This is too lewd!
Make yourself feel better, Yuu-nee.
Won't you hate a perverted big sister?
There's no way I'd ever hate you, Yuu-nee!
Even if... Even if I become really, really perverted?
I'd like to even see that!
I'm getting stirres up.
I'm getting rubbed inside.
I'm about to...!
Akira-chan, it's okay.
You can cum inside me anytime.
Akira-chan...!
I'm going to cum!
Akira-chan's pouring a lot inside me...
Your thing is twitching a lot inside my womb.
Yuu-neesan, she had such a sloppy look...
Oh no, I have to go get the things that I forgot at school!
Well then, I'll try not to be late,
so look forward to dinner later!
I'll give you a healing kiss
The intruding lady's
shameful
sexual cure
Original Animaiton
The cute and horny district -
Lady teacher and the excellent
shameful sister mix
Why were they...?
Wait, are they lovers or something?
Besides...
Also, Kimika-sensei said something about how it's his treatment.
And that face of hers...
W-what the heck was that, really?
A-Akira!
W-what is it with you?
Why are you here?
W-what are you also doing here, Sana?
This is our house, you know...
I just thought of using your toilet.
S-Sana!
This is not the toilet!
No, I...
What? You can do it with Yuu-neesan and Kimika-sensei,
but you can't do it with me?
What are you saying?
This is embarrassing so get out already.
I said, I'm going to do this "treatment" thing of yours to you!
Wait, calm down Sana.
Shut up, just show it to me!
Ow, ow...
Hey, don't try to hide it!
What are you getting embarrassed for?
Even if you say that...
It's fine so take your hands off already.
O-okay then.
This is your standard treatment procedure, right?
Then there's nothing to be embarrassed about!
It's getting aroused...
It twitches a lot just be touching the tip.
They say it'll feel good if I do it like this.
This is also good too, right?
I know quite a lot about these...
This hot and stiff thing inside my mouth is going wild.
Something feels like...
This is, Akira's cum.
So this is what it tastes like.
Sana, we're already done here, right?
What? It felt great for you earlier and you're
already done with me now that you came?
Stop fooling around.
Sana...!
It feels arousing, right?
Feeling horny again after looking at my body?
It's okay.
I mean, it's okay to do to me whatever you did to Yuu-neesan.
It hurts.
Does it hurt a lot?
Well it's my first time,
so it would hurt, right?
I'm fine, so go on.
Oh, ouch...
Sana, blood is coming out.
Of course, I said it's my first time, right?
Is that how it is?
It's the proof of my still pure body so you should be pleased, you know?
Just move around the way you want to.
Just come all the way.
You don't have to mind me.
If you suddenly come strong like that...
Oh no...!
What are you thinking? Thrusting intensely
already when it's just my first time.
I-I'm sorry!
Be a bit gentler.
I do want to make you feel good, but I'm still...
Anyway, just go easy at first, okay?
It hurts...
Does it feel good?
It feels great inside you, Sana.
I also feel you inside me.
You can try doing it a bit harder now.
Akira's right at my very insides...
Hey, Akira...
I want a position where I can see you clearly.
I can see you well now.
Wow, it's going even deeper than earlier!
Akira, you don't have to move.
I'm going to do it for you.
This is... so very deep...
Sana, I'm...
It's okay.
Release it whenever you want to.
Release it inside me...
Akira...
Your semen is going inside me.
I can feel it.
It's amazing...
Ouch...
It still hurts.
Of course it would.
It's your first time, so it should be done gently.
K... Kimika-sensei!
Why...?
Because it's my turn when it's evening.
Geez, Akira-kun,
you did it with Sana just right after you did it with Yuu.
That was really lewd of you.
You've already shown lots of "action" today,
don't you dare think you can count me out of that now, okay?
No, wait...
Akira...
Oh no.
Please don't look.
Oh my...
That looks a bit painful, Sana-chan.
Oh my, already back up again, eh?
Akira-kun, your cock seems to be in good health today.
Kimika-sensei, don't.
Please stop.
Geez, Sana-chan, you're making such a mess.
No...
Please no.
Where are you touching me?
Where? You already know where, Sana-chan.
No...
Don't insert your finger in there.
Come now Akira-kun,
you also need to keep Sana-chan's pussy clean.
Akira, stop it...
Don't lick my pussy.
Akira-kun, your cock is great.
It's very stiff, and it feels good.
Her fingers are inside me.
This cock, reeks of inexperience and innocence...
Something is inside, in both holes...
I can't...
Sana-chan, your butt is squeezing my finger tightly.
I... can't take it anymore...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Sana-chan, I'm also going to...!
Akira-kun!
This is...
Rub it in me more!
Thrust your cock more!
You're really just straightforward with it, Akira-kun.
And it really feels great!
I'm going to go crazy with your cock, Akira-kun.
Pour it all deep inside me.
Fill up my entire womb!
My pussy is caressing your pleasure-crazy cock.
I'm about to cum.
And you too, Akira-kun...
Let's cum together.
It's coming out!
It's bursting from inside my womb!
I'm home!
Akira-kun... Akira-kun!
That's...
Wow, you're getting really good at it already, Akira-kun.
This is his "treatment".
Sana-chan!
Why, hello there Yuu.
Welcome back.
Yuu-nee!
W-Well, I...
Welcome home.
My, my, so everyone's doing his treatment right now.
And you also seem to be giving it your best, Akira-chan.
It's about time for dinner, so get changed quickly, okay?
Kimika-sensei.
Oh, Sana-chan. Hey, do you know where Akira-kun is?
Wait a sec Kimika-sensei.
Are you planning on doing it again with him?
What a rude thing to say. Today's an important day.
The actual result rests on today's examination.
Kimik'a-senpai and Sana-chan!
Infirmary
We just can't do this!
You say that, but you're actually doing it better than us two.
Am I wrong?
Akira, Kimika-sensei,
I'll be the one to lick the tip.
It doesn't matter who does it.
As long as it please Akira-kun.
If I leave him to you Kimika-sensei,
he'll turn into a good-for-nothing wimp!
There's no way he'll become like that.
I'm a doctor, you know.
Please don't quarrel you two.
But you also want to have him to yourself!
What are you saying?
Senpai, this is his treatment.
You're just trying to fool us.
Yuu-neesan...
You really are cute, Akira-kun.
Making all of us go crazy like this...
Akira-kun, you're about to cum, right?
You can do it whenever you want.
No way, I'll be the one to make him feel good.
Akira-chan, just cum okay?
Release it to me.
I feel like I also want to have a gulp of it now.
There's lots of it.
Akira-chan.
Akira's cum...
Is he getting better now?
How was Akira-chan's
phisical examination?
The result of Akira-kun's
checkup was good. No
abnormalites. I had him
visit a hospital in order
to elaborate on the
details. And... please
after two hours. Oh,
and no need to bring
Sana-chan with you.
Akira-kun, this is amazing.
You've become absolutely great at sex.
Akira's tongue is licking my pussy.
It feels good...
Hey, hey, hey!
Kimika-sensei!
S-Senpai!
Didn't you say that he was already well?
Akira-kun, do it more!
Akira, no...!
Well, he did become well.
"Well" in terms of rehabilitation standards?
Akira's licking it.
I just peed.
What rehabilitation are you talking about?
That's right, senpai!
If it's about rehabilitation, then I'll be the one to do it for him!
Yuu-neesan, that sounds kind of different...
You're complaining again, and yet you also love Akira-kun's cock.
That's not it.
Please don't say it like it's a crime.
Listen you two, I'll be the one to take care of everything for Akira-chan.
Yuu-neesan, you're trying to take advantage of the chaos here.
For you to say that...
You're also quite daring now, Yuu.
I'm the nurse of Akira's cock.
Even Nonomi is also now like that.
You're really such a bad boy, Akira-kun.
Geez, I never knew you were this perverted.
Akira-chan, I'll be the one to take care of you from now on, okay?
Then...
Yuu-neesan!
Akira's cock!
Akira-chan, cum inside me!