I really love your breast.
Stop calling me nee-san.
Why? Does it bother you?
Just a little.
Then, what should I call you?
It is fine if you call me Erika.
I feel shy for that.
Oh my, you say cute things.
Don't make fun of me!
Put... put this aside.
And then, there was such a big eggplant.
Toudou-kun.
Ichinose-sensei.
Are you returning with your sister?
The siblings come sure good along.
N-No, it is nothing like that...
Right, right
Here, take this.
I made a rough sketch.
Sorry for troubling you.
The library has it.
Come tomorrow.
It is a little difficult but give your best.
I am looking forward.
Let's take a bath to gether.
No, I dont feel like it.
Earlier you were gazing at Ichinose-sensei's tits, right?
What is that all of a sudden?
You don't have to hide it.
Since you are a boob freak you just forget about me when you see bigger boobs.
I don't want to hear that from you.
I love perverted stuff.
Weren't you the one who started it first?
I just did it for my respect to my mother.
Because of my obligation, I did a skinship to make my younger brother satisfied.
You are so stupid... I don't know why you are so happy about it.
You have to do it?
Just because sensei has bigger breasts than you...
You are an amazing idiot.
Jumping his sisters boobs, letting your heart stolen by a beautiful teachers big breasts...
Beside that you are still carrying mother's picture.
I am aware of it.
That is another story!
I should stop spoiling and idiot.
Keep your head up!
Erika-senpai, have a good morning.
You are in my way, Kuno!
Hey, you there!
What happened?
Erika-senpai was completely selfless!
It is like always.
That's not it!
It is completely different from her usual manner.
What happened?!
Hey, spit it out!
You are annoying!
It is just a quarel between siblings.
I see... So you did something bad.
Well then, I have to comfort Erika-senpai.
Erika-senpai!
Is he retarded?
Found it.
What is this?
Ichinose-sensei.
Stay still.
Don't make a noise.
W-What are you saying?
Forgive me, if I said something strange.
But, I couldn't hold it any longer.
Toudou-kun is the type that I like very much.
If you are near me, but my body feels hot.
Hot you say...
You shouldn't say that... If someone hears it...
What is with such a thing?
There is no need for such improper things.
That's right...
Why do you have it...
I am the one who is surprised.
Doing such a disgusting thing sense of duty aside but as siblings...
Todou-kun if you don't want that everyone learns about this sloven secret...
How about being my toy?
We will do various fun things.
Beside that, you like the thrill, right?
Yuuto.
Tonight I am studying at my friend's house.
Therefore you don't have to prepare dinner for me.
I see... That saves me trouble.
This is bad...
This is really bad...
Todou-kun, how do you begin your sex with your sister?
How you ask...
With a normal kiss.
With a natural loving feeling?
Yeah...
You are no fun...
It is a long awaited sex. You have to enjoy it.
Put your pride in it, Toudou-kun.
With your dexterity in your brush, you made me happy.
With my... brush?
This is a canvas.
More intense, like Gog.
It feel good, Toudou-kun?
Sensei...
I got wet.
Please use this.
Say, do you also want it?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Yes!
I want your cock.
Is it okay?
What are you trying to accomplish?
Oh, it is just you...
Even greeting you makes me feel sick.
Endure it a little, Morikawa.
We aren't here to teach him manners.
What do you want from me?
We don't have a business with you.
When Erike-senpai got our earlier, she somehow wasn't looking energetic.
Yesterday displeasured, today tired.
What happened really?
Today, unusually Erika-oneesama didn't appeared where you are.
There isn't something unusual about it, right?
Hey, don't hide it.
I can careless if it's about you, but if something happens to Erika-oneesama, I won't tolerate it.
I am back.
Yuuto.
I somehow smell a strange scent...
What is this about?
Scent?
It is like a sweet scent of a parfume.
T-That is...
You are hiding something, right?
H-Hiding?
Who was she? Who was she from the school, spit it out.
Y-You are getting it wrong, nee-san.
I was drawing in the art room all the time...
It is just that Ichinose-sensei's scent came to me.
Really?
Yes, really.
I can believe it, right?
It is all right.
Thank goodness.
I thought, that I was hated by you because of a meaningless quarrel.
I will make peace with you.
You got it, right?
If you make Erika-oneesama unhappy, I won't forgive you!
You shouldn't.
It is risky.
What happened to you?
My sister exposed you from your scent.
Oh my, that happened?
I personally don't mind it though...
Yuuto-kun won't have fun now.
I know a good place.
This swimsuit looks fun, right?
But you know, drinking a lot of milk is your prise.
Drink a lot, okay?
Great! You did it!
Beautiful...
You are beautiful, Erika-senpai.
Peeping films?
That's right, the moron Kuno was taking pictures of you with his camera.
I don't think thatit will be a harm though...
Please confirm these photos. I was worried.
Thank you, Morikawa-san.
Yuuto?!
Yuuto-kun, honestly you are tired of me, right?
Involved with such a lewd teacher and wondering what will happen in the future...
I am indeed an bewdy woman.
But you know, the feeling that I now have... you aren't playing with it, right?
But you were the one who said...
But it would be awkward.
If I fell in love with my student..
That's why I came to a resolution.
Someone must have told you before, the true essence of love will snatch in a moment.
As I thought!
You were unfaithful.
It is the picture that Kuno took.
You are the ones in the picture, right?
N-Nee-san!
Yuuto is mine!
Give me my precious family back!
I am trusting Yuuto.
He is just decived by this middle-aged woman, right?
That is...
You sure say harsh thing, although I kept your secret.
Secret?
I took some lovely pictures, you know?
This one. It is you two, right?
That is how it was...
I took these. They look good, right?
When I learned your secret, I was really perplexed.
You looked like happy lovers.
But, you were just being honest to your feelings.
Sensei...
I see, it is fine then.
In this case I will just take Yuuto back.
Let's do it here, Yuuto.
Let's show her, our shape.
While you are doing this, you don't expect me to sit quitely and watch it, right?
I got wet.
Can you endure it?
Expel me out in front of Yuuto-kun's eyes...
It is humiliation, you know?
This is cunning, please stop it.
If you are going to do, do it together?
Together with sensei?
Don't forget your lunchbox, Yuuto.
I know, nee-san.
Wait for me, Yuuto!
Today is my turn.
Yuuto, hurry up and come here.
It is no fun to go with that woman, right?
What are you sayin? A promise is a promise.
Today is my the day where I will have fun with Yuuto.
You are clinging all over him.
Wait!
Let him go!
Geez.
I somehow involved in a strange story.
This might be not so bad.