Will father be okay alone?
Since he is not a child, it's obvious that he will be okay.
Branch manager, huh?
Father has finally become a manager.
I appreciate fathers diligence but Sapporo is quite away from here.
If mother was alive, they would have gone together...
Yuuto!
It has been already a year. Stop being effeminate.
You don't have to say that...
Get a hold of your self!
Our life of welfare is thanks to those two.
Nee-san...
With fathers short-term loan, the house which was originally planned for three people, became the house for me and my sister Erika.
Erika-neesan and I aren't bond by blood.
I, who grew up by my mother, still remember how I started living with a new mother and sister.
My new mother was really gentle.
When my step mother died, I couldn't belived it.
Are you looking at mother's picture again?
N-Nee-san...
Hey, boy with oedipus complex, if you are that much love with mother's tits, how about going to heaven?
Your speaking style is cruel!
Father told me, come good along and take care of Yuuto.
But if you are like that, I have no other choise than being strict.
Mother...
Yuuto, you look at nothing but mother's tits...
W-What is that all of a sudden?
I know that you like adult women's tits.
All perverts look at them like idiots.
How do you know that...
I know everything about my younger brother...
Nee-san...
Nee-san, are you all right?
What is? I don't have to be worried by you.
You forgot to bring the lunch box?!
Sorry, I was careless...
Don't be careless!
What will you do now?!
I will buy something from the convenience store.
It can't be helped. You really are an idiot!
Did your smart ass brother something childish again?
There is no need for the "smart ass" Kuno-kun.
Huh? Erika-senpai since when did you became so gentle?
Kuno-kun, I am more kind and tolerant.
That is how it was.
I used an improper word.
As an apology, alove me to kiss your hand.
My love is too much for you heart.
As a tenth year student stop fooling around and study.
What a shame.
But I came one step close to senpai's heart again.
To her breast, right?
There is no mistake, that her big breast is covering a wonderful heart.
I am yearning for it.
What is wrong?
Ichinose-sensei.
Good morning, Toudou-kun.
Are you done with your subject?
That is...
Don't be late, okay?
Ichinose-sensei has a great body, right?
You are right there.
Toudou-kun!
Oh, it is just Morikawa.
Say, where is Erika-oneesama?
Obviously, my sister is in her class.
Won't she come over here?
Why does she have to come here?
Because I want to greet her.
Lately, I had no chance to talk to Erika-oneesama.
Say Morikawa, I don't want to be stingy about peoples preferences but...
Are you lesbian?
What are you talking?!
I am not a lesbian!
It is just that I like Erika-oneesama from the bottom of my heart.
Thats why I am saying, she is a woman.
That is wrong!
Erika-oneesama is the only entity named Erika-oneesama on this world.
You are a real lesbian.
I said, I am not!
Yuuto!
I borrowed it from the library. Here, bring it back.
Okay.
Bye, I am leaving it to you.
Erika-oneesama, me too.
Wait for me!
Say, how is the croquet?
It is tasty.
I see, that's good.
What? Do you want to be praised more?
It is okay.
Say, the exams are starting soon, how are your studies going?
It is better if you don't hear.
What is with that? You should study a little.
A little.
Not a little!
If your scores keep falling, how will you apologize to father?
You are annoying!
I was busy with the housework and had no time for studying.
Sorry, I just wanted to help you.
It is okay, you have your own plans.
"Study properly" is enough.
If there are things you don't undestand, ask me.
I will teach them to you...
Yuuto.
Yuuto?
Alright!
Yuuto.
N-Nee-san.
What is with that?
That what is with that is, that I thought, I would wash your back.
Stop doing such a thing so suddenly.
What is? You don't have to hold back.
In the absence of father, I thought, I would encourage my lonely younger brother.
You are the one who is lonely.
Don't put me in the same category with you.
I don't like when a boy with oedipus complex says some strange things.
Again! This topic...
But don't you like mother so much?
Isn't it the truth that you love mother than me?
But mother is no longer here.
In the place of mother, I will cherish you.
It is okay to touch them.
Suck it.
I will do it too.
Nee-san!
You came a lot.
It must have felt good.
I can't do the housework, instead of that I will help you in this way...
Is this okay with you?
You can't find such a sister elsewhere.
There definitely isn't another one.
It is like a dream.
It is a scandal!
What is a scandal?
It is obviously a scandal! The way that Erika-senpai smiled at you.
She had a smile on her face.
Is it bad that she laughs?
It is not like that!
You as her younger brother never saw her smiling face!
That is what I am saying!
It is strange.
There is clearly a change in Erika-senpai to be seen.
Is that so?
Don't hide it, younger brother!
Say! Erike-senpai...
... found a boyfriend!
Kuno, I know that you have nothing to worry about.
My sister is still single.
Is this the truth?
Yes, you don't have to worry.
There is no mistake, right?
Yeah!
He is sure sharp sighted...
Be careful while using the charcoal.
You have to hold it skillfully.
Don't hesistate to go into details.
It is better if you bigger the shadow.
It will be more precise.
Such a nice fragrance.
What is wrong?
No, nothing particularly.
This is bad.
Nee-san...
Does it feel good?
Yes!
Really?
But don't come yet.
Nee-san, why are you doing this?
It is may pleasure when you are happy.
No, that is...
But... I...
If you do that, our bond as siblings will disappear.
Got it?
Cuming!
Morikawa?
Kuno said something strange but what is really going on?
What should really going on?
In the lunch break, you were together with Erika-oneesama, right?
I saw you both coming out from the class room.
Nee-san lost  her pass-key and asked me to help by searching.
Really?
What will you do if I am lying?
How does not blood related siblings look at each other?
What is that supposed to mean?!
Nothing really.
Senpai, did you lost your pass-key today?
Yeah that is right.
I couldn't figure out where I lost it, so I asked Yuuto to help out.
I see.
Um, Erika-senpai...
What is?
I wonder if you have some kind relationship with your younger brother Yuuto.
Relationship?
A relation between a woman and man.
W-What are you saying?
Morikawa-san, I and Yuuto are siblings!
What are you saying?!
But I have a feeling, that you two have such a relationship.
There is a dirty smell...
Don't say rude things!
I won't allow you to say weird things to Yuuto!
I am sorry.
Please forget what I said.
You really said nothing, right?
Isn't it obvious? Who would say that?
But that girl definitely sensed it.
What should I do if someone finds it out?
You don't have to ask your self. No one will find it out.
How are you planning to hide it?!
I am such a fool... Just because I was lonely...
Because you said some strange things, nee-san was really shocked!
But you two no matter what look like lovers.
What the hell are you talking?!
We are siblings!
That is right, a woman and man not related by blood are siblings.
Hey! Get a hold of your self!
Then, there is really nothing between you two?
Didn't I said that it is obvious?!
In that case you don't mind when I have a relationship with your sister, right?
I will really go for Erika-senpai.
Don't get in my way!
Yuuto?
I am sorry, Erika-senpai.
Morikawa-san..
Yuuto-kun will not come.
He is not coming?
But the mail...
You sent...
I love you.
But that is...
Being lesbian has nothing to do with that!
Senpai, I love you!
Wait! Isn't this ridiculous?
It is not ridiculous! I love you!
Senpai...
Morikawa-san...
You shouldn't do this.
Erika-senpai...
Let me do it.
Hello?
Yuuto, help me!
Nee-san?
I beg you Morikawa-san, please stop it.
I wont.
I want, that you also love me.
But if you force me like this, even I...
Will it be okay if it is not forcibly?
No, I didn't mean it like that...
See, you don't love me after all.
B-But... that is...
Morikawa!
Yuuto!
Morikawa, what the hell are you doing?
Don't get in my way.
I just asked Erika-senpai for a favor.
What is that favor?
I love Erike-senpai... That's why...
But my sister doesn't feel that way.
But she doesn't hate me either.
I told you that she doesn't love you.
She expressed her feelings strightly... I am somehow envious.
You are right. However you shouldn't exaggerate it.
She really loved you.
No, she is probably still loving you.
If she was male, I might have put some thoughts in it...
If she says so, she should do a sex exchange.
That would be troublesome though.
Nee-san, why don't you look for a lover?
Because many people are in love with you...
That is...
The reason is, that I might feel sorry for my kind younger brother.
This is a little too much.
You shouldn't hide your precious feelings.
What is your precious feeling?
Previously, it was my mother.
But now I can't even remember her face.
If you love me rather than mother, I will forgive you.
Erika-neesan...
Do you remember the first time when I and mother come?
Since that time, I was always in love with you.
But you were seeing nothing but mother.
Sorry.
She told me before she died, to take care of you.
She said, you are from now his mother.
But now I will stop.
Not as a mother, neither as a sister...
I won't hide my precious feelings anymore.
Does it feel good, Yuuto?
Yuuto! Yuuto!
Nee-san!
YUUTO!!!
A new life started between me and my sister. We continued, as nothing had happened.
If not, our secret would be soon revealed.
But we didn't realized, that someone could easily see through this camouflage.