My name is Scarlett of Vastia.
I was captured during my travels and made
to fight to the death as a swordswoman.
As a part of a last-ditch attempt,
I concocted a plan with a smuggler named
Gustav to get me across the border.
To that end, I gave him my virginity
through lessons he gave me on how to be a proper
prostitute so that I could be transported as cargo.
However, before I knew it,
I had opened my heart to him.
We were able to get to the border
without being recognized,
but it seemed that my identify
was about to be revealed.
So, to allay any suspicions,
I acted out my role as a prostitute
with Gustav watching.
It was so embarrassing that I wanted to die,
but I desperately clung on to my sanity.
Even so, the man never intended
to let us go in the first place.
Warrior of the Colosseum
~Another Story~
Trapped War Maiden 2
What are you planning to do
to me by bringing me here?
Take a wild guess.
Are you saying you're not done
even after all of that?
Now that I look at you better,
as royalty, your skin is so much better
than any maiden I've ever seen.
All this time, you've known who I was?!
I could tell just by looking at you.
I could tell that you're Scarlett of Vastia,
the woman who was made
into a killer, but then escaped.
What about the guild
that got me here, Fractale?
What about Gustav?
I spared his life.
But I don't think he'll get too far
especially not with a warrant
for his arrest being issued.
He's alive! Gustav's alive!
Shouldn't you be worrying more
about yourself than others right now?
Wait, don't...
What is this? It's so cold! Stop it!
Don't fret, it'll get warmer soon enough.
What's going on? My body's on fire!
This is an aphrodisiac in the form
of a lotion, used for training slaves.
Your body is throbbing
with desire right now, isn't it?
A-Aphrodisiac?
Did you just cum from
having your nipple pinched?
We're only just getting started.
No!
Wh-What?
You're drinking like a faucet.
You just came again!
Look at how sensitive you've become.
Pinch her most sensitive part, her clitoris, next.
No, please don't. Please, stop!
Oh, dear, you peed yourself.
Did it really feel that good?
Please, I beg you.
Put your dick in me, I need it now!
Please put it in me!
No problem.
So, you're finally in the mood, are you?
Please, Master.
Please use this dirty slut's
pussy as you will, Master.
Please pound me so hard that my insides will be
nothing more than a sloppy mess once I cum!
I want your cock!
How could I say no?
Just how great does the meat-stick
you've been anxiously waiting for feel?
This is the first time I've felt like this!
After having sex with this aphrodisiac once,
you'll never be able to go back to regular sex.
I'm getting so turned on!
My body's getting hotter and hotter!
I can't control my lust!
You're going to feel even better
once I cum inside of you.
Amazing!
Your cock is pulsing inside me!
It's going to cum!
It's going to cum inside me!
Ouch! That hurts!
No way! That's my ass!
Don't put your cock in the...
It'll feel good soon.
Stop it!
My pussy and ass are dripping with cum!
Gustav... Where...
Where are you?
From then on, I was whipped by them
for hours on end day after day.
All the while, the effects of the aphrodisiac
ran rampant throughout my body.
Please... I beg you... let me rest.
If I cum any more, I'll...
No! No more! I'm cumming and cumming, but...
I'm going to lose my mind if I
keep cumming from these lashings!
So that slave girl is finally obedient now.
Of course. After being exposed to that
much of the aphrodisiac, anyone would.
Well, we lost the pleasure
of shaming her into submission, but...
this isn't too bad either.
Hey, swordswoman, your Master's here.
I've been waiting, Master.
Master, your cock is so hot and hard!
It's twitching so much!
Does it really taste that good?
Yes, it does! I'm getting soaked
just from sucking on it!
Oh, I see! Is that right?
I never thought that you'd
become this much of a slut!
It's all your fault, Master.
I'll never be able to go back to the way I was
because you used so much of that aphrodisiac!
I love your cock!
If you really like it that much,
then starting moving your hips more!
Yes, Master! Like this?
I will do any dirty or depraved thing you want,
so please use my pussy to make yourself feel good!
Excuse me!
Would you like to join us? My ass is free.
Please put your cock into my ass!
Interesting. I guess we haven't
tried double penetration.
Sure. I'll fuck you in the ass like you want!
They're rubbing! They're rubbing inside me!
I can feel them both rubbing
my stomach! It feels so good, Master!
Both my pussy and ass feel amazing!
This is turning me on so much!
I'll be sure to really blow my load in your ass!
Yes, please! Cum in me!
Please fill my asshole to
the brim with your hot cum!
You can tell that we're
going to cum soon, can't you?
Yes, I can!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming too!
I'm cumming!
There's so much! There's a wave
of hot stuff pouring inside of me!
You came a lot for someone whose partner just died.
Oh, yeah, that Fractale, right?
The one who was killed when he got too close
to the Vastian border, trying to rally soldiers to his cause.
What was his name again?
Uh, it was Gustav, right?
G-Gustav is dead?
Hey, it hurts if you get that tight!
Gustav!
Fuck! That hurts! Stop it!
What's going on? I can't take it out!
Somebody help us! This is fucking agonizing!
It was ripped off! My dick was ripped off!
You really think you'll get away with this?
You're nothing but a fucking slave!
I am not a slave!
I am Scarlett of Vastia.
I am the herald of the war goddess, Ellis.
I am the war maiden who protects Vastia!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fyurie
quality check: fyurie