My name is Scarlett of Vastia.
~Another Story~
Warrior of the Colosseum
The War Maiden Who Gave Up Everything 01
Where'd she go?!
This way!
Hey. You okay?
You're shaking.
I'm fine. You're not a soldier, are you?
No, I'm not from this country.
I'm a member of the guild Fractale.
Fractale?
Are you the war maiden
who ran away from a death match?
If you get yourself involved with me,
they'll start targeting you too.
Where are you going to go dressed like that?
Vastia.
Hey!
So they made you fight after poisoning you?
Indeed.
The people of this country want to see
Vastia royalty such as myself killed.
I see.
You said you're a part of Fractale before, right?
I beg you, could you smuggle me out of this country?
Well that's a tough request.
Smuggling anything out
of this country is a tall order.
If they found out that I was aiding
the escape of a war maiden,
then who knows what would happen to me...
Also, could you even compensate me
for the amount of danger I'd put myself in?
We Fractale members expect payment
for our delivery services.
I want to leave. I want to go
back to my home country.
For that sake, I'll do anything.
The only thing I have to give right now is this.
This will be my first time,
so I'm unsure of whether or not I can satisfy you, but...
All right, you have a deal.
Is this really your first time?
You seem to be really aroused.
I wouldn't lie about that.
This is my first time, but I'm aroused.
Something deep inside me is throbbing!
Why's this stuff starting to come out of me?
Okay then, let's have a taste of your virginity, Scarlett.
Already?! No, not yet...
Ouch! That really hurts! Don't!
Yep, it's really tight.
All of it's in now.
You're horrible! I told you not to!
It's gonna suck if you're this resistant.
I'm going to make you into a prostitute after all.
A prostitute?!
No! Stop it! Don't move!
It really hurts! It's going to rip!
In order to get enough money to get you
out of here, I need you to work as a prostitute.
If you're a prostitute,
I can write you off as my baggage.
If you're not convincing enough,
they'll see right through you,
so I need to make sure that you
become a prostitute, body and soul.
Can you do that?
Yes, I'll do it. This is all for the sake of getting home!
I'll do whatever it takes to get home!
All right then, from now on,
I'm going to teach your body the pleasures of sex.
Oh my god, it's so intense.
At this rate, I'm going to lose my mind!
My stomach is being turned inside out!
Just like that. You're doing great.
Try gripping my dick tighter!
Your dick is so hard and hot,
and it's getting even bigger!
It's because your pussy feels so good.
You're making me get serious.
No, don't say that!
Why am I getting so hot from my first time?!
Okay, here I go.
Wait, are you going to cum inside me?
If you do that I'm going to get pregnant!
If you're going to be a prostitute,
your body needs to reek of the smell of cum.
Now take everything I've got!
No! Stop! Don't cum inside me!
No! Don't!
Okay, that should do it.
Rest a bit and we'll leave at sunrise.
You're from the trading guild Fractale?
Fourteen bales of wheat, wine, and a prostitute?
You're taking all of this to Vastia?
Yes, so could I get permission to cross the border?
"Of course, no problem."
That's what I'd love to say,
but a killer is on the loose and she's actually
a member of the royal family of Vastia,
so we've increased the security
to ensure that she doesn't escape.
That's rather frightening.
I'll be sure to not cross paths with her.
She kinda resembles that prostitute you have.
She resembles the war maiden, Scarlett.
You're mistaken. This prostitute is
a high quality asset that I'm selling to nobles.
Even more of a reason I can't let you take her.
I can't let you take such a suspicious
person into the houses of nobles.
How about this, I take her for a ride
and see if she is or isn't the one we're after.
Wait, you can't...
If you cooperate,
I'm willing to let you go on your way.
Or is she not actually a prostitute?
I'll do it. I can't afford to give up here.
I'll continue to play out my role as a prostitute.
All right. If it'll lay your suspicions to rest.
These tits are so soft and springy.
You really are a high quality prostitute.
Thank you very much for your words, sir.
I will be waiting outside.
Oh, no. I need you to stay and watch.
What?
Having someone watch while you're being fucked
is rather embarrassing, wouldn't you agree?
I love teasing women like that more than anything.
See, her nipples are already getting rock hard.
You're getting aroused, aren't you?
No way. This is really embarrassing,
so why am I getting so hot?
So that's why I need you to stay here
and watch every last second of this. Okay?
Yes. As you wish.
So, how about you clean my cock first?
Yes. I will service your meat stick with my mouth.
It's clean enough, so do it with your boobs now.
Yes, as you wish, sir.
Oh, that's great. Just like that!
I'm going to cum soon.
I'm gonna cover your face with it!
Yes, please go ahead.
Sully me with your cum all you want.
That was fantastic!
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
So please give us our permission
to cross the border.
Who said I was done?
This is where the fun really starts!
Oh, this is great.
How is it? Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good, sir.
Please use my body as you will.
I need to keep up this act of being a prostitute!
This is all so I can get home!
Bear it! You need to endure, Scarlett!
Come on, move your hips more!
More! More!
Yes... Sir...
I will move my hips as much as you need me to,
and I will service you until you are satisfied!
I'm going to cum! He's going to make me cum!
I don't want to cum!
No! No way!
Amazing, it just sucked me in! This is superb!
Thank you very much, sir.
Sir, now that you've had your fun,
may we have what you promised?
To let such a fine product out
of this country would be a shame.
Wha...
Gustav!
I'll give you permission to leave the country.
However, the prostitute stays here.
No way! You're saying this isn't over yet?
No! No way!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fyurie