No way.
It stops here, Mint!
Evil spirit, begone!
From the far-off clarkness,
No matter how much time passes,
the evil Suima invade the Earth.
I will never forget your kindness.
What is this?
My once sealed off heart felt warmth for the first time.
I'll face them with my heart on fire!
So as I thought, things are quite different here.
Anzu has witnessed some very
strange teaching tecnniques!
Or rather...
Oops. I don't have time for this.
Anzu's House
So if I pass that audition,
I might become the kind of singer l've
wanted to be since I was a child.
Okay! For starters, I'll give myself some private
training to prepare for those lessons!
Don't you "meow" me!
Youre gonna help me, okay?
I'm not feeding you for free, ya know!
If this can feel good, then those
perverted lessons should be a cinch!
Come on. Lick me harder!
Now, do what that little brat and
the other chick were doing.
If I can raise my voice just a little higher...
That hurts!
Don't use your claws!
~ Midsummer Night's Melody ~
Okay.
Well then, let's put in another day's work!
That stupid and ditzy-looking octopus!
And that little brat whose only
talent is to be annoying...
I'm not gonna let them beat me!
Shit.
I guess I need nourishment first.
Sheesh, this is a rich person's house.
The least they could do is have some nicer garbage.
I must hurry and prepare Master's breakfast.
Now is not the time for this.
You must'n, Master!
I vowed to save myself for marriage!
I may have dressed like a boy,
but Master... I've always...
Yes. Yes!
I'd do anything for you, Master!
Your cover's been blown!
That was a pretty sweet flip!
Who are you?
I've seen you cleaning the mansion and all,
but I had no idea you were a girl!
If others found out, it would be chaos!
N-No! I'm not.. I mean, I'm not..
What are you doing?
Just making sure.
Please stop that.
They seem real to me.
Huh? Lemme see.
The stupid censors are making it hard to see.
I don't see a *****,
so at least youre not a hermaphrodite, I guess.
Don't...
Come on, come on!
You were in the middle of masturbating, right?
Hurry up and cum!
Then we can talk afterwards.
I'll take this opportunity to see how
well my training is progressing.
A cat's tongue is rough, so it feels
better than a man's, doesn't it?
Even if you say that,
I've never been licked by either, so I don't know.
Even though you dress like a
boy, you're bigger than me?
You bitch!
Why are you pretending to be a boy anyway?
B-Because....
Come on, come on, just spit it out!
If you don't, I won't let you finish.
Please don't stop!
I masturbate every day to keep myself pure for Master.
Master's father told me to!
That reminds me.
You were sighing "Master, Master!"
back there. Don't tell me you're...
That's... That's not..
Now, think of me as your Master and cum already!
Come on, come on!
No! I can't...
And with this, I'll be able to climb
the ladder and be a singer!
I'll get to say goodbye to the doghouse!
Master!
If you really insist, then I'll ask Haruto-sama.
But does this girl have talent?
Or some other appealing quality about her?
Um, well, she's, uh... Her, name, Anzu, is pretty cute.
This is so irritating!
Let me introduce myself!
I, Torii Anzu, was born into an
impoverished sweets shop.
But I always thought, "This isn't where I belong!"
So I ran away from home.
And all alone, the harsh wave of
society threatened to crush me!
But I was able to burst through
with hard work and talent!
And I discovered this mansion that produces singers!
And that's how...
I've come here to take lessons
to prepare for an audition!
Well you are unique.
I'll let Haruto-sama give you a little test.
Vulture Bombers, go!
Parallel Thunder, on!
Those are our magic words.
Fight with your life!
Stand and face it!
The seven stars dance in the sky.
To defeat the evil sorceror's conspiracy,
we are the phantom army, Mirage Seven!
Launch attack!
We'll defend the peace with the
mysterious power of our seven stars.
She's not particularly good,
but she does project a very unique atmosphere.
So does that mean, Haruto-san...
Very well.
I don't mind adding her to the lessons.
I'm impressed, umm... Leader?
Yes. Starting today, allow me to call you "Leader"!
What the hell is that?
Appearing out of nowhere and acting
all chummy with Onii-chan.
Leader, now that I'm here, you needn't
trouble yourself with painful obstacles,
like that brat and that octopus.
"Octopus"? She means me?
Come! We're beginning today's lesson.
Anzu, since this is your first time, you get to watch.
Leader, you're making me watch?
That's impossible!
In preparation for this day, l've
undertaken harsh personal training!
Personal training?
Correct!
Just you watch!
How's this, Leader?
Isn't this also a special lesson?
Sakura, play that particular tune
we were discussing before.
Huh? But I thought you forbade it.
Never mind, just play it.
Okay.
The carrot... is scraping my insides.
Now. Let's begin today's special lessons.
For Ichigo, we have cosplay sex.
I've been looking forward to this, Onii-chan!
Cosplay is Ichigo's specialty.
It's not just ordinary cosplay, though, Ichigo.
No, sir!
Let's use this for the first song.
From the far-off darkness,
the evil Suima invade the Earth.
I'll face them with...
...to protect you.
If we had no words to speak,
then we wouldn't be able to laugh together.
Yes...
Grasping hold of courage...
We are...
Ichigo-chan's really into it.
Anzu-san, what do you...
I guess she didn't hear me.
For Mint's special lesson, we have anal development.
Anal... That's my butt, right?
Butt, huh?
Just putting my finger in scares me.
What are ya saying?
You push stuft much thicker than
your finger out every morning.
What the hell?
You two! Be quiet.
Mint needs to break through her instincts to resist.
But I'm not sure if it will feel good in my butt.
Yes! That's what I'm talking about, Mint!
I told you this before, but I don't want you
to ever forget about your embarrassment.
If you forget about that like others have,
then your charm will disappear!
"Like others have." See? He's talking about you, brat.
But you're the one who's just had
a carrot jammed up your ass!
Relax your body.
Good.
First concentrate your feelings on your butt.
S-Sensei...
How does it feel, Mint?
It tickles.
I feel like my strength is leaving me. It feels weird!
Just relax.
That hurts, Sensei!
I know it hurts. Just bear with it.
I'll get you used to it little by little.
Okay.
Sakura, begin playing.
Tsubaki Oujo-sama!
Please wait just a few minutes in the library.
Master is currently teaching a
lesson and cannot be disturbed.
Would you please not recycle
lines from the last episode?
Well, well, Tsubaki-san.
Lovely as always.
Tsubaki? You're intruding,
and our perfect lesson has been ruined.
Lesson? This disgusting act is a lesson?
I'm only using sex in their lessons
because it produces good results.
To prove myself, l'd even give a boy the same lessons,
even though I'm not into that.
The same excuse as before.
Now that you mention it, there's
a very successful rap artist,
who used to be a pupil of yours.
Don't tell me...
Piercing into my body,
it's your hard, thin, and gorgeous thing.
Your thing's so great it makes me cry!
Now I get it.
I thought Leader was unusually interested in buttholes.
Please don't jump to such disgusting conclusions!
Fine then. It seems you must go that far.
But if your beloved pupils don't pass their audition...
You must marry me!
Very well, Tsubaki.
D-Don't do it, Sensei!
Don't make that sort of promise!
She's right, Onii-chan!
Why are you listening to a pushy bitch like her?
Don't worry.
I have faith in you, girls.
Sensei...
Onii-chan!
Well! If you have that much faith in me, Leader,
then I suppose l'd better get into top gear now!
The brat and the octopus are only holding you down.
Holding him down? That's you, bitch!
Ichigo-chan, don't squabble.
We must focus on our lessons.
Fine! Bring it on!
I like your spirit, everyone.
It's all thanks to you, Tsubaki.
That was a very forceful proposal, Tsubaki-san.
P-Proposal?
That's just the way I work.
Hello? Yeah, it s me.
Be sure to bring plenty of talented
girls to the next audition.
Past the deadline? Just extend it!
Understand?
If only she were a little less fake,
she might even be cute.
Haruto-san!
Sakura-Oneechan?
I mean, Sakura-san, when you heard
that we were having special lessons,
didn't it bug you?
It's part of my job.
Really? Then what is this?
You love him too, don't you!?
Ichigo is very perceptive about those sorts of things.
Composing good music so that I can be
near Haruto-san... That satisfies me.
But not Ichigo! Ichigo loves Onii-chan so much.
That's why I want to keep him all to myself!
Ichigo-chan, that's very good for you.
I'll compose a song that will convey
those strong feelings of yours.
Really?
Thanks, Sakura-Oneechan!
Mint! That melody...
It's the song that woke me from my long sleep.
In a past life, you composed it for me.
In a past life, I did that..
In your past life, you were drawn to me.
Deep into the forest,
you took your first steps.
Our meeting was destined.
Yes. The longer we touched, the
brighter both of us shined.
You knew that I was a demon,
and that making love to me would end
your life, but you didn't hold back.
We were completely unaware that
we would meet a sad ending.
The demons would not forgive our union.
Despite that, we...
No, because of that our bond was
stronger, and deeper than before.
I've been feeling... this whole time...
I'm cumming!
This sad ending of which you speak...
Did the demons kill my former self?
No, that's not what happened.
What was it, then?
Everything felt so good that I forgot who I was.
I forgot that I was a life-eating succubus.
Umm, you see, because I did that with you,
your lifespan was reduced significantly.
So you're saying the former me
had sex with you too often.
It was your fault, Haruto-san!
Ah, I mean, the Haruto-san in the past life.
I tried to stop you, but you kept coming back for more.
I see.
So the reason I'm so sexually powerful now is
because of what happened in my past life.
Just when I thought this was some twisted sort of
demon-and-human Romeo-and-Juliet tragedy,
it's just a nonsensical porno plot!
Okay. Time for your final lessons.
Girls, good luck!
Sensei, I must live up to Haruto-san's legacy.
I must make Ichigo's love blossom!
Ouch! Ouch!
I must be free of my class!
I must rise to become a star!
We will all pass the audition together!
Judges
Haruto, I expect you to keep your end of the bargain.
I've already reserved the wedding hall and the flowers,
and I've put down a hefty deposit.
Sorry to force you to spend so frivolously, Tsubaki.
You're quite confident, Haruto.
I too eagerly await the results of this audition.
Well, I'll see you later.
Haruto-san, is everything okay?
I hope she didn't bribe the judges
or something illegal like that.
There's no need to worry about that.
Even Tsubaki is a part of this entertainment world.
She's not so stupid that she would
destroy promising new talent.
Haruto-san! You're being too naive!
When a woman has marriage on the brain,
She'll do anything to make it happen.
Is... Is that true?
It's starting, Haruto-sama.
And now, we'll begin a festive audition
to discover tomorrow's stars!
Next up is Anzu-san.
Vulture Bombers, go! Go!
Parallel Thunder, on! On!
Those are our magic words.
Fight with your life! Say!
Face it! Yes!
The eating utensils dance in the sky!
I'll break up the conspiracy of the octo-brat combo!
The mysterious ranger Anzu-sama!
Launch attack! Oh!
My meals are made by a mysterious cat.
I will protect the secret!
Silly Anzu. She changed the lyrics
without my permission.
Well, it was unique.
I'm doomed!
My days of being blackmailed will continue forever!
N-Now, now, Shion-kun, calm down.
I'm Mitsuishi Mint
I'm singing, "Love With You."
ikutsumo no yoru o sugoshite mo
Even if I always make it through the countless nights,
anata no hohoemi wasurenai
I still can't forget your smile.
kudakareta watashi no kokoro ni hajimete kanjita utsukushisa
For the first time, I felt beauty enter my broken heart.
nureta kuchibiru kasanete
Our wet lips touched,
ashita o mitsumeteta
as we gaze into tomorrow.
kinjirarete mo hiki modosarete mo
Even if it's forbidden, even if I must return,
Don't stop love
Don't stop love.
Dream in the dark ima wa hitori
Dream in the dark. Now you are alone,
nagai yume no naka
trapped in a long dream.
Dream in the dark itsu no hi ni ka
Dream in the dark. Still, some day,
deai o shinjite
I believe we will meet.
ah kono tokimeko o
Ah, this passion.
Love with love with love with you
Love with, love with, love with you.
O-Oh, something's wrong!
I can't! I must hold back.
If I reveal my demon identity to the
audience, Sensei will get in trouble.
Mint-san...
It's just like that other time.
If she can't restrain her rising feelings,
things will get way out of hand!
Mint!
Argh, here goes nothing!
ima wa hitori
Now you are alone.
kurai yume no naka
trapped in a long dieam.
Dream in the dark itsu no hi ni ka
Dream in the dark. Still, some day,
Ichigo, don't tell me you're...
mezame e shinjite
I believe you will awaken.
Dream in the dark ima wa hitori
Dream in the dark. Now you are alone,
nagai yume no naka
trapped in a long dream.
Dream in the dark
Dream in the dark.
itsu no hi ni ka
Still, some day,
deai o shinjite
I believe we will meet.
ah kono tokimeki o
Ah, this passion.
Love with love with love with you
Love with, love with, love with you.
If we sing together,
you'll be able to keep your demon self from surfacing.
Love with love with love with you
Love with, love with, love with you.
Thank you for doing this, Ichigo-chan.
They're a nice pair.
Yes, even more than I envisioned.
Hearing those girls makes me want to believe
in your special lessons completely.
But, sorry to say, today's audition is for a solo singer.
This is a real pickle.
Those two broke the rules.
We can't let them win.
Who else would it be then?
In that case,
that one unique and strange girl who stood out.
That's right.
So could you send out the invitations straight away?
Oh, and one more thing...
Now announcing the audition winner!
Hang on a sec.
The winner is... Torii Anzu-san!
Anzu-san! Look this way!
Tsubaki-san!
Looks like I've finally risen into the world of stars!
What the hell are you babbling about?
You're going to be very busy on
promotion campaigns for the company.
So busy that I'll make you regret
you won this stupid competition!
H-Hey, wait a minute!
You... You cant mean it!
That wasn't in the script!
I'm sorry, Ichigo-chan.
Because of me, you didn't...
I didn't do it entirely for you, you know.
I mean, if it got out that you're a demon,
people would think I'm a demon too!
That's why I did it.
Okay. I'll take your word for it.
Thank you, Ichigo-chan.
You were both very good.
Sensei!
Onii-chan!
But you are still far from my image of perfection.
If you'd achieved that,
the judges would unquestionably have
named both of you as the winners.
Thanks!
Sensei, I will continue to work hard at my lessons!
What the hell, Mint? Suddenly playing the good girl?
At the next audition, Ichigo is kicking ass!
Right, Onii-dian?
I can't help but be jealous,
watching them like that.
I agree.
But in my case, I wish Haruto-sama
had a little more lust for business.
But if Satou-san were that kind of person,
you wouldn't be working for him right now.
kitto yume ni tsunagaru
Surely, this season of beginnings
And what about you, Shion-kun?
hajimari no season
will make my dreams real.
I was just sort of thrown into being his butlerr, and I...
makka ni takanaru mune wa
My pounding chest, burning with passion,
sunawachi ni asu o matteru
is waiting for tomorrow to come.
Anzu told me that you're a girl.
Shion-kun... I mean, Shion-chan.
Huh? You...
Don't worry. I'll take care of you now.
mabushiku hikaru ame agari no gogo
The post-rain afternoon shimmers brightly.
tachidomari sora miageta
I stood still and gazed at the sky.
haru no hi sagaru
Those days of spring have passed.
ookiku shinkokyuu
I take a deep breath,
atarashii kaori
and smell a new fragrance.
minareta hazu no keshiki mo
And the scenery I once thought dull and familiar,
ureshikute
is now so pleasing.
zutto owaranu omoi
My never-ending feelings
itsumade mo mune ni hirogaru
will grow in my heart forever.
kitto yume ni tsunagaru
Surely, this season of beginnings
hajimari no season
will make my dream real.
zutto owaranu omoi
My never-ending feelings
itsumade mo mune ni hirogaru
will grow in my heart forever.