So beautiful.
I borrowed this mansion from
my uncle to give music lessons,
but I had no idea that there was
a room like this in the attic.
Still, that crazy uncle of mine sure collected
lots of useless junk from all over the world.
Umm... What what?
"Watchman of the New Moon"?
"Barat mint leaves are smashed
and mixed into water..."
What's that?
A melody is materializing in my head.
Wh-What's this?
What's the meaning of this?
Th-This fragrance is... mint?
~ Midsummer Night's Dream ~
I've taken on a new pupil to
prepare her for an audition.
Take care of things for me again, Sakura.
I will, Haruto-san.
Haruto-san, will you be giving Ichigo-chan and
your new student "special" lessons, too?
Yes.
They have the talent for it.
Do you have a problem with that?
I completely understand how these
lessons benefit the students,
but I'm concerned that if your
methods leaked out to the public...
it might cause a scandal.
I'm worried about you.
Even if that happened, we can just
say they made it up to frame me.
I compose good music and sell it to their artists.
That's all they care about.
And that's your attitude as you continue
to chase after "perfection", isn't it?
"Perfection", huh?
When you say it like that I get
the feeling it's a bit different.
It's just me being selfish.
My actions are restricting your career
as an independent composer.
That's not true at all!
I wished for this myself!
Haruto-san!
I'm... I'm gonna...
Cum as many times as you want.
This is the least I can do for you.
That's plenty for me.
I'm almost there.
Haruto-san, I...
Haruto-san, what's that song?
Sakura, you're awake?
Actually, I don't know either.
I think I've heard it somewhere before, though.
That's unusual.
You usually never forget a phrase once you've heard it.
That's true.
You've got a point.
I guess this room isn't really set up for dining alone.
But it allows you to consume the vast
quantities of food you need all at once.
In a way, it works out nicely.
I see. That's another way of looking at it.
Ever since I was a child, your body has amazed me.
Where in your thin body does all that food go?
Sorry, but that's a secret.
Haruto-sama...
...as your personal assistant I must speak
to you about a job-related maner.
I'm not certain you should take on that new student.
It's bothering me in some way.
And why is that?
Leave aside the fact that she has amnesia
and doesn't know her family origins.
Saying she's from the Kaon family in
order to promote her is a bit much.
That's not germane.
I recognize that she has musical talent.
That's all that matters to me.
Very well.
Covering your back is also part of my job.
Master, the lesson room has been prepared.
Thanks.
Shion-kun, you're first rate.
You're so skilled that it was a waste
for you to be my uncles butler.
If only you'd graduate from being
a cherry boy, you'd be perfect.
0h, Master, why must you always tease me like that?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Mint-san?
Wh-What do you think, Sensei?
This is the first time I've worn clothes like this.
You were naked the first time I saw you.
Sensei?
But after seeing you like this again,
I'm sure you'd look better with
a little more mass in your butt.
Ah, that's Master for you.
Mint-san, please understand this.
Haruto-sama doesn't have ulterior motives or anything.
I hope that you don't hold his behavior against him.
No, I don't mind at all.
So, Master, since Mint's full name is Mitsuishi Mint,
I've decided to say that she's my cousin.
I guess that works.
But just don't use your position to
take advantage of her, Shion-kun.
T-Take advantage?
Why must you always jump to conclusions, Master?
Again, let me explain.
Haruto-sama really means no harm.
Yup, Ichigo is berry cute today!
Today I get to do my first performance with Onii-chan.
This is a perfect opportunity to
solidify my bond with him!
That song was perfect Ichigo!
It was like the gentle whisper of an angel!
It paralyzed me!
It granted me the peace of a green forest!
Ah, I cant even find the words to express
how beautiful your song was, Ichigo!
Oh, dear.
But Ichigo still needs many more lessons from you.
Really?
Then let's have a private lesson right here.
Yes, that's right.
Teach me a good lesson!
Yeah, right!
In order to cross the threshold into adulthood,
Ichigo had better work hard at her lessons!
Onii-chan!
Thank you for helping me, Sakura-san.
This should be enriching for both of us, Mint-chan.
Onii-chan? Who's this?
Ah, Ichigo.
This is my new pupil, Mitsuishi Mint.
I'm Mitsuishi Mint.
Nice to meet you.
"N-New pupil"?
Meaning, a new character in the series?
Meaning a new love interest?
Meaning I have to share my screen time?
Meaning, my rank goes down...
...until I'm just a boring supporting character?
No!
"Onii-chan"?
Does that mean she's your little sister?
Hell, no!
Umm, I mean, I just call him that to be cute.
In that case, maybe I should also
refer to Sensei that way.
Only one of the characters is allowed to do that!
Well, nice to meet you.
I'm Oizumi Ichigo!
Nice to meet'cha!
Ichigo-chan...
That's a delicious-sounding name.
I'm a newcomer here, so any help you could
give me would be much appreciated.
Let's do our best, Mint-san.
Ah, so the custom in this country is to shake hands.
Nice to work with you.
That's girls for you.
They become friends so quickly.
Haruto-san, I don't think that's quite what happened.
I guess she's so-so.
Though I guess if Onii-chan
picked her, it's to be expected.
She's not bad at this either.
But she's still no match for the great Ichigo!
Your running pace is uneven!
Ah, stupid Mint! I'm sick of her!
After a few days of lessons,
what's your impression of Mint?
Good question.
Not only does she have high musical aptitude,
but her dedication to training is admirable.
Your perception is quite accurate.
Hearing that from you makes me
feel even more secure, Sakura.
Bah, to think I call her Sakura-Oneechan,
all respectful-like.
That stupid four-eyed bitch.
Mint!
I went through a lot of trouble to make myself
the bratty-yet-lovable little sister character!
You think I'm gonna share that
position nicely with you?
This isn't that kind of anime!
Why you...
Ouch! That's your fault too, Mint!
Because of you, Onii-chan is...
That's right.
That means Onii-chan will...
And the winner is... entry number 13.
Oizumi Ichigo-san!
Thank you, everyone!
The warm applause from all of my
beloved fans is my pride and joy!
Ichigo!
I can't keep this to myself any longer!
Won't you form a unit with me?
Onii-chan, could you mean...
Ichigo...
Ichigo-chan?
Your lesson starts soon.
Would you like to come to the practice room with me?
Don't interrupt my fantasy when
it's getting to the good part!
And I definitely won't let you have my Onii-chan!
Ichigo-chan...
I was taking lessons with Onii-chan
long before you came along.
So the early bird catches the worm!
Or first come, first served.
Anyway, that's what it means!
I see. So Ichigo-chan loves him too.
But I've been waiting for him
for so long, from so far away.
I can't reveal that to him yet though.
But someday...
Haruto-sama, is the "special lesson" starting today?
Yes, it is.
If anyone other than you attempted this sort
of lesson, it would be sexual harassment.
Excuse me.
Well I suppose they wouldn't
even attempt your methods.
Is that so?
I've never thought of a way to teach a
traditional lesson, so it never occurred to me.
That statement is very you.
Rather, you need that sort of statement.
I really put you under a lot of
stress, don't I, Satou-chan?
And I appreciate your continuing support.
In the spring, when I was ten,
you moved next door to me.
Since then, I've been preparing for this.
Behind Haruto, the eccentric genius musician
who raises so many successful artists,
is a calm, serious, bookish man.
That's how everyone has to see it.
But even I can't predict the future.
Today, we're starting a special lesson
to prepare you for your audition.
A special lesson?
Anything you want Onii-chan!
Wh-Wh-What?
Well, then.
Who wants to go first?
Me! Me! Me!
Ichigo wants to go first!
Well then, Ichigo, let's start with you.
From the far-off darkness, the-
Onii-chan! What are you doing?
Don't mind me. Just continue, Ichigo.
B-But..
I guess I didn't explain myself enough.
Listen well both of you.
My special lesson is to use sexual pleasure to bring
the best and strongest sound out of your voice.
"S-Sexual"? Onii-chan, are you serious?
In order to burst through your limits
and bring out your true voice,
you need the pleasure derived from sex.
Come, Ichigo.
I guess that sort of makes sense,
but it's easier said than...
What's wrong, Ichigo?
If you don't want to do it then Mint can go first.
No way!
Sakura Oneechan!
From the first verse again, please!
From the far-off darkness,
Sensei, I can't watch anymore.
Why not, Mint?
Watching me train her is part of the lesson.
But, I... I...
Mint-san, what about the special lesson?
Shion-san...
...did you know about the special lesson?
Satou-san did tell me what happens during it.
But I've never witnessed such a session.
I was shocked.
Doing that during a singing lesson?
Is Sensei that kind of person?
I'll admit that Master is a bit selfish as
well as a womanizer and narcissistic,
and he's a bit rude and always
teases me for being a virgin...
However when it comes to singing,
no one is more serious than he is.
Please understand that at least.
So you trust him, don't you?
Well I'm only an employee of his, so...
I still don't think I'm ready for
that kind of lesson, but I'll try!
Shion-san, thanks for your help!
Truthfully I'm envious of Mint-san and Ichigo-san.
If only he knew I was really a girl!
I apologize, Sensei.
We're about to enter the main
segment of the special lesson.
Watch closely, Mint.
I'm kinda scared, Onii-chan.
This time, you don't need to sing.
Just make sounds when you feel like it.
Just make sure those sounds are
powerful and authentically you.
My authentic voice?
My authentic voice...
Onii-chan...
Wow! This feels much more intense than before!
It's because of the blindfold.
It intensifies all your other senses.
And the only natural response to the
sensations of your body is to raise your voice.
Onii-chan!
Break through the barrier!
Time to burst forth with your real self, Ichigo!
Onii-chan!
It's no use.
It's true.
Sensei's eyes are very serious.
But I'm still too embarrassed.
I'm worried that if I start feeling
too intense that I might...
Haruto.
This looks like a very luscious house
to use for teaching voice lessons.
Lady Tsubaki!
Please wait just a few minutes in the library.
Master is currently teaching a
lesson and cannot be disturbed.
I'm a busy womam I have no time to wait around.
Well, well, Tsubaki-san.
Lovely, as always.
Satou-chan, isn't it?
You're going to let me see Haruto.
During his special lessons,
outsiders are not permitted to enter.
Even you, Tsubaki-san, his college classmate
and daughter of our current sponsor,
are no exception.
You think you can get away with
treating me like everyone else?
Ichigo has never done this before!
That'not your voice.
It's not supposed to sound like that!
From deeper inside!
Make the whole room vibrate!
Ring it out!
If you must then I can't stop you.
But Tsubaki-san, please try to remember.
How is Haruto-sama when he's angry?
We have a very interesting problem
between the three of us, don't we?
Though at first it wasn't so extreme.
F-Fine, I get it.
I'll wait in the library.
The proud Lady Tsubaki is walking
away like that? I don't believe it!
Satou-san, is it really that horrible an
occurrence when Master gets angry?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming
Onii-chan!
Ichigo is cumming!
Grasping hold of courage...
I suppose I should congratulate you, Haruto.
She sounds much better than before.
She still has a long way to go, though,
and she still doesn't use the mic properly.
Oh my, you're so strict.
So this is the result of the special lesson.
Thank you very much!
Onii-chan, how was Ichigo's singing?
Very nice, Ichigo.
Don't forget how your voice sounded today.
Aw, Onii-chan said I was good!
Sensei really does look pleased.
I wish he would look at me that way.
No. He doesn't even need to look at me that way.
I just want him to look at me forever.
And I know it must be...
Never underestimate the cunning of a girl in love.
Mint is out late tonight.
Don't tell me...
It's unlocked.
Mint, right?
I didn't even say anything.
How did he know?
You and Ichigo are the only
things on my mind right now.
And Ichigo wouldn't have knocked.
She would've just jumped into the room.
It's a simple process of elimination.
Sensei...
Sensei, can we have a special lesson right here?
Right here?
Mint, you bitch!
But if I barged into the room right now,
Onii-chan would probably say...
Stay right there and watch!
Yup, I thought so.
Are you ready, Mint?
Your eyes look no different from the way
they were during Ichigo's lesson today.
You need to release yourself to
pleasure and let out your true voice.
But, I'm embarrassed.
You don't need to let go of your embarrassment.
It's part of your charm.
But be sure to release yourself of your own free will.
Use the naughty sounds of our
bodies as your accompanist.
No! Not so suddenly!
Stupid Onii-chan.
Telling Mint that being
embarrassed is part of her charm.
I don't suppose he'd say that
my charm is that I'm horny.
But if I see something like this, I can't...
Sensei!
Try moving on your own, Mint.
That is how you can release yourself
from everything that binds you.
That is how you can find your true voice!
But I'm not...
There's nothing to fear.
No matter how twisted you look,
no matter how lewd you look,
I will not abandon you.
Sensei, I... I...
How about it, Mint?
Try raising your voice more!
This feels great!
Sensei... I...
What was that?
Sensei!
Th-This is super hardcore imagery here!
I'm sorry, I forgot to tell you.
When I've merged bodies with men before,
I've also sucked the life force from them.
What should I do?
What now?
H-How?
When I suck a man's life force away,
he usually takes at least a week to recover.
Mint, your voice when you were
cumming just then was really nice.
Umm, Sensei? It's about my identity.
While you still have that sensation in
your body, try singing something.
F-For real, Onii-chan?
She's a freaking demon, you know? A demon!
It ends here, Mint!
Evil spirit, begone!
Get away from Onii-chan at once!
Ichigo, why are you dressed like that?
Umm, well I just thought I'd
match the mood of this scene.
Hey! Never mind me. It's Mint who looks weird!
Onii-chan, aren't you freaked out?
It's not my place to say.
Never mind that. Listen to Mint sing!
You'll be able to hear just how much she's changed.
What the hell?
If it's singing you want, Ichigo can...
That's it! I'll return you to sanity with my singing!
From the far-off darkness,
No matter how much time passes,
the evil Suima invade the Earth.
I will never forget your kindness.
What is this?
My once sealed off heart felt warmth for the first time.
I'll face them with my heart on fire!
When we-
To protect your, my dear.
Since when did you return to normal?
I heard once before that music has
the power to transform demons.
It must be that.
I don't really understand,
but what I do understand is that
both of you have improved.
I look forward to your auditions.
What's wrong, you two?
I guess no matter what's going on...
you always place music at the top of your priorities.
I hate to admit it, but I guess
you're right. We do need work.
Mint! Well settle this score at our audition.
Ichigo-chan, are you okay with this?
Even though I'm not human...
I don't care about that anymore!
I'll beat you fair and square,
and then I'll get Onii-chan to respect
me as an artist and as a woman!
You're both nice and excited.
Mint and Ichigo.
I saw it.
So as I thought things are quite different here.
tada bouzen to nani ga shitai ka tte
I asked with my mouth agape, "What do I want to do?"
tachi domatte sora o miageta
Standing still, I gazed up at the sky.
masshiro na kumo funwari to oyoide ita
Pure white clouds swam lightly by.
mezasu mono nani mo nai sora no naka
What I aim for is in the empty sky.
miezu ni tsukarete doko made yuku no oshiete
Unable to see it, I become exhausted,
Wondering how far I'll go. Please tell me!
let's take power sakende iru
Let's take power! I'm screaming out.
tsuyosa o ima tsutaeyou
It's time to show others I'm strong.
let's take power todoite iru
Let's take power! I'm reaching it.
namida mo yorokobi ni kawaru yo
My tears will change to joy.