UCHU PLANNING
Producer Shin Maruyama
Character Designs &
Art Direction Yorihisa Uchida
Music Nobuhiko Kashihara
Original Story &
Direction Yorihisa Uchida
Should we be looting an
abandoned ship like this, Guy?
A buck's a buck. Don't get your panties in a wad.
You're still pissed at me, aren't you?
If you hadn't been fucking around
on that last deal,
we'd have been rich by now.
Doesn't this strike you as a little odd?
There's no damage.
Maybe we'll find the answers on the bridge.
Is this a space ship or a haunted house?
Guy, let's get out of here.
This whole thing rubs me the wrong way!
The only thing that doesn't is your vibrator.
Guy!
Who are you trying to kill?!
Fuck off!
Please, help me...
Here...
Take this...
...Doctor Vail...
...prison planet, Geo...
That was really gross!
Prison Planet Geo, huh?
Now, that's what I call interesting.
GUY
PLANET GEO
Would you like more, my love?
Oh yes...
Let me have it now, ah...
It's true, you've served me well.
Zena, attend to her!
Just relax...
Again...
Do you like it?
Yes...
Madame Heel, you have my most
eloquent thanks for your continued patronage,
and you are more beautiful
than I even expected,
but don't you think you're pushing the
boundaries of professional ethics.
I mean, doing this kind of business and serving
as the warden of the prison planet, is well...
Is none of your damn business!
But seeing the quality of this shipment,
I may forgive you.
These are much too good for prison scum.
Listen up, slaves!
No matter who or what you were before,
you are now just property.
My personal property.
Let me impress upon you how important it is
for you to ensure my purchase
was a wise investment.
Should you fail, know that l
am Helga Hildius Heel,
Warden of Prison Planet Geo.
My word is law.
Get your ass inside!
Hey, wait a second!
I said, wait, god dammit!
Open this fucking door!
Well, well, look what the guards dragged in.
Hi...
You're awful cute for a boy.
I think we're gonna be good friends.
Be nice and I won't hurt you too badly.
No thanks, I'm not into bestiality.
Don't get cocky with me, boy.
You'll be begging for it by the
time I'm through with you.
Stop it, you undersexed warthog!
Keep your filthy paws off me!
Just relax and enjoy it.
Aw, dammit! Can't you understand
when someone means no?
You'll be feeling fine in just a second.
Oh, ho! What's this? Somebody's got a secret.
I like surprises.
Damn you!
Guy!
Party's over, fat boy.
Your affections aren't returned.
Guy!
What's up, Doc?
Oh, nothing!
You...
You gotta have more guts than
brains to fuck with me.
Bad move, fat boy.
Wha? What?!
Sonuva... Your ass in mine!
Any other predictions, fat boy?
Serves him right.
So, what have you learned?
The scale of this operation is mind-boggling.
They're using these prisoners as slave labor.
Illegally, of course.
To manufacture equally illegal youth drugs.
That's the way I've got it figured.
The monster we found was Allen Hase.
He was working here all right, with
some guy named Doctor Vail.
And that card?
Anything on it?
It could be a new rejuvenation drug.
I won't know until I break the fuckin'
code on the piece of shit.
Why don't we just locate this mysterious
Doctor Vail guy then?
At the very least, I think he ought
to be able to crack the code.
Warden Heel doesn't deserve
a monopoly on this.
We may see a profit out of this yet.
Zena! Zena, please!
Don't send me to the pit!
Anything! Anything but that!
Don't touch my boots, you pig.
Being assigned to the pit
frightens you, does it?
Work hard and maybe the warden
will send you back.
No, please!
You know that no prisoner who goes
down there ever comes back!
Asshole!
You've all received life sentences,
life sentences without parole.
Madame Heel has now generously
offered you this way out.
If you work hard, she'll reward you for it.
It's not as though you have a choice, you know.
All right!
Look at the fuckin' girls!
Exactly right!
Pick out the one you like.
The best workers are always well rewarded.
Oh, think you'll finally get laid?
All right, get on the elevator.
Good luck, you'll need it.
Aw, this sucks!
Guy, why don't we just do what we came to do?
Don't start.
Why not?! I'm beat!
I'm hot! I can't breathe!
Did I say you could take a break?
Get back to your post.
Gee! Haven't you ever heard of taking
a fucking breather?!
You sound like someone who
enjoys getting whipped.
Cut it out!
Guy!
Raina, will you calm yourself down?
Hey, how can I whip him if you won't move?
Shit! I'll have to beat you later.
Stay there.
Excuse me!
Oh... Oh... Help me...
Is that...
I think so.
He said no one comes out of here alive!
All right, get back to your assignments,
and uh...
Someone toss that corpse in the incinerator.
Maybe Planet Geo is another name for Hell.
- Hi there!
- Oh, no!
You're staying here!
Two's a crowd when you're one.
I'm coming, so there.
Oh, no, you're not!
And if I scream?
Fuck it! I don't care.
Lucky!
Again! Do it again!
Use that impertinent litte tongue of yours.
Just think of all the girls you'll spare from a
similar fate if you can satisfy me completely.
Who's out there?!
Please accept our apologies for interrupting a
tender moment such as this, Warden Heel.
Who the fuck are you?!
Guy!
I wasn't expecting to find you under quite
these circumstances, Cara.
Cara?
That was stupid.
Having caught you be the tail, so to speak,
I have a small favor to ask.
My life for a pardon and release, right?
Well, that'd be nice,
but what I'd really like is to meet
your friend Doctor Vail.
What?!
What do you know about Vail?
Let's just say we run into an old friend of his.
You're spies! What have you found out?
Shut up! Remember who's got the
knife against her throat.
Now, let's not be hasty. I can get him for you.
Now, that's being a good bitch.
No tricks, all right?
We're screwed!
Guy!
I knew you'd find me.
Find them! Don't let them escape!
A Block, checks out.
B Block, checks out. C Block, checks out.
Damn it, where the hell are they?
Explosion in B Block!
What?!
Hey, good thing your friend knew
where the armory was.
Yeah!
Thanks to her, we've still got a chance
of blowing this shithole.
She can borrow my clothes
when we get back to the ship.
This has gone far enough.
All right, get a platoon down to D Block.
I'll meet them there.
Hey, look! Is that a way out?
Yeah!
Out of the pan and into the fire...
I've found them! Over here!
Surrender at once!
Whatever you do, don't stop running!
Drop the bridge! Do it!
Cara!
Raina!
What the... Where the hell am l?
Who is out there?
And what do we have here?
Doctor Vail, I presume.
So, Doctor Hase finally managed
to do himself in.
What a fool, using himself for
his mutation experiments.
Shit! Then, this data doesn't hold the
formula for the fountain of youth?
Only if you want to be a very old monster.
Hase's specialty was gene
manipulation and assembly.
But most of his results can be duplicated by
simple exposure to the geo plasmids.
Plasmids?
The virus-like organisms that inhabit Geo,
which is itself a huge living organism.
This place is the central processor,
the "brain" if you will.
Have you ever heard of panspermia?
In this theory, all the stars in the universe are
made up of thinly dispersed "life particles".
Planet Geo is proof of panspermia.
This is a truly amazing discovery.
Are you out of your fucking mind?!
Shit! Do you know what I've put up
with because of this?!
Stop! That data is valuable!
There he is!
Let's take this from the top again.
Now, are you working for the government?
Or maybe another syndicate?
No, I'm not! Neither! I'm just a two-bit thief!
Goddamn that hurts!
Leave me the fuck alone!
Now then, prepare to spill your guts.
Excuse my interruption, sir!
They've finally found the last escapee.
Right! I'll be right there.
Warden Heel, you'll leave a piece
of her me, won't you?
I'll leave something.
Guy...
I wouldn't waste my worries on him, my dear.
Now then, how can we occupy
our time while we wait.
Perhaps your new friends would like to play.
I said not to bring any guns in here!
Sir, the escapee is hiding
somewhere in these caves.
Down among those anomalies...
Well? Go down there and get him then.
Right! Uh, yes, sir!
Whatever you do, do not use any
guns in this part of Geo!
What are you babbling about, Doctor?
This is the planet's central processor.
If you set it off, it could be catastrophic.
Not this nonsense again? Are you still
trying to prove that this planet's alive?
Do it! Sweep the area!
No! You must not!
Please, stop them!
Please, stop them.
Shut up! And don't touch my sled!
Please... Please stop this.
What the hell?!
Oh, my God!
What the... Fuck!
Wh..What the... Now what's going on?!
My "crazy theory" just acquired a great
deal more supporting evidence.
Fuck off!
Fuck it! Bad move...
Take that! And that! And that!
Have another, you freak!
Ah, shit, no ammo.
Please! Where are you going?
Where does that leave me?
This is insane.
This can't be happening!
What?!
Huh?!
Why is that alarm sounding?
And I thought felt tremors just then.
Raina...
You got such a cute ass,
I'm going to give it a big kiss.
Bastard! I won't forget this.
You've got a big mouth.
I'll have to shove something in it.
What a stud, two women at once!
Where's my stupid partner at a time like this?!
Guy, damn it, where are you?!
Guy!
Guy?
Danger! Evacuate these levels at once!
Evacuate at once! Danger!
What's going on?
Somebody answer me!
Zena!
Danger! Evacuate at once!
Hang in there, Guy.
Fuck!
My jewels... All my precious jewels...
I can't lose them!
This is all your fault!
Everything was fine until you showed up!
You've ruined everything!
You've destroyed all that had value to me!
We've got to go!
I know, but Guy...
Guy...
Go on, Raina! Leave!
Cara!
Get out now, Rania! Get out!
Get out while you can!
Cara!
Goddammit!
Dammit! Let her go!
CARA!!
G..G..Guy!
Guy!
Danger! Evacuate at once!
Out of all those people,
only ten percent made it to safety.
Still, under the circumstances,
that's an amazing number.
I suppose we should consider
ourselves lucky too, huh?
Lucky? Us?
Whadda ya' wanna do with this slave trader?
The garbage chute.
About your friend, I'm sorry we lost her.
Guy, who was she?
We're out of fuel.
Eh?! Of all the stupid things!
What are we going to do now?!
We're gonna die watching the stars roll by!
That"s what!
We'll never see home again!
Oh, God, and my library books!
What's so funny, you freak of nature?!
Turning into that thing must have left you
mentally unstable. You've flipped!
Guy, I don't wanna die!
This can't be happening!
Please, Lord! I'll be good from now on!
I promise!
Guy, why don't you do something?!
This is space crusier PC-001.
We have received your distress call
and are own our way to your rescue.
Okay, so we're lucky!
You're trapped and your screams
seem about to freeze
Then he cuts the darkness like a knife
He gives a wink just to say hello
It feels good
He's the best there is
The road ahead leads towards your dream
But dynamite's hidden along the way
It's romantic, you know
But to him, it's just a game
Two rash, adventurous hearts
Suddenly they come together
It's a whole new universe
It's a hazardous escape
He tosses you a kiss along with his smile
But the joke
Is on you
It's a hazardous rendezvous
But there's never been such a promise
It could happen any time
So fall in love!
It's a hazardous escape
And you can't dodge your feelings for him
You'll have to move fast
Or go mad
It's a hazardous rendezvous
And there's never been any hope before
It can happen any time
So fall in love!
Fall in love!