You're trapped and your screams
seem about to freeze
Eat this!
You're trapped and your screams
seem about to freeze
Then he cuts the darkness like a knife
He gives a wink just to say hello
It feels good
He's the best there is
The road ahead leads towards your dream
Shit, Guy! What a stud!
But dynamite's hidden along the way
It's romantic, you know
Raina, why do you suppose this party's
getting so out of control?
It's romantic, you know
But to him it's just a game
Not my fault...
Two rash, adventurous hearts
Well, no more party tricks, okay?
Suddenly, they come together
It's a whole new universe
It's a hazardous escape
Catch!
He tosses you a kiss along with his smile
All right...
Best hand gets to pilot the spaceship.
He tosses you a kiss along with his smile
But the joke
Is on you
Okay!
Turn 'em over!
It's a hazardous rendezvous
Tough luck, Guy!
But there's never been such a promise
It could happen any time
What?! You cheat!
So fall in love!
Four sevens beats your high card, I think.
It's a hazardous escape
That means I win.
I wanna see a rule book!
And you can't dodge your feelings for him
I wrote the rule book.
You'll have to move fast
Or go mad
It's a hazardous rendezvous
And there's never been any hope before
It can happen any time
So fall in love!
Fall in love!
Now then, since I'm steering this time,
it's time for a challenge.
GUY
PLANET FREZON
Dammit all!
Can't you drive any better than this?
Enough! Shut your mouth!
This road's almost as fucked up as you are.
Mister Charm...
All right, what brings us to a
backwater like this?
Look over there.
What the?
Hey, that's the place on all those
universal peace and love pamphlets -
the People's Free Church of Frezon.
Good guess.
It's also the location of our next target.
Are you shitting me?
I'm serious.
There's a heavy payoff waiting for us in there.
They call it the Goddess of Gold.
Goddess of Gold?
To those in the path of shadow,
listen to Lady Arcana.
All those who have not found the true path,
I, Noima, shall guide.
The eve of the promised miracle is at hand.
Tomorrow, as the three moons of Frezon
converge in the midnight sky...
The combined rays of their luminances
shall encircle our Goddess in holy radiance.
Then, the seals restraining our
Goddess shall be at last severed.
And we, the chosen acolytes,
shall become one -
one with the gods!
The Golden Goddess was
discovered among the ruins.
Its value as an artifact alone is astronomical.
And that's to say nothing of its ransom value.
Or worse comes to worse, it'd make a rather
hadsome stack of gold bars, ya know.
What is it, Guy?
Something's dead up ahead...
Oh, gross!
These bodies are all fresh.
What do you think happened?
I don't know.
Get back, Raina!
Not so tough!
Raina!
Fuck!
Guy, quit fucking around!
Why don't you do your trick?
Bitch, bitch. Why don't you become
an honest woman?
What the fuck's that mean?!
It means some things are impossible.
Out of my way!
Remind me not to ask for your help again!
Shit, no ammo!
Raina, get off your ass!
Guy!
Guy, what were those things?
You're asking me?
I'd investigate, but we've got an
appointment with a golden lady.
Lord Noima! Lady Arcana!
Lady Arcana! Lord Noima!
Lady Arcana, Lord Noima, l,
a poor orphan girl, beg for your help.
Since my parents death,
I have been enslaved by a relative,
a cruel and evil man who beats me constantly.
Please, I beg for your divine mercy!
Help me, please!
You cause more trouble than
you're worth, bitch!
Now, get your worthless ass
back to the house.
It's him! My cruel and evil relative!
Is this what you've been up to?
You asshole!
You're not supposed to be using live ammo!
Well, at least you didn't have to ACT scared.
This is private business.
It is our holy duty to defend the weak.
Hah!
What the?!
Guy!
No need to fear, my little lost lamb.
You're under our protection.
Shit...
I wasn't ready for that.
From this day forth, you shall dwell with us.
Moreover, you shall be freed of all earthly ties.
Take care of yourself, Raina.
Finding the treasure is up to you now.
Raina, don't fuck this up.
I've got trouble enough.
Too much light, dammit.
Lady Arcana,
the leaders of the flock request a conference.
Lady, what shall I tell them?
Noima...
Lady Arcana?
My Lady Arcana...
You know I've never done this.
That's what's worried you?
Tonight, we take possession of the greatest
power our world has ever known.
And after conquering this planet,
we will turn our attention to the stars.
Noima, l...
Arcana...
Again! Again!
Heh!
Time to fly!
Busy, busy, busy!
[Arcana] How gratifying to see all of Frezon's
heads of state in one place.
As you know,
each of your regions has been donating forty
percent of your gross profits to our holy cause.
However, this is no longer enough.
All donations must now be
raised to sixty percent.
I'm sure none of you will find this a problem.
What?! Is she serious?!
Now, if I were a golden goddess,
where would I be?
This in an outrage!
My people are already starving!
We can't live with your extortion!
Your church is nothing but a cancer,
Ieaching what little we have left!
That's one of those creatures,
just like in the village.
Have I made my position clear?
Yesterday, a village died.
Tomorrow perhaps, this fool's city shall follow.
That's what happens when you lose your head.
Now then, is there anyone else
with something to say?
Oh, fuck, I'm sleeping in a nut house.
Long enough...
Which way?
None shall pass.
Prepare to die most unpleasantly.
Shit...
Amateurs...
What a bunch of morons.
As if I'd let myself get sucker-punched twice.
Oh great one, Goddess of Gold,
grant unto us your chosen servants
the ultimate power!
This intruder may not proceed.
Stop him at all costs!
By your command.
Perfect! Did we kill him?
Shit! That was a new set of power armor too.
Raina!
Raina, are you all right?
Guy...
The treasure's here, this way.
Fuckin' A!
Way to go, Raina!
Look at the moons!
Our time has come.
Soon, we shall become gods ourselves.
Sorrí to interrupt, ah, your theological debate,
but I'm looking for a golden goddess.
Seen one around here?
Dog of an unbeliever!
For such insolence, you'll die.
Your flesh will serve us well
as our first sacrifice.
Did you really think your appearance
here was by chance?
Heh, no, I thought it was because
of your lousy security.
Come on, Raina, the treasure's
as good as ours.
Raina?
Raina, what's wrong?!
Raina!
Are you listening to me?
Raina, you hear only our commands.
You will kill your friend
and bathe in his blood.
Taste his blood, eat his flesh
and suck the marrow from his bones.
Now, Raina!
Raina?
Raina...
If this is a joke, it's not funny.
No one can resist our ultimate power.
You've only one chance.
You've got to kill her first.
Cut him down!
Raina...
Don't do it.
Can't Guy... I don't want to, but...
I have no choice.
Kill me, Guy!
Kill me before I kill you!
Delightful!
One might almost believe they were lovers,
wouldn't one?
I'm getting tired of this.
He sacrificed himself for her?
What manner of man is he?
Not man enough to survive this!
No matter how much you resist,
you cannot win!
I shall disembowel the girl and wrap your
corpse in her bloody viscera!
Raina...
She will not be harmed!
You will not touch her!
After all this, you still defy us?
He's either mad or very stupid.
Ah shit, here we go again!
Impossible!
Lady Arcana, look!
Noima, complete the ritual.
Right!
Yes!
Now is the time, now is the moment
for which we have prepared.
Now we shall rule the universe,
and my first act will be to crush that insect.
The time has come for you to DIE!
G..G..Guy...
Damn you! Where are you hiding?
There can be no escape.
Your soul has already been promised - to us!
Now, infidel...
You die!
Up yours!
Guy!
Lady Arcana, escape now.
What are you saying?
We will live forever.
Perhaps. I regret that I shall not follow.
Noima!
I don't understand.
We had the power of the gods.
How could we fail?
Arcana!
Damn you all!
Guy!
The time has come for you to learn
what it means to lose all
that is precious to you.
Guy, don't think you've won this easily.
This was merely foreplay.
Until the time we meet again...
Oh, Guy...
About those two...
I wonder what they had in mind?
After they conquered the universe, I mean.
Who knows?
In all honesty, I have a hard enough time just
imagining the two of us even getting rich.
Same here.
I wonder if we'll ever find
what we're looking for?
And speaking of which, Raina!
Why did you go and destroy
the Golden Goddess?!
Why did I?!
You'd have been a blueberry pancake
if I hadn't, you stupid dork!
Oh, really?!
Everything was going fine until you
stuck a knife in my stomach!
You arrogant prick!
Making something of it, bitch?!
Harping, neurotic little...
Over-inflated bag of ego on steroids!
Hey! What were YOUR hands
doing on MY tits?!
You must be imagining things.
Why would I wanna touch a boy's tits?
Are you calling me a boy?!
It's so warm
In this dream
I've found myself living in
I was alone
In the night
With the darkness creeping in
As I lay
My body pressed
Cold and tight against the glass
The voices from
The heavens came
Wafting down
My heart says go for it
And I reach out my hand
Yet, when it seems I should have it
It's out of my reach
Oh, lonely way
I'm stranger
Now discovering
A new land
Oh, lonely way
I'm stranger
I'll try any way
To get there that I can
Through a narrow, too confined space
Fighting against the wave of time
I find we've reached
All that I sought
When I was still seeking
Despite the bleak
Grey urban streets
I see reality with my eyes
I've a mirror world
Inside my mind
That will not fade away
But if we break that mirror
Will it let my feelings out?
Would they fall as shooting stars
In the midnight sky?
Oh, lonely way
I'm stranger
Now discovering
A new land
Oh, lonely way
I'm stranger
I'll try any way
To get there that I can
This old and used up husk
Still harbors a burning flame
Together, we can do anything
Let's walk on through
Oh, lonely way
I'm a stranger
Discovering a
New land
Oh, lonely way
I'm a stranger
I'll try any way
To get there that I can