I like you.
Please, accept this!
I'm with you always, senpai.
A-Alright. Thank you.
Good for you now, eh.
Thank you very much.
I'll go on ahead.
Ribbon, Chocolates, and the Cherished Sweetheart
Such a massive pile of chocolates again this year, huh.
Japan isn't even a polygamous nation, this is so unfair!
Oh, here comes the super stud.
Stop with that already, jeez.
It's been half a year since you had a girlfriend,
and yet girls still confessed to you regardless.
It's really outrageous!
See Nagamine-san over there?
She might look like she's okay with it,
but I bet she's just about to start to lash out in a rage already.
Nagamme Yuzuha is my girlfriend.
I was attracted to her mysterious aura,
so I confessed to her and we started dating half a year since then.
Though, I think that incident earlier
today must have been really bad.
And I wanted her to be the first one to give me chocolate today.
Hey.
Can I finish preparing the materials at your place?
Oh, okay, of course you can.
Also,
I wanted to give you my chocolate.
I felt a bit embarrassed,
so I really waited until it was just the two of us before giving this.
Would you accept my chocolates too?
Here it comes!
Thank you.
Huh? I haven't given it yet.
Can I enter now?
Okay.
I wonder what the "preparation" she talked was
about before giving me the chocolates?
H-How erotic!
This is what she was preparing for?
All of this, for me.
This personality mismatch is just too intense for me!
No, no, this is actually kind of perfect for me.
Here's the chocolate.
Does she want me to eat it that way?
It tastes sweet.
Yuzuha?
There's still some more.
More chocolates.
These are all yours.
Do whatever you want with them.
Wow.
It feels soft.
I want to fondle it more.
It tastes so good, Yuzuha.
This is the best Valentines gift.
Really?
Was it weird?
Not at all!
In fact, I'm actually happy with it.
Then, let's continue.
It feels so hot.
That feels good.
I can't hold back anymore.
I want to put it in you.
I'm your present for today,
so just do whatever you wish.
I'll... put it in, then.
This is for you, Tomo-kun.
My first time.
I've wanted to give,
a present that only the two of us can share.
As your girlfriend.
As your sweetheart.
Yuzuha!
I'm your girlfriend,
and yet I.
I felt very insecure, and was never at ease.
The only one I love...
is none other than you, Yuzuha!
I'm happy.
Tomo-kun.
Tomo-kun!
I love you.
I really.
I really, really, love you!
Yuzuha.
Me too,
I love you too!
I love you, Tomo-kun!
Senpai, in here are my feelings for you for this year!
I know it's late, but please accept it!
Well...
I'm the only one who can pleasure Tomo-kun's dick.
I won't let anyone lay a finger on it.
I-I see.
Looks like her jealousy is really straightforward.
Oh, is that so?
Whoa, so Kurimu-chan's going to save
Micheru-kun. (Cream and Mitchell)
Your panties are exposed, you know.
Anyway, there are lots of other parts
in that chapter that are good, too!
See? Like this scene here.
And this one.
The main character, who sets out on an adventure
for his beloved one, and his friends.
Now this is where the story really starts!
That's all good and well, but how long are you going to stay here?
Hey, is the next volume for this month still not out?
Oh, it was the day before yesterday.
I've yet to buy it, though.
Then buy it already, okay?
Hey, buy it yourself!
But you see,
our home is strict and manga are not allowed there.
Please-oh-please-okay?
It's always been like this, but jeez.
See you tomorrow, then.
Hey, that's the latest release of Icha-Ero-Dou!
Oh crap!
Hey, what did you just say?
Let me go!
Why are you trying to run away?
I'm going home already!
I said wait!
– Oh crap, oh crap, oh crap, oh crap oh crap, oh crap, oh crap, oh crap.
– You just said Icha-Ero-Dou earlier, right?
That's exactly what I heard!
So.
I can still feel the sensation of her butt on me
You don't just read monthlies here, but also doujinshis?
I'm sorry.
So girls also read those?
Girls aren't exactly prohibited from reading those, you know.
Oh, so you masturbate with it, too?
With doujinshi, I mean.
Eh?! Why are you asking me that?
Well, boys usually buy that kind of stuff for that so.
W-Well...
I guess I could say yes.
Oh, sorry I asked such weird questions.
Huh?
Normally, I wouldn't feel anything when she clings to me.
Strange... Masami kind of looks very cute today.
Did she always look like this?
Huh? What's this?
So-Sou-chan?
Hey,
do you want to.
Do something naughty... like what people do in a doujinshi?
You're the one who asked first, okay?
Don't you try to run away from this, too.
Wow.
So they feel this soft and tender.
It feels embarrassing.
This is... Sou-chan's dick.
That feels good, Masami.
It's good, just keep it up.
Your face looks so lewd, I just can't get enough of it.
Oh no, I'm about to cum!
It tastes weird.
Wait, so we're not finished yet?
I haven't fucked your pussy yet, you know.
W-Wait!
Doing these naughty things always ends with sex, you know.
And just how did you reach that conclusion?
It's in Creamy Pie doujins, too.
No, please Kateid-sama.
It's in so deep!
Kurimu-chan had sex with the knight captain there!
Besides,
you're very wet already.
So you're trying to imagine it all.
Jeez, I don't know anything anymore!
It's tight.
It feels hot.
My dick feels like it's going to melt.
So-Sou-chan.
Be more gentle.
Sorry, but I just can't.
Oh no, I'm starting to feel weird.
I'm.
Oh yes.
Sou-kun, it's all weird.
I'm starting to feel weird!
It's not weird.
It's just normal.
Because we're having sex.
Is that.
Sou-chan, I'm about to!
I'm cumming.
Hey, Sou-chan.
What?
I'm alright with cosplaying,
but why can't I wear any undies?
Oh, that.
Take it as a rental fee.
You're always reading my manga, anyway.
Lecher! Sou-chan's such a pervert!
Mornin'.
Good morning.
Everyday, at the same time, at the same place,
I always meet my crush.
The time we spend waiting at the bus stop,
makes me feel very happy.
Even if these are unrequited feelings.
The Heart's Guidepost
Nishimura Keiji-kun.
He's the soccer club's mid-fielder.
How good for you.
Looks like your prince charming is also working hard today.
Na-Nayu-chan!
Th-That's not it!
I'm just idling by the window because it's too hot.
Oh come on now.
Still not honest with yourself, eh.
It's written all over your face, you know.
That you totally like Nishimura-kun.
Nayu-chan!
Why don't you just boldly ask him out?
A-Ask him out?
I can't do that!
I like you, Nishimura-kun.
Hey, would you like to go out with me?
Eh? Okay.
I accept.
Really? Yay, I'm really happy!
Oh, you can just call me Kyou.
Then, I can call you Keiji-kun too, right?
I wasn't able to focus on the class properly.
I even forgot my pencil case in the classroom.
Have I become weird?
I like you.
Huh?
Oh yes.
It really hits the spot.
Why?
Whoa.
That surprised me.
I thought it was a teacher or someone else.
Why is it not Nishimura-kun?
We broke us, of course.
He told me we can't have sex, even though we're already dating.
Besides, it's not your business who I go out with, you know.
Anyway, you're a nuisance.
Can you get out already?
You can cum inside me today.
Can I?
I wonder what I was worried about.
If I just mustered my courage and confessed to him before then,
then Nishimura-kun would never have had to experience that.
Oh no, I'm totally drenched now.
You're quite early today.
Oh, you're right.
It was quite a downpour.
Yeah.
Yesterday, right afterschool.
I'm sorry.
Wait, why does Nishimura-kun know?
I was also watching over your side.
I was really surprised.
It's been less than three days since we broke up
and she's already doing it with another guy.
Then the thing about breaking up.
Nope, haven't heard of it.
Well, she might have been like that from the start.
I'm sure... it turned out quite better because of it.
I guess so.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
I can't just watch him like this.
I don't want him to be hurt again like that.
You're.
I should have told him earlier.
Well, it looks like I just confessed in
the spur of the moment, though.
But, I don't care anymore.
Because.
I... love you, Nishimura-kun.
I love you.
For a long, long time already.
I... accept your feelings.
I'm very happy.
I never thought that the girl who really holds
me dear was already so close to me.
Nishimura-kun.
Please go out with me, Sugawara.
Aoi... so Sugawara Aoi is your full name.
Such a cute name.
You're beautiful, Aoi.
Nishimura-kun.
Try to relax.
It's going inside.
Does it hurt?
I-I'm alright.
It's you, so it does not really hurt.
Please, just continue.
Wow.
Your love juices are overflowing.
It was just a dream.
To be one with you.
To hear your voice, feel your breath,
sense your warmth very close to me,
makes me so happy.
Right now, I'm in total bliss.
Aoi!
Nishimura-kun.
I'm cumming.
I love you.
H-Hey, what are you doing at the campus?
It's not any worse than sex though, right?
Startle!!