Um, Mika-san?
Look at how big you've gotten.
I'm confiscating this.
W-We shouldn't be doing this, Mika-san!
What shouldn't we be doing?
Aren't you the one who keeps checking me out?
You're such a pervert.
Oh, god!
Mika-san?
Here are the boobs you love so much.
I don't do this for just anyone, you know?
Geez, being captivated by my boobs like that...
Mika-san!
Sheesh. You're so cute, Manager-san.
It's a shame that you're not my manager.
Mika-chan, are you ready for the gravure photo shoot?
Oh, my.
Crystal Baby
Mika is
going a
gravure
photo
shoot
That's it! Just like that, Mika-chan.
That expression is perfect!
You're a natural!
Now be a bit more flirty.
Yeah, that's it!
Why'd you do that? I'm your girlfriend!
Say something!
S-Sorry...
Do you really like boobs that much?
Well, yeah...
Then, between my boobs and Mika's, which are better?
M-Miyu, you're going on stage soon.
You need to be careful with your outfit.
It's not like I can sing when I'm feeling like this!
Do I even need to say it?
I love your boobs more, Miyu.
Ryoto-kun, you dummy.
So, did you guys do... it?
It?
S-S-Sex...
Sex? Could it be you wanna do it right now?
No,
but, your dick...
I'm just asking you if you put your dick
inside Mika-chan's pussy or not!
Miyu...
Does it really bother you that much, Miyu?
You're not even trying to answer
my question. You big meanie.
I mean, I'm your girlfriend.
I don't want you having sex with anyone else!
Then, I'm gonna put my dick inside
your pussy, just like you want.
It went in!
So good!
Ryo-kun! Ryo-kun!
More... Make love to me more!
Miyu, you're so tight!
It's because my pussy doesn't want
to ever let go of your dick.
So that's why...
Love me! Love me, and only me!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm going to do my best, so cheer me on, okay?
Of course I will.
Yes, hello?
A gravure photo shoot?
Okay, I'll do it.
Crystal Baby 2
Yeah, that's great!
Now, turn this way a bit.
You two are doing great!
Okay, look over here!
Good work.
– Thank you for your hard work!
All the new swimsuits we wore today were so nice.
Seriously!
I'm going to show you my one-hundred
percent in the next shoot.
Don't think this is all I got!
Shake
Hey.
Manager-san.
Ryo-kun!!
Manager-san...
Good girl.
That's it for today.
Your next shoot isn't until tomorrow morning.
You're free to do whatever you want in the meantime.
Really?!
Yay, yay! We're free!
Sea Hut
Isono
Are we really?
Maybe I'll go shopping.
Hey, let's go have steak.
Steak sounds good, doesn't it?
And then, we can have mochi ice cream.
We could have crepe, too!
Hey!
Sheesh, she's always like this
whenever she gets free time.
What I want to do most, though...
Is go on a date, just the two of us.
I wanna go on a date too.
How did this happen?!
Why the heck are you here, Mika-chan?!
Because it's a date. Isn't that obvious?
Giggle
Alright then, I'm going to be borrowing
Manager-san's dick first.
No, you can't!!
Hey, look at it!
First, you slide just the tip in,
and then you force it all the way inside...
So good! It feels so good!
Manager-san, does it feel good?
Your dick is getting so hard inside my pussy!
How cute.
Mika-san, if you're too rough,
I'm gonna cum immediately...
That's fine! Cum inside me!
Cum lots inside my pussy!
I told you, you can't!
Miyu-chan?
I won't let him cum inside you.
Oh, my.
Angry
Why are you even playing with my
boyfriend's dick in the first place?
That's because I like him too.
It's a given that I'd want to do sexual things to him.
Look, he's still so hard.
He's so cute.
No matter how much affection I shower him in, though,
his head just won't stop thinking about you.
There's really no space for me in there.
That's why I've already given up.
Is that true?
Miyu-chan, you're the only one I love!
You'll make love only to me?
Yeah, just you.
Ryo-kun!
Miyu-chan, your pussy looks so happy!
If you suck that hard, I'll...
You're so wet already.
It's embarrassing!
I'm having sex even though Mika-chan is looking!
If we bend over like this, he'll be able to see everything.
Ryo-kun, you pervert.
Now, now. Let's all feel good together.
Sheesh.
Mika gets it again? That's not fair!
I'll give it to you too!
You're important to me too, Mika-san.
So... How about the three of us keep
working together like this?
Well, I guess having a threesome felt good,
so if it's once in a while...
My pussy felt better though, right?
What are you saying?
Creampies are forbidden now! I forbid it!
– What the heck are you saying?
– Are we really going to be okay like this?
– No, what the heck are you saying?!
So apparently, that teacher is
nicknamed "the black hole".
Lel, what's this one called, then?
I finally found you.
Friend of yours?
Nope...
The Hero!
Wait a min...
What? You got a girlfriend?
No, I don't even know who this is!
Mr. Hero!
Fucking normie, die in a fire!
Alice-chan out of nowhere!
Welcome!
May I ask how many in your party?
I don't know who this girl is, but who even
hugs someone out of the blue like that?
She is pretty cute, though.
I guess I could talk to her,
even if she's not making any sense.
So what did you want to talk about?
Ah, yes.
I have come from a different
world to meet you, Mr. Hero.
Sorry, I'm not into that kind of stuff.
W-Wait, please!
This again?!
This time, I'm not letting go!
Okay, I get it already!
I love how you smell.
We're ready to check out...
Yes... Understood.
I don't know the exact circumstances,
but you can't just cling to a stranger out of nowhere.
I-I apologize, I was just so happy.
I, Alice Fairy, have come this
far to have my wish granted.
I don't get what's going on at all. I'm going home.
Oh dear, it's so big!
– Wha... wait!
– I'm digging in.
Stop...
She's not listening to me!
I-I'm cumming!
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since I've had cum. It's so good!
Do you mind if this gets a taste too?
Yeah, right. I'm going home.
Don't do this again, alright?
It's dangerous.
Later.
Aww, he's just as good a person as I remember him.
I just got sucked off by a girl I don't even know.
She was cute so it's me, I guess?
Oh? So this is your base of operations in this world?
No need to stare so much at my stuff.
So? Breaking into a stranger's apartment and
trespassing... What are you trying to do?
Oh, my apologies.
I was just very excited.
We're finally alone, Mr. Hero.
Are you for real?
Now, do you believe me?
My world had to face a great peril.
However, you came and saved us.
What? I did?
I, Alice Fairy, worked with you as a General,
and sometimes as a lover.
Oh, I see. So we were lovers.
That's why you followed me to
this world when I returned.
Well yes, that's true, but you also...
You also went back on your promise to marry me,
and ran away with the princess!
Well, not much I can do about that...
Do you even know how I felt seeing you
spend each night with the princess?
Hey, come on. Don't cry.
I refused to give up, and came here.
In just one night, you turned me into a woman.
The love you gave me that night
has brought me this far.
You're mine and mine alone.
I'm going to make this dick mine too.
Hero, please let me make you
feel good from today onward.
Shit, it's rubbing against her so much!
All of your dick has gone inside me!
Your dick is so amazing!
You're like a baby.
Your dick is throbbing so hard inside me.
Please make my pussy remember the taste of your dick!
Good... It feels so good!
Your dick is so amazing! Give me more!
Give me more!
I love cumming with your dick.
There's so much of your cum inside me.
I love it when you cum inside me!
When I woke up, Alice was gone, without a trace.
You won't get enough nutrients
if bread is all you're having.
Mr. Hero.
Here you go. Please eat this.
Yeah, thanks.
I have found a place for myself in this world.
It's the room right next to yours!
translation: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: bis
quality control: hyakupercent