Umm, Mika-san.
You're already this hard, eh.
Maybe this is too good for you?
Th-This is bad!
This is... Mi-Mika-san!
What exactly is bad about it?
You always look so obscenely at my
boobs whenever we meet, you know.
You pervert.
Whoa.
Mika... san?
Here, the breasts that you adore so much.
I don't do this kind of service much, so enjoy.
My oh my.
Now you're all over my breasts.
Mika-san!
Honestly.
You really are such a cutie.
Mr. Manager.
Sorry if it's not going to be me, though.
Mika-chan!
Is my wardrobe for the gravure photoshoot done?
Oh... my.
Mika's
currently at
a gravure
photoshoot
That's great Mika-chan.
That expression is really nice.
It gives such an impact.
Try to make it even more inviting... whoa, yes, that's it!
Why?
I'm your girlfriend, Ryouta, and yet.
Say something!
I'm, sorry.
Do you really love breasts that much?
Well... yeah.
Then which are better, Mika's breasts, or mine?
M-Miu!
Your turn is about to start.
You have to handle that wardrobe with care.
But, these feelings just keep bugging me and I can't stand it!
That's.
Something I don't even need to say.
You're the one I'll choose, Miu.
Stupid Ryouta-kun.
Then, did you do "it"?
"It?"
Se-Sex.
Sex?
Oh, do you want to do it now?
That's not what I mean.
Your... dick.
I'm asking if you inserted your dick in Mika's pussy!
Miu.
Does it really bother you, Miu?
Jeez, you're not even answering me properly.
Meanie.
I'm your girlfriend, you know.
I don't want you to have sex with anyone but me!
As you wish, then.
I'll put my dick inside your pussy.
It's in!
Oh yes.
Ryou-kun... Ryou-kun!
Make love to me more... and more!
Miu, your insides are gripping me really tight.
My?
That's because I no longer want to let you go!
That's why, I!
I want you to love me, and me alone!
I'm about to cum.
I'll do my best now,
so cheer me on, okay?
Of course.
Yes, hello?
A gravure photoshoot?
Alright, I understand.
Good, good.
Okay, just a bit more.
Extend it a little further.
Yes, that's superb.
Great, great.
Alright, now face here.
Good work.
Good work, everyone.
Good work, everyone!
All of the new swimsuits were really nice.
I know right?
I'm going to show my all at the next photoshoot!
I can't do much more than this!
Hey.
Oh, Mr. Manager.
Ryou-kun!
Mr. Manager.
Good.
Now this ends our work for today.
The next photoshoot will be tomorrow morning,
so you two are free until then.
Really?!
Yay-yay!
Hooray for days off!
That's great.
Why don't we go shopping?
Hey, why don't we all go for some steak?
I want some really good steak
And then some mochi ice cream afterwards!
And some crepe as well!
Hey!
It always turns out like this during these times.
Good grief.
But,
the one I really want to do most,
is a one-on-one date with Mr. Manager.
Me too.
I want to go on a date too.
Why...
did it turn out like this?!
Wait, why in the world are you here, Mika-chan?!
Oh? Why for our date, of course!
Ta-da! I'll be taking Mr. Manager's dick first.
No, stop!
Hey, look.
Insert the tip first, then instantly push it all the way down.
Oh yes.
That felt really good.
Mr. Manager.
Does it feel good?
Your dick feels like it's getting even harder inside me.
How cute.
Mika-san, if you keep doing it that intensely I'll.
I'll soon!
It's alright.
Just cum a lot.
Cum lots inside my pussy!
I said stop!
Miu-chan?
I won't let him cum inside you!
My oh my.
Why are you playing with
another girl's boyfriend's dick, anyway?!
That's because I also love Mr. Manager.
I'll want to have sex with him, of course.
Oh, it's still quite stiff.
How cute.
But, while I'm already giving him lots of love,
he's only ever had eyes for you.
I never had any place to go in between you two.
That's why I'm giving up on him.
Is that true?
You're the only one I love, Miu-chan!
Are you going to love only me?
Yeah.
Only you.
Ryou-kun!
Miu-chan, I see your pussy's already quite delighted for this.
If you keep sucking me like that.
You're already like this.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm... having sex all while Mika-chan is watching!
This position completely exposes us.
No, you're such a pervert, Ryou-kun.
Well, if it comes to this then we
might as well pleasure each other.
Jeez.
Hey, it's Mika-chan again!
No fair!
I'm going to insert it now.
Mika-san's important to me, as well.
That's why, I want us to work hard together from now on.
Jeez, well, doing a threesome was quite pleasurable, I guess.
If she's witch us, then.
But,
my pussy felt better, right?
What are you suddenly asking?!
Cumming inside is not allowed!
Not allowed, you hear me!
Will things really be okay?
That teach's nickname seems to be "black hole".
That made me LOL hard.
Then what about our math teach?
I've... finally found you.
Do you, know this girl?
Nope.
My hero!
Hey, just wait!
So... you have a GF already?
No! I don't even know this person!
My hero!
You real-lifers can go to hell!
A wild Alice-chan appears!
Welcome!
I'm not sure of such a recruitment method,
but suddenly hugging me like that is just.
But, she sure is cute.
Well, I guess I could just hear her our for the moment.
So... what is it that you want to tell me?
Oh, yes.
I've traveled from another realm to meet you, Mr. Hero.
Sorry, I'm not really into those things.
Wait, just wait, please!
That again!
I'll never let you go again.
I get it, I get it already!
I really love your scent, Mr. Hero.
I'll be taking the receipt.
Yes, thank you very much.
I don't really know the situation,
but I'll have to tell you that it's quite
troublesome to just hug me like that in public.
I'm sorry.
I was just so happy.
I, Alice Fearie,
came all the way here to fulfill the love that I never had.
Jeez, I have no idea what's what anymore.
I'll be going, then.
Oh my, how sturdy-looking!
I shall be taking this.
Stop!
She's not listening!
I-I'm cumming!
Thank you very much.
I haven't tasted such good cum in a long time.
Do you want to have a taste of this next?
Stop fooling around.
I'm going home.
Don't do this thing to anyone else.
It's not safe.
See you.
My, he's still the gentleman that he's always been.
I got a blowjob from a girl I just met.
She's cute at least, so I guess I'll just let it slide.
Oh, so this is where your base is in this world, Mr. Hero.
Stop looking around too much.
So, what exactly do you want to do
after coming into this place uninvited?
Eh? Oh, I'm sorry.
I just got too excited.
Now it's just the two of us, Mr Hero.
Whoa, is this for real?
Now do you believe me?
The world I was in suffered from a great crisis.
But you, Mr. Hero, saved us all.
Wait, me?
And I, Alice Fearie,
was one of those who assisted you, and was the task handler.
I'm also your sweetheart.
I see.
So you and I were lovers.
Then after I returned to this world, you went to follow me.
That's true, but.
The issue is,
you left me, the one whom you vowed to share your life with,
and then went on to marry the princess!
E-Even if you say that.
The feeling that I had watching the
Queen and you together everyday.
Hey now, don't cry.
But, I never gave up, and eventually came to this place.
You made me into a woman, albeit only for one night.
But, I was able to get here because of my love for you.
My one and only hero.
I'm going to make this dick mine from now on.
Please, pleasure yourself with me everyday.
Mr. Hero.
Oh crap, she's really rubbing it hard.
Your dick... is now all the way inside me!
Your dick is amazing.
Mr. Hero,
you're like a child doing that.
Your dick is twitching inside me.
Starting today, the shape of your dick,
will forever be remembered by my pussy.
Oh yes, that feels great.
Your dick is amazing, Mr. Hero.
More.
More!
I really love cumming with your dick.
There's also lots of your cum.
I also love being cummed inside.
After that,
Alice disappeared as soon as I woke up.
She left without a single trace.
Eating only bread for lunch isn't
good for your nutritional balance.
Mr. Hero,
here.
Please eat this.
O-Okay.
Thank you.
Oh yes, I've also found my place in this world as well.
The room besides yours.
Eh?!