I like you! Please accept this!
I'll forever cheer for you, Senpai!
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Good for you.
Thank you so much.
I'm leaving.
Ribbons, chocolates, and the one I love.
Another good haul of chocolate this year.
Japan doesn't allow polygamy,
so how is this even fair?
Huh?
There you are, playboy.
Sheesh, quit calling me that.
It's been half a year since you got a girlfriend,
and people are still confessing to you.
Damn, that's just wrong.
Look, she might seem docile and
okay with what's happening,
but inside, she's probably burning up with anger.
My girlfriend's name is Nagamme Yuzuha.
Taken in by her mysterious personality,
I confessed to her half a year ago and we started dating.
I guess what happened this morning wasn't exactly good.
I wanted the first chocolate I got today to be from her.
Hey, would it be okay if I prepared
a few things at your house?
Huh? Yeah, of course.
Also...
I-I want to give you some chocolate.
It's too embarrassing, so I wanted
to wait until we were alone.
Will you accept my chocolate too?
Finally!
Thank you.
I haven't even given it to you yet.
Can I come in yet?
Yep, come in.
What kind of preparation did she
need to do to give me chocolate?
S-So hot! So this is what she needed to prepare.
Did she do all of this for me?
Wow, this is crazy.
No, this is perfect!
The chocolate...
Is she telling me to eat it?
So sweet.
Yuzuha?
There's still more... chocolate.
Do whatever you want with them.
Wow, they're so soft!
I want to touch them more!
It tastes so good, Yuzuha.
This is the best Valentine's Day present ever!
You mean it? It wasn't weird, was it?
Not at all! I'm extremely happy.
Okay then, let's continue.
It's so hot.
That feels really good.
I can't wait any longer.
I want to stick this inside you.
I'm your present, Tomo.
You can do whatever you want to me.
Okay. I'm gonna put it in.
I'll give you my first time.
I wanted to give you something that would
become a memory for just the two of us.
As you girlfriend... As your lover.
Yuzuha!
Even though I'm your girlfriend, I...
I can't help but feel so uneasy.
The only one I love is you, Yuzuha!
I'm so happy!
Tomo-kun...
Tomo-kun!
I love you! I really, really love you!
Yuzuha!
Me too. I love you!
Tomo-kun, I love you!
Senpai, these are my feelings for you!
I'm a bit late, but please accept them!
Um...
I'm the only one who can touch his dick.
I won't let anyone else near it.
Eh?
Huh?
Hmph.
You're kidding...
Yuzuha's jealousy is a bit extreme.
Oh, really?
Cream-chan saves Mitchell-kun?
I can see your panties!
Besides, there are better parts than that, you know?
Huh?
See? Like here and here.
The hero sets off on a journey with his
trusted allies to save the one he loves?
This is it!
That's great and all, but how long
do you plan on staying here?
Hey, has this month's Poppo come out yet?
Oh, it came out two days ago.
I haven't bought it yet though.
Be sure to buy it, okay?
Buy it yourself!
But my parents are really strict about manga, so I can't.
Pretty please!
This isn't anything new, but still...
Okay, see you tomorrow!
Oh!
The new Icha-ero books.
Crap!
What did you just say?
L-Let me go!
Why are you running away?
I told you, I'm going home!
Just wait a second!
Crap crap crap crap!
You definitely said "Icha-ero". I know you did.
Let's see...
I can still feel her butt on my face.
So your real purpose in coming here wasn't
just for manga, but for the doujinshi too?
I'm so sorry.
So girls read these too, huh?
W-Well, it's not like it's against the law
for girls to read this or anything.
Hm?
So you masturbate and stuff with doujinshi too?
What? Wh-Why are you asking me that?
Well guys usually buy these to do that.
I-I guess I might have...
Sorry for asking such a weird thing.
Wait...
Usually she doesn't feel a thing from hugging me.
It's okay, right?
How do I put this?
She's just really cute right now.
Was she always this cute?
Huh? Wh-What?
S-Sou-chan?
Listen,
do you wanna try doing perverted things
like they do in those doujinshi?
Don't forget you're the one who started this, okay?
Yeah, don't flake on me either.
Wow, they're so soft and squishy.
This is so embarrassing.
So this is his dick?
That feels really good, Masami.
Yeah, just like that.
Her face is so erotic. I can't take it anymore!
Crap, I'm gonna cum!
It tastes weird.
You're not done yet?
I haven't put my dick in your pussy yet.
W-Wait!
It's a rule that to really do perverted things,
one has to put their dick into a pussy.
Where is that rule even written?
In Creamy Pie's doujins...
Oh, I'm gonna break. It feels so good!
The knight commander and Cream-chan
have sex, don't they?
And she was really wet too.
You're already fantasizing aren't you, Masami?
Shut up, you jerk.
It's so tight and hot!
I feel like my dick is going to melt.
S-Sou-chan, be more gentle.
Sorry, I can't!
Oh, no. I'm starting to feel funny.
I feel so good!
Sou-chan...
I'm...
I'm feeling really weird!
Don't worry.
It's not weird.
Of course you feel good. We're having sex.
Sou-chan!
Sou-chan, no more!
I'm gonna cum!
Hey, Sou-chan?
What is it?
I don't mind cosplaying, but why can't I wear underwear?
Yeah, about that...
That's the fee.
You're always in my room reading manga for free after all.
Sou-chan, you pervert! Lecher!
Morning.
Good morning.
Everyday at the same place and same time,
I get to meet the one I love.
These brief moments I spend alone
with him makes me so happy.
Even if he never returns my feelings.
Signpost of mind
That's Nishimura Keiji-kun.
He's a midfielder for our school's soccer team.
How nice.
Your prince in shining armor is working hard like always.
M-Maya-chan?
I-It's not what you think.
It's hot so I'm just trying to catch a breeze by the window.
Geez, you're not honest at all.
It's so obvious: "I love Nishimura-kun"
is written all over your face.
Maya-chan...
Why don't you just confess already?
Confess? I could never do that!
I like you, Nishimura-kun!
So could you like go out with me?
Y-Yeah. Let's go out.
Really? Yay! I'm so happy!
You can call me by my first name, Yuna.
In return, I'll call you Keiji-kun, okay?
I couldn't focus in class today either.
I forgot my pencil case back there too.
What's going on with me?
Yeah, sure.
It feels so good, Yamashita-kun!
Why?
What the hell?
You scared me. I thought you were a teacher.
Why aren't you with Nishimura-kun?
Obviously because we broke up.
He said that even if we were dating,
we couldn't have sex.
Anyway, who I date has nothing to do with you.
So, could you like, leave already?
You can cum inside.
For real?
What was I worrying about?
If I had just worked up the courage to confess earlier,
all that stuff with Nishimura-kun wouldn't have happened.
Geez, I'm soaking wet.
You're early today.
Yeah, I guess.
It's raining hard, isn't it?
Y-Yeah.
About after school yesterday... Sorry about that.
Wh-What? Why does he know about that?
I saw what happened there too.
It really surprised me.
We had only dated for three days and she was already
doing that kind of thing with another guy.
But, I heard you two broke up.
No, she never told me that.
I guess, she was just that kind of person.
I-It's probably a good thing you left.
Yeah, maybe.
Well, no helping it.
I can't be a bystander anymore.
I couldn't stand seeing him get hurt the same way again.
Sugawara?
I should've told him sooner.
This might be a really clumsy way to confess to him, but...
Even so, I don't care.
After all...
I like you, Nishimura-kun.
I've liked you for a while, Nishimura-kun.
I'll accept your feelings.
I'm so happy that there was a girl this close
to me who thought so dearly of me.
Nishimura-kun...
Go out with me, Sugawara.
Aoi? Your full name is Sugawara Aoi?
That's a really cute name.
You're so beautiful, Aoi.
Nishimura-kun...
Relax, Aoi.
It's coming inside!
Does it hurt?
I-I'm okay.
Because it's your dick, it doesn't hurt.
Please keep going.
Wow, you're letting out so much love juice.
This must be a dream. I'm connected to you.
I can feel your breath, warmth, and hear
your voice so close to me. I'm so happy!
I'll never be happier than I am right now!
Aoi!
Nishimura-kun!
I'm cumming!
I love you!
smooch
Wh-What are you two doing here?
Well it's better than having sex in school, don't you think?
gulp
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: bis | punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent