Express.
Every time I get on a train,
I'm reminded of the time I was molested.
Crimson Girls
~Dominated by Molesters~
Part Two NOZOMI SUBMISSION Chapter II
It happened so suddenly... I couldn't resist them at all.
I won't let them get away with it again.
I'll make sure they get
turned over to the police!
Huh?
What's going on?
It's the same guy as last time...
Not this time!
I won't let any of you get away
with it this time! I'm gonna report...
You're a smart girl.
But if anyone's going to get reported, it's you.
Falsely accusing someone of molestation is a crime.
I told you last time, didn't I?
This is your punishment.
Bad girls need to be punished.
I love the taste of your armpit!
Your boobs are so nice and supple.
I guess I'll touch your ass.
Somebody's hand is violating my body!
He's not even hesitating to touch my private parts!
My body's getting so hot
even though I'm being molested!
What's happened to me?
If I knew my nipples were going
to be played with on a train,
I would've worn a bra.
I can't believe I'm getting off from being molested!
They're touching my private parts against my will!
Excuse me.
You like this, right?
Huh? What's he gonna do?
Hey wait! No way!
What on earth is this thing?
It's small, but it's vibrating so intensely...
I've never felt anything like this before!
No, I can't escape!
They're in front of me, behind me,
above me, and below me!
I've never heard of a person getting off
from being molested, so why?
So why am I?!
Whoa, wait! What are they
gonna do to me now?!
Hurry up and take out this vibrating thing alreally!
Huh? He's taking it out...
They're going to make me cum again!
I promised myself that I wouldn't
let this happen to me again!
But I'm going to cum from being molested!
That's the girl from before.
And those guys with her...
Sorry, please move!
Please let me through! Dammit!
Crap, I lost sight of them.
Could that man have been...
Cleaning in progress
Please! Stop!
Not enough with your clothes still on?
That's not true... at all.
You wanted this, didn't you?
No!
You were so gung ho about reporting us before.
Are you done resisting now?
No! No, I'm...
Sto...
You think I'd stop? I told you already.
This is your punishment.
No, stop!
You're really getting off for someone
being punished, aren't you?
No! No, I'm not!
I can't believe I'm getting this wet
even though I don't want this!
I shouldn't be, but...
You're just a dirty pervert, aren't you?
I'm not a pervert! I haven't even...
Oh? Are you a virgin perhaps?
So a little girl who hasn't known a man
thought she could take us on?
No!
I'm going to cum again!
That was a great reaction from a virgin.
Did you actually want something like this to happen?
No! I...
Did you do those bad things on the train
hoping that you would get punished like this?
What's happening?!
My brain feels like it's being pulled out of me!
Punishment.
This is all punishment for falsely
accusing someone of molesting me.
After seeing the men who I accused for fun
receive punishment for a crime they didn't commit.
I felt better about myself.
Yes, that's me.
I didn't do anything wrong!
I just wanted to eat hamburgers
with my friends. What's wrong with that?
You broke a Buddhist discipline!
You'll be hit 20 times as punishment!
Ow! Stop! Ow!
Ow! Stop! It hurts!
Because of how strict my family was,
I've always had to endure punishments.
Did I want that?
But I won't be satisfied with just that.
I realize that now.
My body has been this way since my childhood...
It actually wants to be punished!
I'm sorry!
I've been a bad girl!
So, please punish me!
Then punish yourself.
Okay.
Is this my punishment?
Will it absolve me of my sins?
What's wrong? Is that it?
Your sins must've been really light, then.
Are you okay with making so much noise?
It'll get even more embarrassing if someone finds out.
I don't care!
I'm a bad girl!
I've been a really bad girl!
So, please make me feel even more embarrassed!
You poor girl.
As you wish!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm being raped!
In a place like this, with a man I don't know...
My pussy is being pounded by his dick!
He took my virginity
and is giving me my punishment!
But even though I don't want this at all... even though
this is something that shouldn't be happening...
My body can't help but feel good!
It feels so good!
Punish me more...
Give me something harsher!
Please punish my sinful pussy with your dick!
I'll give you a much harsher punishment.
So? Just like you wanted,
I came inside your sinful pussy.
Punishment... feels so good!
Next up is her.
The Crimson Girls' leader... Nanase Saki.
translator: hikarukon
translation check: nyanpasu
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fyurie, punk4real
quality control: fyurie
Makino? Could you check the mailbox?
Understood.
We have something from an unknown sender.
Look at this!