W
Crimson Girls
~Molester Watch~
They’re called the Crimson Girls.
A rumored group of female detectives.
I heard about them several days ago.
Shit, let me go!
Apparently, everyone in the underworld knows them.
Take him to the cops immediately, Mitsu.
Okay.
I like strong, proud women.
The excitement I get from the moment I make them surrender...
I could never tire of that feeling.
Spending any more time on this piece of trash is a waste.
There are many other people who deserve our help more.
I’ll go back ahead of you.
Okay, Nana-san.
I like strong, proud women.
The excitement I get from the moment I make them surrender...
I could never tire of that feeling.
Chapter One
Honey Surrenders
Ever since birth, I’ve been blessed with a mysterious power.
And it was like, sooooo cute!
I can manipulate the weak hearted.
This power comes in handy whenever I want to make a girl mine.
What?
He’s just touching me?
Doesn’t look like it’ll end with just that.
Just cut it out...
Is he a molester?
Don’t get cocky!
He wasn’t alone?
Don’t touch me, you cowards!
How dare they...
I can’t let them get away with it.
How annoying!
Oh no!
It really is so cool!
Hey, Himiko...
That isn’t yours, is it?
I’d never wear something that ugly!
Up until now, you were the “hero”, and now look at you.
Kuroha Mitsu.
How does he know my name?
You dress so provocatively... don’t pretend you don’t want to be touched.
Don’t talk like you know me!
It’s different...
The way he touches me is different from the others...
No!
What was that?
It felt so powerful.
Like I’m falling asleep.
At this rate... I’ll scream... out loud...
The Crimson Girls will form a line and bow before me.
And the first to fall will be you.
Mitsu.
If this continues...
No!
I have to fight back!
This is so frustrating!
In front of these scumbags... I’m...
In a place like this?
No way!
Hey, that bra... let’s snap it.
You don’t need to hide them.
You want to go further, don’t you?
Now your face looks girlish.
Stop saying... that...
This guy really is different!
Whenever he touches me... I can’t fight back!
No wait!
I can’t let him get away with it!
It’s inside... my pussy!
Inside... of me...
This can’t happen!
It can’t feel good!
Now I can’t think of anything!
Nozomi?
Now... now is my only chance.
I’ll shove his hand away... kick my legs...
And knock them out!
This is so frustrating!
How does he make me feel so good with every touch?
I’m completely under his control!
I don’t want to continue this.
I can’t keep this up!
Please... no more...
You really disappointed me...
The “great” Crimson Girls... aren’t as great as the rumors say.
No! My body is so hot!
It won’t listen to me anymore...
I’m cumming!!!
Wait up, Nozomi.
Is that all? Is it over?
What’s going on?
Why?
Why did I have that flashback?
Idiot! Stop thinking about that!
I prepared something similar to your beloved Nana-san.
I think you owe me a little smile.
If I ask her to change clothes, she obeys.
Her body wants me, but her mind protests.
Oh no... everyone is watching.
I can’t take this.
If you don’t walk faster, you’ll be shamed right here.
Your face says you’re in ecstasy.
I’m not in the slightest...
Wait!
Wait... stop it...
What are you... hey...
Mitsu, what’s going on?
Why did you take so long to call?
Nana-san... no...
Stop it... Turn off the phone...
Turn it off!
I can’t... have this...!
Hey, Mitsu? What’s wrong?
Nana-san...
What’s happened?
She looks so lazy.
It appears you’re not strict enough with her... Nanase Saki.
Who are you?
Don’t worry, you’ll meet me soon.
What do you want?
Mitsu, are you okay? Answer me!
I came...
While Nana-san was listening, I was fucked by men I don’t even know.
Mitsu... Mitsu?
Oh no... no...
No... I’m cumming... no... I can’t... cum...
Mitsu? Mitsu!
Stop... I don’t want... to cum...
Mitsu! Mitsu!
Sorry, but Kuroha Mitsu’s virginity and her heart belong to me now.
Mitsu? Mitsu! Please, answer me!
I want to see your defeated face soon, too.
I’m looking forward to it, Nana.
Oh... yes!
Does it feel good, Mitsu?
Yes! It feels good!
Do you want more?
Mitsu, be strong! Don’t give up!
Yes!
No... I keep cumming over and over.
Please... more, more, fuck me harder!
Very well, I’ll do it.
While you show me your pitiful face, you’ll swear eternal loyalty to me.
Kuroha Mitsu
Surrender Complete