The story so far
Your face says you're in ecstasy.
I'm not in the slightest...
Wait!
Wait... Stop it...
What are you... Hey...
Mitsu, what's going on?
Why did you take so long to call?
Nana-san... No...
Stop it... Turn off the phone!
Turn it off!
I don't... want this at all!
Hey, Mitsu? What's wrong?
What happened?
Quite a slutty face she's making here...
Your girls are not very well disciplined, are they?
Nanase Saki.
Who are you?
Don't worry, you'll meet me soon.
What do you want?
Mitsu, are you okay? Answer me!
Mitsu?
Sorry, but Kuroha Mitsu's virginity
and heart belong to me now.
Mitsu? Mitsu! Please, answer me!
Soon, I want to see your defeated face too.
I'm looking forward to it, Nana.
Does it feel good, Mitsu?
Yes! It feels good!
Do you want more?
Mitsu, be strong! Don't lose!
Please! More, more!
Fuck me harder!
Very well, I'll make you cum.
While you show me your pitiful face when you
orgasm, you'll swear eternal loyalty to me.
Stop it, I'm begging you...
Forgive me!
Help me, Saki-san! Save me!
Why am I feeling it so easily now?
My mind's going blank...
It feels like I'm going to faint any minute!
It's too late for me...
So my power's effectiveness has lessened, huh?
No choice, then.
Now you're going to suck it.
Yes...
Yes, just like that. You're no longer
that woman's subordinate.
You're my slave.
Yes.
Nanase Saki's Detective Agency's Crimson
Girls' member, Kuroha Mitsu.
This girl is completely under my control...
Sperm...
Next, I'll have a stronger, prouder woman
who will struggle when I bring her down...
Crimson Girls
Dominated by Molesters
This man is a molester!
Eh?!
Wait, what?!
N-no, you're wrong, I-I-I, I'm not a...
A molester?
Just a minute, you!
W-wait! I didn't do...
Really!
Playing dumb about it, you really are the worst!
Hurry up and throw him out!
I-It's a misunderstanding!
It was probably just your bag!
She doesn't even have a bag!
Part Two Nozomi submission Chapter 1
We did it again!
When you have all that stress built up, framing someone
as a molester makes everything better, doesn't it?
We were so right to aim for old, rich looking guys, huh?
We got paid so much not to keep spreading it!
Even the old guys who act high and mighty. Once you say "I'm gonna
spread your name on the internet", they pay up right away!
Being forced to pay us when they didn't even do anything
kinda makes you feel sorry for them, doesn't it?
How about letting them actually touch you a little?
No way! They're molesters, isn't that gross?
Being touched by a molester. There's absolutely no way...
Hey, you there.
Have you seen this girl around here?
Don't know her.
Me neither.
You know her, Nozomi?
No, I don't know her, but...
You remember seeing her?
N-Not really.
I see.
If you remember something, contact me here.
Nanase Saki?
Detective?
I've framed countless people as molesters
to blow off stress, but...
Since I'd never actually been touched by one,
that was my first time seeing it happen.
That woman, right inside the train, it was so...
If it were me who was surrounded like that on the train...
Eh?
What?!
It can't be! Is this... a molester?!
Then... This can't be! It's really happening? To me?!
A real molester is being so...
U-Um...
No way! No, not there!
This is...
There are two of them?!
No! Everyone around me is!
This can't be! I'm surrounded?!
A molester should be handled like how I usually do.
All I have to do is just call them out on it!
Just grab the man's hand, let out a good, loud
scream, and it'll all be over for them!
These guys are real molesters, actual bad people after all!
I won't let you today.
You always mess around on this train, framing
innocent men as molesters, don't you?
Why does he know that about me?!
Did you enjoy leading men around
by the nose, terrorizing them?
You're a pretty interesting girl.
I love subjugating cheeky broads just like you.
What is this guy saying?
This is...
No!
Why?! I can't resist!
I should be able to just bring this to an
end ike I normally do with molesters!
I can't do anything!
No! If this keeps up, I'll end up like
that woman from yesterday!
My body feels hot... Is this what it's like
to be touched by an actual molester?
There's no way I'm getting off by being molested like this...
Because they're the enemy of all women!
Pretty soaking wet, aren't you?
No! No! I can't stand it!
No way... Just now...
I...? They made me cum?
In the name of all the pitiful men you've framed
and humiliated as perverts up until now,
we're going to be delivering divine justice.
We?
No! They're going to keep going?
How long do they plan to keep this up?
Please! Hurry and end this!
What's wrong? Your body's been trembling for a while
now. You just came, are you about to cum again?
Stop it...
Or else!
Here, I'll humiliate you even more, right here in this train.
No! Even though they're forcibly doing
this to me, in this situation...
Getting off on a train while being molested
by perverts, and with people watching!?
I'm not that much of a pervert!
How do you like the hands of the
molesters you hate so much?
Feels good, doesn't it?
You're wrong! You're wrong! It doesn't feel good at all!
No!
I'll cum! They're going to make me cum!
By these kinds of guys!
They're gone?
Who cares about that!
Station attendant! I was molested by!
Why are you guys here?!
Stop!
No!
What? No! No! You can't! What?
No! No! I don't want that!
Don't not that!
Not there!
I'll make it feel good soon.
No, no! Stop!
Stop!
What's coming inside my butt? This is!
No! My butt's dirty!
Of all places, I definitely can't let
myself feel it through there!
Don't squeeze so tightly.
What's wrong? You're starting to
have spasms inside, are you?
No...
My asshole... Such an embarrassing place... No!
How much more?
Isn't this enough already?
Is it... over?
No, no!
No...
Stop it... No!
There's a penis in my butt!
Even though I'm still a virgin!
To have my first time be in my asshole!
No... Why is it so good? In my ass, even...
How is it? Feels pretty good, doesn't it?
Just be honest.
Feeling it this easily from anal of all things...
It's just the kind of girl you are, isn't it?
W-Why? I'm not some kind of pervert
who likes it in the butt...
Stop it! Please don't do this to my butt!
Don't make such a dirty place an erogenous one!
No! Ah, no!
I don't want this, so why is it so...
It's started to feel good, hasn't it?
Can't even hear me anymore, huh?
No! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum from being fucked in the ass!
This is... This is really bad!
So it wasn't a dream after all...
translator: kuro-kun
translator check: hikarucon
timing: v1toush
typesetting: haidaraaaaa
editor: punk4real
She was a more interesting woman than I thought.
I'm begging you, I'm at my limit! Please give me your semen!
Let me cum! Shoot your hot seed inside me, please!
Sakura Nozomi... She's the perfect toy
for before I hunt Nanase Saki.
Next time, I'll make her fully submit.