Previously
Your face says you can't get enough of this.
It doesn't feel good at all!
Hey...
Wait a minute!
Stop! What are you going to do?
Mitsu? What's the matter?
You didn't call me, even though it's this late.
Nara-san! No! Don't!
Put down the phone this instant!
Ow!
This is the last thing I want!
Hey! Mitsu! What's the matter!? What happened!?
You look so pathetic.
Your woman hasn't been properly trained... Nanase Saki.
Who is this?
We'll meet soon enough, no need to rush.
What are you after?
Mitsu! Are you alright!? Answer me!
Mitsui? Mitsu!?
Hate to break it to you, but...
Kuroha Mitsu's heart and virginity are mine for the taking.
Mitsu!?
Mitsu, please! Answer me!
I want to hurry up and see your spent face already.
I'm looking forward to it, Nana.
Does it feel good, Mitsu?
Yes, it feels incredible!
Do you want some more?
Yes!
Mitsu, hang in there! Don't give in!
I beg of you! Harder! Please fuck me harder!
Alright! You should cum.
Don't you dare think about retaliation while
showing me your pathetic slutty face.
Please stop! I can't take it anymore!
Save me, Saki-san! Seve me!
When did I start getting turned on so easily?
My mind is going blank...
It feels like I'm going to pass out again.
I...
...can't take it anymore!
It seems my powers have started to wear off.
Guess it can't be helped...
Alright... suck it.
Okay.
Yeah, that'll do.
You're no longer that woman's subordinate.
You're my slave, you see.
Yes.
Nanase Saki's Private Eye Office...
...Crimson Girls's member, Kuroha Mitsu...
This woman has completely fallen under my control.
Yay, sperm!
The next one is much stronger...
I'm going after the tough-as-nails woman.
Crimson Girls
~Molester Domination~
This guy is a molester!
Why do you say that!? No, you've got it all wrong!
I-I-I...
Molester, you say!?
You sick son of a bitch!
W-Waita second...! I didn't do anything! Honest!
Trying to play innocent is the worst!
Let's get the authorities.
I-It's all a misunderstanding! My bag
must have hit up against you!
You don't even have a bag!
Chapter 2 NOZOMI delivered clothes
We pulled it off again!
Outing molesters sure is a great way to relieve stress, huh?
We hit the bullseye by picking that straight-laced
geezer who looked like he had money.
We sure made a killing in settlement money!
Even cocky geezers give in when we
threaten to spread it all over the net.
He got this much taken from him even
though he really didn't do it.
I feel bad for him.
Then why don't you let him cop a bit of a feel for real?
No way! Molesters are gross!
I definitely don't want to be groped by a molester.
Hey, you, come here for a second.
Have you seen this girl around here?
Hmm? I have no idea.
Me neither. Do you know her? Nozomi.
No, I don't know her, either.
Have you seen her before?
N-No, I haven't.
Alright then. Call me at that number
if you remember anything, please.
Nanase Saki... A detective...?
We've outed so many molesters in
the name of stress relief, but...
I've never actually been molested before.
That was my first time seeing it in person.
That woman... She was molested so much in the train.
If I was also cornered by a molester like that...
What the?!
Don't tell me... this is a molester?!
This can't be happening! Come on now! Me?!
Real molesters go this far?!
U-Umm...
Th-This can't be happening! Not there!
Stop! Don't do this!
There are two molesters?!
No, I'm surrounded by them!
No way! I'm surrounded!
I can just do the usual with this molester.
I should just call him out as a molester.
I can just grab the man's hand, yell
out, and these guys are done for!
These guys are real molesters. They're the real deal!
I won't let you do that today.
You always toy with innocent guys on this train by
making them out to be molesters, am I right?
Why does he know about me?!
Was playing with fire fun when you took advantage of guys?
You're a rather interesting woman.
I love putting cocky chicks like you in their place.
What is this guy talking about?
He can't be serious.
Why?! I can't resist him.
Molesters should be easily dealt with like usual, yet...
...I can't do anything.
This is no good. At this rate, I, too...
...will be molested like that person was yesterday!
Ah! My body is hot.
Is this how it feels to really get molested?
There's no way I could be getting turned on by being molested.
Molesters are the enemy of women everywhere!
You're rather wet, aren't you?
No! Oh no! I can't take it!
No way! I was... made to cum just now...
You've been put to shame for your
outing games up to this point.
In place of those poor guys...
We shall give you divine punishment.
We...?
No! This is still going to continue?
How long do they plan on keeping this up? Please!
Get it over with already!
What's the matter? Your body is twitching from before.
Are you going to cum again even though
you just got done doing it?
Stop... it. Or else...
Or what? I'm going to shame you some more inside this train.
This is bad Even under these circumstances... Even
though I'm being forced to do it...
I can't believe I'm getting aroused as this molester
touches me in front of other people...
I... I'm not that kind of pervert!
Well? How do the hands of an actual
molester feel? Pretty good, huh?
Nope! No way! No way this feels good in the slightest!
I'm going to cum. If he makes me cum...
...In a place like this...
He's gone! But that doesn't matter!
Mr. Station Attendant! I was touched by a molester...
Why...are you guys here?
Stop it...
No! What are you doing!? Don't! No way!
Wait! What are you doing!?
No!
No! Don't! Don't! No!
Don't touch me there!
I'll make you feel really good!
No! Don't!
No!
It's in...my ass.
This can't be! Don't! I've never had it up the ass!
There's no way I'm getting aroused in such a place!
Don't tighten up so much! What's the matter?
You got wet inside there all of a sudden.
No! Not my asshole! No!
This is embarrassing, so I don't like it!
How long are they going to keep this up?
Haven't I suffered enough already?
IS it... Over?
Huh?! No! No!
There's a cock... in my asshole!
I'm still a virgin, yet I'm getting it up the ass first.
No! Why does it feel so good... in my ass?
Well? Doesn't it feel great?
Be honest already!
To think that anal would turn you on so easily...
You sure you aren't a natural?
No way! I'm not a pervert who likes it up the ass...!
Ah! Stop! Don't cum in my ass!
Don't sully up my erogenous zone!
I don't want this, so why am I...?
It's starting to feel pretty good.
It seems she can't hear me anymore.
I can't take it! I'm going to cum! From my ass...
He's making me cum! In my pussy!
No!
That... wasn't a dream after all.
That woman was more interesting than expected.
Please! I'm at my limit! Give me your sperm!
Let me cum! Cum inside me, please!
Sakura Nozomi... You will make for the perfect
play-toy before I hunt down Nanase Saki.
Maybe I will fuck her six ways from
Sunday the next time I see her.