Arisugawa Academy
One! 2, 1, 2!
1 ! 2!
One, 2! 1, 2!
Hurry!
Custom Slave
Sayako's Chapter
Please, let me go home.
No!
Stop it! No!
Please, stop it!
Stop it! Stop it, please.
Please let me go home.
Stop it! Please stop it.
Does it feel good, Mistress Sayoko?
Your training has just begun.
From here on, I will slowly unmask
your true identity.
No, please stop this!
Your true character, a horny slut
who loves to be fucked by men.
I'm not horny, I'm not a horny slut!
Is that so?
It's hot. It's hot. Why?
Chairman Takahashi. Is there anything
I can help you with?
Saeko, good timing. Get the camera.
As you please, Chairman.
Chairman.
It has a nice ring to it.
The aphrodisiac you make
works wonders as usual.
It is an honor
to be praised by you, Chairman.
The former Chairman
was this young man's uncle.
Well, it is a recommendation from him.
Should we let him, Your Excellency?
Yes.
But understand that Arisugawa Academy
is owned solely by us.
In return for granting you power
as Chairman...
you must fulfill your obligation.
You are to train female students
to be sex slaves...
and present them to our organization.
I'm counting on you, young man.
Yes!
A network for the purpose of presenting
top officials with young sex slaves.
Just you watch, you senile old fools.
No! Don't film me!
What a delight it is to watch the girls
become slaves to their own sexual desires.
Their innocent bodies service me.
and start to moan with pleasure...
and then become my fame, my fortune!
Was that, a dream?
I wish it really was, a dream.
You're not going to turn
at that intersection?
Yes, Mistress Sayoko.
When I came by, it was very crowded.
Is that so?
It may be a bit roundabout.
Don't worry. It's good to do different things
once in a while.
She's....
Isn't she from my school?
Now, wake up.
What are you doing?
Stop it! Not there.
No!
It's wet.
No, it's so hot.
It feels good.
I'm sick, or could it be.
I will unmask your true identity.
Your true character.
My true character?
It's what you really desire
deep down in your heart.
I don't know what I want!
You don't?
I can see it.
That desire hiding deep within you.
All too clearly.
You, Mistress Sayoko, a horny slut
moaning in ecstasy being fucked by men.
No, I'm not horny, I'm not a horny slut!
It was like yesterday to me.
My, my.
You look like you're having fun,
Mr. Politician.
Yeah, next week's Sayoko's birthday.
So I thought, maybe after dinner
I could show everyone a slide show.
If you do that, she'll be embarrassed.
Yeah?
She invited a lot of her friends.
Why don't you not go overboard for once.
Yeah.
What a nostalgic picture.
It's hard to choose just a few.
My.
That girl, she is still a little child.
By the way, is she already asleep?
Yes, already.
Was there something at school today?
She seemed really tired.
Someone may pass by here,
and yet I'm doing this lewd.
Use your mouth more.
If you don't make me come,
I'll walk you through school like this.
I'm sucking on a teacher's hard penis.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
That feels good, Sayoko!
It's getting bigger again.
I'm coming. Drink it all up.
Good job, Sayoko.
Good job the other day, Yui.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thanks to you I was able to get my hands
on Sayoko's body.
Today's training is your reward for that.
Thank you very much.
Saeko told me that in order to bribe
that driver, she used your body.
Your body was
a hundred times better, Master.
You really turned out to be
a wonderful slave.
Goodbye!
Master, please watch me as I climax.
About Yui Suzuha, who was presented
at the organization's party the other day...
currently it seems that her popularity
is doing very well with the guests.
Well of course. I personally trained her
as a sex slave.
You sound like a father boasting
about his daughter.
"Training cannot be realized without love,"
is my cherished opinion.
However...
with my way of loving....
Hello?
If it isn't Mikkazuki.
How's your mother doing?
I see, that's good to know.
Student Council meeting on the weekend?
Still, you're pretty into it. Are you planning
to become a female politician?
You should say that
to the birthday girl herself.
Hey Sayoko!
Yes! What is it, Father?
This call's for you.
Thank you, Father!
Hello, Mikkazuki!
I see. You can't come yet.
Really? Promise me,
make sure you come! Bye-bye!
Sayoko, look this way.
Come on, Father.
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much!
Congratulations, Sayoko!
Congratulations, Mistress Sayoko!
Everyone, thank you very much!
A daughter of an upper-class family
or a horny sex slave.
Which is the true you?
What's wrong, still won't come out?
Stop.
If you don't hurry,
the students below will notice you.
No! Why do I have to go through....
I'm scared because I feel
like I'm going to become, another person.
Don't worry,
that's a sign that your body...
is awakening to your true identity
as a masochist.
No, but...
You're not really a rich daughter.
You were born a masochist slave.
No, that can't be.
You should be true to yourself.
You don't think I don't know
that your body heats up...
the more humiliating the situation is?
No!
I can't hold it!
Now!
Sorry, Sayoko, for calling you
to the Council room so sudden.
No.
This is out of the blue...
but have you heard the rumor
that our students...
are being forced into prostitution?
I never heard that.
It's just a rumor, right now.
But you're a beauty, so you shouldn't be
so careless and watch out.
This is a warning from a friend.
Well, you should be okay...
with your father being a politician and all.
My, looking at pictures
of Sayoko's birthday party again?
It's okay, isn't it?
Take a look at this.
She turned out so cute and beautiful.
Really, she turned out so well.
Sayoko, you are my treasure.
My, you always go overboard with her.
It's getting late.
It's already this time?
I guess I'll go to sleep.
It will be such an ordeal
when Sayoko gets married.
I won't! I'm not letting her get married!
What a difficult father.
Come on!
I can't.
You were born a horny slut, right?
Sayoko.
You were born to be trained by me
and become a sex slave, right?
Yes.
How's that? Feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Where does it feel good?
My ass.
Your big hard cock
is rubbing back and forth inside.
You shameless whore. No one would think
you're a well-behaved rich girl.
What are you to me?
I'm your slave, Master.
That's right, a horny sex slave.
Yes, I am a horny sex slave
that gets off on anal sex.
Well said. I'll give you a reward.
Thank you very much.
Yes! Yes!
Your cock is going in and out.
I'm....
You ready?
You can come now.
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Sayoko!
I raised you to be the horniest slut.
Yes. I am your horny slut, Master.
Please treat me with love again.
To the birth of my cute sex slave,
who pledges loyalty only to me.