Enjoying the day, are we Saionji?
You sure idling off like that is a good idea?
He's slacking off again.
Disgraceful. He is an embarrassment
to the employees of this company.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ah, thank you. Good work to you as well, Sakuragi-san.
Did you just return from field work?
Ah, yes. I'm so tired that I don't have any energy left.
Oh, that can't be. You are still in your prime.
Sakuragi-san is so kind.
She treats me nicely and to top
it off she is extremely beautiful.
She truly is a rare woman, especially
in this day and age.
Hey, Saionji! What are you doing?!
Oh, Manager! Good day.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hi, Ayana.
You sure are a pro at changing gears, aren't you?
Hey, Reiko-sensei is looking for you!
Now get going!
Huh? Do you mean the head
of the research department?
What does she want with me?
Shut up!
It's best to keep that kind of useless chatter
to a minimum and get going already!
Okay, okay.
Saionji-san, see you later.
But really, what is this all about?
New Drug Experiment! Office Ladies Drugged in Aphrodisiac
The Lady Superior(s) Get Taken!
Excuse me.
Doctor, is there something I can do for you?
Let me stop you right there.
Err?
I dislike formality. Just call me Reiko.
Huh?
It's Re-i-ko.
R-Reiko-san...
Good.
The reason why I called you here is that,
I want you to try out our new product.
New product?
Yes, an aphrodisiac.
Oh, I see. An aphrodisiac...
An aphrodisiac?!
Our new product is an aphrodisiac.
You have to spray it on your body.
H-Hey, wait a minute!
What?
Why did you give this to me?
I'm ashamed to say this, but I don't
have a girlfriend to try it on.
I know that.
Then, just try on the girl in our company instead.
Huh?!
If you use that drug,
no woman will be able to resist you.
If something goes wrong, I will take responsibility
since you're under my care.
Even you have a girl or two that you like, don't you?
That ends our discussion. Do you have any question?
No, I don't.
If so, I'll leave it to you.
Th-Then I'll betaking my leave.
An aphrodisiac huh? Is this thing really effective?
Oh, welcome back.
So you're the only one left now?
Yes, everyone already finished their tasks.
You're the only one who isn't finished yet, old man.
Foul-mouthed as always.
Oh, right. Maybe I should try this on her?
Seriously, old man. What are you doing?
Oh nothing. Just taking care of your shoulder stiffness
since you have been sitting like that for a while now.
Stop it! It's disgusting!
Hmm? What's wrong, Kawasaki?
Get out of my way!
What the hell is happening to me?!
I didn't feel like this at all until now.
But the moment that old man
touched me, I suddenly...
Getting aroused because of that guy... It can't be!
What was that?
Wait, what do you think you're doing?!
Don't try to escape. You're already this wet.
That's a nice reaction!
N-No... Don't touch me!
What a cheeky girl.
Hey, wait!
Don't!
I can't believe this. I am so horny.
Alright then...
Old man, you want to do me, right?
At last. Finally being honest, are we?
Because I like feeling good.
Oh look, ready and able at your end already, huh?
You sure are well endowed for
an old man such as yourself.
Delicious...
Amazing, Kawasaki!
Isn't it...!
But, you can't cum yet.
Don't ask for the impossible...!
Pathetic... But you can still go on, right?
If we stop now, it would be such a waste.
That's the spirit!
Hurry up and come here already...
You are such a slut.
It's so good!
Wow, did you climax right off the bat?
This is so weird...
Why the heck is sex with this old man,
an out of the world experience?!
Enslaving this cheeky girl with my
cock and reducing her to this...
This aphrodisiac is the real deal, no doubt about
it. ill have more fun with it later on.
No,- I'll cum! I'm going to cum!
Good, so good...
This feeling is amazing Please
continue pleasuring me.
Terrific! Absolutely terrific!
I'll cum inside, okay?
Yes, cum! Don't hold back. Cum inside me!
Here it comes!
Amazing. I might end up getting addicted to this...
Next, let me take the lead.
H-Hey!
I'm not satisfied yet.
Old man, you can keep going, right?
After all you have an outstandingly youthful
vigor down there for someone of your age.
W-Well yeah...
Just as I thought, this is great!
So? It feels good, right?
It feels good alright, but if this continues
I'll loose control of this situation...
Oh no! Don't suddenly start pumping as well!
To be driven wild by this old man...
Wow, that's a nice view from down here Kawasaki!
Geez, you pervert...
But I...
...again... I'm going to cum again!
Please! Cum inside me!
Release your semen inside me!
Yes! More, more! Pump harder!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I am cumming!
This is the best...
This drug is really something!
To be able to make a woman this horny...
I'd better say thanks to the doctor.
Excuse me!
Reiko-san, this is absolutely an amazing stuff!
This aphrodisiac is truly effective!
So the drug worked well for you, did it?
Reiko-san, what's wrong?
Ah, nothing.
Good job. You've proven the drug's effectiveness.
Then, what should I do?
Oh, right.
want you to continue monitoring the
effects of the drug for anything new.
But, it will take time to verify
the research data in detail,
so I need you to keep the details
of this project under wraps.
O-Okay...
Alright then, I'll give you a call
once I have any new updates.
Ah, okay. Excuse me.
There's still some drug left.
Reiko-san doesn't need to know,
about me indulging in some more fun on the side.
Here she comes!
If I use this drug the, lovely Sakuragi-san will be mine.
Sakuragi-san.
I apologize for calling you up here out of the blue.
Saionji-san...
So how can I help you?
Umm, actually it's about our Manager.
It's like he's never satisfied with my work.
Oh, about that... It's probably because
his job is quite stressful.
So I thought that maybe you could give me
some pointers to improve this situation...
Ah well, let's see...
Umm...
Sakuragi-san, is something wrong?
I-I'm sorry, I...
Are you okay...?
P-Please stop!
Wh-Where do you think you are touching...?
Sakuragi-san, could it be that you are getting horny?
What's gotten into me?
Don't...
Please, let me go.
Are you sure about that?
Please stop this...!
Even though you say that,
you're already this wet.
Wh-What was that right now...?
To climax in a place like this...
Sakuragi-san, you are more perverted than I thought.
No, y-you're wrong.
I did not cum...
Please stop!
I'm going to lose control!
Saionji-san...
I... I...
What's wrong? Do you want me to stop?
No, please don't stop.
Embrace me.
Now then. Without further adieu,
I'll be sliding my cock inside you.
It hurts!
Sakuragi-san you were a virgin?!
Yes...
Then it seems that Manager hadn't
got his claws on her yet...
I'm sorry, Masao-san.
I gave my virginity to another person.
Sakuragi-san, even though it's your first time,
you're already enjoying this intensely!
I... I can't stop myself...
To have sex in a place like this...
Even though this is my first time, I am on
cloud nine! This feeling is amazing...!
More! Thrust deeper into me!
The combination bf pain and pleasure
down there is exhilarating!
Okay, then.
I... I'm going to cum!
To make Sakuragi-san fall for me like this...
No, stop! Doing that will amplify
the pleasure uncontrollably...
I'll go crazy!
Sakuragi-san, at this rate, I'll be cumming inside you!
No, don't cum inside!
But I can't do that if your legs trap me like this.
No... Stop! I'll become pregnant!
Please, stop!
Even-though you don't want me to, it's already
gone beyond my control now. Take this!
No...!
No! Stop! Stop!
It's coming out...
It's so hot inside and your penis is still twitching...
I'll make sure she falls irreversibly
deeper into the world of lust.
Sakuragi-san, let's continue riding
this roller coaster of pleasure.
Here we go!
Sakuragi-san, you look amazing in that position!
Good! So good! My pussy is loving it!
Here! My cock is aggressively ramming your womb!
My womb is being violated...
I'll cum!
I am about to let it out!
Yes! Cum inside! fill womb with lots of cum!
Wow, tis feeling is amazing.
So good!
So Sakuragi-san has finally transitioned
into a full blown slut, huh?
With this, Sakuragi san is mine.
Even that Manager won the able
to do anything at this rate.
To Massao-san, I finished my work already so I'll waiting for you in the office. It will be great if we can go home together.
Sent it...
Good, good.
When Manager comes back, he will end
up seeing you like this, won't he?
Oh no!
Well if someone else walks in, then they might end
up spreading rumors about you being a horny slut.
No, please don't do that to me!
But it's true, isn't it? Otherwise, you wouldn't be
having sex with another guy now, would you?
P-Please don't say that...
Then, should I stop?
No, please don't stop!
It seems you're smitten with my cock, huh?
Please, do it more aggressively. Do it harder!
Alright then, Sakuragi-san. Which one do
you like better, me or the Manager?
Ehh!?
If you still love the Manager,
then I'll stop this right now.
It's you! I love you more, Saionji-san!
Good! It feels so good!
I'm cumming!
I'm climaxing on Masao-san's desk while
being fucked by Saionji-san's cock!
Sakuragi-san, I'll cum once more inside you!
Yes, release it inside of me!
To be filled with semen...
In a place like this...
Cumming inside me...
I'm cumming!
I'm sorry for making you wait, Ayana!
Oh, Manager. Good work!
Hey, why the hell are you here? Where's Ayana?!
You mean Sakuragi-san?
Sakuragi-san went home earlier.
What? Hey, you didn't do anything
bad to her, did you?!
Of course not. Are you sure she said
she was gonna wait for you?
That can't be... Ayana...
Dammit! Like I'll ever believe what you tell me!
Thank you for your hard work!