You're examinee number 39, Shiraiyuki Yoko, right?
Principal's office
Yes.
Sorry to call you all this way out of the blue.
So what do you need from me?
I don't understand why I'm the
only one getting an interview...
Now now, calm down.
How about you take a look at this first.
Th-That's...
Yes, these are all pictures of you and other girls
conducting in a very inappropriate manner.
Does this jog your memory at all?
U-Uh, I can explain...
You're an excellent student.
However, with this, we'll have to rethink
giving you a recommendation.
P-Please, there must be something we can do about this.
I've already passed this information
onto the other teachers though.
Please! I'll do anything!
Oh, really? Anything?
Are you being serious?
Y-Yes!
Whether it's cleaning, throwing out the trash...
And this was the start of my underground
school admissions test.
Second Underground School Admission Exam
Boy, school girls really are the best.
You're so cute, Yoko-chan!
Those clothes you're wearing would
get aroused even if I didn't want to.
How shameless!
Their gazes feel like daggers.
It feels gross.
But I can't defy them.
I love being able to just barely see through her clothes.
No! Don't look!
Okay now, I'm gonna shoot my stuff all over you.
No, don't do that. You'll see everything!
Stop!
Using these things are really great
for moving things around.
Next I'll thoroughly inspect your body, Yoko-kun. Okay?
Okay.
Men's hands are so rough and they
have such lewd movements.
Oh no, my nipples are getting hard!
I can't believe that getting touched
my a man could be this...
Yoko-chan? I'm gonna make you all clean.
No, don't lick me down there!
Young girls really do give off the best smells.
Let's have a taste.
You taste like a girl here too!
I'm being licked all over and he's even tasting my foot.
I'm being eaten by these guys!
This is so embarrassing!
N-No, not there!
Something the matter, Yoko-kun?
My pussy's being spread wide.
But why... why is he only touching the outside of it?
No, if he keeps teasing me there, I'm gonna...
What's this? You're spreading your legs on your own?
You really are quite the naughty girl.
N-No, I'm not! My body just did it on its own!
I guess I don't have a choice.
No! Not there!
Not my butt!
Hm? Then where would you prefer it?
Everyone, please look here.
She's moving her own hips so that
she can enjoy this with her ass!
No! I don't like if there, but...
My butt's...
Well then, let's play with these too.
No! Not my nipples!
No!
They're filming me.
All these men are seeing me in
this really embarrassing state.
Come on, you want this in you now, don't you?
No! Stop!
If you touch me there, right now, I'm gonna...
No, stop!
You're not very convincing when
you're swinging you own hips.
The vibrator is...
They keep vibrating against my butt
and n-nipples. It feels so good!
There's nothing more delectable than seeing a school
girl swinging her hips to masturbate in real life!
Th-This is so embarrassing, but
if feels so good, I can't help it!
You're just about at your limit, aren't you?
Come on now, cum in front of everyone.
No, please! Don't look!
Don't! Don't look!
No! Stop that!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
Now you want the real thing, don't you?
O-Oh no...
Your face doesn't look too happy,
but you're moving like you are.
Did being touched by men turn you on?
Th-There's no way.
I'm being forced to do this.
This is exactly what I expected from a beautiful
honor student. You're a real fast learner.
Why... men are dirty and creepy. I
definitely shouldn't like this, but...
When I'm sucking his dick, my body gets so hot.
Maybe I should give you a reward?
He's making it vibrate harder?
My clitoris feels so good!
Come on, you can't just stop.
Sorry.
Before, I never thought I'd ever
suck a man's dick to feel good.
But now I'm getting so turned on by this despicable act.
Your hole down here is twitching
as if it wants some fun too.
No, stop!
Come on! Come on! This feels good, doesn't it?!
Stop!
If you keep doing that at the same
time as my pussy, I'm gonna...
It's so embarrassing, but I can't hold my voice back.
It feels so good.
The way it's twisting around inside me...
That's some good technique you got there!
I'm about to cum soon too.
My head's going blank. I can't even think of anything.
Oh god, this is it. I'm gonna lose my mind.
I'm gonna cum too! I'm gonna cum again!
You really came hard there, huh?
How about you play with me now?
Y-You're kidding... More? This isn't over yet?
So, next we're gonna... hold you up like this.
No! My pussy's being stuffed with a vibrator.
Alright, Yoko-kun, I'm going to take your ass' first time.
N-No! Something that big won't fit into my butt!
S-Stop! Don't! No!
That's good! You're really squeezing me tight.
Wh-What should I do?
I've cummed so many times that my body's so loose now.
I'll give you the remote control for the vibrator.
Huh?
When you feel like you can't wait any
longer, you can use it as you wish.
Wh-What's he saying?
The principal lightly rubbed against my nipples
while thrusting his dick inside me.
My body being incredibly sensitive
after cumming so many times,
instantly felt pleasure and it began
to melt all my thoughts away.
It felt like I was about to cum but couldn't or more
like I was just constantly in a state of cumming.
It made me lose my mind.
I started sweating out of every pore of my body and let out
moans and voices I've never even heard myself make before.
I did't even care about the stream
of drool from my mouth.
I just forgot everything and was so taken
over by the pleasure and arousal.
I can't! I can't hold on any longer!
And from then on, second turned to
minutes, minutes turned to hours,
and within the space of pleasure and arousal,
I became immersed in my perverted five senses, peed
myself, and kept begging for even lewder things.
No! No! This is bad!
This is making my pussy feel really weird!
I'm starting to want more!
We're all ready to go here.
Please! I want it!
I want a dick!
Please! Please, I beg you!
Mess my dirty pussy up with your dicks!
Fuck me hard!
After all that teasing with the vibrator, my pussy
came immediately after his dick came inside.
A young girl's raw pussy really is the best.
Your pussy just keeps sucking me in!
What's going on? This is my first time, but it feels so good.
My pussy's twitching so much. It's so happy now!
More! More!
The way you moan like a slut is very arousing.
What? Do dicks really feel that good?
Yes! So good!
They're so good! The dicks in my butt and pussy are...
They're filling up my body so much!
Their dicks continued rubbing against
me over and over again,
making a wave of pleasure wash over
me, washing away all reason.
I was so happy being connected with their big dirty
things that I couldn't hold back my moans.
I'm about to cum.
It'll be your first creampie!
N-No, not inside...
Your dick's moving faster and it's starting to twitch!
It's coming! It's coming!
What's going on? It felt too good
and now my mind's going blank!
Everyone, please look. The honor student, Yoko-kun is
opening her legs, welcoming anyone to come inside her.
We're not even close to being done yet.
And after that I had lots of sex with
the teachers until the morning.
Oh my god. Your dick's going so
deep! It's touching my womb!
My dick's big and it feels good, doesn't it?!
I never knew that being held by
a man, being fucked by a man,
having sex could feel this good and make me so happy.
Oh, Yoko-kun, you're really into this, huh?
More! More! Thrust it harder into me!
Sex! Sex! I love sex!
This is so dirty. Having sex with a dick
is so good, I feel like I'm gonna melt!
Good, good. Keep it up.
Your expression right now is great.
What's wrong with me? I'm going to get addicted to this.
I can't live without dicks anymore!
Please! Fuck me harder! I love it when my pussy gets fucked!
I love it! I love it!
Watching you look all lewd like that made
my dick come right back up, Yoko-chan.
These dicks are so hard. They're
all getting turned on from me.
That makes me so happy.
Even though I'm doing something so nasty,
my body just keeps getting hotter.
I'll never be the same again!
No...
Come on! Come on! Squeeze your asshole more!
O-Okay. I'll squeeze both my pussy and butthole.
I'll do anything you tell me to, so please... give me more!
Fuck me harder!
Okay, I'm gonna shoot my load in you again!
Rough... So rough!
Cum! Cum a lot!
I want all of your cum inside me!
I don't have to go back to how I was.
Principal's office
Okay, Yoko-chan.
How about you face the camera and say hello as usual?
Okay!
I used to be a man-hating honor, student but
thanks to the training of my teachers,
I've become a convenient cum dumpster for everyone!
OK to fuck
Cum dumpster
Look closely at my pussy.
My dirty pussy loves dicks a lot, so
fuck it, a lot tonight too, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: bakaproxy
softsub: торрент иваниваныч