Examinee no. 39,
Shirayuri Youko, correct?
Yes.
Sorry for calling you on such a short notice.
Umm... what's going on?
I'm the only one who ever interviewed here.
Anyway, try and calm down.
You need to see these.
Those are!
Indeed. Those pictures show all of your indecent
activities with other female students.
Surely you remember these?
Umm, these are.
You're an outstanding student.
However, such acts shall not be tolerated, especially
for someone who just enrolled here.
This can't be. Isn't there something you can do?
This matter has already been forwarded to the other teachers.
Please, I'm willing to do anything!
Oh? Is that so?
Are you certain?
I am! Whether it's cleaning, or garbage disposal.
And thus, began my "other" enrollment to this school.
Students really are nice.
гы-гы...
Youko-san's such a cutie.
I'll definitely get an erection after watching these bombshells.
So sexy.
Their stares are boring into me.
So gross.
But I can't say no.
The way you see it through is very nice.
No, don't look.
Here, I'm gonna squirt a lot more.
No, please, not there... it'll get exposed!
It almost seems like I'm teasing you if I use this.
Now then, why don't I check this body out for myself?
Got it?
Yes.
A man's bulky hands... they're lewdly fondling me.
No, my nipples are getting stiff.
So being touched by man is this.
Don't worry, Youko-chan, I'll clean you right up.
No way. Don't lick me there.
Young girls really do smell very nice.
Lemme taste.
It tastes like a girl here as well.
They're licking me everywhere, checking
my every taste and scent.
I'm being eaten alive by a man.
It feels so embarrassing.
No, not there.
What's wrong, Youko-kun?
My pussy's being pried wide open.
But.
But why are they only touching the outside?
No, if they continue teasing me like this I'll.
My oh my, spreading your legs on your own,
such a slutty girl.
Th-That's not true. My... body did this on its own!
Looks like I'll have to proceed, then.
Wait, not there!
Not in my ass!
Oh? Then where would you like me to put it, then?
Everyone, look.
She's so aroused, that she started moving her hips by herself.
No, it's not my ass!
I don't like it, and yet, my ass feels good.
Why don't we do it here, too?
Not my nipples.
They're filming me.
I'm completely exposed in front of all of these men.
Here, you want this in here, too, right?
Stop, stop!
If you do that now, I'll... stop!
That's not really convincing, seeing
as how you're shaking your ass.
It's vibrating.
My ass, pussy and nipples are all being vibrated.
I-It feels heavenly.
I can't get enough of this vibrator-masturbating
high school bitch.
I-It's so embarrassing already,
but it feels so good that I can't help it.
You're at your limit, right?
Just cum in front of everyone.
No! Please, don't look!
Don't look. Don't look, please!
No, stop!
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum!
You're probably craving for the real thing now, right?
Th-This can't be.
Wow, your face might be saying no,
but you seem to be raring to go.
You got horny after being fondled by men, eh.
That... can't be.
I'm just forced to do this.
As expected of our gorgeous top student.
She's a quick learner.
Why?
Men are just stinky and gross.
I shouldn't even be getting into this and yet,
my body just gets hornier as I suck these dicks.
Why don't we give you a reward, then?
There's those vibrations again.
My clit feels good.
Hey now, you mustn't stop servicing me.
Okay.
I need to pleasure the men before they pleasure me.
The thought of doing something so wretched
wouldn't have crossed my mind before.
But right now, this thing is making me all horny.
Your hole is also twitching, begging for it like crazy.
Please, not that!
Come now, you like this, right?
Stop.
Not my pussy, too!
I-If you keep doing that.
I can't restrain myself longer.
It's so embarrassing, but I just can't help but moan.
Oh yes... it feels good.
It's rubbing hard.
I see you're becoming really wild.
I think I'm about to cum, too.
My mind's all blank.
I can't think of anything.
I'm at my limit now.
I'll go crazy at any moment.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum again!
You sure came hard.
I shall be your partner this time around.
No way.
We're... not done yet?
Now, we're going to do this next.
My pussy's taking it all in.
Youko-kun, you're about to lose your anal virginity to me.
You can't!
That thing won't fit in my ass!
S-Stop, stop!
Wait, stop!
That's good, it's wrapping around me quite nicely.
What should I do?
I've cummed so many times that my body just took it in.
I'll give you the vibrator switch.
Huh?
Just use it whenever you can't hold it any longer.
Wh-What's he saying?
The principal fondles just right at the base of my nipples.
He moves his dick while shaking me left and right.
My sensitive body feels a surge of pleasure as he does this,
and it's starting to fry my brain.
I'm on the brink of cumming, and yet I can't cum.
The imminent buzz of climax incessantly pesters me.
It's making me crazy.
My entire body's sweating.
I've never moaned like this in my entire life.
I'm so aroused, that my drool just keeps on pooling on the floor.
The pleasure has completely overtaken me.
I can't deal with this any longer.
I'can't hold it anymore!
After that,
I hadn't the foggiest idea,
how long I'd been cumming in this orgasmic hell.
I shamelessly started peeing with my legs wide open,
and simply continued pleading for more.
No, no.
This will no longer do.
If this continues, my pussy will crave for it till it goes crazy.
I want it more. I want it more!
We're all prepped and ready here.
Please, I really want it!
I want a dick.
I beg of you, I beg of you!
Please stir your dicks into my slutty pussy,
and... make a complete mess of me!
My pussy, which has been stimulated
continuously by that vibrator,
instantly came when a dick penetrated it.
Doing it raw with youngsters is amazing.
Her pussy just keeps on sucking me in.
What is this?
It's my first time, and yet,
I'm so aroused.
My pussy's gushing out love juices, unable to control itself!
More, more!
Squealing wildly like an animal,
it really turns me on!
Well? Do our dicks feel that good?
Yes, they're amazing.
It feels great.
Both dicks in my ass and pussy feel great!
Fill me up inside.
The dicks continued fucking me, rubbing
hard against my ass and pussy's insides.
They continued raping me with my
mind on the verge of total collapse.
These vulgar things elicited such ecstasy in me,
fueling my already perpetual moans.
I'm about to cum.
This is the first time a man cums inside of you.
No, not inside.
Your dick's twitching and pulsating so hard inside me!
It's coming!
It's coming. It's coming!
What's this? It feels so good that my
mind's gone completely gone.
Take a good look.
Our diligent top student, Youko-kun, is spreading
her legs open, inviting any man to come in.
We're just getting started.
Afterwards,
I had lots of sex with all of the teachers till dusk.
This is amazing. Your dick is going deep inside me.
It's hitting my very depths!
My dick's big and pleasurable, don't you agree?
I never knew
that getting fucked and raped by a man could
feel this pleasurable... and gratifying.
You're really getting into this, Youko-kun.
Please fuck me harder.
I love sex. I love sex!
It's so slutty.
Getting fucked feels so good that I'm about to melt.
Good. Keep that up.
Your expressions are really improving.
Now that I've learned about this, I'll
definitely become addicted to it.
I can't live without a dick anymore!
Please, I want you to violate me more!
My pussy just loves sex!
I love it. I love it.
Looking at how slutty you are, Youko-chan,
makes my dick get so hard.
Such stiff dicks.
Everyone's getting aroused with me.
I'm happy.
I'm doing such a vulgar thing, and yet
my body can't help but get horny.
There's no going back.
No.
Come on, squeeze me with your asshole more!
Okay.
I'll squeeze harder with both my pussy and ass.
I'll obey your every command.
So please, do it more.
Violate me more!
Alright, I'm gonna cum it all inside you again.
So intense.
But I'm happy.
Just cum. Cum it all!
Pump it all inside and impregnate me!
I don't want to return.
Now, Youko-chan,
direct your daily greetings to the camera.
'Kay.
I was the top student who despised men.
But after the principal and the other teachers trained me,
I've become a full-time cum dumpster for everyone!
Look at my pussy carefully.
This is my dick-loving perverted pussy.
Please rape me lots tonight.