Feels so good!
Your anger was directed
towards your sister, not me.
Sister, this feels so good!
I’m going to protect you,
no matter what happens.
Traitor!
Why am I here?
Helena, can you tell me why?
Theodora-sama!
Theodora-sama.
You were here all this time?
I was looking for you.
Enemies might be lurking around.
Please don't wander
around without thinking.
I’m sure there aren't
any enemies around here.
Besides, my life means
nothing to you people.
And you're worried about me?
I’m sure there are several high-ranking
officers that feel that way.
But for people like myself, commanders
like you who lead us to victory...
...are very important.
If we keep on winning, our chances
of returning home becomes greater.
So for people like you,
I’m a good commander.
Yes!
I've been keeping track of
our army these past 3 months.
But during that time, the toll of
dead and injured isn't even 10 percent.
I’m very fortunate to be alive.
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Elfen Laid Vol. 2
She's here...
What's wrong?
Don't just stand there. Come here.
You came to see your lovely sister.
Why don't you show some emotion?
What? You don't love
your sister anymore?
This is boring.
I was expecting you sisters to reunite in
tears, but what is this?
Hey, come on out.
Theodora-sama...
He was about to be executed for
insulting a high-ranking officer.
What is the meaning of this?
Is it because he was sympathetic
towards me? This is just too harsh!
I felt pity, and spared his life.
You liar!
Comfort him.
Didn't you hear me? I told you
to comfort this pitiful virgin.
Stop messing around!
Why would l do such a thing?
Theodora.
No, it's dirty.
You're not thinking of finishing
this with a handjob are you?
Do it just like your sister.
Take a good look at her... Helena.
She's doing this all for you.
You should be appreciative.
Get your hands off of Helena...
I’m sorry, Theodora-sama.
But my hips are moving on their own.
Just looking at you suck my
cock makes it unbelievably big.
It feels good, Theodora-sama.
My lovely Theodora.
Your love and anger towards your
sister, or anger and hatred towards me.
But more importantly,
anger towards yourself.
Is your heart about to burst
with all these emotions?
If so, then you're the
woman I’ve been looking for.
Rather than worrying about you,
Helena's too busy doing it with me.
At least, try to refrain yourself
from riding him like a horse, right?
Theodora will give up her
virginity to save her sister...
No, she'll even give
up her life to save her.
She's that kind of woman.
She's a noble-minded woman.
That's what l was attracted to.
I thought it was lovely.
That's why making her a
puppet in despair...
Just doesn't do it for me.
Your clan rebelled against my army.
But you're doing all this just
to save your pitiful sister.
They don't care about you. They're just
a bunch of little shits.
Leave early tomorrow
morning and eliminate them.
You go and finish
what's left of your clan.
Yes, that's it.
Giving up on acting like a
puppet... That's not like you.
You try to hold back, but you can't.
The look of anger on your face,
as if you want to tear me apart...
That's the real you!
What do you want?
How did you know it was me?
Your scent.
You lower class people smell horrible.
You didn't violate the older sister?
We've had enough of the younger
sister, and now we're bored.
Let's go and do the older sister.
She has the brow of a young
boy, now that's really nice...
It'll be interesting to see
how long she can stay tough.
Shut up.
We can do her while we
kill her younger sister...
Ear! My ear!
Didn't you hear what l said?
I told you to shut up!
Get out of here.
If you want to live that is...
Yes!
Hey, carry her out.
I said carry her out!
I can't believe he took my ear.
That bastard...
I can't stay here.
I’ll sell her to the slave dealer and...
What are you doing? You dimwit!
Where do you think you're
going with that woman?
I was thinking of taking
her out for a walk.
Hey! Come back here!
I’ll kill you!
I think this is it.
I have to live in disgrace anyway.
What did you do to Helena?
I’ll kill you!
I’ll definitely kill you!
I brought you here to
tell me what's going on.
Why are you all tense?
Under the existing circumstances,
it's impossible to eliminate them.
With my powers, l mean with our
current military strength, it's not easy.
I need 200 reinforcements,
plus an extension of one week.
Then we can do it...
Why are you doing all this?
Is it because of your sister?
What?
What are you trying to say?
I already know about your failed
mission from the messenger.
Now you have nothing to worry about.
You're free to go now.
What is the meaning of this?
I was interested in your ability
and your so-called sisterly love...
...but you couldn't even finish the job.
Let's just say l lost
interest in you people.
I’m asking what you did to my sister!
I think you already
know the answer to that.
I’ve had plenty of fun with your sister,
but I haven't played with you yet.
You should try to relax.
If you stay calm, the
pain will be gone quickly.
I want to get a good look at your face.
Kill me.
You killed my sister after you played
with her like a toy.
Kill me too.
I have nothing to protect.
Helena, my pride...
I have nothing left.
A map and invitation
to the rehabilitation facility.
Your sister's there.
What do you mean?
I thought you killed Helena.
At this time, the stable
should be unguarded.
Take any horse you like.
What is the meaning of this?
This is probably some trap or...
Go.
You're worried about your sister, right?
You treated Helena cruelly and now
you feel sorry and offer your sympathy?
It’s because l love you.