Stop!
Stop it! Please!
Just shut up and watch.
Your girlfriend's getting
banged by some strangers.
You don't get to see that every day.
I’m coming. Drink it up!
I’m gonna release it!
You went too fast.
Sorry. The sun's been
wearing me out these days.
Me too.
I’m coming.
Stop it! Anything but that!
I’m coming, I’m coming, I’m coming!
Hey, let me get some.
Release plenty of it inside her.
We have to purify these
savages with our seed.
You can never be too careful.
No more!
Please stop!
Let's continue.
Do as you're told, bitch!
She tried to bite me.
Stay away from her mouth!
No. No!
Stop!
This is great.
She reacts to pain and tightens up.
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Elfen Laid Vol. 1
One day, soldiers from the
kingdom came into our forest.
They wanted us to surrender.
They wanted to conquer us.
They wanted to trample over us.
They wanted to insult us.
We tried to defend ourselves.
But they were just too much for us.
They eventually overpowered us.
My friends were raped,
houses were burned down...
They took everything from us.
My father was the head of
the clan, but they killed him.
And my younger sister went missing.
She didn't know how to fight.
I had to protect her.
And then l also became their slave.
They're moving me by wagon
and keeping me alive.
I guess they have some use for me.
I couldn't save my clan or my sister.
For me to live in
disgrace from here on is...
Hey did you hear that rumor
about the clan leader's...
Yeah. They caught his
daughter who was hiding, right?
She has nowhere to go anyway,
she gave us a lot of trouble.
My sister...
Helena is alive?
Huh?
Yeah, that's right.
She was caught not too long ago.
She's probably being taken before
our supreme commander, Julianus-sama.
Is she alright? Is she injured?
I hope you bastards didn't rape her!
Be quiet! We don't know anything.
I mean, why do we have to help
transfer a beastly woman like you?
Plus we have to deliver
you without a scratch?
Give me a break!
Other soldiers are having
way more fun than we are.
Don't do anything stupid.
She's like the princess
of these savages.
They think she can be of some use.
They might punish us if we hurt her.
Helena, you're alive.
I’m glad.
I’m going to protect you this time.
I promise.
What is this feeling?
Commander.
Commander!
We brought the other
daughter of their clan leader.
You savage!
Bow!
It's okay. She's their princess.
But...
My name is Julianus.
I’m the supreme commander
responsible for the subjugation.
Princess of the savage clan...
Why do you think l captured
you without any harm?
You thought it was useful to
keep us as part of your rule.
You did such terrible things to our
people, they're not going to forgive you.
But you don't want any of us to
retaliate against your kingdom.
So you decided to capture the
daughters of the clan leader.
You're a very wise princess.
To put it bluntly, you're right.
Subjugation of the frontier
is only the beginning.
As we keep on ruling
other territories...
We don't want to make any enemies.
Do whatever you want.
I don't care what your intentions are.
In this situation, I have
neither rights nor choices.
But I have just one request.
What is it?
Sister, father, my people...
Helena!
Helena...
Sister...
I want you to guarantee
my sister, Helena's safety.
I heard she's being kept here.
Fine. She was just collateral anyway.
So what do you want from me?
As a sign of integration, l was
thinking you could be my wife.
Luckily, I’m single.
Be your wife?
But if you're willing to sacrifice
yourself to save your sister...
Let's see...
I heard that our army had some
trouble against your command.
I want you to serve
us as a skilled commander.
Me? As a skilled commander?
That's right.
There are many rebellious
clans in this region.
You're going to help me crush them.
The princess of a clan that has already
been suppressed will crush them...
It’s a good idea right?
Fine. I have to live in disgrace anyway.
The plan that you're using right now...
It didn't go very well.
No, it's just that...
Those savages were much
stronger than we thought.
Provide 3000 soldiers for Theodora, and
place them on the front line.
Have them leave tomorrow morning.
I’ll take full responsibility.
Yes!
Do you people object?
Then, I guess everything is settled.
There you have it.
Do a good job.
Don't forget. Your sister's
life is in your hands.
You should go talk to
your sister tonight.
It may be the last time
you'll see her alive.
Helena, I’m going to protect you...
No matter what happens.
Sister, please be safe.
Who's there?
What do you want? I’ll scream for help.
Nobody will help you.
Sister!
Anybody would be scared if
they woke up and saw his face.
But what you have to be scared of
is what we're about to do to you.
I’ll do you real good with this thing.
No! Please stop!
Stop it!
No, no! Please stop!
No!
Hey girlie.
If you're scared already, you might die
after he sticks his thing inside you.
Now, let's begin shall we?
No! Please stop!
Let me go! Please!
That feels good doesn't it?
Okay, start moving.
Ouch!
It hurts!
You gonna come?
You will huh?
Then release it inside her.
N-No!
Stop it!
No, don't go.
Was it painful?
This time, we're gonna
give you lots of pleasure.
Don't be frightened.
This is gonna help
you have fun.
This is gonna do the trick.
You started feeling
good already, didn't you?
The power of this medicine is
unbelievable.
Just wait for a bit, you'll
be getting more action.
Okay.
No!
Okay, I’m gonna get some too.
She's giving in completely.
I did it. I came back alive.
I came back for you Helena.
Helena... Helena...
Helena!
Where are you?
You...
What did you do to Helena?
Calm down.
This way.
I’ll kill you!
I’ll definitely kill you!
What are you gonna do after you kill me?
If you kill me, your sister will die.
Your anger was directed
towards your sister. Not me.
You can't forgive your
sister, who was violated.
So you want to kill me
and let your sister die?
That's what you want, right?
It’s my sister.
I have to tell you something.
You see...
My ass...
Feels so good.
I’m gonna cum!
I’m gonna cum from my ass!