Auntie, make your lips
narrower and stroke it better.
You're doing good. Next, lick the tip a lot
as you move your head back and forth.
That's way better than before.
I'm coming...
I'm coming, auntie!
Auntie, your face while you're doing blowjobs
looks so lewd!
It's syrupy and it feels great, auntie!
No... I can call you mama when
we're alone together, right?
No, I'm not your mother!
I'm Yutaka's...
Stop hitting me at the same spot!
I don't want this! I can't bear this!
Stop! Go a little slower!
This is so intense!
No! No!
Mother
Beloved Mother
The Transformation Of My Beloved Mother
Ahh...
I'm tired of playing this game already.
Hey, Yutaka.
What?
Just bear with it a little more.
I'm gonna find a more fun toy for you next time.
Really? What kind of toy?
I'm sure that you're gonna like it.
Yutaka, it's almost time for your cram school.
Ah... Okay...
Mom...
...Miyuki-san.
Masato-kun...
Thank you for always playing with Yutaka.
Oh no, thank you as well.
Oh yeah, Masato! Stay here for the night.
We don't have school tomorrow,
so let's play again when I get home.
I guess it can't be helped...
Sorry, I'll accept your hospitality.
D-Don't be...
Your... fingers!
You're so wet, mama.
That's not...
Hey, your hands are slacking on cooking.
What should I do? I became easily aroused now.
Masato-kun...
Let's stop doing this already...
Do you hate this, mama?
That's because you're a friend of Yutaka,
and I'm his mother!
If that's so, then you should
fight me back even more.
You should have fought back
when I first assaulted you.
If you keep touching me like that...
I'll end up craving for it!
More... I want you to touch me deeper!
I'm begging you, I'm itching for more!
Rub me inside too and make me come!
Hurry up, please!
No... Keep on doing that!
I'm coming!
Please...
I want it here inside!
I'm home!
That's too bad.
We'll continue this next time, mama.
What's wrong with me?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Lower your voice. You'll wake Yutaka up.
So this is how your pussy feels like
when you're not aroused, mama.
This makes me feel so horny!
Papa told me about it.
Women feel good no matter
how much they try to endure it.
They fall down deeper
no matter how much they resist.
How is it, mama? Does it feel good?
No... No...
Your face shows like you're craving for it.
Does having Yutaka beside
you make you aroused?
So deep!
Shake your hips, then!
Don't you want my semen?
Yes! Oh no...
So deep... I'm...
I'm gonna come...
It's so deep!
Mama, did you come?
I haven't yet!
But I'm feeling so good!
You're gradually getting more honest.
That's because your dick is rubbing me so much!
You have a lot more to learn about sex, mama.
That hurts!
Do you like spanking? You're so wet that
they're stretching out like strings.
You really are indecent, mama!
I can't take it anymore! I'm begging you!
This feels too much for me! I can't take it!
I'll stop if you'll let me come inside.
No! Anything but that...
You want it, right?
Mama, don't you want my semen?
I'm coming! I can come inside, right?
You can't! But...
I want it! I want it!
I want your semen!
No, I can't stop it...
I can't hold myself back anymore!
Come! Shoot your semen!
You're mine now.
You're my mama now.
After that, I fell so low and ended up
becoming Masato-kun's woman.
I drowned in pleasure
and lusted for Masato-kun like I'm a beast.
Miyuki-san, you look so different lately.
I-Is that so?
You look prettier now.
I can't think about anything else anymore.
I can't go against his orders!
This every day filled with obscenity and immorality...
I don't want to escape it!
Not so deep...
It's so thick!
Don't make me come with that device!
Hurry... Give me your dick!
Don't do that! Stop!
Make me come with your dick!
No, I'm coming...
I'm coming!
I'm coming, so stop!
No!
I'm coming! I'm coming again!
I can't stop coming!
I want to drive you crazy even more, mama.
Wow!
Mama, you're so lewd!
I'll put mine in the front while
the vibe is in your ass.
It's alright, mama.
Even if you stay still, your pussy is shuddering.
It's the best!
Wow! Your love juice won't stop flowing out
even when I'm abusing you this much!
I've been coming all along!
You can come any time you want!
My whole body is craving for semen!
I'm coming! Good, so good!
As long as I can have sex,
I don't care whatever happens!
Come already!
Use me more just like a toy!
Incredible!
Something amazing is coming!
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming already!
I'm coming!
Masato-kun... Can you at least untie me?
To think that there were times
that you're having sex with Masato
without me even knowing...
Huh, Yutaka?!
You've been keeping such a dirty secret from me!
Stop this, Yutaka! This is something that's...
That's what sex is, Yutaka.
Doesn't it feel good?
Yeah, your insides feel
so good, mom! Damn it!
You finally called me mom for the first time!
We'll both be having sex with mama from now on.
No way!
Hey! Just shut up a little, mama!
Yutaka, forgive me for keeping
this from you before.
I wanted to enjoy sex with both of you.
It's alright now, Masato.
I am so happy!
To be able to have sex with mom...
It's like a dream!
Mom, I'm already gonna come...
I'm gonna come inside you!
I'm gonna come in your mouth too!
Isn't it fine, mama?
From now on, I'm gonna rape you every day too.
You'll be able to have sex every day.
Isn't it the best, mama?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization