You're gonna need to suck harder if you want me to cum, Miss.
That's better. Now tease my tip with
your tongue while moving your head.
You've gotten so much better at this.
I'm cumming.
I'm gonna cum, Miss.
That face you make while sucking my dick...
It's so hot.
Your soaking wet pussy feels so good, Miss.
Actually, you said to call you "Mom"
when it's just the two of us, right?
That's right. I'm your mother.
I'm your...
You keep hitting my g-spot over and over again!
Please stop! It feels to good!
I can't...
Please, slow down!
This is too much!
No! No!
Mother
Mother Fucker
#1 My Dear Mother's Transformation
I'm tired of this game.
Hey, Yutaka?
What?
I'll find you something more fun to play with.
Really? Like what?
Something I'm sure you'd like.
Yutaka, you have cram school soon.
Oh, yeah.
Mo...
Miyuki.
Thank you for always coming over to play with my son.
You're a good friend, Masato.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Masato, why don't you spend the night?
We don't have school tomorrow.
We can play again when I get back.
Sounds good to me.
Sorry, I'll be in your care.
N-No problem.
Your fingers... They're...
This wet already, Mom?
Don't say that...
Hey, dinner's gonna burn if you don't pay attention.
This is bad... I get turned on way too easily now.
We shouldn't do this anymore, Masato.
Do you really mean that, Mom?
You're my son's friend! I'm his mother!
Then try fighting back.
You could have resisted me when I
first came onto you, but you didn't.
If you keep touching me like that...
I'm going to want it so bad!
More... I want you to go even deeper!
More... I want it deeper...
Rub my insides!
Make me cum!
Hurry! Please!
Oh my god!
Just like that!
Keep going!
I'm gonna cum!
Please...
I want it in here!
I'm back!
That's too bad.
Guess we'll have to pick this up another time, Mom.
What am I...
Wh-What are you...
Keep it down, or else Yutaka's gonna wake up!
So this is what your pussy feels like
when you're not wet and ready for it...
It really turns me on!
My old man told me that the more a woman resists
a guy, the harder they end up falling for them.
How is it? Does it feel good?
Your face tells me you want even more.
Getting turned on in front of your own son?
C'mon, move your hips, Mom.
Don't you want my cum?
N-No! I-I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum!
Did you cum, Mom?
Not yet!
But it feels really good!
At least you're being honest now.
When you pound me like that, I can't...
I want to see you drown deeper and deeper in pleasure.
That hurts!
Don't lie. Your cunt's twitching so much right now!
You're such a slut, Mom.
I can't take anymore! Please!
It feels too good! I can't take it!
I guess I can help you out,
but I'll have to cum inside you.
No! You can't!
You want it, don't you?
Don't you want my cum?
I'm cumming. I can do it inside, right?
No! I...
I want it! I want it!
I fucking want it!
I can't stop myself! I can't stop!
Give it to me! Give me your thick load!
And now, you're mine.
You're my Mom.
After that, I broke. I became Masato's woman.
He drowned me in pleasure, and I continued
to fuck him like an animal in heat.
You've been acting a little different lately, Miyuki.
You think so?
You've become really beautiful.
I can't think anymore.
I can't go against him.
I don't want these scandalous, lascivious days to stop!
I want them to last forever.
It's too deep...
So big!
Don't make me cum!
Just give me your dick already!
No! Stop!
Make me cum with your cock!
No, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Stop moving it!
No! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
I can't stop!
I want to see just how crazy you can get, Mom.
Wow, you're such a dirty slut.
I'll leave the vibrator in the back door while I take the front.
You're incredible, Mom.
Even though you're holding still,
your pussy is spasming like crazy.
It's the best!
Amazing. The love juices just keep flowing out!
Please cum! Cum whenever you want!
My entire body's craving your cum!
So good!
I don't care what happens as long as I can keep doing this!
Fuck me! Make me your toy!
So good!
I'm gonna cum so hard!
I'm cumming!
Shove it in me, Masato. Make me cum!
I can't believe you and Masato were doing this!
Yutaka?!
You were having all of this fun without me?
Stop! Yutaka, we can't...
This is sex, Yutaka.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah, it feels so good inside Mom!
That's the first time you've called me "Mom"...
Let's fuck Mom together from now on.
No!
Shut up, Mom!
Sorry, I kept this a secret from you, Yutaka.
I wanted all of us to be able to have sex together.
It's okay, Masato.
I'm so happy! I've always dreamed about fucking my mom!
Mom, I'm about to cum!
I-I'm gonina cum inside you!
It's okay if he blows his load inside you, right Mom?
I'll fuck you every day from now on too, okay?
How nice. You can have sex every day now, Mom.
translation: hikarucon
timing: ragingheartsexcelion
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editing: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч