There's a person I'm in love with.
Her name is Saori... My aunt.
I know it's wrong to have these feelings for her,
but I refuse to give up on her.
I'll make her mine, by any means necessary.
No! Akira?!
Feeling good?
Tell me... I'm good, right?
Yes, you are...
I'm seriously in love with you.
I understand.
But if you truly love me, you won't force yourself on me.
Please try to understand, Akira.
Mother
Mother Fucker
#2 My Mother's Secret Side
Thanks again for all your help, Akira.
Where's Kazuma?
He went straight to video games
the moment we finished studying.
That son of mine...
Still, he's been studying really hard.
That's true. His grades have been improving lately.
He must have a really good tutor.
You're too kind, Saori.
Hey, now, I'm your aunt!
Don't call me by my name.
Call me "Auntie" like you did when you were little.
It's because I love you.
I think you're just confused...
You feel this way because you walked in on me naked...
I'm not confusing lust for love!
I love you!
I'm in love with you!
Look how wet my kiss made you.
I'm so happy!
Stop!
Please, stop!
I have a husband and son!
Not there! Stop!
Saori... Please take my first time!
Akira?!
No! Anything but that!
We can't!
Amazing!
I'm one with you right now!
I'm gonna cum!
I just put it in, but I'm ready to burst!
Akira...
Stop moving.
Listen to me!
Saori...
Go all the way in slowly, and then all the way out.
Good! Just like that!
That's good!
Good! More!
Incredible!
You're so big!
If this keeps up, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna...
Here it is!
I'm cumming!
You're soaking wet!
I made you feel really good, right?
This...
This can never happen again.
No way!
This can't be the last time!
It's just like he said...
That day would be the first of many.
Akira loves me earnestly...
Something I haven't felt in a long time.
My body can't go back to being unloved and unused.
Saori... You're so beautiful.
You're fucking me so hard!
You're making my head go crazy!
So hard! You're fucking me so hard!
I'm cumming! I'm already cumming!
Have mercy on me!
Your cock is so deep inside me!
Oh, god!
I'm cumming!
I can't go back!
May I call you "Mother"?
Would that make you happy?
I've always thought it'd be nice to have you as my mother.
Incredible... You're so hard.
I can't believe how hard it is.
It's making my heart race!
It's twitching so much, ready to burst.
Go ahead! Cum!
Cum from Mommy's hand job!
It's okay! Cum!
Give Mommy your cummies!
You're so good, Mother.
Of course. I'm taking the lead today.
Sorry, my hips are moving on their own!
I can't stop riding your dick!
There's so much...
There's so much flowing inside me!
I'm sneaking out of the house to commit adultery...
I'm the worst.
But the moment I step into his house,
my body completely submits to him.
I can do nothing but give in to my impulses.
I'm gonna fuck you until you can't move anymore, Mother!
Do you love me, Mother?
Yes! I love you!
I love you and your cock!
My cunt can't get enough of you!
I can't stop!
It's so good!
Keep going!
Keep fucking me! Don't stop!
I can't get enough!
It feels too good!
I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
I shouldn't be doing this...
How's it going? Studying hard?
Yeah. Don't push yourself too hard, Mom.
I'm fine, Kazuma.
Thank you.
Even though Kazuma's home...
I can't hold my voice back!
Kazuma's gonna hear me!
Don't move your fingers so much!
Now it's my turn!
Your cock is so big and manly!
Bigger than your husband's?
Yes! Bigger and better!
I love it when you cum inside me!
Make me cum! I'm begging you!
Let's cum together!
I want to cum with you!
Fuck me as hard as you can! This is the last
time we can do it until the baby is born!
Yes! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Welcome back, Mom.
Thanks, Kazuma.
Guess I'm a big brother now.
Yes, be nice to your little sister, okay?
I kinda want a little brother too.
Next time you get pregnant,
make sure it's a boy, okay?
O-Okay.
I might get pregnant again!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum again!
translator: hikarucon
timing: ragingheartsexcelion
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editing: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч