There is a woman that I love.
She is my aunt, Saori-san.
Even I think that being in love with my aunt is strange.
But I'm definitely not giving up.
I'll make sure that she'll become mine...
...no matter what it takes!
You can't do this, Akira-kun!
I want you, Auntie...
For a long time now, I...
You're just confused!
I seriously am in love with you!
I-I understand.
But you shouldn't force yourself
to me if you love me, right?
Please understand, Akira-kun.
Mother
Beloved Mother
The Hidden Side Of My Beloved Mother
Sorry for the trouble, Akira-kun.
Where is Kazuma?
He's done studying and is now busy playing games.
Oh, that boy...
But he's studying diligently.
That's right, it seems that his grades went up
all thanks to his top-notch tutor!
Thank you, Saori-san.
Calling me Saori-san...
I'm your aunt.
You can just call me auntie like back then.
I love you...
Huh?
Y-You are mistaken.
You just happened to see me naked.
You're still saying that...
I love you, I love you!
Saori-san, you got wet from my kiss!
I'm happy!
Don't! Please don't lick me there!
I have a husband, and Kazuma too!
Not there...
Saori-san, please have my first time!
Akira-kun?
A-Anything but that!
A-Anything but that...
Wow! I became one with you, Saori-san!
What should I do?
I feel like I'm coming even
though it's just my first time!
Akira-kun, stop moving your hips!
Look to me!
Saori-san...
Start from the entrance and
push it slowly deep inside.
Yes, that's right!
You're doing great!
That's it, more!
Amazing! It's so huge!
No... If this goes on, I'm...
I'm...
I'm coming already... Saori-san!
Keep thrusting as you come!
You got so drenched. This means
that you felt good, right?
This would be...
...the first and last time, okay?
That's impossible.
There's no way that I can let this be the end!
Just as Akira-kun said,
our relationship never ended.
With Akira-kun's sincere feelings,
I got a taste of a man's body
again after such a long time.
There might be no going back for us now.
Saori-san, you're beautiful.
I'm sloppy inside and it feels good!
You're stirring me up inside!
If you keep shoving it in, I'll go crazy!
You're so intense!
I'm coming! I'm coming already!
I can't... I can't take it anymore!
Your dick is rubbing deep inside me!
No... No, I'm coming!
I'm really gonna come!
It's coming out!
I can't stop myself anymore!
Can I call you mom?
Will that make you happy?
I always thought how it would be
if you were my mother, Saori-san.
Wow, you're so thick.
I made you this hard...
It makes me feel aroused!
You're throbbing down here,
like it's gonna burst at any time.
It's okay, shoot it out!
I want you to come from my handjob!
Good boy, come!
Cover me with your sperm!
Mom, you're amazing!
That's right, I'll do the moving for today!
I'm sorry, my hips are moving on their own!
My hips won't stop!
You're coming so much!
You're coming a lot inside me!
I stayed out for the night, leaving my family
at home just to cheat on my husband.
I'm the worst.
But at the moment I entered his house,
I couldn't help my body from feeling hot!
Mom, I'm gonna keep raping you tonight
until you can't move anymore!
Mom, do you love me?
Yes, I love you!
I both love you and love having sex with you!
My pussy turned crazy!
It won't stop trembling
Good... It feels good!
I've been coming non-stop!
I won't be able to let go of you
after teaching me this kind of sex!
It's too stimulating!
I'm gonna die!
I'll get pregnant... Even though I shouldn't be...
How is it? Are you studying well?
Yeah. Mom, don't push yourself too much.
I'm fine, Kazuma
Thank you.
Even though Kazuma is on the second floor...
I can't hold my voice back!
Kazuma will hear us!
Don't move your fingers so hard!
This time, I'm going to slide it in between these.
Akira-kun, your dick is so huge!
Bigger than uncle?
Yes, way bigger than him. You're wonderful.
I love your dick and semen! I love them both!
Please make me come!
Make me come with you!
Let's come at the same time!
I'm begging you, just for the last time!
Thrust it in with all your strength!
I'm at my limit... I'm coming, I'm coming!
Welcome home, mom.
I'm home, Kazuma.
So, I'm a big brother now.
Yes, you are. Get along with
your little sister, okay?
Listen, I want to have a little brother as well.
Give birth to a boy next, okay?
R-Right...
I might give a birth again soon.
I'm coming! I'm coming again!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization