What are we going to do today?
W-Well...
You will abuse my body.
Stop!
I will take pleasure in
offering myself to my master.
That's enough!
That's well said.
Come on, turn around.
How about we kiss?
Yurika!
Hello.
I'm going to class.
Ichijo-san, hello.
Hello.
I am in a relationship
with Yurika Ichijo.
She is the president of the floral art dub.
And the most beautiful girl in high school.
Not to mention she has a big chest.
I didn't think it was possible.
I-I'm in love with you!
Would you go out with me?
Uh...
I...
Yes, I would be delighted.
I will never forget this blue
sky during our first date.
This crepe is delicious.
Being able to eat a delicious
crepe after school is like a dream.
I know eating a crepe is not an ideal date.
If you'd like to go anywhere
else, let me know.
What I'd like to do?
Well, as long as it's within my ability.
So Yurika?
Do you have any suggestions?
Uhh, it may be a little reckless.
But I would like to see
where you live Yusuke-kun.
So that's what your room looks like.
This is the first time I enter a boy's room.
It makes me nervous.
My heart is beating wildly.
R-Really?
Yu-Yurika...
I want you.
I want to feel everything.
Me too.
Let's discover sex together.
Yurika!
The way you knead my
breasts is embarrassing.
Yurika, I'm about to penetrate you.
Wow, your penis is amazing!
This big thing is about to penetrate me.
I hope you're ready.
Good.
Here I go.
Yes...
A-Are you okay?
I'm fine, you can go on.
Don't worry.
Go ahead and make love to me.
Yurika making love with you is fantastic.
My body reacts to every bump!
They're making my mind go blank!
Even though the pain remains vivid Yusuke-kun
does everything to put me at ease.
Yusuke-kun.
Yurika I will not be able to resist any longer.
Yusuke-kun you can cum.
Yurika I love you so much.
Me too.
I share the same love for him.
An eternal love.
At least I hoped.
Yurika?
Hey wait for me!
It's not nice to leave without me.
You've been distant these days.
Yusuke-kun.
Is something wrong?
Forgive me.
Want to go somewhere together for once?
We could go wherever you want.
Good Evening.
Madam.
The master awaits your
arrival with impatience.
Forgive me Yusuke-kun.
I can not come with you.
Yurika?
Seeing her get in this car
gives me a bad feeling.
Who can be the man this
driver was talking about?
I hope I didn't cause him any problems.
I don't like this in any way.
I hadn't given it any thought before.
We had finally become a couple after
declaring my love for her several months ago.
A message from Yurika?
Oh, is it recording?
Perfect.
Who is it?
Begin by introducing yourself.
W-What's the meaning of this!
I'm in my second year at
Kageyama High School.
My name is Yurika Ichijo.
And what size is your chest?
My chest measures approximately 168cm.
And what are we going to do today?
W-Well...
Your dick will ravage my
vagina over and over again.
I will take pleasure in
offering myself to my master.
That's well said.
Come on, turn around.
How about we kiss?
Look at all the juice your
pussy left on my hand.
Let's take a close up of your
wet slit with the camera.
You rarely see a pussy so nice this wet.
Are you excited?
T-That is my...
What?
Trying to lie to yourself?
This will make the sequel more crisp.
Do you feel ashamed?
You should not, though.
Those were just some personal problems.
By becoming mine you saved your father's
business and the future of its employees.
We are about to consume our relationship.
Look at my cock penetrate
my dear Yurika's pussy.
By going deep and pushing hard.
No!
Get ready because your pussy
is going to get expensive.
All this wetness shows you love it.
I want to hear you screaming
about how exciting my cock is.
You know you'll end up
obeying my orders anyway?
Well Yurika! Start telling
me how good it feels!
Don't listen to him Yurika!
I will continue to penetrate
you mercilessly until you obey.
Come on Yurika!
No it's too hard.
Poor Yurika... Do not say anything.
Forgive me Yusuke-kun.
Your penis is too much!
This cock is a hundred times
better than that of Yusuke-kun!
My pussy is going wild
every time you penetrate it!
Your words make me want
to fuck you even more!
I will repaint the walls of your vagina
by emptying my balls inside you!
I would love that!
All this sperm is going to
get me pregnant. I know it!
I can't keep fucking like this!
Stop!
I feel weird!
I'm getting dizzy!
You'll destroy my pussy!
Enjoy your favorite dick my pretty Yurika.
No... I'll end up going mad!
I'm thinking about it.
You haven't sent your
boyfriend a message yet.
Come on... Keep your penis going.
So Yurika want to leave him a few words?
Come on, please fuck me more.
Speak or else I'll stop.
No! Not that!
In that case
do it!
Yes! Anything you want!
Forgive me Yusuke-kun.
I'm now bound to serve
my master as he wishes.
S-So...
I'll do everything my master wants so
that he empties his balls within my pussy!
Listen to this sound!
It's the sound of my pussy getting fucked!
Master! Please fill me with all your sperm!
Your sperm is going so deep inside of me.
I just love
this feeling.
I love you.
Since that day
I had no news from Yurika.
I spent my days waiting
for her to contact me.
I know it's horrible.
But I masturbated several
times to the video.
Despite what happened,
I can not forget Yurika.
I'm sorry I didn't reply to
any of your messages.
Yurika?
I'm here on my master's orders.
He wanted me to show
you my pregnant body.
Then.
He wanted me to make love to you.
One last time.
So for the last time in our lives.
Let's make love.