So why exactly did you come here today?
I-I'm here... representing my Dad's company to...
Stop it...
Satisfy you so you won't hurt him.
Stop it!
Well said. We're gonna be married, you know that?
How about a kiss to seal the deal?
No... Yurika!!
Morning!
Good morning.
Thank you for the drive.
Ichijou-san! Morning!
Good morning.
Flower Arrangement Club
I have a girlfriend.
Her name is Ichijou Yurika.
She's a typical rich girl
daughter of a corporate executive.
She's well-known for her beauty in our school.
And for her big tits too!
With nothing to lose, I confessed to her...
I... I like you!
Please... go out with me!
Um... I...
I will. I would be glad to.
DARAKU NO REIJOI THE ANIMATION
Our fifth date was the
one that I'll never forget.
It's so delicious!
Walking around in our
uniforms after lunch is like a dream.
Yeah, but having a crepe
on a date is kind of cliche, huh?
If there's anything else you want to do,
your wish is my command.
Something... I want to do?
Of course you gotta make sure
it's something I can actually do though.
Uh... Yurika?
Are you feeling okay?
Uh, you might find this vulgar,
but I'd like to visit your house, Yuusuke-kun.
So this is your room, huh?
This is the first time I've ever been
in a boy's room. It's kind of nerve-wracking.
It's also really... exciting.
R-Really?
Y-Y-Yurika...
I'm gonna undress you.
I feel like my mind is drifting off.
Me too...
We're in the same boat.
Yurika!
Th-That's embarrassing!
Yurika, let's get started, okay?
Wow, so that's how it gets?
And it's going to... go inside me, right?
Yeah. Loosen up a bit.
Okay, I'm gonna put it in.
A-Are you okay?
M-More okay than I thought.
I'm fine, so love me lots, okay?
Yurika!
It feels so good!
It's getting so hot inside me!
It feels like I'm all mixed up!
It hurts, but Yuusuke-kufls doing his best for me.
Yuusuke-kun! Yuusuke-kun!!
Yurika, I'm about to hit my limit.
Yuusuke-kun, do it.
Yurika, I love you.
Yeah, I do too.
I really felt as if he was precious to me.
It was...
supposed to be that way forever.
Yurika!
Hey! Wait, Yurika!
You just left without saying anything.
That's not too nice.
I haven't really been able
to talk with you recently either.
Yuusuke-kun...
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Hey, do you wanna come
over to my place? It's been a while.
Well, you know... we haven't done it recently either.
Welcome back.
Ojou-sama.
The Master is waiting for you.
I'm sorry, Yuusuke-kun.
I need to go!
Yurika!
That wasn't her family's car, was it?
Who did he mean by "the master"?
I wonder if I did anything to make her mad?
I never even thought of
being able to date a rich girl before...
It's been several months since we started dating
and we just started feeling like a real couple, but...
A text from Yurika?
Oh, it's working?
Great.
Who's that?
Okay, introduce yourself.
Wh-What is this?
I'm Ichijou Yurika, a second
year at the Kageyama Academy.
What are your measurements?
105-62-88 from top to bottom.
So why exactly did you come here today?
I-I'm here to represent my Dad's
company to satisfy you so you won't hurt him.
Well said.
We're gonna be married, you know that?
How about a kiss to seal the deal?
Take a look. My hands are drenched now.
Alright, next up let's give the camera
a good look at your naughty area.
It looks like you wet yourself down there.
Are you turned on?
N-Not there...
What's wrong? Don't be so reserved.
You can be as loud as you like.
Do you have a guilty conscience?
You don't need to feel guilty.
That's just how things work. A company
going under isn't such a rare sight.
Thanks to you agreeing to become my wife...
you saved not only your
father but many of his employees as well.
This'll be our first step as husband and wife.
Look, my raw dick is going inside you, Yurika!
No!
You're holding your voice back, huh?
But your pussy's honest!
Your pussy is completely drenched.
My dick is better than your boyfriend's isn't it?
Admit that my dick feels
better than some random brat's!
Just forget about that guy and
become mine! Isn't that why you came here?!
Come on Yurika, tell me that my dick's better!
Don't, Yurika!
If you become mine in both body and soul,
so many people will be saved!
Come on, Yurika!
I can't hold back!
I'm begging you, Yurika!
Don't do it!
I'm sorry, Yuusuke-kun.
I can't anymore! Your adult dick
is better than Yuusuke-kun's!
I've been coming so
much from your dick!
You just made this scene perfect, Yurika!
I'm going to fill your insides with my
cum as a reward for saying that so well!
Yurika!
I-I'm gonna cum! I...
There's so much... inside me,
I'm definitely gonna get pregnant!
No! We're having such rough sex!
No!
This is gonna make me go crazy!
My mind's snapping!
This is so rough, I'm going to break!
Come on, Yurika, you need to get a good
taste of this dick that you love so much!
I-I'm breaking!
Now that I think about it, you haven't
broken up with your boyfriend yet, have you?
More... more dick...
Okay, Yurika, give him a proper farewell.
Please... more...
If you don't give a proper farewell, we're done here.
No! You can't!
Then do it.
O-Okay, I'll do it!
I'm sorry, Yuusuke-kun.
I'm going to become Master's woman.
S-So...
Please fill my pussy with tons of your cum, Master!
Pump it full of your cum.
Make Yurika... make me pregnant with your cum!
It's coming out.
Master's cum is...
I love it.
I love sex.
A little while later,
a rumor started about
Yurika withdrawing from school.
And I just kept waiting for
another message from Yurika...
even though I knew it would never come.
At first, I hated them, but...
The one I hated the most was me
for masturbating to that video so many times.
That's why I can't bring myself to hate her.
Sorry I never replied to your text.
Yurika?
Master told me to say hi and to show
you what I look like that I'm pregnant.
He also told me to have sex with you, Yuusuke-kun.
So, yeah, let's do it...
one last time.