Kiriko Ragawa.
Math teacher at Heiwa Academy.
Twenty-four years old. Single.
Five feet 5 inches.
One hundred and 10 pounds.
Large breasts.
A little wasp waist...
and a tight curvy ass.
Black belt in both judo and karate.
Her hobbies include playing sports
and traveling.
She loves spicy caviar.
She hates tomatoes.
Kiriko-sensei...
l want to see you naked.
l want to see how you look when you have sex.
What is your favorite position?
Do you cry out when you come?
Do you like to be tied up?
Do you like thick cocks?
Or do you prefer them long?
l wonder how good your pussy tastes.
Can l come inside you?
Do you think you'll like to get gangbanged?
Will you like swallowing my cum?
l wonder what...
makes you excited in bed.
And so Z equals HX equals GFX and....
Sensei.
Kiriko-sensei...
l want to see what you're really like in bed.
l'm just dying to see...
how you fuck.
Depravity
ls it bad?
lt's a deep cut.
You'll definitely need stitches.
lt's bleeding a lot.
l figured. My head fucking hurts.
So now what?
Do you want to leave?
Hell no!
After the shit l put up with so far?
l'm not giving up.
l thought you would say that.
This should take care of that for now.
lt will help a bit.
Thanks.
She really earned her black belt in judo and karate.
She really knows how to put up a fight.
Yes, she's no ordinary math teacher, for sure.
She's probably the best prey we have ever had to date.
Tough Ragawa Kiriko-sensei.
This is the first time restraining our prey took so much effort.
Yes, l really like it when you resist!
Makes me tingle!
l especially like the hatred
burning in your eyes right now.
lt makes me want to come just looking at you.
How are the other two doing?
They're in the infirmary.
l gave them some painkillers.
Snow's got a fracture, Persona has a broken rib.
How about yourself?
Okay, except....
See?
Damn, she broke your tooth!
l can't believe the strength on her.
A strong body. And a tough mind.
l wonder how long...
you'll be able to put up a fight.
We've been preying on female teachers for some time now.
Plenty of them put up a good fight, mind you, but...
once we break them, they fall apart.
By the third hour, they're moaning.
By the fourth hour...
they're begging for our cocks.
l want to see...
the expression on your face...
as you beg for more...
and come uncontrollably.
We do want you to put up
a damned good fight, though.
l want you to resist us as long as you can.
Don't worry about the syringe.
This isn't a sedative or anything of that kind.
This is an aphrodisiac.
lt's a potent, special formula...
that violently stimulates
your sexual organ into a frenzy.
lt promotes an uncontrollable desire for sex...
and it is effective for roughly 12 hours.
You can come as many times as you want.
But this treat isn't for you.
We inject this into ourselves...
so we can continuously please you without stopping.
As a rule, we refrain from using drugs on our prey.
That takes away some of the fun, don't you think?
Our only tool...
is our hard cocks.
You will soon be begging to get stuffed...
with our tools in every way imaginable, l promise.
Why is she laughing?
Should we give her something?
You think l'll be begging for your cock?
You guys are fucking hilarious.
You couldn't make me come
even if you tried your best...
l won't feel a damned thing!
So why don't you go back home
to your mommy and daddy...
do your homework, and go to bed like a good boy.
What?
Wait a minute, you won't be able to go
back home to your parents after tonight...
because your sorry asses will be in jail!
You'll regret the day you ever thought of this stupid idea!
How wonderful!
A fine lecture, for sure!
lt's amazing that you can keep up this resistance...
in your completely helpless state.
A shining example of strength.
That's why you are our ideal teacher.
Kiriko-sensei, your fighting spirit
makes you our ideal prey.
You are physically strong...
and mentally tough.
lt makes breaking you worth all our troubles.
See, you are so beautiful when your cheeks flush in embarrassment.
Let's see if l can make you prettier!
Stop it!
Don't!
l said stop!
Filthy dogs!
Get away from me!
l can't take any more of this!
l have to get away!
l have to....
See, your nipples are enjoying the attention.
Your body is a lot more honest than your mind.
You have to restrain your victims
because you're a cowardly piece of shit!
Filthy animals!
That's my girl, l don't want you to give in
so soon after a quick fondling.
That would be boring.
After all, we've only just started.
Now let's see what we have here.
No!
Bubble!
Jack!
Get up, right now!
She got away from us!
Troublesome cunt!
lf she gets out, we're fucked.
l think we should get the hell out of here.
No, l think we're still all right.
You don't think Ms. Prim and Proper...
will be running out of here buck naked, do you?
l know where to find her.
Shit. Where is it!
Where the hell are my clothes!
P.E. uniform. l hope this fits.
Wow, look at that!
lsn't she amazing?
Kiriko-sensei!
Looking good!
Here you go, Kiriko-sensei.
Thank You!
She said thank you!
Sensei, look over here!
Hey, come talk to us!
Sensei, are you ignoring us on purpose?
Sensei, come on, come over and talk to us, too!
Pretty please!
Sensei, Kiriko-sensei, wake up, can you hear me?
Are you awake now, Kiriko-sensei?
You might want to be awake for this.
l can't imagine that you'd want to
sleep through this one.
Shit!
l didn't want to get rough on you like that.
l don't like to use stun guns,
but l don't want any more injuries, either.
l only use it when l have no other choice.
Untie the rope right now!
Otherwise, you'll really have something to cry about!
What's so funny?
lt's just that you look so funny,
threatening us in that uniform.
Look at those little shorts.
And your name tag on the t-shirt!
Female Pig
We planted that uniform just in case, for you.
You bastards!
We figured that if you were to escape...
you would go look for your clothes in this room.
Goddamn it!
The uniform was an appropriate choice!
The shorts are crawling up your pussy...
and it shows off your cute bellybutton.
But l especially like the nipples
stretching against the shirt.
A female pig seems like a fitting title to you right now.
You think you're funny, you stupid assholes!
l take it you don't like your name tag?
Well then, in that case...
l'll take it off, just for you!
l think it's a neat little trick, don't you agree?
No!
Your shorts wants to show you
a trick too, just for you!
What? Wait, don't!
l think you know.
Now, we all get to view
the precious prize that we're after.
Your...
wet...
pussy.
No!
Wow!
You fucking bastards!
Now Sensei, there's no need to be so embarrassed.
Your cunt is absolutely beautiful.
You've got a luscious mound of shiny, pubic hair...
a very large clitoris...
and you have pink, delicious lips.
You should be proud of your pussy!
l really like the way she smells.
The smell of hairy, sweaty,
unwashed pussy turns me on.
What l can't believe is that you aren't
dripping wet with excitement yet.
You are a challenge, for sure.
All the teachers we preyed on before,
regardless of their vocal resistance...
were soaking wet and ready by this point.
You bastards couldn't excite me!
Your mental control over your body is amazingly strong.
Stop, don't touch me!
l have an idea. How about we make
a bet with you, Sensei?
We are going to fondle your cunt
continuously for ten full minutes.
You can't get wet or aroused at all.
lf you can handle that, we will promise to untie you and let you go.
Stop fucking around and let me go!
Why, you don't think you can handle it?
Don't you want to prove us wrong?
Our filthy hands couldn't excite you
in any way, right Sensei?
lt's all right l'm sure you'll prove us wrong.
All right, let's begin.
Ten minutes starting right now.
Wait, just wait a minute!
Start!
Stop!
Sorry, are we being too rough
with your precious clit?
Please excuse me.
This is a sensitive spot after all.
We'll start off very gently.
l'll add some lubrication
to make things better, just for you.
You sound like this is really turning you on, Sensei!
Fucking shut up.
Your filthy hands make me want to vomit.
l really hope so, since it hasn't even been a minute yet.
lf this feels good now,
you won't last the whole ten minutes.
Yeah, we still have plenty of time to play.
Goddamn it, if they keep going like that...
l really will end up coming!
Her clit is getting hard already!
Yeah, it's getting bigger, too!
lt's getting much bigger!
And much harder, too!
Shut up!
Check out her nipples!
Three minutes so far.
Let's show her what we've got!