Depravity 3
ls she coming?
lt's still on.
What?
What a girl, Kiriko...
l can't believe you used your earrings.
Looks like you kicked our asses.
What are you gonna do?
l would like to kill you.
But l am not the one to punish you.
Really? You think so?
You're gonna live to regret this.
Shut up!
l have to call the police.
lt looks like l have to get myself out.
Ouch!
What is this?
Damn, those ass-holes! Okay. Where's the windows.
What are you doing? What do you want?
Even though you did this to me, it's no use.
Go away, go away, don't come close, you dirty cowards.
You guys can't fight a little girl like me without your knife?
Oh, you are really something.
We wouldn't have a chance without this.
So, What do you think about this?
Just face it, no matter how strong you are,
you are nothing but a woman.
Oh, you are quite good at giving head.
How do you feel, little girl?
Such a beautiful body, l can't hold out any longer.
l want to fuck her too.
l'm coming.
Never mind.
Sleep well, boys
Not yet. She's going to wake up.
Hold on, it's almost done.
Okay. lt's done. l'm going to insert it.
Go ahead.
Good morning, Kiriko-sensei.
What are you doing?
What are we doing?
You know this, just your standard enema procedure.
lt's going into your body, the cold liquid.
Now the situation has changed.
l was just about to give up.
lf l wouldn't have woken up in the health center,
you may have already escaped from here.
lt really, really hurts. l think my rib is broken.
My collar bone...
Oh, l just want to fuck you asap.
Using any injection is against the rules.
Never mind, you also did it too much.
Look, look at his poor cut up dick.
lt looks like you have some teeth in your cunt, baby.
The situation is still fuck up even though l took the emergency measures.
And that guy is blind because of you.
My gang is seriously wounded,
but l finally got you here.
l said, ''call it off,'' but...
Nobody agreed with me. They all want you badly.
Therefore, we all took a bunch of pain killers
to feel no pain.
But the side effect is that we can't control ourselves...
We can't control our behavior
and there's no way to act properly.
Here comes the last shot.
No! Help me!
l will listen to you, anything,
l will be a good girl, just let me down.
Nice try, but l can tell from your eye.
That face, you must think
that you can run away from here.
Damn you...
But...l will never let you go.
Kiriko...
Senpai?
Stop it. l'm going home.
Please, just let me go.
Kiriko, it's Okay.
l will never let you go, Kiriko.
That hurts.
Kiriko, you belong to me.
Now there's nothing your can do, Kiriko-sensei.
l will never surrender.
Then l'm gonna wear you out, bitch.
By our dicks this time.
Come on, lick it.
Let us fulfill your body, girl.
Also in the body.
This is cruel.
Oh...so tight.
lt's out.
l'm coming...
Coming out
Wow, looks so good.
Alright, please also drink this, Sensei.
l will deliver it to the dept of your throat.
You are drinking now.
Yes sir
Stop it, stop it!
What? So eager to suck it? Alright...
Stop it!
Stop it! Please forgive me.
lf this continues, l...
No, l can't become weak.
What should l do?
l missed my best chance to escape.
No, don't touch me there.
No, it's going deeper.
l can't stand it.
Oh, sounds like she is farting, the enema is working.
Looks like you are right. Sensei, you are shitting.
l have got to stop this.
Oh, her pussy is getting tight.
Oh God, it's getting more sensitive.
Are you starting to enjoy this, Kiriko-sensei?
No! No...!
You are so good, your the best.
You also starting to enjoy it, l'm happy to see this.
No...
Oh, so good, Kiriko. l am ready...
You are so excited now. Yes! That it!
No! No...!
l'm coming.
No...!
How do you feel, Sensei?
Just kill me.
You want me to die so badly.
Just kill me now, and let me down.
You are tough indeed, but just stop that.
Just stop pretending.
You know perfectly clear.
That your body wants it bad.
No, l hate this feeling.
Why does this kind of thing happen to me?
Sensei, take off your mask.
No, stop it
Get rid of all your fake appearance.
Stop it, stop it!
Let me see the real you.
Stop it...!
Oh no, it's so...
lt feels so good.
Come on, Sensei, stop fighting the feeling.
Relax and enjoy the pleasant sensation brought by my dick.
lt feels so good.
l can move it. l can feel it moving inside.
And don't think about anything else.
l want to hear your original voice.
lt feels so good, so good.
l can't help it.
Unbelievable.
She's coming.
Yes, this is a really great feeling.
lsn't it, Kiriko-sensei?
Whatever...
More, I just want more.
Give me more.
Please...
Okay, let her down.
Please, just fuck me hard.
Wonderful!
The sound of your tight pussy is wonderful.
l will fuck you all l can till l die.
lt's sucking like a vacuum cleaner.
My dick is really delicious, isn't it?
lt tastes so good.
You are totally different from the beginning.
l am coming!
Okay. l am coming too.
lt's so hot, it's coming out.
Here, have a taste of this.
Amazing. More, give me more.
Oh, my pussy is full of cum.
And l have a dick in my ass.
Rub it inside, yes...
Cumming, cumming, l'm cumming!
Oh my god, cumming, cumming!
l'm cumming!
Why does it feel so good?
Why do these thing feel so good?
l can't feel myself and my mind is empty...
l feel like l just want more and more.
Give me more, more...
l can't believe it, pretending not to like it.
l am actually just a slut.
You are right.
But it's not what we are doing to you.
We are helping you to reveal your true inner self.
Thank you...