Depravity 2
lt's been four minutes.
l'm getting wet!
l need to resist!
Look, her face is turning bright red!
She's biting her lips and trying to resist!
How cute!
Stop!
This has to stop!
You know you like it.
You should give up, Sensei!
No, l can't come like this!
Stop!
Look at that, her pussy's dripping wet!
lt's running down all over her ass now!
You're soaking wet, Sensei.
You lasted 5 minutes, 43 seconds.
This ended quicker that l thought.
Were we really that good?
l'm not aroused at all!
My body was just reacting.
Nothing else!
That's not going to change...
no matter what you do to me.
l'm not going to submit to you bastards!
You will give in eventually.
Regardless of how much you resist right now.
We'll make you submit to us.
With your body and soul.
All right, bye bye!
Kiriko-sensei, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Grading tests tonight?
Yes.
That's too bad! l wanted to ask you out to dinner.
l have to finish this tonight.
l understand. Have a good night!
Thanks, see you tomorrow!
l need to get this done.
Now, we're going to make you have an orgasm.
You're going to be completely exposed...
and at our mercy!
Do whatever you want!
We will.
That's the idea, right?
Good, tie her up!
Okay!
What the...!
Damn you!
A splendid view!
Your pussy and asshole's totally exposed.
l can even look deep inside!
Whoa, check that out, it's bright pink inside!
Look!
See the juice flowing out of her pussy!
So, how does it feel?
Do you like it when filthy bastards like us look inside you?
She's not talking to us!
Are you trying to ignore us?
That's fine with me.
Seeing how long it takes for you to give up...
is part of the fun.
Now, Kiriko-sensei,
it's all right if you enjoy yourself!
You have a magnificent pussy.
lt's nice and wet, soft, and very warm.
The tightness of your pussy is unbelievable!
l'm sure your pussy will make us
come very quickly...
over and over and over again!
l'm sure your pussy will clean out
our balls of come.
Feel anything yet?
l do believe you're starting to enjoy this.
She's still totally ignoring us.
She's the very first one!
That's true.
lt doesn't make a difference.
Since your pussy's responding to us so nicely.
Just look at this!
You're continuing to get much wetter.
Yeah, it's starting to get slick and slimy, l like it.
Your clit has been erect this whole time.
lt seems to like us.
Look, it's quivering!
See Sensei, we know you're enjoying this.
You can have fun with her big, fat clitoris.
Sure!
You can keep her back door company,
if that makes you happy.
Roger!
No!
Can you feel that?
This is our infamous triple attack.
lt's been infallible.
No, l don't feel anything!
Are you sure, because l think you're lying!
You're so wet, you're splashing us.
God, l'm going to come!
lf you're not feeling any of this, that means...
we're just going to have to work that much harder.
No more!
Otherwise, l'm going to....
Come!
lt's time to go!
You just had an orgasm.
l...l did not!
Why the hell would l come for you fucking bastards?
Please excuse me.
lf you didn't have an orgasm...
then we'll just have to continue.
H...Hold on!
No, it's too sensitive now!
lf they continue, l'm going to come again!
We won't stop until you have an orgasm, Sensei!
All this resistance can't be good for you!
You'll see, we're going to humiliate you!
l can't come. No!
Goddamn it, l can't take this anymore.
Hey, check out that massive puddle she's building.
My finger's tired.
My pussy's throbbing.
Again!
No!
Stop, l can't take this!
Please!
Will you promise to tell us the truth, Kiriko-sensei?
Did you come?
l did.
How many times?
Three times, l came three times!
Now, l told you the truth, so take your filthy hands off of me!
We can't do that yet.
What?
You might be satisfied now...
but we haven't completed our mission yet.
Watching you resist having an orgasm
might be very entertaining...
but we're still not finished.
We want you to cast aside...
every bit of pride that you have left...
and surrender to the waves of pleasure.
We want your body and mind to submit willingly.
Relish the ecstasy.
No, l can't take it!
Wow!
Look, she's coming!
We did it!
Man!
Yeah!
Damn, she's squirting!
Yeah, l love it when the pussy trembles!
And l love it even more when it squirts like this!
Damn, she's got one hell of an amazing wet pussy!
Yes.
lt's wasted on such a proud,
repressed woman like you.
Well, that was fantastic!
Watching you climax so hard like that!
You've got what you wanted,
so let me go already!
Get you vile fingers out of my body!
Untie the fucking ropes!
We can do that for you.
We're done fingering you for now.
However, you couldn't resist us for 10 minutes.
Take a look at them!
These drugs have made us come
several times already while fingering you.
We still have plenty of life left
in these rods, just for you.
Don't you want one of those hard,
thick, meaty cocks...
pounding your wet pussy? We'll do you, then.
Why would l?
Come on, l swear you'll have a good time.
l'm very sure of it.
Besides, l know you're body's
still very sensitive...
after all those orgasms.
We'll just continue molesting your body,
until you can't come anymore.
All right, here we go!
No!
Please stop!
l'm inside her!
Kiriko-sensei! l know you want have
your pussy swallowing my fat cock!
This is a very special moment of our togetherness!
Can you feel my hard rod filling you up inside?
l feel it.
This is my last summer as a student,
l'm going to have fun!
Kiriko-san!
l got you a soda.
Need more oil?
Let's go swimming!
Yes, l do need more oil.
Please allow me!
Kiriko-san, does it feel good?
Yes!
Does it feel good?
Pull it out, right now!
Now, don't be shy.
Can't you feel your pussy gripping
and squeezing my cock...
like a mother fucking vice?
That's...
not...
true!
See, your pussy's telling me...
that it wants me to stay here!
lt wants to be pounded!
l can feel it throbbing right now!
lt wants to be fucked!
Damn, look at him pumping! He's going off, man!
No!
Can you feel the end of her, inside?
Yeah, l feel my cock's banging against it!
My cock fucking you like a jackhammer, right?
Stop!
l can't handle this anymore!
Why can't you handle anymore of this?
Are you going to come?
Come on, Kiriko-sensei.
Just be honest.
We know you love it.
You enjoy being hammered by a thick, meaty cock.
Am l right?
Sensei?
l love it!
Yes!
Will you go out with me, Kiriko-san?
Okay.
Stop it!
Look at that body!
l want to see more!
Coming up!
Don't!
l really want to fuck her!
She's getting wet, too!
Damn!
Hey, l'd bet she likes it!
Lift your ass!
Let me see them!
Chill out!
Here, take a look!
Check out her little twat!
lt's nice and pink!
lt's getting juicy and slick!
l can't wait, l'm going to fuck her with my cock now!
No!
Sensei, hurry up!
Just admit that you love it!
l can't think.
My body's burning up!
Does she feel good?
All right, suck on this!
Don't fucking bite me!
Kiriko-san...
How do you like fucking and sucking at the same time?
Where does it feel good?
Everywhere! All over!
All over my body!
l love cock!
Give me more!
Yes, much harder!
Fuck me harder!
Just keep pumping!
Yeah, we did it! She finally gave in!
l thought she would take a lot longer.
True.
But she's a woman, and they're all predictable.
l agree.
More!
Keep fucking me, harder!
l think we can stop playing around now.
Yeah, let's really have some fun with this one!
Here, do you want to slurp on this pulsing popsicle?
Give it to me, give it to me.
D...Don't let her!