So why exactly did you come here today?
I-I'm here... in the place of my Dad's company to...
Stop it...
Satisfy you so you won't hurt them.
Stop it!
Well said. We're gonna be married, you know?
How about a kiss to seal the deal?
No... Yurika!!
Morning!
Morning.
Good morning.
Thank you for the drive.
Ichijou-san! Morning!
Good morning.
Flower Arrangement Club
I have a girlfriend.
Her name's Ichijou Yurika.
Moon Flower
She's the typical rich girl daughter of a company president.
She's a famous beauty in our school.
And for her big tits too.
I confessed to her with nothing to lose and...
I... I like you!
Please... go out with me!
Um... I...
I will. I would be glad to.
Depraved rich girl
Training records of netorare with a sheltered rich girl
Our fifth date was one that I'll never forget, even now.
It's so delicious!
Walking around in our uniforms after
lunch, eating is like a dream.
Yeah, but having a crepe on a date is kind of cliche, huh?
If there's anything you want to do, your wish is my command.
Something... I want to do?
Of course you gotta make sure it's something
I can actually do though.
Uh... Yurika?
Are you feeling okay?
Uh, you might find this vulgar, but I'd
like to visit your house, Yuusuke-kun.
So this is your room, huh?
This is the first time I've ever been in a
boy's room. It's kind of nerve-wracking.
It's also really... exciting.
R-Really?
Y-Y-Yurika...
I'm gonna undress you.
I feel like my mind is drifting off.
Me too...
We're in the same boat.
Yurika!
Th-That's embarrassing!
Yurika, let's get started, okay?
Wow, so it gets like that?
And it's going to... go inside me, right?
Yeah. Loosen up a bit.
Okay, I'm gonna put it in.
A-Are you okay?
M-More okay than I thought.
I'm fine, so love me lots, okay?
Yurika!
It feels so good!
It's getting so hot inside me!
It feels like all of me is being mixed up!
It hurts, but Yuusuke-kun's doing his best for me.
Yuusuke-kun! Yuusuke-kun!!
Yurika, I'm about to hit my limit.
Yuusuke-kun, do it.
Yurika, I love you.
Yeah, I do too.
I really felt as if he was precious to me.
It was...
supposed to stay that way forever.
Yurika!
Hey! Wait, Yurika!
You just left without saying anything. That's not too nice.
I haven't really been able to talk with you recently either.
Yuusuke-kun...
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Hey, do you wanna come over to my place? It's been a while.
Well, you know... we haven't done it recently either.
Welcome back.
Ojou-sama.
The master is waiting for you.
I'm sorry, Yuusuke-kun.
I need to go!
Yurika!
That wasn't her family's car, was it?
Who did he mean by "the master?"
I wonder if I did anything to make her mad?
I never even thought of being able to date a rich girl, but...
It's been several months since we started dating
and we started feeling like a real couple, but...
Yurika
A text from Yurika?
Oh, it's working?
Great.
Who's that?
Okay, introduce yourself.
Wh-What is this?
I'm Ichijou Yurika, a second year at the Kageyama Academy.
What're your three sizes?
105-62-88 from top to bottom.
So why exactly did you come here today?
I-I'm here in the place of my Dad's company
to satisfy you so you won't hurt them.
Well said.
We're gonna be married, you know?
How about a little kiss to seal the deal?
Take a look. My hands are drenched now.
Alright, next up is giving the camera
a good look of your shameful area.
It looks like you wet yourself down here.
Are you turned on?
N-Not there...
What's wrong? Don't be so reserved.
You can be as loud as you'd like.
Do you have a guild conscience? You don't need to feel guilty.
That's just how things work. A company
going under isn't too rare a sight.
Thanks to you agreeing to become my wife, you saved not
only your father but many of his employees as well.
This'll be our first step as husband and wife.
Look, my raw dick is going inside you, Yurika!
No!
You're holding your voice back, huh?
But your pussy's honest!
Your pussy is completely drenched. My dick
is better than your boyfriend's isn't it?!
Admit that my dick feels better than some random brat's!
Just forget about that guy and become
mine! Isn't that why you came here?!
Come on Yurika, tell me that my dick's better!
Don't! Yurika!
If you become mine in both body and
soul, so many people will be saved!
Come on, Yurika!
I can't hold back!
I'm begging you, Yurika!
Don't do it!
I'm sorry, Yuusuke-kun.
I can't anymore! Your adult dick is better than Yuusuke-kun's!
I've been cumming so much from your dick for a while now!
You just made this scene perfect, Yurika!
I'm going to fill your insides with my cum
as a reward for saying that so well!
Yurika!
I-I'm gonna cum! I...
There's so much... inside me. I'm definitely gonna get pregnant!
No! We're having such rough sex!
No!
This is gonna make me go crazy! My mind's breaking!
This is so rough, I'm going to break!
Come on, Yurika, you need to get a good
taste of this dick that you love so much!
I... I'm breaking!
Now that I think about it, you haven't broken
up with your boyfriend yet, have you?
More... more dick...
Okay, Yurika, give him a proper farewell.
Please... more...
If you don't give a proper farewell, we're done here.
No! You can't!
Then do it.
O-Okay, I'll do it!
I'm sorry, Yuusuke-kun.
I'm going to become Master's woman.
S-So...
Please fill my pussy with tons of your cum, Master!
Pump it full of your cum.
Make Yurika... make me pregnant with your cum!
It's coming out.
Master's cum is...
I love it.
I love sex.
A little while later,
a rumor started about Yurika withdrawing from the school.
And I just kept waiting for another message from
Yurika even though I knew it'd never come.
To: Yurika
I'll be waiting for you on the school roof.
I want to see you.
I want to see your face, hear your voice.
I'm not mad at you.
I'm begging you, please,
just once is fine, let me see you.
At first, I hated them, but...
The one I hated the most was me for masturbating
to that video so many times.
That's why I can't bring myself to hate her.
Sorry I never replied to your text.
Yurika?
Master told me to say hi and to show you
what I look like now that I'm pregnant.
He also told me to have sex with you, Yuusuke-kun.
So, yeah, let's do it...
one last time.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч