Where the Cornage Plain stretches over the continent...
There is a kingdom called Carnia.
ln the spring, you'll see lots of red flowers.
ln the summer, green all the way to the horizon.
ln the fall, you'll see the wave of golden rice and wheat.
ln the winter, you'll see white plains everywhere.
lt is a beautiful kingdom full of colors.
lt gave me hopes and dreams, but all was stripped from me.
l'll never forget my homeland.
Who said that time will ease your pain?
The crime he committed hasn't been atoned.
My heart scorched.
So hot, so violent...
The scorching black flames...
So many days, so many nights....
l have been waiting for the right time...
lnside my black eyes, the flame of revenge burns.
Episode 1, Pulling Strings
ls this okay with you?
What's the matter?
Your finger movement isn't right.
Okay.
Show me.
Good, keep going.
l haven't even shown this to the King.
No, don't look... No...
Okay, Stop it.
l said, stop it.
Yes.
You have become much better than before.
No...
lt's a very wise decision.
l'm going to serve for you and your country
lt shall be my honor
No...
Don't move so fast...
Don't hold back, it's not good for you.
Release everything.
Your nasty voice and all of your desires.
Please...
Please, more, faster...
Thank you very much.
Claude.
How long are we going to do this?
As l mentioned before, the differences between Carnia forces and Raven forces are obvious.
Numbers of soldiers, there fighting spirit and strategies.
We are behind the Ravens in military aspects.
Moreover, our loss of the first battle, and our King's current condition...
l would say Carnia's victory is doubtful.
You mean Carnia is going to....
Then what am l doing...
No...
We have a winning chance, because of this doubtful situation.
Huh?
lndeed, the lost of the first battle caused damage.
On top of it, we showed Raven that Carnia is weak.
Then, we'll unleash the mercenaries.
Raven will have a tough time dealing with them.
Also...
And?
Soldiers will fight and risk their lives when they feel they have nothing to loose.
But when they are winning they get over confident and make mistakes.
That is their weak point.
But can we win the war?
Even though the Ravens are strong, there
forces are weak after this battle.
Their expedition must have reached its limit.
After three months, the Ravens will be....
Winter is coming, isn't it?
Correct, my heiress.
Until then, l need to sleep with other men besides my lord...
Please understand...
Okay...
Ah, Claude.
Anything else?
No...
People called me a runaway general.
lt has been eight years since l left my country.
Now l'm back.
My pledge!
You are going into battle.
You are going to fight for your country, may lose your life!
But l am fighting with you.
Like this country is your treasure, each and everyone of you are my treasure!
l swear that for the rest of my life, l will fight for my treasures!
Greatest Dynasty, Carnia!
Useless feelings.
The training of Queen Ellene is on schedule.
Now, the two princesses...
Princess Tiaris doesn't have good feelings for her mother-in-law Ellene.
Plus, she has doubts about her own existence.
l can use this.
Well, it won't be a problem.
Tiaris...
Ha, ha, ha, Claude...
l thought you swore revenge, Claude!
l can't be swayed like this.
The problem is the second princess, Eulicia.
l need to examine her a little more.
Who is it?
l'm Rizel, Lord Claude.
What is it?
Princess Tiaris is....
Tiaris?
Let her come in.
Excuse me.
Claude.
What happened to our first royal princess?
Coming to this kind of place.
And it's also a late evening.
Your father may grieve if he finds out.
Stop messing around!
You know my father is sick.
Excuse me.
So, what can l do for you?
Lord Claude...
Good.
Excuse me.
Claude, answer me!
What were you doing inside my mother-in-law's room?
We were just talking about the future.
Claude, don't lie!
Well, l was teaching her a lesson.
A lesson?
That bitch needs a lesson?
lt's for our country, princess.
l can't tell you, even for you Tiaris.
Don't you call me by my first name.
Princess Tiaris...
What purpose would this serve?
You would kill me, the one who knows the plan to save our kingdom.
What are you going to do after l die?
What am l...
Please answer me.
Well...
Princess, you can't always save a kingdom playing fair and square.
The righteous only win in the stories of sages and poets!
Ah...
You have no clue on how many sacrifices have to be made, in order to gain a victory!
Don't look down at me!
l can fight too.
Oh, so you want to fight?
No...
Ouch! Uh...
How?
What's your military strategy?
How will you provide provisions?
Moreover, for your loyalty, your eyes will be stabbed, and arms and legs cut off.
Are you prepared for the worst?
The Queen has been fighting on her own in order to save Carnia.
Are you ready for that?
For your country, are you ready to sacrifice yourself?
l can't put your mother-in-law down.
l...
Please go back to your room.
We need to avoid any rumors about us.
Understood.
Princess.
Please return to your room...
Are you okay?
l'm fine.
But, please let me stay here for a while.
Who is it?
lt's Claude.
Come in.
Excuse me.
You came, Claude.
Princess Tiaris.
How are you feeling about last night?
Claude, l have a request for you.
Let me do as my mother-in-law does.
Are you serious?
Yes. l have been alone thinking since we parted.
Thinking of where or whom l stand for.
But, l couldn't figure it out.
All l have learned has been useless!
Carnia's people are suffering so much.
Even my mother-in-law is fighting, but...
l have not done anything...
Claude, please!
Let me fight like my mother-in-law
lt's going to be a sacrafice, more than you think.
lt's all right. l can endure.
Okay.
Well, l'll see you tomorrow.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
l'm going to train you starting today Princess Tiaris.
Before that, l need to do one thing.
A thing?
Yes.
l need to take your virginity, Princess Tiaris
What?
Your role is to please men using your body
lf they know you are a virgin it will not help them!
l understand.
This is nothing. Why would you scream?
Oh, no!
Ouch!
No!
Why?
ls this how you make love?
l haven't got any sweet words nor a kiss from you...
So cruel...
You're misunderstanding.
This is not love making. That's how we make a lot of money,
What....
l don't mind the other men taking your virginity, if you wish.
The other men?
Yes.
They're men who really love virgins.
That way, we get more war funds from it.
But, it's not for them to take...
So l thought l would honor you instead.
Okay, thank you for your concern, Claude.
Okay, ready?
No...
No, don't...
Stop it!
Please...
Wow, the pearl of Carnia.
You have a good pussy
No...
Please, don't look.
Stop it, don't touch me!
lt hurts!
Stop it, please...
You were a virgin, but now you are a woman.
What? Uhh, no...
Ouch...
No...
Stop it, Claude!
Remember, this is having sex with a man.
Ouch, ouch!
No...
lt hurts, like my body is torn in two.
But kind of bittersweet...
Who is it?
lt's me.
Please come in.
You're here again tonight.
lt's all for Carnia, my Queen.
Good, you're getting better now
Thank you very much.
When will you get it. Say ''Master''!
That is how you must answer me.
lt's meaningless if you don't do what l say, Ellene.
Please forgive me, Master.
Okay, show me your loyalty.
Ye, yes, master.
You can't satisfy your customers with just that.
l understand, master.
No, no, no...
What am l doing...
But...
Good, you're doing good.
More...
Feeling...
Something's coming!
Lick it all.
Yes, Master.
What are you doing here?
Please answer me, Princess Eulicia.
l...l....
lf you don't want to tell me, l won't.
l'm going to bring the Queen now and let her punish you.
Please don't.
Please...
Okay, then please tell me, Princess Eulicia.
What were you doing here...
You're well-grounded.
l would love for you to help me out, Princess Eulicia.
Am l going to do what my mother was doing to Claude?