Tucked in the corner of the Cornage Plains, which straddles the continent,
is a country called Carnia.
Red flowers bloom in spring.
Greenery runs to the horizon in summer.
ln autumn are waves of golden fields.
The winter is painted in the pure white of snow.
A beautiful country full of color.
lt gave me dreams and aspirations.
But it deprived me of everything.
The native country l will not forget.
Who ever said,
''Time will heal all wounds.''?
Without paying for sins.
Playing with men's hearts.
Heated.
Aggressive.
A dark black flame.
The mornings of many battles.
The nights of many battles.
Just waiting for the moment.
ln the gloom of my eyes the flame kept burning.
VOLUME 2, UNDERCURRENTS
So you, Princess Eulicia,
as Queen Ellene and Princess Tiaris did,
will fight for Carnia?
Yes, but l have one request.
ls that permitted?
Please ask without hesitation.
Just once,
have sex with me the way normal people do.
Sure l can.
Relax, and leave it all to Claude.
Please, don't be frightened.
Yes.
No!
No.
Not even my father has seen me.
Then let me take my time and take a good look.
Please be gentle.
Claude...
How does it feel?
l'm getting all tingly.
My body is so hot.
That is a natural thing,
Princess Eulicia.
Claude...
What is it?
Please, call me
by my name
Eulicia.
Alright, Eulicia.
My pussy juice is flowing. l'm so wet.
Don't look away. Take a good look.
Do you like it?
lt looks delicious and strong.
Touch it.
Yes.
lt's so thick and hard.
So this is your cock.
Lick my cock.
You want me to lick it?
Yes. A man and a woman must make each other hornier.
Like the way l licked you earlier,
lick my body.
Yes, l will.
Hey, Claude?
What is it?
What a surprise.
You'll get used to it.
Keep licking.
Her time has come.
But what incredible talent.
This is her first time?
She must have inherited this talent
from her stepmother.
Please don't look.
l beg you.
Claude!
Your mouth is being neglectful.
Keep licking it, Eulicia.
You're hot and ready.
Can l pop your cherry?
What?
Oh, yeah.
But how do l do it?
Squat on top of me.
l'll show you the rest.
l'll do whatever you want.
Like this?
Yes.
Let me take away your virginity.
lt's thick!
Slowly lower your ass, Eulicia.
Yes, like this?
lt hurts!
No!
This is what a man is like.
Get used to it.
Now move that ass.
Yes.
lt hurts!
Do you like it? Does it still hurt?
lt hurts, but l'm so horny.
That's good, Eulicia. Don't be scared.
Claude...
My pussy hole is throbbing, Claude!
lt's so hot.
Eulicia...
You're the only one l've fucked like this.
Even Princess Tiaris and Queen Ellene
were never fucked like this.
Yes.
For my country,
l will fuck you like the devil and send you to hell.
Bare with me.
Whatever you want.
Whenever you encounter hardships,
remember tonight.
No, no, yeah!
Claude, thank you so much for fulfilling my desires.
lt went very well.
You've got Princess Eulicia where she's weak.
You've exposed the country's weakness.
And to save the country, the stepmother and older sister
give themselves to you.
You have no choice but to sacrifice your body.
That's no trouble at all.
Even though you're a genius at lewdness,
to drive a virgin that crazy,
requires beauty and evil.
What a dangerous man.
No wonder you were called Master Dale's hidden sword.
Sorry, l was out of line.
Give me your report.
Leiben has stopped their military expansion.
They are awaiting for supplies from their country.
Although they have been achieving consecutive victories,
many of their soldiers
are wanting to go back home.
Also...
General Leberly is having difficulties with aspiring soldiers on the rise.
ls that so? Thank you.
Carry on.
Understood. l will proceed.
What's the matter? Aren't you going to fuck me?
Please wait a little longer.
She should be here soon.
Somebody is coming?
Why did you invite someone at a time like this?
lt seems she is here.
Please come in.
What is the meaning of this?
Why is my mother here?
Today's training requires the help of Queen Ellene.
What?
What are you saying?
As l have just said.
No. Mother, please don't look.
You must look.
Yes.
Do as l say.
l will.
No.
Please, don't look.
Fondle her tits.
But...
Do it!
No, don't.
Mother!
Please, no.
Why...
Stop.
Getting turned on?
l can't be.
Let's see.
Yes, real wet.
Ellene.
Yes?
How is Tiaris' pussy?
Tiaris' pussy is...
Be succinct.
Stop!
Tiaris' pussy is swollen red,
and her pussy juice is flowing from deep inside.
Please stop...
Continue.
Her throbbing swollen clit protrudes.
The pussy juice dripping out of her hole,
glistens and shines.
Please no more. l'll do anything else you say.
Good. Now lubricate her pussy with your mouth for my cock.
What?
Do as l say.
Lick your daughter's pussy.
You mean that?
Can't you love your daughter?
No, mother.
Please dont! You can't do that!
You don't have a say.
l'll have her lick your asshole instead.
Wait, l'll...
l'll stick my tongue in.
Hurry up then.
Good. Lick her cunt real deep.
Peel back her hood and suck her clit.
Yes.
Stop...
What? Cumming already?
No, l'm not.
Your body doesn't lie. Ellene...
Yes.
Suck my cock before l stick it in Tiaris.
Your enthusiasm is admirable,
but your stepdaughter is getting lonely.
l can't take it anymore. l'm losing control.
Don't.
No...
Don't...
You're going to cum.
Put my cock inside her.
You mean that?
lf you don't, she'll go crazy.
No, don't.
Good. That's enough, Ellene.
Now just sit back and watch Tiaris cum.
Yes.
Mother, don't look. Please don't look...
at me cum...cumming.
No.
l'm going to cum.
This can't be happening.
l lost forty percent of my forces?
Yes.
Continue.
The Carnian forces are using mercenaries.
Their unrestrained tactics
have confused our forces and forced us to retreat.
ln addition...
What is it?
There is a rumor amongst the soldiers.
The man leading the mercenaries is identical to Claude.
Claude?
Nonsense.
He is undercover on another assignment.
Firmly tell the soldiers that this is not true!
Understood.
Claude?
lmpossible.
l commend your great efforts
in our recent victory.
The efforts of Claude, in particular, has helped us defeat Leiben.
Please keep fighting for Carnia.
l am grateful for your kind words.
The war will continue.
But tonight, we toast to victory.
The Great Dynasty of Carnia!
To the Great Dynasty of Carnia!
Congratulations for your victory.
We owe it all to you.
Do you think l've grown?
Yes, it's amazing.
That's good.
What about you has really grown?
Claude?
Yes?
l have another reward just for you.
What might that be?
Come this way.
What's the matter, Princess Tiaris?
Why are we here?
Nobody else will come here.
This is...
This is my reward for you.
Tiaris,
you nasty girl.
You really meant this as a reward?
Sorry. l'm just real horny.
l need it bad.
That's what l thought.
And since when have you not worn panties?
l wondered what would happen
if l didn't wear any in public.
And you got too horny?
lt's amazing how nobody noticed how wet you are.
l know. My pussy makes this nasty sound.
My heart is pounding.
lncredible. You really are lewd.
l can't help it.
l need it bad.
l've got to have your dick.
Shove your cock in my pussy!
l guess l'll just have to.
Claude...
More...
Please...
What a nympho.
Claude, you made me what l am.
You're going to blame me?
l'm sorry. Please don't stop.
l've lost interest in this reward.
l refuse.
No, no way. Please don't say that.
Please.
Then serve me like a reward.
Yes.
lt's thick, hard, and beautiful.
Does it feel good?
lt feels good.
l'm so happy.
l can't take it!
Please, stick that cock in my pussy.
l can't take it any longer.
lf l wait any longer, l'll lose my mind.
Alright.
Bend over and show me your ass.
l'll fuck you hard.
Yes.
ls this the way you like it?
Hurry up and stick your cock in my pussy.
Fuck me hard.
No need to rush. Let me give it to you.
lt feels so good.
Why did you stop?
Push your cock in and out more.
l beg you.
Hurry up and fuck me harder.
Make more noise so that the others can hear.
l can't do that.
Let's forget it then.
No. Don't pull it out!
l'll do as you say. Please don't pull it out.
Let's hear it.
Fuck me harder!
Be specific about where you want what.
l want it bad!
Fill my wet hot throbbing cunt with your big fat dick!
Fuck my pussy with your big fat dick!
l beg you!
That's the way l like it.
Take this thick dick.
Oh yeah, l love it.
Harder. Fuck me harder!
Your cock is the best!
Oh no!
l going to cum.
l'm cumming!
You've really gotten good at this.
You're the best of the three.
l know you've been fucking my mother and my little sister.
But...
But what?
This might be selfish, but in your heart, only think of me.
Princess Tiaris, if that is what you desire.
Thank you, Claude.
Oh, King. Sleep a while longer.
Until l dishonor those you love,
and take away this nation from you and make it mine.
No, that's not enough.
l will lead those you love into depravity.
They will become the most vulger women in the world.
Then you too will experience the humiliation
of forever losing those things you protect.