Leave. l need someone who can guarantee a secure life to...
...over fifty thousand employees, and who can build on the trust l have created.
Being related to you is nothing but a hindrance!
No, please don't say that.
Oh my! The amount of money they owe is incredible.
ls this your friend, Master?
What you're basically saying is...
...l have to prove to you that l have people who support me right?
No... Please don't look at me...
Do you?
Do you have even one person who will do anything for you?
lt's only a matter of time until she turns into a slut.
Ow...
Mai?
lt's you, Masaki!
Onii-chan!
Long time no see!
Yeah, how've you been?
Onii-chan.
l always hoped that we could walk home together like this.
l took me a minute to realize it was you.
Women change so much when you don't see them for a while.
l grew my hair out and l've been cheering on the cheerleading squad.
Are you in any clubs?
No. Lately l've been helping my dad with his work.
Your father? That's amazing.
You're going to be the next president, so l guess that makes sense.
What's wrong?
But l have a problem...
A problem?
lt has to do with the Mutsuki Corporate Group.
There's nothing left l can do...
The Mutsuki Group? You mean, my dad's company?
Yeah...
l'll do anything if l can help. Dad will definitely listen to me, so...
l'll help you out.
Really, Mai?
Leave it to me, Onii-chan.
The story is...
...l have to do something about this.
A loan agreement?
Your dad borrowed money from my dad.
lt's past the due date, but he hasn't paid it back. lt's really a bad situation.
My dad? You have to be joking.
l'm telling you the truth, Mai. l have to do something quick.
Can you talk to your dad about it? Please?
Sure! Don't worry. lf my dad can't pay you back, l'll take care of it.
Really...? You'll take care of it?
Ueda.
Here.
Ozaki.
Kanna.
Kanna? Mizuki Kanna?
Kanna is absent? How unusual.
Kimura.
Here, here!
Once will do.
Here.
This time it was too long.
Mai.
Onii-chan! Hi.
What did your dad say about what we talked about last night?
Um... Well...
Could you wait a little longer, for the money?
l had no idea it was such a huge amount of money!
l can't pay you back this second, but l will soon. Please?
Mai, you don't understand what l'm going through.
What do you mean?
lf l don't get that money back soon...
...my father is going to do something terrible to me.
Worst case, l might be killed.
Mai, bye!
See you tomorrow!
Bye! Let's go, Onii-chan.
Okay...
Onii-chan...
lf l sue your dad, you'll lose your home.
You wouldn't want that to happen right?
l don't want to lose my home, but l don't want you to get killed, either.
l... l... l've always loved you...
l've always loved you... Ever since we were kids...
Mai...
lf l can help, l'll do anything.
Really, Mai? You'll do anything?
Onii-chan...
N...no. Onii-chan, stop...
Onii-chan... l don't really understand.
My heart is able to relax when l'm touching your body.
No... Onii-chan, you shouldn't...
You're so sensitive.
You're already wet down here.
You're wrong... l'm not feeling it...
But it's making so much noise.
l don't understand...
Look at how wet you are, Mai.
lt's my first time, but it's okay if it's with you...
You're such a good girl, Mai.
Hold it down with your fingers so l can take a good look.
Yes, just like that.
Does everyone really do this?
This is normal. A woman can't say ''let's have sex'' outright.
That's why they tease like this.
lt feels so good. lt's so strange. l think l'm going to lose my mind...
Onii-chan... Don't stop... Lick my pussy more...
l'll give you something better.
You're going to stick that big thing in?
Mai, don't worry. lt'll feel really good in a second.
lt's inside... Your cock is inside me...
Onii-chan, you're inside...
No, don't move... l... l... l can't take it...
Onii-chan no... Don't move...
l'm going to pee... l'm going to pee...
This is punishment for cumming before me.
l feel it... l feel it... You're fucking me up the ass...
l can feel the shape of your dick...
Onii-chan, do you love me?
Do you love me? Well? Do you?
Of course l do... Mai... You're special to me.
l'm so happy Onii-chan...
Mai, here l come...
Mai, lick it clean with your tongue.
Your dick is so hot...
Hey, it's me.
What? Say something.
You were absent today...
Act a little friendlier, will ya'?
Make sure you come tomorrow.
We're going to have fun tomorrow afternoon.
Come to the archery dojo, and make sure to wear your archery uniform.
lf you don't come, l'll distribute those pictures. Got it?
Afternoon... Archery dojo...
Riko, there's going to be a lot more women soon.
Make sure you organize the files. lt's going to get a lot busier.
Yes. l will keep them organized for you.
So you can find the files anytime...
How dare you tell me to use a condom!
You don't understand your position yet, do you?
l'll train you so you'll learn to never talk like that.
You're terrible... How could you do this...
Are you still embarrassed? You even wore your archery uniform.
Your pussy is wide open.
Please don't...
lt's coming out... .
What are you doing right now?
l'm mastur... l'm masturbating in front of a mirror in the sacred archery dojo...
And?
l'm using my fingers to play with my clit, and...
...there's a lot of cum coming out of my pussy.
My pussy is getting hot...
What color is it?
My pussy is dark pink.
You're a pervert that gets excited when people are watching you.
Look, there's someone else watching you.
No... Don't look at me...
Please... l want your cock... Give me your cock...
Here.
lt feels so good... lt feels so good...
Your cock is so hot... lt's so hot...
lt's so hard... lt's hard like a rock...
Look at how much you're feeling it, you slut.
l'll pound your slut body and l'll pour my cum into you.
Thank you so much. l want lots... l want you to cum all over me inside...
l am your what? Say it.
You're my master.
What are you?
l am a slut who is getting fucked by my master in front of someone.
Thank you for cumming lots. l'm so happy, Master.
That was so good.
Mai...
You're a liar. You said l was special. How could you do that to me?
l'm not lying. You are special.
Liar! Liar! Liar!
SHOWER ROOM
You're really good, Mai. You're so cute. l want to see everything.
l can love everything about you. l'll show you proof that l can.
l'm scared, Onii-chan.
lt's okay Mai...
You're so cute, Mai.
What are you doing, Onii-chan?
No! What is it? What are you sticking in me?
Stop, my stomach is...
lt hurts... lt's going to come out... lt's going to come out...
You're terrible. l hate you...
We've only just begun.
Onii-chan...that's...
lt's an item that proves you're special...
Onii-chan... lt's moving inside me... lt's like a living thing is inside me...
This the first time l've felt this way...
l'm going to go crazy...
l can't anymore... Onii-chan... Onii-chan, l want your cock... Please give it to me.
l can't wait anymore.
Mai, if you want my dick, you need to ask politely.
Master, please fuck me with your penis.
M... Master...
Please fuck me... Please fuck me with your penis... Please...
Good girl.
Onii-chan, it's so big. lt's so big.
l'm going to go crazy.
You're all the way inside me.
Onii-chan, more... Fuck me more...
More... More... Make me wet...
lt feels so good...
Onii-chan, l can't anymore...
l'm going to cum... l'm going to cum...
No... No... l can't anymore...
l love you, Onii-chan.
Did Riko send something?
The data on my women and the sex pictures?
Where did she send them?
To the police?
Riko... What do you think you're doing?
That's for making me suck your nasty cock, you old fart.
Riko! What did you...?
Why did you send those files to the police?
lt's about time you came, you idiot.
What did you say?
An idiot is an idiot.
All l did was tell the cops what you and your dad have been doing.
lsn't it obvious?
What do you mean, ''What we've been doing''?
She sent all the info about your secret connections with politicians...
...and your double books.
What?
And she sent the info on my debt collecting game, and pictures of me in the act.
You guys were surprisingly open with the information, so it was really easy.
Riko, what made you do such a thing?
You asshole... You might not remember me but...
l'm one of the many women you fucked, blackmailed by our debts.
My parents didn't want to go into debt.
Some people don't know how to run a business, and some women...
...were forced into it, believing their parents' debts would be erased.
l was one of those many women.
Just as l thought, l started to work here as a maid and you didn't recognize me.
lt made my life easy, because l was able to look at your double books.
lt did make me laugh when your idiot son started to do the same thing as you.
Your ride's here. Make up your mind.
You've had your way up till now... Aren't you satisfied?
You said it yourself: you can't buy people's hearts...
How dare you, you bitch!
lt's the police. Open the door.
Open the door, Mr. Morikawa. lt's the police. Open the door!