SEARCHlNG
Saint Luchia Academy HP Loading
Saint Luchia Academy HP
Hey Riko.
Yes, Master?
ls this all the information on our targets?
Yes.
They're all rich women from good families.
How'd their parents get millions of dollars into debt?
l don't know... Times are tough.
Riko, turn up the volume.
Yes, Master.
When my dad disowned me l was taken aback, but...
l never thought this would turn into such a fun game. lt's better than l thought.
You idiot!
There's no need to yell like that. All l did was borrow your car...
Well, l did get into a minor accident but...
You don't have a license.
On top of that...
...you plowed into someones house and the other person in the car has severe whiplash.
And the cops are involved because you damaged private property.
You should be thankful no one's dead!
Do you have any idea what you've done? Do you have any regrets?
Do you have any idea of my position when you do things like this?
Of course l do. You're the Don of the construction industry and...
...you're the president of three academies, Sir, Sir, Sir, Sir...
That's right. l was able to pay them off this time, but if someone...
...had lost a finger or something, it would have been disastrous.
Don't you understand that?
Plus, when was the last time you went to the academy? Months ago?
Why are you always like this? You don't regret anything.
l've thought about this for a while... Although you're my son...
...you are unfit to inherit the Morikawa Family fortune.
l'm disowning you!
Leave. l need someone who can guarantee a secure life to...
...over fifty thousand employees, and who can build on the trust l have created.
l have no use for someone as reckless as you.
Being related to you is nothing but a hindrance!
Wait, dad... What you're basically saying is...
...you want to see me with a lot of people who support me right?
Do you have any?
Do you have even one person who will do anything for you?
Of course l do! There are a ton of people who would...
Without money involved? Money will make people do anything.
Even pathetic idiots can have money.
l'm going to take away your allowance and credit cards until further notice.
lf you want money...
These are the invoices that l figure l'll never see the money from.
See if you can collect the money.
Prove to me that you have the ability to manage people.
lf you were lying to me... You understand what l'm saying, right?
Master.
Master, if you don't go to bed soon, you'll be late for class.
Can't you tell l'm busy right now?
l really need you to go tomorrow, or else l'm going to have problems.
By your father's orders, this place will be cleaned out... Even the people...
Here's your pajamas.
Oh my! The amount of money they owe is incredible.
ls this your friend, Master?
What?
This is the company your classmate's father operates.
Really?
Oh my, it's in the millions.
What do you mean?
There are a lot of students at your father's academy...
...who are heirs to big name companies that owe money to your father's business.
lt's nothing out of the ordinary, but in such tough times...
...if they were billed this much, it wouldn't be good.
So that's the connection. This sounds like fun.
Oh really?
Riko! Find out who goes to my father's academy from those bills. Right now!
Yes! l'm so happy that you're interested in classes again!
l'll use this to blackmail them and have my way with them.
l'll make it so they have to listen to me.
Did you hear? The president's idiot son is here!
lt's probably because he doesn't have enough attendance.
Okay, sit down.
l'm taking attendance. Everyone sit down.
TO MlZUKl
Hi. Sorry l made you meet me.
Masaki, you're coming to class again.
l was wondering what happened to you.
Yeah, l've been busy with a lot of stuff.
l'm helping my dad with his work now.
That's why l couldn't come to school.
But isn't your father the president of this academy...
...and the president of a giant corporation?
We're the same age and you're helping his work? That's amazing.
l bet l would only get in my dad's way.
What do you want to be?
This is so embarrassing... l want to become a nurse.
l like taking care of people, and l want to do good for society, so...
How about you? What do you want to be?
Me? l want to be...
A debt collector!
There are a bunch of bastards who won't pay up because...
...we're in the middle of a recession. lt's troubling me.
What do you think, Mizuki?
What do l think?
You return what you borrow by a certain date.
That's the obvious thing to do in society, right?
Y...yes.
Yeah, not giving back what you borrowed is like stealing.
lt's terrible.
Yes, it is.
The reason l asked you to come is...
CONTRACT
Do you know what this is?
The one who borrowed money is your father.
Apparently, your father says he can't return it...
...with the current financial state of his company.
Y...you're lying!
Stop saying such things! My father would never build such debt!
You may be the academy president's son, but this has gone too far.
How am l supposed to believe something like this?
Really? Then what are you going to do if it's true?
Go ask your father directly. You're in for a reality check.
l'll be waiting here tomorrow afternoon.
By then, l'm sure you'll figure out l'm not lying.
Let's continue our chat tomorrow.
What's wrong? Why are you so down?
You don't look so well. Are you okay?
Yeah, you're not yourself. You should go home if you're not feeling well.
Do you want me to tell the teacher?
l've been waiting for you.
Judging by the way you look, it wasn't what you expected, huh?
So, when are you going to pay us back?
Can you wait a little longer?
My father's working day and night trying to rebuild the company.
lt wouldn't be right if the company is forced to go out of business.
Once the company gets on track we can pay you back.
Would it be possible for you to wait a little longer?
How long am l supposed to wait?
A year or two...
We're not getting anywhere...
l'm going to call your dad and collect the money right now.
Wait, please!
l'll do anything.
l don't care what happens to me, so please wait a little longer.
You'll do anything? Anything?
Yeah, l guess you have no choice...
lt's for your father's company... Your father's...
No...
Yeah, right. Your nipples are hard.
No, please don't say that.
lf your nipples get hard with this... l wonder what'll happen...
...if l pet you down there?
You're wet already. Wanna see?
Now it's my turn to have fun.
Wait, not that. l don't want to... l want my first time to be special.
Are you sure? Some people are gonna go through rough times if you refuse.
lf it's your first, you should try to enjoy it.
No...
Here's a present for your grand opening! This one's for you! lt's a big load!
You can't... No! Don't!
Good job.
What are you going to use this for?
l'm goin' to class.
SCHOOL lNFlRMARY
What do you want? Why did you call me here?
l have a favor to ask. l want you to put this on.
That's...
You want to be a nurse right? l'm sure it'll look good.
But... l refuse!
Why? lf you have to pay what you owe...
...you won't be able to pursue your dreams...
Now do you remember your place?
Well?
How do you feel?
Are you having fun humiliating me?
Don't get me wrong. l'm trying to make your dream come true.
Aren't you happy? You're a nurse now.
That's...
You want to do good for society, right? l'm sure you'll help me out.
Where should l examine first?
Look how it grew!
No...
You're wet from me fondling your breasts? You're such a perverted nurse.
Nurse, l have a question.
Why is your mouth down there drooling so much?
Why does it make funny noises down here when l play with it?
Nurse, can you make funny noises down here?
All l did was play with it a little and it's dripping wet.
Are you sure you've never done anything until yesterday?
l should examine it closely.
No!
So that's how it looks inside!
Please stop.
l wonder if it'll open up more. Oh! lt opened up! How about a little more?
Stop this...
l can see all the way in. This is amazing!
Don't look at me...
You're getting wetter, you dirty bitch.
l'll use this to finish you off. You'll go crazy from the pleasure.
What did you put on me?
lt's...getting hot...
...lt feels strange...
How strange does it feel? Say it.
Look at that face on you. You want it so bad.
This is what you want, isn't it?
Your pussy is so tight. lt's sucking me in. You wanted it bad, didn't you?
No... You're wrong...
The popular girl with good grades from our class...
...got raped in a classroom and is role-playing in the infirmary...
lf the guys from our class found out they'd be blown away!
No...
lt's a good photo opportunity, so let's take pictures.
No... Don't take pictures!
lf l upload this to the internet, you'll be an overnight sensation.
No! Please don't do that.
l'm going to cum. l'm going to cum.
You came when you got your picture taken.
You're a real submissive bitch. There must be something wrong with you.
lt's only a matter of time untll she turns into a slut.
l'll keep cornering her, and in the end l'll...
Ow... Be careful! Watch where you're going!
Ow... Don't look!
Onii-chan? Are you Mr. Morikawa's son, Masaki?
Mai?
lt's you Masaki! Long time no see!
Yeah, how've you been?
lt's been so long. How are you doing?
lt's really been a while since l've seen you. l'm doing well. Very well.
Onii-chan.