From: Segawa Asaka | To: Segawa Shunsuke | Shun-kun
This spring break you've got to, got to come home!
Looks like for spring break this year I'm going
to be toyed around by my sisters...
Shun-kun! Welcome back!
Asaka-neesan...
As expected I can feel really secure
from hugging Shun-kun!
That's enough right, Asa-nee?
Welcome back, Shunsuke! How does sis'
chest feel after being away for so long?
Feels good, right?
Wait, Tsukino-neesan...
Here, here!
Tsuki-nee! It's my turn now!
I get it, Yuki.
Welcome back, Shun!
Yuki-neesan!
I haven't seen Shun for so long!
I can't take it anymore!
Hey! That's no fair, Asa-nee!
Hey...
Shun-kun!
Shunsuke!
Shun!
Shun-kun? Thank goodness, you're awake.
Geez, finally up, huh?
Shun, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine...
Shun-kun... I have a favor to ask...
Huh?
Shun-kun... um... we...
We want Shun-kun's sperm!
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: Nicolai | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
My Sister that are Perverted  and Busty
In the Case of Asaka-Neesan
Shunsuke... please listen without getting surprised...
All three of us sisters have caught
a disease of unknown source.
Disease?
You guys are all sick? That's...
Note: A medical certificate indicating that the sisters have
been diagnosed with idiopathic estrus syndrome.
But... why are we doing this?
Shun-kun... the disease we have causes
us to go into heat without control.
There's only one way to cure this disease!
To cure this disease, we have to
take a male's sperm regularly...
Regular Intake of a male's sperm
Yes?
If you don’t help us, we could
possibly die from this disease!
Shun, please give us your sperm!
Shun-kun... please...
Wait, wait! You don't have to do these
kinds of things with a sibling to...
If you don't help us, we'll end up having sex
with someone we don't know every day!
There's no way I'd do that!
Me too... rather than doing it with a stranger...
I want to do it with Shun-kun!
Shun-kun's the only one I'd do it with!
Me too... I don't want to take the
sperm of anyone other than you...
I want Shun’s semen, too!
Hey, wait...
Even if you say no, we're completely in heat...
So we'll be getting you to give us the semen we need.
That's...
Besides, your body is reacting to our bodies, anyway.
This is Shun-kun's...
So it gets this large...
Shunsuke's penis is really hard!
Amazing... sorry, Shun-kun, I can’t stop anymore...
It's your first time getting a titty fuck, right?
Shun, does it feel good?
It's really hot, and it's twitching...
That's the proof that he’s feeling really good.
Something is coming out of the tip!
Amazing... it can still get larger!
Hmm? Are you cumming?
Coming? You mean the semen?
Let it out, Shun!
You let out lots, didn't you?
The smell is amazing...
So this is... Shun-kun's semen...
What was with that yesterday?
A dream? That's right, it was a dream wasn't it?
There's no way something like
this could happen in reality.
Good morning, Shun-kun!
It wasn't a dream...
Thank you for the medicine yesterday.
Asaka-neesan... could it be that...
Yeah... it seems like it...
What do I do?
Please!
Help me, Shun-kun!
Can I squeeze it in between, Shun-kun?
Shun-kun's it getting really hot...
Just wait, I'll lubricate it with my saliva...
Sorry for putting something like spit all over it...
But if I don't it'll hurt for Shun-kun...
Shun-kun's is shimmering from my saliva... it's so lewd...
I'm... doing it outside... sorry for
being such a naughty sister.
Shun-kun's is getting hard between my boobs...
Amazing... it's still getting larger!
If it's this large, you'll definitely let out lots, right?
Shun-kun's semen... it's so thick!
It's sticking onto my tongue and
I can't swallow very well...
And it's got such a strong smell...
More... give me more of your sperm... Shun-kun...
Hey, wait, Haruka!
Hey...
I, I saw what happened!
Yesterday... Onii-chan and Onee-chan...
were doing perverted things right?
That was because... um...
If you can do perverted things with Onee-chan, then...
Then as your childhood friend I want
to do those things with you, too!
Onee-chan was doing this to Onii-chan's thing...
Do you feel good, Onii-chan?
Am I doing this right?
Should I just keep doing it like this?
Onii-chan’s thing is very thick and sturdy!
If I do this, my body becomes hot, too
Maybe Onii-chan's heat is passing over.
Something is coming out of Onii-chan's thing's tip...
Does the tip feel good, too?
Onii-chan, is there anything wrong
with how I'm doing this?
Haruka's titty fuck feels really good...
I'm very happy! Onii-chan is feeling it from my titty fuck...
I want to... make you feel it... more...
There's so much of Onii-chan's semen...
So you let out this much...
Did Haruka's boobs feel good, Onii-chan?
Yeah, of course.
That's great to hear!
I'm... I'm sorry, Shun-kun, I can't endure anymore...
I want Shun-kun's semen!
When rubbing Shun-kun's with
my boobs... I feel good, too!
Shun-kun's is really hot!
It feels like... I'm getting hot too... and I can’t stop!
Do you feel good, Shun-kun?
Shun-kun's is moving between my
boobs... my body is tingling!
It's so happy from doing this with
Shun-kun, it's getting turned on!
It feels good! No... I can feel it... my
body is so hot it's going crazy!
I'm sorry for being... such a slutty sister...
You came a lot, didn't you? I'm so happy, Shun-kun.
Asaka-neesan... what are you doing?
You can keep going right?
Just drinking it when you let it out
isn't enough for me anymore...
It’s my first time so I might not be doing
very well but... I'll do my best.
Shun-kun’s is going inside me! Amazing, it's so large...
It's completely filling me up...
I shouldn't... shouldn't be doing
this but... I can't stand it!
I'm sorry for having no self-restraint!
I got...Shun-kun to take my virginity...
It's rubbing.. It's rubbing inside!
It hurt a bit... much there's so much stimulation...
Shun-kun... I might be feeling good from this...
It’s my first time... and yet I'm moving
my hips feeling a lot from it...
It's so slutty... I'm really embarrassed!
Amazing... Shun-kun's is thrusting deep inside of me!
There's nothing slutty about it, Asaka-neesan!
Really? If Shun-kun says so, I won't
have to worry about it, right?
Because... the erotic Asaka-neesan... is really cute!
Geez, Shun-kun. Cute was supposed
to be something we say to you!
But you've grown up so much
in no time... it's incredible...
Nee-san, I'm going to...
I shouldn't let you cum inside...
but I don’t want you to pull out!
It's flowing in... so much... even though
I'd get a baby if you came inside...
The proof of my deflowering is mixing
up with Shun-kun's semen...
And Shun-kun is still really hard inside me...
It's like my mind is going blank... I can't think anymore...
It feels good! Shun-kun's is rubbing so much
inside me, I think I'm going to cum!
Can I? Can I cum? Something is coming!
It's huge but I think we'll get it here!
Nee-san, I'm going to...
It's fine, let it out where you want!
I want to cum inside like this!
You like it inside? If you cum anymore,
I could get Shun-kun's baby...
But... but I... I want it inside, too!
Shun-kun, you're so rough! No, I'll cum!
Shun-kun's semen... the basis for
a child... is filling my insides...
I might get pregnant...
Asaka-neesan!
Huh? Wait, not now!
Um...
Welcome in!... just kidding?
Um, this is... um, you I just thought um... I could
wear cute clothes like these once in a while, too!
Um, yeah... they're quite cute. Well then, I'm off...
What, Nee-san?
I got in heat... from Shun-kun seeing
me in these... it seems...
So sturdy!
Wait, Asaka-neesan...
No way! I'm in heat, after all.
It's Shun-kun's fault, so please take responsibility...
That's...
It's hot and pulsing... I can't hold back anymore!
I'm getting more daring and perverted just from
looking at Shun-kun's pleasured expression!
Is my titty fuck getting better?
Don't ask when you already know the answer...
But I don't know! Shun-kun has to tell me clearly...
You are, you're getting better, Nee-san!
Yay! Then shall I work harder?
It's making squeaky noises, are you about to cum?
It's fine, let it out! Let Onee-chan drink lots of thick stuff!
It's coming out! There's so much...
I'm happy you felt so good from this.
But...
Even if I drink the semen, I'm not
getting out of heat at all...
Let me drink more of Shun-kun's tasty semen!
Fill my mouth up with your semen!
Shun-kun's thing is shivering... It's
shaking from wanting to cum!
Let it out! Wash away my heat with your perverted milk!
Semen!
Semen tastes so good...
More, more! This isn't enough... can you
cum more? You can cum more, right?
I... I'm not satisfied...
Let this part of me drink it this time.
I can't take it anymore. I want
more and more of Shun-kun!
It's tight... but... it feels really good!
It's twitching inside!
No... I'm really feeling it...
I'm showing my embarrassing side to Shun-kun...
I'm embarrassed... but my hips won't stop...
I'm getting so sensitive; I can make
out Shun-kun's shape down there...
I'm gonna cum!
It's fine, let me drink lots!
Shoot it directly into my perverted womb!
So much is flowing in! My womb is filling up...
Semen... so much is flowing in... it feels good!
More... I want more... of Shun-kun's semen...
Semen is slippery and making noises inside!
Again... so much of Shun-kun's
semen is inside me... it's hot!
Shun-kun's body temperature... is sinking into my body...
Please, it's not stopping yet!
My womb is going to break!
So rough... if you do it that much, I'll melt down there!
I think I’m melting down there... no... I...
Cumming again!
Let it out where you want!
I'm cumming inside again!
If you cum inside again, I'll get Shun-kun’s baby...
But I want it inside!
Shun-kun's semen... won't fit in my womb anymore...
It's flowing out from that place....
Such a waste...
It's going numb... my body is really feeling it...
No... I shouldn't be doing this in Shun-kun’s room...
Here... if I hit this place... No! It's too strong but...
No... it feels good!
No... I can't do this... on Shun-kun's bed... but... I...
Why? Why am I so slutty?
My nipples are so hard, and I'm
drenched down here, too...
But, I can't stop! I want more!
Coming... coming... I can't... I’m cumming!
I'm cumming from masturbating on Shun-kun’s bed!
No... it's just not enough... what do I do...
Then, it's my job to calm you, right?
Shun-kun! How long have you... how
long have you been watching!?
I'll help calm the disease of Asaka-neesan.
Please, Shun-kun.
It's coming in...
More... come in more, Shun-kun.
Shun-kun’s Is the best! It's completely
different from the toys!
Just a little more... it'll hit the deepest... part...
So deep! It hit the deepest part!
Come! Thrust hard!
Amazing... it's so rough... I’ll make noises...
I’ll make embarrassing noises...
But... I can't stop... it feels too good!
It feels so much better than doing it alone!
Shun-kun's is hot and it feels good!
Nee-san you're squeezing so hard I...
It's fine, let it out! I want Shun-kun's semen like this!
Ejaculate while you're deep inside!
It's coming deep inside! Shun-kun’s semen...
It's coming out, right? Shun-kun's semen
is flowing deep inside my womb...
Shun-kun's is still hard inside me!
You're cumming inside... and yet my hips won't stop!
I'm sorry, my body is moving on its own!
Shun-kun, please, more, I want
more! This isn't enough at all!
I'm sorry for being so naughty,
but I can't stop getting in heat!
Shun-kun, more, more... move more roughly...
Please, Shun-kun, give your semen to your naughty sister!
This is embarrassing, but please stir up your
slutty sister's insides more and more!
Please! Thrust lots and lots with Shun-kun large thing!
More! Do it more roughly!
It's coming... Shun-kun's large thing is coming...
So thick! Amazing! Thrust more!
It feels good! Shun-kun's is so hot!
It's so hot my mind is going blank!
No... I'm feeling it so much already,
if you do any more I'll go crazy!
That place... is being spread open by Shun-kun!
I'm so happy... please fill me
up with Shun-kun! Shun-kun!
More!
No... I'm going to... cum already... so... you
can cum when you want, Shun-kun...
No... I can't...I'm...Shun-kun, something
incredible is coming!
I'm going to cum...
Cum, Shun-kun! Cum together with me like this!
I'm cumming inside like this!
You're cumming inside again? If you do
it anymore... I'll really get pregnant!
It's coming out... so much of Shun-kun's
semen is coming out...
I can't drink all of it anymore...
I'm definitely going to get pregnant...
Hmm? Did I wake you up, Shun-kun?
Asaka-neesan?
We did it all night after that,
and you're still not satisfied?
Yeah... it's hardly enough...
Shun-kun even fell asleep...
But Shun-kun's can get hard even when you're
sleeping and it can let out lots, so...
I drank lots of Shun-kun's medicine.
I'm sorry for being such a naughty sister...
I'm sorry, but my heat isn't going away at all!
So... so please...Shun-kun...
Shun-kun's semen...
Give me more...
It feels good I No... my body is still pulsing
and yet...Shun-kun's is getting large again!
Are you cumming? Are you letting
out semen? Let out lots!
Let out lots of semen I Calm down Onee-chan!
Shun-kun's semen tastes so good!
Asa-nee! Shunsuke doesn't belong
to only Asa-nee you know!
That's not fair, Asa-nee!
You've been making loud sounds
non-stop since last night!
And ruining sleep...
That's because... my heat wouldn't stop and...
After hearing those sounds Asa-nee made...
You got me in heat, too!
Now I'm in heat, too!
Well I still haven't calmed down either!
Shunsuke...
Shun...
Shun-kun...
Please give me your semen!
koishitara kinou made no kimi wa kawareru kara
If you fall in love, then everything  about you up
until yesterday, will be completely changed.
cho ippo fumidasu nosa yuuki dashite
So please bring out your courage, and take that one step forward.
tsukanaisou no kimi wa poker face
Aren't you tired of that poker face?
Warui koto iwanai kara
I wan't talk ill, so...
atashi no atsui mune ni
with this warm chest of mine...
mou akiramete dakarenasai
Please give up and me huge you.
me wo sorasanaide kawaii shy boy
Don't look away may shy boy.
mou wakatterunn dakara
I know what are thinking.
atashi no yokomete mite
You're looking at me from aside,
mousou shiterudeshou nainane
and daydreaming, aren't you?
hen ne irorawamakuri no
It's strange, that in this dramatic world
dorama no hi no inma
All different things have underlying connections of fate.
atashi no kyara nai noni kimi wo
It's not really my thing but,
zutto oikaketeru
I'll keep chasing for you.
kisetsu no kaze no you ni atashi wo surinukeru
Like the wind of the seasons, you fly right past me.
You speak an I'll kimi wo kitto tsukamaeru wa
Say the word, and I'll definitely catch you.
koishitara kinou made no kimi wa kawareru kara
If you fall in love, then everything about you up
until yesterday, will be completely changed.
cho ippo fumidasu nosa yuuki dashite
So please bring out your courage, and take that one step forward.
hohoende my boy
Please smile, my boy.
atashi dake ni
Smile only to me.