Sender: Segawa Asaka | Receiver: Segawa Shunsuke | To Shun-kun
During your summer vacation this year,
you absolutely,
absolutely have to be home, okay?
Looks like I'm going to be a play thing for my
?sisters for this year's summer vacation.
Shun-kun!
Welcome home!
Asaka-neesan.
It feels really relieving to hug you like this.
That's enough already Asa-nee.
Welcome back, Shunsuke.
How do I feel after a long time?
Feels good, right?
Hey, Tsukino-neesan!
There, there!
Tsuki-nee, I'm next.
Alright already, Yuki.
Welcome home, Shun.
Yuki-neesan.
We haven't met in a long time.
I can't hold it anymore.
Hey, that's unfair Asa-nee!
Hey!
Shun-kun.
Shun.
Shun-kun!
Thank goodness, are you awake now?
Finally, you're awake.
Are you okay, Shun?
Yeah, I'm alright.
Shun-kun, I have a request.
Shun-kun... you see...
We...want to have your cum!
What?!
My big and horny sisters
Asaka-neesan’s situation
Shunsuke, I want you to stay calm as I say this.
The three of us actually touched upon a rare disease.
Eh?
A disease?
Diagnosis
Ayakawa Asaka, Ayakawa Tsukino, Ayakawa Yuki
The following people are diagnosed
with Sudden Sexual Arousal Syndrome
All of you? That can't be...
B-but...
Why are you doing this?
Shun-kun.
This disease makes us sexually aroused
?regardless of our current mental state.
There is only one way to cure this.
To cure this, we need to take in an adequate
?amount of a man's semen regularly.
an adequate amount of a man's semen regularly
What?
If you don't help us,
we might die because of this disease.
Shun, give us your cum please.
Shun-kun, I beg you.
J-Just wait a sec!
That doesn't mean us siblings have to do it!
But if you don't do it for us,
that'd mean we would be doing it
?for just any beastly man out there.
I definitely don't want that.
Me too.
Instead of doing it with someone I don't know,
I want to do it with you instead!
No, I definitely won't want it if it's not you.
Even I also don't want to take semen other than yours.
It's Shun's cum for me.
Just wait a minute.
Even if you don't want to,
we're in a rut right now, so we'd still try to get it anyway.
That can't be...
Besides...
Your body is properly reacting to our bodies already.
So this is Shun-kun's...
So it becomes big like this.
Shunsuke's dick sure is stiff.
Oh wow.
I'm sorry, Shun-kun.
I can't stop anymore.
It's your first time experiencing a tit fuck, right?
Does it feel good, Shun?
It feels really hot and twitchy.
It's proof that he's feeling great.
Something is dripping from its tip.
Wow, it's still getting bigger.
What, are you about to cum?
Cum? So he's about to release it?
Just cum, Shun.
You really came a lot, huh.
It has a strong smell.
So this is Shun-kun's cum.
What was that yesterday?
A dream.
That's right, it was just a dream.
That just can't be real.
Good morning, Shun-kun.
It wasn't a dream.
Thanks for giving us our medication last night.
Asaka-neesan, could you be...
Yeah, it seems so.
What should I do?
Please, Shun-kun, help me out!
Can we play for a bit, Shun-kun?
Okay.
It's starting to feel really hot.
Just wait there.
I'm going to lubricate it with my spit.
Sorry for putting spit on it like this.
But it'd feel painful for you if I didn't.
Look, your thing is getting sandwiched between my bust.
That looks horny.
And we're doing it outside.
Sorry for being a lewd sister.
Your thing is getting harder between my breasts.
Amazing, and it’s still getting bigger.
If it's this big, it's sure to release a lot of cum, right?
Your cum, it's really odorous.
It gets stuck on my tongue, so I can't swallow it perfectly.
Also, it has a really strong smell.
Give me more of your cum please, Shun-kun.
Hold on a sec, Haruka!
Hey!
I saw it.
You were doing something indecent
?with Onee-chan yesterday, right?
That's, well...
If you can do indecent stuff with your Onee-chan,
then you can also do the same with your childhood friend, right?
Onee-chan was doing this to you.
Onii-chan, does it feel good?
Am I doing well?
Should I continue?
Your thing feels really thick and sturdy.
While I do this, my body is also starting to feel hot.
Seems like your heat is being transferred to me.
Something is coming out from the tip.
Does this part feel good too?
Onii-chan, am I doing it right?
Your tit fuck feels very great.
I'm happy.
That you're feeling aroused with my tit fuck.
I want you to feel aroused more.
There's lots of your cum.
So it comes out like this.
Onii-chan, did my breasts feel good?
Yeah, of course.
That's great.
Sorry about this, Shun-kun.
I can't hold it anymore.
I want to have your cum.
And it also feels good for me to do it with my breasts.
Your thing feels really hot.
It feels like I'm also feeling hot.
I just can't stop.
Does it feel good, Shun-kun?
Your thing is trying to move between my breasts.
My body is starting to feel tingly.
I feel so happy doing this with you, that I'm starting to feel horny.
It feels good.
Oh no, I'm really getting horny.
I feel so hot that I might just go crazy from it.
Sorry for being an indecent sister.
Lots came out.
I'm happy, Shun-kun.
Asaka-neesan, what are you doing?
You can still cum, right?
I can't endure just making it cum like that anymore.
This is my first time,
don't know if I can do it well.
But, I'll try my best.
You're now inside me, Shun-kun.
It's really big.
It totally fills me up inside.
We shouldn't do this, and yet...
Sorry, your sister just wasn't able to hold herself back.
I just had my virginity taken by Shun-kun.
No, it’s rubbing inside.
My insides are getting rubbed.
It hurts,
but this sensation...
Shun-kun, I think I'm starting to feel good already.
It’s my first time, and yet I feel aroused,
?moving my hips on my own.
This is just indecent.
I'm ashamed.
Amazing!
Your thing is penetrating my very insides.
This is nothing indecent, Asaka-neesan.
Really?
If you say so, then I can keep doing it without worries, right?
That's because, this horny you is very cute.
J-jeez, oh Shun-kun.
Cute is a word that we usually use for you.
Now, you're all grown up.
Feels somewhat strange, right?
Nee-san, I'm about to...!
You're not supposed to cum inside me,
but I just can't take it out.
You came lots inside.
I might even get pregnant from this and yet...
My virgin blood and your cum is mixing together inside.
And your thing is still stiff inside.
My mind is starting to go blank.
I'm starting to lose sight of my surroundings.
It feels so good.
I'm going to cum if you continue rubbing inside me.
Are you listening?
I'm going to cum.
Something is coming.
It feels like my mind has been taken
?somewhere else by your big thing.
Nee-san, I'm about to cum again.
It's okay.
Just cum however you want to.
I want to cum inside.
You want to cum, Inside?
But if you do that I might get pregnant.
B-But... But, I...
I also want it inside.
Shun-kun, this is so intense!
Oh no, it s going in...!
Your cum...
It's all inside my womb.
I might get pregnant.
Asaka-neesan.
Wait, right now I’m..!
Umm...
Welcome!
...or something like that.
Actually Shun-kun, this is...
I just thought that it was cute so I tried putting it on.
Y-yeah, I think it's really cute.
I'll be leaving then.
What is it, nee-san?
I became sexually aroused,
after you saw me...
It seems...
This is fun.
Hey, Asaka-neesan...
Nope.
I'm feeling horny already.
It's your fault, so take responsibility for this, okay?
No way...
It's hot and throbbing.
I can't take it anymore.
Just seeing your ecstatic face already makes me more daring.
And more horny.
Is my tit fuck getting better?
You're the one who knows that better than I.
That's not true, I don't have any idea.
if you don't say it clearly...
It’s getting better, nee-san.
I'm glad.
Then I'll try even harder.
It's making sloppy sounds.
Are you about to cum?
It's okay, release it.
Let me drink more of that smelly stuff.
There it is!
You came lots.
I'm happy that you're getting aroused like this.
But...
...even if I drink your cum,
my sexual arousal doesn't go down.
I want to drink more.
I want you to fill my mouth with more of your cum.
Your thing is trembling.
It wants to release it.
Cum please.
Wash away these horny feelings with your cum.
Your cum...
It tastes great.
This is still not enough.
Just this won't be enough.
Can you still cum?
You can still cum, right?
I'm not satisfied yet.
This time, fill me in here.
I can't hold myself any longer.
I want more of you.
It feels tight!
But, it feels good.
Your thing is twitching inside.
Oh no, I'm getting really horny.
You're completely seeing my embarrassing side.
This is really embarrassing.
But my hips won't stop.
I'm now very sensitive.
I can even feel the shape of your thing inside me.
Hey, I'm about to cum!
It's okay.
Make me drink lots down there.
Pour it all deep inside me.
Lots of it is flowing inside.
Your cum is filling me up.
Lots of it is still coming out.
And it feels great.
More, I want more of your cum.
It's making me all sticky and wet!
Lots of your cum came out inside again.
It feels hot!
Your fluids are seeping deep inside my body.
Please, I just can't stop yet!
My womb is about to break.
This is intense.
If you continue doing this,
I'm going to melt down there.
You're going to rip it all apart.
But, I'm still...I'm about to...
I'm going to cum again.
Just cum however you want to.
I'm cumming inside again.
I'm going to get cummed inside again.
I'll get pregnant with your baby!
But, I still want it.
I want it inside me.
Your cum...
My womb is already completely filled.
It just overflows outside.
What a waste.
It feels all tingly.
My body is getting aroused.
Oh no, I shouldn't be doing this in Shun-kun's room.
Here.
Whenever I hit this spot...
No, it's already very stimulating for me.
It really feels good.
I'm not supposed to be doing this on his bed.
Why...
Why am I this horny?
I'm even pinching my nipples like this.
I want this hot feeling to go away.
But I can't stop!
I still want more.
Something is coming.
Is coming!
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum on Shun-kun's bed,
while playing with myself.
Oh no.
This isn't enough.
What should I do?
Then, I just have to make you satisfied, right?
Shun-kun! Since when were you...
Since when were you watching me?
I want to make your disease go away.
Please do.
It's going in.
More, push it more inside me.
Your thing is really the best.
Totally different from those sex toys.
Push a bit more, you're nearly at the deepest end.
It's really deep!
It's at the very end.
Now push forward and back.
Amazing.
The intensity makes sloppy noises.
It makes those really embarrassing noises.
But, I can't stop.
It feels really good.
Compared to masturbating, the sensation is completely different.
Your thing is very hot and feels great.
Nee-san, you're gripping me very tightly.
It's okay.
Just cum.
I want to have your cum.
Release it while it's very deep inside me.
Your cum is pouring inside!
It's coming out, right?
Your cum is reaching inside my womb.
Your thing is still very stiff inside me.
I'm being cummed inside, and yet my hips still won't stop.
Sorry, my body just moves on its own.
Shun-kun, I want more of you.
This is still not enough.
I'm sorry if I'm this horny.
My arousal just won't settle down.
Move more strongly, Shun-kun.
Please, Shun-kun.
Please give your horny big sister more cum!
Stir up the insides of your indecent big sister!
Please, rub your big thing more inside me!
Thrust it in more intensely!
Your big thing is entering me!
It's penetrating me whole!
Wow, it's so thick...
Rub it in more.
It feels good.
And it feels really hot.
I'll lose control if you continue penetrating me like that.
This can't be, I'm already feeling very horny and yet...
I'll go crazy if you keep on hitting my soft spots like that.
Your thing is widening up my hole!
I'm happy.
Fill me up, Shun-kun.
Shun-kun, do it more...
I'm about to cum.
So you can cum whenever you want, okay?
Oh no, I'm already...
Shun-kun, something big is coming.
I'm about to cum.
Cum, Shun-kun.
Let's cum together.
I'm going to cum inside.
Are you going to cum inside again?
If you cum any more inside,
I'm really going to get pregnant!
It's coming out...
Lots of your cum is flowing out.
I can't take it all in anymore.
I'm definitely pregnant now.
Shun-kun, did I wake you up?
Asaka-neesan?
We already did it the entire night the other day,
yet you're still feeling horny?
Yeah, it's still not enough.
You fell asleep in the middle of it.
But, it still becomes big even when
?you're asleep, and even cums a lot.
So I drank lots of it.
Sorry for being a slutty big sister, Shun-kun.
Sorry for this, it's just that my arousal won't go down.
That's why... that's why, Shun-kun...
Give me more of your cum, please?
Ehh?
This feels great.
N-No...
My body is still tingly all over.
It's completely filling me up inside.
Is it about to come out?
Cum lots of it.
I want you to cum a lot.
Treat my sickness with it.
Your cum...it tastes delicious.
Asa-nee!
Shunsuke isn't just yours, you know!
Asa-nee, that's unfair.
I heard you moan all night the other day.
I wasn't able to sleep.
Well that's...
That’s because my arousal won't go down.
Hearing that voice of yours
made me sexually aroused too!
Me too, I feel horny now.
Even I am still feeling aroused right now.
Ehh?
Shunsuke.
Shun.
Shun-kun.
Give us your cum, please.