Demon Busters, make up!
For love and justice!
The pretty idol soldiers.
Demon Busters!
H-Hey, Sensei. What is this?
We've never done this before.
You fool. It's called anime.
We should offer this kind of service too, you know.
B-But, it is embarrassing...
in more ways than one
Quit your whining! We're just getting started!
What?
Hi there! Demon Busters starts now!
Oh evil creatures, begone!
Demon Barrier!
It's my turn!
Royal Lovely Suite:
Demon Flush!
Insta-Kill:
Buster Sword, Miracle Rainbow!
Slice arid dice!
I'll finish this.
Fire up! Dynamite Flame Wheel!
Victory is ours, mostly thanks to me.
This is kinda embarrassing.
Oh, come on.
It's fun! It's like we're heroes or something!
W-Well, we defeated all of them, at least.
That's what you think.
T-Tentacles?
I-It's no good.
I can't break free.
Damn.
I didn't expect the boss to show up.
I've been waiting all this time for
all of you to use up your mana.
Wait, this voice...
Are you... Kou-kun?!
I'm sure you didn't expect
that I would be the boss.
I've been really interested
in tentacle play lately.
What?!
No!
They're melting! My clothes are melting!
Please don't look, Senpai.
Man! This is what I'm talking about!
I've always wanted to do this!
Geez... Kou-kun, you pervert.
If you wanted to see me naked,
you should've just asked.
Th-This isn't right!
I-It's no good!
If I get any more of this weird fluid on me,
I'm gonna end up getting really turned on!
You should be feeling horny right about now.
Seeing you guys like that really turns me on!
Huh?
H-Hey, Kou-kun?
Wh-What are you doing?
N-No way!
H-How? The tentacle transformed?
S-Stop it!
If you make it look too much
like a penis, it'll get censored!
Well, why don't we forget about
that dull topic for now and.
A-Amazing.
This tentacle dick feels incredible!
Oh no... My mind is going blank.
Fantasizing...
Just wait. I'll pleasure your dick even more.
This is amazing.
Your dick is kissing my womb.
My pussy is so happy!
I can't stop! My hips are moving on their own!
Sheesh, you're like a baby.
Keep going. Do whatever you want with my tits.
I can feel your dick throbbing
and hitting my g-spot!
My insides are being totally stirred up!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
That's it! Yes!
My nipples are all stiff!
I'm becoming a total pervert!
Your dick is getting bigger.
H-Hey, let's cum together.
Let all your milk out inside
my pussy and feel good.
I-I'm gonna cum too!
Go ahead, you can cum.
Splash your sticky semen all over me!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
That's it, Karen.
You don't have to think about anything.
Just let yourself feel good!
N-No. Please stop.
If you keep rubbing my tits like that.
There! It's scraping my insides!
No, please stop!
My mind is going blank!
Fantasizing...
You're so lewd, Senpai.
Your dick is so hot and it's throbbing so much.
Are you getting turned on by my tits?
No.
It's making wet, sloppy, lewd sounds.
I-I'm feeling homy too.
My pussy's totally soaked.
Your dick's getting sticky from all the fluid.
This filthy smell is driving me crazy!
Incredible! My pussy's being eaten up!
We're connected through our mouths
and genitals! It's too good!
S-Senpai! Please don't stir it up too much!
No! My pussy is twitching!
Go ahead, it's okay.
You can cum whenever you're ready!
I'll be really glad if my tits
and pussy can make you feel good.
Please, Senpai.
Let's cum together.
I can't take it anymore!
No... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Stop fooling around!
You already came a lot. You're still not satisfied?
Well, your pussy is so wet!
It feels so fucking good!
You're feeling horny too, aren't you, Lizera?
I-I'm not! It's all this demonic fluid's fault!
I-I don't feel horny at all!
Fantasizing...
Don't worry, I'll squeeze out all your semen.
Y-You best prepare yourself!
Don't pull so hard!
You're going to stretch my nipples!
I'm taking the lead here. Why do you always
do things that aren't necessary?
Wait! That's too sudden!
I'm trying to make you cum.
But at this rate, I'm going to cum first!
Y-Your dick is twitching inside my pussy.
You want to cum so much! I can tell!
N-No!
If we keep doing this,
I'm really going to lose my mind!
You're still not cumming?
Hurry up or I'm gonna go nuts!
It's okay. We can keep doing it until you're satisfied.
You can cum inside me! Let it all out!
I-I'm cumming... I'm cumming.
It's hitting my g-spot!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Let it out! Shoot your cum in me!
Give it to me!
Please, Kou-kun. Let me off the hook.
I'll go crazy if this keeps up.
Then what happens if
I play with this part here?
H-Hey! No, not there!
Please don't play around with my butt!
Y-You blockhead!
Y-Your fingers feel amazing.
Fantasizing...
My butt feels tingly.
That's not where your fingers
are supposed to go!
My butt.
Your dick is inside my butt!
It feels so strange!
I can feel the inside of my butt twitching!
I don't understand... How can my
first time doing anal be such a turn-on?
No!
Please don't be so rough!
I'm gonna lose it if you do!
My insides are getting hotter!
Please, go faster! You can violate my butt
with your hard cock all you want!
Let out lots of cum inside my butt!
Fill me up!
Your dick is filling my butt up!
I can't believe I'm going to cum
from being fucked in the butt!
Now this is what I'm talking about!
Raping girls with tentacles
until they can't move.
Fucking them until their minds break
and they can only beg for more.
And then covering their bodies
with layers upon layers of cum.
I've always wanted to do this!
Kou-kun, you idiot.
Now that you've sprayed us
with all this cum, none of us can.
Huh? What's happening?
What's going on?
What on Earth?
My strength is back.
I got it!
Kou's possessed body is filled
with a tremendous amount of mana.
His semen has the power to make us stronger!
Damn it!
If that's the case, I'll just hold myself back from cumming
and get you all wasted with my tentacles once more!
What should we do?
We'll get violated by those tentacles again!
In order for us to get stronger,
we have to get him to spray us with loads of semen.
To do that.
To do that?
We're going to masturbate!
What?!
Look at me, Kou.
This is a special service
that you'll only get today.
You can fap to me if you want to.
Now go ahead and cum.
You can splash your semen anywhere you want.
On my pussy, my tits, or even my face.
You need to do this to beat
the demon and return to normal!
This isn't good.
My hips are moving on their own!
You can look at my
lewd parts all you want, Senpai.
Let your libido surge!
Not you too, Karen!
Look at me, Kou-kun! I'm masturbating!
My pussy is soaked because
of the things you did to me earlier.
I-I'm going to cum right away!
Ai-neesan! You look so fucking sexy!
I'm gonna cum!
Kou-kun! Look at me masturbating!
I'm totally hopeless now. I'm such a pervert
that I get turned on by playing with my butt.
Please cum already, Kou-kun. This is embarrassing!
Spray your cum on my butt!
It's impossible! I can't hold myself back anymore!
I'm cumming!
We did it.
We did it!
Success! Here it comes!
Oh shit!
Just wait, Kou-kun.
We'll get you back to normal.
Let's gather up all our mana!
R-Roger!
Here we go!
This is bad! I'm dead for sure!
Disciplinary Committee Room
And so they got me back to normal, but after that.
You can do it. You can do it.
H-Hey.
Stop that! Not two at the same time!
We're just getting started!
We used up a lot of mana in order to save you.
We need you to help us recharge.
Your cock is still so hard. I'm starting to get horny.
And all I'm doing is giving you a titfuck.
Oh god, this isn't good!
It's okay, Senpai.
You can cum on our faces or our tits.
We'll gladly take it all!
So please cum lots!
Your semen makes for
intriguing research material.
I'm going to suck you dry.
I told you, there's nothing left.
Your penis is still hot and hard, though.
Doesn't that mean you want more? Just be honest.
I'll let you cum all over me, okay?
I'll stroke your dick like there's no tomorrow,
so spray that semen all over me!
You made us go through all that,
so now it's our turn to see you get humiliated.
But you looked really adorable when you were
getting buttfucked by tentacles, Konoka.
Y-You jerk! Don't say weird stuff like that!
You're such a pervert, Kou-kun.
You're getting hard from a footjob.
You huge jerk!
I-I can't take it anymore.
I want you to ram my pussy
deep, all the way inside!
My nipples are getting stiff and sensitive.
It feels amazing inside you, Ai-neesan! It's so tight!
I'm going to squeeze your cock even more!
Your dick is so good it's making my pussy convulse!
I'm going to squeeze out all your semen!
This is your fault, Senpai.
You did all those perverted things, that's why.
Now even I'm turning into a pervert.
It's fine, Karen!
I want to see an even lewder side of you!
Okay! I understand!
I'll give it my all!
If you want to, I'll let you do my pussy,
my tits, my mouth, or even my ass!
You can do whatever you want with me!
You're still hard after cumming that much?
Wait, Kou, are you still possessed by the demon?
No, I'm not. It's just that your insides feel amazing!
Y-You jerk! Don't say things like that!
V-Very well. Today's an exception.
I'll let you see all of me.
You want to get me all sticky
with your cum again, right?
You can mess me up some more! Make me cum!
I-I can't go on. I'm at my limit.
I'm about to cum! I'm about to cum!
My hips are moving on their own! I can't stop!
My pussy feels great!
I'm about to cum too!
I'll cum inside you, Konoka!
Go ahead! Fill me up with your semen!
This is it, so please hold me close!
Your cock is getting bigger!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Huh? That looks strange
translator: nyanpasu
tranlation chekc: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: fyurie | punk4real
encoder: punk4real
quality control: fyurie
A demon? Oh wait, it's
just my imagination.
Demon busters starts now!
Let's go, everyone.
Everything will be all right.
Life at school is so fantastic.
Math, English, and Science
always drive us nuts.
We'll solve all these difficult problems.
With our overflowing
energy and bright smiles.
We'll have fun every day!
We're always ready for
unexpected events.
We'll even use weapons
hat we're not familiar with.
For we can adapt to every situation.
Love and friendship are
priceless treasures to us.
Let's count: one, two, three, four.
Demon busters starts now!