Ow, ow..!
It hurts!
Rejoice.
For you are about to indulge for the first
time upon the Demon Lord's own seed.
I-Idiot!
Gigliola...
I'll use my dick to drill you raw, and then cum inside.
Cum... no, no, please...!
Please pull it out.
I'm going to get pregnant!
What's wrong?
Didn't you want to give up your virginity
and slaughter mankind as my servant?
Yes.
All of the humans that killed my family, my brethren...
I want to kill them all.
Then remember this.
You are now mine, until you die.
U-Until... I die...?
Yes, Lord Astaroth.
What is this?
I feel weird.
Do not fret, my little lass.
Just enjoy the feeling.
I really feel weird!
It's coming, it's about to come!
Gigliola...
Here I go!
Receive your very first male seed.
You, you can't cum... inside me!
Take it in!
Now your virginity is mine.
Rejoice, young lass.
Don't call me young lass.
U-Umm, Lord Astaroth?
Please, do me next.
Don't you want another servant?
I am also willing to offer my virginity.
Misca...
No, you must escape!
No, I can't leave you here, Gigliola.
A bold move, young lass number two.
I'm the one who summoned you here,
so the responsibility is also mine.
Very well then, I shall take you two both.
Here we go!
Misca...
You shall serve me from now on.
Obey me, and I shall let you witness even greater things.
Yes, Lord Astaroth.
A dream?
Not a single human to be spared.
My, what a hot spring.
This feeling, and the scenery,
hot springs really are very wonderful.
Himika, you're noisy.
Oh, don't you understand the beauty of hot springs, Onee-sama?
This place is nothing but a bath.
We simply clean our bodies, and then leave the place.
I'll wash your back, okay?
Himika, you always clean weird spots when you do that.
Onee-sama, will you please let your dear
younger sister clean your body?
No thanks, I can wash myself.
My, Onee-sama.
The elder sister shall listen to the younger's sister's request then.
Thank you very much.
I'll get started then.
Hi-Himika, that's not how you clean it.
Yes it is, I'm actually cleaning it properly.
See? Properly.
You're not cleaning it at all...
I told you, wash me properly.
No...
I need to wash it properly, Onee-sama.
Watching two sisters frolic with each
other like that is not bad at all.
Lord Astaroth, this is the women's bath area.
I am the Demon Lord.
That does not matter.
Forget that, I want you to do something about this.
Jeez, what a pushy man.
I am not a man, for I am the Demon Lord.
Alright, arlight.
Well then, Onee-sama, why don't we
both comfort our Demon Lord?
Okay, I understand.
Lord Astaroth, it looks magnificent as always.
I can cum just by doing this.
Just cum as much as you want, Himika.
I'm going to watch as you cum.
Onee-sama, Lord Astaroth.
Good, I'm about to cum already.
Astaroth, cum, please cum.
Here I go, take this!
It's hot, your cum feels hot, Lord Astaroth...
Oboro, straddle my face.
I understand.
I shall assist you.
A-Astaroth, sorry, but please wait.
What's wrong?
I-It's nothing, but I want to take a break.
I haven't cum again yet.
We can't stop now.
But...
Onee-sama, are you about to cum?
Oh, you're going to urinate.
It's an open stream hot spring,
so just do it here.
But...
No problem, I shall help you do it.
Just wait, Astaroth!
I want to see how Onee-sama pees too.
Himika, no, that's dirty.
It's you after all, so it shouldn't be.
What's wrong? It's not good to hold it in.
Onee-sama, it looked beautiful.
Now, continue servicing me.
Well then, Lord Astaroth,
Lord Astaroth, your thing is penetrating me.
Lord Astaroth, you're hitting the very depths of my pussy.
It's trying to hit the entrance to my
womb, while you impregnate me.
I'm, I'm about to cum with you, Himika.
Himika...
Onee-sama, let's cum together with Lord Astaroth.
Yeah, let's cum together.
What's wrong?
We just got started.
Of course.
We just need to get back to our rooms,
and I shall show you how wonderful Onee-sama can be.
Is that so?
I look forward to it then.
Now, Lord Astaroth, please behold.
It's Oboro Onee-sama's alluring form.
Onee-sama, you look wonderful!
I'm about to go crazy with your adorable charm!
I don't get it.
What's so good about these clothes?
Wouldn't it be better for her to wear
a wardrobe that shows more skin?
Do you not understand?
Very well then, here we go.
I don't understand.
Won't this cover up more skin?
Now, Onee-sama,
it's time to show what you can really do.
Do I really have to do this?
Please, Onee-sama.
No.
This is embarrassing.
Wh-What is this?
I can't believe I just...
That's it, Lord Astaroth.
The welling desire to see more.
I believe that you are capable of understanding it.
Is this the power of oriental sorcery?
Alight, let's raise the bar a bit more.
Okay then, Onee-sama.
Now!
Chant what I taught you earlier!
Papa.
Please be gentle with me.
Papa, just wai-
Well?
The feeling is quite different, don't you think?
I never thought that I'd be done in by you.
Here we go, Oboro!
Umm, there's so much of it...
Okay, next.
I see that it's gotten really wet.
Papa, no.
Onee-sama, you can get hornier if you want.
Okay, next.
Up you go!
Pa-Papa, can you please be a little more gentle?
This is good, this is the best.
I haven't felt this sensation before.
This is nice, really nice, Oboro!
P-Papa, you're hitting the very depths.
Your dick is already all the way inside me.
Your grip is also better than usual.
Your insides feel really great.
The way your dick hits deep inside me feels great, Papa.
It's pushing hard, and it's so good.
It's cumming, I'm cumming!
Well then, my child, cum.
Papa, papa, papa!
That was wonderful, Onee-sama.
But the night is still young.
Now then, I shall join you both.
How are you going to spice up things this time?
Oh, then how about this?
Wait, that's...
I'm now about to enjoy this just like yourself, Lord Astaroth.
Interesting, I approve.
Himika, just wai-
Now Onee-sama, open wide.
My insides already feel full,
and it feels like my insides are going
to be ripped apart as it overflows.
Onee-sama,
oh no, I'm... I'm literally going to break!
How about this?
It's big, so you can tell how it looks even from the outside.
Lord Astaroth, I would like you to enjoy her both inside and out.
Yes, this is indeed good.
She's tighter and firmer than usual.
The way your body continues to take all of it in looks lovely.
Please make yourself even more alluring.
I'm going to cum then.
You can call on me once again, my child.
Papa,
I'm, I'm...
Papa!
That was wonderful, Onee-sama.
Himika, you went overboard.
But...
But?
It was amazing.
Onee-sama...
I love you.
But the night is still young.
Onee-sama, let us enjoy this further, shall we?
Hiika, that's what you use when peeing...
That was a great workout.
I shall use the baths again.
Come with me, Gigliola.
Yes.
As expected, my hands really are big enough.
You say that, but aren't you favoring humans more now?
I do not favor anyone.
I simply live in the moment.
That is what desire is all about.
Lord Astaroth, do you still remember the first time that we met?
And our wish.
A wish, eh.
I wonder what it was all about.
To slaughter all of the humans that killed
and harmed my friends and brethren.
I'm going to choose whether I shall take that humane life or not.
Though the idea of eradicating them is still a good idea.
But I also said,
that I shall let you witness even greater things.
Greater things?
You never really hated those women.
I do.
If there is something better than death for them,
then it shall be the one thing that I will show you.
It is your obligation as the one who summoned me.
Something better than death?
Indeed.
To make them do the same things you
two do for the rest of their lives.
Just as we do?
Gigliola, that's unfair!
Mi-Misca!
This is... umm...
Lord Astaroth, please love me dearly too, okay?
Alright I get it already.
You're going to be next.
This time, we'll plead to him together.
Misca...
Now Lord Astaroth, choose whoever you want.
Very well then.
I shall fully enjoy you both.
And I shall start with you, Misca!
Lord Astaroth.
Gigliola, take this!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming again!
Lord Astaroth...!?
Take this!
Gigliola...
Misca...
You two are the best after all.
Now, let us depart toward our new world.
And I shall let you two witness even greater things.
Yes, Lord Astaroth.