No, my nipples...
My nipples are...!
Misca, you look beautiful.
Gigliola, don't play with my clit now!
Its been a long time since I fucked you two.
Guess you really are the best for this.
Thank you for your kind words, sir.
Are you not saying the same things to other ladies, my lord?
You two are the best, that's why I said you're the best.
What I said doesn't have a shred of lie in it.
Well, I guess that is fine.
I'm cumming...!
The entire dominion will soon be yours, Lord Astaroth.
All of the nearby territories and nations
are now surrendering one by one.
I see.
Is there something on your mind, sir?
Then let's go here next.
Here, next?
Let's go, Misca!
Yes, yes!
I'll go, I shall cum!
Your dick, and your cum,
I want it all deep inside of me!
I think, no...
I'm definitely sure that there are still other women
on other continents that do not know my name.
A declaration of an invasion, sir?
No, I actually plan to overrun them.
All of the world's finest ladies shall become mine.
I shall never give them to any man.
Are you being serious, sir?
I'm always serious.
You sir, are the type that is still serious about foolish things.
Well, perhaps there is just one way to go.
This is not the first time you have shown your foolishness anyway.
Just keep on following me.
And I shall let you see even better sights
than you have ever witnessed.
Lord Astaroth!
What's with the long face, Vanessa?
What could you possibly be doing here?
We are in the middle of conquering the small countries.
All work and no play makes ruling dull, correct?
We don't know when our enemy will make
its move while we idly stay here!
I think you should take a break, too.
Gigliola.
Understood.
Gigliola, what are you doing?
Hey, don't just touch me like that!
Misca, don't tell me...
Now, now, no need to be shy.
Stop, hey...!
I cannot accept this kind of humiliation.
My oh my, I see you have no more clothing.
You're the ones who took them off!
Here, we have the ultimate wardrobe for you.
Ultimate wardrobe?
What's with that weird swimsuit?
This is the ultimate wardrobe of this region.
Don't you want it?
This feels even more embarrassing than being naked.
Oh.
I am no longer that young.
I don't think I would be able to entertain
you if I wear something like this.
You need to ask this thing if that's true or not.
I can feel it pulsating in my hands.
Is Lord Astaroth interested in my...
In my unworthy body... ?
Please stop.
This place is...
Oh no, my body is becoming sensitive.
You can't, sir, please don't fondle me there.
Though, I think this place is too hot for us.
Lord Astaroth, what are you doing?
I can walk by myself!
Lord Astartoth!
This is...
The beach sands may feel too hot for us.
Feels quite cool in here, right?
Indeed it is.
We still have lots of time.
Rest whenever there's time.
Because I still need you to work for me.
Yes, thank you very much.
And part of your job is to make me feel good.
Y-Yes...
It smells good.
It reeks of a man's scent.
It's becoming stiffen.
That feels good.
Now, use your big tits.
Yes.
Here you go, Lord Astaroth.
How is it?
It's starting to get really stiff.
Straddle me.
Wait, won't we be exposed in this area?
What's wrong? Do it already.
As you wish.
Not bad.
Your body shines even more while wearing this swimsuit.
Lord Astaroth!
Hey now, don't stop using your mouth.
Yes, sir.
Your mouth stopped again.
My apologies.
Hey, what's the point if I'm the only one enjoying this?
No, not there...
Oh, looks like you ejaculated quite quickly.
Your fortitude seems lacking for a knight.
Please don't say that.
Now then, let's violate you.
Spread your legs.
Yes, please violate me, Lord Astaroth.
Lord Astaroth?
Take this!
This, I wanted this!
Lord Astaroth, Lord Astaroth!
Push it in, and violate me more!
Oh no...
It hurts, but it also feels good.
It's hitting deep inside me.
I'm really taking it deep inside.
Lord Astaroth, this is amazing!
It's hitting right at its very core,
and still trying to push through!
Cum is flowing inside my womb...
Lord Astaroth's cum is inside me.
I'm going to get pregnant.
As expected of the only tavern in this village.
Looks like all the loafers have assembled here.
Everyone, I shall now give you pleasure.
You can enter now.
Go on, hurry on in.
Master is waiting.
E-Even if you say that...
What's wrong? Go inside already.
Now now, just go.
Lord As-, I mean my lord,
Why am I wearing something like this?
There is a tradition here of praying to rabbits
in order to have good children.
A treasured culture of this small country.
I don't think anything will go wrong even
if we appoint you as the "rabbit".
Praying to rabbits? You're the demon lord, right?
I'm not really in a great hurry for an invasion.
Just show them how you play with yourself.
H-Here?
As the rabbit it is your duty to share happiness with everyone.
In a few moments, I shall let everyone
witness something very good.
Please enjoy.
Now then everyone...
Please enjoy the show.
They're looking,
all of them are watching me.
Watching as I embarrass myself by doing this.
Watching their future ruler do something shameful.
All of these strangers are watching me play with myself.
This humiliation, this... this...
Watch.
Please watch me.
The view is great, right?
Are you all enjoying this right now?
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Everyone, all of you watch me.
Watch my lewd self get horny as I'm being ogled by everyone.
Watch my slutty self...!
I came.
I came as their eyes were on me.
I came as they watched me masturbate.
I'm... I'm...
Now then, I shall make this even more exciting.
My lord,
it's deep!
It's inside me, it's deep inside me!
It feels good, it feels good!
My lord, your thing is pushing into my asshole!
Deeper and deeper!
I'm about to cum again, my lord.
Can I... is it okay for me to cum?
Please, I beg of you, let me cum!
Let me cum!
Very well then, cum to your heart's content.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to cum.
All while being exposed shamelessly.
All while being anally fucked.
All while my pussy is exposed.
I'm cumming!
It's deep inside.
Your hot thing is deep inside me.
Lord Astaroth.
Hey, rabbit.
We're not done yet.
Eh?
They all seem to have gotten horny after watching.
Be sure to take care of them as well.
I-I understand.
This is good, this is good!
Now that's my rabbit!
Become whiter and whiter with my cum!
Humans sure are troublesome.
Lord Astaroth, it's time already.
Yeah, just wait a sec.
Lord Astaroth, we have to go.
You're right.
But you and I need to cum first before we start anything.
If you want to proceed, then feel free
to make me cum as soon as possible.
We already did it lots yesterday.
Is it still not enough?
Of course not.
I'll do it with any woman I want to anytime.
Any woman you want?
Would that be me, sir?
That's right.
It's you.
I'm happy!
Lord Astaroth!
Just use me however you want!
Yes, that's good!
That feels great, Lord Astaroth!
Just keep on violating my pussy with your thing!
Conquer me with it!
I want your cum, I want your cum.
Please poor it all inside me.
Please impregnate me with it!
Squirt everything, and make me pregnant with your cum!
Lord Astaroth!
It's coming out.
Your cum is pouring inside me.
My womb is now full with it.
It feels good to be impregnated.
Well done.
Now, prepare your battle cry, and command our troops to battle!
Yes.
Misca, give me a towel.
You will go with that.
Yes, I shall go with this.
Vanessa, we are already behind schedule.
I understand.
Right now, I am the military's primary pillar,
and completely fulfilled as a woman.
There is no better form of happiness in this world than this.
Everyone, I ask of you.
Are you all fulfilled?