Daemon Busters!
Make-up!
Beautiful Idol Battle Girls,
fighting for Love and Peace!
Daemon Busters!
J-Just wait, sensei!
What the heck is this?
You never told us anything about this!
Fool.
This is the anime version.
We have to at least put up a show to make us stand out.
B-But...
This is embarrassing in many ways, though.
What are you saying?
We're just getting started, you know.
Now, now.
Daemon Busters, start!
Bad, bad, go away!
Daemon Barrier!
Here I go!
Royal Lovely Sweet Daemon Flash!
F-Finishing move!
Buster Sword - Miracle Spirit!
Crush them all!
I shall end this.
Explosive Dynamite Flare Wheel!
We won.
Mainly because of me, though.
A-Acting like that again...
This was embarrassing for me, you know.
What's wrong with it?
It feels like being a hero character, so it's fun.
W-Well, we did wipe out all the enemies once again.
I really wonder about that.
Te-Tentacles?!
Oh no, I can't get away from it.
Damn...
I never thought the boss was actually hiding somewhere.
I've been waiting...
...for the moment when everyone's energy is almost used up.
Huh, that voice...?
Could it be...?
Kou-kun?
I bet not one of you has ever thought of the
possibility that I'm actually the big boss.
Lately, you see...
I've realized just how interesting
tentacle play might actually be.
Eh?!
No...
It's melting, my suit is melting away!
Se-Senpai, stop!
Stop looking!
This... this is it!
I've wanted to do it like this!
J-Jeez, Kou-kun,you pervert.
You could have just asked nicely if you wanted to see me nude.
This is just...!
N-No good.
I'm literally drenched with its fluids.
I-It inevitably causes me to become aroused...
Looks like everyone's gotten quite horny now.
Seeing everyone's lewd bodies...
It makes me start to crave for it, too.
Huh?
Wait... Kou-kun?
What are you trying to do?
No way...
Why...
The tentacles turned into dicks!
S-Stop!
It looks almost like a dick,
and it feels like these tentacles are clinging to me more!
Well, let's abandon that observation for a moment.
Putting it aside...
Wow...
This tentacle dick feels good.
What should I do?
My mind is starting to go blank.
Just you wait,
I'll make your dick even livelier, Kou-kun.
Amazing...
Your dick is constantly kissing the entrance to my womb.
My pussy is completely filled with pleasure.
My hips are moving on their own, and I can't stop it!
Jeez,
you're like a baby.
I-It's alright.
Do whatever you want with my breasts.
It's twitching, hitting all of my tender spots.
My pussy's insides are all tingly.
It feels like I'm going to melt!
Oh wow...
My nipples feel totally hard and stiff now.
I'm starting to become hornier and hornier.
Y-Your dick is bulging, filling me inside.
Hey, let's cum together.
Let's both relieve ourselves by having
you fill me inside with your cum milk.
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum too.
Just do it.
Cum it all.
Soil me with all of your cum milk.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
It's alright, Karen, no need to think about anything else.
Just drown yourself in pleasure.
No, this can't be.
I mustn't!
If you rub my breasts like that...
Oh no, it's rubbing itself hard inside me.
Stop, please don't!
I'm...
Se-Senpai, you're just so erotic.
Your dick feels so hot and stiff.
Are you feeling aroused with my breasts?
No...
My nether regions are making erotic sloshing noises.
N-Now I'm getting aroused as well.
I'm getting wet.
Y-Your dick too, is starting to secrete these
lewd fluids, making it completely wet.
This erotic scent just makes me unable to resist!
Amazing.
I'm being licked there, on my pussy!
Senpai and I are currently connected
on our lewd parts, with our mouths.
What should I do?
Senpai, no... if you stir me vigorously inside like that...!
Oh no...
My pussy is starting to twitch.
I-It's alright.
Just cum whenever you want.
As long as you get aroused with my pussy and breasts...
...I-I'm happy.
P-Please, senpai.
Let's cum, let's cum together.
I'm about to...!
Oh no, I'm cumming,
I'm cumming!
Y-You...!
Stop messing around already!
You already came lots of times.
Are you still not satisfied?
But it just...
It just feels so good inside this wet pussy of yours.
You're feeling pleasure from this too, right?
Th-That's not true.
Th-This is just because of all the fluids soiling me...
That's why I...
Why I...
Listen, I'll be the one to squeeze all of your cum out, okay?
So prepare yourself.
Don't pull!
My nipples, my nipples will be stretched out!
I'm the one doing the fucking, and yet
you do all these unnecessary things.
It's holding me in!
Wait, don't just suddenly...!
I'm supposed to make you cum and yet...
And yet I'll be the one to cum first if this continues!
Your dick is pushing really hard inside me.
Even you can't resist the desire to cum.
N-No, this isn't good.
If I keep on doing this lewd stuff,
my mind will go completely blank.
Won't you cum yet?
You have to cum now,
or else I'll...
Alright then, just cum as many times
as you want until you're satisfied.
Just cum it all inside my pussy.
Fill me with your cum!
I'm about to cum, too.
I'm cumming.
It's hitting my tender spots.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Just cum.
Pump all your cum into me.
All into me!
I beg of you,
please don't fuck me so deeply.
I-If this continues...
I'm going to go crazy.
Well then...
Why don't we try fucking you here instead?
H-Hey, wait...!
Not there!
Don't!
Please don't play with my ass!
Idiot!
Your fingers, they're vigorously stirring my ass.
My ass's insides feel all tingly!
Th-That's...
My ass is...
Isn't the place where you put it in.
It feels so tight in my ass.
This dick... as it goes inside me, it actually feels...
It feels... so weird, and yet...
My asshole grips it firmly as it goes in and out.
But, what now?
I never thought that being fucked in the ass
for the first time could feel this good.
If you keep on fucking me intensely like that...
I'll...!
It's getting hornier and hornier, despite trying to hold back.
Please, continue fucking me.
Just rape me with your big dick as much as you want to.
My ass is completely filled with your dick...
For me to cum in my ass...
This can't be...
This is it!
Eventually making women unable to even react with tentacles.
Breaking them until I feel all tingly.
And after I completely leave them
in a stupor with countless fucks,
I pump cum inside to completely fill them.
I've always wanted to do this!
J-Jeez, Kou-kun, you idiot.
If you cum inside this much,
we can no longer...
Wh-What's this?
What the heck is that?!
What's happening?
I feel like my powers are returning to me.
I see, now I get it.
This Daemon-assimilated body of Kou
has become a vessel of energy.
So, Kou's cum basically grants us strength!
Damn...
If that's the case...
I'll just have to restrain from cumming,
and then leave you in a stupor again with my tentacles!
Wh-What should we do?
We're going to get fucked by those tentacles again!
In order for us to gain more strength,
we need to make Kou's tentacles cum on us even more.
For us to make him do that...
For us to make him do that?
...Everyone must masturbate in front of him!
Look, Kou,
I'll only show this to you today.
This is today's special.
You can fap to my masturbation if you want to,
so just cum already.
On my pussy, on my breasts, or just on me,
cum wherever you want to.
Th-This can't be helped.
This is all to defeat the Daemon and
return senpai back to normal.
No, no...
My hips... they're moving on their own...
Se-Senpai, you can watch how lewd I am all day!
Make yourself completely aroused with it.
Even Karen is...!
Kou-kun, look, please look at me.
I'm masturbating right now.
I've been fucked a lot b those tentacles earlier.
That's why my pussy is now this wet.
No, oh no...
I'm about to cum.
Ai-neesan.
That really looks erotic!
I'm the one here who's about to cum!
Kou-kun, I'll be doing this, okay?
I'll show myself doing it, okay?
I'm a bad girl.
I'm now a pervert who also gets
aroused when fucked in the ass.
Please, Kou-kun,
this is embarrassing, so i beg of you,
hurry up and cum quickly.
Squirt all of your cum onto me.
No good.
I can't hold back anymore.
I-I'm cumming!
Here it comes.
Here it comes!
Here it finally comes!
I'm screwed.
Kou-kun, just you wait.
We're going to get you back to normal.
Concentrate all of your powers!
R-Roger!
Here I go!
Oh no, this is bad!
This will end with me getting killed!
Afterwards, I somehow returned back to normal,
but if you ask what happened after that...
Go and cum. Go and cum. Go and
cum. Go and cum. Go and cum
W-Wait... stop, don't...!
You two are doing it at the same time!
We're just getting started.
We used up a lot of our mana just to save you.
You'll have to replenish it all for us.
Kou-kun, your dick is still very lively, see?
I'm getting horny myself just keeping up with this tit fuck.
This isn't good!
It's alright, senpai.
We'll take everything, whether it goes
on our face or on our breasts.
Just cum lots!
I need to collect your cum for my intriguing experiments.
I'm going to have to squeeze every drop of it today.
I told you, there's almost nothing left!
Your dick is still hot and stiff.
It actually feels so pleasurable that you want more, right?
Here, just be more honest with yourself.
You can cover me with much more cum.
I'm going to give you a handjob all day so just keep it squirting.
It's all your fault that I was exposed so shamelessly.
It's our turn to get back at you now.
But, you just looked very cute while you
were being raped by those tentacles.
I-Idiot!
Please don't say such strange things.
For you to become this aroused with my feet.
You really are a pervert, Kou-kun.
You came again, idiot!
I can't hold back any longer.
I want you to rub me hard inside my deepest spots already.
Both my clit and my nipples are totally aroused right now.
Amazing,
your insides are squeezing me really tightly, Ai-neesan.
Yup, and I'm about to squeeze you even further.
Your dick feels so good, that my pussy can't help but twitch.
I'm going to squeeze every last drop of your cum!
Jeez, this is all your fault, senpai.
Because you've done lots and lots of lewd things to me.
And I'm starting to become lewd, too.
It's okay, Karen.
I want to see you become even hornier!
Okay!
I understand.
I'm going to let it all out!
Not just with my pussy,
but with my breasts and mouth, too!
Even with my ass...
If you just go with it, senpai,
I can give you anything!
You already came lots, and yet your dick still remains this stiff.
K-Kou, are you still possessed by a Daemon?
Not anymore,
but it feels really good inside you, Lizera.
idiot!
Stop saying weird things!
Very well, then.
I'll make it special for you today.
If it's you, I can show every shameful part of me.
You wanted to completely cover me in cum, right?
You can mess me up more if you want.
So make me cum!
Oh no, I'm at my limit.
I'm about to cum, too.
I'm going to cum.
My hips just keep on moving.
I won't stop!
My pussy feels so good!
Me too, I'm going to cum.
Konoka, I'm going to cum inside!
It's okay.
Cum. Cum it all inside me.
This is our last, so let's cum together.
This can't be. Your dick is getting even bigger.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum!