THE DESERT ISLAND STORY X
Don't Iook at me Iike that.
You Iike it, don't you?
Toko. HeIp me.
Answer me!
I see. You don't Iike it with me.
Then I'II make it more fun.
That girI, Natsuno.
You know what I did to her body?
If you don't know...
...I'II show you using your body.
No. HeIp me.
What's wrong? Why don't you scream?
No one is going to come for you.
We're on a desert island.
Episode 4: Sunrise
Toko! Toko! Where are you?
-What's wrong, Natsuno?
-Toko has gone to rescue Ayaka.
Stupid bitch. It's too risky now.
I toId her so.
Yuka went with her.
-What shouId we do, Natsuno?
-Let's go.
Natsuno. Okay. We aII go.
Sooner or Iater,
we have to settIe the score.
A nice dress, isn't it?
You Iike it?
Toko, Toko.
This is how a woman shouId be dressed.
I aIways wanted to enjoy a girI Iike you.
I Iike you a Iot. Let me have some fun.
No. Toko!
Toko, maybe
we shouId have brought aIong Natsuno.
Why don't you go crawIing back to them?
-I'm coming with you.
-Thank you, Yuka. Here we go.
Pretend you're enjoying it.
This is not satisfying you?
For a frigid girI Iike you,
this position works better.
That reminds me,
we haven't done it to that girI.
If you miss her, she can join us.
Kaneda is such a bastard.
He's having aII the fun.
I wonder how big my cut wiII be.
Maybe I shouId kiII Kaneda
and keep the money and girIs to myseIf.
HeIIo, Toko....
I found their stash.
Mr. Aoki. You're one of them?
So what? I aImost had you, too.
What about Natsuno?
Was that just for show?
She feII head over heeIs for me.
What a nice body she has.
Yuka! HoId her!
Yuka, not you.
Kaneda and Ibuki had aII the fun.
It's my turn--
Mr. Kaneda.
I was going to take her downstairs.
She's been caIIing your name.
Your friend, Ayaka.
Not Ayaka.
Not Ayaka!
-What happened to Toko?
-Don't worry, Toko is tough.
-Shush!
-Sorry.
Let's go.
Mr. Aoki.
-What are you doing here?
-I've come to rescue Ayaka. This way.
I brought your friend.
Ayaka.
You're here for me, Toko.
I'm sorry, Ayaka. I'm sorry.
-I'II never Ieave you.
-Don't forget about me.
I wiII rape you right in front of her eyes.
Toko.
Mr. Aoki, where is Ayaka?
Mr. Aoki!
What are you doing? Open up!
Yuka captured Toko for us.
We'll enjoy you later.
No. Not you.
Natsuno.
You're joking. TeII me you're joking!
Not you, Mr. Aoki.
No.
Toko.
You're getting sensitive, aren't you?
Ayaka. I can't....
No.
Let your friend hear your moaning.
What is this?
You may be tough, GirIie,
but you're cute Iike this.
Time to put it in.
It's a bad storm outside.
It's over. Even Toko is in their hands.
Hitomi.
There must be some way. Don't give up.
But even Yuka is one of them.
That must be a Iie.
I wish it was....
Yuka.
-I--
-Yuka!
I wiII not forgive you!
Stop.
PIease, Natsuno, don't.
-Get away from me, Hitomi.
-Don't be so hasty, Natsuno.
-She soId us out!
-Natsuno!
TeII us everything, Yuka.
You were a virgin. Nice surprise.
Not so hard.
No.
Let's do it in my favorite position.
Ayaka!
It's getting better, isn't it?
You're stubborn. How do you Iike this?
What?
That works, doesn't it?
No.
No, no. No more.
Toko.
Ayaka.
Quiet.
How did you get out?
Your voice is trembIing.
-You betrayed us?
-So what?
She's our friend.
What a pathetic man.
Thanks for everything, Mr. Aoki.
Wait. You can have aII the money.
Now that Ibuki is dead,
Kaneda is aII you have to take care of.
-Ibuki is dead?
-See, we just can't trust you.
Why don't we chop it off?
Yeah!
Not a bad idea.
HeIp me.
Ayaka.
I'm sorry, Ayaka. It's my fauIt.
It's not fair, Ayaka.
You're aIways Iike that.
It's not fair. You're aIways the good girI.
Toko.
Toko! Ayaka!
So, Aoki ran away?
With the girIs?
And the bag of money.
I think they found a way off the isIand.
Why didn't you go with them?
I thought I'd rather trust you.
I Iike that. You Iove me that much?
Not here.
Mr. Kaneda?
I hate it when peopIe think I'm stupid.
-I hope Yuka's successfuI.
-Shush!
Let's just foIIow the pIan.
Sure.
I've been waiting.
I'm tired of raping her.
Yuka.
PIease, run, both of you!
Why don't you Ieave behind the snitch?
-We're not Iike you.
-Give me Aoki.
-We'II exchange him for Yuka.
-Do you know what's going on here?
We're not going to Iet you have your way!
I see.
You made a mistake.
What? You stiII wanted Aoki?
Oh, yeah, you were sIeeping with him.
You, beast!
Let's see if a girIie can commit murder.
Don't mock me.
Now I'm the onIy man on this isIand.
Wait.
-What's wrong?
-It's Toko.
Don't worry, they're fine.
Ayaka.
She is suffering.
Why do you say that?
Hey, FIora.
I'II go take a Iook. Stay with Hitomi.
-Hitomi, take care of Ayaka.
-Don't do anything stupid.
Don't worry. I wiII.
No. If you do it Iike that....
Just bear it, Toko.
Good. Be good friends.
Natsuno, not there.
Yes.
Bear it untiI Kaneda gets sIoppy.
But....
Good. Soon I'II bring aII the girIs here.
No, Toko. Just Iet me do it.
But, Natsuno. It's not fair Iike this.
Toko.
Okay. If I'm the onIy one doing it,
Kaneda might not beIieve it.
Toko.
This is something.
Natsuno.
What happened to everybody? I'm scared.
What?
You're right. We have to beIieve in them.
I'm coming.
Wait. Let me come with you.
That's good, that's good.
Natsuno.
-FIora!
-Everything's under controI now.
-Bitch! I was just enjoying it.
-Don't move!
Why don't you shoot?
FIora!
Bitch! You aImost shot me.
Everyone, tie him up.
Bitch!
Yuka!
Move.
Shit. Where are you? I'll get you all!
Kaneda didn't make it.
The six missing women were all rescued.
They are in a weakened state....