THE DESERT ISLAND STORY X
Hurry!
Are you aII right, Ayaka?
I'm sorry, I'm aII right.
She's had it.
We can't push her anymore.
Let her take a break.
Or she won't make it.
PIease, Yuka, FIora.
Nobody's behind us.
-It Iooks Iike--
-Yes.
We're on an isIand.
Toko, Iook over there.
Our boat.
We're aIone on this isIand.
With them.
Episode 1 - Castaway
You gotta be kidding.
You didn't say
anything about this costume!
Why don't you just go home?
I'm not begging you to work for me.
Toko.
Don't you Iike it, Natsuno?
FIora?
It's cute.
See? I designed it myseIf.
Isn't this too short?
That's what I Iike about it, Yuka.
It's cute.
But you can aImost see....
I came aII prepared.
A bIoomer. So Japanese. So nice.
You're a IittIe weird, FIora.
Natsuno, Toko worked hard
for tonight's party.
-PIease heIp her out.
-Ayaka, Ieave her aIone.
If you want me to wear this siIIy thing
you'II have to pay me a fortune.
That depends on your performance.
She's resisting a Iot.
Maybe she's afraid her Iegs
are not good enough to show.
I have good Iegs.
UnIike you girIs.
Hurry up, then.
We don't have much time.
Next story.
The police announced they have a lead
on the 300-million-yen burglary.
They have identified 2 suspects.
Photos of the suspects
have been released.
Are you enjoying yourseIf, Kaneda?
It'II be fun tonight.
They seem to be having fun
over there.
Maybe her dad owns the hoteI,
but what an arrogant bitch.
If you taIk Iike that,
she might not pay you.
FortunateIy this party
preparation doesn't Iook too hard.
HeIIo. I'm tonight's chef, Aoki.
You're so beautifuI.
You must be Toko.
Toko, your chef's here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're Iate. We've been waiting.
I'm Aoki, your new chef.
Nice to meet you.
WeII. Thanks for coming.
Anything wrong?
She's a IittIe fragiIe.
Don't mind her.
AII we have to do now
is to dress up this cabin.
Yuka and Mr. Aoki
wiII handIe the kitchen.
Yes, sure.
Everybody eIse,
pIease get ready for the party.
Okay.
Let's go Iie down for
a second, Ayaka.
I'm sorry, Toko.
We don't have much time.
Let's get started.
AII right.
Thanks, everybody.
The kitchen's over here.
We have it aII set up.
He's so cooI, isn't he?
I prefer more mascuIine men.
I'm sorry, Toko.
This is your first party
and I'm Iike this.
It's not your fauIt, Ayaka.
If I had....
No, Toko. You're wrong.
I wiII forget about it,
so Toko, pIease forget about it.
This is the Iast box.
How's it going with you girIs?
We dressed it up,
but it doesn't Iook any different.
Toko and Ayaka
are taking their time.
Yuka is gone with Mr. Aoki
and they're not back either.
I wonder what
they're taIking about.
Yuka is rather
aggressive, you know.
You think they're....
You're interested in him, too?
You're aIways making fun of me.
I hate you.
What is this?
What's going on?
We're moving.
The boat's moving?
AII the dressing up we did.
This is serious.
We're aIready so far away.
-Someone go check the bridge.
-I'm going.
No need to rush.
Who are you?
I heard there was a boat party.
This must be the boat.
Stop joking. Who's driving it?
This is my cruiser.
We're going back.
You don't see what's
going on, do you?
You've been so pampered...
...you can't teII if you've been
hijacked or if it's a TV show.
Just because
we're women...
...it doesn't mean you can take
advantage of us.
Whatever it is you want,
what can one man do aIone?
Behave yourseIves,
and you won't get hurt.
Mr. Aoki.
Do you think
you can get away with this?
My dad must have
sent out a search party by now.
A search party?
In this storm?
Storm?
Is this boat big enough?
If we're Iucky.
It's a gambIe.
You're insane.
It's this or a death sentence for us.
We're taking a chance
to escape to a paradise.
Why are you taking us, then?
A paradise is
no paradise without women.
Don't touch her!
No.
Let's enjoy ourseIves.
Hey, Iook happy,
you're enjoying it.
Don't touch Ayaka.
What is it with you?
Don't do anything to her.
She is....
I don't care.
But this makes it more fun.
No! HeIp, Toko, heIp!
Stop. Do it to me, if you have to.
Shut up and wait your turn.
PIease, not Ayaka.
Not Ayaka.
Look at your face, it's too much.
I won't Iet a scum Iike you
have your way.
This is good.
Why don't you
kick me around now, huh?
You're boring.
Thanks for waiting.
Ayaka!
Toko.
Toko, we'II aIways be together,
won't we?
Of course. I'II protect you, Ayaka.
Liar.
You're a Iiar. You never protected me.
Ayaka....
You didn't help me.
When I was suffering.
No. You're wrong, Ayaka.
Toko.
Ayaka.
I'm so gIad. You're aII right.
How about the others?
Are you aII right?
Untie me, pIease.
In a second, Hitomi.
What the heII are you doing?
Idiots, do you think you can run?
Run, everybody!
Wait for me.
Don't be so mean.
Take me with you.
No!
-Hitomi!
-Run! Hurry!
Hitomi.
-Ayaka, Natsuno, Iet's go.
-I'm sorry, Hitomi.
No! Don't Ieave me.
Come on, hurry.
HeIp!
Hurry! Move!
Shit.
I'm sorry, Hitomi.
I'II kiII you aII.
You wanted this, didn't you?
What?
You wanted to hunt women.
Yeah. Right.
Let's go back.
What can we do?
We'd better caII the poIice.
We don't have time.
We don't know...
...what they're doing to Hitomi.
They may be doing
something horribIe to her.
But if we go back,
they might kiII us.
Toko.
I....
Enough!
I'm going back by myseIf.
Wait, it's too dangerous
if you go aIone.
Let's go caII the poIice.
What did Ibuki do to you?
Why don't you teII me?
Answer me!
I see. He's sweet to girIs.
But I'm even sweeter.
What is everybody waiting for?
We have to run.
But we're on an isIand.
Let's hide somewhere
they won't find us.
We have to go rescue Hitomi.
Toko.
I'm worried about Natsuno, too.
You mean it, Toko?
No. Don't go.
Don't worry.
I'm just going to take a peek.
Why don't you aII hide in the cave
we saw aIong the way?
PIease sit tight and wait for me,
Ayaka, won't you?
Toko.
I warned you.
FIora, Yuka,
pIease watch after Ayaka.
No.
You're aIready enjoying it?
Ibuki trained you weII.
I'm not enjoying it.
Mine may be too big for you.
No, no more.
Looking good! You'II enjoy it!
It hurts. You're tearing me apart.
No, no.
-Go check that way.
-Bunnies, where are you hiding?
Hitomi.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Hitomi.
Are you aII right?
Mr. Aoki?
Did you see Natsuno?
No, but I was too busy running.
I see.
She went to heIp Hitomi.
We have to hurry.
Wait. I'm coming with you.
Mr. Aoki....
Wait here.
I'm going to use the radio for heIp.
-Shit, what's wrong with this?
-It's broken.
Now it's totaIed.
WeIcome back.
TO BE CONTINUED