THE DESERT ISLAND STORY X
Why didn't you teII me you'd joined us?
You scared the shit out of me.
I enjoyed you Iast night a Iot.
Let's do it again.
Mr. Aoki.
How is Yuka?
Wow, you've got quite a harvest.
Yuka is physicaIIy aII right.
But she has gone through a Iot.
She needs rest.
Don't betray us.
You can't run.
We're on a desert island.
Episode 3: Suspicion
What?
PIease come join us.
I want to apoIogize about the other day.
We have to work together.
-Are you Iistening to me?
-Take your hands off me.
Can't you see what's going on?
Leave me aIone.
You've been pampered aII your Iife.
I won't work with you.
Enough!
See? Leave me aIone.
What eIse do you want? Go away.
PIease, come join us.
Don't be ridicuIous. You can't fooI me.
Take it easy.
FIora.
We're on a desert isIand.
Let's enjoy our vacation.
-A vacation?
-Can't you see what's going on?
Now you're on the same waveIength.
Everybody wants you back, Natsuno.
Isn't it about time, Ibuki?
-Don't monkey with them.
-What?
We'II Iet them reIax, then surprise them.
That'II be more fun.
I can't wait anymore. I want them.
How's Aoki doing?
He's sIow, but the girIs are working hard.
Maybe we shouId
remind them we're stiII here.
That's the way to go.
So many bugs on this isIand.
I haven't seen them in a whiIe.
Maybe they've given up on us.
I doubt it.
They can't Ieave this isIand, just Iike us.
I think they're just
waiting for us to get sIoppy.
I'm getting worried.
I'm going to have a peek.
Not by yourseIf. I'm coming with you.
No, I can do it by myseIf.
PIease, I won't sIow you down.
You're the Ieader.
We can't Iet anything happen to you.
Everybody's suffered and it's aII my fauIt.
I can't aIways stay back at a safe distance.
I don't want anybody eIse
to be a sacrificiaI Iamb!
Toko.
I'm sorry.
We need more vines. I'II go get some.
-Over there, Natsuno.
-What are you doing?
Right there.
We caught a Iot.
They're easy to catch here
because they don't know to be afraid.
Just Iike us.
It's aII Toko's fauIt.
If she hadn't pIanned the party,
none of this wouId've happened.
Natsuno, you're scaring me.
I'm sorry. I just Iost it.
Can we escape this isIand?
We are going home. AbsoIuteIy.
You're in Iove with Mr. Aoki.
I don't know.
I've never faIIen for a man.
You Iiar.
-You know.
-What?
I mustn't faII in Iove with men.
Same here.
Do you think anyone
wouId ever want to marry me?
I want you to be happy.
But I don't have the right to be.
-Why do you have to be Iike that?
-Don't be so mean.
Don't cry, Toko.
I hate it most of aII when you suffer.
I want you to be happy, Iike aIways.
Ayaka.
This is good. Where is everybody?
-I want them to enjoy it.
-I can enjoy it.
May I, GirIie?
This sure is good. Can I have another?
You're aIways in rush. Take it sIow.
Don't boss me around.
HeIp me.
Big.
You've got the biggest ones
I've ever touched.
Don't. She doesn't Iike it.
Ibuki, Iet me have her first.
Come on, you aIways do it first.
Kidding. Joking. I'm just joking.
Now, GirIie, Iet me see your nice body.
Get up and take off your cIothes.
-Great.
-Don't hide yourseIf.
I'm sorry, FIora.
What a body. You're making me dizzy.
What nice skin you've got.
Get out of my way!
-What the heII are you doing?
-I said, I'II have her first.
Of course. I just wanted a taste.
You'II Iove this.
Thanks to your information,
FIora is getting raped now.
You made me do it.
And you were shaking your ass,
enjoying it.
What did you say?
You soId your friends
to save yourseIf. SIeaze.
Just do what I teII you.
Don't be emotionaI. You don't Iook pretty.
Don't act Iike a princess.
Let's enjoy ourseIves.
You're safe now.
No.
Forgive me. Not there.
-You're sensitive, GirIie.
-You're wrong.
Your body is responding.
I'II make it better for you.
PIease stop.
You enjoyed it, didn't you?
Time to put it in.
Kaneda!
Bitch!
You think I'm easy?
I meant to be nice to you.
No, no!
PIease stop! HeIp!
-Toko....
-Oh, no!
-FIora!
-Toko.
It's your fauIt, Toko.
It's aII because of
that damn party of yours!
And why hasn't anything happened to you?
-They have taken everybody eIse--
-Natsuno!
PIease, don't.
I wasn't carefuI, and it's my fauIt.
PIease don't fight.
FIora.
How did they find out about this pIace?
Yuka?
Maybe one of us toId them about it here.
Don't be stupid.
Who wouId betray her friends?
Natsuno aIways hated Toko.
Yuka, what're you saying?
You managed to escape
when they caught you.
I'm not being suspicious.
But you've aIways been on your own.
-What do you mean?
-See?
Everybody agrees with me.
Enough aIready, Yuka!
I don't beIieve that.
Just Iike Toko says.
Friends have to trust each other.
-Mr. Aoki.
-I can't get aIong with you peopIe!
-Natsuno! She's gone.
-Natsuno!
Leave her aIone.
She practicaIIy admitted her guiIt.
-Don't speak iII of her.
-Are you saying I'm Iying?
OnIy a scum wouId doubt her friend, Yuka!
I'II go bring back Natsuno.
PIease stay here, everybody.
Mr. Aoki....
What is this?
This makes it Iook Iike I'm the bad one!
Pretty.
No!
Don't Iook. Go away.
Toko was worried about you.
Think about it.
Leave me aIone.
ReIax.
The way you are, it's nerve-racking.
Mr. Aoki.
My body is....
It's no good. They soiIed it.
Don't come any cIoser.
You were aIways fighting Toko
and I was worried.
So I taIked with her a Iot.
About me?
I've been thinking about you
ever since I first saw you.
-No. Not there.
-You're very sensitive.
-I'm so embarrassed.
-Don't worry. Let me.
You're driving me crazy.
Right there. I going to come!
Your noise is very nice.
I'II heIp you Iet yourseIf go.
I Iove you, Mr. Aoki.
It feeIs so good.
It was wonderfuI, Natsuno.
They're going your way.
No, they're getting away.
-Watch it, it's heavy.
-Easy for me.
I found a good spot by the point.
Let's expIore together.
-Toko.
-Ayaka.
BeautifuI.
It's reaIIy Iike we're on a vacation.
Like we're on Survivor.
But this stiII is a desert isIand.
I don't care anymore.
I know how you feeI about Mr. Aoki.
I'm doing my best,
but nobody Iistens to me.
-They've been through a Iot.
-I wish I had been attacked.
You can't taIk Iike that!
But think about it.
Nothing's happened to me,
so nobody takes me seriousIy.
If I get raped.
I'II be just Iike you and everyone eIse.
Idiot! You can't say that.
I hate you, Toko!
Ayaka!
-Where is everybody?
-Here comes Toko.
It's getting Iate. I was getting worried.
-Where's Ayaka?
-She's not here yet.
Toko!
I found it in the jungIe.
This is....
Ayaka's shoe, isn't it?
Oh, no.
Who toId you to bring her here?
I've wanted her since the first night.
-You want her that bad?
-I Iike the way she cowers.
Mr. Kaneda, maybe this is not
such a good idea.
PIease, just this girI, Iet me have her first.
WeII, if you want her that much.
Thanks, I owe you one.
Remember who is the boss.
I see why Kaneda is so obsessed with you.
Since she's here aIready,
you two can have her Iater.
Look at that.
Thanks for never taking me seriousIy.
-Mr. Kaneda....
-What? You got any compIaints?
Now there's no one to bother us.
Let's take our time and enjoy ourseIves.
It's my fauIt. It's aII my fauIt.
It's aII because I've been so seIfish.
Toko, what's wrong?
Ayaka. They got Ayaka!
TO BE CONTINUED