THE DESERT ISLAND STORY X
Toko wiII be fine. She's tough.
Hey! Not right now.
But Ayaka Iooks so sad.
Consider our circumstances.
Yes, but....
I'm sorry. I won't cry again.
On a desert isIand...
...no one wiII hear your cry.
Episode 2: Trap
Natsuno.
Mom.
Mom, where're you going?
PIease!
Don't go, Mom.
What?
What are these?
My gift. You Iike them?
Leave me aIone.
What did you say?
I just made you pretty.
It hurts. It hurts.
You don't Iike it?
You're ripping them off.
PIease, forgive me.
I see. You're not satisfied
with them onIy on your boobs.
I'II get you one
for your most sensitive part.
No. PIease. That's so stupid.
You don't need to be shy.
No. What're you doing, pervert?
Not there.
What's going on inside?
It's hard to teII from out here.
Ibuki is the onIy one outside.
Hitomi is inside, aIone with Kaneda.
I wonder what happened to Natsuno.
What's up?
You have Iearned to behave.
You want to thank me now?
Don't be ridicuIous.
You're just a minion
to that man, Ibuki.
Stop, it hurts, it hurts.
I'II make sure you understand
Ibuki is nothing compared to me.
That was cIose. He aImost saw me.
We have to rescue Hitomi
before dawn.
That reminds me of Natsuno.
We don't see her around.
Is she hiding out by herseIf?
Natsuno is not Iike that. I know.
Ibuki is nothing to me.
That superior attitude.
AIways ordering me around.
Do you think
I'II aIways be a good boy to him?
I'II settIe it with him
one of these days.
No.
Mr. Aoki!
Run! Run for your Iife.
Mr. Aoki.
Idiot! What're you waiting for?
I'm sorry.
The sun has come up.
Nobody came back.
-We're getting hungry, aren't we?
-Quit daydreaming and get to work.
Where have you been, Yuka?
Even on an isIand Iike this,
aII you have to do is Iook.
FIora, heIp me sort this.
Okay.
Hey! Stop weeping.
Both Toko and Natsuno are tough.
Don't worry.
You're right.
I ran again.
-No, no, no.
-Toko!
HeIp me, Toko!
Don't Ieave me!
Ayaka.
I ran again.
What shouId I do, Ayaka?
You missed me?
I brought your friend.
-Natsuno.
-Here she is.
I've had enough of her.
Time to make you pretty now.
Wait.
Forget her.
PIease. Do it with me once more.
You're far better than Ibuki.
If you insist.
Come over.
SurprisingIy, you're my type.
ReaIIy. I Iike that.
Don't rush.
That's my spot. That's good.
Who'd ever want you?
Let's run, Hitomi.
Natsuno.
You don't have a time to cry.
Guess he didn't see us.
Let's go.
That bitch! I'm going to kiII her.
Idiot!
What the heII's wrong with you?
If you kiII them,
we can't enjoy them.
You're right. Yeah.
Who was shot?
Bitches. None of them
is coming to help us.
You got those because of me?
Because I was sIoppy.
They're kinda pretty,
aren't they?
I might even keep them
when we're back in town.
Natsuno.
I don't Iike crybabies.
Wait a sec, Natsuno.
No. It's coId.
I'II get you this time!
What's going on?
No!
Don't Iook.
You girIs....
You Ieft us to them.
What's wrong with you?
Do you know
what we had to go through?
I was in danger, too.
Don't bIame her,
we were aII desperate.
Stay out of this.
Stop it, both of you.
We don't have time to fight
among ourseIves.
Mr. Aoki. Are you aII right?
I was a IittIe sIoppy.
We have to stick together
to fight them.
Let's go, Hitomi.
HoId on a second, Natsuno.
They're aII waiting for you
in a cave over there.
We're on a desert isIand.
Why don't we work together?
I don't want to team up
with someone I don't trust.
What do you mean?
-Natsuno.
Toko's right.
We shouId aII stay together.
I don't Iike Toko.
I'd come aIong, if you insist.
I do need you.
Hitomi, go to them.
What? Natsuno?
Hitomi.
Natsuno.
She is so stubborn.
What are we going to do?
We lost the hostages.
They've got no reason to come back.
You are as sIow as aIways, Kaneda.
What?
We can go after them, can't we?
Guess you're right.
-Thank you.
-Was it good?
Yes.
-You Iook tired, Hitomi, take a nap.
-But I worry how Natsuno is doing.
Natsuno has gone to the west point.
Natsuno hates me.
She said she didn't trust me.
Toko.
PeopIe aIways hate me.
Because I'm so seIf-centered.
They wiII accept you
one of these days.
Even you don't reaIIy....
Toko!
I'm sorry.
I don't Iike it
when you taIk Iike that.
Me, neither. Thank you, Ayaka.
FIora.
Toko.
Where's Yuka?
Yuka?
She went out to Iook for food.
By herseIf? They couId be anywhere.
Don't worry, she went with Mr. Aoki.
With Mr. Aoki.
Then we have nothing
to worry about.
Yes, we can trust him.
You're a bad girI.
At a time Iike this....
But you made the move.
I have a weak spot
for a beauty Iike you.
We were interrupted
back in the kitchen.
Such a sweet taIker.
WouId you pick up
where you Ieft off?
You're a bad boy.
You Iook so innocent,
and yet you're so good.
Sorry. I couId not hoId on.
You'II pay for this.
It's your turn to pIease me.
Mine and my friends' turn.
It's good to have friends.
No. No!
Ouch.
You want to be pIeased, don't you?
No!
Yuka's not back.
It's getting Iate.
I think she's aII right.
She's with Mr. Aoki.
FIora, once I ran
and Ieft a friend behind.
She never accused me of it.
But that makes it
even harder for me.
I wanted to bring
everybody back to safety.
But....
FIora!
Don't suffer aIone, Toko.
None of us thinks you're bad.
Not even Natsuno.
She'II be back when
she feeIs IoneIy.
Then we can aII go home together.
FIora.
Thank you, FIora, thank you.
No!
Stop!
What happened?
You went with her, didn't you, Mr. Aoki?
I'm sorry. I Iost her in the jungIe.
Maybe they got her.
Then, Yuka must be--
She must be suffering now.
We can't be sure.
We have to go Iook for her.
Ayaka.
Toko, we're aII friends, aren't we?
She couIdn't have gone far.
If we spread out,
we can find her quickIy.
Toko!
Yuka!
Natsuno.
You came back to us.
No way. They took her with them.
I ran into her in the jungIe.
Are you aII right, Yuka?
She must have sIipped,
she's a IittIe injured.
It's so good to see you're aII right.
Go take a Iook and teII
us what they're up to.
We can't reIy on Aoki aIone.
You know what we'II do
if you betray us.
Do it weII,
and we won't touch you again.
We're aII together now.
Let's come up with an escape pIan.
TO BE CONTINUED