You know, it's not like I hate it.
What do you mean? Hate what?
You know what.
You know, everyone is gone for today.
Otokawa-san.
You're wet.
No.
Oh no!
Oh, no. That was fast!
I'm sorry!
Don't apologize.
Let's do it one more time.
You're terrible.
I'm sorry!
Honestly, what's wrong with you?
No, it shouldn't be like this.
I'm a bit disappointed.
So, what is wrong with you, then?
It seems I've become hypersensitive.
Welcome everyone.
I would like to give a warm welcome to the clients of our Morimoto group.
Now then.
Many of the women you are already familar with.
They have been trained, to suit the tastes of each and every one of you.
Please, enjoy them all.
I want you to take a good look at everyone down there!
All of you...
...will have the honor to service one of these influential gentlemen!
Only those who pledge
allegiance to Morimoto...
...and hone their bodies to the utmost limit...
...will be given the honor to
participate in a banquet like this!
Yes!
I've finally got it!
Now all I need to do is look for the list of names.
But first, I'll have to send this.
Damn, no reception.
Now what? Huh?! This is bad!
What could this be?
I have no choice!
It's a trash chute!
Morimoto, should be feared.
I'm safe.
You. What's wrong?
Oh, um. I took the wrong turn.
I see! You're one of those girls owned by Leona-ojousama, right?
Yes! Silly me, I got so lost.
I have an idea.Why don't you play with us for a while?
New staff members almost never come down here.
Stop!
Excuse me, everyone.
Today, the hero we are proud of, Araki Madoka-san, will report.
Fellow members!
I, Araki Madoka, have returned safely...
...from my undercover investigation of the Morimoto mansion.
Just as our initial
information claimed...
...the Morimoto family offers a harem service...
...for members of the political and financial society.
I saw with my own eyes our school alumni performing at the location!
Unfortunately, it was too dark to see what was going on in detail.
Regardless, it does't change the fact that we are in a difficult situation!
The unsavory heresy of the Morimoto family, grasping our weaknesses...
...whether it be socially or financially and using it to their advantage.
I have also discovered a list of students which are blackmailed.
This secret list is kept hidden and contains...
...the features of body and spirit of each of our noble comrades.
And I have found its whereabouts.
Here and now, this horrifying list must be seized and made public.
Therefore I would like to create a team and a strategy to obtain this very list.
Any volunteers?
Anyone?
Honestly, it's a good thing it's weekend.
No one from the circle will come.
Don't worry about anything...
...I'll let everyone know that you'll to be studying all night long.
OK.
Luckily there are many nursing diapers lying around.
So, don't let it bother you, OK?
I'm sorry about everything.
It's OK. Just hurry up and fix it.
Oh, no!
Are you sure it's a good idea to force our way in?
We're not forcing our way in.
Preparations are being made.
After that.
Takigawa-kun? Tell me what's going on?
Hi.
So are you telling me that
you're starting a revolution?
A revolution may scare people.
It's about restoring justice.
We are going to defeat the evil.
Hujiwara and Endou are also participating in this group?
Yup! Because...
...usually we are pursuing cases that cannot be solved, right?
But this feels more like it could be successful! Come on.
My thoughts exactly!
So, you should join us, Otokawa-san!
It's probably not possible for us
to run into any vampires or skyfish...
...but, our case is more about real everyday stress!
Otokawa-san.
I once failed a written exam.
I had no idea...
...that the supplementary class for failing would be that disgusting act.
They said they don't need our remorse.
To learn the consequences physically...
...they made me do many things...
...and inserted many things...
...and made many things come out.
Right there, I decided...
...this tragedy must be
stopped by somebody.
Even yesterday, when I was investigating the Morimoto mansion...
...I made a mistake and was caught by some men.
And then...
I had to take ten shots from them!
Ten shots!
Learn to refrain a little!
But, I won't lose! I vowed that I will,
without a doubt, send them to hell.
You, and the power of the dormitory students are needed!
So, please! For everyone's sake!
Even if you say that.
I know that you people have a thin relation with Leona's group.
Of course.
If we fight seriously, we might change something for the future.
Otokawa-san!
There's one thing that's been bothering me.
You see, he's...
What?! It's leaking?
Shh! No, don't say anything!
Really, I've heard rumors about you being amazing...
...I guess it's really true.
Please, stop.
Um, does it feel good each time?
Why don't you give me a break, Momoe-chan!
Hayami-kun, Morimoto Leona jumps in, because you're like that.
Be more straightforward!
Straightforward?
Hey, why don't you have the nurse, Kawahara-sensei, take a look?
Kawahara-sensei?
Yeah. She may know some magical healing methods...
...and besides, there is one more thing. Kawahara-sensei is our advisor.
Oh, yes.
Speaking of Kawahara-sensei...
...I have heard rumors that she is opposing the school committee.
She is someone we definitely want on our side.
Oh, I see.
Let's not do this. I have a bad feeling about it.
Just what are you trying to say?
No, I'm being serious.
The animal inside of me is being very cautious.
That animal being there in the first place is a problem.
No particularly unusual excitement.
Well, everything is normal.
Anyhow, let's do a more precise examination.
Even with the school equipment,
I can examine various things.
Is something the matter?
Oh, nothing.
Sensei, can you keep this a secret?
I understand.
You're very sincere, Otokawa-san.
Um, I think I'll be going now.
Well then, give my regards to everyone.
Thank you.
Well, now...
...would you like medicine? Acupuncture? Vasectomy?
There are many choices in today's world.
Um, let's start with the examination for now.
Well, I'll just give you some sleeping pills for now.
Why don't you sleep here until I get ready?
OK.
So you want to steal this list of names?
Yes. The list is holding all of our weaknesses.
You must understand how important it is.
Really?
So, the necessary information has been gathered?
Yes! As we speak, a few of our comrades are making preparations!
All we need is the group to carry out the plan.
Well, we have already been put through terrible things.
This is not the time to think!
Not every battle in the war against the Social Club can be won!
We just had a complete defeat!
Just when I finally forgot about it!
I'd prefer not to bring up any meaningless talk.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Well, I assume you are still joining up, right?
Of course.
All right!
Everyone gather around!
Yeah!
Well, then.
Hey, by the way, where's Ta-kun?
That's right. What happened to Ta-kun?
He's got a lot of things to do.
I'm sure he will be very busy all night long.
Ah, yes, yes. He's helping us out.
Hm?! Oh? Why am I?
Um, Sensei? What's this?
I'm sorry, Hayami-kun.
Sensei.
You've heard about me, right?
About how things aren't going very well with the school.
The reason...
...I am a graduate of this school and I know it very well.
This school, no, the Morimoto group, is indeed cruel.
I, also, fought desperately.
I still do, even now. Just with my feelings though.
But, I just can't do it.
A body that has been trained cannot hold back. Do you understand?
I knew it.
I couldn't refrain myself.
Hayami-kun, why don't you leave it up to me?
Hayami-kun, endure this.
Damm it!
Hayami-kun! This is just beginning!
Hayami-kun!
Amazing! What is this? It's incredible!
Preparations here are complete!
Everyone, let's go!
All right!
Just leave it to me!