It looks like the security is down. We'll be OK.
All in all, our information seem to be correct.
I know it just can't be wrong.
Maiko, where's the basement passage?
Over here.
Yeah!
This is the interception team. Can you hear me?
Over.
I can hear you, captain.
Mapping is also complete.
We're heading down to the basement now.
Contact us if anything happens. Over.
Affirmative. Leave it to us.
Ok, let's go!
All right!
This school has a secret superior organization.
A superior organization?
Yes. Even in the financial society...
...only a selected few are allowed into the secret organization.
Students with well formed bodies advance even more.
They'll get to service important men...
...from around the globe with their bodies.
That's horrible.
Using sex to control humans yields the best results.
Being a member of the Morimoto group is very difficult.
I was also involved in that group.
It doesn't feel bad being told that you're pretty and attractive.
I was inclined to try it out and was thoroughly trained. Then...
And then?
It was terrible. It the end, I was dropped right before the debut.
From that moment on, I was treated like trash.
It was cruel!
I hate the Morimoto family, who made my body this way.
But as you know, hate itself does nothing.
If you don't fight, nothing will change.
Sensei! That's right! We must fight then!
Sensei, the thing is.
A secret list of names?
That's right. Everyone calls it the slaves list.
If we get that list in our hands and leak it to the media...
...we can overturn the Morimoto group.
That's what this is about.
Sensei?
You should rest for a bit.
This is it!
Ruri! Yuuki! It's your turn!
Leave it to us then!
Hey, you! What are you doing?
Yes!
There is nothing I can really do about these types.
Are you saying to give up after we've come this close?!
What about all the trouble we went through to get here!
Well, you know, I'm just a computer geek.
Hey, just wait a minute.
Right to 16. Left to 28. Then, right.
It's written on the back.
Leona's handwriting.
Onee-sama, there is a call for you.
Oh, yes, this is a surprise.
What's it? How do you know about all of this?
Yes, I understand.
Leona, confirm the security of the mansion.
Especially of the vault!
Onee-sama! Someone has hacked into our computers!
The safe!
Alert all guards within the mansion!
We must not let them get away!
We've been discovered!?
What? That was too fast!
This is bad.
If they found out, there's nothing we can do.
All we can do is to get out here right now
Maiko, find us a different route now.
Onee-sama, the scrambler will be OK.
Notify all guards!
The criminals have taken top secret documents.
Do whatever it takes to catch them!
There are no restrictions on how they are apprehended.
Live ammunition is allowed.
All guards! Dispatch now!
Um, what is going on?
I'm really sorry.
I just couldn't let it happen.
I see you've awaken, Hayami Takurou.
The principal?
Kawahara has told me of your foolish plans.
Just be prepared!
Captain? Do you undestand? Do you read me over?
This could be bad.
Hey, they're still deep inside right?
I wonder if they're ok.
What's that?
Earthquake?
No it's not!
Reina-sama. We have captured three of the suspected individuals.
Good job. And what about retrieving the documents?
A vehicle outside of the premises has been alerted.
It seems they were relaying transmissions to the escaping group.
I see. Then have them taken into custody.
I will leave all of any methods of interrogation up to you.
Roger!
Hey, what are you doing with us?
What do you mean? Of course, we're interrogating.
No!
Stop it!
What are we going to do? The others have been captured.
They were easily spotted just outside the mansion.
We slipped through. You see.
Oh, Morimoto Reina.
To all the trespassers...
...as you can see, your members have been captured.
There is no way of escape.
Just give up and surrender.
What?
As you can see, a new friend seems to have just arrived.
Welcome, Hayami Takurou-kun.
Why Ta-kun?
Why?!
The safety of these people depends entirely on your actions.
Turn yourselves in at once! This is an order.
We'll have to give them up.
There is nothing that can be done but to abandon them.
But why?
Because, we finally got our hands on the list.
After all that you want to return it to them?
But, we don't know what's going to happen to Hayami-kun and the others.
There is no way we can leave them here.
No, we can't.
In a revolution, there are always casualities.
You cannot be so sympathetic!
I understand. You guys go on ahead. Don't worry about a thing.
I'll be able to save them all by myself.
Let's leave it up to Otokawa.
Our job now is to let the world know of this list.
Saori.
You've been good help, Kawahara.
Yes, thank you, Reina-sama.
Because of you, we had enough time to respond to a tight situation.
Thank you very much.
Hayami-kun.
What?
Will you please be kind enough...
...to use your superb abilities to assist the Morimoto family?
I don't believe there are any plans to do so.
I see. What a shame that is!
Kawahara-sensei! Why did you betray us?
People are not always white or black.
That's true, Sensei.
Your skin was a beautiful pink color.
It was very pretty!
Reina-sama.
The commandos have captured one of the members.
Otokawa Saori!
I'll leave her up to you.
You have done a foolish thing, Otokawa Saori-san.
Well, at least I'm not as foolish as you people.
Morimoto Leona.
That is true.
Where is the name list that you stole from us?
How should I know? My only concern is to rescue my friends.
You have to release Hayami-kun and the others right now!
Oh, my! So you think that you are the heroine of justice, do you?
Moreover, a silly one.
Show this conceited Miss Piggy the true horror of the Morimoto family!
As much as you like!
Roger!
What's that you doing?!
Now, go ahead and enjoy it fully.
Kaoru!
Yes. Leona-sama.
Finish her!
Otokawa-san has been captured?
Kawahara-sensei.
I don't like this.
Kaneda, what should we do?
We've been completely surrounded.
We should give up and surrender.
What are you saying? Justice always wins.
Surrendering is not one of our choices!
Do you hear what I am saying?
Hey, look at over there.
Looks like we can get out from here.
Let's go.
Kawahara-sensei!
So, where did the others disappear to?
Besides, this mansion is too large!
Oh!
It's a dead end.
Now what?
OK, jump.
No way!
There's no choice. We are gonna have to go back.
What's that?
Water.
Run!!
Everyone! This way!
Oh.
I will not let your sacrifice go to waste!
Hey, there. It's your old buddy.
Oh!
I owe you for those last ten shots.
Now you just follow me. This is the way out of the mansion.
Oh, thanks a lot!
Otokawa-san.
Hayami-kun.
Let's get out of here.
I can't. My body is numb.
I knew it.
Kawahara-sensei?
That's happened to me before.
It's a side effect of the sex enancing medicine.
You'll be ok. Don't worry. I know how to cure it immediately.
But how?
Listen carefully, Otokawa-san.
All you have to do, is to cum again.
Just cum?
Yes. The poison is active over a certain period of time...
...but the effects can be removed by female hormones.
If you feel it, and cum, you'll be able to move right away.
Hey!
In the end, all of us were able to escape from the Morimoto mansion.
But, for us renegades, there were sad news awaiting.
The name list got wet, and the ink smeared.
Not one word was legible.
All that was gained was lost.
The Morimoto family has quieted down as expected.
It must mean that they are worried...
...since they don't know about our mistake.
It was an unexpected conclusion for this large case. But, oh well.
Because...
...for me, a beautiful goddess is smiling upon me.