Hm? What's wrong?
What's this?
This guy is amazing.
His thing just started to expand inside my mouth.
It becomes longer and reaches the back of my throat.
It's like a living being.
Just imagining something like this inside of me, makes me...
I...
Matsuno!
Yes.
The examination has not yet ended.
I'm sorry.
Your nipples are already firm.
Listen carefully, Matsuno.
You are not allowed to lay a finger on him.
He is for the pleasure of my sister as you know.
Understood, Reina-sama.
Now, continue with the examination.
You've passed the exam. I must give you an A.
This should be it.
Excuse me.
Is... is anyone there?
What?
Who's there?
I'm Hayami! I'm a transfer student. I'll be staying here.
A transfer student? Oh! Hayami Takurou-kun?
Yes!
I see.
You should've said something. You surprised me!
I'm sorry!
Welcome to Saint Arcadia School dormitory!
I'm the manager, Otokawa Saori.
Nice to meet you.
Ah, yes. My pleasure.
Hm? Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
I was thinking how pretty...
Huh?
Oh, I mean this is a pretty place.
The building is large, as you can see.
But there are few people living here.
How many are there now?
Well, actually you are the 5th.
Interestingly enough all the others are female.
Really?
But, well, I wouldn't get your hopes up if I were you.
You'll most likely be disappointed.
Huh? Oh.
Yuuki.
Hm?
This is the transfer student, Hayami-kun!
Oh! It's the rumored one!
I'm Miyagishi Yuuki. Nice to meet you!
Hello.
Let's move on.
Oh, um, huh?
Yes. That's good.
Well, ok, for now, here is the key to the room. Do you...?
Hey, is there anything to eat? I'm so hungry!
Oh! Are you the new transfer guy?
You know, that's not the point!
Put on some clothes!
How many times have I told you not to walk around naked?
Why not? But my bra and panties are gone!
Oh! I'm Nonomiya Ruri. You can call me Nonomi-chan.
Enough already! Come on!
See you later!
Hm?
Hah?
Oh, um.
Hm?
I thought maybe it's time to introduce myself.
My name is Kaneda Maiko.
Dripping wet.
Sorry about that. I just try to get used to it.
I'll do something about it eventually.
Yuuki. You're inserting it again.
Shut up! What's wrong with that? It feels good!
You, idiots.
Could this be heaven?
Seems like I've come to a really nice place.
At this rate, starting tomorrow, my school lifestyle would be like...
Oh? Is someone there?
Ah, could it be?
Miyagishi-san?!
I knew it! What perfect timing this is!
Hey, what do you think you are doing? There's no escaping.
Hm? Ah.
C'mon. Why don't we just enjoy that we bumped into each other?
What are you doing?
What are you saying?
Doesn't that feel good?
This is bad!
Woah?! What's this? Maybe I really should if it's bad.
Actually, I have brought lotion!
Huh?
Please.
No way!
I'm going to cum.
That's ok. Let it out.
Delicious! Now it's your turn to please me.
Miyagishi-san, something is strange.
I put a vibe in my ass. Feel it?
What's this? It's expanding inside me and thrusting deeper. That's amazing.
It's so good.
I can't hold it any longer!
I am going to raise it a level.
I can feel the vibration. It's too amazing. It's just too amazing!
Me, too!
Go ahead and cum! Now!
You're amazing. Oh, yes, oh, more.
So, this is the school I'll be attending starting today. What a great feeling!
Yes. Well, it is a splendid building.
Oh? Look over there!
Everyone is standing in a line.
Huh? Oh!
Huh?
Hey, what do you think you are doing?
That hurts!
I have never seen your face. Right, Otokawa?
Answer her!
I'm Hayami Takurou, the transfer student.
And, you're introducing him?
Good morning.
That's just not right.
It should be "Good morning to you, Leona-sama".
Takurou-kun!
Good morning to you, Leona-sama.
Good morning, Hayami.
See you, good bye.
Leona-sama, what is she?
Hurry, come on. Let's get going.
Oh, wait for me!
I see. Thank you.
Well then, you'll teach the class normally. No, you must hold it in.
Yes, understood.
Onee-sama, I just met him.
He seems like he's pretty good!
Is it ok if I take him?
Yes, of course. Do as you please.
Depending on the special training, he will develop more.
I've been admitted starting today. My name is Hayami Takurou.
Nice to meet everyone.
You'll be sitting behind Otokawa-san.
Huh?
Hm, this is great.
Hello.
Hi.
Hm? What's that?!
That's the Social Club building.
Huh? What's the Social Club?
I'll show you!
Who are you three?
We're from the Social Club.
The Social Club?
Yes, I'll show you what the Social Club is about. Come here!
Oh, hey!
What are you doing?
This is a small greeting from the Social Club.
Now then, today we'll start at page 83.
Wow. It's getting really big!
What is this?
So tell me, what's the matter?
His thing started thrusting deep into my throat. Further and further.
Thrusting into your throat?
So tell me, what are you guys?
We're members of the Social Club. The advisor is Matsuno Kaori.
What?
The teacher?
Yes.
We have come here to invite you to join our Social Club.
You understood?
Is that what the teacher decided?
No, this is an order from our club president. Didn't you know that?
Order from the club president?
That's right.
Today after the school, make sure to come to register for our club.
You understand now, don't you?
Hey, wait!
So who is the club president?
It's Morimoto Leona-sama.
Leona.
Well, we'll be waiting today after class.
Takurou-kun, you don't have to go to the Social Club if you don't want to.
Um, yeah.
Oh, um, this is. That girl.
Oh, you idiot!
This guy is amazing.
His thing just started to expand inside my mouth.
It becomes longer and reaches the back of my throat.
It's like a living being.
That's the same way I felt.
I would definitely like to have a taste of that. Then, bring Hayami here.
About that.
He's gone?
Yes. Gone. We're sorry.
He's got some nerve ignoring my invitation.
Listen. I don't care what it takes, you bring him here.
Yes!
Understood?!
There is no human that can defy me. He should understand that!
Hayami-kun, what's wrong? Are you getting sick? Are you ok?
Don't worry, I'm ok. I think somebody must be talking about me.
Then it's ok.
Hey, Yuuki. It's hamburger again.
Yes, it's hamburger again.
Saori's hamburgers are good, but to eat them everday.
Hey, I'm the one being forced to cook everyday.
You, too, Hayami-kun!
No, I was wondering if it was ok that I didn't go to the Social Club today.
It's okay, but forget about that place.
Oh, no. I'm wondering what kind of person Morimoto Leona might be?!
Morimoto Leona.
She is the daughter of the Morimoto financial group...
...who manages our Saint Arcadia School...
...and is the president of the school association.
Also, she is the president of the Social Club.
Her older sister is the school principal, Morimoto Reina.
They are famous sisters even in the society.
The main attention of daily operations is the Social Club.
And then, the contents will be.
That's enough. Stop talking about it already!
That's right! He'll find out eventually.
I bet your family must be going through a lot of troubles
Don't get involved in such trivial things.
Oh, what?
You're in the same position.
Hey, what do you want to do for lunch?
I think I'll have pastries.
Me, too.
Hayami-kun, you want to go to the cafeteria?
Sure. Oh, but maybe I'll do this first.
What?
It's a physical exam.
They said to come during lunch.
What? I see. Be careful, Hayami-kun.
Huh? What do you mean?
Oh, just a feeling.
I see.
Good afternoon.
Oh, welcome! Let's see, Hayami Takurou-kun, correct?
Yes.
Hm? You're nervous.
No, not really.
I see.
Well then, can you lie down over here?
Excuse me.
It's ok. Don't worry.
Hey! It's you!
You're that girl from the Social Club.
Where am I? What's going on?
Huh?
Welcome to the Social Club! Hayami Takurou!
What?!
Hayami, do you have any idea...
...that I brought you here, so that you can help us with a Social Club event.
So, what kind of event is that, then?
This is to pursue the joy of love.
Also, everyone has been looking for a new member.
Right at that time, Reina-oneesama told me about the interesting new student.
After the admittance exam...
...do you remember
Reina-oneesama's interview?
Oh! Now that you mention it, I can't remember after that.
You see. Reina-oneesama had you take a test.
My test.
Yes! She told me: "That one is wonderful. I insist that you take him!"
What are you saying?
Think of it as an honor.
I'm giving in and allowing you to be my own personal pet!
That's nonsense!
Oh, no you don't. You don't realize that you can never go against me.
Why is that?!
Well, do you have any idea why you were able to enter this school?
What?
Everyone related to this school is tied to my Morimoto financial group.
Your father is the same.
An accounting manager who used all of the company's money.
He got caught and should have lost everything.
Yet he was able to easily change jobs.
How do you know that?
Well, the future of all financial groups depends on talented people.
In exchange for helping all the humble citizens...
...we had them give us back a tribute in return.
That is the students of our school!
That's absurd!
But you know that story doesn't matter.
The only thing I really
want now is...you!
I must refuse.
Well, you can't. I must also test you.
Now, it is time to prepare for the feast!
Move over.
You! Fill me up! Oh, yes, you do.
Yes, I am cumming!
Next it's my turn!
With this, you can't cum even if you wanted to.
Hineki, slowly build up his energy...
...and then take every single bit of him that you want.
Yes. Isn't that unbearable? Isn't that hard?
What's that?
Looks like it would be worthwhile to eat up.
That's amazing.
His fingers. They're better than a vibe.
It's strange. I've never felt like this.
I'm cumming!
Hayami-kun!
Ah. Hm?
That sure was a long physical. Did something happen?
No, nothing. Ouch!!
I used up my hip, I mean, I twisted my hip.
Really? Hey, Hayami-kun. Do you think you are going to join any clubs?
Clubs? Oh, I haven't thought about it yet.
This is just a recommendation...
...but, here, what do you think about the Paranormal Studies Club?
Paranormal? Studies?
Yeah. I am the club president and we're recruiting members right now.
Occult, huh? No, I think I'll look around first.
I see. What a shame!
If you don't hurry and decide soon...
...you're going to get dragged into the Social Club.
Huh? Ouch!
Hayami-kun, is something wrong?
Hayami! You have passed the test. Wonderful results!
Come back to the Social Club tomorrow for registration.
Wait!
You are just too late! Hayami-kun has already signed up...
...for the Paranormal Studies Club!
Hayami, I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
Huh?
Hey! Wait!
Honestly! I don't care if she's the principal's sister.
I will never forgive her.
I'm never going to give him up. Not my dear Hayami-kun!
Huh? "My?"