This is all mine.
Now, stick it in and satisfy me.
Amazing! Unbelievable!
Oh! Incredible! I've never felt like this before!
No!
It's marvelous! It's so marvelous!
Oh, yes. Marvelous!
Oh, yes. Please cum. Cum!!
All students!
There is a fire in the Social Club building
Ruri-chan?
Please calmly exit the building.
If not, you're going to burn to death!
Wait! Where are you going? Are you leaving me here?
Wait!
Now!
Otokawa-san!
Takurou-kun!
Let's go!
Yeah!
A fire?
We haven't set the fire yet.
I don't know what the hell is going on, but now's our chance!
We have to keep going as planned!
OK!
One. Two. One. Two.
This was a big success!
Yes, I agree. Mai-Mai is amazing! There's nothing you can't do!
Well, yeah.
All right! Let's all go to greet them!
Yeah!
Tell me what's wrong, Mai-Mai?
Well, don't you think we could've watched a bit longer?
Oh, yeah.
Ouch. Hey, what is going on here?
Hm?!
No!
Stop at once!
What are you doing?
Who do you think I am? Put me down!
I said put me down!
Watching you do all that, it looks like great fun.
Ogiwara. Lick with a little more pressure.
Yes, Reina-sama.
Matsuno, I want you to go and check on the Social Club right now.
Yes. Um... Reina-sama...
What?
I would also like Ogiwara-sensei... to do that to me... if that is OK.
That's not possible. You see, Ogiwara is still my partner.
Now go!
Yes. Excuse me.
Hurry Takurou. I wonder if that child is the key?
Um, everyone. Thank you so much. Because of you, I was saved.
What are you apologizing for, Saorin?
Yeah. You have nothing to apologize for.
The bad ones are the stupid Social Club people.
Oh, thank you.
But I am the one who snuck in without thinking about the consequences.
That's not true. Morimoto Leona is the bad one.
Otokawa-san, you don't have to worry about it.
Oh? What's wrong? Did something happen?
Saorin is all red. Ta-kun is all red, as well!
Hey! I know you guys know what's going on. So, stop making fun!
But now...
...it's going to be a full confrontation between us and the Social Club.
They'll probably figure out it was me.
Come on. If it really gets bad...
...we can just hand Takurou over to them.
Oh, that's right!
What are you saying? But, then...
Yes, that might be a good idea.
Not you, too, Otokawa-san.
I'm just kidding!
Give me a break already!
I'm running out of patience!
Cut the ropes immediately or I'll become very irritated!
Hey, tell me who the hell you are!
Testing. Testing.
Morimoto Leona.
Today, we will deliver heaven's punishment upon you.
Punishment? What are you talking about?
What is the meaning of this?
If you don't stop right now, there is no way I'll forgive you.
Hey! Calm down! It's nothing!
Morimoto Leona, due to the wrongful actions you have taken...
...the Gods are angry and have decided that this is unforgiveable.
Today, as messengers from God, we are here to admonish you.
Well then, I'm ready to punish you. Prepare yourself!
Morimoto Leona, how long will you last?
Now, let's begin!
Yeah!
Now, let us prepare the feast!
Hey, me too.
Your breath stinks! Like an old man!
You...you be quiet!
Dammit.
Onee-sama! I was attacked and forced to do things I cannot even say.
And you are saying, that you are not going to do anything about it?
That's not true...
...but first you should tell me exactly what happened.
What happened? Well, that's...
Well, this and that, and all kinds of things...
It happened to me.
I got it... I understand Leona.
Matsuno, please bring her here.
Hm?
Now, tell me exactly what happened in the administrator's office.
Admininistrator office?
Yes. See, yesterday...
I stayed behind to check the equipment...
...but a female student came by.
A female student?
Yes. I asked what her business was, but she didn't respond.
Then, she got closer to me...
...and before I realized it, she was kissing me.
No! I can't hold it! I'm going to cum!
Did you?
Yes. I'm sorry. I couldn't help it, it just felt so good.
During that time, the administration system was taken over...
...and Leona ran into some trouble.
Who is that woman?
She must be the one giving the orders!
Who and where is this female technician?
A dormitory student, Kaneda Maiko.
A friend of your favorite, Hayami-kun.
She's the one.
Well, Leona, I have an idea. Would you like to hear it?
Hm?
A masked force?
Yes, as insulting as possible.
Yes. That's it. That is the path I must follow!
You just wait. Kaneda Maiko!
Hm?
Sudou from the photography club.
We are here to punish you on the wooden horse for your peeping...
...but if you meet our conditions, we'll let you go.
Will you listen to the conditions?
Kyoutou-sensei, thanks for your hard work today.
That was very pleasurable indeed.
That sexy witch, Morimoto Leona.
We put her through a merciless ordeal.
Because of her, we teachers were able to do so many terrible things.
From today on, we shall take back what we've lost!
Machida, do you best, there is still lots to come!
Hm?! What's this?
Kyoutou, listen to the broadcast.
Oh? Hm.
Ogiwara-sensei and Machida Kyoutou-sensei...
...please come to the Principal's office immediately.
What could this be about?
Now, everyone. There are no others that have been called.
There is a request I must ask of you.
Yesterday, an incident took place on our campus.
I would like everyone's help...
...to find and punish the one person who is involved in this incident.
That person is a female student.
Leona will explain the details.
Leona!
I'm going to say this straight out!
The hammer of justice must be dropped on her.
That is the only job here.
Machida, you smell like an old man as usual.
But this time, the disgusting you is exactly what is needed.
I want you to take your filthy
bodies and your filthy pricks...
...and pound them into this woman with everything you've got!
Machida, Ogiwara, Sudou, do you understand?
Yes!
Hey, where's Kaneda-san?
She's not coming to dinner. This happens rather frequently.
Ta-kun, let me explain!
The reason why Mai-Mai isn't coming to dinner is...
Because right now she's
masturbating in her room.
Hey! Stop it.
Masturbating!
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
Good afternoon, Kaneda Maiko-san!
What do you want,
Morimoto Leona-san?
Hm?! Well, it doesn't matter who I am.
You are the one who has done something very bad.
Oh, that thing yesterday?
It's not just "Oh." How could you do that to me!
To have me kidnapped...
...to have all those horrible and terrible things done to me!
You better be ready for what will be done to you now!
Yes?
"Yes?" you ask? Soon you'll see the significance!
You were the one giving the orders! There is evidence.
What's your point?
I see, that's how it's going to be. Then, I have no choice.
Everyone! No holding back! I want you to mess her up really good!
Hurry!
There's no choice. Let's do this!
Hey!
It's hot!
What are you doing?!
That's not enough! Push further and further and futher!
You half-witted group.
Machida! Sudou!
Stab your tiny, disgusting things into her at the same time...
...and make that girl cum!
Tiny, disgusting, you say?
What? Vice Principal and student, no way!
What did you say?
Damn! I can still make a girl like that scream!
Oh, hey. That's my ass.
Well, then, all right! This time I will be your partner!
Oh, Maiko.
Hm?
So, tell me what happened last night?
Oh, nothing.
I must tell you something, Maiko...
...your skin looks really pretty today.
Really? It has been a while since I got so much.
What? Masturbating?
O-Onee-sama...