Well, then. That's all right! This time I will be your partner!
How's this?
Onee-sama! Why do I have to...
...wear this embarrassing outfit?
Because lately, you have caused too many shameful acts.
Like I told you, this is your punishment.
To have a member of the Morimoto family suffer this disgrace.
It makes me look like someone's pet dog.
I gave you a superb gift called, Hayami Takurou.
And you couldn't even
properly play with him.
Onee-sama! Please stop.
No. This is a punishment for talking back to me.
Oh, stop!
Control yourself, Leona. I've prepared more fun for you.
I can't! I can't hold it! Onee-sama!
Hey, it says, "Lustful Petting Couple."
This one says, "Princess Masturbate Anywhere."
"Lez Lez Couple."
Oh! That guy that sneaks around with a camera!
What comes around goes around!
Be quiet!
Leona-sama!
Today more foolish people have been arrested.
I will say this again.
Within the school campus, all male and female relationships...
...and any type of sexual activity is forbidden!
That's crazy! No way, it's unreasonable!
Oh, I wonder what the problem is.
Some students, even within the clubs, have become a bit "loose".
You shouldn't be one to talk!
From now on, anyone
caught on the campus...
...corrupting the public
morals will be removed!
No exceptions!
What could this mean, Otokawa-san?
I don't know.
But isn't this good? I don't think it's a bad thing after all.
What?
Hayami-kun, you should be the happiest one of us all.
Well, yeah, but still.
It's prohibited on campus, but...
...in the dormitory, it should be ok!
Huh?!
I don't believe it. It's itchy!
Leona-sama is a bully. Why do we have to wear these too?
What?!
This is only a greeting.
Oh? I thought Ogiwara-sensei
would be the night watch today.
Um, I was told to bring this here.
Um. Matsuno-sensei.
I took his place...
...I wanted to be alone with you, Hayami-kun.
Huh?!
You sure are honest down here.
S-Sensei.
Let's not do this.
This is prohibited by Morimoto Leona.
Don't mind Leona-sama! I'm a teacher, therefore I work for Reina-sama.
If I don't take this chance, you'll never look at me, Hayami-san.
More. Stick your tongue in deeper.
Amazing! My clitoris is so hot... inside my slit as well...
Let me lick yours, Takurou-kun.
Since the last time.
I've been waiting.
It's too much, I'm coming!
It's going all the way into my body and filling me up completely!
I'm going to cum again!
That was the best...
Oh? Karen-sama?
Karen-sama?!
Hayami-kun didn't come down for dinner.
I wonder if there is anything wrong.
Who knows? Maybe he's masturbating?
Maiko, just stop it.
This has definitely got to be bad.
What should I do?
See... I knew it.
You're right.
Masturbating in front of a mirror, huh?
What a narcissist he is.
You! You've been kissing!
That's just not fair, Ta-kun!
Hey! Why are you taking off your clothes?!
He should be ok doing it three times!
That is im... im.. im...
IMPOSSIBLE!
Leona-sama, this is the forth one.
Oh, my.
Just like Himeki, she's totally spent.
It's almost enviable.
Hm.
I will not forgive this breach of etiquette at my school.
Doesn't smell like men...
What? Then that means?
That person is using a condom.
For this crime to happen now. How evil!
With full force, search for the criminal!
I can't stand it! For girls of age not to have sex or even masturbate.
Hi!
Oh, what do you mean "Hi"? Who are you?
Let's do something good.
Huh?
You are so cute.
Very cute. Can I eat you?
No, I can't stay. No. I have to leave and go to class.
No!
Hm?
OK, I accept your challenge.
Be quiet.
While there's already something terrible happening at our campus...
...you go and enjoy Hayami-sama all by yourself.
Serves you right, Matsuno.
Is Himeki still unconscious?
Yes.
I'm concerned that the girl will continue like that for a while...
To have one with such skills at this school...
...and on top of that...
...why must I be stuck in this condition?
Leona-sama! Look at this!
What is this?
It was left at the front door.
Hm?
Tonight, the number one, at the school dormitory?
The international students, that means the target is indeed Hayami Takurou.
Now I see! Let's capture the criminal!
Prepare to leave!
Yes!
What happened to everyone?
Who knows? And I made Nonomi's favorite hamburger today, too!
Oh?
Nonomi! Yuuki!
Kaneda-san!
Get a hold of yourself!
Just watch out!
She is...
Maiko.
Is Hayami present?
Y-Yes.
Who are you?
I'm Linda Hamilton.
I'm here for a friendly round.
You will fuck me!
W-What are you saying?
Otokawa-san.
I really wanted to do it with you.
Today, I finally got the OK.
"OK" for what?
Ouch. What?
Everyone of the dormitory...
...and the international student, Linda Hamilton-sama....
...I, Morimoto Leona, have arrived!
Morimoto Leona?!
What is this?!
That's Morimoto Leona!
Good evening everyone!
To think, the one skilled enough to make my lovely girls cum in one shot...
...happens to be an exchange student!
These past few days...
...I've been trying my best to restore this school's morals...
...and during that time, you've caused quite some unrest.
It was good timing I must say.
Now look here.
The pictures of evidence!
Oh, will you stop already?
Everyone... this is bad.
I can't believe it. It's so horrible!
Oh, the horrible one is this person!
She's laid a hand on every student.
On top of that, she targeted my precious Hayami-sama.
Otokawa-san, if you don't understand...
See!
What?
Last year's school event, the member election was entertaining.
This much pee is quite rare to see.
This is a valuable picture.
I was given some kind of medicine.
What? That's terrible!
For a man to worry about a woman's heart, my heart is pulsing for you.
But, how unfortunate!
As you can see, currently...
...there is no way that I am able to display my love right now.
Don't tell me... that everyone...
I've got quite a bit of stress built up...
...and with this event, why not challenge Miss Linda?
If Hayami-sama wins, the dispute shall be settled. But if you lose...
If I lose?
This useless dormitory will be knocked down on the spot.
What?
What is that? It's poking deep inside my body! Oh, it's truly amazing!
Let's try this out.
Hayami-kun!
Oh, you're alive!
E-Everyone...
I knew you could do it, Hayami-sama!
You've done a good job fighting back that crazy exchange student.
But, I've decided to knock it down anyway...
It's an annoyance!
What?!
While I am forbidden from any lustful acts...
...why on earth should I allow any of you people to enjoy it?
Stop right there!
That's enough. I will take over now!
Leona, did you have fun playing?
Onee-sama?
I'm truly sorry, Hayami-kun, for all of this disruption.
Leona.
You mustn't do such cruel things to Linda-san.
Why not?
Because Linda-san is a sex exchange student!
It was me who asked her to exercise with the students of our school.
Onee-sama, stop with the nonsense already!
Oh? I sent you a letter, so that you would not be left out.
What?
I'm truly sorry, everyone. It really is inexcusable, so I'm apologizing for it.
Let me do this.
This is Hayami-kun's midterm test of love.
Oh, my. It's all soft. Zero points here.
This is twenty points.
Thirty points.
Forty points.
Fifty points.
Sixty points.
What's with her? Onee-sama just wanted some fun, didn't she?
Well, then everyone. Bye!
Everyone in the dormitory. See you in class tomorrow!
Ah?