Oh, would you like a refill?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, no. I've got you all wet.
I'm really sorry. Oh, what should I do?
Oh, I know. I get a tissue.
Tissue, tissue.
Look I found a tissue.
Um, let's see.
Otokawa-san.
Miyagishi-san? Nonomi-chan? Why?
So, Ta-kun likes Saori.
Huh?
Even though I'm giving you so much service...
...yet...Ta-kun...
Nonomi is trying to comfort you...
...who was shamelessly used by the Social Club.
What are you talking about?
Talking about it is useless. You cold-hearted jerk.
You should be punished!
What?!
Nonomi, make it hard!
Sure!
Oh! Looks like it's getting better.
Hey, I'll forgive you if you let us have a little fun, alright?
Nonomi! Give it all you've got!
Ta-kun, you're amazing! Unbelievable!
Ta-kun! You're amazing!
It's so amazing.
I can't hold on!
Cum!
Wow, Ta-kun. Your penis grew hard again.
Hm, I can't let it go waste!
I agree, Yuki. Then I guess we'll switch!
All right!
What?!
I can't anymore.
Hayami-kun? Are you ok?
Are you feeling alright?
Oh, no, I'm all right.
It sounded like you were having a nightmare.
It was nothing.
I see. Well, alright, then. If you need anything, just let me know, ok?
I got some medicine for you.
That Hayami. I know there's still something about him.
Yes, there is still the training.
Yes, I believe he'll be the best pet.
Yes, so that's why.
You should play with him more.
It's not like he can escape from the school.
Just observe him with the other girls in the dormitory.
If you can awaken the latent abilities with careful training...
...he'll become the ultimate pleasure machine.
Yes. If we don't, I won't be able to reach ecstacy.
Let's thoroughly enjoy him.
Matsuno, notify everyone in the circle...
...if one person in particular wants to join the club.
Squash, lacrosse, high-jump, discus, golf...
There doesn't seem to be any normal competition.
I guess it's a high-class female school.
Hey, Hayami-kun
What are you going to do about what Morimoto Leona said yesterday?
Huh?
You know about the Social Club. She asked you to join, didn't she?
Oh! That's right!
Well, at that time I thought it would be better if you joined my club.
But the Paranormal Studies Club isn't an official club yet.
Honestly, we're nothing spectacular.
Oh? Is that so?
Yes. But in order to keep them away...
...you'll have to join an established club. Or it could be bad.
Hm, I see.
I guess it could be bad if I don't join some kind of club.
Hm?
Hey. Is something wrong?
What are you doing?!
Quiet! Don't give us away.
What's going on!? Hm? You are?
I'm Sudou. And you're the new transfer student, Takurou-kun.
What are you doing in place like this?
Quiet! Lower your voice! I am in the Photography Club.
I'm following my important subject.
Mm?
This is the Tennis Club. This spot I found is the best ranked.
You're just a peeping tom!
It's for business!
Oh, so you're going to sell the pictures.
Of course!
Oh, that's good.
Amazing.
Oh, no. I'm out of film.
Hayami, watch them for me. I don't want my subject to get away from me.
What?
Sudou!
Ouch! What are you doing Sudou?!
My, look at you! Aren't you being daring?
Ah, no. That is. Um.
I don't want to hear any excuses. I know you are the culprit.
Hayami Takurou-kun.
Huh?
I'm the captain of the Tennis Club, Yamanaka Yumi.
How should I have you take responsibility for your misconduct?
Maya, Akane.
What do you think we should do since he saw our precious naked bodies.
Well, of course you know.
Yeah. If he saw us naked, then we should see him naked also.
Yes, I agree.
Hayami Takurou-kun.
Hayami?!
The rumored one?
What?
Hey, let's hurry and test him out. This should be fun!
I agree!
What are you going to do with me, huh??
Here.
Oh, see. You are already so hard.
Well, then, Maya first.
Here I go!
Yours is amazing.
If you don't try harder, we won't let you go!
Hey, it's already a big flood!
It's getting bigger again!
Wow. I've heard from stories, but for it to be that much.
Unbelievable! Unbelievable!
I can't hold on any longer!
buchou = captain
I don't believe it, Buchou. That was amazing!
Yes, it was.
I can't believe it. We should definitely report this to Leona-sama immediately.
Before that...
This time let's enjoy it together, alright?
Sudou.
Hey, are you ok? I've got lots of pictures to show you.
That jerk.
I'll give you a discount. Later, Hayami.
Bye!
Wait! Sudou!!
Woah!
Sudou!
You want to join our club right?
Come. Right this way, then.
Buchou, this person wants to join our club.
Wait, I didn't exactly say I wanted to join.
It's ok. We welcome all people who want to try out our club.
I am the captain, Yamagata Saki. Nice to meet you.
And, your name is?
My name is Hayami Takurou.
Huh?
Hayami-kun, since you're here, why not join us for a very fun event?
An event?
Yes, an event.
Under the circumstances, we need a male to help us out.
What?
Everyone, start the preparations.
What are you doing? Hey!
Buchou, the preparations are done.
Then, let's begin.
Now, give me some of that lovely sun oil.
This is the rumored one.
Oh, what's that?
Huh? What's wrong?
What's this? I've never seen this before.
That's amazing. It's just how Leona-sama described it.
Leona?!
So you are telling me that you are all part of that same Social Club?
You don't need to worry about anything.
Anyway, hurry with the sun oil.
Just come!
Yes?
Hayami-kun?!
Leona-sama.
It seems that Hayami-kun...
...had come across the Tennis Club and the Swimming Club.
I see.
And I suppose that you are now going to tell me exactly where he is.
And where is he now?
He is at Otokawa Saori's.
Hmph.
Then let's have her be involved next!
We'll let them play together then...
...until they have had enough of it.
Hayami-kun?
Otokawa-san.
Wow, you really scared me. You fell right to the floor.
Sorry.
You fell right over and passed out. Honestly...
I bet Morimoto Leona and her gang attacked you again, didn't they?
I'm really sorry, Hayami-kun. I said that I would protect you and I meant it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
There is no way I'm gonna sit around here any longer.
I won't let anyone have my Hayami-kun.
How long are you planning to sleep?
Miyagishi-san? And Kaneda-san?
I am here also.
So tell me what's everyone doing here?
Oh? Where is Otokawa-san?
What's this?
You know what she did?
She sneaked into the Social Club while you were sleeping.
And believe or not, she got caught.
Oh, poor Saori!
Otokawa-san.
Good luck.
I'll leave the rest up to you!
To come here on your own. You did the work for us.
What is that? You'd better hurry and untie these ropes!
Otokawa-san...
...do you understand why you're being put in such a shameful position?
I think I can imagine.
I'm sure that Hayami-kun is your goal. Isn't that right?
Right! How clever of you!
We are friends who both fought for the student body presidential campaign.
So, you will help, won't you?
After you treated him so awfully?!
Oh? What are you talking about?
You think it is ok to talk in that tone?
Hmph!
Otokawa-san!
Hayami-kun! Don't do it!
Takurou-kun!
Electricity.
That's right! Play carefully!
Huh?!
But, don't you think for one minute...
...that I won't do whatever it takes to make you join up with us.
Hayami, will you join the Social Club now?
No.
I see.
Himeki.
What are you doing? Otokawa-san has nothing to do with this!
Well, of course she does, huh?
It's because she is my rival.
Huh?
No! Stop!
Stop it!
No, stop!
Stop it! Let Otokawa-san go right now!
Then join our club.
Oh, my. How wonderful! Hayami has finally joined the Social Club.
Let's begin the preparations!
I'm sorry, Hayami-sama.
Before you join...
...we need the information about your amazing body first.
Hayami-sama, the right one next, please.
Leona-sama.
That's wonderful, Himeki.
Orgasm is at 80% right now.
It's amazing. His blood flow is increasing more and more.
I can feel it throbbing.
Ah?!
Oh.
Amazing. So this is the secret.
It's hard, yet soft, the ideal penis.
This combined with semen power. It is an extraordinary and beautiful gift.
Wow, look at it.
Hayami-kun.
The real part of the experiment is about to begin.
This time let me have the pleasure.
It's crazy.
I'm getting dizzy.
All right!
This should open the lock.
It seems like we might make it on time.
Ta-kun seems to be in a pinch.
Just a little bit further.
Will we make it?!
I will test the final data with my own body.
Think of it as an honor, Hayami!
Do your very best until the end...
...in front of Otokawa.
This is?
What? What's going on?
Huh?
Look, this is all mine.
Now, I want you to come inside and satisfy me, so I can get my pleasure.
Amazing! Oh, it's unbelievable.
Oh! Incredible! Oh, I've never felt this before!
No!