The Self-Conceited, Sadistic President: Maina McMuffin.
A blonde beauty who is half-Jananese and half-European. Leadership runs in her family her grandfather's the prime minister, her father's the CEO of a large conglomerate, and she's the student council president. Her intelligence and athletic ability make her seem like the perfect student, but this bewildering blond belies a secret she's super sadistic and endlessly enjoys belittling boys. One day, she notices a lustful gaze from her classmate Souta. She decides to make him her new boy toy, whittling him down slowly...
The President's Masochistic Assistant: Hyoudou Shino
Maina's loyal assistant. Everything she does is for Maina. She dislikes Souta as he diverts Maina's attention from her, but she knows Maina only sees him as a toy. Regardless, she wishes to get him expelled.
The Embodiment of Pure Desire: Mouri Souta
An underclassman who has a crush on Maina. He was exposed to an S&M magazine when he was young, which warped his mind into having strange fetishes. He eventually got pushed over the edge when he saw a girl in a similar position to one of the girl's in the magazine. One day, while Maina was giving a speech, he imagined her being tied up. Maina caught on to him and his fantasies, however, and constantly teases and scorns him for it.
Souta was overjoyed that Maina had taken an interest to him, but also had to endure being constantly teased and bullied by her. He showed no signs of breaking until Maina caught him lustfully gazing at her, as if he wanted to lick her entire body.
Unable to bring his situation up to any teacher, he vented out his frustrations in a notebook. There he jotted out his fantasies of Maina being submissive to him. One day, he found a mysterious glowing notebook that makes whatever is written in it come true. Intrigued with this strange notebook, Souta begins to live out his wildest fantasies.
The Super Sadist President Maina
is Dominated by the M-Note
~Teasing the Sadist and Masochist~
Good morning, Souta.
There you are with that sick male gaze again.
You really are the enemy of women.
G-Good morning. I-I wasn't looking at anyone like that.
It's not good to lie.
You better apologize, unless you want me to
show everyone that bulge in your pants right now.
Sorry I became aroused while looking at you lustfully.
God, you're sad.
Well, I'll forgive you this time, but don't expect
me to be so nice if I catch you doing this again.
Student Council Room
Aren't you paying that boy too much attention?
You don't understand, Shiina.
It's rare to find a boy that doesn't
hold back his lust like that.
He only thinks about unleashing his wild,
animalistic desires onto me.
He wants to break me down and bend me to his will.
I thought school in Japan would
be boring, but this is perfect.
Maina!
You understand too, right?
I lusted over you again, President Maina.
I'm sorry.
Maybe this is too soft a punishment for you?!
How dare you look at her with
those eyes! You damn plebeian!
The more you do this, the more
intense the punishment will be.
Where did this come from?
Whatever, it's the best!
Goddamn, she's a real big-tit slut!
Show your true colors, you masochistic bitch!
My true colors? Please enlighten me.
President Maina!
Seems like trying to reform you was a waste of time.
If that's how you see me, you'll need
a much more severe punishment.
W-Wait, it's not what you think! It's just a fantasy of mine...
Shut up!
I don't want to hear your worthless excuses!
Leave your pants and get out here!
B-But...
It's your punishment. Hurry up!
Three, two, one...
Zero!
I told you to come out, didn't I?
Are you looking down on me?
I'm going to have to educate you thoroughly.
I'll carve you how you're supposed to interact with a
woman into your very bone, you worthless horndog.
Look at how pathetically hard your penis is.
Your foot is stroking my meat rod!
Th-That's what you call it?
It's embarrassing to think you're
deriving pleasure from this...
Hey!
What are you doing? Cut it out!
I won't forgive you for defying me!
No! Don't do it harder!
Let go of me!
Stop it, you bastard!
I said stop!
Wh-What is this?!
No!
How could I let myself be defiled by a man?
I can't believe this!
I can't believe this...
How dare you! I'm going to use my
authority to have you expelled.
I'm sorry! Please don't expel me!
I'll do anything!
Anything, you say?
Then get on your hands and knees
and clean up the mess you made.
Who cares if she's the Prime Minister's granddaughter?
She thinks she's so high and mighty
when she's just a cheeky brat.
H-Huh? What's this?
These are all idols who committed scandals.
You pervert!
I won't forgive you for what you did to Maina!
I'm definitely going to get you expelled!
Wasn't that Shiina, Maina's old assistant?
I'm a pervert
I declare death upon this man who defiled me.
However, guiding stray sheep is my duty.
Henceforth, he will be my new assistant.
Please look forward to his rehabilitation.
Her assistant? More like her slave!
Take this, you slut!
You're my personal foot rest. Feel honored.
Hyoudou Shino goes to Mouri Souta's house to apologize.
She strips naked, asks him to tie her up, and gets punished.
I feel better after writing all that.
At least tomorrow's Saturday, so I can take it easy.
I-I need to speak with you.
I've realized what I said was wrong
and rude. Please forgive me.
I-I think it's wrong for me to be
persecuted just for daydreaming.
Yes, you're exactly right.
So, that's why...
I-I apologize.
P-Please use this to...
Use this to punish me!
Wait, this is exactly what I wrote in the notebook...
H-How?
P-Please.
Punish me...
This is so embarrassing...
Just like in my porno mags...
Wh-What are you going to do next?
Ow!
It hurt for me too, bitch!
But you cunts kept going!
It hurts!
I can't believe this is happening to me!
Ow!
No!
Stop!
What the hell? You're soaking wet.
No!
That's not true!
Want me to get mad at you,
you fucking masochistic cunt?!
No, you're wrong!
That's not...
That's not what I'm thinking at all!
Guess I need to punish you
harder till you learn to stop lying.
Punish me harder?
Ow! You're going to rip it!
It hurts so much!
That's the point.
Ow!
You're punishing me with your dick!
You're dick is ramming into me so hard!
Ow!
I can't believe you're feeling it from this, you masochist.
I'm not...
I'm not a masochist!
No!
I'm gonna turn you and the president into my slaves.
You're gonna turn us into... slaves?
How wonderful!
I can't believe I'm feeling so good from my punishment!
I'm...
You're dick is punishing the deepest parts of my pussy!
No! Slow down!
You're cumming so much inside me!
I-I'm sorry! Are you okay?!
Thank you very much for showing me kindness
even though I was rude to you, Master.
With this, I can make Maina...
Master Souta!
Your cock is so deep inside me!
No!
You say that, but your hips don't lie, you big-tit slut!
You're right!
I really like this!
I love having your manly dick in my slutty pussy!
I had it all wrong!
I love being punished by your dick!
You're actually a masochistic whore, aren't you?
Please punish this masochistic whore!
Punish me more, Master!
Your dick is wonderful!
It's so deep inside me!
Why are you the only being pleasured?
My deepest apologies! I'll work
harder to pleasure you, Master!
Does this feel good, Master?
It feels really good for me!
Please give my womb your blessing, my master!
So much cum!
My pussy is just for you, Souta!
Good morning, Souta.
Hurry up and get up already!
P-President Maina?!
Why are you here?!
It's a slave's job to wake up her master.
Are you still half-asleep?
M-Master?! But you're...
Get it together.
You're my master from today onward after all.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
M-Maina, this is an order.
Put both hands on the desk and stick your ass out.
Is this good?
What are you going to do with my legendary hips?
You won't break me!
What are you doing?!
Stop! That's my vagina!
Don't look!
"Pussy" sounds way hotter than "vagina".
You're eating me out!
My pussy is!
So this is your first time, huh?
Your cock is rubbing my insides!
I can't believe I'm servicing you
while you're sitting in my seat.
What a great idea, Master!
Your dick is twitching...
It's going to punish me!
Make me feel good, President.
Okay. I'll make you happier than you've ever been.
It's slamming into me so deep!
You're even fondling my boobs!
If this goes on any longer, class is going to start!
I'm almost there...
I'm so happy!
Master... I want you to cum!
Flood me with it!