The Self-Conceited, Sadistic President: Maina McMuffin.
A blonde beauty who is half-Jananese and half-European. Leadership runs in her family her grandfather's the prime minister, her father's the CEO of a large conglomerate, and she's the student council president. Her intelligence and athletic ability make her seem like the perfect student, but this bewildering blond belies a secret she's super sadistic and endlessly enjoys belittling boys. One day, she notices a lustful gaze from her classmate Souta. She decides to make him her new boy toy, whittling him down slowly...
The President's Masochistic Assistant: Hyoudou Shino
Maina's loyal assistant. Everything she does is for Maina. She dislikes Souta as he diverts Maina's attention from her, but she knows Maina only sees him as a toy. Regardless, she wishes to get him expelled.
The Embodiment of Pure Desire: Mouri Souta
An underclassman who has a crush on Maina. He was exposed to an S&M magazine when he was young, which warped his mind into having strange fetishes. He eventually got pushed over the edge when he saw a girl in a similar position to one of the girl's in the magazine. One day, while Maina was giving a speech, he imagined her being tied up. Maina caught on to him and his fantasies, however, and constantly teases and scorns him for it.
He writes all his delusions out in his notebook out of anger. The next thing he knows, the Assistant to the President, Shino appears before him and does exactly what he fantasized about. Just like he wrote in the notebook, he punishes Shino and is able to fuck her as he pleases. With a new found sense of power, he sets out to make Maina follow his orders, using the notebook by scribbling his fantasies so that they are realized later...
The next morning, he finds that reality has bent to his fantasies...
Maina up to that point had always been bullying Souta, but when she arrived in her office, she recognized Souta as her master and swore herself as his slave...
But Maina had always looded down on people, so even though she swore to be his slave, she still acted high and mighty even while Souta was punishing her...
The Super Sadist President Maina
is Dominated by the M-Note
Training the Sadist President into a Masochist.
Listen, you're my master,
so you need to become a person worthy of that.
I know that the fantasy I wrote in the notebook
about her being my masochistic slave is reality now,
but... something's off.
Sorry, I need to go to the bathroom.
I wonder what's wrong...
It's not an upset stomach, is it?
He needs to shape up.
M-Mina! This is an order.
Put your hands on the desk and stick your ass out this way!
What did you just say?
Stick my hips out like some common wench?
Sure. This is the first time you've
given such a conceited order.
Alright, how's this?
What are you going to do to these hips
of mine that are the envy of everyone?
Pull your panties down and pull up your
skirt so that your ass is clearly visible.
This is punishment!
You're punishing me?!
Alright. I'll even follow your most demeaning orders.
Hey, that's...
Souta-kun? My hips aren't meant to be...
You've been acting too high and mighty.
I need to teach you that I'm the master!
This is so demeaning, but I'm the masochistic slave.
I need to bear this...
You won't... Break me!
Wh-What are you...
I haven't given up yet!
You're my precious masochistic slave, Mina.
I'm going to give you the carrot and the stick.
It's already kind enough of you to touch my hips,
but now you're hitting them and rubbing them?
Y-You hit me again!
But you were just rubbing me there!
You hit me again!
I told you, this is punishment!
You keep hitting me and rubbing me...
what kind of clever punishment is this?!
I'm...
What are you doing there?!
Don't look at my pussy!
I like calling it a vagina more than a pussy.
Souta-kun's eating me out!
My vagina's being...
Is this is your first time doing this?
Of course it is!
Only a man I deem worthy is allowed to touch me!
I thought you were just another one of those blonde sluts.
Now that I think about it, you called me
a Holstein slut in the bathroom before.
This punishment is...
Your finger is...
It's ramming itself in and out of me!
No, that's...
Stop!
You got this wet from being spanked?
You're such a perverted masochistic slave, Mina.
I was supposed to keep him as a pet, but
now he made me his masochistic pet!
So that's what you had in mind when you were bullying me?
I'm going to make you regret that!
If this keeps going, I'm going to...
No!
I... Someone like me can't...
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum from Souta-kun as his masochistic slave!
Oh my god, I've never felt this before!
I'm overflowing!
I'm so...
Are you okay, President Mina?
I'm fine thanks to you breaking my fall. Thank you, Master.
Oh, look at that mess...
P-President Mina is kissing me?
I've never done anything like this with anyone before.
I knew I chose right.
Master, your dick is so hard, it's about to burst.
You want to cum, don't you?
I'll give you my virginity, Master.
Your masochistic slave will give you it.
Your dick's coming inside me!
It's pushing up into my vagina!
Does it feel good, Souta-kun?
I want you to feel good from my vagina!
I'm not a virgin anymore...
Does it feel good?
It feels amazing!
Souta-kun, your dick is...
It's rubbing around me, deep inside!
Please, feel more from me!
Please feel good from me!
Souta-kun?
It's okay.
You want to shoot out your sperm, don't you?
You can do it whenever you want!
This pussy is just for you!
Fill it with your sperm!
It's coming!
It's exploding inside me!
There's a flood of Souta-kun's sperm inside me!
What's wrong, Souta-kun?
I want more!
You're still going?!
It's...
It's going even deeper than before!
Souta-kun, it's so good!
I was supposed to be pleasuring
you, but you're pleasuring me now!
Let's feel good together, President Mina!
I'm so happy!
I can feel good with Souta-kun!
Is my body satisfying you?
Yeah, it feels really good!
That's great!
This is your personal vagina.
It's yours and yours only!
I'm going to cum again!
Let's cum together!
Together!
I... I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Your sperm is flooding my vagina!
There's so much...
This is why you're my master!
I never really expected her to
become a real masochistic slave.
That notebook's the real deal!
Mina McMaphon Anegakoji will follow all orders from Mouri Souta and feel real embarrassment which will awaken her masochistic side and ultimately turn her on
It happened just as I wrote it. What I wrote became real!
I can't believe I'm pleasuring you while you sit in my seat.
You have some great ideas, Master!
Souta-kun's dick...
It's twitching so much!
It's scolding me!
Make me feel good, President.
Okay! I'll give you happiness that's
better than even this, Master!
I need to make it really wet with my saliva.
It's throbbing!
It's so amazing!
Cum, Souta-kun!
Spray it all over me, Souta-kun!
Cum!
Give me lots!
Wow, there's so much of Souta-kun's sperm!
I'm like a doggy in this position!
I'm kneeling and being penetrated from behind!
This is so demeaning!
But it feels so good!
It's ramming me so deep!
And my boobs are being groped too!
If this keeps going, class is going to start!
Just a little more!
I'm so happy!
I want you to cum inside me, Master!
Cum a lot!
No, that's... So good!
Dirty juices are dripping out onto my desk!
So good! We're doing this on the desk I study with!
And now I'm pleasuring my master on it!
No! So intense!
It's okay. Do it whenever.
Do it whenever you want and cum however much you want!
You're going to make me cum again!
I'm cumming!
Master's sperm!
There's too much of it!
I don't think you understand
just what a masochistic slave is.
You don't see them too often around school.
I need to start a campaign to get more people to know
you, Master, so we can liven this school up more!
Okay, Souta-kun, let's start preparations right now!
P-Please wait, President!
What's the matter, Shino?
I have something I need to speak with Souta-kun about.
Can you wait?
I-I have something I need to
talk with Souta-sama about too.
S-Souta-sama?
Souta-sama, no... Master!
It's painful being ignored!
Please allow me to pleasure you!
W-Wait, Shino!
Souta-kun's my master!
You should find a different mas...
I'm Souta-kun's slave too. I was his slave before you!
There can only be one master and one slave.
Did he break that rule?!
I guess I did tie Shino-senpai up...
Souta-kun and I are official partners!
If... If this gets out, the order of the school will break!
If that happens, Souta-kun...
his very existence will be erased!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Master...
You're already so hard after just cumming.
This is a fetish of yours, isn't it, Master?
The sensation of the glove and my
skin feels good, doesn't it, Master?
Okay.
It's time for the biggest surprise!
So perverted. In a place like this?
Shino, you're so erotic.
You always went on about how girls need to be elegant.
Master!
That's so good!
More! Punish me harder!
Spanking me while shoving it inside me? You're so wild!
Master, you're so amazing!
You're doing it out in the open like this!
It's such a surprise!
So good!
Your dick is shoving so deep inside me, it's impaling me!
Your dick is harder and twitching
even more than usual, Master.
You're about to cum, aren't you, Master?
I can take care of Master's dick!
Just a little more!