The Self-Conceited, Sadistic President: Maina McMuffin.
A blonde beauty who is half-Jananese and half-European. Leadership runs in her family her grandfather's the prime minister, her father's the CEO of a large conglomerate, and she's the student council president. Her intelligence and athletic ability make her seem like the perfect student, but this bewildering blond belies a secret she's super sadistic and endlessly enjoys belittling boys. One day, she notices a lustful gaze from her classmate Souta. She decides to make him her new boy toy, whittling him down slowly...
The President's Masochistic Assistant: Hyoudou Shino
Maina's loyal assistant. Everything she does is for Maina. She dislikes Souta as he diverts Maina's attention from her, but she knows Maina only sees him as a toy. Regardless, she wishes to get him expelled.
The Embodiment of Pure Desire: Mouri Souta
An underclassman who has a crush on Maina. He was exposed to an S&M magazine when he was young, which warped his mind into having strange fetishes. He eventually got pushed over the edge when he saw a girl in a similar position to one of the girl's in the magazine. One day, while Maina was giving a speech, he imagined her being tied up. Maina caught on to him and his fantasies, however, and constantly teases and scorns him for it.
For Souta who had always admired President Maina, being able to reprimand her was like a dream come true. She followed every one of his orders all the while complaining. She was truly an obedient holstein slut... Souta was enjoying being pleasured by her through his various punishments of her and her tit fucks, but after punishing her and then leaving her alone, she began to seek out punishment from him on her own, being unable to resist any longer...
The girl he fucked as a test, "Hyoudou Shino", was a faithful assistant of Maina's. But even so, she changed after that day and willfully pushed Mania out of the way to pleasure her new master...
Maina was in disbelief that there was someone else vying for the same position she was... This kind of relationship was supposed to be a one on one kind of deal, so the fact that there were two slaves went against the rules. To resolve this problem that she basically made up, Maina took it upon herself to have Souta solve this problem...
Now in this situation, Maina came up with a certain plan. They would both bleasure Souta's meat stick ang fight for the position of who could be his rightful slave.
The Super Sadist President Maina
The scorning complete sadistic coplete masochist
M-Maina! This is an order.
Put your hands on the desk and stick your ass out!
Hey, that's... Souta-kun? My hips aren't meant to be...
You've been acting too full of yourself.
I need to teach you that I'm the master!
I can't believe I'm pleasuring you on
my knees while you're sitting in my seat.
You have some great ideas, Master!
Souta-kun's dick...
It's twitching so much!
It's scolding me!
Make me feel good, President.
It's ramming me so deep!
And you're groping my boobs too!
If we keep going, class is going to start!
Just a little more!
I'm so happy! I want you to cum inside me, Master!
Cum a lot!
I'm Souta-kun's slave too. I was his slave before you!
There can only be one master and slave.
Did he break that rule?!
I guess I did tie Shino-senpai up...
Souta-kun and I are official partners!
If... If this gets out, everything will fall apart!
If that happens, Souta-kun...
his very existence will be erased!
Master...
Your dick's so amazing, Master.
Master, please feel good from me.
Seeing you feel good makes me so happy!
I never thought you'd go this far, Shino.
But I'll make him feel even more pleasure.
Being at the bottom of your bed was a bit of
a culture shock, but it taught me a thing or two.
You're already so hard after just cumming.
This is a fetish of yours, isn't it, Master?
Uh, fetish? Uh, well...
No need to feel ashamed, Master.
Everyone has their own tastes.
A true masochistic slave
can figure out his master's tastes.
As expected of you, President.
You really live up to Master's name for you, you blonde sl...
Shut up!
Shino, you're the same as me, you know?
If anything you'd be a "cool slut".
I-I am?!
So far so good. Let's move to the next step.
The sensation from my glove
and skin feels good, doesn't it, Master?
It's starting to come out. You're about to shoot
out that sticky cum of yours, aren't you?
Okay, finish here.
It's time for the biggest surprise!
So perverted. In a place like this? How perverted!
Your sperm is shooting out and filling up my armpit!
Very impressive, President.
Now then, it's my turn, I believe.
Wha... You moved so quickly, Shino!
I'll make your dick big again, Master.
Wow, Shino knows that technique?
Master, I'll make your dick feel good with my pussy, okay?
It's so hard! This must be your reward for me!
No, it's thanks to me!
You only made it cum. I'm the one
who made it this hard again, President!
She was supposed to be no match to me!
How'd she become this formidable?!
I'll squeeze your dick real good with my pussy, Master!
Shino... you're so erotic...
I thought you were supposed to be more refined than this!
Master! Now, I'll do this...
That's good!
More! Harder! Punish me!
She's made Master move on her instead!
I'm so happy that I can make your dick feel good, Master!
I like it being done to me like this...
I feel so constrained! I...
What?! Is she more perverted than he is?
Master's cum is filling my womb!
Cock, penis → peepee, dick
Pussy → Vagina
Shino, you really showed just how indecent you are.
But now, it's my turn to...
Drat, it was finally my turn too. Now that it's come to this...
I'll just have to forcefully push back the school closing time!
That's too much, President!
Please me more composed.
It isn't like you to become desperate like this.
Why do I feel like I'm being pitied...?
I know I have to choose between the two of them, but...
If I choose one of them, the other will...
The final decision is up to you, and only you, Souta-kun.
We'll take turns pleasuring you and you'll have to decide
who is better suited to be your masochistic slave.
Understood.
I want you to choose me so I won't be holding back.
To win against her, I'll have to...
Souta-kun?
Hurry!
Good morning!
It's time for your dick to wake up already.
If you don't cum soon, you'll be late.
Master is forcing my head down!
This is another way for a masochistic
slave to pleasure her master!
It's going so deep!
Master's semen is...
As a masochistic slave,
I thought I'd be happier being seen by everyone.
Good morning, President, Master.
Oh, good morning, Shino.
Good morning, Shino-senpai.
Master, you can just call me Shino.
Just having you call me by my name makes me...
I have something for you, Master.
I-It's for later when I pleasure you.
Further, stay away from the classroom!
Maina
All right, Master, no one is around. What shall we do?
I thought as much. At this time,
in this place, in this perverted pose...
Making all of the students leave and then hitting my ass?
Your ass just feels so good, Maina.
I'm very proud of my hips.
Choose me and every part of me is yours.
You're wet.
Hitting me while sticking it in me?! You're so wild!
Master, you're so good!
You're doing me so boldly!
What a surprise!
Good! Your dick is hitting me so deep!
This...
It's coming all the way to my womb in this position, Master!
I see, you want to show this to everyone.
You're showing off your masochistic slave.
I still haven't decided yet.
I see you know how to tease us! You're so good at it!
I wish you'd pick sooner than later though!
So good! You're being so rough!
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Fill me with your semen, Master!
Master, your semen's overflowing!
It'd be better if he just made up his mind already.
Being indecisive is a Japanese trait.
I have something for you...
Master, you're... you're getting so hard!
Your dick's even harder and twitchier than usual, Master.
Are you about to cum, Master?
I just need a little more time
to take care of your dick, Master.
Master, you can cum whenever you'd like!
Wow, there's so much of your cum, Master!
Now I'm the one being taken from behind!
Having Master come into me like this makes me so happy!
Having my boobs rubbed and squeezed feels so good!
Having my pussy ravaged by
your dick is making my womb go crazy!
You're rubbing my pussy all over!
I'm overflowing with your dick, Master!
Your pussy's the best, Shino!
Master, I'm...
Let's cum together.
Yes! Let's do it together!
I'm cumming!
You're pouring so much cum inside me...
That makes me so happy!
Why?! Master's going to choose her!
Master, uh, I... Here!
It's... a lunch box.
You're always eating bread... and I'm good at cooking.
Nobody's ever done this for me before.
This makes me really happy!
Master, do you really prefer her...
Is he even worrying about the
choice between me and Shino?
Shino's very daring when it comes to sex.
And she's a refined lady.
She's a perfect Japanese woman.
I don't think I can be your masochistic slave.
I figured this would be the last time, so...
Don't worry about choosing one of us anymore, Master.
I haven't made any decisions yet, though.
I'm happy just even hearing you say that.
I...
I promise I'll think about it hard, so just wait.
Master, if you keep saying these happy things,
I'm going to start to get my hopes up!
No... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Shino can give her everything to be
a masochistic slave, but what about me...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: shiroyasha
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
She's changed so much.
She's become more of a masochistic slave than I have.
Your dick feels too good, Master.
I want to focus on pleasuring you, but I...
No! No! You mustn't, Master!
I'm going to...
You're tired, aren't you?
I'll help.
Master's being nice to her?!
No! No!
I need to hold out until Master cums!
I...
You're banging against my womb!
No, so deep!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Shoot your semen out.
Shoot it down my throat!
It's rough, but you can do
whatever you want to me, Master!
Wow, it's going so deep in me!
It's even hitting my baby room!
It's surprising my womb even though I have a perfect body!
No! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
How pathetic, President.
You've abandoned me and now you're confronting me?
Have you heard the rumors about you?
If there's anyone suited to run a negative campaign
against you, there's no one better for it than me.