hanime.tv
presents
Are we clear?
You're my husband.
So you've got to be worthy of that title.
While she has become my slave just like I wrote...
There's something weird about this.
Sorry, I gotta go to the bathroom.
What's wrong?
Did he get a stomachache all of a sudden?
He's got to pull it together.
M-Maina! This is an order.
Put both your hands on this desk...
And stick out your ass!
What did you just say?
Put my hands on the desk and
indecently stick out my hips?
Very well.
This is your first time you've been
so cocky with your orders.
How's this?
You're gazing at my hips, the likes of which
everyone envies. Now what will you do?
Pull up your skirt...
Take off your panties, and show me your ass...
For spanking!
You're going to spank me?
I see.
It's a humiliating demand.
But I'll show you that I can take it.
Hey!
Souta-kun, you're hitting my hips...
You're always so full of yourself as President!
I'll teach you who's in charge!
This is humiliating.
But right now I'm your slave!
I can take this easily!
I absolutely...
won't give in!
W-What are you doing all of a sudden?
I haven't given up yet!
Maina, you're my precious slave.
I won't always treat you harshly.
I'll take good care of you too.
You should be honored just to touch my hips...
But you're striking and fondling them!
You hit me again!
But you were just rubbing!
You hit me again all of a sudden!
I told you. This is punishment.
Switching between spanking and rubbing...
That's so mean and sly!
Why I...
W-What are you doing?
No! My pussy!
Don't look!
Say "pussy" in Japanese.
You're eating out...
my pussy!
So this is your first time...
Of course!
I have to deem a man worthy
before i let him touch me.
You experienced blonde bitch!
Come to think of it, you called me
a Holstein bitch in the bathroom.
I should punish you for that.
Your fingers!
You're rubbing inside!
No! Not that!
No!
Getting hit gets you wet and horny...
You're a real masochist slave, Maina.
I planned to keep you as a pet.
But I've become your masochist pet!
So that's what you were thinking
while you bullied me...
Think about what you've done!
At this rate, I'm going to...
I'm going to come!
You're making me come!
You're making me come...
I'm your slave, and I'm coming!
That feels so good!
It's my first time feeling like this!
My pussy's overflowing...
Are you OK, President Maina?
Yes, because you caught me.
It's thanks to you, master.
Look how dirty...
Y-You're kissing me!
So this is your first kiss...
You're the man I chose after all.
Master, your cock is so hard.
It's like it could burst.
You want to come, don't you?
I'll give you my virginity.
Your slave...
Just like this!
Your cock is inside me!
It's prying open my pussy!
Souta-kun, how does it feel?
I hope my pussy makes you feel really good.
My virginity... now I'm...
Does it feel good?
It's the best!
Souta-kun, your cock is rubbing me inside.
I want you to enjoy this even more!
I'll make this feel even better for you!
Souta-kun, you can come.
You want to come, don't you?
Come whenever you want!
My pussy's all yours.
Give me lots of come!
You're coming!
It's bursting out inside my pussy!
There's so much of your sperm!
What are you doing, Souta-kun?
I want more.
There's more?
You're going even deeper than before!
Souta-kun, that feels great!
I'm supposed to pleasure you.
But you're making me feel good!
President Maina, move with me.
I'm so happy...
that I get to do this with you.
My body feels so good!
Me too.
I'm so happy.
My pussy's all yours.
I'm all yours!
No!
I'm going to come again!
Me too. Let's come together!
Together?
I’m...
I'm coming!
Souta-kun, you're coming so much!
It feels so good.
That's why you're my master!
To think she'd actually become
my slave in real life...
That notebook is the real deal!
Maina MacMahon-Anegakouji will listen to ﻿Mori Souta's indecent orders.
Despite the humiliation she feels, it thrills her masochist side and turns her on.
It's not word for word,
but what I wrote is coming true!
Sitting in my seat then making
me kneel and service you...
That's my master!
Souta-kun, your cock...
It's twitching.
Make me feel really good, President.
OK, I'll make you feel better than
you've ever felt before, master.
I'm going to make you much happier.
It's throbbing!
Yes!
Come!
Souta-kun!
Come all over me, Souta-kun!
Come! Come a lot!
Wow! You came so much!
Look at all your sperm!
Doing it like this... It's like we're dogs!
Making me kneel...
and putting it in from behind...
This is so humiliating!
But it feels so good!
You're rubbing me deep inside.
And you're rubbing my breasts!
If we keep doing this...
Class is gonna start!
I'm almost there.
I'm glad.
Master, I want you to come inside me!
Come a lot...
No!
That feels so good!
Our lewd liquids are dripping onto the desk!
This is the desk I use in class...
and I'm using it to service Master!
No! That's too hard!
Go ahead.
Come whenever you're ready.
Come as much as you can!
You're making me come again!
I'm coming!
Master... you came too much!
I'm your slave.
But it seems you don't completely
understand what that means.
I hardly see you at school.
So I'll be your campaign girl.
I'll make it clear that you're my master.
That should stir up the excitement!
OK, Souta-kun! Get ready!
P-Please wait, President!
I'm having a talk with Souta-kun right now.
Could you step out for a moment?
I have to talk with Souta-sama too.
Souta... sama?
Souta-sama... No, I should call you Master!
You've been leaving me all alone,
and I can't take it!
Please let me service you!
W-Wait a second, Shino!
Souta-kun is my master, not yours!
I am one of Souta-kun's slaves, just like you.
The relationship between slave and
master must be one on one!
You broke that rule!
Well I did tie up Shino-senpai...
But Souta-kun and I are officially partners!
If this news were to get out,
the whole campus would be in chaos!
Then Souta-kun will definitely...
cease to even exist!
Next time On "Super Sadistic Student Council President ﻿ Maina-sama Gets
Controlled by the M Note"...
Master...
You just came, and now you're hard again...
You've done this a lot, haven't you.
Feeling my skin and the glove...
Doesn't it feel good, Master?
OK,
What a surprise!
Doing it here...
You're such a pervert!
Shino... you're so erotic.
I thought you were elegant and mild-mannered!
Master!
Yes!
Harder!
Punish me!
Spanking me while putting it in...
How wild!
Master, that feels great.
You're exposing me so boldly...
What a surprise!
Yes! Your cock is hitting me so deep inside!
Master, your cock is throbbing.
It's harder than ever before.
Master, you're about to come, aren't you?
Master, I'll take care of your cock.
Just a little more.