Self-centered Sadist School President
Maina McMahon
Biracial, blonde, big tits, clear headed, athletic. As the grand daughter of the Prime Minister, and daughter of the head of a financial conglomerate, she is a perfect person that is adored by students and teachers alike. However, she also has a sadistic side to her where she feels ecstasy from having guys bow before her and look at her with adoration. Out of all the people that worship her, she took interest in Souta who's eyes were gleaming with lust. She then tried to break his desires and make him bow before her by training him...
Perfect Masochist President's Assistant
Hidou Shino
Assistant to the President, Maina, Shino adores her. She's confident and pretty popular but is very loyal, putting everything she has into serving Maina. She finds Souta to be a nuisance for grabbing Maina's interest, but she tolerates it by thinking of him as just a play thing. She tells herself that she will erase him one day, but...
Incarnation of Worldly Desires
Mouri Souta
He is one of the younger classmate who fell in love at first sight, seeing Maina. After reading an S&M magazine and being shocked by it, his sexual tastes got weird, and he can now only look at women in that way. Seeing Maina on stage, he imagined her prostrating herself in front of him as he ties her up... But, Maina picks up on this, and now he is teased and ridiculed on a regular basis...
Maina ruled as the perfect student council president. Her existence was not only admired, but second to none for the students. Because this, she had no doubt that even if she went against Shino, she would win. And yet... Shino's overwhelming technique and faithfulness to service creates a crack in Maina's confidence that Maina doesn't even know exists...
Able to do anything perfectly and always giving everything her all, Maina has absolute confidence in herself, with her right hand woman, Shino, by her side... Able to make anyone prostrate themselves before her, Maina for the first time has found a person that she looks up to...
Previously on Do S na Seitokaichou-sama
ga M Note ni Shihai Saremashita...
You just came and you're already hard again...
This must be what you like then.
Not exactly, but...
Okay...
Finish it off here.
This is the biggest surprise...
I can't believe you're fucking that spot...
You're such a pervert...
Shino, you're so quick...
Master's penis...
I'll make it all lively again...
Wow... I didn't know Shino had that
technique under her sleeve...
It's so good!
Harder!
Punish me harder!
She's just a pleasure device for Master
as he moves his hips like a monkey...
Sticking it in as you spank me...
You're so wild!
My boobs are getting squeezed and shaken...
It feels so good...!
Master's penis is messing me up...
My womb is going to open up...
Master...
Do you prefer her more than me...?
Master, you don't have to be conflicted anymore.
The thing is...
I still haven't decided yet.
That makes me so happy to just hear that...
I'll actually think about it, so wait a bit more.
Master, I'll get my hopes up
if you say stuff like that...
No...! I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum!
Shino is willing to give everything
as a masochist slave.
What about me...
Master! It feels so good when you hit me there!
Master is fucking me like always...
And yet...
Your penis is corrupting and enslaving me!
Master, you can pour your thick cum
into me whenever you want.
Master...!
So much of Master's cum flowing inside me...!
Your thick cum...
There's even the President's love juices.
Master, next up is my turn.
Don't rest just yet.
Master, I'm going to make you
feel good with my pussy.
She's so passionate and different
than how she used to be...
The one who changed more by
being a masochist slave is...
Master's penis feels so good...
I want to serve it and yet...
No. No, Master!
At this rate, I'm going to...
It must be tiring.
I'm just helping.
Master is giving her nice words...
No, I can't.
Just a bit more before I can make Master cum.
I can feel it.
Master, I'm going to squeeze
out your cum with my pussy!
Master's penis...
It's so big... I'm cumming... I'm cumming...!
So much of Master's cum...
Ms. President, are you there?
Just a moment.
What's wrong?
Ms. President, there's only 5 minutes
left before the meeting.
Sorry!
I'll be there right away.
It's so rare for the President to forget something...
Ms. President, that's not the right document!
The President has been weird lately.
Does being a masochist slave mean
that even the President goes crazy?
Master's penis is grinding
me so deep... It s so good!
I want to be fucked like this by Master forever.
You're going all the way to my womb...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming...!
The President didn't end up coming.
I haven't even seen her in the mornings
lately. I wonder what happened.
The weird rumors bug me too.
I agree...
I'm supposed to be advancing the Masochist
Slave Law as its campaign girl, and yet...
O-oh, Shino...
What's wrong?
President,
you're pitiful.
I can't pretend I just didn't hear that...
Hello, Grandpa?
Eh?
No! I should be more than enough.
I'll make sure before the deadline to...
Yes... leave it up to me.
You disregard me and go above my head?
Have you heard the weird rumors about you?
Rather than the campaign be slandered,
I think I'd be more fit as a replacement.
Who would have thought I'd be betrayed
by the one closest to me.
I must have been on something.
I'll make you regret opposing me.
Shino, are you okay?
Thanks for making the call.
Your plan surprised me, but I had stuff I wanted
to talk about with him anyways.
Wake up, Master.
You'll get a spanking if you
don't get out of bed soon.
Hurry up.
It's time to show everyone how
happy masochist slaves are.
Is that your attempt at a showcase?
Shino, I said that I would make you feel regret.
Just watch.
I'll make you rue the day you
made me your enemy.
The President...!
Is that what masochist slaves are made to do?
But the President looks so happy.
With the trust that me and Master have, lots of happy
things are waiting for a masochist slave like me.
Who would have thought the
President would do that.
But, she's just as she always is...
It looks like our showcase made
other students interested.
I won't lose to Shino.
Looking down on me... I'll have
to punish Shino later...
Master, why are you patting me so suddenly?
Both Shino and I cherish you very much.
I was wrong...
I shouldn't have compared us to each other.
Master, let it all out.
Shoot your cum out.
Shoot it into my throat...
There's so much...
As expected of Master...
This position... if you go that hard...
It's painful, but it feels so good
being manhandled by Master.
Master you can go rougher... deep inside...
Amazing. You're so much wilder than you look.
I'm so happy right now.
I was being stupid.
There's no way Master, with
your amazing dick, would...
So good! It's going in so deep.
All the way to the baby room!
Your talents impress even me, the perfect human.
I want to be with Master like this
forever, as a masochist slave...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...!
You're pumping your cum inside me...!
Master, you're just too good...!
President, Master...
Master, so you've made a decision?
Yes, I've decided.
I see.
Either one of us will become a masochist
slave to someone other than Master...
He's late.
Master...
Shino...
I see...
The one that Master chose is...
President, wait. It's not what you're thinking.
My masochist slave is you, Maina.
So Shino is going to become someone
else's masochist slave.
Oh!
I feel so lucky and unlucky at the same time.
Then that means, Shino will...
I'll be fine. I'll do my duty even if it's not Master.
No... Shino is going to...
But there's nothing that I can...
It's alright.
I won't be separated from you and
go off somewhere, Master.
Shino, it makes me glad that you would say that,
but you're going to be someone else's...
Wai... Master?
Maina, this is an order.
Make Shino your masochist slave.
Good morning, Master.
Time to wake up.
Thank you for such a fantastic order yesterday.
But is this okay to do?
I just confirmed it.
Confirm?
You went straight to Grandpa?
Yes, Grandpa.
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
Oh really?!
Yes, I would expect nothing less of my Master.
Yes, I'm sure we'll make it succeed.
Grandpa seemed very happy.
You really are my Master.
Such a fantastic Master... I'm so
glad that you're my Master.
Master, good morning.
You're greeting me while sucking a dick...
Forget that, what do you think
you're doing, Shino?!
I'm making the penis of the Master of my
Master in preparation for my Master.
Stop!
Listen to me, from now on without my permission,
you're not allowed to play with Master's penis.
Then licking it is fine?
No!
Then how about sucking it?
No means no!
You're impudent, even though
you're my masochist slave.
This is all for your sake, Master.
If I do this...
Just what do you think you're saying...
What is this?
Good morning, we're in the middle of
making your penis lively right now.
Good morning, Master.
I want you to have a great morning by starting
it off with my morning blow job.
Master, your throat must be parched.
Wet it with my love juices.
Your mouth is on my pussy...
Shino, you're so daring.
I'll do anything for my Master.
Just who are you addressing
when you say Master...
Gosh, there's no chance for me
to be off my guard with you...
Your tongue feels so good inside my pussy...
But, you are my rival and masochist slave.
Master's penis is pushing all the way in...
So good... Master's penis fits so tightly inside...
Master, you seem so happy.
I'm going to have my turn as well. But
I'll stick with just the tongue for now.
No, Shino.
I won't let you go any further.
Master's penis is mine!
Master's possessions are also mine...
So Souta's penis is also mine...
I'm done with you, Shino.
But just like that, come at me.
You're the only person who I recognize as my rival.
I'll tend to Souta's penis plenty for my Master...
For the last time, Master's penis
is mine and only mine...!
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч