GIGOLO (DOCHINIPIRA)
There are a lot of pretty girls out today.
Hey, it's Kaito-kun!
Okamoto!
You haven't been at school at all lately.
I was worried and was wondering what had happened.
I've been busy with work.
So I won't be back for a while.
A part-time gig?
No, no.
My actual job.
Actual job?
Yup.
I'm a seduction artist.
No way!
I'm telling the truth.
I had a woman this morning who gave me 50,000.
I don't believe it.
Well, see ya.
I don't have time to waste chatting with campus friends.
See ya later.
Wait just a minute.
Would you like to seduce me?
I draw a strict boundary between work and school.
But this isn't the campus.
Are you sure?
I came here to go shopping.
Well, I guess it's okay to break the rules sometimes.
Kaito-kun!
Amazing!
I had no idea... it would feel this good.
So this was your first time?
Yes.
I'll give this back.
But why?
I'm a professional seducer.
I don't like to take advantage of beginners.
But I don't mind.
I've always liked you, Kaito-kun.
I thought you'd be the perfect type to take my virginity.
And I didn't have a chance until today.
A professional must stick to his policy.
I wonder if I sounded too cheesy back there.
You bastard!
Oh, shit!
You fucker, come back!
Come back!
You've double-crossed us for the last time, pal!
You're fucking dead!
Don't fuck with the Hazakura gang!
You want the gang to kill you?
Or would you rather join us?
If you join, we can forget about our differences.
I like to work alone.
I won't join a ga-
Fucking brat!
We'll teach you to talk like that!
That's enough, boys.
Asswipe.
Which gang are you with?
I'm not in any gang.
I don't know who the fuck you think you are, but-
Cut it out, man.
Hello, Suzuki-san.
I apologize.
B-Bro?
This man is a friend of our boss.
I apologize, sir.
I'll overlook this incident today.
I'd like to have a talk with that gigolo over there.
Thank you very much.
Come, Jin.
If you want to lecture me, save you breath, Suzuki-san.
Do you think you can survive out there forever as a lone wolf?
Alone against all the gangs.
What about you?
I'm an exception.
The boss is my friend.
My rank and position are different from yours.
What the fuck?
Don't underestimate me just because you're more experienced!
If you keep acting tough, that pretty face of yours will get smashed eventually.
Oh, thanks for the newsflash.
You fucking gigolo.
I don't need to tell you that besides Hazakura,
there are plenty of other gangs swarming around here.
Unless you make your mark and fit in somewhere,
you'll be in trouble with all sides.
You scare tactics won't work on me.
I'll con enough women to get back at you in time, Suzuki-san.
H-Hot.
Here's the Porsche you requested.
Take me anywhere you desire.
Hey, wait! What happening to your face?
Yo.
Don't "yo" me!
You've been gone for three days.
Have you been pimping again?
Don't act like you're my wife.
You knew about my lifestyle when you decided to be with me.
What?
Don't pretend you don't know.
You owe your half of the rent.
Ah, well, I kinda lost it all.
Don't worry. I'll make it up to you in bed.
Good-for-nothing gigolos who come home after neglecting me for so long don't get any!
Ranko...
Cheer up already.
You'll get gray hair!
And I wouldn't want your awesomeness to be spoiled.
Then would you like to take a bath?
I'm in the mood.
Yes, yes.
I'll get in the mood and devour you.
This is child's play.
You dick! Oh, yes! Right there!
Ranko!
Should I be your escort in the road to Heaven?
I apologize if I've hurt your pride with economy class.
First Class is 100,000.
Very well.
Kick ass!
Whoa, her technique is crazy-good!
Even though I'm a pro, I can't hold still!
Very nice. Very nice!
Pound me harder!
One sheep, two sheep, three sheep,
four worms, five worms...
And what was that water animal in Belgium?
What was that?
Now you've done it!
Shit!
Oh, shit, he's from Hazakura!
We're getting out of here.
We can't get caught up in a turf war.
Where'd she go?
Oh, fuck!
I didn't get to pocket the 100,000 yen because of the confusion!
I did it for free.
I'll have a Campari and soda.
So you messed up, eh?
Suzuki-san...
Take it as protection.
But I don't need...
one of the Hazakura leaders was just gunned down at a hotel.
They'll keep getting stronger in this area.
So take it.
It should prove useful to you.
Suzuki-san, why are you taking me into your confidence?
Because I'd like to see you survive long enough to become a real pro.
Or maybe because...
while you're still alive, I want to make you quit your job.
You just don't want me to steal your prey, right?
Dumbass.
Fine, can you seduce that lady over there?
She's top class!
If you can't seduce her, she's mine.
Fine, I'll do it!
Should I fetch you another?
To your healthy!
How much?
I'll pay.
200,000.
Umm...
I dislike hotels.
Drop down and crawl!
Don't mess with...
Lick my boot.
I'm leaving, okay?
If you make a fool out of me, you'll pay dearly!
I'm the Hazakura boss's woman.
You're not getting away!
Umm...
You will address me as "My Queen"!
N-N-N-No, stop!
But you're a professional seducer, right?
Show me what you're made of!
Shit.
The tables have turned.
I'm gonna make her crawl now!
Yes! Yes!
Ya got me, Suzuki!
Jin!
You idiot!
Who'd you seduce this time?
My God!
The top fashion designer, Hana Morie...
We need to talk.
Well, I'll call you next week.
Let's talk.
I'm busy.
Make it quick, okay?
Don't fuck with me!
You pointed me at a real psycho bitch!
Don't be such a fucking baby!
If you can't figure out what kind of woman she is before you fuck her, you're not a pro.
If you want to be a real pro, then show more discretion.
If you blame others for your lack of street smarts,
you'd better quit being a male whore while you're still alive!
A Cobra?
Want a lift?
You're my type.
I know who you are.
A Roppongi gigolo, right?
If you can make me cum for real, I'll let you keep this car as a present.
Your Cobra?
What's your decision?
Idiot!
What do you think you're doing?
I haven't finished yet!
There's a sequel if you're willing to wait.
You even talk stupid.
That's not it at all!
I've just never been with a woman as good as you.
Yes.
Chigasaki?
Okay, I understand.
Come with me.
I'll give you a chance to perform the sequel.
Don't you want the Cobra?
Who the hell is this woman?
Have we met somewhere?
Perhaps.
Looks like we've attracted some bad company.
That can't be.
Whoa, that's a Cobra all right!
I kinda got roped into coming along with you.
But do you want the sequel right here?
I like the ocean.
Huh? Didn't you came here on business?
Yes, but before that, make me burn.
Oh, show us the goods, man!
If you're gonna take it that far, ya might as well take off her panties!
Fuck off!
Showing of in your Cobra.
And now you're giving us a free peep show?
Go ahead and gloat all ya want now.
We'll take it all from you while you're not looking.
You fucking punks.
Run for it!
Awesome boobs!
You asshole!
Do you know who the hell I am?
I'm Kaitoh Jin, the boss of the Hazakura gang!
If you mess up my face,
there's no telling what my pissed-off subordinates will do in relation!
And if it's my woman ya want, you'll have to kill me first.
Well, I'll let it slide for today.
But if ya don't get lost now, you'll fucking pay.
Let's go.
Fucking asshole!
You think that scares us?
Now I've gotcha...
It stops here, you rotten shithead.
If you don't let that boy go,
I'll splatter your brains across the sand.
Hey, babe, put that toy away, okay?
You think that cheap thing would fool us?
Only the first shot was "playing."
Just to inform you,
this wouldn't be the first time I've filled filthy scum like you with lead.
Even if I let you guys live,
there's no doubt you'll just give other people shit.
So go tell your pals to stay the fuck away from me.
W-We're sorry!
P-Please have mercy!
Please forgive us!
You're from that... the hitman?
Oh, dear. So you recognize me?
I'm not involved!
I'm not involved with Hazakura at all!
Aren't you the fierce Hazakura gang boss, Kaitoh Jin?
That was just a story!
To get them to back off.
I hate the idea of working for a gang.
I only told them that to try and save you.
I'm also outside the gang world.
I'm Mizushima Ai.
The "speeding bullet" of the assassination world.
You think I chose you only for sex, Mr. Gigolo?
Why, then?
To get closer to the Hazakura boss.
But I told you I'm not involved with them!
Jin-chan, isn't your friend Suzuki a friend of his?
That's not it at all!
Suzuki's just my instructor as a gigolo. He helps me out!
But Suzuki is deeply involved with Hazakura.
By investigating them, I found you.
S-So the sequel was...
I wasn't kidding.
Before we storm the boss's stronghold.
Before we go kill people?
Let me tell you something about speeding bullets.
They have no place to call home.
That's why their lives burn with passion.
They get very hot... especially before they kill.
You...
Call me Ai.
Ai, here I come!
Yes! Very nice!
I can't stand it!
Amazing technique.
And your sequel was as good as advertised.
You too.
Hey, why don't you give up being a speeding bullet and live a happy life with me?
That can't happen.
Come on. Turn on the engine.
As promised, the Cobra is yours now.
I don't want it!
If it means being the target of a gang, I don't want this car.
I won't let you say you're not involved after all we've been through.
Come. I'll make you check out the boss's hideout for me.
But I don't know what the boss looks like.
Just the opposite. When Hazakura's goons spot me in the street, I can't get any jobs.
You don't seem like you're lying.
So you still don't trust me?
Regardless, you're accompanying me to his hideout.
After all, if I fail, the Cobra will need a new master.
I don't want it!
If I'm successful, I'll give you this car anyway.
But until then you're just my chauffeur.
You just don't quit, do you?
You helped me to relax.
Now I can shoot in there with a clear mind.
She's got me beat.
I've gotten myself mixed up with a crazy woman.
Check on the boss!
The boss!
Ai!
Step on it.
Come back!
Shit!
I can't stand it!
Are you okay?
It's nothing big.
I got the information I needed.
Just quit already!
A woman like you shouldn't be doing this!
A hot woman shouldn't risk her life for a living.
I can't stand it.
Are you serious?
Yeah, very serious.
I haven't heard warm words like that in a long time.
However, I can't turn back now.
Let me tell you about my family.
They got caught up in a Hazakura dispute with the Komatsu,
and they were all killed.
It happened in the spring.
When I was six years old...
Happy birthday, Ai-chan!
He's with the mob!
Come back here, you bastard!
My family wasn't involved.
They just happened to be next to the Komatsu table,
so they ended up full of holes.
As the only survivor, the Komatsu boss took care of me.
But one day on the street, I saw the face of the man who stole my family from me.
And he was with the Hazakura, I suppose.
Yes.
The one the cops executed was a double.
And I couldn't let that murderer,
or the boss who gave him the order to kill,
get away with it!
I had no idea.
Of course, I was raised apart from the gang.
But last year, the Komatsu boss betrayed me,
so I had to kill him.
That's why I hate mobsters!
Do you think what I did was excusable?
Do you have any idea what it's like to have to kill the man who acted like a father to you?
But isn't that why you're a hitman?
I don't really think that's right.
I knew you wouldn't understand anyway.
Anyway, I'll take you and this Cobra to the hideout.
But after that, I'm dropping out.
I won't let you do that.
Ai!
He's not at home or at the mob headquarters.
And if he's not at his second home in Chigasaki then he must be at his mistress's house!
Hey! Don't tell me we're gonna...
Never mind. Just take me back to Tokyo.
I know what his mistress looks like, but I don't know where she lives.
You have to help me find her!
I have no obligation to help you.
You will help me.
Look at this photo of Suzuki's.
You might know the place!
You do know.
You do know where it is, don't you?
Please tell me!
Please!
Tell me!
Watch it!
Even if I knew...
Even if I knew where it was,
I wouldn't take you to such a dangerous place.
I couldn't do it!
I'll use any means necessary to find him.
If there's one thing I dread,
it's being killed by my enemy when my target is right in front of me.
Ai...
If you want to run away, then run away.
I won't ask for your help anymore.
If you can't help protect me when it really counts,
you're just a smart-ass Gigolo!
Go ahead and watch quietly as the Hazakura gang kills me!
Get out.
Get out already!
Jin...
I'll take you there!
On one condition...
Promise me you won't die.
Jin!
If the mob boss is at his mistress's house right now,
and there's no chance you can get out of there alive,
give up on it.
That's the condition.
After you find out where the house is, you'll have plenty of other opportunities to act.
If there's no chance of getting out alive, then don't go through with it!
I don't want to go through all this trouble to take you to your death.
I'll keep that in mind.
I don't usually like to do this sort of thing.
But it can't be helped.
I won't let you say anymore.
I won't let you get caught up in this.
I promise.
He's here.
That's the boss's Renz.
Got it?
Keep your promise.
What the hell am I doing?
Was it okay to let Ai go?
I should stop her.
Ai!
Ai...
I've been waiting for you, "speeding bullet of Komatsu."
Die!
The little bitch thinks she can fight.
You'll have plenty of time in Hell to regret your mistake.
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Ai!
Don't fuck with me.
You gigolo.
So you're teamed up with this stray cat?
Stray cat? Don't you fucking call her that!
You two can have lots of fun in Hell together.
Ai!
Boss!
Hang in there!
Boss, you okay?
R-Run away, Jin.
Boss!
Someone's in there!
Open up!
Boss!
Ai! Hang in there.
S-Stop the car.
I'll get you a doctor!
So don't die.
Don't you dare die!
It's no good.
I know that myself.
Don't try to be all cool.
Sorry, I couldn't keep my promise...
Sorry.
You idiot.
You're such an idiot!
I want to be buried at sea.
I love the sea.
I have many precious memories of playing with my family by the sea.
Ai! Pull yourself together!
I'm glad I was able to meet you before the end.
I'll never forget that thrill.
Thank you.
Ai...
Please kiss me... one more time.
Ai. Ai!
Ai!
Ai!!
You can have that back.
Really?
I don't need that fucking thing.
I'll take care of myself!
I'm not gonna rely on a gang!
As you wish,
you fucking gigolo.
He never learns.
It looks like it wasn't all a waste then.
What's all this for?
It's the anniversary of when we moved in together!
One year!
Come, sit down, sit down.
We'll have the main course in bed.
But, I'm not in the mood for that today.
Then I'll put you in the mood.
Ranko-chan's wonderful technique wows even Jin the professional gigolo.
Ranko!
See? You are in the mood.
Okay! Then we're pulling an all-nighter!
Okay!
I really revive quickly.
Yes! Oh, yes!
Very nice!