Every month on the day of settling down my rent,
I receive a sexual service from
my landlady, Asou Miyuri-san.
She suddenly came wet from a late afternoon shower.
I lent her my shower since I couldn't
take seeing her in that state.
The landlady came out of the shower
looking sexy in her bathrobe!
If she teases me while looking like that,
I won't be able to hold myself back!
She took her robe off as she shook her hips
and humped on me as she squeezed me dry!
I took a bath with the landlady after sweating a lot.
Huh, landlady?!
Was that clothing just a body paint?
She scrubbed me with her squishy soft
body that I couldn't hold myself back.
I got carried away and ended up
being quite rough on her!
I thought that she got so into it as well,
She made sure to charge me more for going overboard.
I have to do my best this month as well so
I can continue to enjoy sex with the landlady!
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing
Little Landlady
Third Pop For The Room's Rent: How many years has it been since I last had P.E. lessons!?
"Don't You Like Teachers (with Black Rim Glasses and in a Lab Coat)" Volume
Y-Yes?
Good evening, Tanaka-san!
I came to collect the payment for this month.
G-Good evening, landlady.
U-Umm... What's with the attire?
I had to deal with some real estate
company stuff earlier today.
How do I look?
Overflowing with adult charm and
looking like a capable woman, am I?
O-Oh... You look great...
Considering the landlady's height,
it looks nothing more than a cosplay.
But she looks cute in it anyway!
Oh, Tanaka-san. Were you
in the middle of studying?
Ah... Sorry for making such a mess in the room.
I am currently working on my college stuff.
Tanaka-san!
If it's alright with you, shall I tutor you?
U-Umm, landlady?
I-It's difficult for me to move
if you're clinging that much...
I won't be able to read your notes unless I do this.
Please don't mind me here~!
Oh my!
Oh...
Tanaka-san, you should get your eraser.
B-But...
Come on, hurry up!
Wait, landlady! Why did you just moan?
Gosh, Tanaka-san! You're breathing so heavily.
Did you want to touch me down there that much?
Hi-yah!
Ahh... W-Wait!
Here you go, here you go! How is it?
The texture of stockings feels good to touch, right?
W-We can't do this, landlady!
I need to do my schoolwork.
I'm not the landlady!
Call me "sensei" for now, Tanaka-kun.
Uhh... U-Umm, sensei...
I'm tutoring you seriously here,
but isn't your mind filled with dirty
thoughts instead, Tanaka-kun?
This calls for a punishment!
I'm not even stepping that hard on you!
Did you get sensitive down here to react that much?
S-Sensei, this feels good!
My, oh my!
This is supposed to be a punishment,
so you shouldn't be feeling good.
Then, how about we do this?
S-Sensei, that feels good!
You're not allowed to come! You have
to hold it in even if it feels good, okay?
N-No way, I can't!
I even feel like I'm gonna come right now!
No, you cant!
We'll end it here if you come.
Look over here! Don't you
want to put it in my pussy?
If you ended up coming just from my feet,
you won't get a taste of this
mushy and gooey hole!
Well, aren't you doing your best?
You want to put this inside
my "pussy" that much, huh?
N-No good! I can't hold it in anymore!
It feels so hot!
Gosh, I told you to hold it in!
As a punishment, we'll postpone this until next time.
T-Tanaka-san?! What's with you all of a sudden?
After getting teased that much,
there's no way that I'll be able to
hold back! Let's go on, please!
W-Wait! Don't suddenly put it in—!
T-Tanaka-san, calm down for a moment!
Y-You're hurting me!
Don't force yourself on me!
Landlady, landlady!
More... I'll make myself feel good even more!
Tanaka-san, wait!
It's been a while since I last had
one inside so it's painful for me!
No—!
No! If you keep on doing it roughly,
you'll end up breaking me down!
Landlady, I'm coming! It's coming out!
No!
L-Landlady? Umm...
Little Ooya-san
Heart-throbbing little landlady!
I forced myself on the landlady!
No, I should pull myself together!
I made her go through something bad!
I'll sincerely apologize!
L-Landlady, I'm sorry for forcing
myself onto you earlier!
It will never happen again,
so may I ask for your forgiveness?
Tanaka-san, you're prostrating yourself...
L-Landlady?
I-I'm sorry, it's because you
tend to do the strangest things
that I accidentally burst out laughing.
Aren't you such an earnestly good boy, Tanaka-san?
Well-then, Tanaka-kun...
Let's continue our lessons.
Pay close attention, okay?
Huh, lessons? But what happened earlier was...
We'll be having P.E. lessons this time.
We'll study using my body!
Listen carefully.
This frilly part in the middle
of labia majora and labia minora
is the vaginal opening or the pussy!
The vaginal cavity's job is to
stimulate the male genital.
It has many swelling creases and it
can be widened and tightened up!
Of course, it is a woman's erogenous zone.
Want to try touching it, Tanaka-kun?
Huh?! Can I really touch it?
Y-Yeah... That's right...
It's a highly sensitive spot, so do it gently—!
Ah... You're hitting me at a good spot right now!
You have to enjoy sex this way as you consider
how your partner feels, okay?
Yes... Landlady, I truly am sorry for earlier.
U-Umm... If it's alright with you,
I hope to be under your care from today onwards.
Yes, I forgive you!
Come on! Aren't you all
good to go now, Tanaka-san?
Alright, we'll continue this on the bed.
Okay, Tanaka-san!
Yes, here I go!
Y-You're doing great!
I'm feeling your huge dick so much, Tanaka-san!
Landlady, are you feeling good?
Yes, I'm feeling so good!
I can feel how you're treating
me with so much care!
Landlady, the shape of your insides
changed in this position, it feels good!
Me too, I like this! I like this position!
Come on, Tanaka-san.
It's alright, you can go a little rougher on me!
Don't hold yourself back!
But I feel like I'm gonna come if I go any further!
It's alright, please come as many times as you want!
I'm coming!
Landlady, umm... Can we do it a bit more?
Yes, it'll be my pleasure!
Tanaka-san, you're fantastic!
You already came that much before,
but you're still as hard as a rock!
How does humping above me like this feel?
It feels great! More! Please keep moving!
I'm coming!
Landlady... Landlady...
You're doing great, Tanaka-san!
I want to be connected with
you forever just like this!
I'm sorry, I'm already—!
Come, come!
Shoot a lot into me!!
By the way, for this month's rent...
I gave you private lessons so
I have to charge you for that.
E-Ehh...
I don't have a chance to decline
if you'll only tell that to me now.
Alright then! You have my
regards for next month as well!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization