Saaya, who's someone I cherish
is always looking at me.
Her charming facial expression does
not change a bit no matter what I do.
She just steadily keeps on staring at me.
Cute, cute Saaya...
Saaya is my angel.
We'll always be together.
Saaya will never betray me.
She is always there for me.
Saaya... It's already been three months
since you came here in my house.
You just keep on getting cuter.
Oh, Saaya... My cute Saaya...
The way you look at me is so lovely, Saaya...
Saaya has only me in her eyes.
I am Saaya's only one.
You've always been dwelling
inside my heart as well, Saaya.
Now, throw yourself into me.
Into me, now.
Oh... It's no good, Saaya.
I'm doing something bad again.
But, I can't help it!
I'm poking and spreading
you open like this, Saaya.
All of these are because you
are so adorable, Saaya.
Oh, Saaya...
Your skin is silky smooth.
Saaya! This is wrong...
For me to enjoy so much...
from playing with your body!
But just a little more...
A bit more would be okay, right?
Won't you say it's fine, Saaya?
Oh, Saaya... Spread your thighs wider!
Let me reach it better, Saaya!
I'm touching it, Saaya.
My hand is on your important
place. Let's proceed.
Let's come together,
Saaya. It's okay, right?
Saaya, you shouldn't do that...
Stop looking at me with those
adorable eyes, Saaya!
Oh, Saaya! Oh, Saaya!
Th-Th-This is bad! Oh!
Saaya, I love you... I love you, Saaya!
I want you, Saaya—!
Saaya!
Saaya...
I defiled you yet again...
You'll forgive me, right?
It's alright, I'll clean you up good.
I know it, Saaya.
You won't get angry even
if I do something like this.
That's because you're my angel.
This is my first year as a new graduate
and member of the adult world,
I got into a job that isn't related
to design, not even a bit.
This is a "Health Food Sales" job.
What, you say that your health products
are good for the company?
Yes, if these are taken in even in a state of
insolvency, the employees will—
Are you an idiot? Where can you find
something that useless nowadays?
No! Like I say, even in a state of insolvency,
the employees will be more proactive...
Dumbhead! We are currently
undergoing a company restructuring!
We have no need to be lured
on health products!
Can't you do something about it?
Go away! If that is such a wonderful
drug, why not drink it yourself?!
Y-Yes...
I already got used on these.
Getting vented on of the customers'
stress is part of the job in Sales dep't.
Even so, I'm also going to be laid off
if I don't reach my sales quota.
But even at a time like this,
I end up thinking about Saaya instead.
I shampooed her today, so I'm sure that
her hair is now fluttering in the wind...
Saaya... You're my angel.
Saaya?
It's Saaya! Why is she...
I can't believe this! That hair, that eye color!
There's no mistaking it. That's Saaya!
That's it! I thought about her
so much that she became real!
And it's perfectly the same
as how I thought she will be!
So cute! How cute she is!
This is a God's gift to me!
And here I thought nothing
good is happening,
But now, I don't care
about that job anymore!
She has to wear the same dress...
I have the money today.
I'll have it order-made!
I'm looking forward to it,
that girl is the doll just for me!
I live alone without any relatives,
but my parents left me a lot.
I'll still be fine in the next two or
three years even if I splurge it.
Now that I think about it,
it's fine even if I stop working.
I don't need to work, I can just
live together with Saaya!
This is good. It turned out
perfectly like Saaya's dress.
Right, Saaya? Isn't this alright?
You're fine with this dress even
if you got bigger now, right?
Is that so? I knew that
you'll be happy about this.
That's right, no matter
how much you love me,
you won't be able to tell me
what you feel, right?
But everything is okay now.
You see, God sent a human
version of you in this world.
I'll bring her here so just wait, Saaya.
Hey!
Huh?
Oh, sorry. Did I surprise you?
Huh, no...
You see, I'm Nakamura Kazuya.
I'm a fashion designer.
Huh, fashion designer?
Yeah. I might not look like it,
but I've been in fashion shows.
That's amazing!
Not as much as you think.
And... do you need something from me?
Oh, right.
The truth is I made a design for the next
show, but I can't find a good model...
I've been searching all this time,
and you seem perfect for it.
Huh... Me, a model?
Yes, it has to be you. Please!
No way... Someone like me...
I'm begging you! You'll get
paid good enough!
No way, I'm not...
Then, it's decided.
I'm glad... Thank you!
Wow, you have a wonderful house!
The atelier is on the 2nd floor.
Let's go upstairs.
It's in this room.
Come in. This is the dress that
will be shown tonight.
Wow, it's adorable!
Let's try it on you, Saaya.
Huh?
U-Umm, what did you call me?
Okay, try to see it on you
in front of the mirror.
Look, it suits you.
You look good in it, just as I thought.
Alright, Saaya. Try wearing this dress.
U-Umm, my name is Mariko...
What are you talking about, Saaya?
You're Saaya who's right there.
Right there... you mean the doll?
Haven't you always been
living together with me?
And then have you not answered my feelings
and transformed onto that body, Saaya?
Wait, what are you talking about?
I get it, Saaya.
Your memories aren't totally gone
since we've always been together.
Your mind may still be in disarray,
being just incarnated.
Umm, I'm going home!
Wait, Saaya.
I'm not Saaya!
Saaya, you're just confused at this moment.
You'll realize that you are
Saaya if you calm down.
I have no idea who that Saaya is!
Stop giving me trouble.
You have to wear the dress, Saaya.
No!
Please! Stop doing this!
Stop!
Such huge breasts!
Your tits are huge, Saaya!
No—!
Oh... amazing! It's perfect!
You really are Saaya, see?
I've said that I'm not...
Look, it suits you! It's like made to fit you.
Alright, well have fun together
like we always did, Saaya.
No...
Come one, try saying it. "My name is Saaya."
You're wrong! My name is Mariko!
If you keep saying that,
I'll have to punish you!
Or could it be that
you wanted me to do that?
No...
So, what is it?
Are you not Saaya, or are you?
I am Saaya...
So please spare me from any more of this!
You finally admitted it, Saaya.
We'll now be doing great stuffs, okay?
Here, spread them open.
No, stop! Stop!
What's this, Saaya? Could
it be that you got wet?
Th-That's not true!
Then why are your panties soaked?
Look, right here.
Huh? My finger is sinking in.
So your body has a hole.
Hey, Saaya. What is happening down here?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Then, I'll take these off since
they're just a bother.
I'm going to have a good look.
Look, they're drenched! Is this pee?
I never peed!
Then what is it, huh?
It doesn't smell like pee.
Here, try sniffing it yourself.
How is it? Here, doesn't it smell good?
It's a juice that comes out
when you do something lewd, right?
I can't breathe! I can't breathe...
Stop this! I am not Saaya!
My, my... You really are a stubborn one.
Then, seeing this should make you
remember that you are indeed Saaya.
Here it is, Saaya.
This is something that
you stare at every night.
No!
Hey, hey... This shouldn't shock you.
Weren't you always glad to be
showered with my semen?
Here, try licking it.
I said lick it!
I see...
Something scary awaits if you
keep being stubborn, Saaya!
Alright! There, it's in.
Right, just like that. That's the way!
Come on, swallow it deeper!
That's it, have a good taste
using your tongue.
Remember my scent, Saaya!
It's slippery and it feels good!
There... there... there!
You were tiny in the past
so we couldn't do this.
But it will be fine from now on!
That's it, Saaya! It feels good!
Great, that's great!
You're drooling so much!
You're so lewd, Saaya!
My thing is filling your tiny mouth!
It's so wet, this is the best!
My thing is going in and out of your mouth!
You're so cute, Saaya!
It's so warm!
I never thought that your mouth
would feel this good!
I-I'm about to come!
You can't! You can't...
You can't!
I'm coming sooner than I usually do!
You're amazing, Saaya!
No way!
I-It's coming! It's coming out, Saaya!
I finally managed to squirt in your mouth, Saaya!
There's so much of my stuff inside you!
No... Why are you doing this?
I always dreamt about it,
that someday you'll become human.
And when we meet, I'll squirt
in your mouth firsthand.
With this, you've now
become the best doll!
Oh... This is weird!
There's something weird
on you down here, Saaya.
I-It's been there all this time!
Nah, you never had it before!
That's right, it's a side effect of your
incarnation from a doll to a human.
Alright, let's shave it off!
I'll clean it up for you.
No! P-Please stop!
It' gonna be alright! Stay still
and it'll be over soon.
P-Please! Stop this!
Please—
Okay, it's done! Now it looks
like how it used to be.
That dress is torn now. We don't need
it anymore, so let's throw it away.
Let me have a good look
of your naked body.
No! No—!
Oops, stop moving.
It would be bad if I cut you somewhere.
No! Stop! Let me go home!
Stop saying stupid things!
Isn't the fun just starting?
Look, your huge tits are now exposed.
I'm done tearing it off you.
How perfect! You don't
look like a doll at all!
You look just like a human does, Saaya!
I'm begging you, this is embarrassing!
Such an enticing body.
Alright, where was that hole before?
Here, it's in. It's in.
My finger is getting sucked inside!
Huh? Now it's getting pushed out!
No!
No! No...
It's foaming and dripping a lot!
You shouldn't pee, Saaya-chan!
I never... peed myself!
Then, is this love juice?
You got aroused, Saaya.
Then I'll put one more finger in.
Look, I have two fingers inside!
Your hole is amazing, Saaya!
No!
No—!
No, you'll tear me up!
Here, here! I'm thrusting
two fingers inside you!
Can we put more fingers inside?
No, It'll get torn! Don't!
Saaya, you're dripping
wet just like a waterfall!
Does getting fingered feel good, Saaya?
No!
G-Good! Please keep doing it!
Do it yourself next.
I'm gonna be watching you.
That's it, stimulate the beady part more.
You're feeling quite good. Right, Saaya?
You're dripping a lot of love juice.
Yes, do it even more!
That's it...
Look at this.
I already got like this.
Saaya, take a good look!
Haven't you been always looking at it?
Here, Saaya. Lick it
with your tongue again.
Your mouth is the best, you know.
Hurry up. That's it!
You're doing great, Saaya!
Coil it around! I'm feeling even better!
Come on, take it in deeper! Yes!
Good!
Your mouth is so warm
and it feels so good!
This is bad, Saaya! I'm feeling
so good, I'm gonna come again!
Oops! That's the way!
Alright! Lie down there while
you're masturbating, Saaya.
Your important place is sticky, Saaya!
Your entrance is already wide open!
Aren't you feeling too good, Saaya?
Then, I'm gonna put not my finger,
but my thick thing inside this time .
Now, I wonder how it feels like
reaching beyond even deeper, Saaya.
Oh, it's in!
It totally went in, Saaya!
That's good, Saaya! You're
squeezing me tight down there!
I'm gonna start moving this time!
Oh... How is it?
You can't!
You can't! It's so big!
Here, here! Here you go!
Thrust it in! Thrust it in!
My thing is going inside you....
More... Thrust it in more!
Look at it, I'm pushing it inside!
We're connected!
It's inside, so deep!
My bulbous part is poking inside you.
Your insides are so rough and uneven!
Thrust it in, more!
Y-You're amazing, Saaya!
Move your hips!
That's it!, Yes, that's it! Good, Saaya...
More, move it more!
More, keep doing it more!
More, thrust it in more! More!
More!
That's so good! Y-You're
squeezing me so tight, Saaya!
I'm gonna come!
Not yet... You can't come yet, Saaya!
Oh... Saaya! If you
squeeze me that hard—!
I'm gonna come! More!
Saaya! I'm coming!
Coming... Coming!
I'm coming!
Saaya...
You are Saaya, aren't you?
Huh? Yes...
I am Saaya.
This doll is Saaya as well.
Then this means that there are two of you.
Huh? What do you mean?
What I mean is, you should
combine with this doll Saaya.
It's not that perplexing,
it's something really simple.
Alright, spread it wide again.
What are you going to do?
I'll put it inside here.
No way! Th-That's impossible!
It can be done.
Didn't my huge thing
manage to fit inside before?
Here you go, Saaya!
I-It hurts!
Hey, hey! Stop acting spoiled, Saaya!
It would be a problem
if there are two of you!
E-Even if you say that...
Come on, come on!
No! It's scraping me so much inside!
Please stop ramming it inside!
Put it in yourself then!
Here, hurry up!
Try to turn it around
while getting it lubricated!
I-It hurts!
Push it in like I told you. You're doing
good. Keep rubbing it in like that.
There, there! You're getting wet again.
Look at that, you're now
catching your breath!
Did it start to feel good?
Th-There's no way—
It completely went inside you!
No, it all went in! What should we do?
You're amazing, Saaya!
You sucked it in just like a vacuum cleaner!
No way! The whole thing went inside!
It's not my fault even if it gets stuck!
But you're the one who told me to do it!
Hmm, what's that?
Saaya?
Wh-What's wrong, Saaya?
Your eyes are shining!
Oh, you're floating!
You're scaring me, Saaya!
I am Saaya!
Th-Th-That's right. You're Saaya, aren't you?
I've been stuck inside the doll until now.
And you did a lot of cruel things to me!
I-I never did anything cruel to you!
But since I was a doll back then,
I endured everything you did.
So this time, I'll do the opposite.
O-Opposite?
That's right! You will go inside me!
Oh, have you come back to your senses?
I'm going home now, okay?
I don't think we'll meet again,
but take care of yourself. Alright then!
H-Hey! W-Wait!
I-I can't move my body!
What's with this? What happened?
H-Hey, don't go!
Can't you hear my voice, Saaya?!
Well then, bye bye!
Saaya...
Don't go! Come back here!
I'm begging you... Come back here!
Saaya...
Saaya—!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization