Dorei Maid Princess
Translation: Voldemort | Editing: Solidus Snake | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
This is a special monster I set aside just for you.
Yes. I can control it with this ring.
You're controlling it?
Yes.
By concentrating, I can control each
of the monster's tentacles at will.
Please don't move it!
Oh dear.
Finished already?
At this rate, I think we had best stimulate
her ass as well as her vagina.
Is that fine with your?
My ass?
Lotte, you are to become my possession - every part of you.
Your possession...
Will you do this for me, Lotte?
Yes.
Eric, you will become... my master!
Your slippery tentacles... thrust them deep inside of me.
You can have everything!
Yes.
Every part of you, Lotte.
How ironic.
I'm using a monster to violate Lotte.
Eric! Hurry up and come!
Wait up, Lotte!
We mustn't do this!
If we leave the castle, the monsters will come.
Oh?
Then you'll protect me, won't you?
Yep! I will protect you!
No matter what happens, I'll protect you, Lotte!
I had no idea I would have to protect her like this...
I'll break!
My ass will break!
No!
It hurts!
It's too tight in my ass!
I know.
I can feel the hard place I'm touching.
That's my uterus... my uterus... my uterus!
That's right.
I'm going to make your uterus feel good right now.
And as I do this, I'm going to stimulate
your ass to trigger your memory.
Prince Eric's monster will teach your ass to lust for him.
How lucky for you, Princess.
Remember this feeling Lotte!
Learn how to be turned on by your ass.
Imprint it on your entire body!
I'm imprinting it!
It's imprinted on my ass!
I will repeat this all day and night.
Until every single organ in your body
exists to fulfill my sexual desires.
Uncle wishes to see me?
Yes.
There are rumors circulating that Lotte's training is not going well.
I see.
Thank you.
Breidonner, you really are a dependable man.
No, sir.
I am merely a loyal servant to you, Prince Eric.
Eric, we've been expecting you.
Uncle?
No, King Karl.
You may dispense with the formalities.
How is Princess Lotte's training proceeding?
Well.
Thanks to the tools you sent, her training is proceeding beautifully.
I see.
Though there are rumors circulating that it is not going well.
But you should simply ignore them.
I will.
Thank you.
Breidonner.
Is it true that Eric lets Lotte roam freely through the castle?
Y-Yes.
So she may still have some fight left in her.
Then it's also likely that she hasn't sworn complete loyalty to him.
It is also advisable that he lock her in the
dungeon when she is not in training.
How is it, Lotte?
Does my monster please you?
Yes!
Master!
The tentacles are deep inside my ass...
Please make them squirm to fuck me harder.
I'm not stopping at your ass.
I'm going to fuck it to the very tip.
Understand, Lotte?
Yes?
To the very tip?
Going inside... Master is coming deep inside!
Lotte!
Let the tentacles behind you pass through.
Pass through?
That's right.
Let it pass through to your mouth.
To my mouth!?
C-Come!
Use your monster tentacle cock to pierce through my mouth!
What strong resolve.
Now, let your entire body become a pussy for your master.
Here I go.
It's invading me.
It's all the way inside my stomach!
Very good.
This is Lotte's stomach.
Eric, your dick...
It's not there yet!
I'll fill you up with plenty of cum.
I will fill you up, to nourish you.
Come in!
Come in, Master!
Fill me full!
Please!
Master...
It came out!
Lotte, suck it!
The tentacle coming out of your mouth...
Think of it as my dick!
Amazing!
I can feel your entire body!
I feel like I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
My entire body has become a vagina.
It's a vagina just for your sake, Eric!
Please cum in me, Master!
Every hole and passageway in my body
exists only to help you cum, Master!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming into all of your organs, Lotte!
I endured it.
You pass, Princess.
This is rather extreme.
I see no reason to do this after all we've been through.
My uncle told me to.
So please, remain my slave until your final training session is over.
As you wish.
What's wrong, Breidonner?
Capture him at once!
Breidonner?
Please run away, Prince!
Lotte?
Prince Eric.
I won't let them kill my Master!
Master!
Keela!
Impressive.
She truly is a witch of Vilen Kophen.
Prince...
Breidonner!
Be strong!
It was an honor... to serve all these... years...
Breidonner!
It appears we must say farewell.
Princess Lotte, please take care of the prince...
I promise to protect him!
Eric will not die.
We will see to it that he lives.
Being protected by two beautiful women.
I am... pleased... for you...
Prince... please... look upon... me...
Breidonner!
Master, now is not the time to be sad.
I have a plan.
Please let me have the bodies of the intruders.
What are you going to do?
I intend to discover who tried to kill you.
Using my magic, I will search their minds.
I hope you find an answer swiftly.
We have very little time left, it seems.
We must hurry with the final training session as well.
Now, Lotte, here is your final training session.
Uh, but...
Whit's the matter, Princess?
Your final task is to please your master using your body.
You are prepared, aren't your?
Y-Yes, but, the only other time I've pleasured him
in the conventional way was my first time.
And being seen by someone is not...
Oh.
In that case, you needn't worry.
After all, in this training session,
I will also be participating.
And so, let us pleasure you, Master.
W-Wait! Not there!
You needn't hold back for your slaves.
See?
Eric?
It's shivering with pleasure.
Master's virgin anus.
N-Not there!
Y-You shouldn't lick him there.
It's strange!
Strange?
If you think that, then take a good look at this, Princess.
When Master is stimulated in such a "strange" place,
it makes his penis very big and hard.
Y-Your tongue... it's so deep!
See?
It's so hard.
Master, the tip of it has become wet.
Eric!
Master!
Please let me pleasure you, too.
No, I'm gonna pleasure you.
Eric, you fool!
How dare you get pleasure from Keela!
Lotte, you too?
It's so hard and hot!
You got this way from her!?
From her!?
Hey, Master,
I please you more, don't I?
What about me, Master?
I please you more.
I please you more, don't I?
Both of you... You both please me.
I don't want to hear that!
I'll bite you!
That's good, Lotte.
His balls have risen.
Your balls are so big.
Let me suck! Let me suck!
Fill me with love!
Fill me full of your delicious love!
You are so strong, Master.
And yet, your shivering ass is so cute.
It's no use.
I'm cumming. Cumming!
Wait, Master.
Cum inside my mouth.
I'll swallow it.
I'll swallow it all!
It's still hard.
Even after he's finished, there's still so much?
Certainly.
We can do it again, can't we?
Do it? Do what?
Isn't it obvious?
I will pleasure your mighty cock with my disgusting pussy.
Hey, not so fast!
Do not interfere.
You stay there and watch what I do closely.
Amazing.
So this is Keela's...
How do I taste to you?
Very good, Keela!
I don't even have to move.
Eric looks like he's enjoying himself.
While moving up and down on it,
I'm also squeezing it from the inside.
Am I also able to do that?
We'll have to make you able.
See? Like this...
Fine, fine I get it.
Let me try!
Oh no.
I want you to keep watching until Master cums.
It... It's coming!
It's coming, Keela!
Then cum, Master.
Fill me with your cum!
It's cumming!
Cumming deep inside!
It's filling my pussy!
Eric, are you cumming?
I'm cumming!
She's making me cum!
It's unbelievable. Your insides, Keela.
Thank you very much, Master.
Untie me at once!
It's my turn now!
Keela, hurry and get Lotte down.
Not yet.
Master...
The real intensity begins now.
It's sucking me!
See? I'm sucking it.
Like this.
Please move, Master.
Move.
Move and fuck me!
Please, Master.
Thrust around like a monster.
Cum as much as you want!
Okay, I will.
As you wish.
You're amazing, Keela.
It's so tight.
He's obsessed.
Let's show her.
Let's show the Princess the looks on
our faces when we reach ecstasy!
I'll help you cum, Keela.
I'm cumming!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
That was very good, Keela.
Eric!
You filthy cheater!
Now.
It's your turn to please Master.
Don't look at my ass.
After watching something so embarrassing,
I'm now doing something just as nasty.
Your ass and pussy are linked now.
Show Master how tight your ass is with your pussy.
So Eric is going to know what I look like inside...
Time to begin, Lotte.
Move your pelvis and squeeze me tight.
Yes, Master.
Like this?
Master!
You're watching me.
It's tight.
You can tell that from my ass.
Does it please you?
Do I please you more than that bitch?
Oh my, what a sore loser, that Princess.
Of course you please me more.
Then please let the good feelings flow, Master.
Look at my asshole.
It's tight!
My pussy is hugging your cock.
You can see it, can't you?
You can see my ass throbbing.
Yes, I can see.
I understand what's going on.
Look.
Keep looking!
Look at my disgusting asshole.
Stare at it, Master!
Now, time for me to reward you.
R-Right there!
That's my special place!
The place I want you to penetrate
with the tip of your penis, Master.
Lotte, you love having your uterus fucked, don't you?
You made me love it.
Master made me love it.
Right there! Hit it right there!
Fuck me, Master!
What a selfish slave you are.
Right there!
If Master touches me there...
Your cock...
Oh no.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
But I don't want to cum alone.
You cum too, Master.
I don't want to cum alone.
Then I'll cum.
I'll do it while watching your asshole.
I'm cumming.
Look.
Keep looking.
Look at my asshole until I cum.
Fuck me with your eyes, Master!
Lotte!
Master... Master!
You're filling me with cum!
I'm cumming... Cumming!
Amazing! Amazing, Master!
Master, anal is amazing!
You're right, it is amazing.
So soft... and so tight.
It's sucking on me too.
What a nasty asshole you have.
Mess me up with your cock, Master.
Mess me up!
Very good, Keela.
Master... Master...
Now, both of you open your mouths.
I have a reward for you.
Get a good taste.
Your pee.
Master, your pee.
So delicious.
You suck at this.
You're barely drinking it.
What about your?
It's all over your face.
Let me...
In the end, please feed me.
Feed me inside.
Master!
I'm cumming!
Very well done, you two.
You have passed all of your training.
Of course I have.
Why did you wish to see me all of a sudden, Yan?
It's about the person who killed Breidonner.
How did you know?
I summoned him.
I entered the memories of the assassins.
And I had Lord Yan investigate the contents.
Eric.
I know who was after your life.
Who was it?
It was...
tooi kioku tadotte miru
Searching my distant memories,
soko ni wa itsumo kimi ga ita
I find that you are always in them.
tsuyogatte mo kizu tsukete mo
Even when I'm stubborn or when I hurt you,
kawaranai de ite kureta ne
You still stay there for me, unchanged.
kimi no manazashi ga
Your gentle gaze
yasashisa watashi ni oshieta
Taught me kindness.
nani mo osorenai
I fear nothing now.
eranda michi o mayowazu ni yuku dake
I will walk unwaveringly down the path I chose.
kitto doko made mo tsuite yuku yo
Surely I will go with you anywhere.
okori ni kakete mo a Akiramenai
Even if my pride gets in the way, I will not give in.