Now then, Prince Eric.
Please take this pill.
What is it?
It's crucial to your stewardship.
It enables your slave maid to drink your cum for all eternity.
It allows you to cum all day long.
It's a special recipe that has been passed
down along my family line of witches.
I'll take it.
Well then, this enslavement will proceed for the next week.
Are you okay, Lotte?
I'm fine, Eric.
Wh-What are you doing?
The enslavement begins now!
He is no longer "Eric," but "Master"!
Yes, but not yet...
You are no longer a Vilen Kofen princess!
You are a disgusting slave.
If you fail to accomplish this duty, then this chance is over.
Fine.
Understand me... I wish for you to escape quickly.
Keela!
As a noble princess of Vilen Kofen, you
may choose any profession you wish.
Shut up!
I will become a slave maid.
No matter what humiliating circumstances befall me,
I made the decision to become Eric's slave maid!
Oh, really?
I wonder how much longer you will be able
to maintain your strong demeanor.
We'll teach you to look up fearfully in time.
Princess Sow.
As you wish.
We made a promise to each other when we were kids.
That we would stay together forever, no matter what.
Lotte...
Why did this happen to us?
We're walking a very confusing path at the moment.
For the sake of our relationship,
and for the sake of our future,
our only choice was to break her - to tram her as my slave maid.
Dorei Maid Princess
Translation: Voldemort | Editing: Solidus Snake | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
But it surprises me how our rival country, Vilen
Kofen, was destroyed so completely.
We surely owe this victory to our witch's army.
Lotte... I hope you've been captured safely.
Prince Eric, we must execute Princess Lotte...
Don't say that!
We will take her as a living hostage.
But the castle will fall any minute now,
and besides, even if we let her live...
I will absolutely not permit Lotte's demise.
Eric!
No, you spineless sorceress!
Do you fear me?
Show yourself at once!
Eric! Eric!
Well done, Eric.
We have captured Princess Lotte alive.
Now we will be able to give her a formal execution.
Father! What did you just say?
The witch army helped us defeat Vilen Kofen in exchange that
we allow them to personally oversee Lotte's execution.
But, Father...
Prince Eric,
this feud has gone on long enough.
The death of Princess Lotte is a small price
to pay to end a war of generations.
But they're dirty beasts!
They're disgusting monsters!
You of all people should know that!
I do know that.
Then why...?
Princess Lotte is rather popular among the witch tribe.
So either Lotte dies or our country falls under their wrath?
Exactly.
It was our best option of winning this war.
But that plan is evil and immoral!
Eric, don't question your father's authority.
I'm sure your reasons for wanting Lotte as a hostage are personal.
Yes, but...
There are plenty of beautiful princesses around.
Please give her up for the sake of your country.
But, Father...
This is the one thing... The one thing that I cannot allow!
If we let Princess Lotte live now,
peril will come to our country later.
And the witch clan is i frightening adversary indeed.
Eric...
F-Father!
What if Lotte became my slave maid?
What?
A slave maid, he says?
I've never heard of such a thing.
A slave maid...
She is a special maid of noble upbringing
who belongs solely to her master.
She satisfies her master sexually and is one
hundred percent loyal to her master.
She also often serves as an escort vessel.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you realize how many years it takes
to break in a new slave maid?
Countless days of torture and conditioning,
which sometimes makes the girl go mad.
And what's more, the conditioning is usually
supposed to begin in childhood.
Just one month.
Please give me one month!
I will break her in myself.
So please, Father, spare Lotte's life!
Brother, this is a good idea.
But Carl!
If something were to happen to Eric, the future of Balt,
we would have no heir.
If that witch became Eric's slave maid,
this problem would be alleviated.
Though not entirely...
Yes, but...
Brother...
Thank you so much!
Uncle Carl!
Then I will grant you one month.
If she fails to become a proper slave maid by
the end of the month, she will be executed.
And you will be punished as well.
Understood, Eric?
Yes, I understand, Father.
Then please bring Lotte to me at once.
My method of "saving" Princess Lotte was a lie.
I had no intention of turning her into a slave maid.
I just needed time to convince everyone otherwise.
And I only had one month to do it in.
The executioner...
Slave maid, you say!?
Lotte, please hear me out.
Don't call me so familiarly by name!
The only reason I did not kill myself was so
that I could kill you with my own hands!
You goddamn witch fraternizer!
How dare you speak to Prince Eric in that manner!
You men step back, please.
But, sir...
I wish to speak with Princess Lotte alone.
I will summon you if I need you.
Then... we'll be outside the door.
The sorceress Keela has been waiting in the adjoining room.
Fine, I understand.
You sure are brave, Eric.
What do you intend to do alone with me?
I haven't changed at all since childhood.
Not even in a situation like this...
Why are you bringing up the past now?
Lotte, please listen to me.
If you fail to become a slave maid in a month's time, then...
Silence!
A slave maid, you say?
You damned traitor!
Lotte...
Don't look at me with those eyes!
We share the same heart... So why?
Shut up!
I'll kill you!
One more push and you will have reached my heart.
You didn't need to tell me!
Lotte... I really have loved you all this time.
Shut up!
You still say that after all you've done!?
We did kill your father...
I suppose after everything I've done, I deserve to be killed by you.
That's not it!
Why did you betray me?
I couldn't escape my ties to my country.
I'll admit, our fathers hated each other.
But once they pass away,
we could...
I'm sorry.
But for the sake of my ego... I want you to live on.
There's a woman named Keela who can turn you into a slave maid.
I'm begging you, please undergo the training.
For my sake, I want you to live on.
Perhaps my dripping blood was what convinced Lotte to trust me.
I lost consciousness soon after,
but Keela brought me back.
Just a minute.
Aren't we going to start the training?
We'll begin the training now.
You just watch over there.
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm going to teach you how to perform fellatio.
Just a minute, get away from Eric at once!
That's, "Get away from Master at once."
I already know how to do that.
Oh, are you jealous?
Why would I be!?
You belong to your master.
But your master does not belong to you.
Sorry, Lotte.
Go ahead, Keela, show her how it's done.
Yes, Master.
It's been so long!
You taste delicious, Master.
Wonderful, Master!
All right, Keela, may I violate your throat?
As you wish.
Please violate my throat-pussy.
Now, it's your turn, dear.
Master's cock is fantastic.
If you cannot become a slave maid and end up getting executed,
I wonder if I can become his slave instead?
Wh-What!?
Master, please violate my throat at once.
Oh, you're really getting into it now, aren't you?
No, I just know I can please Eric better.
I don't want this cow to defeat me!
Lotte...
Lotte, use your tongue more.
That's right.
Eric is training me.
Yes.
U-Use your throat.
Yes, Master.
I-I'm sorry.
Oh dear, at this rate, your only dinner will be Master's cum.
You'll never cut it.
Suck on this every day to practice.
What a disgusting act for a princess.
Master and I will train you thoroughly, so prepare yourself.
Come, Master.
Lotte!
Prince Eric.
You mustn't be so easy on her.
Ah, yes, you're right.
Unless she can clear this hurdle within
a week, there's no future for her.
I understand.
For Lotte's sake, I will become a tough slave driver.
I'm sorry, Lotte.
I'm sorry.
I'll be harder on you,
to save you.
But this scene would have never appeared in my dreams earlier.
L-Lotte?
Eric...
You were watching over me the whole time?
Only because you wouldn't release my hand.
Prince Eric, you certainly are quite reckless.
Keela... Do the others...
Fear not.
No one knows what happened except for me.
I found you before your soldiers.
But if they had found you first, Princess
Lotte would have been killed.
So you couldn't kill me.
Don't misunderstand!
I only spared your life because there was no way to escape anyway!
And besides, if I become your slave maid, I will live, right?
Yes.
That way seems like the safer bet.
Yes, it does.
So don't misunderstand my actions!
I do this only to survive.
Lotte...
Why are you making that face?
You crybaby.
Lotte!
Idiot.
You'll open your wound.
Keela, may I ask a favor?
Any favor of yours, Prince Eric, I will gladly obey.
Thank you, Keela.
And I as well.
Let me make one thing clear as well.
I will not hold back in your training.
Any failure in your training will  result in your demise.
I am prepared for that.
There's one more thing.
One more thing?
Saving your life will most likely put Prince Eric's in danger.
He is placing himself in a dangerous position
between you and my witch clan.
Keela... Don't say that...
So if your training is not proceeding well,
I might quit before the month is up.
As you wish.
I will tolerate any harsh punishment.
For I am Lotte Vilen Kofen!
As a witch of Vilen Kofen would say.
We will begin your breaking promptly tomorrow.
And one more thing...
What?
If you are still a virgin, see to that tonight, Princess.
Prince Eric's wounds should be healed enough.
Listen, Eric...
I... Um... I'm a virgin.
I thought so.
We'd better take care of that tonight.
It's my first time, okay?
Y-Yes...
Hurry up and fuck me.
Okay, I will.
I'll fuck you hard.
I've always dreamed of doing it.
Undress.
Amazing... It's gotten so big.
Is this your first time, too?
Yes, it is.
I wanted you to be my first.
I see.
Well, shall I lick it?
Yeah.
Is "yeah" all you can say?
Sorry.
Say, men like this, don't they?
Yes, it feels good.
Very nice, Lotte.
Lotte... Lotte... Lotte!
You soiled my face!
That is unforgivable!
Sorry!
It's still throbbing.
Eric!
B-Be gentle, please.
I will. Time to fuck you.
You're very wet.
I wouldn't know!
Slower... Slower please, Eric.
Yes, I understand.
Eric!
Lotte.
It feels...
It feels so good inside you.
Me too.
Even though it's my first time,
it feels so good!
Can I move more?
I want to fuck you thoroughly.
If you move a little, I should be fine.
Too fast, Eric!
It's my first time, remember?
Sorry... but I can't hold back.
I-I'm going to cum!
W-Wait, Eric, I don't want to get pregnant!
No!
I want to shoot it inside!
I want to be the first man to soil your uterus!
Eric!
Lotte!
So hot!
It's coming... Lots of your cum is going inside me!
The look on your face after your first time is really cute.
Don't look...
I want to make your body melt until morning.
With my cum.
If you do that, I'll never forgive you as long as I live.
But you need lots of practice.
It's been a week now since our first time.
To become a slave maid, Lotte has lived solely off my cum.
You sure tried hard, Lotte.
You've passed the first test.
You did well living off of nothing but cum for an entire week.
Good job, Lotte.
But for the next three weeks, your meals will
continue to be only your Master's cum.
If you manage to live that long, that is.
Consider this to be the start of the real test.
I was just starting to hunger for more anyway!
As long as you have that stubborn attitude, you'll be fine.
Now, receive your reward from your Master.
Suck it deep into your throat.
You should have received plenty of practice this week.
Yes.
Your throat belongs only to your Master's penis.
Your naughty throat lusts for it.
I'm cumming soon.
Thank you very much, Master.
Good girl, Lotte.
Time for your reward.
Thank you.
Drink my piss.
I want to mark your body with my scent.
You cannot drink without your Master's permission either.
Now you will drink your Master's urine.
Lotte, you're so cute when you're nasty.
I will inform the King that she has passed the first week's test.
You've really hung in there well.
I'm going to become a slave maid.
This is nothing.
However, Eric...
What?
Forcing me to drink your urine... That is unforgivable!
tooi kioku tadotte miru
Searching my distant memories,
soko ni wa itsumo kimi ga ita
I find that you are always in them.
tsuyogatte mo kizu tsukete mo
Even when I'm stubborn or when I hurt you,
kawaranai de ite kureta ne
You still stay there for me, unchanged.
kimi no manazashi ga
Your gentle gaze
yasashisa watashi ni oshieta
Taught me kindness.
nani mo osorenai
I fear nothing now.
eranda michi o mayowazu ni yuku dake
I will walk unwaveringly down the path I chose.
kitto doko made mo tsuite yuku yo
Surely I will go with you anywhere.
okori ni kakete mo a Akiramenai
Even if my pride gets in the way, I will not give in.