You've got amazing tits, Princess!
My fingers are being drawn in as I fondle them!
Stop squeezing so hard!
Hey! Is that any way to return a compliment?
It's your own damn fault for having such slutty tits!
Dorei Maid Princess
Translation: Voldemort | Editing: Solidus Snake     Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
I like it with your hair.
Hey, stop that.
I like it! Tangled around like that.
Feels like hundreds of little tongues are licking it.
Pervert!
How dare you put such a disgusting thing in my hair!
N-No!
Here I go!
Gross!
Hey, hey, Princess.
Don't get so caught up in getting your hair fucked.
Here we are doing our best to arouse every
other sensitive area of your body!
Impudent fools...
You think your pitiful tools excite me?
Hey, hey, what did you say about my "pitiful tool"?
See? See? See?
Don t! Stop it!
Don't!
Huh? I can't hear you.
Don't do what, Princess?
Please stop this.
Not surprising behavior from a Vilen Kofen princess.
Our dirty cocks can't satisfy her?
Are you unsatisfied because we have
yet to pleasure your other hole?
Not there!
Don't!
What? Still not enough?
How is it now?
How does it feel to be double penetrated by two
disgusting cocks from your rival country?
They're hitting each other inside...
I don't care anymore! I'm cumming!
Lotte...
How could this be happening to her?
This is a nightmare.
A horrible nightmare.
No, it's not a nightmare.
You are staring at reality.
Prince Eric, you failed to make Princess Lotte your slave maid.
Oh?
Keela, what are you doing?
You cannot concentrate in your condition.
Lotte.
Lotte is busy every single day.
She must tend to the men.
That is a fate you helped befall her.
I did not... cause this to happen.
Princess, a Vilen Kofen witch's pussy is heaven on earth!
You think such a complement would make me happy?
I'm cumming!
I'll fill you full of disgusting man cum!
I'm almost ready too!
You think I'll drink your filthy cum?
You beasts... I don't want your baby!
I'm cumming!
Lotte...
I... I'm cumming...
Lotte.
If she can't become a slave made, she will
continue to undergo harsh days like this.
Violated continuously by your men,
she will lose her sanity.
Will you dismiss what you see as an illusion?
Or will you face reality and try to change it?
It's your choice, Prince Eric.
Thank you, Keela.
I will not let Lotte lead such a pitiful existence!
For her sake...
I must redouble her training!
Looks like it's arrived.
From Carl.
The tools we must use in her training.
I must change myself.
Be a different man in front of Lotte.
Say, Princess,
how does it feel to live off of Eric's cum?
Why do you want to know?
I merely wish to hear your opinion.
Master's cum is hot and strong.
Dripping with juice, it slides around
in your mouth, making nasty noises.
You will slurp at his seed like it is your own life force.
I was just wondering what that felt like.
It's even better than I thought it would be.
Shall we trade places?
Stubborn as usual, I see.
But that sort of attitude is not befitting of a slave maid.
We will begin the second stage of your training today.
You look like a frog on its back, Princess.
Aren't you ashamed?
Very well.
Then we will train you with this tool today.
Wh-What is that?
What is it?
Why, it's something to shove into your pussy.
Can't you tell by the look of it?
B-But... It's so big.
It won't fit!
It definitely won't fit!
Then we'd better quit your training.
And then Master will belong to me.
Get away from him, you bitch!
Then you will continue your training?
But it's... so big.
It appears you don't understand, Lotte.
The only way you can live on is if you become a slave maid.
That's disgusting!
Tolerate it, Lotte.
Shall we trade places?
Don't be ridiculous.
She is my slave.
This is my pleasure.
I don't want anyone else to have it.
Wonderful, Prince Eric!
Lotte, let me have lots of fun with you.
Yes, please have fun with my body, Master.
Relax your body, Lotte.
Your body should be able to take something this size.
No! No! No!
Eric!
Please wait!
Call me Master, Lotte!
Master!
Oh my, oh my, how disgusting.
I don't think this clumsy pussy hole can satisfy Master.
It can. I'm perfectly fine.
Good girl, Lotte.
Get turned on by it and scream for me, Lotte.
It's really cute.
Become a dirty slut for me.
A whore only for my personal use.
Eric...
Good girl, Lotte.
That hurts!
She came from having her clit squeezed.
Princess Nasty.
Oh, how disgusting.
I didn't cum! I didn't cum!
You're right.
A slave mustn't cum so quickly.
She mustn't reach ecstasy so soon.
You will never become a slave maid with that attitude.
You will learn in time.
It's about time to take things up a notch, Lotte.
I will puncture your precious uterus.
Yes, Master.
Please shove that tool all the way inside of me.
Deeper!
It can go in deeper, Lotte!
Thrust it in deeper!
Amazing! So incredible!
My pussy is spreading open so wide!
That hurts!
I'll break inside!
No... Not there!
It's in so deep!
The deepest part of me!
It's my uterus!
You're hitting up against my uterus!
That's right, Lotte!
Remember it well!
Remember the sensation, of having your uterus hit!
I'll remember!
How could I possibly forget something like this!?
You sure did well, Lotte.
Master...
Starting tomorrow, I'm going to use a bigger tool each time.
This dildo will be inserted into you seven days from now.
A slave maid?
I didn't know you were into that sort of thing.
It's a special circumstance.
Well, how's your country Altoze doing?
Your western enemy-neighbor, Bekkurere,
is preparing to invade Big Natte.
Yimbit, right?
Could you stop using that name?
Thanks to your country's quick resolution,
my homeland is being treated like the enemy.
Sorry about that.
Did you summon me, Master?
So this is your slave maid.
A witch of Vilen Kofen.
Princess Lotte.
I'm thirsty.
Bring me some water.
Wh-Why must I?
Bring it.
Yes, as you wish.
I thought a slave maid only existed for sex.
But that doesn't appear to be the case.
Well, she is still a maid, after all.
She must be able to handle household tasks.
However, her cooking was... too salty.
Uh, nothing!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's coming out...
You mustn't drop it.
Squeeze tight.
Yes!
I can't!
Go... in...
No!
You came again?
Cum?
What's this?
Her household tasks have an extra challenge.
She must keep up her sexual training.
That is why I keep a dildo inside of her while she works.
But that's not all.
Not that.
Have mercy!
What's happening?
Is she okay?
Take a look.
What's that?
It's a special monster Keela brought over.
It's pulsating inside me!
Please don't touch my clitoris.
N-Not there!
The monster wiggles around in search of moisture.
Not there!
Not in that hole!
It's inside... going inside both holes.
Slipping around...
I-I'm cumming!
Please don't make me cum!
She came again?
Yes, but the real training begins here.
When the monster absorbs enough liquid,
it engorges itself automatically.
It's the perfect monster to enlarge a woman's pussy.
I see.
It appears your slave maid training is proceeding well.
The witches in Altoze can see far off.
But... It seems as though you keep looking down at your own feet.
There are many people who circle around by your feet.
It's only a matter of time before your own father is targeted.
I'd keep your guard up if I were you.
Lotte...
Lotte, let's show Keela your results for this week.
Oh my, oh my, she's doing well.
But if she's stretched that much, I doubt she can return to normal.
A wide, sloppy hole like that emit bring
Prince Eric much pleasure, can it?
That isn't...true!
It's not sloppy.
I can... tighten it!
Lotte, show me your tightening powers.
Push that dildo out.
Y-Yes.
It's throbbing!
My pussy is throbbing like it's alive!
It's soaking wet from her disgusting uterus.
I doubt we can use it again.
Do it.
Try again.
Yes.
No... Stop...
Did she cum?
Or perhaps she's giving birth?
Well? Does it feel good, Princess?
It's coming...
Very impressive.
It's almost as though she's giving birth.
It's coming out... Watch me, Master Eric!
Yes, I'm watching.
Show your Master how you give birth to the dildo.
I... I'll show you.
I'll birth it.
See?
It's born.
Good girl, Lotte.
You've improved a lot.
I can practically see all the way to your uterus.
Don't look.
Amazing.
It's shivering from the absence of the dildo.
It's so cute.
Please don't say that.
I'll give you a reward.
I'll let you cum.
From your uterus.
From your whole body.
Uterus... whole body?
This monster was supposed to be used for the next level.
But it's your reward for trying so hard.
What is this?
It's tickling me!
It's inside!
Swirling inside of me!
It's breaking me... Breaking my uterus!
It hurts....
It's your reward for giving birth to the monster.
It hurts!
It's too intense and too deep!
I'm cumming... Help... I'm cumming!
Look! Master, look!
See? It feels good!
Very good.
Show me how nasty you are!
I can't stop cumming!
It feels so good!
tooi kioku tadotte mini
Searching my disant memories,
soko ni wa itsumo kimi ga ita
I find that you are always in them.
tsuyogatte mo kizu tsukete mo
Even when I'm stubborn or when I hurt you,
kawaranai de ite kureta ne
You still stay there for me, unchanged.
kimi no manazashi ga
Your gentle gaze
yasashisa watashi ni oshieta
Taught me kindness.
nani mo osorenai
I fear nothing now.
eranda michi o mayowazu ni yuku dake
I will walk unwaveringly down the path I chose.
kitto doko made mo tsuite yuku yo
Surely I will go with you anywhere.
okori ni kakete mo a Akiramenai
Even if my pride gets in the way, I will not give in.