What is this?
These are piercings to show that you have passed your training.
So they're symbols of victory.
Yes.
The jewelry of a slave maid.
They're also known as "cursed piercings".
They were created from a special magical substance.
Cursed?
Those who wear these piercings will be sexually
aroused 24 hours a day, 365 days a year.
Sexually aroused 24 hours a day...
If you're frightened, we can stop here, Princess.
Hurry, put the piercings on me, Eric!
Lotte!
I can't live with you unless I show proof that I'm your slave, can I?
Then the answer is simple.
I doubt that those piercings are truly cursed anyway.
So I'll become one!
I'll become your around-the-clock slave!
I am honored and happy to have sex with you any time!
Dorei Maid Princess
Translation: Voldemort | Editing: Solidus Snake     Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
Now we begin.
Hurry on with it.
Does it hurt?
Not at all.
But it's hot,
and it makes my body throb.
The sensation will continue forever.
That heat is a mark of your slave maid status.
This is the mark of the slave maid.
Let's put on the other one.
Th-This is... amazing!
Amazing!
This will continue... forever?
It feels good, right?
Yes!
Now I'll put this one on.
Two on your genitals.
And one more.
No! Not...
Oh, it's amazing!
How amazing, Lotte.
I'm not even touching you and you're soaking wet.
Eric!
Right there? Right there?
Yes. Right here.
I'm so sensitive right now!
Please pierce it!
Pierce it with your cock!
No.
There's something else I must first pierce.
A piercing on my clitoris?
Then I'll surely cum.
I'll cum instantly!
This will complete your training.
I'm cum... cumming!
Withstand it, Lotte.
I'll push it back.
Even though it feels great... I'll push it back.
Lotte.
Please overcome this obstacle.
Because I too am about to pass through a harsh obstacle.
Everything is proceeding according to plan.
How are you feeling today, Uncle?
Eric... aren't you supposed to be in training?
Yes.
I had Yan here deliver that false report.
So you caught me, Eric?
Yes, I investigated you.
If you were killed, I knew that the throne would go to me.
Yes.
But as you can see, I'm still alive.
I was able to escape from your plot.
I see.
So you saw through me... I suppose.
I didn't want to believe it was so.
That you would try to take my life.
I... I tried to kill you...
For the sake of the kingdom... That's how I felt.
You are still naive.
You have no right to be on the throne.
However, even so, I pity you.
Because this kingdom will fall.
That's why... I...
There is a document that holds the names of your betrayers.
You should assassinate all of them.
And bring your kingdom back from destruction.
Please... Build a strong kingdom...
With Lotte at your side.
Uncle...
Eric, now is not the time to dwell on sadness.
There is still one thing you must do.
You must move the country forward.
That's right.
You are exactly right.
And thus, the time of destiny had arrived for Lotte and me.
That is a witch of Vilen Kofen?
What a glorious blessing!
And her personal trainer from a witch clan, Keela.
How was Princess Lotte's training?
Lord.
She has completed the training in just four weeks.
She now has only one task remaining.
Then we shall begin.
Yes, Lord.
Now, Lotte Vilen Kofen.
If you can defeat this Cyclops, then it will prove
you can protect your Master from anything.
Lotte!
Snap out of it!
What was all that training for?
You're becoming a slave maid, right?
Remember this.
I am Lotte of Vilen Kofen.
But I will bury that name along with this beast here.
I used to be Lotte Vilen Kofen.
But now I am Eric's Lotte!
Lotte.
That was an impressive battle.
And what's more, you endured the training
and became a slave maid as promised.
From this point forth, you have my blessing as my son's slave maid.
My son has not only enemies outside our
country, but within these castle walls.
And I am not young enough to protect him anymore.
In my place, please take care of my son.
And so, now the final ceremony between
slave and Master will take place.
Another ceremony?
It just never seems to end.
This is your necklace of loyalty.
This necklace insures that when the person who puts
it on dies, the person wearing it will also die.
Which means that we must die together.
That's right.
And this is a pill that will insure your pregnancy.
Well then.
D-Don't do that.
Goodness, Eric...
Now, I'm putting it on.
Seems like the pill has worked.
It's so hard.
What a lewd mouth.
From doing this, I can tell where you're erect.
Your nipples are firm.
And they're trembling.
Let me see, let me see!
I want to see my nipples.
You're right.
Your penis is so sad.
It wants to go inside of me.
Poor thing.
Let's put it in.
Okay. Here we go!
Just from putting it in, you came?
No, I didn't. I didn't.
You're so stubborn.
And you say you didn't cum now?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I lied, Master.
Every time it goes in deep, I cum.
If you keep it up, I'll go crazy.
Then go crazy!
It's making loud squishing noises.
It's so dirty.
We're so dirty!
This is mating.
Mating to make a child.
Mating is amazing!
I'm making a baby with the man I love!
I'll cum a lot inside of you.
And you'll be fertilized!
Yes, I'll be fertilized!
And I'll get pregnant!
I'll hug your sperm with my egg!
It's done.
The sacred semen of your penis is flowing into me.
Master has claimed me as his own.
Oh, please don't stop cumming.
How selfish of you.
You're just a slave.
See?
There's still more to come.
It's so chilling!
My boobs... my nipples feel so good!
Master, you're so wonderful.
It's so beautiful.
Your beautiful penis.
No matter how much flows out,
it continues to grant me with more semen.
I know I got pregnant.
I became a mother.
You sure are eager, Lotte.
Lotte, I feel it trembling.
The entrance to your uterus.
Can you?
Oh no, really?
Don't push on it too hard.
I think it can go in.
Inside your uterus.
I won't stop.
Oh, stop!
If you do that, you'll mess me up.
Your penis will destroy me!
Oh no! My uterus is being fucked!
It's inside!
Master's dick is all the way inside my uterus!
Here I cum, Lotte.
Inside your uterus.
I'll fill it full of cum!
If you do that, what will happen to me?
Lotte, your entire body has became my vagina.
I really... did become... Masters vagina...
I thought that our days would be happy from then on.
However, the king ordered me to depart south
on a diplomatic mission right away.
And then, we fought war in an unfamiliar land.
Our days of struggle continued.
Then, six months later...
Eric, and Lotte.
Congratulations on a job well done on the war to the south.
We should be rid of them at last.
And Lotte,
I hear that you saved my son from death
countless times during this war.
I thank you.
I do not deserve those words, Your Majesty.
I merely acted as a slave should to protect my Master.
But with your body in that condition, I cannot
call your work anything short of incredible.
I have never heard of a slave maid as devoted and skilled as you.
You truly are a blessing, Lotte.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
We will have a banquet tonight to celebrate your victory.
Please prepare to attend immediately, my son.
I would be honored!
Before the banquet has even ended,
You drag me out here and ask me to do this...
Isn't it exciting?
And besides, I don't see you protesting at all.
Well, I want you.
It's already this hard.
Can I bite it?
Your dick gives me so much delicious juice when I chew on it.
And these...
You have a lot stored up in there.
Master's seed is trapped in his testicles.
L-Lotte!
It's cumming.
Already?
Silly dick.
How rude!
It tastes great tonight.
Lotte, sit here.
With your back facing me.
Okay...
Already in my uterus?
How intense!
I feel it all the way in my uterus!
I love being touched there.
Amazing!
You're so amazing, Master!
Your dick is fucking my uterus.
And we're doing it outdoors.
Just like animals.
And what's more, you're about to become a mother.
See? Inside your beloved uterus, there's my cock.
No, not there!
There's a baby in there!
Milk... I'm lactating!
I came from my nipple!
There's more.
I'll make you cum more.
Not yet.
I just came.
Give me a break.
If you're so rough with me right now, I'll...
I'll cum!
I smile... I smile for you, Master.
I suppose I was too rough with you.
But...
But?
But it's your baby, Lotte.
I'm sure it's strong and healthy.
Eric...
I love you, my Master.
Well be together forever.
tooi kioku tadotte miru
Searching my distant memories,
soko ni wa itsumo kimi ga ita
I find that you are always in them.
tsuyogatte mo kizu tsukete mo
Even when I'm stubborn or when I hurt you,
kawaranai de ite kureta ne
You still stay there for me, unchanged.
kimi no manazashi ga
Your gentle gaze
yasashisa watashi ni oshieta
Taught me kindness.
nani mo osorenai
I fear nothing now.
eranda michi o mayowazu ni yuku dake
I will walk unwaveringly down the path I chose.
kitto doko made mo tsuite yuku yo
Surely I will go with you anywhere.
okori ni kakete mo a Akiramenai
Even if my pride gets in the way, I will not give in.