How have you been?
Oh I see!
What in the world...
Is happening?
The Opportunism-Glasses,
Or in short, the Oppogla!
They're glasses that let you see what you want to see!
Stuff I want to see... that can't be...
How is it?
What does Hiroto see?
"What", you ask...
I see Charlotte naked...
This morning, she came here out of nowhere.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
The Slave Rabbit and Anthony
I Will Grant All Your Perverted Wishes
Well, we have a transfer student
to introduce to everyone!
Woah!
Amazing!
She's cute!
I'm Charlotte Hatsune, nice to meet you!
My goddess!
So cute!
Her hair is so long!
So, you'll be sitting beside Maejima-kun.
Okay!
She's going to sit beside me...
Huh? A rabbit?
Nice to meet you, Hiroto!
There was a rabbit just now? And how does she know...
How I know your name?
Eh?
You see, Charlotte can read people's minds!
We left off at page thirty eight last time.
Let's read off from there and translate it.
So in short, all Hiroto only thinks
of perverted things all day!
After that, we'll go over the grammar
we learned last week and...
Don't joke around!
Maejima-kun! Class as already started so please be quiet!
Ah, I'm sorry...
Geez, I got yelled at because of you.
Stop talking to me already.
But why?
Besides, you're lying when you say you can read minds.
I hate perverted things.
Oh... I see...
Then Charlotte will teach Hiroto about your true feelings!
Anthony, could you take out the Oppagla?
Alright!
And now we're like this but...
Wow, huge!
Hey Hiroto... I shall I give you fellatio?
Charlotte... no, stop!
You can't...
It's fine, no one can see Charlotte right now.
Huh?
It's rock hard, you little perv.
Not that... there...
You feel good?
Maejima-kun?
What's with those glasses?
S-Sh-Shiraishi-san! Th-This is... um... it's...
Are you okay?
Um, yeah, this is a... mistake...
Um, have you seen Hatsune-san?
Eh?
I wonder where she went...
I thought I'd show her around since I am the class rep...
No way... she really can't see?
Maejima-kun?
Um, Shiraishi-san, can you turn around for a bit?
Eh? Like this?
Then put your hands on the table...
What are you trying to do?
What am I saying!?
Maejima-kun?
It feels too good!
This is bad... Shiraishi-san's pussy is... right in front of me...
Charlotte... That's right, just a little more...
At least tell me what's wrong? Is
there something on my skirt?
Can you stay like that for a bit?
Geez, Maejima-kun!
Cumming!
To think that I'd be able to cum while looking at
Shiraishi-san's bare pussy right in front of me...
Maejima-kun, are you okay!?
You look a little strange...
Woah, she's sucking on... my...
It gets a little embarrassing if you
look at my skirt so much...
Hey, are you listening?
She's drinking it...
Shiraishi-san, you don't have to
worry about someone like me..
No way! I am the class rep!
Shiraishi-san's boobs are wobbling right in front of me...
I'm really okay...
Okay, but please listen to what I say.
Maejima-kun's should try and talk with everyone in class.
I think it's a bad idea to always be so reserved.
Shiraishi-san, it's a bad idea to show them like that...
Ah, Charlotte, more on the tip...
If you don’t become friendly with everyone,
you'll just drift further and further away...
Stir your tongue around, take it
in your mouth and suck hard!
Hey, are you listening?
Yeah...
I am...
More... faster... rougher movement!
Geez...
I want to cum one more time from Shiraishi-san!
What's up, Prez?
Sensei was looking for you!
Really?
Himeno and Kashiagi...
I'll go right away, so could you wait for a moment?
Woah, as expected Himeno shaves!
Kashiagi's boobs are huge...
This is bad!
You know you can just leave him alone for now...
Cumming! Just one more time
from looking at Shiraishi-san!
Cumming!
Maejima-kun?
Charlotte, don't spill it... deeper... down your throat..
Look up here.
Huh?
Eh?
So she really can read minds!?
I'll see you later then, Maejima-kun.
Uh, yeah.
Phew.
See? Like I said, Hiroto is a super pervert, right?
Hey Hiroto...
Starting now Charlotte is going to...
Give you the perfect,
most pleasuring...
sex designed for you!
Dorei Usagi to Anthony
Who... Who are you?
No Trespassing
Besides, what do you mean by the perfect,
most pleasuring sex designed for me?
What kind of sex... is that?
Who knows?
"Who knows"!?
Hiroto is the only one that would know.
Don't joke around with me!
I've said it before, right? I can read minds.
I get it, now.
Hey wait...
Like this?
Just now, Hiroto said that he wanted
to see this inside his mind...
That's, that not...
Want me to spread it more so you can watch closely?
Sure, is this good enough?
Close your... eyes...
Don't look over here.
It's wet...
My fingers are... inside Charlotte...
So this is a clitoris...
Her reaction is amazing...
Woah... Charlottes pussy is tasty...
I'm doing such crazy things at school...
No... I'll cum, I'll cum!
Cumming!
She's peeing?
It's not pee...
Eh?
You want to put it in?
Huh? No... but... um...
It's my first time... and I don't have a rubber...
It's a little too much to be doing it raw...
What did you make me take...
Who knows?
And what is this!?
No way! I haven't done anything and I'm
rock hard... no, I'm almost cumming!
No... I'm gonna cum!
No way, cumming! Cumming!
That can't be... inside is really bad...
Creampie... it's slippery and feels way too good...
What you Just took now is "that" pill which
will make you think of nothing but sex...
and get erections and ejaculations uncontrollably.
in abbreviation, called the Ejac-nonstop.
You, you are... who are you?
And is it really okay? With someone like me...
Hiroto is who I want...
C'mon, you want me to move like this, right?
I know everything, you know? See, see?
Rubbed the tip only with the tight area at the entrance...
No... no more...
This is too good... cumming!
So much sperm again... so much...
Is this what you want?
It's cumming again...
More... I want to cum more inside of Charlotte!
So much is coming out!
From behind this time!
Thrust me lots, Hiroto!
I really can't stop cumming!
More is coming out! This is bad... It feels too good!
More, more...
it's so wet and slippery I'm losing my mind!
I could cum forever!
Hiroto...
You know that Charlotte has always been...
Saving her first time for you...
Charlotte... Who are you?
Huh? What?
You hear perverted sounds?
From above?
I think It's right up there.
Really?
There doing it here?
Wow... you're still coming.
Do you feel good?
Hmm? Okay,
so you want to see the sperm flow out from my pussy?
Pull out slowly...
From now on, Charlotte will make all
your perverted dreams come true.
W-What are you doing?
Maejima-kun?
Shi-Shiraishi-san!
Ehhh!?
This is, um, it's...
Cumming again!
Dorei Usagi to Anthony
Shiraishi Miho.
She's the class rep, with perfect
grades and is good at all sports.
Always in the top three when ranking
the popularity of the girls in school.
With a high guard to guys, and a serious personality.
Prez!
The perfect idol and dreams for any guys.
Prez.
Geez, Prez!
Huh? What?
Are you okay?
Oh!
Maejima-kun.
This morning, Shiraishi-san was something like that.
I took Shiraishi-san to the nurse's
office so she could get some rest.
What about the stuff on her clothes?
Yeah, I washed them.
I think we angered Shiraishi-san.
it's fine It was like a miracle that Shiraishi-san bothered
to deal with someone like me in the first place.
Besides, I have Charlotte now.
Well, thanks to Charlotte, I'm not alone anymore.
Yeah...
Please go visit Shiraishi-san later, it'd
be bad to just leave her like that.
Oh... Yeah, guess you're right.
Nurse's Office
W-What is this?
I woke up from my body being so hot...
Back then... Maejima-kun and Hatsune-san...
They were having sex, right?
Huh? No way, I'm wet...
Why... I’m getting... really hot...
I'm feeling strange...
No one's here... right?
Even though I've never... masturbated before...
This... the edge of the bed... just might feel good...
It's throbbing...
So good...
No... what am I doing?
It's like... I'm a pervert!
But it feels good... My hips won't stop!
No... something's coming! Coming!
It's coming!
This is bad... the sheets and my panties are all wet...
But... just a bit more...
I'm taking off my panties at the nurse's office
at school, and spreading my legs like this...
I'm such a pervert!
Pervert... pervert...
Does sex... feel like this?
A penis going... in and out...
Maejima-kun's would go like this...
Ah, so good! Cumming!
Cumming!
I can't stop, it feels good... It feels good!
I can't stop, more, more!
Shiraishi-san? Are you awake?
Um, this is... isn't...
I'm so sorry!
Wait!
Shiraishi-san?
I want to have sex!
Huh?
I... I'm really strange... I can't help but want sex!
You'd probably think I'm crazy or something...
But... can't I... want sex?
Of course... you can...
So this is... Maejima-kun's?
Wow, it's getting hot!
Shiraishi-san, I'm... gonna...
I can't hold back anymore!
Shiraishi-san, don't!
I'm sorry! I...
It's fine. I was surprised earlier,
But the smell of Maejima-kun's semen
is exciting my womb! So...
Are penises... this hard?
Shiraishi-san...
Amazing... Maejima-kun's penis is inside...
Hey wait...
Shiraishi-san, don't! If you press with your
hips and move like that so suddenly, I'll...
Inside... so tight! It's squeezing...
I'll cum again, I'm gonna cum inside! This is bad!
My hips won't stop... my insides are twitching... I...
I'm really gonna cum!
It's fine, inside, you can cum inside!
Sex! I'm... having sex with Maejima-kun!
Maejima-kun... please... more! Do me more!
Mad as the March Hare.
In other words, a powerful aphrodisiac.
After smelling this, Shiraishi-san should
be wanting sex uncontrollably.
Charlotte, is it really okay to send
Hiroto over to Shiraishi-san?
What's wrong with that?
But then, your feelings...
Of course it's fine. I'm here to
grant Hiroto's wishes, after all.
Shiraishi-san... it feels really good!
I feel really good, too! Maejima-kun's penis
is so hard and hot, it's amazing!
I'm... cumming again! I can't stop cumming!
It's coming out... it's splashing into me!
More, thrust more! Mess me up!
Maejima-kun's penis is going in and out of me!
I can see it all!
It's coming!
Amazing! I'm getting filled up by Maejima-kun's semen!
More... fill up my womb more!
Shiraishi-san...Shiraishi-san!
Shiraishi-san!
Maejima-kun, cum!
Let out more and more inside me!
Maejima-kun... more, give me more of semen!
Let out lots of the origin of a baby!
Deeper inside... let out more!
Lots... and lots!
Shiraishi-san...
Maejima-kun... it's still flowing...
Thanks to Charlotte, I'm not alone anymore.
But I got disliked by Shiraishi-san...
Charlotte?
Didn't I say?
I can hear all the thoughts in Hiroto's mind!