Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Episode 2
After the Rain in Early Summer
Rain, rain, rain.
Maybe I should skip school.
Tomomi?
I wonder what's wrong with her.
She seems to be feeling low these days.
Oh, my, it's you, Yui.
How long have you been there?
What's this "Oh, my, it's you, Yui"?
I knocked on your door several times, and you didn't answer,
so I came in to wake you up.
What are you doing?
Just wondering why you woke up on your own.
Maybe that's why it's raining.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's going to rain all day.
Yui doesn't seem to have a care in the world.
Did you say something?
Oh, you don't want breakfast.
I should clean the table.
Oh, dear.
Could you be quieter on the stairs?
O-Ouch...
Onii-chan, are you all right?
Strawberry pattern...
Idiot.
Please explain that part, will you, Mizuno-san?
Mizuno-san?
Yes!
Why is a smart student like
Mizuno at a loss for words?
I wonder what's wrong with her.
Maybe something happened.
If you're worried, why don't you go talk to her?
She's your childhood friend, isn't she?
Why are you so mad?
I'm not... mad.
Tomomi-san is our neighbor.
I'm also worried about her.
She's feeling low these days.
Then why don't you talk to her?
It might be easier for her to talk to another girl.
She doesn't seem to like me that much.
Anyway, you'd better talk to her.
Hey, Yui!
Why does Tomomi hate you?
Tomomi isn't like that.
What an insensitive man Makoto is.
You wouldn't know a girl's secret.
Yui-san and Tomomi-san happen to live close to you,
and they're misinterpreting the situation.
I, Saionji Aritomo, will save you from that misunderstanding.
Huh?
What is Aritomo doing?
From this angle, he looks like an idiot.
You got turned down, didn't you?
You loser.
The two most insensitive men of Yasohachi Academy are here.
Before their stupidity infects me, I should leave.
You get treated like that because you're always chasing girls.
Why don't you try sports instead? Sports!
Devote yourself to club
activity... and sweat.
The sweat of adolescence!
That will be a beautiful memory of your school life.
Makoto, what are you doing?
Oh, it's you, Akira.
I was thinking of going home, but then it started raining.
Tell me...
Does your body melt in the rain?
Oh, I see.
Yui probably has a folding umbrella in her locker!
Yui... Narusawa... Yui.
This is it.
Narusawa Yui
Even if it's locked...
If I use this to fiddle with it...
It's open. It's open!
Akira.
What are you doing?
Acting like a thief.
Shame on you.
What do you mean,
"What are you doing?"
I was just borrowing Yui's umbrella to take home.
A man shouldn't open a girl's locker without permission!
Not to mention that it's Narusawa Yui's locker.
What wrong, Akira? You're blushing.
I'm embarrassed!
He broke her locker.
Yui will be mad about this.
I knew it. She did have an umbrella.
Oh my, that's cute.
Really cute.
Sign: Yasohachigaoka
Makoto-kun.
You'll catch a cold.
You're always nice.
Is that Yui-chan's umbrella?
Yeah.
Should we walk home together?
You used to tease me
and make me cry.
What? I did?
Lots of times, really!
No way! I don't remember anything like that!
Oh, you're mean.
Not true! You just said,
"You're always nice."
That just popped out.
You were a bully.
Oh, no!
I'm a feminist!
If you're in any sort of trouble, you can talk to me.
I'm so embarrassed that I can't tell you.
Don't be nice to me.
The rain didn't stop even after midnight.
The awkwardness between Yui and me remained,
so I had to eat dinner alone...
and I had nothing to do.
You look troubled, young man. Drink this.
It's alcohol!
It's whiskey.
Irish whiskey.
Alcohol is alcohol.
Alcohol is the best of all medicines.
It cures everything.
A troubled young man should drink.
So I'm telling you, every man must find his own way.
Misako-san, you're quite drunk.
I'm not drunk at all.
So I'm telling you, every man should live as he pleases.
On his own...
Ignoring women's feelings.
Gee. You were drinking all night with Mom.
You've got some nerve.
Oh, don't shout at me.
I have a hangover and maybe a cold too. My head aches.
That's what you get for...
sleeping on the floor in the living room.
Justice has been served.
My head aches.
I don't feel good.
Hey, look.
I'm going to throw up.
Look there.
Stop complaining and look at that!
Tomomi. And she's with Yoshiki.
I'm delighted that you asked me for a date.
Then ten thirty on Sunday,
in front of Studio Ataru.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bye bee.
Skip, skip, oh, I can skip.
A date?
She's going on a date?
And it's with Yoshiki.
I can't believe this!
Bye bee.
What's with that?
Still, amazing things can happen between boys and girls.
That's what Mom told me.
Of all men, it's Yoshiki!
How could that happen?!
Why are you so angry?
Oh, we're late!
No...
No!
Stop it.
No.
Please stop it.
No!
No...
Yoshiki!
No. No!
Stop it, Yoshiki.
Stop it, Yoshiki!
Stop it!
How can you be half asleep?
I-I didn't hit him that h-hard, guys, right, right?
I just poked him.
It was a dream. I'm glad it was a dream.
Tomomi-chan, you're naughty.
Naughty...
This is a good opportunity.
Sensei. I, Nagaoka Yoshiki, have cleared the hurdle!
Onii-chan, what's wrong with you?
Are you angry because
I didn't make lunch?
About this morning and that dream...
That dream?
I have a bad feeling.
A dream? A bad feeling?
I see!
Photography Club
Photography
Club
I found it.
I knew it. That was a prophetic dream.
My hunch was right.
Damn Yoshiki.
This is why Tomomi's so depressed.
Damn it.
This angle...
He...
He took this photo from my room.
That's right.
How can you throw them
around like that?
I visited your room when you happened to be away.
Now, now, don't look at me with such a fierce expression.
I wasn't expecting to shoot photos like that from your room.
How did you get in?
Well, that's...
I stopped by to deliver a photo of Yui-san and her youthful mother
at the spring Sports Festival.
Did Misako-san really let you in?
Yes.
She gave me delicious milk tea.
She said, "Please make yourself at home in Makoto's room until he comes back."
And by chance, I happened to look out the window.
Wow!
I didn't know that Tomomi-san was your neighbor.
I was very lucky.
V-Violence is bad.
If you like the photo, I'll give it to you.
This is a rare picture...
I'll bring you to justice!
The tickets for my date.
Give me all the negatives and any other pictures you have of Tomomi!
Onii-chan...
Hey, are you feeling all right?
We see each other every day.
It might be inappropriate.
Good morning.
Um... Yoshiki isn't coming.
He told me to give these to you.
He said he wouldn't follow you anymore.
So you knew.
N-No...
I thought it couldn't be true, but...
Huh?
That angle was from
your room, wasn't it?
Your...
Yui-chan...
Onii-chan wouldn't do something like that.
Yoshiki got into Onii-chan's room while he was away.
And Mom...
Is that so? I knew it.
Huh?
So Makoto-kun tells you everything.
That's not true.
I just overheard it.
I was being nosy.
I knew it.
I'm quite familiar with Makoto-kun.
Tomomi!
I knew it.
Makoto-kun, you are nice.
We're childhood friends, aren't we?
Right, but...
I don't want to be just childhood friends.
I want you to see me as a woman.
It's beautiful.
I didn't know that our town was this beautiful.
You're beautiful too, Tomomi.
Thank you.
I want to see your beautiful figure.
Is that all right?
Would you turn off the lights, please?
Mine are small, and I get embarrassed.
No. Come on.
You're so beautiful.
And you're not small.
Now take your hand away.
No. I can't do it.
Are you going to hide it forever?
You're mean.
Who said that I'm a bully?
Come on.
Will you promise not to laugh?
Yeah, I won't laugh.
A man is as good as his word.
I'm embarrassed that
you're looking at me.
I want to kill myself.
You're as cute as a baby.
It suits you.
Really? You don't dislike me?
Why would I?
Because... I...
It's soft here.
D-Don't!
Are you that sensitive?
This is wonderful.
You're responding so strongly
because you're always playing with it.
Don't say that.
It's embarrassing.
But this feels great.
No! Not that rough.
I'll break.
No.
No...
Tomomi...
Please. Makoto-kun, hurry and come in.
Makoto, please!
Hurry. Hurry!
Tomomi.
Are you all right?
I'm happy.
I always dreamed of doing this with you.
I feel honored.
But it was a bit different than I expected.
In my dream, you were rougher and more insistent.
You wouldn't stop, even if I begged you to.
Do you want me to be like that?
Tomomi, I'm going to be rough!
Yes!
L-Like that!
You're beautiful, Tomomi.
Makoto-kun!
Please be quiet.
Summer vacation is starting tomorrow,
but you mustn't be impatient.
There are lots of temptations in the summer.
Well, I hope you make good summer memories.
Sign: Yasohachi Academy
Yay!
What are you doing?
Ah, beige!
You brat!
Brat?
You act like a brat!
And you are a brat.
Watch where you're walking.
What the heck is wrong with that woman?
What are you doing, Onii-chan? I'm leaving you behind.
All right! Starting now,
it's summer vacation!
To be continued...
totsuzen no ame ni furarete
Showered by a sudden rain
kasa mo sasazu ni aruita ra
Walking without putting up my umbrella
machi yuku hito ga henna kao shite mite ta
People in the street looked at me strangely
mada haru asai san gatsu no gogo
On an early spring afternoon,
tsumetai ame no sora miage
I looked up at the sky in the cold rain
odoritaku naru youna kibun de aruita
I walked with an urge to dance
arifureta nichijyou ni itsuka kokoro ga kumotte ta
My heart was clouded by the familiar days
sonna koto sae kizukazu ni ita
I didn't understand anything
keredo
But...
honno sasayakana nandemo nai youna yuuki dakeredo
It was a small piece of courage, almost like nothing
sonna koto de naze ka sukoshi kokoro ga hareta
I don't know why, but it brightened my heart a bit
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking