Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
It's cold. It looks like it might snow.
Hey, Onii-chan.
Huh?
What do you want for Christmas this year?
Nothing. I'm too old for that.
I don't feel that way.
That's why you're such a child.
Yui, you're taking the long way round.
Oh? Yeah.
I have something in mind.
There's something I want you to see.
I didn't know there was a church here.
It's cute, isn't it?
I've decided this is where I'll hear my wedding bells ring.
What's that?
I knew you wouldn't understand.
You're not romantic at all.
Her wedding bells will ring here?
So this is where she wants to get married?
Onii-chan, let's go.
Yeah.
Huh? It's snowing.
I thought it was cold.
Episode 5
White Christmas . . .
Invitation: Saionji's Annual Grand Xmas Party
All night, Christmas Eve
I'm certainly going to invite a lot of people to my party.
But the only person I really want to invite is...
you, Narusawa Yui-san!
However, that night...
Your beautiful mother can come too, of course.
Thank you.
It must be him.
Damn Kondou Makoto.
I've heard that...
Kondou Makoto is going...
on a date with his girlfriend on Christmas Eve.
Oh, that's too bad!
I also invited him to my party.
I'm planning some entertainment, so please...
If it's all right, I can also have a limousine pick you up and take you back home.
No.
You don't have to go that far.
I'll be waiting for you.
Then...
See you there.
What were you talking about with Aritomo?
Onii-chan.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Did Aritomo say something mean?
Depending on the circumstances, I'll beat the crap out of him.
No, it's nothing.
By the way, can we go home together?
No, I can't.
You should go home first.
Sorry to interrupt you!
Kondou Makoto-senpai, please take this.
What is it?
A love letter.
I'm Tsuzuki Kozue.
I love you. Will you be my boyfriend?
Huh?
As the saying goes,
"Hide a tree in a forest."
Found it.
Omiya puts it back every day.
Shimizu has had the same magazine for three days.
And Takegi borrowed five.
I'm earning money by renting them out, so I don't give a damn.
This shelf isn't the right one.
Oh, I knew it was you, Kondou-senpai.
You're Tsuzuki Kozue, right?
Yes.
So you're a library assistant.
Books in this section are difficult, but you come here often.
You must work hard.
Well, I was looking for materials for my report.
It's hard to find satisfying materials.
May I help you?
No! I'll look for them on my own!
No, I'll help you. It's my job.
No thanks!
Ssh!
I'm sorry. I'll be quiet.
What kind of material are you looking for?
Oh, were you looking for this?
No, well...
No, I don't read that kind of magazine.
This is disgusting.
Well...
So these magazines were here.
I'd like to do things like that.
Senpai.
Yes.
Mission accomplished.
As compensation, I want you to take me on a date on Christmas Eve.
S-Sure.
Make sure to meet me in front of Studio Ataru at four.
Pinky swear. Cross my heart and hope to die, stick a needle in my eye.
It's a deal! Hurray!
Truth arises from lies.
Makoto-chan really does have a date on Christmas Eve.
That's unpleasant, but nonetheless, fortune is favoring me.
This way, Yui-san will be mine.
When is my turn?
This is a great party.
Look, Yui, a tiger is doing a trick over there.
That pool has been converted into a skating rink.
There's cuisine from all over the world.
What's wrong, Yui? You don't look like you're enjoying yourself.
Huh? That's not true!
My, my. I hope you are having a good time.
Yes. Thank you for inviting us.
For the adults, drinks from all over the world are being served in the lounge.
Oh, that's nice. You know how to please your guests.
Sign: Sake
Let me show you around.
Oh, Gramps, you look nice.
Oh, my, my. Thank you very much.
Yui-san, are you enjoying the party?
Yes, thank you.
Don't be so distant.
This is between you and me, is it not?
Should we go dancing in the hall?
Who are you?
How about a commemorative photo?
Wh-Why couldn't you choose a better costume?
Well, then... What about this?
Or this?
How about this, Aritomo-kun?
Look, I can change into many costumes.
Th-This isn't good for my heart.
Hey, Aritomo-kun, don't you think it's cool?
I feel dizzy.
Yui-san, let's go somewhere quiet.
So Yui-san is here too.
That's gross.
To think... I was holding a guy's hand.
First of all, I don't think I invited you guys!
Yui-san?
I'm glad I'm here.
Where is Yui-san? I don't see her.
Yui-san...
I wonder if Onii-chan is here.
So he really is on a date.
Sign: A Journey of Love and Dreams
I got dressed up, so I'd like to have dinner at a restaurant.
I'm not sure that's possible.
Today is Christmas Eve. Every place will be fully reserved.
I thought of that. I already made a reservation somewhere.
Medicinal Cooking Restaurant
Jashuumon
Welcome, welcome.
So this is the restaurant?
I'm Suzuki, and I reserved a table.
I'd like you to serve the dish that makes girls horny.
Bring a lot of it.
Of course. We've prepared it as usual.
Please take a seat.
I'm Tsuzuki. I reserved a table.
Sure. Please come in.
We haven't ordered yet.
I suppose this is the way they operate.
Maybe this is a Christmas special then.
This tastes good.
I've never had this dish.
Me either.
So you've never been here before.
Right.
This restaurant was in Dad's address book.
My dad works at a trading firm.
He uses a lot of restaurants for wining and dining clients.
It was easy to get a reservation using his name.
If he works for a trading firm, he must go on a lot of business trips.
Yes.
How about your mom?
They got divorced when I was eight.
I'm sorry.
Not at all. I'm fine.
I'm used to living alone.
You're strong.
Yes.
What are you doing, you old baldie?
Stop messing around!
Hey, this isn't what I expected!
Huh?
I was ordered to serve this to Tsuzuki-san, the one who made a reservation.
I'm not Tsuzuki, I'm Suzuki.
Yes, I was told to bring the dishes to Tsuzuki-san.
That's what I've been telling you.
Listen! I'm not Tsuzuki. I'm Su-zu-ki!
Listen!
Shut up!
I also reserved a hotel room!
I'm full.
Bring that young gal back to me.
Should we leave?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Sign: Reception
I need to take a shower and clear my head.
Well, you're lucky.
We're usually full on Christmas Eve, but we just had a cancellation.
Are you all right, Kozue-chan?
No. It's painful, Senpai.
It's painful.
Please...
Are you all right?
No...
Onii-chan?
This is Kondou. I'm not home right now.
Please leave a message after the beep.
So he's not home yet.
So Kondou-kun isn't home.
I wonder what he's doing.
It's starting to snow.
Let's go inside and have
something warm to drink.
Thank you.
This is a big scoop.
A good chance for a photo!
Saionji-kun, you're nice.
Yes.
Yui, you are the one who must choose your path.
What are you doing?
A hotel? What was I doing?
What's going on, Senpai?
Well, um...
I don't like this!
Wait!
K-Kozue-chan.
You lecher!
Wh—
What on earth happened?
Kondou
Narusawa
It must've been that medicinal cooking.
Note: We're at Saionji's big party.
Your dinner is in the fridge. Misako & Yui.
I knew it.
I didn't see Yui's bicycle.
But did she really go to Aritomo's party on a bicycle?
Yui.
K-Kozue-chan.
I'm sorry about that.
I should be the one to apologize.
No, I think the food was to blame.
Yes. I think so too.
But to be honest, I was glad.
Huh?
You embraced me.
Kozue-chan.
I was happy.
Someone held me tight,
and it was someone I love.
I was really happy.
But I was also scared.
When I was a child, I used to play hide-and-seek.
Once when I was "it," the other kids' moms came and got them.
One by one, they left.
When I started looking for them, they had all gone.
I still dream about it,
and I wake up in the middle of the night.
Ready or not, here I come.
No matter how many times I call out, there's no answer.
Senpai.
What's this? It seems to be different from mine.
Stop it, you lecher.
What about this?
All right.
What's wrong, Senpai?
I'll use my hand.
Huh?
Is it here? Here?
Senpai, no!
That's...
You're already...
No, I hate you, Senpai.
Now you hate me.
Don't stop.
More.
All right. I'm coming in.
This is great.
Here.
Senpai, thank you.
Will you be all right if I don't see you home?
Yes. I have to go to the airport and meet Dad's plane.
Traffic will be heavy now,
so I need time to get there.
Oh, Senpai.
I think...
I won't dream about that anymore.
Okay.
Good night.
Those two are late, though.
So he's not yet home.
Hello.
Hello!
Is that you, Makoto? Makoto?!
Oh, it's you, Akira.
What's this "Oh, it's you"?
Anyway, I'm glad you're home.
I-Is Yui home yet?!
Huh? No.
What?!
I lost sight of Yui two hours ago!
What? In this snow?
Don't you have any idea where she went?!
Someone kept hitting on her, so she went to the bathroom.
She left this mansion,
and that was three hours ago.
Information should be accurate.
You bastard! If you knew, why didn't you stop her?!
Why didn't you tell us this sooner?!
Hello? Hello?!
Sometimes girls need to be alone.
Yui...
Where are you?
A place where she can be alone?
Card: Merry Xmas Onii-chan
She must be there!
All right!
Merry Christmas.
Excuse me.
Cool!
Really?
Oh, it's Senpai. He's cool.
Yui.
Onii-chan!
Well, I thought this was good weather for skiing!
And by coincidence...
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Jingle bells.
Here.
Huh?
I'll carry you home.
Heave, ho.
Note: From "Touryanse," a traditional Japanese crosswalk song.
"Going is fun, but returning is scary."
What's that?
It's a children's song called "Touryanse."
I know that.
"Going is fun, but returning is scary."
"Even in my fear, let me pass."
"Let me pass..."
Ouch!
You're as stupid as ever.
Oh, it's you, Izumi.
What? Are you going to your morning practice?
Having to practice during the winter holidays must be awful.
I'm not like you.
We're going to have a big athletics meet.
All right, I'll go cheer for you.
Where is this meet?
Myououin in Toujimura.
Well, I'll be expecting you, or not.
See you.
Yeah, do your best.
Toujimura?
That's rather far.
Kondou Makoto.
To be continued...
totsuzen no ame ni furarete
Showered by a sudden rain
kasa mo sasazu ni aruita ra
Walking without putting up my umbrella
machi yuku hito ga henna kao shite mite ta
People in the street looked at me strangely
mada haru asai san gatsu no gogo
On an early spring afternoon,
tsumetai ame no sora miage
I looked up at the sky in the cold rain
odoritaku naru youna kibun de aruita
I walked with an urge to dance
arifureta nichijyou ni itsuka kokoro ga kumotte ta
My heart was clouded by the familiar days
sonna koto sae kizukazu ni ita
I didn't understand anything
keredo
But...
honno sasayakana nandemo nai youna yuuki dakeredo
It was a small piece of courage, almost like nothing
sonna koto de naze ka sukoshi kokoro ga hareta
I don't know why, but it brightened my heart a bit
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking