Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Episode 11
Dream and . . .
Gee, what was Yui thinking?
Why didn't she tell me that she'd transferred to Yasohachi Academy?
Of all possible schools, she ends up at one with a bunch of animals.
Nyuubai
Oh, Akira, it's you.
You scared the crap out of me!
You're exaggerating.
I just tapped your shoulder.
Akira, why are you carrying all that stuff?
Oh, I'm going camping.
During this holiday, I intend to get away from the bustle of this inhuman city.
I'll spend time surrounded by Mother Nature.
I'll see the blue sky, drifting white clouds,
and sunlight filtering through trees.
I'll hear birds tweeting...
and the sibilant sound of a running stream.
Can you hear them too?
Oh, I can.
All right. Let's go!
Nyuubai
Enjoy camping.
Don't push!
Nyuubai
Why was Onii-chan so mad?
I'm not a child anymore.
I can choose whichever school....
Let go of me.
What?
What are you doing?
Hurry and get in.
Onii-chan.
Sign: An overnight trip to Touji hot spring
Touji hot spring?
Would you please explain, Akira?
Explain?
My dad's the manager of the town club for the aged,
so I asked him if I could take the bus to the hot spring with them.
We're going to a hot spring in this steamy weather?!
No. We're going to a riverside camping site that's on the way there.
S-So I have to spend time with these old farts until we get there?
It's just five or six hours. No big deal.
I'm getting off! Let me off!
Sh-She's cute.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Maybe it's afternoon already...
She's cute.
What's wrong?
I'm not getting off.
Thank you for using Nyuubai Kougyou's touring bus.
I will be your guide for this trip.
My name is Nonomura Misato.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
Nonomura Misato-san...
Let's make this trip to our destination,
the Touji hot spring, an enjoyable one.
How about some singing?
Um, anyone who wants to sing...
Are you gonna have sex?
That young man has balls.
Y-Young man!
Good job, young man.
No!
Sign: Yasohachi Station
Ticket: Touji Hot Spring
Touji
Yui, are you attending an all-girls school?
Yes. I don't want to attend the same school as you.
Really...
I see.
Did you want me to attend your school?
Not particularly.
We've been in the same school since elementary school,
so I just didn't expect you to change.
All right, I've finally pitched the tent.
Now I have to catch some fish for dinner.
Where did Makoto go?
I suppose he went to gather firewood.
Tent: Yasohachi Academy Mountaineering Club
All right, I'll catch a lot!
Really. How could Akira bring me to a campsite like this?
There are no girls around here.
No matter what,
I have to get to Nagashima Lodge,
where Nonomura Misato-san is staying.
And I'll stay there too.
Maybe I should go back to the bus road and then head over there.
Perhaps I'm lost.
How unlucky.
A girl is screaming.
It came from this direction!
S-Someone help me.
Help me!
Hold on!
Thank you.
I always come here to gather herbs, so I'm used to this path, but...
I'm glad I saved you. The truth is, I'm lost.
You were gathering herbs, so you know this place?
This is my home town.
Where do you want to go?
Nagashima Lodge.
What? Our lodge?
You work at Nagashima Lodge?
Yes. My mom runs it.
I'm lucky.
Because we're on a mountain,
we don't have many facilities,
but please enjoy the hot spring as well.
Dream
You didn't need to prepare such a luxurious dinner.
How can you say that?
You saved my daughter's life.
Well, I just came across her by chance.
Mom, didn't you say that city guys are scary?
But apparently some are courageous and kind.
Indeed. Maybe I need to change my opinion.
Dream
Mom doesn't like me to go into town.
I'm just worried about you, Kumiko.
I'm not a child anymore.
Mom, I only have you,
and you only have me,
so you needn't worry that I'll leave.
Well, I hope so.
But if I never leave here,
maybe I'll never get married.
My, my, do you have someone already?
Oh, no. I don't have any...
You're blushing.
Stop it, Mom.
Makoto-san, the food will get cold.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I was wondering what to eat. There's so much.
I'll try this.
Delicious!
It may not look appetizing,
but it has a well-rounded taste.
I'm full.
Now I'm happy.
There are open air hot springs all over the place.
This is why I came here.
Huh? Maybe I came here for something else.
Oops, I slipped! I'm falling!
Nonomura Misato-san.
You got off the bus at the camping site.
I didn't really want to get off there.
I wanted to spend time with you.
But Akira forced me...
I totally forgot about him.
I couldn't catch anything.
I'm starving.
So you're through with this boyfriend.
Yes. This trip was intended to relieve my heartbreak.
It was my day off, but I volunteered to go.
I thought that if I was with older people,
I would forget the bad times.
Then... it would've been better if I wasn't around.
No. I had fun.
I'm glad you were there.
I was able to forget my bad memories.
But you bumped into me twice.
Is this really a coincidence?
Or is it fate?
Maybe it's both.
I fell asleep in the hot spring.
Sign: Open air hot spring
I feel a bit dizzy.
Huh?
Is that silhouette...
Yui?
Onii-chan!
Yui, what are you doing here?
I thought I ought to apologize to you.
Apologize? For what?
Are you still mad about me transferring to Yasohachi Academy without telling you?
I-I'm not mad.
I was just surprised. It was so sudden.
Really?
Yeah.
You really aren't mad?
Not at all.
I shouldn't have worried about it.
I feel relieved, and now I'm hungry.
Maybe I shouldn't have rejected that offer.
I wonder if she'd still make dinner.
Okay! I'll go ask.
What about you, Onii-chan?
I'm full.
Narusawa-san and Makoto. Why are you here?
What about you? What happened to camping?
I failed. I couldn't catch any fish. I feel so ashamed.
I was so hungry I couldn't sleep.
I decided to come to this lodge as an emergency shelter.
Kawajiri-kun, I'm hungry too.
Why don't we both ask the owner?
Narusawa Yui-san, you're too nice. Let's ask together.
Gee, Yui is nice to everyone.
How did Yui know I was here?
I'm starting to feel hungry.
Maybe I should ask Kumiko-chan for something.
Dream
Wow, this is a really great treat!
I'm so moved.
It looks delicious.
Our chef has already gone home, so I made it.
I hope you like it.
Delicious!
Yummy.
This is good.
You'll make someone a great wife.
This is like heaven.
Kumiko-san, thank you.
Not at all. You're friends of the person who saved my life.
What? Onii-chan saved your life? Really?
Well, I did.
What? Tell us the story.
Sign: A few days later...
Yui-san is living with Kondou Makoto?!
To be precise, they're merely housemates.
Don't put your eerie face so close to me!
Cohabiting or not, she's living under the same roof as that pervert Kondou.
It's means the same thing!
What's with those hands?!
I just put them on yours.
Take them off! Take them off!
Take them off!
A-Aritomo-kun, are you all right?
No closer! No closer! No closer!
Don't come any closer!
Nagaoka Yoshiki-kun.
Will you take me to Narusawa Yui-san's house?
You mean Kondou's house?
Not Kondou's house.
Na-ru-sa-wa Yu-i-san's house.
Now listen. It's the same thing.
It's not the same!
That was a good angle!
Hey! Why are you standing there?
Be careful!
He's scary.
I finally reached it, but...
All right!
Is that so?
Yes. Apparently Narusawa's mom runs that café.
Does that matter?
Kondou
Narusawa
Hey, you.
Is Narusawa Yui-san home?
Huh?
I'm Saionji Aritomo, Narusawa Yui-san's classmate.
I came here to see Yui-san. Please take me to see her!
What's he saying? Is he stupid?
I'll go home before his stupidity infects me.
What?
Aren't you working here as a maid?
A maid?
What? You don't even know what a maid is?
An assistant, a servant.
You look like a country girl,
so I thought that's what you were.
Th-This is bad.
Oh, Kumiko-chan.
I knew it. You're Kumiko-chan from Nagashima Lodge.
What's wrong?
M-Makoto-san!
When did you leave your home town?
I left home to see you.
I'm glad you're here.
Sakuragi Kindergarten
Wh-What?
Onii-chan, dinner is ready.
Kumiko-san, what's wrong?
Well, she suddenly started to cry.
Sakuragi Kindergarten
Anyway, why don't you let her in?
Oh, come in, Kumiko-chan.
Kumiko-san, are you all right?
Yui-san is living under the same roof as that Kondou Makoto.
How could this happen?!
Shut up.
Ouch.
Shut up!
You're annoying!
What a savage town!
She seems lost. She must've had some bad experiences on her way here.
She's all tuckered out and asleep.
Her sleeping face is cute.
My, my, you're acting like her big sister,
but she's the same age as you two, right?
She doesn't look it.
She's kind of unspoiled and naive.
Damn it. I lost.
Was Kumiko-chan's mom worried about her?
She sounded calm on the phone,
but she's the mother of an adolescent daughter.
Do I make you worry too?
What do you think?
She worries about you to death, because you're so helpless.
Gee, Onii-chan, you're mean!
Stop it! I'm sorry, Yui.
I'm almost at the point of finishing this game.
I'm sleepy.
You two shouldn't stay up late.
Hurry and go to bed already.
Yui, I made your bed up in my room.
Anyway, good night.
I'm going to bed too.
Onii-chan, I hope you finish this game before morning.
Shut up. This is very easy.
Then good night, Onii-chan.
Sure.
What's wrong with this?
I see. Great.
Oh, is that you, Yui? I'm almost there.
How was...
Oh, Kumiko-chan.
What's wrong?
Am I really a country girl?
What? Did you have a nightmare?
Your friend Saionji-san mistook me for a servant.
Saionji? Do you mean Aritomo?
He's a bit crazy. Don't worry about it.
I want to see stars.
I'm going to finish this in a moment, so please wait.
There aren't many stars.
Maybe I can see better from over there.
I should brush my teeth and go to bed.
Is that Kumiko-chan?
Where is she going this late at night?
Is she homesick?
Even in this park, I can only see a few stars.
I wonder if Makoto-san and Yui-san...
are more than just friends.
Oh, yeah?
A girl alone.
Were you waiting for us?
Want to do something nice with us?
Something nice?
Yes, something nice.
I'll give you a really nice experience.
Just come with us.
A girl alone at night is just asking to be raped.
Yeah, she's waiting for it.
N-No. Stop it, please.
Shut up!
Let's do this already.
Stop it, you two!
Yui-san.
Are you alone?
Another helpless sheep comes along.
Then let's share them evenly.
Sure.
Hey. Yui? Kumiko-chan?
Where did those two go so late at night?
I was about to finish that game.
That's Yui's scream.
Yui!
Stop it!
Don't resist.
You wanted this, right?
Onii-chan, help me!
Onii-chan?
You're calling for your brother, not your boyfriend?
Yui!
What's wrong with her calling me?
V-Violence isn't good.
What about what you're doing?
I won't stand for this!
Onii-chan!
Yui!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
I knew you'd come and save me.
Are you sure we shouldn't go to the station with you?
Yes.
I'm fine.
When you come next time, bring your mom too for some vacation time.
Sure. Thank you for letting me stay.
I wonder what Onii-chan is doing when you're about to leave.
Please let him sleep some more.
Then I hope you do well, Yui-san.
See you.
Farewell.
Yui, I'm about to finish this game.
Booklet: Africa
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
Oh, it's you, Yui.
Are you all right?
Yeah. I was dreaming.
Dreaming?
Yeah. About when you transferred to Yasohachi Academy.
A lot of things happened.
Yeah.
To be continued...
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking
Preview
Final Episode
「Brother and Sister . . . or . . . 」