Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
What are you doing, Onii-chan?
Um, nothing.
I just wanted to feel like a kid.
Whatever. Would you please help me clean?
I don't like work.
How can you say that?!
Because of you, I have to clean the science room.
You had class duty during lunch break,
but you ignored it and left school.
You don't get it, do you?
Every day, we're locked up inside this school, like birds in a cage.
We should be free sometimes to enjoy the wide world.
Are you saying that buying croquettes is freedom?
If you don't like manual labor,
could you do some brain work?
I don't have any more pages left to write.
Left: Class Duty Log
Right: Roll Book
You ripped the pages out of the duty journal?
If you keep throwing those scraps of paper, Tendou will yell at you.
Scraps of paper? Yui-chan, this is...
Science Room
Hey! What are you doing littering the school grounds?!
What?
Where are you?
Where are you hiding, Kondou Makoto?!
Violating school regulations, skipping cleaning duty,
and littering the school grounds.
On top of that, trying to avoid my interrogation!
You deserve capital punishment.
And that means cleaning bathrooms for a week.
Help me, please!
Is he practicing for the scavenger hunt at the autumn sports festival?
No, he should be practicing for the folk dance,
but he has no sense.
By the way, was Tendou's hair always that white?
Maybe he dyed it.
So he's vain about his appearance.
Onii-chan, how long do you plan on hiding?
Hey, Yui.
On the girls' list in this roll book,
why is number thirteen blank?
So you were slacking off on your class duties and didn't notice.
If I remember right, one girl had to take a leave of absence because of illness.
She wasn't sure when she'd return,
so she was taken off the roll book.
So they removed this girl's name. That's sad.
Yeah.
Can we hurry and finish cleaning?
Hey, what's her name?
As I recall, it was Sugimoto...
Sugimoto?
Sugimoto. Oh yes, Sakurako.
Yes, Sugimoto Sakurako-san.
Yes, it was a very cute name. I remember it.
Paper: Prescription for Sugimoto Sakura
Yasohachi Community Hospital
Sugimoto Sakurako.
So she used to be my classmate.
Episode 4
Autumn, the Season of Withered Leaves . . .
Sign: Yasohachi Academy
So starting today, I can't go home with you.
Really?
Aren't you disappointed?
What?
The Theater Club recruited me.
Book: The Last Leaf
I'm going to have a leading role.
Why can't you be happy for me?
That's great.
Onii-chan, you don't like it?
I don't care.
Well, I'll be looking forward to the Cultural Festival.
Don't screw it up by getting stage fright.
Why is he so uninterested?
It's Sugimoto Sakurako. Sugimoto Sakurako.
I'll certainly take photos of Narusawa Yui's triumphant moment on the stage.
Th-Thanks.
On a different subject, what's wrong with Sugimoto-san?
Are you worried about Kondou-kun?
He seems interested in that other girl, Sugimoto Sakurako.
Why won't the wind blow?
I'm looking into this by asking other people.
Oh, I saw it.
She was in class 2-B, but her name was removed from the roll book.
The photo on her application form shows that she's a real beauty.
A good cha—
What's wrong with you, Yui-san?
You're letting that pervert take photos just as he likes.
Oh, Saionji-kun.
If you have anything on your mind, you can talk to me.
I, Saionji Aritomo, the hero on stage and your partner as well,
will listen to your problems.
Thanks, but I'm fine.
Let's go to the rehearsal.
Sure. The hero and the heroine appear together for rehearsal.
We might become the talk of the school.
Narusawa is gone.
You!
That way.
Yui-san. Yui-san!
A picture of a rejected man chasing a girl.
What did you say?
A good chance for a photo!
Fly away!
So I have to fly away again today.
Maybe it would be easier to ask at Reception.
Huh?
A paper plane?
Is this yours?
Yes.
Then, here you go.
Are you all right?
I'm fine! I'm fine.
Isn't he cute? He's Turbo.
Yes.
Uh, nice to meet you. I'm Kondou Makoto.
Oh, I'm Sugimoto Sakurako.
Are you enrolled at Yasohachi Academy?
Huh? Yeah.
I see.
I used to go to Yasohachi Academy as well.
I know that.
I found your name in the roll book.
Then you're my classmate?
Yes. I was surprised when I found this in the park over there.
The paper plane I threw.
Yes. It hit my head.
Accidentally?
Yes, accidentally.
So things do happen accidentally.
Yeah.
Yasohachi Academy.
I thought my name had been already removed.
Not possible. We're classmates.
Classmates?
Onii-chan, are you going home already?
Yeah.
You seem to leave school earlier these days.
Is that so?
We have rehearsal in the gymnasium today.
I'm having problems with my role.
Can you watch me act and give me advice?
Um, I'd rather enjoy it on the day of performance.
Well, I hope you do your best.
Onii-chan...
Are you all right?
Perhaps I'm a bit tired.
I'm sorry. I forgot that you're ill and was fooling around.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I'll come again tomorrow.
Thank you.
But you don't have to.
You have a girlfriend, don't you?
Someone beautiful and not sick like me.
What's this so suddenly?
I don't mind. Could you still come see me sometime?
I don't have a girlfriend!
Really? But...
I'm not visiting you because I pity you.
I come here every day because I enjoy seeing you.
Thank you.
So you'd better recover soon.
Then we can have a date outside.
Yes.
All right!
Where would you like your first date to be after you leave here?
Let me see...
Mount Kisaragi Observatory.
That shabby place?
Yes. I was hospitalized right after I was accepted at Yasohachi Academy.
I was supposed to go there for orientation.
I see.
You went there with your classmates, right?
Actually, I skipped school that day and went to a movie,
so I've never been there.
All right. Let's go there.
You're quite the delinquent.
I'm not a delinquent.
Afterwards, that violent teacher, Tendou, made me clean bathrooms for a week.
"Kondou Makoto, you're going to clean bathrooms for a week!"
That's funny. I'd like to hear more about your school life.
Will tomorrow be all right?
Tomorrow I have checkups throughout visiting hours.
I see.
Then I'll come here at night.
That's dangerous.
You'll fall off again.
Next time, I'll be fine.
All the weak branches have already broken.
So when is lights-out?
Nine thirty.
Then I'll be here at ten.
Sure, ten o'clock.
S-Sorry! I'm not a suspicious character!
Don't shout.
Sakurako-chan!
Sakurako-chan, is it all right for you to be out of bed?
I wanted to see you outside.
What's wrong?
I'm walking... with someone beside me.
Sakurako-chan...
Thank you, Kondou-san.
Come on, you can call me Makoto.
That sounds like we're lovers.
Aren't we?
You make me happy.
If I could die like this...
Sakurako-chan.
Are you all right? Would you like to go back to your room?
It's been a while since I walked outside.
I was worried.
Thank you.
Are you cold?
No, I'm fine now. What about you?
I'm fine. Men are happy to be outdoors, whatever the weather.
I feel like I'm in a dream.
Withered leaves are falling.
When they all fall down, I'm going to wake from my dream.
It's not a dream.
Sakurako-chan?
It's the nurse. I have to go.
This...
It's all right. You can wear it.
But you'll catch a cold on your way home.
It's fine. I'm happy to be outdoors, whatever the weather.
I'm grateful. Thank you.
So our member on the Cultural Festival Committee will be Kondou Makoto.
Cultural Festival               Committee Election
He's not in any club,
and he's skipped the class's preparations for the Cultural Festival.
I don't want to!
The Cultural Festival Committee
does chores like making preliminary arrangements and hanging posters!
Kondou
Niimi
I think it suits you.
What? This is an abuse of democracy!
I prefer freedom. I don't want to join any club.
I don't want this!
Kondou-kun,
the success of the Cultural Festival depends on the members of the Committee.
They represent each class.
I'm counting on you.
Sure. I'll do my best.
He's really susceptible to beautiful women.
What a wolf.
For the week before the Cultural Festival, I couldn't go see Sakurako-chan.
Armband: Cultural Festival Committee
Damn it.
The bathrooms stink these days.
Well, I did visit her once, late at night.
Sign: Cultural Festival
Yasohachi Festival
Poster: Cultural Festival
Tomorrow is the Cultural Festival.
I'm excited. This year's special event is the play.
Hello.
We're very sorry.
We can't put you through to a patient unless you're a relative or it's an emergency.
Whatever.
Once the Cultural Festival is over, I'll be able to meet her anyway.
And the more she misses me,
the fonder her heart will grow.
Is that so?
Yui-san, what's wrong?
Tomorrow is the day of the performance. It makes us nervous, right?
Y-Yeah.
A Cultural Festival Committee member and an astonishing photographer.
Weird
You two seem to be getting along well.
I hope you'll keep that up and support us,
as the highlight of the festival.
Now, Yui-san, let's go rehearse.
He said I'm an astonishing photographer.
Astonishing
Some people do recognize my work.
I-I'm strongly opposed...
to all forms of violence!
What?!
Yoshiki-kun, will you do me a favor?
After all, I recognize your skills as a photographer.
Really?
Sign: Yasohachi Academy Cultural Festival
Film Club
Screening
rt Exhibition
Film Club
Screening
rt Exhibition
Film Club
Screening
rt Exhibition
Film Club
Screening
rt Exhibition
Film Club
Screening
rt Exhibition
Art Exhibition
Kondou-kun, you've done well.
And it was a good idea to take photos as a record of the festival.
Cotton Candy
Takoyaki
Well, as a member of the committee, that comes naturally to me!
Then I hope you two enjoy it as well.
Sure.
I'm going to get some compensation, right?
Yeah. If you print all of them,
I'll tell you about a footbridge
where you can take panty shots.
You'd better keep your word.
The Cultural Festival, the biggest event at school.
When I tell her the story of how I directed it,
Sakurako-chan will look on me with passionate eyes.
The play with Narusawa Yui-san in the leading role is about to start.
Damn it. Why is Yui playing against that bastard Aritomo?
Armband: Cultural Festival Committee
She visited his villa in the summer.
Wait. I wonder if there's a love scene.
I should at least check it out.
What have I been drawing until today?
I feel miserable.
His acting is really miserable.
All I have left of my life is that one leaf.
Yes, that one leaf.
When that leaf falls, I will die as well.
My life is wavering. My life is fluttering.
Please help me.
The wind is getting stronger.
Please, spare that last leaf...
I feel like I'm in a dream.
Withered leaves are falling.
When they all fall down...
Onii-chan...
Visiting
hours
are
over
Visiting
hours
are
over
Sign: Yasohachi Community Hospital
Poor Sakurako-chan.
Dying... That was sudden.
After such good care for two years.
It'll be sad around here.
Yeah.
Dead?
Sakurako-chan... is dead?
Sign: Yasohachi Academy Cultural Festival
I cried watching this year's play.
Yeah. The heroine was a really good actress.
She really appeared to be in pain.
Onii-chan.
Oh, it's you, Yui.
Yui-san. Leave that guy alone.
Let's celebrate the success of our play.
Are you all right? What's wrong, Onii-chan?
It's nothing.
See, Yui-san? There's nothing wrong.
That applause was to celebrate us as the hero and heroine.
Now let's take advantage of these circumstances and join the folk dance.
Leave me alone.
I'm talking to Onii-chan.
Then I'll go over to the folk dance first.
Yui.
What?
I'm sorry, but can I borrow your bicycle?
Sure, but...
Where are you going?
Mount Kisaragi Observatory.
What? That's quite far.
It's all right. We don't have school tomorrow.
Be careful.
Yeah, thanks.
Sakura... ko-chan.
Sakurako-chan.
Sakurako-chan is alive.
She's alive. She's alive!
So it was your bird that died.
I thought of putting Turbo's soul on a paper plane and...
you made a paper plane as well.
I want to make a memory with you.
But you'll catch a cold.
I don't want to be in bed anymore.
All right.
You're already...
What's wrong?
I'm embarrassed.
You don't have to be.
Now...
look.
It's shining.
Now, come with me.
All right.
This is wonderful.
You're beautiful, Sakurako-chan.
Really, Makoto-san?
Yeah.
Please, don't be rough.
Onii-chan!
You don't usually come to the library.
Don't be silly. I'm a regular patron here.
Physical strength isn't enough for men.
We also need to be good at studying and the martial arts!
You kinda sound like Tendou. He must be influencing you.
Why would Tendou influence me?
What's this?
Were you bringing these into the library?
I was going to exchange them with Shimizu in the library...
Oh, it's nothing.
Sorry to interrupt you!
Kondou Makoto-senpai, please take this.
What is it?
A love letter.
I'm Tsuzuki Kozue from class 1-A.
I love you. Will you be my boyfriend?
Huh?
To be continued...
totsuzen no ame ni furarete
Showered by a sudden rain
kasa mo sasazu ni aruita ra
Walking without putting up my umbrella
machi yuku hito ga henna kao shite mite ta
People in the street looked at me strangely
mada haru asai san gatsu no gogo
On an early spring afternoon,
tsumetai ame no sora miage
I looked up at the sky in the cold rain
odoritaku naru youna kibun de aruita
I walked with an urge to dance
arifureta nichijyou ni itsuka kokoro ga kumotte ta
My heart was clouded by the familiar days
sonna koto sae kizukazu ni ita
I didn't understand anything
keredo
But...
honno sasayakana nandemo nai youna yuuki dakeredo
It was a small piece of courage, almost like nothing
sonna koto de naze ka sukoshi kokoro ga hareta
I don't know why, but it brightened my heart a bit
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking