Oh, I'm jealous! I've never flown in a plane before.
You can count on a souvenir from me.
Aren't you wearing any undergarments, Karen-san?
Normally, you don't wear anything under a yukata, right?
Karen-chan doesn't wear anything when she sleeps, either.
Yui-chan, how do you know that?
It's a secret!
H-Hey, wait up!
I'm coming too!
Wow, it's so big!
The air's fresh too!
It sure is.
Let's get in already, Yui-chan.
Are you two all right?
Gee, Karen-chan!
Sorry!
Why are we suddenly at a hot springs?
Well, I'll explain later on.
Let me tell you how Senpai's love story turned out.
I don't understand guys.
Classmates
The
Graduate
Chapter 2
Minori, Tomomi, and the Hot Springs Trip
In the end, I came here again.
I wonder if she's all right.
Since I'm here, I might as well stop in at school.
Oh my, Yui, what are you doing?
All my underwear seems childish.
If I dry them where Onii-chan can see them, he'll make fun of me.
Ryuunosuke-kun has already left.
Didn't he come back this morning?
Ah! I've been looking for those panties!
Now that you mention it, they're not mine.
So you took them, Mom!
I even asked Onii-chan about them.
Don't make such a huge fuss.
They were expensive.
But they don't suit you.
But Onii-chan likes mature girls!
So I thought if I wore them,
he'd be more interested in me.
Even though you're not going to show them?
That's true, but...
Anyway, it's fine! Feelings are what count!
You're my daughter.
Even if you don't rush, you'll still become a beautiful woman.
Beautiful enough that Onii-chan will look at me?
Don't worry. Believe in yourself.
Minori-kun.
Sanshirou-senpai.
Are the flowers doing well?
Yes.
During the break,
nobody came to the garden and destroyed them.
Remember the picture book of flowers you gave me on graduation day?
I'm still taking good care of it.
No!
School Infirmary
I have to dry them somewhere.
Senpai, is something wrong?
Minori... -kun?
Yes, I'm Minori.
I'm really sorry I was rude to you the other day.
I've been hiding my real self the whole time...
because I don't trust other people.
Actually, I have no friends at all.
You're the only person I can talk to, Senpai.
Because of a certain someone, I think I can change!
But... But!
What should I do?
I-I'm not sure.
However, the most important thing is to say what you really feel.
And you should apologize from your heart for lying.
What if I do, and he doesn't forgive me?
Apologize again and again,
until he forgives you.
If it were me, that's what I'd do.
That's what I'd do.
Senpai, I will apologize to him.
I'll talk to him without my mask.
Um, well, this is...
Well, um...
Senpai, let me say one thing.
When you come back to school,
be sure to wear your uniform and bring a bag with you.
Still, I'll have to say farewell to this uniform soon.
I liked it a lot.
Students in the other schools like it too.
I-It's better if you don't hop or jump when you're dressed like that.
Why?
Why? Well, because...
You're acting weird, Sanshirou-senpai!
You're talking like Onii-chan.
You said "Onii-chan" just now,
but do you mean Ryuunosuke-kun?
Please keep it a secret that I call him "Onii-chan"!
I'll treat you to anything, whether it's a parfait or anmitsu or taiyaki.
Otherwise, Onii-chan will come to hate me.
I won't tell anyone about it.
Really?
O-Of course.
Tomomi-chan!
Why does it bother you?
I've had enough!
Don't worry, I won't photograph your face.
I'm only interested in what's below the neck.
No!
Tomomi... -chan?
I won't do it!
Then I'll show the photos to Ryuunosuke-kun.
What's the matter, Tomomi-chan?
Yui-chan, Sanshirou-senpai!
Mama!
It's nothing.
I have things to do now. Later.
Tomomi-chan, h-hey!
Sorry!
Senpai, I have to go!
Yui-kun!
They aren't getting dry.
I may have to go to my temp job dressed like this.
Are you here, Tomomi-chan?
Oh?
Um... I...
Sorry, I mistook you for someone else.
I remember! You're the girl from the convenience store!
Th-Thanks. You saved me.
It was less embarrassing than walking, right?
Anyway, excuse me.
So she's in the same school as me.
But I've never seen her before.
Yui-san?
Miyuki-san!
Do you know where the Mizuno family residence is located?
Your mother was worried, so she contacted me.
She suggested that learning the piano would make a change of pace.
Gee, that mother of mine...
I only studied the piano when I was young.
Besides, I don't really have time right now.
Tomomi-chan, you seem down.
You're always willing to give me advice.
I'd like to be there for you.
Everything is fine.
If anything comes up,
you'll be the first person I call.
Even if the exams are near,
you still need time to rest.
Why don't we go shopping together?
That sounds good!
Does it have anything to do with the piano lesson?
Skill alone won't improve your piano playing.
The sound reflects the player's heart.
I believe that to make the melody sound clear and refined,
a lesson in calming mental anguish would also be useful.
That said,
there's no way to buy swimsuits during the winter.
I thought it'd make her a little bit more open and frank.
That's so strange.
All right, this should do fine!
I tried to be a little adventurous.
It looks really cute.
Hey, why don't you try some on too, Tomomi-chan?
I-I don't really...
Don't say that. Come on, how about this one?
Come on, hurry up!
W-Wait, Yui-chan!
Don't worry. Leave it to me!
I'll do it myself.
You've got great proportions, Tomomi-chan!
Compared to me, I think you're better—
No, my thighs are fat.
Why don't you also try one, Onee-san?
I'm just accompanying them.
Don't say that. Take a look. This might suit you.
See?
I-I can't.
It only has strings for support. That won't work.
You won't know unless you try it on!
No way. I...
The same goes for men.
You won't understand them if you just stare at them.
Sometimes you have to take the initiative.
I think a bikini suits you, but you'd look even better in a cute one-piece.
You think so?
You look cute.
Really?
Oh, welcome.
Hello.
I see...
Sanshirou-san,
this is the best time of your life.
You think so?
Sometimes you want to feel that way but can't.
Just like me at the moment.
Women fall in love and
become more beautiful.
Men fall in love and become stronger, right?
I might dry up if I weren't in love.
Oh, yes. Do you have some time?
Hey, Sanshirou-san,
what do you think of this?
I used to wear this when strolling down the streets.
I-I think it suits you quite well right now.
So they teach flattery at university too.
But you've made me very happy,
so I'll show you something special.
I haven't dressed up for other people in quite a while.
It makes me nervous.
I wonder what sort of people wear these?
I think it would look good on Karen-san. She's mature.
I'm sure it would look good on you too, Yui-chan.
I'm fine. I've decided not to hurry.
These are good enough for me right now.
Yui-chan. Miyuki-sensei!
What are you doing here?
I just finished a studio photo shoot.
Karen-chan, did something nice happen?
Wh-Why?
Because you seem happier than usual.
I have a week off, starting tomorrow.
So you've managed to get a vacation!
Maybe it was thanks to that coup d'état.
Misako-san really is beautiful.
But in the end, I wasn't able to meet Miyuki-san today.
Are we fated to remain separated?
That's why I said it, didn't I?
Waiting won't do any good.
I have no choice. You're so pitiful.
Shopping
District
Allow me to provide you a chance.
Just this once, all right?
Ticket: Year End Lottery
3000 Yen Lottery Ticket
Sir...
Shopping
District
If you wish to try drawing lots, please give me your ticket.
Today was fun!
It's great to do this occasionally.
Oh?
Youko-chan!
A bit of the loli look,
droopy eyes, no make-up...
but wearing a very short skirt.
Really, boys would love someone like you, Yui.
What?
What's with Youko-chan?
Welcome back.
Mom, what's the matter with Youko-chan?
She told me to give this to you.
What is it?
An invitation card for a trip to the Touji hot springs.
Akira-kun got it as a gift and then gave it to her.
Someone won this in a lottery.
Why did she give it to me?
First, she said something about Ryuunosuke-kun.
He'll go if you come along as well.
So she left two pairs of tickets.
Now that you mention it,
she wasn't her usual self today.
Mom, that outfit!
It's cute, isn't it?
Yes?
Sorry for calling you late at night.
No problem. I'm really glad you invited me.
It's just for a day, though.
I'm still looking forward to it.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Thank you for taking this bus for your wonderful trip!
I, Nonomura Misato, will be your bus guide for this trip!
We will arrive at the Touji hot springs in about three hours.
Until then, please enjoy your ride.
Sanshirou-san,
we haven't had a chance to meet since then.
I wonder if you're all right.
Miyuki-san. Miyuki-san!
Yes?
What were you thinking about?
N-Nothing...
Let's get in the hot springs right away.
Otherwise, it'll be a waste of time.
Why don't we rest a bit first?
You two just don't get it.
When you get to a hot springs,
you must first change into a yukata.
Is that so? I didn't know.
You shouldn't take her too seriously.
Huh? Am I wrong?
Oh my, someone's still on the bus.
Sir, please wake up.
We have arrived, sir.
I-I'm sorry.
You had a great sleep along the way. I feel bad about waking you up.
You'll look cuter if you tie it higher.
Miyuki-san, why don't you take off your bra?
Huh? That would make me feel embarrassed.
Isn't it okay?
Only us girls here.
You don't have to worry.
I feel chilly.
It's because you slept on the bus.
You'll feel better if you warm up in the open-air hot springs.
Actually, I was about to do that.
Walk along this passage and turn right. You'll find the hot springs for men.
The left side is for women, or so I've heard.
Thank you so much.
Wait. Was it the other way around?
Oh, bother. I'd better go in as well.
Special Open-Air Hot Springs
Male
Female
I guess I still look good.
Oh, I'm jealous! I've never flown in a plane before.
You can count on a souvenir from me.
Oh you're here too, Miss Tour Guide.
Y-Yeah.
Aren't you wearing any undergarments, Karen-san?
Normally, you don't wear anything under a yukata, right?
Karen-chan doesn't wear anything when she sleeps, either.
Yui-chan, how do you know that?
It's a secret.
Hey, wait up!
I'm coming too!
I can't compete with youngsters.
Your mouth is huge!
You could fit a rock inside it!
A rock?
Yep. A rock as in "rock, paper, scissors."
That's silly.
Yui-san, you have a really strange way of thinking.
Your point of view is unique.
If you try music or painting,
your talent might prove useful.
Yui-chan, would you like to partner with me?
In any case,
I want to try playing the piano and violin.
I can teach you to play the piano any time you want.
Miyuki-san, why did you study piano?
To be honest, I had mixed motives.
I fell in love with my music teacher during elementary school.
I studied piano because I wanted him to notice me.
Hey, we should try the other baths too.
Let's go exploring!
It might be fun!
Let's go, let's go!
I'll stay here a little longer.
All the men from the cities are like wolves!
You shouldn't go to places like that by yourself.
Mom, you don't understand me at all!
Seriously, that girl of mine.
This is huge too! Amazing!
You're the landlady here, correct?
Allow us to join you.
It's truly a wonderful hot springs.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Uh, I'm so sorry! I thought there was no one else here.
Thank goodness. I thought I'd been found out.
What are you doing here?
Um, well, that's...
Oh, you're the boy from before.
Please don't misunderstand.
I thought... this was for... men.
Did I give you bad information?
What was that?
Maybe someone's swimming over there.
I'll go have a look.
Me too.
It must be great to be young.
You all have such beautiful bodies.
And supple, beautiful skin too.
N-No way.
You've never been touched by a man, have you?
If you keep refusing,
you won't experience real love, young lady.
Did something happen?
Did he come here to spy on us?
Y-You're wrong. There's a reason for it.
Sanshirou-senpai?!
Why am I here?
You fainted in the baths.
Still, I'm glad to see you're okay.
I was so worried the other day that it kept me from sleeping.
I'm really grateful.
Did that guy beat you up badly?
I'm pretty bad at fighting.
Why did you protect me,
even though you're bad at it?
Um, well...
I'm so happy! That man used to be...
That aside,
I never thought I'd meet you here.
Somehow, this makes me feel like it's fate.
I-I'd be glad if that were true.
Sanshirou-san, what do you think about being kind?
Wh-Why are you asking so suddenly?
People are kind to others so that they'll be treated well in return.
Or perhaps they want to be seen as kind, right?
They want to be seen as kind,
because they want to be loved.
If that's the case,
kindness is a means of tricking someone.
Miyuki-san...
I believe that true kindness is when you act with no expectation of a return.
But that's just...
I-I'm sorry. I was rambling.
Can I give you a response later?
I don't have an answer for your question right now.
But I'll figure it out. Definitely!
All right! I'll be waiting.
Um...
Can I come in?
I-I'm going to the baths again!
Senpai, it must be nice.
For me, love and life are always one-way and only bring pain.
Tomomi-kun...
You know, people are always in pain, to some extent.
That's what proves we're alive.
It's how you face it that's important, I think.
The people who can always smile
are the ones who can overcome it, right?
Senpai...
S-Sorry. I was being hifalutin without really knowing anything.
You look down, so I unintentionally...
I feel fine now, thanks to you.
Senpai!
Please don't scare us anymore.
Senpai, why are you here?
Perhaps you're chasing her?
N-No!
I won an invitation card in a lottery.
A lottery?
The hot springs feel good.
Would you like to give me piano lessons when we get back?
Of course, with pleasure.
I feel like I could make wonderful sounds.
You look happy now.
It's all thanks to Sanshirou-senpai.
His words put me at ease.
Sanshirou-san?
I won't turn away anymore.
I have to let him know that he's wrong.
That aside,
Sanshirou-senpai is a mysterious person.
His words somehow calmed me
and warmed my heart.
There's something I don't understand.
It's you.
Miyuki-san, if you don't mind,
can we meet by ourselves next time,
just the two of us?
I have something I need to say to you.
At two o'clock on the third of January,
can we meet at Hakujagaike Park?
O-Of course!
I want to know... more about you.
Ain't that great, Senpai?
I'll keep the bath incident a secret,
so please forget about
seeing my naked body.
It's a promise.
hajimete no date no hi no asa wa
On the morning of our first date,
kagami no mae de nankai mo
in front of the mirror,
fuku kigaete bakari zutto kimaranakute
I indecisively kept changing my clothes.
anata wo sanjuppun matasete ita
I made you wait half an hour longer.
itsumo wa fuzakete asonde iru no ni
Usually we joke around,
anata to te wo tsunaide arukeba
but just holding hands and walking together
sore dake de ureshikute
made me happy.
keredo hazukashikute
Still, it was embarrassing too,
zutto anata no kao mirenaino
so I couldn't look at your face.
itsumademo
I wish
toki wo wasurete iraretara
this moment would last forever.
kono mama aoi sora wo
I wish we could watch the blue sky,
futari nagamete iraretara
just like this, together.
todoku kana
I wish
anata e no afureru kimochi
my overflowing feelings would reach you.
sono mama tsutaetai
I'd just like to tell you
konna ni anata ga suki dakara
that I love you so much.
Translation: ElyasRay
Translation Check: anon
Timing, Editing: Collectr
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: DestroyKing