Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
The weather's lovely, isn't it?
Yeah.
When we visit Dad's grave, the weather is always fine.
He used to say that rainy days made him feel calm.
So he was different.
I left the flowers at the water tap.
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
I'll go get them.
Narusawa
Family
I'll be back.
Narusawa
Family
What do you think, darling?
Narusawa Family
Yamashita
Nagaoka
Narusawa Family
Yamashita
Nagaoka
Yui has grown up, hasn't she?
Sign: Abbot's Quarters
There it is.
How can you be so careless?
Your forgot the offering.
Oh, it's you, Abbot.
Long time no see.
Yeah.
You seem to grow more every time I see you.
Misako-san is as young and beautiful as ever.
I think it's been long enough.
Huh?
Um... the weather is nice.
Is there someone you like?
Wh-Why?
You're still bad at concealing your feelings.
And...
that means...
This boy had better have a thick skin.
Anyhow...
It's been ten years.
She should live her own life.
As a mother, she's raised you really well.
Misako-san has her own future too.
People meet and fall in love.
They love each other, part,
and then meet again.
It all keeps repeating.
Oh, yeah!
We're having a competition at the main building.
It's going to be busy.
Narusawa
Family
Episode 6
Feelings, Cloudy, and Then . . .
Yasohachi Shopping District
Year End Raffle Sale
New Year's Greetings
Headband: Sale
Lapels: Yasohachi Shopping District
Year End Raffle Sale
You've got it!
You've won!
Raffle Drawing
You've won the special prize!
I won. I-I won!
Ouch.
You're as stupid as ever.
Oh, it's you, Izumi.
What? Are you going to your morning practice?
Having to practice during the winter holidays must be awful.
I'm not like you.
We're going to have a big athletics meet.
All right, I'll go cheer for you.
Where is this meet?
Myououin in Toujimura.
I'm not expecting your support, but I'll do my best anyway.
See you there.
Yeah, do your best.
Toujimura?
That's rather far.
Hey, Makoto.
What is it?
If I win the title, what will you give me as a congratulatory gift?
What do you want?
Think for yourself.
All right. What about tons of kisses?
J-Just joking.
Oh, you were just joking.
What was with that look?
Is she...
Isn't that Akira?
I found you.
Why is everyone so vigorous in this cold?
I suppose this will surprise you.
Take a look!
Tickets: Special Prize
Yasohachi Shopping District
What is it? Tickets for a hot springs trip?
I won this at the lottery in the shopping district.
It's a special prize.
Bus tickets to go and return, the lodging fee, and some luxurious meals.
Would you like to come with me?
I'm not some grandpa or grandma.
Why don't you ask someone else?
Oh, why don't you ask Yui?
She likes hot springs.
Yu—
Ask Yui-san...
Th-That's...
How can I? A young couple going together to a hot springs...
That'd be embarrassing.
Tickets: Toujimura Hot Springs
Toujimura Hot Springs?
Myououin in Toujimura.
Akira.
What?
Toujimura Hot Springs...
I'll go with you.
Then what about Yui-san?
The package is just for two, right?
Only two people can go.
If you don't go, I can ask her.
I don't go on the trip, and Yui-san does...
What are you saying?
I have a higher priority use for that ticket!
I can't breathe.
Then why don't you ask her yourself?
That'd be embarrassing.
I think we've done this before.
I forgot something important.
Yui and Misako-san are visiting their family grave.
The scenery is beautiful.
If only I could be seeing this with Yui-san.
Where is she now?
Makoto...
Title: Guidebook
Myououin.
Well, because I'm on a trip,
I thought I'd check out some famous and historic places.
Your tastes are quite like some grandpa's.
There's so much snow.
Let's snowboard on the ski slopes.
That doesn't suit you.
Girls snowboarding on the ski slopes...
That's also nice.
Work up a good sweat with sports,
and then relax in the hot spring.
It's going to be like heaven.
Anyway, this bus is really slow.
That's part of the trip too.
The ski slopes aren't going anywhere.
Idiot. Izumi's competition will be over.
Did you say something?
Um, none of your business.
Whatever. Your scarf is vulgar.
Why are we stopping so abruptly?
Flat tire.
I'll need ten minutes to fix it.
Please wait inside the bus.
The competition is going to be over.
Has the Lord turned His back on me?
Myououin
I'm lucky.
Hey, Akira, go on to the lodge without me.
I'll meet you later on the ski slope.
Please take care of my bags!
Myououin
Detour
As I thought. He's all talk and no action.
This dam is huge.
I don't have time for that.
I have to hurry.
The sweat on her chest.
Archery outfits are sexy.
But sportswear that hides too much of the female body is a drag.
It's time for the aerial tram.
I should go back to my lodge.
Maybe the ski slope will have better pickings.
But ski wear also hides too much of the female body.
Winter sports are...
Oh, yes. A-An open-air hot springs.
I should go back to my lodge.
What's wrong with me?
This really looks like a 200-year-old lodge,
and the ski slope is right in front of it.
I'm quite satisfied.
Sign: Express Aerial Tram Station
Myououin ⇔ Touji Hot Springs
Narusawa in ski wear is good too.
Why are you here?!
Ski wear that fits tightly on her body.
This is great.
Answer my question!
Oh, you're Kawajiri-kun, right?
Y-Yui-san...
Wh-What are you doing here?
Makoto told me that you were visiting the cemetery.
Um, well...
Yeah. Mom insisted on snowboarding,
so we suddenly moved to this lodge.
She's really working hard at it.
I'm tired.
What? Isn't that Onii-chan's bag?
Is he with you?
Y-Yes.
Where is he?
I think he's at Myououin.
What?
I didn't know you snowboarded.
I also enjoy snowboarding.
It kinda goes with judo.
I thought it was you, Yui-san.
Saionji-kun.
I glad I'm here.
When I was examining this side from my mountain lodge,
I saw someone who looked like you.
I'm thinking of going somewhere.
Where?
Myououin.
With this, you'll get there in a flash.
Please sit here.
Hold on tight.
It's like an Osoto Gari in judo.
By moving, you can make it turn.
And set your center of gravity low.
Lowering your center of gravity is the key.
Where's Narusawa?
Please remember that.
Hey, hurry and tidy up.
The truck is going to leave!
What are you doing? Don't be lazy.
E-Excuse me. What happened to the archery meet?
Is it over?
Yes, as you can see. We're clearing up.
Um, who won the title?
That would be Kushino-san of Ebine academy.
What?
What about Yasohachi Academy?
Yasohachi?
Yasohachi Academy.
Oh, Shinohara Izumi-san...
She came in 18th.
How come? She was one of the best bets for the title!
How would I know?
Excuse me. I have to clean up.
Izumi?
You'll catch a cold.
Well...
that wasn't your last competition, right?
Cheer up.
It's getting dark.
Are you looking for someone?
Yui-san.
Onii-chan.
What? Kondou Makoto?
So he's here too.
Onii-chan.
How can he do that? That scarf...
I started knitting it last summer, as his Christmas present.
Yui-san!
Come on, cheer up.
Now let's go.
Go away.
So now you show up.
I don't want your pity!
Wh-What are you saying?
Go away.
I hate you. Go away!
You're immature!
You seem to like that boy.
D-Don't be silly!
Cut the crap!
Look at that.
Falling in love and shooting an arrow...
Both depend on your frame of mind.
How can you separate the two?
It's impossible.
If you could control everything that's floating in your mind,
you'd be able to reach your goal.
But you lack concentration
and blame others for your failure.
That's very immature of you.
Do you know why the competition is held here at Myououin?
You do know, right?
A long time ago,
to test their capability as archers,
martial artists shot arrows from one end of the building to the other,
without hitting the eaves or the floor of the veranda.
The best archers competed with all their might.
But eventually, it became a competition
to shoot as many arrows as possible in a limited amount of time.
True martial arts are not a show.
The reason why I rent out this place for the competition is...
to let as many youngsters as possible learn what life is about,
through real martial arts.
It must've been twenty years ago.
There was a young man who suffered from a broken heart.
He decided to leave the woman he loved for his friend.
This young man shot arrows from here
and missed with just two.
People have 108 worldly desires.
Place each desire on an arrow and shoot at that bell.
How about it?
Can you hit the bell with all the arrows?
Izumi.
You're good. You're quite athletic, Kawajiri-kun.
Not at all.
Strike a pose.
You look good in ski wear too, Narusawa's mom.
Come on. Stop calling me "Narusawa's mom."
I've decided to live as a woman.
I don't understand.
It's all right.
The time will come when you do understand.
Anyway, please take lots of photos of the snow.
Is that the nightwatch bell?
That brings back memories.
It's been nineteen years since I last heard that sound.
Yes, it was nineteen years ago.
There are only graves from here on, right?
I don't like this!
Y-Yui-san. Yui-san!
Yui-san...
Yui-san. Stay strong.
What's wrong with you?
Kondou Makoto?
Shinohara Izumi?
Yui-san, I don't like that Shinohara Izumi either.
She speaks and acts like a boy.
She has no delicacy.
Aren't they well suited to each other?
I...
can't beat Izumi-san.
She's so dedicated.
What are you saying?!
You're better than anyone else!
No. You don't need to be better.
I, Saionji Aritomo...
Aritomo...
Y-Yui-san...
Yui-san.
Stupid jerk. Stupid jerk!
Stupid jerk!
I hate you, Onii-chan.
To be continued...
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking
Episode 7
Farewell . . .  Forever . . .