Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Wedding bells...
Huh? I think I've seen her before.
Got it. She's wearing the same jacket as Onii-chan.
What's wrong?
Onii-chan, are you feeling sick?
Or did you eat too much?
Sometimes I have things to think about too.
There's something I can't remember.
Something I must have forgotten.
What do you mean?
Something important... about you and me.
Oh, yeah.
I saw someone wearing a jacket just like yours.
Really. Where?
Near the church on the hill.
Yui, why did you go there?
N-No reason. Just taking a walk. Yeah, just a walk.
But she was a cute girl, well matched to the cherry blossoms.
Could it have been Sakurako-chan?
But...
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
You suddenly stopped talking.
Are you all right, Onii-chan?
M-Maybe I should go for a postprandial walk.
I wonder who it could be so early.
Yui, I'll answer it!
Who is it?
Hi! Are you doing well?
What? It's you, Yoshiki.
Oh, Nagaoka-kun, good morning.
Yui-san, good morning.
It's the first day of the spring holiday.
What do you want?
I heard that you two are going to leave soon. That's kinda sad.
We'll come right back after we attend our parents' wedding ceremony.
I'm envious that you two are going to Africa.
And all by your lonesomes.
Yoshiki, what are you holding?
Oh, I almost forgot.
It fell out of that mailbox.
It's from Dad and Misako-san.
Huh?
I'm presenting a publication at a scholarly conference,
so we've decided to hold our wedding ceremony in Japan?
That means you two are going to be legally brother and sister.
Older brother
Younger Sister
And I'm going to witness it.
Older brother
Younger Sister
What should I wear?
Who said that you're invited to Dad and Misako-san's wedding?!
So we're going to be brother and sister.
Let go of me.
Y-Yeah.
Final Episode
Brother and Sister ... or ...
Can: Sakura
Can: Sakura Drops
Infirmary
Sign: Yasohachi Academy
So I'm really going to be her brother.
Makoto-san.
I knew it!
Long time no see.
Sakurako-chan.
This is a scoop.
Kondou is quite popular.
This is a big scoop.
Unlike Saionji, he doesn't just settle for a normal, middle-class life.
What's the matter with Saionji-kun?
Well, he succumbed to a reasonably convenient girl and settled down.
You bastard.
A-Always...
I've heard that voice before.
Hi, Saionji-kun.
Are you doing well?
Who did you say is normal?!
Just settled? What do you mean by that?!
So you heard all of it.
Why am I, a patrician, being compared with a commoner like Kondou?!
How dare you?!
Because of... that...
Even though Kondou is seeing Yui-san, he's also...
That's why I said...
it's a big scoop.
Don't put your ugly face any closer to mine!
Y-You made that happen.
Shut up!
Bag: Yasohachi Greengrocer
Um, what else do I need?
Oops! I forgot to buy Onii-chan's favorite potatoes.
Potatoes, potatoes.
What?
Sign: Yasohachi Shopping District
Onii-chan.
I see. That's why you were at school.
Also, I wanted to see you.
This is beautiful.
I remember now.
Onii-chan is nice to everyone.
That's all it is.
All right.
Onii-chan is late.
I wonder what he's doing.
Wh-Who's there? Onii-chan?
No...
Saionji-kun.
G-Good evening, Y-Yui-san.
I-Is Kondou home?
No, he's not back yet.
I knew it.
What?
No, i-it's nothing!
Maybe he's in trouble.
Oh, yes. Yes, that's it.
Right, I forgot...
How could I, Saionji Aritomo, do that?
You don't have to worry, Yui-san.
I saw Kondou this afternoon.
He asked me to give you a message.
I totally forgot about it.
He said he'll be visiting a friend's house,
so don't worry if he comes home late.
His friend is...
Kawajiri. Yes, he said Kawajiri.
Yes, yes, that's it.
Really?
Well, I don't need to worry about it then.
Th-That's right.
Lock the doors.
Yes. Thank you.
Well, then. Good night.
Is that you, Gramps?
Could you ask Saionji Intelligence to find out where Kondou Makoto is?
Yes! Hotels, parks, theaters,
any place he could go on a date with a girl!
What? You still can't find him?
Search the town thoroughly!
Kondou's whereabouts are still unknown.
Yui-san?
I didn't intend to deceive you.
No. Thanks, Saionji-kun.
I looked everywhere I could think of.
I wonder where he went.
He should call you, at least.
N-Nagaoka...
Let's take photos afterwards.
Hi there!
Are you two on a date at such a late hour?
Y-You idiot, there are important reasons for this!
No, it's not like that!
I was just joking.
Let me introduce her.
Our new classmate, Sugimoto Sakurako-san.
N-Nice to meet you.
Now I understand.
So you came to submit your application to return to school
and accidentally ran into Kondou.
Yes.
And you two went to Kisaragi Shrine.
Did he behave strangely there?
Like, did he assault you?
You should just keep quiet!
Come to think of it...
I knew he groped you.
Idiot!
Come to think of it?
Yes. He...
Submitting your application to return to school?
I see. That's why you were at school.
Also, I wanted to see you...
so I could thank you.
Thank me?
Yes.
I recovered because of your kindness,
and now I can return to Yasohachi Academy.
Makoto-san, thank you.
Sakurako-chan.
This is beautiful.
I remember now.
Something important?
Yes.
Something about Yui and him.
And what did he say?
He said, "I'm going to my elementary school."
Then he ran off.
So you were wandering around Yasohachi Elementary?
You were looking for Kondou, right?
Yes.
I wanted to give this jacket back to him.
Boo... bies.
Honestly.
I went to Yasohachi Elementary as well.
If I recall correctly, he went to school in the next town.
Yui-san, do you know where Kondou is?
If so, I'll send you there by car or even a helicopter.
Thank you,
Saionji-kun, Sugimoto-san, Nagaoka-kun.
But...
I'll go on my own.
I'm off.
Onii-chan.
Can: Sakura Drops
Sign: Planned Industrial Zone
Construction Starts...
Sign: Danger
There it is!
Onii-chan!
Yui.
Yui, how did you know I'd be here?
Onii-chan, you idiot, idiot, idiot!
Idiot!
Yui.
Can: Sakura Drops
What is it?
Mom left this for me.
I didn't know what to do about it at the time...
so I buried it.
Mom said...
"Give it to someone important to you."
So...
You're the person who's most important to me.
Onii-chan, you'll be late!
Yui, stop calling me Onii-chan!
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking