Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Shimizu
Family
Narusawa
So you're leaving?
Yes.
What about Yui-chan?
I left her a letter.
That's fine, just fine.
I see.
Africa must be hot.
Does that young man still practice archery?
No, he's an archaeologist,
so he's excavating.
People meet one another, part,
and then meet again.
Life is mysterious. You should go.
Yui-chan is old enough now.
You don't need to worry about her.
You're right. Thank you very much.
So...
that young man is an archaeologist.
Try to find a guide for tomorrow by taking lessons from the past.
That proverb makes sense in martial arts as well.
The village may have sunk under the water,
but your home town will always be here.
Come back anytime you want.
I will.
Farewell.
Yamashita
Family
Ikeda
Nakahara
Family
Goodbye, Yui.
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Narusawa
Family
Nakahara
Yui... -san.
"I'm thinking of resuming my life as a woman.
Please support me."
Mom...
Don't... leave me alone.
Episode 8
Spring for Everyone and . . .
Sign: Yasohachi Academy
What is it, Onii-chan?
So I'm really going to be your brother.
What?
Well, my father and Misako-san are getting married.
What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Are you going to the ceremony?
No. Africa is too far.
I can't believe it.
You called me out here just to ask that?
Yeah.
If that was your question,
why couldn't you ask it at home?
It's only you and me now.
Is that all you want?
Yeah.
Because the two of us are alone now...
some things are hard to talk about.
Hey, Narusawa.
Oh, Izumi-san.
Have you seen Makoto?
He's on the roof.
Is that so?
I knew it.
Huh?
Nothing.
If you want to know where Makoto is,
it's fastest to ask Narusawa.
Some snob I know said that. I hate him.
Some snob?
Saionji Aritomo.
Oh yes, that particular snob was looking for you.
Huh?
See you.
Yui-san!
Damn. I knocked over the old man's valuable books.
Seriously.
It's Onii-chan's fault for leaving them there.
What?
This brings back memories.
The first time I met...
Onii-chan is cute.
Onii-chan...
Hey, Yui-san!
Your look of ennui is also beautiful.
Saionji-kun.
Oh, stop it, Yui-san.
Call me Aritomo.
A-ri-to-mo.
We spent a night together in a mountain cottage, didn't we?
You're acting a bit distant.
Come on. Nothing happened between us.
Feeling embarrassed?
You're cute.
That makes me feel embarrassed too.
When I remember our intense hug that night...
Oh, I got carried away just now.
I forgot that I have someone with me.
Onii-chan.
When I went to your house,
he forced his way into the car.
He asked me to drive all over the place.
He was very annoying.
Well, I'm quite tolerant, so it's all right.
But if it were someone else...
I know you were embarrassed.
When you suddenly ran out of the cottage,
I was surprised, Yui-san.
But from the helicopter,
we saw that silvery-white scene, shining under the rising sun.
It was like going to a magical world.
Oh, remembering that now makes me feel warm inside.
It was very moving!
What... do you want?
Ah, right. I wanted to borrow your bicycle.
Ah, Yui-san.
Fine, but can you take me home?
You were finally in my arms.
Why don't you let Aritomo
take you home?
Onii-chan!
Sure, sure, sure.
I'll take Yui-san home.
This car has a very comfortable ride.
It's one of the best in the Saionji classic car collection,
I can assure you.
Especially...
the elegant form.
Its shape is handcrafted.
You can feel the warmth and softness emanating from every part of it.
Just watching it makes my heart tighten with joy.
I-I wonder what's wrong with him.
Onii-chan.
Well, it seems there's no doubt.
They've broken up.
Wow, this makes me feel happy.
Break-ing-up...
So I end up in the water today?
Hey! What's up?
Are you here to ask me out on a date?
What?
Nothing.
The weather's nice.
I'm training for the next archery competition.
I'll get my revenge there.
I'm giving up my vacations.
Therefore, I can't go out on a date for a while!
Damn.
Career Guidance Office
Narusawa-san, I hope you do your best.
I think you'll be able to pass the exam.
Sensei, thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
I thought you were a typical girl,
but you've chosen an unexpected course.
What?
Kondou-kun, you don't seem to be doing well these days.
Oh, Sensei.
When are you going to decide about your future?
Someday.
What's wrong?
U-Um, nothing.
M-My mom and your dad are getting married soon.
If you want to say something, say it.
S-So...
I was wondering if you're really going to skip the ceremony.
Yeah. I'm not going.
Oh, really?
I get it.
Sign: Yasohachi Academy
Hey, Kondou Makoto.
Oh, it's you, Izumi.
Tomorrow is my last high school competition.
Are you going to support me?
Yeah.
Really?
Why?
Well, if you're coming,
everything will be okay.
See you then.
Yeah.
Paper: Evaluation for Studying Abroad
Accepted
Narusawa.
Izumi-san, do you still like ohagi?
Note: Ohagi are rice balls coated with sweetened red beans.
Y-Yeah. Why?
Do you remember when I transferred here? I was so nervous.
You were the first person who spoke to me.
Oh, was I?
It made me feel better.
That time, you asked me...
"Do you like ohagi?
Would you like to have some with me after school?"
And we ate enough for nine people.
The person working at the shop was flabbergasted.
I do remember that!
I still like ohagi,
but I can't eat as much anymore.
That's a nice memory.
It was cheap, and the portions were large and tasty.
Maybe that's why that shop closed?
Yeah.
Well, that's sad.
Oh, I hope you do well at tomorrow's competition.
Yes, I will!
See you.
Bye bye.
Wh-What?
Y-Yui-san's studying abroad?
Yes.
And she's leaving on a plane tomorrow.
S-Something so important...
Why?
Paper: Evaluation for Studying Abroad
Accepted
Why didn't she tell me?
Because you're not reliable.
That's true.
Yes, I'm not reliable.
But my love for her is boundless!
Love is useless.
That's a concise summary of a huge misunderstanding.
Y-Yeah.
My love is a huge misunderstanding.
What should I do?
You should know when to give up.
Just give up.
I never know when to give up.
Uh oh. I have a bad feeling.
Sign: Career
Guidance Office
How can I give up?
Ouch!
I am... reliable!
My love is... not a misunderstanding!
Do you get it, you moron?
Hey, does he know about this?
They're not talking to each other right now.
Well, they've sort of collapsed as a family.
On top of that,
tomorrow is Shinohara Izumi's archery competition.
Kondou promised he'd be there.
And where did you take those pictures?
From the garden of Kondou-kun's house, of course.
You even stoop to trespassing?!
Shame on you!
I'm starting to like this.
You...
Done!
Oh, Onii-chan, wait a second.
Wh-What?
Here you go!
What's this?
Share it with Izumi-san.
You're going to support her, right?
I hope she wins the title.
She'll win the title, right?
Yeah.
Goodbye... Onii-chan.
Red document: Japanese Passport
To be continued...
Preview
Episode 9
Following the Stream of Time . . .
Please watch
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking