It's been a long time since I've been able to relax like this.
Why don't you hit on me?!
I'd go anywhere if I could be with you!
Can't we walk together if we're living together?
Can't we hold hands, go to the movies, or eat lunch together?
Stop it, Yui! Can't you see you're bothering him?!
No! I'm going to say what I want!
Yui...
I wouldn't mind if you saw everything about me.
Hey, take a look.
I'm also growing up.
I know how you feel,
but I've been holding in my feelings for too long.
I don't mind if everyone talks about us.
I won't be scared if we're together.
Then, should I leave this house and live on my own?
In that case, we'd just be classmates.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, you idiot!
Classmates
The
Graduate
Chapter 3
Pool, Confession, and Acceptance!?
I'm here.
Did you have a fight with Ryuunosuke-kun?
No. I got angry by myself... and cried by myself.
Just like old times, huh?
Every time you fought with him,
you'd come over to my bathroom.
Sorry for showing up so suddenly.
I understand how you feel.
I'd also want to speak up and tell him...
that I'm no longer a child.
I wouldn't want him to look at me only through pictures.
It hurts me to say this,
but I have to apologize to him.
There's no way I could live by myself.
I can't imagine living without seeing his face every day.
That tickles, Yui-chan.
It reminds me of what Misako-san said.
Mom?
"Even if we don't do anything,
children still grow up by themselves."
You're becoming more mature.
Gee, stop teasing me.
On New Year's Day, I had a big fight with Onii-chan.
At that point, Senpai's love affair was at a turning point.
Wow! It's cute!
Doesn't it look strange?
Senpai will be pleased.
I haven't worn this kind of clothing for a while, so it makes me nervous.
But...
I want Sanshirou-san to see a different side of me.
That's not good, Miyuki-san!
If you wear a miniskirt,
you have to wear cute underwear that you won't mind being seen.
I-Is that so?
Ah! This might be good!
But actually, I think pink suits you better.
Ah! This is cute!
Have you been waiting long?
Oh, my!
Your face is a bit...
Do you have a fever?
I-It's because of the cold weather.
It's my fault for making you wait so long.
Do you feel warmer now?
Sanshirou-san, let's take a stroll and talk.
Sure! I love taking walks!
Senpai!
Your shoelace.
Let me help you.
I'm good at tying bow knots.
Th-Thanks.
Say, Senpai.
Once there were a sculptor and a critic.
The sculptor believed in his talent.
He spent long hours perfecting his work.
For the sake of his criticism, the critic kept on
studying sculpture day and night.
There! That won't come loose.
Th-Thanks.
It's not a matter of which of them is better.
I want you to be a sculptor who believes in himself and does his best.
A sculptor?
Just kidding. All these words are actually from Katagiri-sensei.
Even the best critic can't know the true essence of sculpture.
Should we go?
Y-Yes.
Do your best, Senpai!
Oh, no! I was supposed to meet Izumi-chan!
The man... who assaulted me in the park... the other day... was actually...
someone I dated before.
I was born into a strict family.
That's why I admired guys like him.
They look like hooligans, they're good at fighting,
and they're kind to girls.
At the time, I considered him to be the ideal boyfriend.
But he ignored my feelings, and that confused me.
I began to think that his habitual kindness was just a front.
So that's why you asked me that question.
Why are you kind to me?
That's vulgar.
A one-piece makes you look like you have no waist.
They're at it again.
If possible, I don't want her to involve me in that.
Thank you for accompanying me despite my selfish demands.
It's all right.
But don't force yourself.
When summer comes,
you'll be able to swim in the real sea.
Katagiri-sensei!
Oh, Yui-san.
That's because...
If you want to be the protagonist,
you need to have courage and the ability to take action.
I want you to be a sculptor who believes in himself and does his best.
Miyuki-san, I...
Yo, Miyuki.
Yousuke-san.
Yousuke, who's that?
Come with me, Miyuki.
Hey, Yousuke!
Ah! You can go home.
Let me go! I don't want to!
Miyuki-san!
You're still wearing kids' underwear.
Wouldn't you be better off
if I taught you a few things?
Mind your own business!
Y-You! Don't be rude to her!
Don't interfere!
Sanshirou-san!
I said it before, didn't I?
Losers shouldn't try protecting women in order to show off.
Let's go, Miyuki.
P-Please wait!
What are you doing?
I'm asking, what are you doing?!
Get up!
Please don't lay a hand on Miyuki-san!
You...
I beg you.
Stop it!
I love Miyuki-san!
That's why I don't want her to get hurt!
I beg you. Stop this!
Don't you have any pride?
Stay out of this!
Let's go back!
Hey, Yousuke!
Please get up now. They've gone.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
You have nothing to apologize for, Miyuki-san.
I'm really bad at fighting,
so that's the only tactic I could think of.
Is what you said true?
That you love me?
It's no lie.
But!
I'm...
I'm not worthy to love anyone.
Actually, she's in the same year.
But as soon as she was accepted, she fell sick.
Then, will she be our kouhai?
What's the matter? Aren't you going to take a shower?
She hasn't gotten used to it.
The nurses took care of her when she was hospitalized.
She feels uncomfortable on her own.
Come with me, Sakurako-san.
Come on.
Let's take a shower together.
Isn't this a school swimsuit?
I've been hospitalized a lot, so I don't have any other.
You're Narusawa-senpai, right?
Y-Yes, and?
You live with Ryuunosuke-senpai, right?
I won't lose to you!
Who was that?
If I'm correct,
she's Tsuzuki Kozue, a first-year student.
Apparently Ryuunosuke-kun is very popular.
I've always dreamed of going to school in this uniform.
Then your dream will soon come true.
I also want another dream of mine to come true.
What's that?
N-Nothing!
I-It's very short, isn't it?
You have to be careful, right?
I've never given it much thought, actually.
Some girls wear bloomers or spats underneath.
You're not concerned?
It bothers me a bit when some old lecher looks at me.
Yui, call for you.
All right!
Sorry I can't escort you.
It's all right. I can go back by myself.
Well, I have to hurry. Bye-bye.
I don't know if you need help or anything.
You seem to be waiting for someone.
I'm the same. That's how I know.
Waiting isn't good enough, is it?
For us.
I felt different when I was with Yousuke-san.
My heart is still beating hard.
I won't forget this night for the rest of my life.
Sometimes, I wish I could make myself small.
Then I'd fit inside your pocket.
We could be together whenever we wanted.
It wasn't a dream, was it?
All right! I'll go to school tomorrow and clean Onii-chan's desk!
Tell me if you want to turn off the lights.
Don't you want to ask me something?
I think you don't want to be asked.
I've hurt Sanshirou-san's heart.
I don't know what to do.
Y-Yui-san?
Please don't move.
W-Wait.
What's going on?
Please feel me.
Is my heart beating wildly?
It's because something very good happened.
This throbbing happens once in a lifetime.
It's good to fall in love.
I hope you get to feel this way as well.
Yui-san...
I wonder if he'll like it?
I wonder if he'll think I'm targeting him by wearing a matching set.
Sorry I'm late, Tomomi-kun.
I-I didn't see anything!
Actually I did, but I'll forget about it immediately!
Senpai!
Yes?
Do you think I'm poorly built?
Um, well, that's not true at all.
You're very...
And my lingerie?
I-I think it looks cute.
Really?
Of course!
At the hot springs, you helped me find my courage.
That's why I've decided to face him squarely.
That's why...
I'm wearing this "Lucky Underwear."
Lucky Underwear?
S-Sorry!
Anyway, please wait a moment.
Yeah.
Still, I'm pleased.
Tomomi-kun is over her troubles, apparently.
In contrast, I...
You look unhappy.
Y-You're...
Are you going to give up just like that?
You definitely didn't look cool back there.
But even so,
it's not for you to decide whether you're worthy.
This is my last magic trick.
Think of this temp job as a way of diverting yourself.
I'll be waiting at 7 PM.
Is something the matter, Sensei?
Your piano playing was different from your usual style.
It was intense but warm.
I-It was?
What's more, your appearance is different too.
Even your scent is different. I see! It's Yui-chan's.
Th-That's just your imagination.
I've been waiting for you.
At 7:00 pm
Make SURE you come!
Book store → Genya
Gokurakuyu
HERE!
This is good
Cake Shop
Toy Store
Don't be late!!
At 7:00 pm
Make SURE you come!
Book store → Genya
Gokurakuyu
HERE!
This is good
Cake Shop
Toy Store
Don't be late!!
At 7:00 pm
Make SURE you come!
Book store → Genya
Gokurakuyu
HERE!
This is good
Cake Shop
Toy Store
Don't be late!!
At 7:00 pm
Make SURE you come!
Book store → Genya
Gokurakuyu
HERE!
This is good
Cake Shop
Toy Store
Don't be late!!
At 7:00 pm
Make SURE you come!
Book store → Genya
Gokurakuyu
HERE!
This is good
Cake Shop
Toy Store
Don't be late!!
At 7:00 pm
Make SURE you come!
Book store → Genya
Gokurakuyu
HERE!
This is good
Cake Shop
Toy Store
Don't be late!!
At 7:00 pm
Make SURE you come!
Book store → Genya
Gokurakuyu
HERE!
This is good
Cake Shop
Toy Store
Goku ra kuyu
Do not enter
Did she wanted me to cheer up by watching naked women?
Women's
Bath
Three! You can keep the change.
I'll pay for myself!
So this is the public bath, huh?
Wh-Why are Miyuki-san and Karen-kun here?!
Oh no, I'm out of shampoo.
You can't get in if you don't take them off.
If you need to talk, here will do fine.
I don't want to talk.
I just want to know something.
What kind of woman did Yousuke-kun once love?
Excuse me!
Yes?
S-Senpai?!
Aren't you comfortable with getting naked?
That's right! I didn't bring anything here!
I don't think your purpose was to look at naked women, was it?
N-No. I don't even know myself!
Excuse me!
Sanshirou-san—
I thought you'd slept with
Yousuke-kun at least once.
But your attitude shows that
you're completely inexperienced.
I-It's none of your business!
That took the wind out of my sails.
You can go back if you want to.
P-Please wait up!
But this is strange.
The bath suddenly ran out of water.
Everything was fine this morning.
I haven't finish talking yet!
You're really persistent, aren't you?
I told you that there's nothing left to say, right?
Can I sit here?
There are other places, you know!
Oh, does it bother you if I sit next to you?
Karen-chan!
Yui-chan!
What do you mean?!
I heard what you said to Yousuke.
"If you want to be my lover,
you'd better look only at me.
Don't force me to follow in your footsteps."
You seem to consider Yousuke to be the bad guy,
but did you even try?
Did you even try to understand him?
Just wanting to be in love is like playing house.
Any man who dates you will end up getting hurt.
I've said this because
I pity that kneeling guy.
You'd better not get close to Yousuke anymore.
A girl like you would even bother the neighbors.
Miyuki-san...
I wonder what's going to happen.
I'm not sure, but it can't be good.
What do you mean?
Take a look.
Please wait!
What you said about me and Yousuke-san might be right.
But...
my relationship with
Sanshirou-san is different!
Are you an idiot? That has nothing to do with me.
Anyway...
that's your problem.
S-Sanshirou-san.
Miyuki... -san.
Sanshirou-san, I...
Can you see me?
My breasts aren't very big.
I feel a bit fat.
Still, I'm trying my best to lose weight!
My biggest worry is my wide hips.
Nonetheless, this is the real me!
I want you to know more about me!
I want to repay you with my real self, for the courage you showed.
I want to know you better, and I want to fall for you!
Miyuki-san...
I might've been kind to you just because I wanted you to look my way.
I can't be sure if I can be kind to someone...
I don't really love.
Even so, I know you can!
Miyuki-san...
I hope things go well for Senpai and Miyuki-san.
They'll be fine.
In this city,
there's a god who supports people in love.
This is the first time I've seen you remove your ribbon.
My wish came true, after all.
You have beautiful hair.
I'd probably be jealous of anyone else.
I'm already his girlfriend.
The one I love told me there's someone else.
But I'm pretty bad at giving up!
That includes you, of course.
B-By the way,
Senpai asked me a very strange question.
He asked me, "What is Lucky Underwear?"
What did he mean by that?
hajimete no date no hi no asa wa
On the morning of our first date,
kagami no mae de nankai mo
in front of the mirror,
fuku kigaete bakari zutto kimaranakute
I indecisively kept changing my clothes.
anata wo sanjuppun matasete ita
I made you wait half an hour longer.
itsumo wa fuzakete asonde iru no ni
Usually we joke around,
anata to te wo tsunaide arukeba
but just holding hands and walking together
sore dake de ureshikute
made me happy.
keredo hazukashikute
Still, it was embarrassing too,
zutto anata no kao mirenaino
so I couldn't look at your face.
itsumademo
I wish
toki wo wasurete iraretara
this moment would last forever.
kono mama aoi sora wo
I wish we could watch the blue sky,
futari nagamete iraretara
just like this, together.
todoku kana
I wish
anata e no afureru kimochi
my overflowing feelings would reach you.
sono mama tsutaetai
I'd just like to tell you
konna ni anata ga suki dakara
that I love you so much.
Translation: ElyasRay
Translation Check: anon
Timing, Editing: Collectr
QC: CP,Saji
Raw: DestroyKing