Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Episode 3
Summer, Separation, and . . .
Geshikougen
Blue sign: Pension Peppermint
Black sign: Guesthouse Iwakawaya
Stop!
Here!
Thank you very much.
Lovely...
More! Louder!
This is no different than being in school!
Why do we have to stay in the same place as the Judo and Tennis Clubs?
Don't complain to me.
Mom made the reservations.
Forget about that. Let's take a swim in the pool.
The pool?
I'll go to the pool after I take a nap.
What? That's boring.
Why don't you go alone?!
See you later.
Why is he so mad?
Oh, I see. Maybe it's because his father has postponed coming back.
His father was supposed to come with us on this trip.
Onii-chan is quite naive.
That was close.
I'm at a resort. It'd be a drag if I had a chaperone with me.
I have to enjoy this summer without my father as much as possible.
It's summer.
Teenage summer. A wild summer!
Nothing is better than swimsuits in the summer.
That's a hot girl. A good chance for a photo.
Looking good...
She's got gorgeous boobs.
That's not cool.
She's slender, and her figure's good too.
She looks like I did when I was young.
She must be trying to recover from a break-up.
So we have something in common.
Cheers to loneliness.
This is quite an elegant garden and building.
I chose carefully, as you requested.
This guest house is popular among commoners.
Gramps.
Yes?
You should call it a "pension."
Gramps, cancel my reservation.
Of course. Would you like to go back to your villa?
Yeah.
W-Wait!
That's... Yui-san.
And she's in her swimsuit.
Young master, you are drooling.
Young master, your nose is bleeding.
I followed the Tennis Club, and I get to see Narusawa Yui. This is great.
Don't photograph Yui-san's sacred figure
in her swimsuit!
What?!
That was Kondou Makoto.
Why is he here too?!
Ouch.
You again?
Beige?
Ouch...
What are you doing?
Ah, beige.
You brat!
How long are you going to lie on me?
Thank you for bumping into me twice.
Are you interested in me?
I'm not interested in some old lady.
You know nothing about women.
What?
What? You want to hit me?
Come on and try it.
I wouldn't hit a woman.
What a show-off.
Women aren't always weak.
Would you like to make a bet?
What's your favorite sport?
My favorite sport is sex!
What about tennis?
Penis?
Idiot.
A joke, just a joke.
All right. I'll play a match with you.
Yui.
What's wrong, Onii-chan? Why are you shouting?
Onii-chan?
Shut up. It's none of your business.
What happened?
Did Onii-chan do something rude to you?
You don't have to worry.
I'm just going to play a tennis match against your brother.
A tennis match?
Shut up. Don't follow me around like a chaperone.
Let's go.
Your brother is short-tempered. That was harsh.
It's fine. He's always like that.
I'm used to it.
Well then, I'm going to play a match against him.
Do your best!
Beat the crap out of Onii-chan!
It's a three-set match.
We'll use a tie-break system.
Okay with me.
I'm Tanaka Misa. I'm going to beat you.
I'm Kondou Makoto. Come on!
That's her real underwear.
I'm not going to lose.
Me either!
Upsy-daisy.
I lost.
Um, what?
Nothing.
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
This stinks of sweat.
Of course. I used it to wipe my sweat.
What's wrong?
I said, it's nothing.
Because I lost, let me treat you to lunch.
What would you like?
Western? Japanese? Chinese?
I'm not hungry yet.
I see.
Then...
Why don't we go to that amusement park?
Yeah.
Sure.
All right. Let's shower off and meet here again in twenty minutes.
Don't be late. See you.
Why was she crying?
Yui, why don't you go swimming as well?
It feels nice.
It's been a while since I've been in a real summer mood.
That's unusual for you.
Yui, that's alcohol.
Sign: Drinking under 20 is illegal.
I know.
Really? But that's mine.
Are you Yui-san's elder sister?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yui-san's classmate.
My name is Saionji Aritomo.
Elder sister?
Nice to meet you.
I didn't know that Yui-san had such a beautiful sister.
My!
I have a villa near here.
Would you like to have dinner with me?
Yui-san can come too, of course.
That's nice. Right, Yui?
This tastes good.
Are you all right?
So you really don't like roller coasters.
Yeah.
But I'm fine.
I wanted to get over something.
Huh?
A little misunderstanding,
a casual remark...
You can't get over this guy?
I don't know.
So your boyfriend looks like me.
Is it a coincidence that we met here again?
Maybe.
Perhaps... it was fate.
I see.
Then I'll be waiting in my room with a bottle of champagne.
I hope dinner will be nice.
It will be.
You can bring your sister too.
I forgot Misako-san was here too.
Yes. They both went somewhere.
Note: We were invited to Saionji's villa. Why don't you come join us? (Yui is with me.) Misako
There's a message for you.
What? They went to Aritomo's villa.
Who'd want to go there?
What's wrong?
As you can see.
I guess we can enjoy our dinner all by ourselves.
It was a splendid dinner.
I'm glad that you liked it.
We recruited a master chef from the Grand Imperial Hotel.
I'll take this young lady to her room.
Oh, let her be.
She just drank something unfamiliar.
As you wish.
So that was Yui-san's first time drinking alcohol. Unexpected.
Misako-san, the stars are beautiful.
Let me show you around the garden.
This is going to be a lovely night.
A-A lovely night... Her smile...
This might be...
Peace.
Wh-Why are you here?!
He said that he is a classmate of yours
and is willing to take a
commemorative photo.
What? Dinner is over? I missed it.
You bastard, why don't you go home?
Your attitude and words
Who do you think you are?
are rather harsh.
Oh, great. I get to see Yui-san's...
Oh, my!
You took that photo of Yui and me.
Nice to see you.
Oh, is Yui-chan asleep?
Her sleeping face...
Stop it.
Yoshiki-kun, I'm going to show Yui-san's sister around the garden.
Sister?
So could you leave now?
Ouch.
I'm thirsty. Mom, I want some water.
Are you all right, Yui-san?
Mom, water.
Mom, water...
Why don't you go get some yourself?
Men don't like drunk girls.
Mom, you're mean.
Mom?
Oh? He's confused.
I should snap Yui-chan's sleeping face now.
A good chance for a photo!
She's Yui's mom?
I thought he was kind of a city boy, but he's rather wild.
Oh, wild men...
Such a wild guy...
Onii-chan, you idiot.
Her mom?
The stars are beautiful.
Yeah. I can't believe I can see so many stars.
There are as many stars as there are people.
And every person is one of those stars.
Which is my star?
Hey, when's your birthday?
March 29th.
Aries. Our affinity should be pretty good.
What about you?
November 27th, Sagittarius.
Not too bad, huh?
What about your ex-boyfriend?
A Leo.
So you two should've gotten along well.
Idiot!
Yeah, I'm an idiot.
You're jealous.
Yeah.
So I'm the substitute for this boyfriend who looks like me and should be...
very compatible.
That's not nice.
Stop treating me like a child.
You're a brat.
First you're sulky, then you get angry.
I'm not a child!
Men who don't understand
women's feelings are children.
What?
Get out of here!
Misa.
Get out!
I won't leave you alone.
You don't look like him.
He looks like you.
Misa.
Makoto-kun...
They're not beige.
I'm not wearing anything.
So when you were at the amusement park...
You were already interested in me at that point.
Misa...
Your pendant is hurting me.
I lost to you in the tennis match,
so I'll be your slave today.
Then kneel before me.
It's big.
Is it bigger than your ex's?
You're mean. Don't talk about my past.
That feels good, Misa.
This is embarrassing.
Let me look at yours this time.
No. Stop it.
How is this? Is it good?
Misa.
You're cute.
That hurts.
I've only done this with one other guy.
Be gentle, please.
I've never experienced anything like this.
No, I'm coming. I'm coming!
Me too. On, no!
It's a safe day.
You can come inside me.
All right.
That's good.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
I'm coming!
The stars are beautiful.
Oh, yes!
Hey, Makoto.
Why don't we go to the pool and take a swim?
Did you say something?
Would you like to have another round?
Idiot.
What did you say?
Is it okay for you not to return to your room?
Why?
Won't your sister worry?
It's all right. Let them be.
She's a nice sister. She cares about her brother.
She's not my sister.
She just lives with me.
I see.
So she loves you.
What? Did you say something?
No. Nothing.
Yes?
This is Misa, right?
Hello? I heard that you were at this hotel.
Hello? Misa! It was my fault.
Misa! Hey, Misa!
Misa.
And this is how my summer love affair ended.
I slept well.
Anyhow, Yui is late.
Onii-chan, you'll annoy everyone else if you stay inside the library.
Please wait outside.
Please. I'll treat you to taiyaki afterwards.
Note: Taiyaki are fish-shaped pancakes filled with bean jam.
You asked me so nicely, and what did I get?
A paper airplane?
What the... Isn't this a prescription?
Yasohachi Community Hospital. Sugimoto Sakurako.
Sakurako-chan?
How are you feeling?
I feel good today.
Right, Turbo?
I don't want you to catch a cold,
so I'll close the window, okay?
Sure.
I think I heard a bird chirp.
Whatever.
Onii-chan.
What are you doing here?
Because you were late, I caught a cold.
Are you all right?
I was joking.
Onii-chan, you liar!
Well, it's already autumn.
To be continued...
totsuzen no ame ni furarete
Showered by a sudden rain
kasa mo sasazu ni aruita ra
Walking without putting up my umbrella
machi yuku hito ga henna kao shite mite ta
People in the street looked at me strangely
mada haru asai san gatsu no gogo
On an early spring afternoon,
tsumetai ame no sora miage
I looked up at the sky in the cold rain
odoritaku naru youna kibun de aruita
I walked with an urge to dance
arifureta nichijyou ni itsuka kokoro ga kumotte ta
My heart was clouded by the familiar days
sonna koto sae kizukazu ni ita
I didn't understand anything
keredo
But...
honno sasayakana nandemo nai youna yuuki dakeredo
It was a small piece of courage, almost like nothing
sonna koto de naze ka sukoshi kokoro ga hareta
I don't know why, but it brightened my heart a bit
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking