Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
My mom had just died.
That's when we first met each other.
Yui...
and me.
Episode 9
Following the Stream of Time . . .
Paper: Evaluation for Studying Abroad
Accepted
Narusawa.
Izumi-san. Do you still like ohagi?
Y-Yeah. Why?
Do you remember when I transferred here? I was so nervous.
You were the first person who spoke to me.
Oh, was I?
It made me feel better.
That time, you asked me...
"Do you like ohagi?
Would you like to have some with me after school?"
And we ate enough for nine people.
The person working at the shop was flabbergasted.
I do remember that!
I still like ohagi,
but I can't eat as much anymore.
That's a nice memory.
It was cheap, and the portions were large and tasty.
Maybe that's why that shop closed.
Yeah.
Well, that's sad.
Oh, I hope you do well at tomorrow's competition.
Yes, I will!
See you.
Bye bye.
Done!
Oh, Onii-chan, wait a second.
What?
Here you go.
What's this?
Share it with Izumi-san.
You're going to support her, right?
I hope she wins the title.
She'll win the title, right?
Yeah.
Goodbye... Onii-chan.
Red document: Japanese Passport
Kondou
Narusawa
Yui-san!
To Onii-chan
She's not answering the phone.
And if she's not at home,
I have to assume that she's already left for the airport.
All right.
Why?
Why did you leave without telling me?
I will...
I, Saionji Aritomo, will catch up with you.
Please wait for me, Yui-san!
Sign: 1998 National Archery Championship
Shinohara Izumi-san from Yasohachi Academy.
Right and justice
Martial training
A good chance for a photo!
Intense photos...
Ladies and gentlemen,
Elf Airline announces that flight 753 to Seoul is now boarding
at gate 13. Thank you.
Sign: Under Construction
Why are they repairing a perfectly good road?
Hey, say something!
And my mobile phone has no signal.
What is Gramps doing?
Argh!
Stop the construction already!
Don't you know who I am? I'm Saionji Aritomo!
Awesome.
Gee... I can't stand this.
Yui-san's flight is...
leaving.
There's no word from Gramps.
Oh, Lord...
Did I do something bad?
Yui-san!
I can't hold it anymore.
The championship goes to Shinohara Izumi-san of Yasohachi Academy.
Banner: National Archery Championship
That's all.
Hey...
Please let me through.
Shinohara-san, a bit more!
Let me take one more picture.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
What's that?
Yui made it.
Narusawa?
Thank you for your patience.
We will be taking off in 30 minutes.
Card: Congratulations on your victory
Narusawa...
She believed I was going to win the title.
Yeah.
Delicious!
It's like the ones from that shop.
Did Narusawa make those ohagi?
They look yummy.
I'm digging in!
Wonderful.
What are you doing? Yui made them!
Why are you eating them, you bastard?!
It's time for Narusawa's plane to depart.
Plane?
What are you talking about?
I-I was told not to say anything.
That was refreshing.
Oh? The traffic jam has cleared up.
Hurry!
If I hurry, I might get there in time.
If we pick up a taxi,
we might get there in time!
Th-This is bad.
Hey, snob!
N-Nice to see you here.
Shut up and drive the car.
What are you doing? Hey!
Come on!
You were in just the right place. Drive the car, Aritomo!
Wh-Where to?
Don't play dumb.
The airport that Narusawa's flight is departing from.
A-Airport?
You really don't know when to give up.
Everyone knows about it.
You spilled the beans, didn't you?!
Shut up and drive.
A-All right.
What are you doing? Pass it!
I can't.
This road is too narrow.
What if a car's coming the other way?
You can dodge it. Just pass.
Okay.
You're quite good at driving.
What? The traffic's all jammed up!
What should we do?
Let me see.
Oh, that road.
How do you know about this shortcut?!
It's a haven for couples.
You peeping Tom.
You idiot!
Everyone to one side.
No way!
This is...
...bad luck!
I can see the airport.
The bridge is up!
Jump it!
Go!
Goodbye, Onii-chan.
Don't go, Yui!
I love you! I love you so much!
Young master! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Kondou.
Never, ever give up...
until the very end!
Go, Gramps! Send that indecisive boy to his girlfriend!
Understood, young master.
Punching him made me feel better.
That was quite cool.
I've changed my opinion of you.
Me too.
You snob.
Hey, what's that?
What is that?
Onii-chan!
For safety reasons,
we're going to return to Tsukumo Airport.
For safety,
we are going back to the airport.
Excuse me. Please let me through.
Excuse me!
Yui!
Onii-chan. Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
Yui. Yui!
Onii-chan. Onii-chan!
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking
The thing is, there are other stories about Onii-chan and me.
The summer before I transferred to Yasohachi Academy,
a girl named Katou Minori-chan was always beside him.
Doukyuusei 2, episode 10:
Encounter and...
Please watch.
Episode 10
Encounter and . . .