Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Don't go, Yui!
I love you! I love you so much!
Young master! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Kondou.
Never, ever give up...
...until the very end!
Go, Gramps! Send that indecisive boy to his girlfriend!
Understood, young master!
Punching him made me feel better.
That was quite cool.
I've changed my opinion of you.
Me too.
You snob.
Episode 10
Encounter and . . .
I took it without thinking.
I'm not going to take any more. It'd just be a waste of film.
So that's how it is.
Everyone settles down and lives normally.
My, my.
Izumi-san, someone is talking about us.
I don't like that.
Really. I'm not interested in her anymore.
Shinohara Izumi
Maybe I should tuck this away too.
Narusawa Yui
Oh, this brings back good memories.
I took this when Narusawa came here to submit her transfer papers.
It's already been a year.
Transfer Notice
Name of student   Narusawa Yui
To the Headmaster of Yasohachi Academy
The student listed above has
my permission to transfer.
Shirobara Academy
School Master
Onii-chan will be surprised.
All right!
Principal's Office
Sure. Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to studying here.
All right! I'll be a Yasohachi Academy student starting next week.
Ouch...
Are you all right?
Yes.
So this vase was yours.
You're the person who's been arranging the flowers in my class.
Hey! Kondou Makoto! Where are you?!
This is bad.
Here you go.
He skipped cleaning duties again.
Where is he, that Kondou Makoto?
Katou Minori. What are you doing down there?
Have you seen Kondou?
Gee, he's quick at running away.
Maybe he left school to buy something again.
Oh, yes. Perhaps I should patrol the school grounds today.
I'm going to crack down on students who violate school regulations.
Wait for it, you regulation violators.
I'm starving.
Oh, a convenience store.
That's Yoshiki. What's he doing?
This is big news.
Oh, I'm busy.
He's as weird as always.
My stomach's rumbling.
Something to eat!
Grilled salmon and rice, fried beef and rice.
Rice balls, sandwiches, rice and curry.
Maybe this would be better.
I want this too.
Oh, a new product.
Which one should I eat?
Welcome.
Huh? I think I've heard that voice somewhere.
Sh-She's cute.
Hey.
Yes?
Thanks for shopping here.
I'm not buying all of them.
Oh? What did you say?
I'll take all of them.
I-I'm starving to death.
Kondou Makoto from Yasohachi Academy, are you here?
Wh-Who are you?
I'm Tendou Shinkansen, a PE teacher.
I'm the adviser to the Judo Club, and accordingly,
Armband: Guidance
I provide educational guidance at Yasohachi Academy.
I'm looking for Kondou Makoto, the problem child and ongoing disgrace of my school.
Well, I'm also cracking down on students
who work or buy stuff on their way home,
both of which violate school regulations.
If you see a student doing that, please contact me.
I'm counting on you, pants guy.
It's punk.
Kondou Makoto, where are you?!
Wow, that was close.
Why are you hiding too?
I-I'm not hiding.
I just hate guys from Yasohachi Academy.
Really...
I'm busy.
I'm starving. Is dinner ready, Yui?
It'll take a bit longer.
Hey, Yui, have you finished the application process?
Yes.
Someone left school suddenly,
and I can start attending next week.
Wow, that's great.
But are you really sure about not telling Makoto-san?
Yes. I'm going to surprise him this time.
Usually, he gets to surprise me.
I should try it.
Oh, I need to tell Onii-chan that dinner's ready.
He's probably starving too.
This is painful. I'm going to die.
Painful...
Onii-chan, dinner time. Come down.
D-Dinner? This is painful.
Onii-chan, are you all right? What did you do?
Yui, my stomach hurts.
Get me some medicine.
Wh-What is all this crap?
I can't believe it.
How could you eat so much before dinner?
I had my reasons.
What do you mean, "I had my reasons"?! Today is a special day.
I worked hard to prepare something nice.
You're horrible.
I won't give a damn about you anymore!
A special day? What did she mean?
This is painful.
Oh, my! The transfer student lives in the same house as Kondou.
I don't believe it.
I bet I can take advantage of this big scoop, right?
What? That's a Shirobara Academy uniform.
Why did you call me out during my valuable lunch break?
I have good news.
Stop it! That's disgusting!
Yuck.
Are you sure? It's a really good story.
It would be fair to trade.
I'll make you a judge in the next beauty contest
for promoting the Saionji classic car collection.
Here's a ticket.
This is what I was talking about. I really wanted this.
And...
She's a transfer student.
Trans-fer student.
She's from Shirobara Academy. At this time of year?
Maybe this cute girl has her reasons.
Give those to me already!
Oh, sh-she's cute.
Right?
When is she transferring here?
Next week.
Well, don't you want to know something special about her?
What's with that hand?
I also want tickets for the Saionji Young Beauty Contest.
I sense something scary.
How can you be so greedy?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
You ugly bastard.
This might cure my stiffness.
It feels good.
Take this!
Fly away!
Damn it.
I forgot to ask her name.
I'm falling.
I can see a flower garden. My...
What? A photo of Yui.
What's it doing here ?
Whoever did that is a terrible person.
Why don't you ask a teacher to help you fix it?
I-It's all right.
What are those two doing?
Katou Minori, with her thick glasses, whom I rejected, and Kondou.
They make a perfect couple.
Soon I'm going to have a wonderful meeting.
I have to get her name and that special information from Yoshiki.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
There's dirt on your face!
Whatever.
No. What do you want?
Stay away from me.
Are you sure? What if I tell Tendou Shinkansen...
that you're violating school regulations by working?
This clearly shows you changing.
Stop it.
You won't lose anything.
I just want to take some upskirt photos of you in a Yasohachi Academy uniform,
without your glasses.
It's for art. Right?
Come on.
No.
I'm going to tell on you.
S-Stop it, please!
Are you going to be all right?
This is good.
Yes, that's it.
Take your glasses off.
O-Otherwise, I'll tell.
A good chance for a photo!
What are you doing?
Kondou! Wh-Why?
You peeping Tom!
What's wrong? Why didn't you resist?
Don't ask me.
Why do you care about me?
Men only care about a girl's appearance.
That's not true.
Liar. You're lying.
You're the same as all the others.
I'm not lying.
So let's go on a date next Sunday.
Okay.
I can finally attend the same school as Onii-chan.
I should've done this sooner.
Um...
Caption: Hot Now!
That will be 1500 yen.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean by that?
I was just passing by and saw you.
Why are you so mad?
I'm not mad.
There are a lot of weirdos around.
You should be careful on your way home.
Yes, and you should go straight home and not buy stuff.
I'll make a nice dinner and wait for you.
All right. I'm looking forward to it.
See you.
Yeah.
So you are popular.
Does it matter?
Not at all.
I have this ticket.
Would you like to go to a movie with me tomorrow?
You hate guys from Yasohachi Academy, don't you?
I won't mind if you don't want to go.
It's not that I don't want to go.
Then let's go on a date next Sunday.
Okay.
Thanks for asking me.
But I have an important appointment tomorrow.
Huh?
I see.
Later, then.
So I wasn't wrong.
This is really fun.
I think it will make a good memory.
Memory?
Yes. I'm going to change myself.
Huh?
My uncle swindled my dad, and he had to shoulder my uncle's debts.
Dad left our house, saying, "I have to clear this debt."
He left Mom and me behind.
I've been working, in violation of school regulations, to support Mom.
So Yoshiki found out and did that.
Yes.
I couldn't believe in others until now.
But Dad has contacted us.
He's finally making progress in his business.
He may be able to clear the debt.
He said he can come back home.
I confessed my love to Saionji-kun.
But he rejected me.
He said, "Only beautiful girls are suitable for me."
That's just what he would say.
Aren't all men like that?
I'm not, at least.
You're...
Would you like to go to a movie with me tomorrow?
You say men shouldn't judge by appearance,
but you use it to your advantage.
I can't forgive you!
Goodbye!
I'm sorry.
I just...
I just wanted to make sure of your feelings.
You touched my heart because you took good care of the flowers.
But now you've trampled on my feelings.
I'm sorry.
I was scared of trusting others.
I was scared of trusting the feelings of others.
I like flowers because they won't betray me.
A while ago, you said you wanted to change yourself, right?
Now...
don't cry.
Let my first time be a good memory.
Yui woke me up earlier than usual.
I'm sleepy.
Good morning, Minori-chan.
Kondou-kun, thank you.
I'll try to live a better life by changing, starting today.
I hope you'll be a good classmate to me.
Classmate?
Is that Katou Minori?
Hey, I thought it was a transfer student,
but it's Katou Minori!
She's cute without those glasses.
She looks cheerful.
I feel like I screwed up.
No. I shouldn't look back.
I have a bright future.
Quiet. Take your seats.
I'd like to introduce a transfer student.
Please come in.
As a classmate, huh?
Please introduce yourself.
Sure.
I'm Narusawa Yui. Nice to meet you.
N-Narusawa Yui-san.
You're even cuter than your photo.
Onii-chan...
Y-Yui. Why?
To be continued...
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking
Preview
Episode 11
Dream and . . .
Please watch