Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
I...
can't beat Izumi-san.
She's so dedicated.
What are you saying?!
You're better than anyone else!
No. You don't need to be better.
I, Saionji Aritomo...
Aritomo...
Y-Yui-san...
Yui-san.
Stupid jerk. Stupid jerk!
Stupid jerk!
I hate you, Onii-chan.
Ikeda
Family
Inoue
Ikeda
Family
Inoue
Ikeda
Family
Inoue
Ikeda
Family
Inoue
Nakahara
Family
Yui... -san.
Ikeda
Family
Yui-san!
Onii-chan, you're a stupid jerk.
Stupid jerk. Stupid jerk.
Episode 7
Goodbye . . .  Forever . . .
It's hot.
Are you going?
Yeah.
Our last... summer here.
Huh?
Next spring, our village will be...
underwater.
Was I dreaming?
Such pleasant old memories.
Yes, it's been nineteen years since then.
I didn't know this hot spring had mixed bathing.
I'm damn lucky.
Oops, my glasses have fogged up.
A-A good...
ch-ch-cha... Nippon cha-cha-cha-cha...
A good chance for a photo.
That's...
Y-Yui-san's mom!
How can you do that?
Don't you feel ashamed?
Is he stupid?
I-I can't forgive you!
Sign: Prohibited
It's suspended...
Your...
How?
Th-This is embarrassing!
One...
more.
I've... done...
it.
Izumi!
Hang in there, Izumi!
I've... done it.
Yeah. You did well.
I couldn't win the title, but...
Saionji-kun!
Saionji-kun. Hang in there.
Saionji-kun.
Y-Yui-san...
I glad you're... all right.
Saionji-kun! Saionji-kun!
It was good to drink sake and enjoy the snowscape.
Oh my, Yui isn't back yet?
I guess Saionji-kun is with her.
Why worry?
They aren't children anymore.
Snow...
Unless you climb Mt. Kilimanjaro,
you won't be able to see it, right?
What's wrong?
Makoto, I'm freezing.
What?
I suppose that's because you were outside for all that time.
Do you mean when I was shooting arrows?
No, long before that.
Since I did my cold water ablutions at the waterfall?
Yes.
You're horrible.
You were beautiful.
Showering under the waterfall in the moonlight.
Shooting arrows behind the fire from the torches.
You were very beautiful.
Treasure
every
meeting
Treasure
every
meeting
Treasure
every
meeting
Makoto, why don't you take a bath?
I'll go later.
I suppose you're tired.
Or would you like to bathe with me?
Idiot.
Hey, Izumi.
Have you always held your training camp here?
Hey.
Izumi?
Izumi!
Hey! Izu...
Treasure
every
meeting
Treasure
every
meeting
It will
never
recur
It will
never
recur
I saw... your...
You watched me doing my cold water ablutions.
That was payback.
Pay-ba-ck.
Wh-What are you doing?
L-Let me go, Makoto!
You've returned to your usual self.
Makoto, do... I smell of... sweat?
No, not at all.
You smell good.
It's something you wanted to see.
Your...
That's not like what it looked like a while ago.
Yeah.
What about yours?
Hang in there.
Are you all right?
Hang in there, Saionji-kun.
I'm freezing.
Shut!
Wait a second. I'll make a fire.
I don't have any matches.
What should I do?
I-I'm freezing.
Mama.
A-kun... is sleepy.
Don't sleep.
You'll die, Saionji-kun.
Don't sleep!
A-kun is sleepy.
Wake up!
Please wake up, Saionji-kun!
Please...
Wake up, Saionji-kun.
Wake up, Saionji-kun!
Please.
You mustn't!
Wake up, Saionji-kun!
What should I do?
Saionji-kun?
No way.
Saionji-kun.
Wake up, Saionji-kun. Wake up!
Saionji-kun! Saionji-kun!
Ouch.
Mama, I won't be naughty!
Don't beat me.
I'm glad.
I thought you were going to die.
Yui-san.
Well, I've learned the shortcut to the lodge.
I'm lucky.
Well, I suppose that's because my behavior is habitually good.
A phone?
On a mountain where there's nothing?
It's coming from over there.
Has there been an accident?
This is bad!
Sign: Incoming call
Yes?
Oh, young master, it is I, your butler.
Since it has stopped snowing,
I was thinking of picking you up.
Butler? Could this be Aritomo's?
What? Reception is quite poor.
I can't hear you very well.
Thanks to the transmitter,
I know the location of the snowmobile.
I hope things went well with Ms. Narusawa.
Narusawa?
Is he with Yui?
Huh?
I can't hear you very well.
Anyway, I will pick you up by helicopter.
According to the navigation system,
there is a charcoal burner's lodge nearby.
Please wait there.
A charcoal burner's lodge?
Is that it?
Now, please don't cry.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan!
Why am I running?
I'm running away?
From what?
Yui's tears.
What... is this?
What... is this feeling?
Is it possible?
Do I...
love Yui?
To be continued...
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking
Episode 8
Spring for Everyone and . . .