Wataru...
Your eyes have been
following me, haven't they?
I've been thinking about you, too.
I love you! Take me!
Mai!
Aw shit!
Maybe it was only a dream... but I was
FINALLY going to make it with Mai!
Who the hell could it be?
I don't care what their excuse is...
Summer Vacation Rules! Totally Awesome!
Hello, Master Wataru is not in right now.
Call back in about 10 years.
Watura Morooka
Wataru, it's me! Kazuya!
Kazuya? Don't you know it's
summer vacation, you asshole!
Why are you calling me before noon?
Kazuya Sakagami
Sorry, but it's a matter of
life and death that we talk!
Tough luck. I'm already
on my way to see Mai.
Mai Sakuragi
Hey, chill out! Can we talk
after you do Mai?
Kenji Aihara
Okay, whatever! I've got to go!
Don't forget! Be at the station, 11:00!
Kurumi Nishina
Oh yeah, today's Kurumi's birthday!
No wonder he's so stressed out!
Production:
Pink Pineapple
Sakimake
Senior
High
Scool
Planning Producers:
Dr. Pochi
Yuta Amauti
Yoshiro Asaga
Originally created by
Masato Hiruda (elf)
Screenplay:
Yuhiro Tomita
Original Character
Concepts:
Masaki Takei
Character Design/Art Direction:
Ryunosuke Otonashi
Visual Art Director:
Masayoshi Kanemura
Director of Photography:
Mitsunobo Yoshida
Satomi Kurokawa
That's Satomi... What's she doing here?
Hey! Wataru!
What the..?
Ouch!
Wataru! Are you here to fantasize
about the girls again?
Misa Tanaka
Misa!
Music:
Tomas Unit
Sound Effects Direction:
Yasunori Honda
Staring at girls like that is
the sickest thing a man can do.
You're just jealous!
What?
Even if you ran your laps stark naked,
Misa, no one would watch...
...you're too pumped up...
like a bodybuilder.
I'll have you know the entire
track team calls me "Bambi"
for my grace and beauty!
Bambi, eh? That's a good one.
Wataru! Make sure you write her back!
Miho Suzuki
Write who?
Miho. And don't play any games
with her, she's naive enough
to actually care about you.
Executive Director:
Kenji Yoshimoto
Alright already!
I'm just too generous
with my affections.
Wataru!
See ya!
Jerk.
Misa is... such a tomboy.
Whereas Mai is so cute and feminine!
Whatever it takes, I'm going to
get her by the end of summer.
Show em what you got, Mai!
On your mark!
Wataru Morooka!
Get your filthy mind off of Mai!
Set!
Uh huh...
She's perfection, the Madonna of this
Educational Institution.
There's no way you could ever
measure up to her standards.
It's stupid to dream about
something you'll never have.
Forget about her, you'll only make
yourself miserable.
Kenji, where do you
get off saying shit like that?
I can say it because I'm more important
to Mai tnan you'll ever be.
What?
Well, you'll find out eventually.
What did he mean by all that?
I forgot!
Miho?
Yes, can I help you?
Wataru!
♥ Wataru! ♥
♥ ♥ Wataru! ♥ ♥
♥ ♥ ♥ Wataru! ♥ ♥ ♥
How's it going?
Well, actually...
Um, could you make me up about
thirty dollars worth of flowers?
A hundred dollars
would be even better!
Hey!
No problem!
You thief!
That's the price of being late.
Do you think I've worked my
ass off all summer to support YOU?
That money was...
To make a "wonderful summer
memory" with Mai, right?
Juggling girls is asking for trouble...
...and Mai is just a pampered,
simpering little ditz...
...who's utterly and completely
incompatible with you, anyway!
You'll only make yourself miserable.
Oh, sure! I haven't noticed you
scoring with Kurumi, either.
That's what this is all about!
Today's Kurumi's birthday.
This is my new plan of attack:
"Presents for Pussy"!
Thank you for waiting.
What do I owe?
Not much for such service!
Thanks.
And thank you, Wataru!
I'm borrowing your scooter!
Hey! Kazuya!
Excuse me...
Yes?
My letter... Have you read it?
Yes, I have. And...
Ta Dah!
Oh no, I'm so embarrassed!
I'm so embarrassed that I'm going to
have to send you a letter in reply!
Miho?
Kazuya, you're late.
I'm sorry. This is for you.
Happy birthday.
Oh, Kazuya! Thank you wery much!
It's beautiful.
But... wasn't it awfully expensive?
Maybe.
Then, I need to give you back
something...
That's more like it! How about
a kiss for starters?
What?
And then we can get on
to some serious sex!
Oh, you're such a kidder, Kazuya.
That was not a joke.
Greetings.
What's wrong, Wataru?
You butthead! You left me to die
out there in the sun, Kazuya!
Hello.
Good afternoon, Wataru!
Kurumi?
Yes?
Kazuya's into ropes and candles. Watch
yourself or you might get burned.
Sure!
But sometimes I like to play
around with candles too!
I'm beat.
What can I get you?
Well, uh...
You know, women don't like men
who can't make up their mind.
Order up.
Right!
In her usual bitchy mood, I see.
Say, Master...
I know she's related to you, but I can't
believe you let Satomi work here.
Given my lifestyle, she's as close to a
daughter as I'm ever likely to have.
She really does try. Eventually, I'd like
her to take over the restaurant.
Master, if you put Satomi
at the helm, this place will sink
like a ship full of bricks.
Oh shit!
That's enough!
You heard?
Each and every word.
What a bitch! She just can't wait
to pick a fight with me!
Wataru... You like that Mai, don't you?
Yep. She's the one.
I see.
You've got your work
cut out for you, then.
I mean, doesn't she like that Kenji guy?
Oh, that jerk's nothing special to her.
I see.
But why are you asking?
No reason.
Oh, right.
So, what were you doing
at the school this morning?
Nothing.
Oh, I get it. You're jealous
about me and Mai.
Asshole!
I've got to make something happen,
before I lose my chance.
Mai!
Here!
Thank you very much.
Oh.
Do you like that kind of book?
Do you come here often?
Sometimes. For my exams.
Hey, let's go out on a date!
What?
C'mon! You need a break!
But... I have to go to my club...
...then there's my piano class...
And other things...
I'm sorry.
Mai?
Was that a no?
I'm dying! God give me strength!
Kazuya!
Listen, please.
Kurumi did... Kurumi didn't...
Man, I'm tired! Kazuya's whining
kept me up half the night.
And worse, I'm not sure leaving her
at the hotel like that was justified,
just because she said no...
What the...?
Looks like someone beat me here.
Huh?
Satomi!
Kenji and Mai!
I'm going to get her!
Get who?
Wataru, come with me.
What? Your parents told you
not to run anymore?
Yeah. They want me to quit
the track club and concentrate
on my college exams.
Well, this is your last year of high
school, after all... I can understand that.
Then again, maybe they think
that if you quit the team
you'd become more feminine.
Wataru, I'm serious about this.
You are so lucky. All it takes to make
you happy is a girl to chase.
Well, excuse me!
Wataru, can you imagine what it would
be like for me, not running anymore?
I started when I was in 6th grade, and
I've got one chance left at the nationals.
I've got to keep running.
Until the nationals.
Then go for it!
Keep on running. Don't worry
about what they say.
Wataru.
You've got to do what's right for you!
You're right!
Thanks, Wataru!
A "Thank You" from HER mouth?
Now THAT'S weird.
Why does this always happen to me?
"Dear Wataru, this is so embarrassing,
but I'm going to write it anyway."
"Could you please take... please take
Miho to a movie... please?"
"I would like to see something with a
love story. I'll be waiting for your reply."
Miho could you tone it down a little?
I'm sorry...
Shut the hell up!          Get out of here!
Wataru!
What the hell did you do to Miho?
What... well... uh...
Miho was crying her head off
when she called me last night!
What did you DO to her?
Well... you see...
Actually, when you think about it, I'm
the one who should be crying...
Hey. You're thinking more of your
perverted thoughts, aren't you?
What?
Listen, Wataru.
Miho is not the kind of tramp
you normally go out with.
If you make her cry again
you're going to answer to me!
Out of all the girls around
here, isn't there one you
really find the most attractive?
Well... I...
Which one?
Actually...
It's you, Misa.
You're the prettiest, Misa.
You jerk!!!
What's her problem?
Mai, bye bye!
Bye Bye!
Come have chocolate patties with us.
Sorry. See you next time.
Is it true you're going out with Kenji?
I guess it's true...
Don't say things like that. It's not true.
Really?!?
That's fantastic!
All a man needs is
the proper disposition
and his strength of character!
Things like money and status don't
matter, isn't that correct, Lady Mai?
Wataru is forged of character!
Is that from a novel...?
"He leapt over the dying flames, then,
the final barrier behind him..."
"...he stood at last, Body and Soul,
beside her."
"...her heaving breasts caressed the
manly expanse of his chest..."
Excuse...
"This sensation! He thought..."
"This was what he had dreamed of with
each magnificent ripple of the glories
beneath her taut sweater!"
Aren't you yearning for
something like that?
Let's go to a South Sea island!
There's an amusement park in Yabuki
that's just opened a waterpark with a
South Sea Island theme!
Let's give it a whirl!
I...
I'll be waiting for you, this Friday,
at one o'clock at the park.
But I have a piano lesson that day!
Then skip it!
Yes...
It's a deal. This Friday, at the park!
Alright!
I guess with some girls
it just pays to be aggressive.
Misa!
Hey! What are you doing down there?
You're bleeding!
Don't worry about it. It's nothing...
Hey!
Keep your hands off me!
Misa!
What are you doing? Put me down!
Don't worry. We can come
back for your bike later.
You're humiliating me! Let me off!
Take it easy...
Let go of me!!! Now!
Stop it!
Leave me alone you moron!
You'll only make it worse
if you won't hold still!
You won't be able to run anymore!!!
The Nationals are coming soon.
You've got to take care of your legs.
Misa...
Did anyone ever tell you
you've got really big breasts?
Asshole! Pervert...
You just wouldn't listen, would you?
The injury to your knee is the direct
result of excessive training.
You've got to have surgery now,
otherwise...
I won't!
Stop being stubborn. The doctor's
insisting because she cares about you.
Misa, you've run enough. Let's
just fix your leg and concentrate
on your entrance exams.
Stop it!
Leave me alone.
Wataru.
Misa.
I tripped during my morning run.
Pretty stupid of me.
Doctor Mako told me about it.
I'm just so stupid. I'll never run again
because I ran too much.
But Wataru... you were the
only one to back me up, to say
"do what's right for you".
Thank you, Wataru.
Misa.
I guess now I can be the girl my
parents want me to be...
Don't talk like that! Everybody's
been worried sick about you!
I know that...
but... but...
Wataru!
Misa!
I don't know much about this...
...but if they fix it right, surely
you'll be able to run again.
Everybody keeps saying that.
But this was my last chance.
That's why I ignored the pain...
All this time... now everyone knows...
I know Misa... but so many
people care about you.
Heck, even I miss having good old
Misa keeping me in line!
Wataru.
Cheer up. Even if you can't run
anymore, that doesn't mean
anything else would change.
I...
Are my muscles too big?
You're just built firm... and very lovely.
I'm happy.
Wataru, I'm embarrassed.
Wataru.
Ready?
It hurts.
Don't move.
Wataru!
I'm getting fed up with
Kurumi acting like a child!
So...?
Shit!
Maybe it's because the only
mature thing you're interested
in is screwing her.
So... what do you suggest I do?
Being honest about your
feelings wouldn't hurt.
Nerd.
But wouldn't it be nice to square
everything with Kurumi? Maybe
you'd even finally get laid!
You haven't heard the worst of it...
Now her father's gotten into the act.
The other day he got on my case,
yelling "What are you doing
to my daughter?"
No shit?
Okay, I've made a decision.
Kurumi and I are through!
I'm changing my focus to older
more mature women.
And what about Kurumi?
I don't care.
That's great! Can I have a go at her?
Go right ahead!
See ya!
Yeah.
Man, what a jerk!
Now, let's see...
Satomi and Kenji?
What? Mai isn't here?
Hey! Where's Mai? Is she
sick or something?
You won't be seeing her anymore.
What? What are you talking about?
Mai and I are...
So anyway, what's the deal
with you and Satomi?
It's none of your business.
In any case, Mai is no
longer available, got that?
Master, where's Satomi?
She called in sick. Took the day off.
That's odd. She's never
done that before.
Tell me... don't you think Satomi's
been acting a little odd lately?
Her temper gets the better of her,
she drops dishes... She just acts
like she's feeling down...
The other day she even spilled
coffee all over a customer!
She did?
Swear to God! You don't have
any idea what's going on?
Alright, Wataru!
You know something, don't you?
No, I don't. It's not my business.
I see... But I'm so very worried...
Oh, hello.
Kurumi, what's up?
Wataru, I...
Kurumi?
So, you think Kazuya's
been avoiding you?
Well, is that something
worth crying over?
But, the last few times we were
together, it was like he didn't
hear a word I said...
...and now, when I call, he always
says he's busy and refuses to see me.
That idiot. I guess
he was really serious...
I...
Was it my fault... when I
rejected him at the hotel...?
Well, that could have
something to do with it...
I mean no! I was only joking, Kurumi!
You and Kazuya were
made for each other.
Just keep smiling at him, Kurumi, and
everything will turn out okay!
Are you sure?
Of course!
Alright, I'll trust Kazuya.
Great, that's swell.
Men and women... Why do they
have to be such opposites?
Well, at least I don't
have problems like that.
Wait, don't hang up!
Satomi!
Wataru?
Is something wrong?
You look a little upset.
Satomi?
What?
Last night, I saw you
and Kenji at a coffee shop.
What were you talking about?
Nothing. I just ran into him in town.
See you.
Well, I'm a little early.
Maybe I can kill some time...
Wataru!
Master, what's wrong?
Oh my God!
What?
Have you seen Satomi anywhere?
Satomi? No, not recently...
I can't find her anywhere!
She didn't show up for work again,
so I called her house...
...and her mother said
she'd left for work hours ago!
I'm so terribly worried. I just pray she's
all right! Please, help me find Satomi
before something terrible happens!
But I have something else...
Please, I'm begging you, Wataru.
I'll do it.
Satomi? No, I haven't seen her today.
You're absolutely sure?
Ako, did you see her?
Has something happened to her?
Oh no! Nothing. Thanks.
Satomi, Master's worried sick about you.
You could at least give him a call...
Satomi, I know it's none
of my business but...
About Kenji...
Leave me alone.
I'm sorry...
Please... I just want to be left alone.
Satomi...
Made it, just in time...
Well, girls DO take a bit
of time to prepare...
Maybe I gave her the
wrong time to meet me?
Yes? Sakuragi residence.
Hello, My name is Morooka.
Is Mai there?
Miss Mai has decided not to see
anyone until the new semester begins...
I cannot allow you to talk to her.
Have a nice day.
What??
What is this?
Mai...
Mai.
I don't know what to do.
What do I do now?
What the hell???
At this moment, Master Wataru is out.
If you have any...
Wataru.
Satomi.
I'm sorry for calling so late.
No, don't worry about it.
Thank you for everything today.
I appreciate it...
Wataru...
Wataru... I...
Satomi, where are you?
Satomi?
Satomi.
Thanks. I never thought
you'd be so worried about me.
It's funny, isn't it?
Um, yeah... Did you call Master?
I worried so many people,
didn't I? I'm sorry...
Satomi.
Wataru... about Kenji... he dumped me.
I was really in love...
but he told me it's over.
Kenji's... already seeing another girl...
Another... girl.
Hold me! Wataru?
Satomi.
Please. Make me forget about him!
Are you sure? With me?
Only... With you it would be alright...
Make love to me, Wataru.
You're beautiful, Satomi.
Th... thanks...
Please make me forget him.
Do it harder.
Wataru...
Wataru... Wataru...
Yes... again... again...
Satomi.
Come to me, come to me, Wataru...
More...
Again, please...
Wataru... Wataru... more...
Satomi... I'm coming...
Me too. I'm coming. I'm coming...
Well, this is good night.
Wataru... I...
You know, I can't wait to
get back to your shop and have
a cup of that great coffee...
Thank you, Wataru...