Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Karen-chan...
This is mine, and this is Onii-chan's.
He'll really be surprised.
We're going to be late. This is bad!
I praise my daughter for still making lunch.
Very good, indeed.
Onii-chan, you're going to be late!
Wake up!
Hurry, wake up!
To outfox Tendou, you mustn't be late for at least three more days.
Karen-chan...
Here
comes
Botsuko
Ouch. You're mean.
Can't you wake me up more gently?
What are you talking about? If you're late,
you'll have to clean the bathrooms every day until summer vacation, right?
That Tendou bastard hates me.
You're also at fault for responding to his provocations.
You don't get it.
Sometimes a man has to fight,
even in adverse conditions, Yui-chan.
That's silly.
Sign: Yasohachi Academy
Kondou Makoto, you're a loser,
just like I thought.
You can't keep your word, even for one week.
Get out of my way!
You're in my way!
Kondou Makoto is hiding behind a girl's back!
A good chance for a photo!
It's bright.
What's bright?
Onii-chan, we made it in time.
It seems they managed
to make it on time.
Gramps.
Yes, young master Aritomo.
What's wrong with your neck?
As you can see, the top of the car has collapsed.
Gramps, you should say roof.
Get rid of that disgraceful crap,
and have the roof repaired.
Then I'll be on my way.
Please have a nice day.
Crap? What's that?
Oh, let me go first!
Don't walk in front of me.
You were riding a bike with Yui-san.
That's...
Karen-chan.
Episode 1
When the Cherry
Blossoms Fall . . .
My school life.
I had a lot of unexpected encounters.
In a certain reign,
among all the daughters of both high-ranking and low-ranking nobles,
someone of no great rank enjoyed exceptional favor.
The idol star, Maijima Karen-chan,
is my classmate, believe it or not.
She started working in show business at the age of eight.
Because she's busy,
she rarely comes to school.
So she has almost no friends.
Why was I sleeping at the front gate?
I can't remember.
What happened to me?!
What was that?
What?
The Emperor felt deeply sorry for her.
His Highness ignored his other consorts.
He loved her so much that people felt he was setting a bad example.
That bastard Yoshiki...
Kondou-kun?
Kondou-kun!
Y-Yes?
Would you read from that point?
Page 32, third line.
Your book is upside down, Kondou-kun.
That's it for today.
As for today's after-school academic and career counseling,
we'll start with Maijima-san.
Okay.
It's lunch time.
Let's hurry to the cafeteria!
I wonder where Onii-chan went.
I thought we could have lunch together.
I'm lucky. I'm the only one listening to her song.
And if the wind blows and flips up her skirt...
i-it will be an exciting moment.
A close-up.
A good chance for a photo.
What's he doing?
H-Hi. So you were here.
Kondou-kun...
You quarreled with your manager,
and you didn't get your lunch money.
Yeah.
It's more like Hikari-san...
Um, that's my manager's name.
Hikari-san takes care of everything.
I don't know why,
but I've suddenly started to hate that.
She says she'll pick me up after school.
I see. You're having a bad time.
Yeah.
You can have my lunch!
I ate a lot of bread after second period.
No, you should eat it.
It's all right. I'd rather let you eat it.
I knew it.
My stomach is too honest.
Then why don't we share it?
This octopus is big.
Indeed.
This is boring.
Why should I have to photograph a couple?
I'm going back.
This tastes good.
Really?
Yes.
You can have more.
Please!
My, you woke up early today, didn't you?
Y-Yeah.
Misako-san, where's Yui?
I suppose she's taking a shower.
Yui? Yui?
Onii-chan? You woke up early today.
What's wrong?
Um, about lunch today.
Huh?
We only have classes until noon,
so I thought we wouldn't need one.
I see. Got it.
Onii-chan!
Was my lunch that good?
Um, y-yeah.
All right.
There's some time left.
I'll hurry and make it.
Really? Then can you make more than yesterday?
If possible, for two.
Huh?
So you've been eating my lunches in secret.
I'm flattered.
I'll do my best!
Onii-chan, you pervert!
They're still both children.
Karen-chan is late.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Who are you?
It's me, me.
Oh, Karen-chan!
Let's go.
Yeah.
I suppose you had to wait a while for me.
Not at all.
Delays can be quite lengthy.
They're exhausting. I hate them.
You look like you're having a good time on TV.
Really? Do I?
Yeah.
I see.
But I feel like I'm having a good time when I'm doing things like this.
Really? If this is a diversion for you,
I'll come with you any time.
But your fans might hate me.
It's all right. My fans are nice.
Some, though, want to take panty shots up my skirt.
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just...
I envy you.
I want to have a normal school life.
I get envious when I watch my classmates.
They seem to be enjoying nice, normal, teenage lives.
Really?
I don't think so.
It's just my opinion,
but I think that you contribute to our teenage lives.
You make us dream of being famous like you.
We all adore you.
And you give us encouragement too. That's why we can keep going.
So I want you to keep going too.
It's a bit cold, even though it's spring.
It is.
Oh yes, this is a ticket to my live program tomorrow.
It's a token of appreciation for lunch. Please come.
Yeah! I'll definitely be there.
So this is where you were, Karen-chan.
I was looking for you.
Hikari-san.
Your manager?
You should tell me where you're going.
It's a nuisance.
I have to apologize to the director and the rest of the staff.
You're going back to school to hand in your paper
for academic and career counseling, right?
I'm sorry.
Are you a fan of Karen-chan?
Huh?
No, I'm not! I'm her friend.
Really? I see you at her concerts and at the TV studio.
What?
Uh, well, I'm a fan too, but...
Thanks for today.
You'll be late.
Let's go.
Damn.
I'm not.
I'm... I'm not just a fan!
I knew you'd be rejected.
I'll sell you some of these
for a low price.
This is a panty shot of Maijima Karen-chan at her open-air concert.
In this photo, she's sweating, so her panties are wedged.
Kondou-kun, as her fan, you...
I'm not a fan!
Karen-chan...
Big star.
Sign: Kondou
Makoto-kun.
Do your best!!
I'll support you.
Big star
Go to college
Do your best. I'll support you.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You're late.
Onii-chan, where have you been?
Aren't you eating dinner?
What's wrong?
Did something happen to him?
He wasn't wearing his jacket.
A troubled boy.
According to Plato,
"Trouble makes everyone grow up"!
Yes, yes.
Um, could you give this back to Kondou-kun?
And give him my thanks.
Excuse me.
A-All right.
I think I've seen her before.
Mom, who was it?
That's Onii-chan's jacket.
Isn't she the idol Maijima Karen?
Really? Oh, my!
Hey, hey, did you know that Makoto-kun had such a famous friend?
She's just our classmate.
Now, after that wild song,
let's welcome the No.1 singer with the innocent and pure image,
Maijima Karen-chan.
You're becoming even more beautiful these days.
Is that so? Thank you.
You have a lot of female fans too.
There's a saying that women become beautiful when they're in love.
Karen-chan, do you have a boyfriend by some chance?
Sign: Let her sing!
Well then, Karen-chan...
with her mysterious smile, will sing her new song, "Smiling Venus."
The next day, Karen-chan didn't come to school.
Hey, did you see Karen-chan yesterday?
Yeah, I saw her. She has a boyfriend?
Everyone was talking about yesterday's TV program.
Faculty Toilet
Something. I think I forgot something!
Kondou Makoto mustn't be late for school for a week.
Cleaning bathrooms. Summer vacation.
Kondou Makoto, late, cleaning bathrooms. Kondou Makoto...
Oh, yes!
Now I remember!
Kondou Makoto is pushing his luck, just because he's living with Narusawa Yui.
He'll pay dearly for it.
What's this?!
Kondou Makoto, are you here?!
A perverted teacher!
Sign: Aniki (big brother)
A good chance for a photo!
Don't you have any principles?!
Kondou Makoto,
you have one more day to show that you can be on time for a full week.
Tomorrow is the day!
Sensei.
Yeah? What's wrong?
Tomorrow is Sunday.
Sign: Beast
The new song you sang on stage the other day was good.
Thank you. But I got a scolding afterwards.
I had to say, "No, I don't have a boyfriend.
Will you introduce me to a prince on a white horse?"
I'm an idol with an image of purity and innocence.
If I'd known where you were sitting, I would've sung to you.
Karen-chan, aren't you coming to school?
No, I'll be busy for a while.
Oh yes, this is confidential.
I have a photo shoot next Monday at Yasohachi Beach.
Can I go too?
Yes, for a little while.
You'll come to see me?
That's nice.
But don't you have school that day?
Yes!
Karen-chan, you should go to bed soon.
You have a hard schedule tomorrow too.
Yes.
Then I'll pick you up at five in the morning. Good night.
All right. Good night.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, take this.
What's this?
You're in a hurry, right? Go for it!
All right. The next photo is a sexy pose with the setting sun behind you.
We'll have to wait for sunset. Let's take a break!
Why a sexy swimsuit picture now?
It can't be helped.
After that live TV program, Karen's innocent image is a thing of the past.
And my boss is angry.
We're going to promote her with a different image.
Well, she has great proportions.
She's sexy despite her innocent appearance.
Why don't you flirt with her?
You might be able to get a sexier shot.
If it's all right with you,
maybe I'll go for a super sexy shot.
Using your usual tactics?
Yeah. Like, "Isn't it cold?
Would you like a cup of hot tea?"
Am I getting photographed in this ?
I don't want to go in the cold sea wearing just this.
Stop it.
You can succeed without doing things like that!
Makoto-kun?
Let's get out of here!
It's warm.
I'm getting a bit cold.
Would you like a cup of hot tea?
Oh, are you going to use that tactic on me?
It's for Karen-chan.
Karen-chan is missing.
What?
Oh, there!
What are you doing? Chase after her!
Go get her!
What are you doing? Hurry!
Th-The thing is, the key is gone!
The key for this one is also missing!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I couldn't ride around the city with Karen-chan in her swimsuit.
We decided to wait at our school until it got dark.
Infirmary
I suppose they're looking for us right now.
Oh, yes! I should call Yui and get her to bring you some clothes.
Right, Karen-chan?
She must be really tired from her hard schedule.
Today also made me tired.
We're locked in.
That's a good smile. Click.
I've been photographed.
Then what about this pose?
Also good.
Click. Click!
The cameraman can ask for a pose.
I'm not inclined to strike a pose like that !
Cameramen don't touch their models.
They violate them with their eyes.
I'm done.
I'll quit taking photos.
I'll become a producer from now on.
I'll do just what I like.
All right. If it's the producer's order, I have to obey.
Wait a second.
Don't.
Don't...
No!
Don't!
I want to see your naked body.
Sure, Mister Producer.
You're beautiful, Karen-chan.
I can feel you inside me.
Karen-chan.
I can't believe it.
I'm going crazy!
Soon after that, Karen-chan flew to New York.
Her dramatic escape made her boss realize how determined she was.
He agreed that she could study abroad to become a proper stage singer,
instead of a sex star.
Maijima
Karen
Onii-chan, let's go home.
What's wrong?
Um, yeah, but wait a sec...
Huh? Tomomi-san?
Why is she with Yoshiki?
Strange. She's acting weird.
Yeah. She's not herself these days.
Are you going to poke your nose in again?
What are you talking about? I'm just being kind.
All right, all right.
Wait, Yui!
H-Hey, Kondou Makoto!
Riding double is illegal!
Whatever.
Riding double is...
Wait!
Damn playboy. Yui-san is mine.
Catch me if you can!
Wait up, you!
Makoto-kun, help me.
To be continued...
totsuzen no ame ni furarete
Showered by a sudden rain
kasa mo sasazu ni aruita ra
Walking without putting up my umbrella
machi yuku hito ga henna kao shite mite ta
People in the street looked at me strangely
mada haru asai san gatsu no gogo
On an early spring afternoon,
tsumetai ame no sora miage
I looked up at the sky in the cold rain
odoritaku naru youna kibun de aruita
I walked with an urge to dance
arifureta nichijyou ni itsuka kokoro ga kumotte ta
My heart was clouded by the familiar days
sonna koto sae kizukazu ni ita
I didn't understand anything
keredo
But...
honno sasayakana nandemo nai youna yuuki dakeredo
It was a small piece of courage, almost like nothing
sonna koto de naze ka sukoshi kokoro ga hareta
I don't know why, but it brightened my heart a bit
Translation: anon
Editing: Collectr
Timing: archdeco
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: Destroyking