I'm thinking back on our youthful days.
"I don't have many memories of those three years."
That's what my senpai murmured on graduation day.
And those few memories centered on...
Karen-chan, a popular idol who entered his school as a junior, one year behind him.
Whenever he met her, his heart throbbed.
Unintentionally, he saw something he shouldn't have,
and he couldn't forget it.
That made him forgetful about preparing for lessons.
Gee, his memories are mostly about girls.
I thought he was a hard-working student,
so I didn't expect it.
Are all boys like that?
Putting that question aside...
the reason I'm in this situation...
Well, I have a reason.
Actually,
it all began during winter vacation, after Christmas,
when I met my senpai again.
Classmates
The
Graduate
Chapter 1
Miyuki, Karen, and the Courage of a Man
Senpai? Sanshirou-senpai?
Are you all right, Sanshirou-senpai?
Y-Yeah. I was just thinking about something.
Do you have problems of your own as well?
As well? What's troubling you, Tomomi-kun?
Is it your entrance exams?
N-No!
You know that girls my age worry about everything.
Losing weight, blah blah, my crush, blah blah, and so on.
When we get together, it quickly turns into something like "The Worry Show."
O-Oh, really?
I'm not worried about my entrance exams.
I'd be lying if I said I'm not
nervous about them, though.
Besides, you're my tutor, and you got into Imperial University without a problem.
I have faith in you.
Even without me, you'll do fine.
May I air out this room a little?
Ryuunosuke-kun's not home today either.
B-By the way, I've been tutoring you for a while now,
but I've never ever seen him.
We used to chat like this a lot.
But...
The last time we talked was on the 19th of December.
It's already been a week.
You really have a good memory.
He always seems to be busy.
Yes?
Youko-chan.
I knew you'd call me.
I saw the flier for bargains too.
You always ask me to accompany you.
Well, Izumi is from an upper class family, after all.
Tomomi also won't buy anything that's on sale.
She always wears expensive items.
I don't mind, but I might choose the same thing.
No way! That's my favorite too.
What do you mean by that?
I don't want to catch a cold, so I'll call you later.
Yup, got it. Bye-bye.
You should take a bath later. I'm taking one now.
What are you talking about?
We can bathe together, can't we?
By the way, Yui,
has Ryuunosuke-kun left already?
Speaking of him, before vacation he always slept until I woke him up.
He seems to be busy during vacation.
Oh, right, Mom!
I ironed his shirt properly. Would you tell him...
Never mind. I'll tell him myself.
If I had a magical mirror,
I'd be even cuter.
Then Onii-chan would...
A tight skirt was the right choice.
Are you all right?
Hey, isn't that Karen-chan?
Yeah! It's Maijima Karen-chan!
Sorry. I'm in a hurry.
Are you all right?
You should be more careful.
Yay!
Yui-chan, you're good at playing games.
Despite appearances, I'm really good at crane games.
Who are you?
Karen-chan?
Oh, no!
Gee, she's so persistent.
I know! Can you come with me for a little while?
If I go alone, I have trouble finding someone to play with.
Do you come here often?
Yeah, secretly.
I want to be prettier than anyone else,
for the special someone I'll meet someday.
Azumi-chan, you're already beautiful, just the way you are now.
You're so sweet, Junko.
But flattering me won't get you anywhere.
A coup d'état?!
I'm going to pull it off someday.
I'll hide somewhere.
But...
They keep insisting that I work,
and they never let me go to school.
They don't give me a break.
I see. It must be hard to be an idol.
I don't want to be everyone's idol.
I want to be the idol of
just one special person.
I'm kidding.
This is the first time I've been to an informal restaurant.
Like this, do I look like a normal girl?
I don't think this is right.
If you use it like that, even I'll feel pity for your camera!
Is Ryuunosuke-kun all right?
I suppose he is. He went out early this morning too.
I'm sure he's out on a date with someone.
I'm sure of it.
Is he dating someone from Yasohachi Academy?
I don't know. Why do you ask?
Huh? No special reason.
So he's popular. He does look charming.
My photos are like art!
You're not allowed to say no.
You'll understand if you let me take your photo.
There... and there, and there.
Will you stop it!
M-My camera!
I'm sorry!
J-Just you wait!
Mama...
Oh, my.
There we go.
Do you remember cleaning the swimming pool?
Cleaning the swimming pool?
Remember? The boys and girls take turns cleaning the pool every year.
That was the first time I met you.
Ah, I do remember!
It happened just after I'd transferred here.
That reminds me. I still haven't received my uniform.
They said they couldn't let an idol help with the cleaning,
so everyone left me alone.
But then you approached me and asked me, without hesitation, to help clean.
For some reason, I felt really happy.
That was probably when I started to be aware of you.
That's why I feel a little tense talking to you like this.
Oh, no!
I-I didn't see anything!
I saw a little, but I assure you I'll forget about it.
Are you Sanshirou-san?
M-Misako-san?!
I-I really didn't see anything!
E-Excuse me.
He didn't need to run away.
Ah, Tomomi-chan.
You should be careful on a day like this.
Nobody wants to see an old woman's underwear.
However,
all sorts of people live in this town.
Gee, enough of this!
I won't...
First and foremost, this uniform. The skirt is too short.
Excuse me.
S-Sanshirou-senpai?!
Do you know me?
Um, no. That aside, what do you want from me?
I'm looking for someone.
I wanted to ask you
if anyone had passed by.
Someone?
Yes, she's short, with big eyes,
wavy hair, and she's cute too.
Oh, right, this "someone" is a girl.
And here I thought you were different from the rest.
But it's as I expected: all men are the same!
Excuse me!
Karen-chan, your house is really huge!
That's why it's called Karen's mansion.
It's too big for my family, though.
You're right. It might be scary.
Scary?
Because it's so big.
The way you say it is sort of cute.
That's just like you.
Do you want to come in?
I want to talk with you.
I'm free right now, so it's okay, but...
Hikari-san?
This is a very important
time for you, isn't it?
What if other agencies, who want to drag you down, learn about this?
Can't I decide what I do with my free time?
Anyway, you should refrain from acting on your own.
Huh? Sanshirou-senpai!
Y-Yui-kun? Are you Narusawa Yui-kun?
It's been a long time.
Who is he?
He's Sanshirou-senpai.
He graduated last year.
He enrolled in Imperial
University straight away.
He was the talk of the school, the first student to do that.
You're an amazing person.
She's exaggerating.
You're just in time. Why don't you join us for a cup of tea?
Th-Thanks, but I'm looking for someone.
E-Excuse me.
Oh! I have a piano lesson!
Are you disturbed?
Getting straight to the point,
you're disturbed about love, right?
Let me tell you what the girl you have a crush on is thinking!
I-I don't really...
H-Hey!
Yes, here's the result!
She has no feelings for you.
However, there's a chance that she might fall in love with you.
And the proof of it is...
See, she's calling you.
This is the work of one of my tutors.
I'm hoping that I can compose something myself eventually.
You seem to have totally forgotten about the lesson, though.
I'm sorry!
That school uniform of yours brings back memories.
That's right! My tutor is also a graduate of Yasohachi Academy.
But no one in my class wore such a short skirt.
It's been a while. Would you like to try it on?
I'd like to see you in it too!
This is it.
Sorry, Karen-kun, but there's something I'd like to ask.
No! You shouldn't do it! Please stop!
Hey, Miyuki-san.
What's your relationship with Sanshirou-senpai?
He saved me when a weirdo was bothering me this afternoon.
Your expression says that you don't believe it.
I have a hunch.
If you become his lover, I'll totally support you.
I see! The same goes for me too!
What are you two talking about?
But today really was fun!
It's been quite a while since I enjoyed my free time like this.
I have to do my best again tomorrow.
Karen-chan, are you free for the rest of the day?
Huh? Yeah.
Then why not...
So she's Miyuki-san.
I wonder if I could meet her again tomorrow.
That depends on you.
If you want to be the protagonist,
you need to have courage and take action.
What an unexpected harvest.
If I use these photos, I'm sure she'll...
I knew I needed to take action if I wanted good photos.
I despise guys who do nothing but flirt and chase girls.
But I was really surprised,
because you suddenly decided to rebel against your manager.
Did that bother you?
I just have photo shoots tomorrow,
so I guess I can laze around in the morning.
Hikari-san will have to look everywhere for me. That'll cause a big fuss.
Will your rebellion be successful?
We demand free time, right?
Mm-hmm.
Here.
Onii... Oops, sorry.
Be sure to keep it a secret from Ryuunosuke-kun, okay?
Actually, he called just now
and said he's spending the night at Akira-kun's.
Do you allow him to stay out at night, Mom?
Karen-san, don't get too friendly with Ryuunosuke-kun, okay?
As you can see, she'd be quite jealous.
So... Ryuunosuke-kun's not home, huh?
That's disappointing.
Karen-chan, weren't you in Ryuunosuke-kun's room the other day?
Sorry about that.
This place is your home too,
yet I came here without telling you.
I'm just jealous of you.
Although we live together, I've only rarely talked to him in his room.
I'm jealous of you, Yui-chan.
You get to live with such a nice guy.
Looks like it'll be crowded if we both get in.
But it'll be fun, like a school trip.
I've been longing for this.
Talking to friends about guys,
and enjoying silly conversations,
just like a normal girl.
Do you wear that ribbon everywhere you go?
The guy I love said that he likes girls who wear ribbons.
That's why.... I decided to take it off only for him.
Are you seriously going to sleep like that?
But I always sleep naked at home.
It's supposed to be good for maintaining my proportions.
Though I'm wearing my panties today.
Is that true?
Maybe I should also try that from now on.
What about you? Why are you wearing that?
Ryuunosuke-kun told me if I exercise wearing a skirt he can see them.
Karen-chan, you're lucky.
You've got a good, mature figure and big breasts.
They've actually become larger recently.
Someone might be responsible for that.
Karen-chan, do you have a boyfriend?
I do.
Well, that's what I'd like to say,
but my feelings aren't returned.
What about you, Yui-chan?
I do... in my heart.
You're lying. You're quite popular.
Even if someone liked me,
it'd only cause problems.
I love just one person.
As I thought, it's chilly without PJs.
You're looking again.
You've been peeking at my back from time to time, haven't you?
N-Not really. I just think you're really pretty.
Do you want to touch me?
What?
I think you're pretty as well.
You have small hips. You're more suited to be an idol than me.
My butt is big.
When I wear a swimsuit, everyone laughs because it makes me look perverted.
You think so? But I'm jealous of you.
That lace is cute.
Isn't it? Today is special, because I'm with you.
Just kidding. I love lace as well.
Don't you want something like these panties and a matching bra?
I'll introduce you to my favorite shop.
I'm sure it'd suit you.
I'll choose some for you.
N-Nothing expensive.
I'm already broke this month.
Nothing happened that time.
When I entered his room,
we just talked, and then he sent me home.
It's the truth. I promise you.
No, I don't really...
I just didn't want you to misunderstand.
All right. I got it.
I was never told that the shoot would be outdoors!
Don't be so selfish!
This is part of your work.
Besides, I told you to stay in touch.
Where were you last night?
Forget it. Hurry up and change.
I'll ask them to start after noon.
Yui-kun!
Huh? Oh, Sanshirou-senpai!
Yui-chan, sorry for making you wait!
Oh, my.
Don't you think it's unreasonable
to wear a bikini in this cold weather?
Um, Karen-kun.
Shouldn't I wait outside?
It's okay. I'll be done soon.
There'll be trouble if Hikari-san finds you.
Yui-chan, could you give me a hand?
The zipper's stuck.
Am I going to be a sex symbol, after all?
It's free. Thanks.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure you'd be an idol,
no matter what your age.
Are you referring to my childish appearance?
No, I don't mean that.
I lied. By the way, Senpai, this is out of the blue,
but what do you think of Miyuki-sensei, my piano tutor?
Well...
What do I think? That's...
Amazing! They're all brand-name goods!
You could try them.
No one will come in any time soon.
Really? Then maybe just a few.
It's true. I can't help thinking about her.
I just want to see her.
That's why I came to this town.
See? It's just as I said.
Sometimes when I listen to
Miyuki-sensei playing the piano,
I wonder whether she's waiting for someone.
Like Prince Charming?
Or someone who would change her life.
Miyuki-san is waiting?
Senpai.
Women are about charm,
and men are about courage.
You've seen mine, haven't you?
No. Well, just a little.
Please keep it a secret that
I'm wearing undergarments.
During swimsuit shoots,
I'm not supposed to wear anything underneath, because it leaves marks.
Right, right.
I'm waiting too.
Men are about courage.
Men are about courage!
A-Anyway, I must speak up first.
Senpai, what are you mumbling?
N-Nothing.
Stop, Yui-kun!
Senpai, what's the matter? Senpai!
Ouch...
Gee, Senpai!
No. Let go of me!
You've become pretty hot, haven't you?
I despise men like you!
Great.
First, I'll get back what you discarded two years ago.
No!
W-Wait!
Who are you?
Sanshirou-san!
Miyuki-san, please run away!
But what about this guy?
J-Just do it!
O-Okay.
Wait!
I'm not done here!
I'll take her place, so let her go!
Are you an idiot?
I let you act all brave in front of a woman.
You're going to pay for it.
I'm against violence.
If you don't have the strength,
then don't try to protect women!
Miyuki-san, I-I've always...
Are you all right, Sanshirou-senpai?
I...
You fainted, so I called Onii-chan...
Oops. I got Ryuunosuke-kun to carry you.
I see. Thanks, Ryuunosuke-kun.
Ryuunosuke-kun?
Oh, Ryuunosuke-kun.
What's that?
What's the matter with him?
You took such good care of Sanshirou that he's acting sulky.
He also said your skirt is too short.
When I'm at home, no one sees them, so it doesn't matter.
And...
miniskirts makes my legs look longer.
But if you're interested, I'll only wear this in front of you, Ryuunosuke-kun!
Those two seem really close.
They're always good to each other.
But they still have a long way to go before love.
I came to understand something.
Love does hurt.
I wonder if Sanshirou-san's all right.
Sanshirou-san, huh?
What a mysterious person.
hajimete no date no hi no asa wa
On the morning of our first date,
kagami no mae de nankai mo
in front of the mirror,
fuku kigaete bakari zutto kimaranakute
I indecisively kept changing my clothes.
anata wo sanjuppun matasete ita
I made you wait half an hour longer.
itsumo wa fuzakete asonde iru no ni
Usually we joke around,
anata to te wo tsunaide arukeba
but just holding hands and walking together
sore dake de ureshikute
made me happy.
keredo hazukashikute
Still, it was embarrassing too,
zutto anata no kao mirenaino
so I couldn't look at your face.
itsumademo
I wish
toki wo wasurete iraretara
this moment would last forever.
kono mama aoi sora wo
I wish we could watch the blue sky,
futari nagamete iraretara
just like this, together.
todoku kana
I wish
anata e no afureru kimochi
my overflowing feelings would reach you.
sono mama tsutaetai
I'd just like to tell you
konna ni anata ga suki dakara
that I love you so much.
Translation: ElyasRay
Translation Check: anon
Timing, Editing: Collectr
QC: CP, Saji
Raw: DestroyKing