Noooo!
A class toilet. The toilet that refused servise. As punishment is now open to all students. Feel free to use the principal.
Forgive me!
You're being too rough!
This is a public toilet.
It's a place that punishes those unable
to withstand regular student labor.
And today... I find myself here as well.
In order to solve the country's
serious work force reduction.
The country introduced the perfect social resource.
For all those whom were unemployed and those
whom failed at going to higher education.
This resource provides a variety of services.
And also the charm the body
outstanding people give.
This resource was given loyal
service in terms of labor.
And it was given as a prize to students
of elite schools that hired them.
~Public Toliet - Watari~
– Damn it... now where is my special toilet at...
– That thing was super interesting. Really!?
That lipstick is so cute!
You bought it right away didn't you!?
I know right? It's soo cute!
It's really good and cute!
This is a new color too!
Wow amazing! Anal sex great!!!
Damn... they're all fools!
Hey, how are you doing?
Hey, Joushima, what's wrong?
You didn't get a high enough score on a
test and your special toilet disappeared?
Y... yeah.
We always come to this place.
Ah, wait... I want to unload!
– No! Wait! Don't cum inside!!!
– Hmm... What should I do?
Ah that? Refusal of labor just arrived.
I'll test it myself later.
New product?
S... Senpai!?
Shouldn't you be in my special toilet!?
You just turned me down to
become your special toilet.
That's why I'm here.
Now all students can come and use me.
After I became a public toilet... now you want me?
Joshima-kun.
Who the hell would want to be in
senpai's public toilet! It's mediocre.
So you don't want her?
Then I'll take her first.
I'm using her! Go find another one yourself!
Do you want my dick?
Would you like to shoot sperm all
over your public toilet sempai?
Come on! Come on! I'm gonna go faster!
Joshima-kun.
I'll turn your face into a cum dumpster.
Although if I want to gain experience.
I can play with this public toilet.
In the end, there is no other choice but to play with it.
Your pussy... it's squeezing me pretty tight.
It feels so good to be able to satisfy Joshima-kun.
This way, I can be your special toilet!
Though you look super geeky,
your pussy ain't that bad.
Thank you for the compliment.
Thank you so much!
Now you understand why you
shouldn't become a public toilet.
This unlucky pussy used to
belong to Watarashi-senpai.
I can't understand what you were thinking!
I finally understand why I became a public toilet.
I'm waiting for students who don't get good grades.
So that I could savor being a public toilet.
Somehow this is making me tired.
The others that choose to be a cum
dumpster toilet have that feeling.
But I also.
Don't crazy talk! You're just a public toilet!
Stay quiet and take my sperm!
I'm going to cum!
Incredible! Incredible!
I'm gonna cum!
Please let me enjoy myself more!
Yeah, I'll make sure to use you to the end!
Joshima-san... Are you almost done in there?
I want to try the new toilet out as well.
Joshima-san.
Shut up!
Go find another toilet!
It's you!
No way...
Isn't that Shichiou-senpai!?
Oh, excuse me. Just passing through.
Man, you trully are something.
You even came into the public toilets.
Ummm...
You just don't know when to quit, Shichiou-senpai!
I can't keep holding it... it's leaking.
Please, come here.
Please... you don't have to ask to
use me as a toilet Shichijou-san!
I look like a dog peeing like this.
It's so warm!
Shichijou-senpai's urine is so warm!
Hehe.
That's an amazing piss! Yeah she
must've held it in for a while.
Yeah, Shichiou-senpai is squirting it a lot.
Wow... amazing!
Thank you... so much!
They both seem to have chosen the public toilet.
People were too scared to ask her
before because she was such a bitch.
Hmm?
How about I let you guys try her out as well?
Man, is it really ok to insert this?
Yeah, just do whatever you want.
But, the ass is mine.
He put his dick inside!
His dick is so hard and throbbing inside my ass!
The penis is perfectly designed for anal sex.
Incredible!
Her butt looks so different than her pussy.
Hey look!
Come on, penetrate her. Shichiou-senpai
can't wait for you to do so as well.
Everyone, learn as much as
you can from doing it with her.
Here
I always worried I looked too geeky before.
The truth is that, the more people that
see me like this, the more horny I get.
Please everyone, penetrate me
with your dildos. Play with me!
Are you sure?
Put them all in at the same time!
Ok... here we go.
No don't!
One by itself made her cum.
I just wont stop cumming!
Wait a minute. This isn't how it should.
We just can't wait to enter.
We wouldn't get the same prize.
It wont feel any worse.
Wow she could really take in a lot.
Senpai's pussy is already very
loose and saggy isn't it?
Wait... Stop this! My mind is going blank!
Amazing! This is absolutely amazing!
I... I couldn't live without this dick.
Relax, senpai is my special toilet for ever.
I'm a toilet as well.
For me it would be no problem doing what
Shichijou-senpai is doing, Joshima-kun.
Why do they love this?
When they came to school they were such
talented women... but much more gifted as toilets.
Yeah, just look at his face full of pleasure.
This feels awesome! I can feel
the vibrations of the dildos!
Shichiou-senpai!
Stop the vibrators!!!
My womb... it's gonna be torn!
Senpai are you still horny? They've
been waiting their turn all this time.
Hmm?
Ah! It seems there is no other choice.
Huh?
Here!
How's this?
Sex between toilets.
Who'll last the longest?
Shichijou-senpai's pussy is sucking strongly.
Amazing! I love you both!!!
How are you doing? It looks like you're gonna lose.
You look very different from yesterday.
Oh, I'm a changed man obviously.
Since senpai has become my special toilet.
I desire senpai, I'll do anything for her.
You also changed, Joshima-kun.
So Watari-san? How does it
feel to become a public toilet?
I feel... like I've found myself in this.
How am I going now?
You did great!
You came! So much semen is coming out!
Cum! Please fill this toilet with all your sperm!
The way this social resource helped improve
and regulate the world of social
economy is worthy of prise.
However, it did not change the fate that people
whom failed the entrance exam multiple times.
Many voluntarily chose this type of slavery.
Now the law of Drop Out is viewed as immoral.
Being a meat toilet is the best!