Boys Communal Bathroom.
Please, stop!
That doesn't feel good!
Holy shit.
You're fucking me so hard!
These are the public urinals.
It's a place to punish the girls who tried
to run away from their duties.
Today is my first day here.
In order to curb the growing problem of
dropouts who end up not joining the work force.
The country instated a law known as the
Societal Resources Restoration Law.
The youths who were unable to find jobs or unable
to move on to higher education on their first try
were made to begin compulsory labor befitting of them.
Though it appeared to be simple manual labor,
it actually turned out to be sexual work,
which then went on to become mandatory
for all those affected by the law.
And to encourage those at the top of the grade standings,
special prizes were awarded to them.
~Public Bathroom - Watarai Seika~
– Seriously, it was so hilarious.
– Fuck, where's my human onahole at?
Your lipstick is so cute.
That's why I bought it!
You think it's good?
Yeah, I do!
Like, seriously, so cute.
This is my first time using it.
Anal is so amazing! I'm cumming!
Fuck, everyone's taking the piss outta me.
Men's Communal Bathroom.
Amazing, right?
Hey, how's it going?
Oh hey, Joushima, what's up?
Didn't you get your own personal cum
dump for scoring so high on that test?
Y-Yeah.
So? You come here to brag?
Wait! I'm cumming!
– No! Don't do it inside! No!
– Shit, everyone's being used?
You eyeing that one?
That's a new one. Just installed today.
I'm gonna try it out later...
New one?
S-Senpai?
You're supposed to be my personal cum dumpster.
After you refused my services earlier
this morning, I was installed here.
Now I'm a toilet for everyone.
Will you use me now that I'm public,
rather than private, Joushima-kun?
Why the hell would I use a dirty-ass
toilet like you, Watarai-senpai?
Not gonna use her? I'm going in first, then.
This one's occupied. Go stick it somewhere else!
You want my cock? I'll cum all over you and
make you dirty like the fucking toilet you are.
Come on! Suck it with all you got!
Joushima-kun...
Now you're acting like a toilet?
You don't even have any experience,
but you wanted to be a public toilet?
I'll see if you have the talent to be a public toilet.
You're gripping me so hard!
I feel like I'll be able to cum over and over again!
I'm so glad that I'm making you feel good.
I'm finally fulfilling my duty as a human toilet.
Yeah, but that's just because
your pussy is tight from not being used.
Still, thank you so much! Thank you so much!
Fuck, do you even know what you are?
You're nothing but a lust-fueled cum dumpster!
This fucking slutty pussy!
Fuck, I don't get what you
or Shichijo-senpai are thinking!
I know the reason why Shichijo-san dropped out.
She was drowning in the
expectations of those around her.
She was just tired of it, you know?
She thought that as a human toilet she'd be able
to satisfy the expectations of those around her.
It's the same for me...
Shut up, you damn onahole!
All you have to do is shut the hell up and drink my cum!
I came already?
Fuck! Fuck!
Oh my god! I'm so happy that I'm making you feel good!
I'm so thankful!
Use me to your liking!
Yeah, I'm going to use you 'till I'm satisfied!
Joushima-san, you're not done yet?
Please, I wanna use that toilet too!
Joushima-san!
Fuck off! She's not something the likes of you can handle!
Y-You guys!
Are you for real?
Wait, isn't that Shichijo-senpai?
Sorry, excuse us.
Seriously, I was in the middle of training her,
and then she starts acting up.
Let's see...
Looks like there's a vacancy, Shichijo-senpai.
No, I can't! I can't hold it in anymore!
Come here.
Please use me, I mean, use this toilet, Shichijo-san.
Equipment
Watarai Seika
I'm peeing like a dog!
It's so warm! I'm being bathed in Shichijo-san's urine!
Holy shit, she's peeing a lot.
She must've really been holding it in.
She's peeing like a fountain.
Damn!
Thank you very much.
Oh, so the rumor that she actually
became a toilet by herself was true?
I didn't know the two of them were such sluts.
I know I interrupted you guys, so as an apology,
I'd like all of you to help me out.
– What?
– Huh?
It's really okay to put it in?
Yep. Put in as many as you want.
This hole is mine, though!
It's inside me! Your dick is so big and hard,
it's spreading my ass wide open!
This hole has turned into a hole for my dick.
Damn, what's that liquid coming out of her?
Hey, let me see.
All right everyone, go ahead.
Shichijo-senpai wants you guys inside her.
Come on, tell everyone what you think, senpai.
I used to be a slut acting out the role
of honor student, but I'm really just a toilet.
Please, put your hard cocks inside me!
You serious?
Put as many as you want inside!
Okay then, here we go.
Did you cum from just that?
I'm going to go crazy from this.
Get it together, senpai.
There are still more vibrators out there.
I'm not responsible for what happens.
Don't make us pay for damages, okay?
If you put any more in, I'm going to overflow!
Shit, all of them really went in!
Her pussy's like a cavern.
This is so...
Don't move anymore! I'm going to break!
Oh my god, it feels so good!
I don't think I can live without cocks anymore!
Don't worry, I'll keep you around
as my cum dumpster forever.
I'm a human toilet.
I wouldn't mind receiving the same
treatment as her, Joushima-kun.
What's going on with them?
The two most distinguished students
were nothing but dropouts.
Yeah, but look at their faces.
She looks so happy.
This feels so good! I can feel the vibrators
in your pussy, Shichijo-senpai!
This is so intense. My insides are gonna break!
Did your womb fall out again?
That's a shame.
Everyone was so nice to put all those toys in you.
Oh geez, I guess we have no choice.
Here we go!
Niimi!
How's it feel to have two toilets up against each other?
Please play nice.
It's getting sucked in me!
I'm gonna pee again!
Wow, you two are amazing!
Looks like something I said triggered a change in you.
You're like a completely different person from yesterday.
Yeah, I've changed. Senpai and I have connected!
I'll do anything to satisfy her!
That goes for you too, right?
So, Watarai-san, how does it feel to be a human toilet?
I feel like I've finally discovered who I am.
What do you think of who I am?
This might be your calling.
You're cumming so much in my asshole,
I'm gonna cum again!
My ass! I'm your toilet!
Please make me dirty with your cum!
So, about the "Societal Resources Restoration Law",
It's believed that, because of it, there has been
great societal and economic improvement.
It weeds out those who can't balance
working and studying simultaneously,
The best
poop hole
Pussy tits
as well as those who decide
to fail by their own volition.
Now let's talk about the "dropout" law.
Being a cum dumpster is the best!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч