School will be starting momentarily.
Equipment please enter the special ops
classroom and prepare yourselves.
Look, here they come.
Hot damn.
All students using the public toilets should
return to their classrooms at this time.
411 Societal Resources Restoration Law
Special Ops Room
Public
Bathroom
Wait, she's the girl who graduated last year.
Some sort of prodigy... What was her name again?
Sh-Shichijo?
– S-Senpai?!     – S-Senpai?!
Cum
inside
2-B Tachihara Miyu
This pussy is da bomb!
Damn, this sucks. I'm jealous of the
guys in the special ops classroom.
Public Bathroom
I want my own personal cum dumpster.
With your grades? Dream on.
Still beats using an onahole any day.
Yeah, no doubt.
I'm out.
You're Niimi-kun, the guy with
the best grades in the school, right?
Nice to meet you. I'm your personal
cum dumpster, Shichijo Reika.
I'll be helping to take care of you from now on.
I'd like you to use me to the fullest
as your own personal cum dumpster.
S-Senpai?! Shichijo-senpai got held back a year?!
There's no way she dropped out!
Shichijo Reika
Tokyo City West 31-10
Drop out
In order to curb the growing problem of
dropouts who end up not joining the work force.
The country instated a law known as the
Societal Resources Restoration Law.
The youths who were unable to find jobs or unable
to move on to higher education on their first try
were made to begin compulsory labor befitting of them.
Though it appeared to be simple manual labor,
it actually turned out to be sexual work,
which then went on to become mandatory
for all those affected by the law.
And to encourage those at the top of the grade standings,
special prizes were awarded to them.
Dropout.
Please turn to page 74 of your textbooks.
It's about the Societal Resources Restoration Law
that was implemented three years ago.
Schools such as ours have adopted
this law as a way to encourage students
to better themselves and to
produce more distinguished work.
So taking the implementation of this law into account...
Hey, dropout! Move your hips more!
That's it.
What about class?
Don't worry, this won't be on the test.
W-Wow, everyone's just jumping right into it.
Am I going to be that way with senpai too?
But...
I've admired her so much, and for so long...
She's the person that I look up to.
S-Senpai!
And now she's in front of me, sucking my dick.
You're so hard. Do my feminine charms
really excite you that much?
– No way... Senpai, you're very alluring.
– You're not going to touch me?
But, you see, this is my first time.
I can't believe that you're my first time.
You're being too rough, senpai!
It feels so good when you swallow my dick!
She's smiling? She's enjoying this? Why?
How can she enjoy doing this?
I'm cumming!
You're so cute, Niimi-kun.
I shouldn't be saying this,
but I don't have any experience either.
Don't worry though, just leave it all to me.
Your private parts are rubbing against my dick...
I'm your personal onahole,
so just cum inside me without worrying.
Niimi Jr. says that he wants to come inside and play.
It seems that he's getting a little impatient.
That's...
I'm inside... I'm inside of her!
I'm having sex with her!
You're huge. Your dick is reaching
all the way to my stomach.
Senpai... Senpai!
Your pussy is so hot and wet!
My dick feels like it's going to melt!
Senpai! I... I'm...
Sorry... I'm really sorry...
You came a whole lot, Niimi-kun.
It's still flowing out from inside me.
I'm very glad that a dropout like me could be
of use to a distinguished student such as yourself.
If you want me to do anything, please let me know.
Lines straight out of the manual? Makes me sick.
Both Watarai-senpai and Shichijo-senpai should've
been able to go to any top university they wanted to.
What the hell's going on?
Also why the fuck am I not
doing this with Shichijo-senpai?
Fuck! That piece of shit stole her!
I get that I earned this, but I don't think
someone like me is worthy of her. I know that!
Joushima-kun...
I liked her too, you know...
Niimi-kun?!
What are you...
The fuck?
Senpai!
Niimi-kun, wait! You can't be so rough all of a sudden!
Oh my god, I can feel it bulging inside of me!
Senpai! Senpai!
Wait! In this position, it's going to go really deep!
Your dick is entering my womb!
Wait! No! That's not where a dick is supposed to go!
Your cum is pouring into my womb!
I feel like my stomach's going to burst!
You can't keep going into my womb!
Wow, this is so amazing!
I can feel my womb being turned inside out!
Please flood my womb with your cum!
No! I can't hold it back anymore!
I'm going to cum with my womb!
Equipment
Shichijo Reika
You knew that I was dating her, didn't you?!
You really think a little shit
like you is good enough for her?!
Switch equipments with me.
Listen up. Shichijo-senpai is mine!
You stole her from me.
I'm gonna show you the same
courtesy you just showed me.
I wanna show you how she moans from my cock!
I-I liked her too!
The fuck did you say?
Also, she's already mine.
Don't get a big head just 'cuz
you got your cherry popped!
How about we leave it at that?
Senpai?
I can't say I'm very impressed with guys
who talk about girls' first times in public?
Also, I don't think I ever moaned
the way you're thinking I did.
But I guess I kind of get why you would
want to hold on to those memories.
I was pretty happy when I took
Niimi-kun's first time too.
If it's any kind of proof of my sincerity,
I'll let you take my first anal experience.
Stop it!
Th-That's not the kind of thing
the real Shichijo-senpai would do!
Sorry, Joushima-kun.
This is something I chose for myself.
All right, Niimi'kun, let's put on a show for him.
Shichijo-senpai!
You don't need to worry about any hygienic issues.
Everything's been cleaned to help me
fulfill my duty to satisfy you.
How about it, Niimi-kun?
It's really clean, isn't it?
Your asshole is covered with fluids
and love juices... it's so erotic!
So this is her first anal experience too?
I'm sorry, Joushima-kun,
but I'm not giving her over to you!
I'm coming in, senpai!
It's so hard to push in!
It's a struggle just to even push it in!
Pulling out feels like it'll take everything I have too!
Yeah, it seems like it's harder
than I thought for you to put it in...
Your big dick is filling my ass up!
Your ass is squeezing me so tightly!
S-Senpai!
Fuck me like you're trying to drill a hole in me!
I'm your personal belonging, right?
Senpai... the girl I looked up to...
She's like an onahole now...
Senpai!
Would you like to use this hole, Joushima-kun?
Don't try to copy Shichijo-senpai!
Oh my god, you're cumming!
Senpai... Is this really okay?
You're asking me this after cumming in my ass?
Also, you said it yourself. I'm yours.
If we're going to be together from now on,
I don't need your consideration.
Treat me as if I were a thing, not a person.
What if I don't do that?
Wait, no!
Squeeze me tighter!
Move your hips more!
Well, if you refuse my services,
I plan to become a public urinal.
N-No!
No way!
What? Are you angry?
Your attitude changed so quickly!
– You're being so rough!
– Your body's very interesting. Just by playing with your ass
a little, your stomach starts convulsing and gets tighter!
How's it feel? How's the ass-fuck you wanted feel?
It feels so good! I don't want you to stop!
Who do you belong to?
I am Niimi Ryouta's human toilet.
Please give me your cum!
I'll do my best. I'll make sure to fuck you so hard that
you won't even think about becoming a public urinal!
I'll make sure... I'll make sure to
break you into little pieces, senpai!
Your cock! Your cock!
Shichijo-senpai... why?!
Why did you become a dropout?!
I heard that Shichijo-san tore up her answer sheet
and left the examination room herself.
She's amazing. She's a beautiful person.
I've made up my mind.
I wanted to be like her. I always followed
in her footsteps because I idolized her.
But I won't become like her.
After all, I am me. Nobody else.
The place where I belong is...
Equipment
Watarai Seika
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: fyurie
quality control: fyurie