Something crazy happened
in Himawari Garden where I work at.
Himawari Garden
Because of the "growth cookies" that the principal kept here,
the kids suddenly grew up into voluptuous adults!
Huh?
The effect of the cookies should wear off in the evening,
but it will be a scandal if their mothers find out about this!
They already are fully mature physically,
but they still act as the same
innocent and dependent children.
But having those huge tits and asses
and seeing them so defenseless...
E-Even I will be...
This is bad! I knew that I can't hold back!
Why did you grow up so erotically!
D-Damn! This feels good!
This feels so good that it's criminal!
This is seriously bad...
But it feels like my cock is melting!
Plump, innocent and forcibly grown up!
Muchi Muchi Kyousei Seichouchuu !!!
Lewd Yet Clueless Girl
I-I wonder what will happen to me from now on...
L-Lily-chan... You can't!
Don't lick me down there so much!
No can do, Cocoa-chan.
Didn't you do a lot of naughty
things with my darling?
So this is your punishment...
Wh-What are you doing, Lily-chan?
Sensei, please help me!
Y-Yuuki-chan?!
I-I became weird!
My tits grew big...
A-And they feel tingly when I touch them!
H-huge breasts with inverted nipples...
This girl grew up with such sexy tits!
I-I can't become a hero like this anymore!
Th-Then... Should I massage them for you?
Massage?
Puffy puffy!
Sensei, wait...
I-I feel weird...
If you keep rubbing them...
Are her nipples getting hard inside?
Not there!
Don't move your fingers!
I can't do this!
It's strange for you to moan so loud.
Aren't you aiming to become a hero, Yuuki-chan?
B-But I feel tingly!
There they are, they came out!
They couldn't help wanting more after I teased them,
so her nipples protruded outwards!
Is she trying to keep her voice down?
Shit! I can't get enough of
her being so erotically cute!
Puffy puffy!
Sensei, don't suck the tip!
Don't suck me there!
Why are you sucking my tits? You look like a baby!
Nothing will come out of my tits!
Her nipples are getting harder
and her tits are getting hotter!
No, don't do that!
Both of my tits and groin are feeling tingly!
I can't take it anymore!
Yuuki-chan!
My groin feels tingly!
No... no, no!
Coming... It's coming...
Something's coming!
Puffy puffy!
Wow!
There's also a lot of pee coming out from your groin!
N-No, you're wrong!
It's not pee, it's something else!
Then... Then what is this?
I-I'm not sure...
But it feels weird.
My groin feels hot and it starts to ooze.
Puffy puffy!
S-Sensei...
Will doing this make my tits shrink?
Y-Yeah! It should... Maybe...
I-I don't want that!
I want you to do the massage and suck my tits again!
Ehh?
I loved it when you massaged me, sensei!
I want it... I want you to do it again on my tits...
Ehh!
Puffy puffy!
Listen, sensei! I saw it!
I saw papa's dick going inside mama's groin one night...
Lily-chan?
It looked like it feels very good so
I told them that I want to do it too!
They said that it's something done to make a baby,
so that I should do it with
someone I love when I grow up.
Th-That's...
I'm already a grown-up, darling!
So let's do it! I want to do it
with you, my beloved darling!
Let's make a baby together!
Sensei, me too!
I love you so I'll do it too!
They're cute, voluptuous, pure and kind!
True to their desire for pleasure and naughty...
But they are clueless girls in the end!
Clueless kids are the best!
Puffy puffy!
My dick is currently swelling so much,
and it feels so bad!
Yuuki-chan, can you be my hero
and save me from this?
O-Okay...
I'm gonna save your dick, sensei.
I will become a hero.
Yuuki-chan!
S-Sensei, I feel weird!
What's happening? My belly feels hot, and I feel so light!
This is so weird!
Yuuki-chan, that's what feeling good is!
Good! Feels good... It feels good!
I-I feel good!
Your dick is making me feel good, sensei!
It feels good!
So lewd... She's so lewd! I can't get enough of this!
S-Sensei, does your dick feel better now?
D-Did I become your hero now?
Yeah. Of course, you did!
With such a sexy body like this,
you surely can save any man!
No way! If you start moving that fast,
I'm gonna feel so good...
You'll drive me crazy!
I can't take it anymore!
Sensei, you're going so fast!
Yuuki-chan, where does it feel better?
On your breasts or your groin?
Both of them! They both feel good!
Feels good!
They both feel good!
I-I'm gonna... I'm gonna get crazy!
I'm gonna come, Yuuki!
Stop! Please stop!
Drink my cock juice using your adult pussy, Yuuki!
Something's coming!
It feels good, it feels good!
No!
It's coming!
They really are amazing!
Both Cocoa-chan and sensei...
Wh-What should I do?
Just from watching them,
my groin feels kind of tingly!
D-Damn, I'll be outrageous for all I care!
I won't get any other chance to have sex
with these lewd girls again!
I lived my whole life just for this moment!
Sensei...
Your dick... Your dick is going inside me!
It's incredible!
Cocoa-chan's huge ass! Cocoa-chan's huge ass!
This feels good!
The truth is, I wanted to screw
this ass when I first saw it earlier!
So weird... I feel so weird!
What's happening?
Weird! This is weird!
What's wrong? What's so weird?
My belly feels tingly and my groin is throbbing!
I-It feels like... It feels like I'm floating far away!
S-Sensei, help me! I-I'm gonna fly away!
Cocoa-chan!
That's what we call as "coming".
Come on, come! Say that you're coming!
Coming... Coming, I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
Coming, coming, coming!
I'm coming from your dick, sensei!
You're getting tight, you're squeezing me so tightly!
Cocoa-chan, this feels good!
Sensei...
Your dick is throbbing and it's getting hotter.
That's right! It's all thanks to you, Cocoa-chan!
Just wait, I'm going to come now!
Sensei, you're coming too... You're gonna come...
M-Me too... I'm gonna come again!
S-Sensei, let's do it together...
No way... Water is flowing out of my groin!
I'm gonna get soaking wet again!
Dick... Sensei's dick!
Me too, I want it to go inside me too!
Puffy puffy!
Darling, darling!
I love you... I love you!
Keep rubbing me more down there!
Lily-chan, if you squeeze me that tightly...
S-Sensei is gonna...
It's okay, let's do it!
Let's make a lot of babies!
I want to have your baby, darling!
A-Are you fine with that?
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's fine!
Your dick feels so good, darling!
It feels good!
Making a baby feels good! I'm so happy right now!
I'm coming... Coming, coming, coming!
Shoot it out! Shoot, shoot it all out!
Come a lot of your dick's white stuff!
Shoot it... Shoot it all inside my hole!
Lily-chan!
It's pouring in... There's a lot of hot stuff!
There's so much... It's so amazing!
Th-This is bad, I can't stop myself!
Lily-chan, your insides feel
so good that I can't stop myself!
It's alright... More, give it to me more!
My insides are already gooey and mushy!
I feel like I'll go crazy!
Lily-chan, I'm coming! I'm coming again!
Let's come together this time!
Darling! Darling! Come!
Come, come, come!
Make your dick come!
I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
Puffy puffy!
S-Sensei...
Please... Let's do it a lot more!
There's a lot of juice oozing out of my groin!
Wipe them off with your dick, sensei!
Sensei, from now on...
I'm gonna save your dick every time, okay?
Baby...
This will be our baby... Right, darling?
What should I do? I'm happy with this,
but I might not be able to last
until evening if this goes on.
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization