I just started working this spring here
in the daycare that my father manages.
I've always been fond of children.
I can get used to everyday life there
and I'll get to play with the kids too.
I couldn't get the hang of it in the beginning.
Preparing meals, and cleaning up afterwards.
Cleaning, laundry.
I prepare the teaching materials at afternoon
naptime as I get their change of clothes dry.
Oh, right! Building up trust with the daycare employees
is also an important part of this job.
It has tons of difficult stuff to deal with as of now.
Seeing it now, this line of work is
more rigorous than I thought.
What a tiresome job.
Unexpected things happen every day.
And I'm sure that tomorrow will be the same.
Plump, innocent and forcibly grown up!
Muchi Muchi Kyousei Seichouchuu !!!
Their Bodies Are Matured! But Inside...
Hey, sensei. Carry me!
Himawarizono
Bear hug!
Just wait a second, Cocoa-chan.
I'm preparing everyone's 10 AM snack.
Ehh, I want it now! Now!
Cocoa-chan is an angelic and pampered child.
Her future dream is to become an idol.
Hey, darling...
What would be our snack for today?
Lily-chan, can you call me sensei instead?
Oh, isn't it fine?
Won't we get married when I grow up?
She's Lily-chan who talks
precociously from time to time.
Of course, her future dream is to become a bride.
Hiiiyaaa!
How is it? It's power of me, the masked rider!
Y-Yuuki-chan, you shouldn't be
hitting others with your sword.
I'm not hitting you, I'm slashing you to death!
Killing is something even worse!
Yuuki-chan loves superheroes and
her future dream is to become one.
She may act like this, but she's a good girl.
Kanon-chan, it's snack time now.
Alright... Good job on not crying...
Good girl!
Kanon-chan is a shy girl who
isn't good at expressing herself.
Her future dream is to become a florist.
Puffy puffy!
Okay! Say it at the same time, everyone.
Thanks for the meal.
Thanks for the meal!
At that time, never have I thought
that something like that will happen.
Huh?
Whoaaaa!
P-Principal, this is bad!
Everyone kind of got big after
eating the cookies in the kitchen!
Their tits... Their butts!
G-Growth Snack?
What the hell is that? I don't understand!
Before that, how can I get them
back to how they used to be?
It will be a huge trouble if the daycare
employees see them like this!
Huh?
They'll go back at evening even if I just let them be?
You're telling the truth, right?
M-Maybe? What's with that uncertain reply?
Just go here already, principal!
Ahh... W-Wait! Just wait!
Damn, he hung up on me!
Hey, sensei! Are you done talking?
C-Cocoa-chan? Is that you?
That's right, I'm Cocoa-chan!
Isn't she already a full-grown woman?
Th-This is bad, my heart is pounding so hard!
Am I heavy because I'm big now?
Ahh... No... You're not particularly heavy...
Sensei?
You see... I took my panties off!
Huh—!
You see, my panties felt so tight
and it hurts on my groin!
Damn, damn, damn! No!
If you keep moving your ass that much...
Huh?
I feel something rubbing against my butt!
Do you have something inside your pants?
Th-That's... not good! No!
Puffy puffy!
Aha, I found it!
It's the hard thing!
Cocoa-chan, you shouldn't touch that!
Sensei, your dick is bigger than papa's!
It's throbbing, this is so much fun!
It feels way different when someone else touches it!
It feels incomparably better than masturbating!
It feels like my cock is gonna melt down!
Sensei, do you like it when I play with your dick?
Wow, it's getting bigger and bigger!
Hiiyaa! Hiiyaa!
I can't take it... Let go of your hand!
Huh?
Coming! It's coming out, coming, coming!
S-Something came out!
S-Sorry! I'm sorry, Cocoa-chan...
White stuff came out of your dick, sensei!
Whoa... It looks like an icing!
Cocoa-chan? What... What are you doing?
This is an icing... I knew it!
Delicious!
Stop... Stop! Don't suck it off!
I can't take it anymore!
S-Sensei...
Huh? K-Kanon-chan?
U-Umm...
I-I want to pee... Come with me!
Oh, right... Kanon-chan still can't wipe herself up.
She still needs assistance.
Puffy puffy!
Sensei, are you there?
I-It's alright, I'm right here.
I'm watching a beautiful girl peeing live!
S-Sensei... Wipe me.
O-Okay...
Hold yourself together, don't lust over her!
She's still the same Kanon-chan inside!
Huh? What's with that reaction of hers?
Could she be feeling good from this?
What's this?
S-Sensei...
It keeps on dripping no matter how much I wipe.
Are you still peeing?
It feels weird down there! I feel tingly!
I'm... becoming weird!
It's alright, you're not weird!
This is how a grown-up body is like.
S-Sensei...
Coming... Something's coming!
It's coming!
Kanon-chan, keep on coming!
Keep on feeling even better!
S-Sensei! No, no...
No—!
I can't get enough of this!
If I shove my cock in her soaking wet pussy right now,
I wonder how good it'll feel?
S-Sensei... Do it more...
Huh?
Th-There's still a lot of juice dripping on my groin...
K-Kanon-chan...
You don't hate it when I wipe your groin?
Yeah... I don't hate it...
Puffy puffy!
Ghh! This isn't sex!
This is just a part of toilet assistance...
This feels so good!
Damn, this feels dangerously good!
I'll immediately come if I relax even a little!
I-It's inside!
Sensei! Your dick...
It feels so hot!
My groin feels hot!
I-It feels so good that I can't stop my hips!
More, deeper!
Wrap my whole dick tightly with your pussy!
I want to... I want to keep rubbing it inside!
Coming...
It's coming... again!
Coming!
Coming... It's gonna come out!
Puffy puffy!
K-Kanon-chan? What are you doing?
No way! You're shaking your hips on your own!
I-I love the shivers!
I love it when my body is throbbing!
More... I want to throb more!
With sensei's d...
Throbbing with sensei's dick!
I love it... I love it a lot!
Kanon—!
I'm sorry, Kanon-chan!
You have such a lewd body!
But I love the lewd Kanon-chan too!
Your tits...
And your pussy!
This feels good!
I feel good too!
I'm throbbing, amazing!
Sensei... I can't stop!
I'm coming!
Kanon-chan, squeeze it all out!
Ahh, I love it... I love it!
I love this!
Puffy puffy!
This is bad... I'm gonna come again!
Kanon-chan, can I come?
Can I shoot a lot
of my pee inside you?
Yes, it's okay!
I love them all...
The throbbing, and the pee too... Everything!
Kanon—!
I love them all!
Hey...
What do you want to be again
when you grow up, Kanon-chan?
My dream is to become your toilet, sensei!
I'll let you pee a lot inside me.
I want to become your toilet!
No... I don't want this!
I can't become a hero with these huge tits!
N-No!
L-Lily-chan!
I feel weird down there!
It's alright, Cocoa-chan.
All the grown-ups, you see...
They feel good when they play down here!
No way! That's the hole where pee comes out!
I saw it last time!
When papa played with mama's groin,
she said that it feels so amazing!
Huh? No way...
I'm starting to feel tingly down there!
We're not kids anymore,
so let's do a lot of things that feel good!
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization