ODAIBA, TOKYO.
GINZA, TOKYO.
A Dissolver has appeared in Odaiba.
Temperature readings indicate an Arch Dissolver.
What? Are you sure of that?
Yes, it shows a 98.25% probability that it is an Arch Dissolver.
We have visuals. Switching to main monitor.
This sudden appearance of an Arch Dissolver is a catastrophe.
Isvelga-kun, immediately dispatch Zeigfried Units.
Commander, only Unit 1 is available.
The other pilots are on leave and are not at headquarters.
How stupid of me.
Order the pilots back to base immediately.
Yes sir. Riska...
who can report back the soonest?
The pilots in closest proximity are Mido-san and Matsui-san.
Units 5 and 6. What about the others?
The other pilots are not in the Tokyo area.
KANAGAWA PREFECTURE.
BATHS RESERVED FOR PRIVATE PARTY
This feels so good.
Oh, yeah.
They haven't appeared in two months and I was caught off guard.
Huh.
Gori-kun, dispatch all units for an immediate counterattack.
Yes sir.
An incoming message in from the coast.
From Yokohama Harbor,
an Aegis Cruiser and two escort vessels are on the counterattack.
KICHIJOJl TRAIN STATION, TOKYO.
MALI AREA
lt's already been a year since we got back together.
Yes, that's right.
Don't. We shouldn't be doing this.
I love my fiance's tits and I'm just getting started.
Doing it like this is so embarassing.
It okay. We could never do this at DAKT Headquarters.
You lie!
I know about you and Reiho-san.
What?
Yeah!
Don't tell me you been doing it with Reiho-san.
Hey!
Don't be silly. You're the only one.
No...
No, not there.
Don't, I'm getting wet.
Feels... Don't, no.
Wait. Let me clean up first.
Alright.
Let's bathe together.
Yeah.
No, don't. lf you keep doing that, I won't be able to hold it.
Hikari, I can't hold it ether. lt okay, right?
What! We going to do it here?
- No.
- Can't hold it, here I come Hikari.
No. This is embarassing.
Not this way.
Don't look at me.
Don't be shy. Your pussy is so beautiful.
Noway. This is embarassing.
No! Kyosuke. Don't.
Don't. My juices are gushing out.
No. I can't hold it.
I'm getting so wet.
I'm going to do it.
It our first time, please be gentle.
It hurts! lt hurts!
No.
It hurts! lt hurts! lt's so deep.
No. lt hurts!
It hurts! I can't take any more.
Your so mean.
You could have been more gentle.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't hold it.
Next time I'll be better.
Next time, not so rough.
I promise. Let's go to the bed.
Please be gentle.
Yeah, more.
I'm getting wet.
More, more.
I'm so horny. I'm getting so wet.
I cant hold it any longer!
Fuck me now. Kyosuke, stick it in.
Huh?
What's wrong? Don't you want to?
I shot my wad earlier and can't get it up yet.
Hikari, how?
I saw it in your porn magazines.
Sucking your cock will get you hard agian.
Hikari.
I'm going to stick it in.
Okay. go ahead, Kyosuke.
It... hurts.
It hurts!
But, I can feel...
your cock throbbing inside me.
You feeling it, Hikari?
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to shoot my cum.
It's okay.
Kyosuke!
I'm cumming!
Now I belong to you.
You better not play around.
Never. You're the only one in my life.
You had sex with Reiho-san, didn't you?
No. I've never done that.
Whenever you get horny, you tell me.
Do somebody else and I'll kill you.
Don't worry. You're my only love.
Want to do it again?
Yeah.
Let me see you jerk it.
Okay.
Assault!
Both are secured!
A Dissolver has appeared.
Both of you to battle stations.
Huh?
RAINBOW BRIDGE, TOKYO.
- Buy time until we're in position!
- Yes, sir!
At this rate, we're doomed.
The enemy plans to destroy DAKT Headquarters.
Hey.
We found Kyosuke and Hikari-chan.
They'll be here soon.
Strange. lt's as if the enemy knew when to attack.
There's a spy among us?
Let me go. Stop this.
Not quite, Yukiko-san.
You have to tell me everything.
I don't know anything.
You're a United Nations agent. Find out for yourself.
Fine. I'll ask your body.
You must be bored with regular sex.
So I will treat you as nothing but slave meat.
Then you will tell me everything.
No, please stop! Let me go.
No!
No! Not there!
No...
No.
Look how sticky and wet you are.
No, don't.
Aegis Cruiser Group damaged.
Message from Land Forces: counterattack has commenced.
This is bad. We have to stop it.
Conventional weapons have no effect. Where are the Zeigfried Units?
Units 5 and 6 will soon join the battlefield.
We attack as soon as the remaining Zeigfried Units arrive.
Order a temporary retreat.
Yes sir!
Here we are!
You guys are late!
Sorry, there was a small distraction.
I'm sure you guys were fooling around.
What?
You can fool around after we get this guy.
Roger that. Hikari, we'll continue later.
Darn.
Attack!
- Roger!