It's not your fault.
I know that.
I know! But...
How long before it self-destructs?
Estimated time is 43 minutes and 52 seconds.
I've calculated the area of destruction.
Everything within a 10 kilometer radius of the Arch Dissolver will be destroyed.
At its current speed,
it will arrive at Ginza 4th Avenue in 41 minutes.
Obviously, the enemy objective is the annihilation of DAKT Headquarters here.
Hikari, how long can you stay in the air?
4 minutes 20 seconds remaining.
Roger that.
Cpt. Gori, we're going in for an attack now.
You commence a general attack in 3 minutes.
Roger.
Relay to all units that we commence a general attack in 3 minutes!
Yes, sir!
Watch out for the crossfire.
I'm aware of that.
To prevent the enemy use of their Time Accelerator,
we will stop it in its tracks just before the general attack.
Kyosuke, go after its legs.
Meanwhile, I'll attack its head.
Roger.
Hikari, you divert its attention by going in around it.
Roger!
All units, Time Accelerator stand by!
Standing by!
Switch on!
Attack!
All units get out!
Roger!
Where am I?
Who are you?
I am you.
What is this?
What's going on?
Stop! Stop this!
Stop it.
Let me go!
No...
No. Don't. Stop.
Stop.
No...
lt hurts! No more! Stop it!
Stop it.
It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Please, no more. lt's going to break.
Hey, Kyosuke!
What the matter?
What are you doing?
No! Stop it, Kyosuke!
No.
No!
No! Stop it, Kyosuke!
No.
No! Let me go. Stop it, Kyosuke!
No, don't! Let me go!
No!
The brain waves of all the pilots are distorted.
Damn. An attack on their psychology.
Commencing general attack.
We've lost contact with the enemy Arch Dissolver.
I think we damaged it a bit.
Immediately calculate when and where it will appear next.
The pilots' life signs have been confirmed.
Gori-kun, rescue the pilots and secure the Zeigfried units.
Roger that.
OPERATION lN PROGRESS.
Hikari.
She'll make it. Her life is not in danger.
Thank god.
However, she must rest for a week.
Both of you come to the Command Center.
Okay
lt will appear at Shinjuku Central Park in 3 hours.
The Arch Dissolver is accumulating energy as it travels through the space dimension.
The next time it appears, it will be at critical energy levels.
We have calculated the Arch Dissolver's detonation time and blast area using past data.
It will detonate 29 minutes after it appears.
Everything will be destroyed within a 10 kilometer radius.
All of Shinjuku will be obliterated.
Riska, what about the other pilots?
There's been no contact so far.
DAKT PARTY
A search party won't find them in time.
Units 1 and 6 will be repaired and ready in 2 hours.
We have to make do with what we have.
Isvelda, have Gori-kun gather his forces in Shinjuku.
Yes, sir.
Ru and Kyosuke-kun, get some rest until then.
Get well quick, Hikari, and let's pick up where we left off.
Kyosuke, can I have a minute of your time?
Huh?
What did you experience during the psychological attack?
I don't remember.
I see.
If that's all, I'll excuse myself.
Please, don't go.
The past all came back.
You mean the past you told me about?
Yeah.
And I had sex with a man in the same place where I lost my entire platoon.
That man, looked just like you.
I haven't done anything!
I know. That's why I'm begging you.
Begging for what?
Please, just have sex with me.
What?
I don't know if I can take another psychological attack.
Maybe you don't like my body.
Not at all. You're beautiful.
I'm sorry, Hikari. She needs my help.
Yes, right there, more gently.
Right there, gently.
Fuck me. Cum inside me.
Are you sure?
You can put it in, Kyosuke.
Okay.
Huh?
Sorry.
We don't have time.
You're awesome.
Are you hard enough to fuck me?
This time, I'm going to do it.
Be gental. This is my first time.
Shit.
It hurts.
I'm used to pain, but this is different.
I'm cumming.
It okay, cum inside me.
Thanks, Kyosuke.
Ru, I'm seeing Hikari.
I know.
I know that. But after this battle, let's do it again.
Okay.
It's time. Let's go.
Yeah.
WEST SHINJUKU, TOKYO
SHINJUKU CENTRAI PARK
We've set remote control mines throughout Shinjuku Central Park.
It won't destroy the enemy,
but we can damage it,
and divert its attention.
We only have one chance.
Make sure we interdict it.
Starting countdown to Arch Dissolver appearance.
20 seconds.
10 seconds.
9... 8...
7... 6...
5... 4...
3... 2...
1... Materialization.
Detonate the mines.
Yes, sir!
Fire!
Good, it worked.
28 minutes until Arch Dissolver detonates. Start countdown.
Attack!
The only way to prevent it from detonating...
is to destroy its life core with a single blow.
It won't be easy without Unit 5.
Kyosuke, it's up to you and Unit 6.
We're depending on you.
Leave it to me.
Heat sensors registers an Arch Dissolver.
Target confirmed.
Target locked.
Fire!
We hit it. What the...
lts core is reassembling.
What?
Is it going to self-destruct?
I don't believe it.
Arch Dissolver's energy level is rapidly increasing.
The time it takes to gain information from her is well worth it.
It's so good.
It's no good. Retreat!
Roger.
I'm going to cum.
You will forget about this when you awaken.
But I have taken measures so that you are my slave.
When the time comes, you will work for me, Yukiko-san.
We've lost the Arch Dissolver.
All sensors read zero.
Did it spare us?
Damn!
What happened to the Arch Dissolver?
We don't know.
We're left with a bunch of questions.
Isvelga-san thinks it might have been a diversionary tactic.
A diversion?
Forget that. Let's continue where we left off.
What? Are we going to do it here?
It's alright. The doctor gave us permission.
Don't. I said no.
Kyosuke... no...
I can't take it.
Don't... no...
No...