This feels embarrassing, onii-chan.
My breasts... aren't really that big...
So please, don't ogle too much.
Mine are small, so...
Onii-chan, you like bigger ones, right?
Onii-chan,
no, not that spot...
It's dirty there.
No...
Onii-chan,
do you want to put it in?
Okay.
Onii-chan,
put it in me.
Ouch!
It hurts.
I'm alright.
Onii-chan...
Do it gently... a bit longer...
Ow...
Onii-chan.
Please cum lots...
inside me...
It's okay.
For you to be aroused like this while
a girl nubs it with her feet,
that's just like a pervert.
You want to put it in here, right?
Nope.
You only deserve to get pleasured by my feet.
Because you're a pervert that gets aroused with footjobs.
Feels good, right?
Exposing your footjob loving self,
aren't you the least bit embarrassed?
Oh, cumming already?
What a pervert you are, cumming with my feet.
Oh come on, now my socks are all soiled.
What are you going to do about this, Mr. Pervert?
Oh my, you already came this much,
but it's still bulging like before.
Do you want to put it in?
I wonder if I'll do it...
Here, come on here.
You want to put it in, right?
Feels good, right?
It's gotten this big, after all.
I'm okay.
I'm just fine.
Just move however you want.
Ow, ow...
Onii-chan,
it hurts.
As long as it feels good for you,
I'm happy.
Please, just keep it up.
Ouch!
Ow...!
Onii-chan,
it's good.
It feels so good.
Please,
make it feel even better.
Onii-chan, onii-chan...!
It...
It feels good... it feels good for me...!
Oh no, something's... coming!
Yes, oh yes.
Onii-chan,
more... more...!
No, something's really welling up.
Me too,
it feels...
I think it feels good for me now too.
Onii-chan,
does it feel good for you?
Onii-chan!
Please, make it feel even better for you!
It's alright.
I'm just fine.
Just move however you want.
Ow!
Ow...
If it's for you, onii-chan,
I'll endure anything.
Please move more.
It's okay.
Ouch!
Onii-chan, onii-chan...!
It's okay, just keep it going,
onii-chan...
Just keep pleasuring yourself, onii-chan.
Onii-chan... more...
There, that deep, it feels good right there...
It feels so good.
Please, make it even more pleasurable.
Oh no, something's coming...!
Does it feel good?
Does this feel good?
Oh yes.
Onii-chan,
more, push it in even more.
Go on, just keep at it, onii-chan.
Your thing feels good, onii-chan.
If it's for you,
I can endure anything.
Please move more.
It's okay.
It hurts.
It hurts, onii-chan.
Ouch!
It kinda feels embarrassing.
You're such a meanie, onii-chan.
If you keep pulling like that,
my swimsuit will get all stretched.
Onii-chan, it feels good.
More, please, onii-chan...!
Oh yes, oh yes.
It feels good.
Onii-chan!
Oh yes...
Oh no, something's happening to me!
Well, onii-chan?
Does it look cute?
L-Like this?
Onii-chan's such a pervert.
It's okay, onii-chan.
Open it.
It feels embarrassing when you ogle me like that.
I-I'm going to cum.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, put it in.
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
Onii-chan, onii-chan...!
It feels good, onii-chan.
Oh no, if you keep doing that I'll...
I-I'm going to...!
No good, I'm about to...!