When he called out to me...
I had something of a premonition.
What sort of premonition?
That perhaps I would... fall in love with this person.
What's he like?
His name is Natori-san.
Simple relations
Well, hello there!
Even if you ask me "why"... It just
seemed like you were free.
Did I really look like I had a bunch of free time?
Say, have you been rather bored lately?
Why did you come with me?
Oh, I don't know...
So, where do you want to go from here?
Anywhere is fine.
Do you want to go and have some
fun at an amusement park?
So this is an "amusement park"?
Wait, don't tell me...
Don't!
Is this your first time?
Natori-san!
Ow!
What are you doing right now?
You're the only thing I think about.
Keiko: Did you stay in touch with him after that?
Nozomi-chan, I made some tea for you.
Thanks, mom!
You made Earl Grey today?
Yeah, doesn't it smell good?
Don't stay up too late now.
Yeah, I know!
Hey, Natori!
Shoko.
You're drooling.
You got yourself a new girlfriend,
didn't you, Natori?
What's with all the questions? Did
you get yourself a boyfriend?
Well, perhaps I will soon.
Well then, same here.
Which means you do have a girlfriend! You
jerk, getting all happy all by yourself!
Don't be stupid! I never said I had a girlfriend!
Geez, you're the one who dumped me.
You're the one who went and
got ahead of himself, Natori.
Well, looking back on it, it was rather entertaining.
Just kidding!
The "Anything Goes" Favorite Circle
Yo!
I saw everything.
You're still hanging out with Shoko.
Yeah, and? Oh, because I was
with her just a second ago?
Are you guys retarded?
You were so depressed just a month ago, going
on and on about how Shoko dumped you.
It was the same old same old for you.
Don't go on babbling about petty things.
I've completely cut ties with Shoko!
I'm dating a younger girl now.
What, compensated dating?
I'm going to kick your ass!
Introduce her to us next time!
Have her bring along some friends.
Come on, now!
I'll get around to it!
Would you like to see my room?
I haven't really been in someone else's room.
Because you're used to hotel rooms?
Na-Natori-san!
Do you have any idea why I invited you over?
As you can see, I live with my parents.
But they're both out tonight.
I wanted to do it in a different setting.
Come on!
I know you want it, too!
Geez, who could it be?
Yes, Natori speaking.
Huh?! You're already on your way home?
Got it!
What's the matter?
My parents did what they needed to do,
and said they're on their way home.
Well then, I should be going.
I guess it can't be helped.
Huh? This is the last bus.
We've got an hour before the next one
comes. Man, I hate the countryside!
Don't you think so, too?
No, not really.
I always ride my bike to the train station.
I don't really ride the bus that often.
Well, we'll just have to wait it out, then.
The moon is beautiful.
And the night air is nice, too.
Do you want me to make you feel even better?
Natori-san!
Your reaction is always over the top!
I like that about you.
People might show up in a place like this!
Well then, let's go somewhere we can't be seen.
We can't take our time at my house since my
parents will be home any minute now.
B-But...
Don't worry! No one will come
through here at this hour
I know you want it. I can see it in your eyes.
I wonder what that look was about.
Western Style Bar
Ah!
She's cute!
Did she bring any friends?
Next time, next time!
This is Nozomi-chan. Be nice to her, you guys!
Hey, can you drink?
She's fine! She'll have a beer.
They look like they get along well.
Cheers!
To tell you the truth
I only see her nights during the
week ever since I met her.
Only at night? Why is that?
She said he's busy during the day with
club activities. He said he has practice
on Sundays as well. Right?
Yeah! As expected of a top student!
You sure are straight-laced.
Don't be silly! Whoever said I was straight-laced?
Meeting up at night could only mean one thing.
Well, you do do that at night.
Oh, that? Ah, I don't really
see it happening, though.
I sure am jealous.
She sure likes it. Nozomi is generally into that.
U-Umm...
What was that? I can't hear you all very well.
Come on, now! The poor thing!
What's the matter? Are you feeling ill?
Oh, I got it! You want to go to a hotel, right?
Huh?!
Shoko!
Thanks for the drink!
Geez, okay, you can have it!
What, you're not buying one, Natori?
I don't feel like it anymore!
A little birdie told me.
That your current girlfriend is rather young.
Damn it! I told those jerks not
to talk to you about it, Shoko!
What are you going on about? What, are you
trying to be considerate of my feelings?
Not in the slightest.
I heard she's pretty cute. Not bad!
But...
I feel rather bad for her that she
has to date a sadist like you.
Who are you calling a sadist?!
You're having sex with her, aren't you?
You know, like playing Molester, or telling her
to come out without any underwear on.
You made me cry quite a bit.
You know you liked it.
What sort of girl is she?
Let me meet her!
Not gonna happen!
She's not at home during the day
because of club activities.
Besides, I haven't called her on the phone yet.
Oh? Then that's all the more reason to call her!
She'll be happy to get the first call from you!
It's making a weird sound.
See? She's not home.
Yes? Hello?
Oh, so you are home! It's me!
Natori-san!
Come on out here! There's someone
who insists on meeting you.
Um... I-I can't right now.
My mom isn't home at the moment and
she asked me to watch the house.
It'll be fine if you lock the door on the way out.
But, umm...
Come on! Let's meet up during
the day once in a while!
How'd it go?
She said she'll come.
See?
Nozomi,
this is the girl who insisted on meeting
you. Her name is Shoko.
Pleased to meet you.
This is rather unexpected.
I can't believe you'd date someone like her.
Really?
At the very least, she isn't the type
you've dated up until now.
Shut it! Are you happy now
that you've seen Nozomi?
What, you're shooing me away already?
That's not how it is! This is the first time
we've met up during the day. Right?
Well, let's get going then.
You're thinking of something weird, aren't you?
You're the one thinking of something, not me!
Nozomi-chan, is Natori mean to you?
Let me know if he is! I'll kick his ass!
I'm okay.
Shoko! Butt out!
Hey, Nozomi-chan!
Do you want to go see a movie together?
There's one that I want to see,
but it's boring to go alone.
Which movie?
Well, Brad Pitt's new movie came out last week!
Oh, nice!
How about it, Nozomi-chan?
Umm, I...
I'm sorry!
Hey! No-Nozomi!
You jerk! Go after her!
Sorry, Shoko!
You're apologizing to the wrong person.
Nozomi!
What's the matter? You're acting differently.
You've got a terrible fever!
I'll be fine. I just want to take a break.
What are you going on about taking
a break?! Not with a fever like that!
Wait here! I'll go and get someone!
Wait!
Nozomi!
Hold me!
Natori-san...
Natori-san!
Let's do it like we usually do.
Nozomi!
It feels so good!
Can you hear it?
How embarrassing!
Now it's my turn!
Natori-san!
Do you want it?
Natori-san! Does it feel good for you, Natori-san?
Yeah, it does.
Good. I'm happy to hear that.
How about you, Nozomi?
It feels really good!
Natori-san...
Thank you for today.
Don't be silly.
I love you, Natori-san.
I love you, too.
Hey! Why are you crying?!
Come on, now!
I'll pick on you some more once you cheer up!
When are you going to introduce
us to Nozorru-chan's friends?
Well, the thing is, she's been flaking
out on me ever since then.
I've tried to call her several times,
but I can't get ahold of her.
There's always a weird sound,
and she never picks up.
She dumped you.
Again?
Geez, what's going on?
Hello?
So you were the one on the phone...
It was just a coincidence.
But I just happened to be in Nozomi's room,
so I was able to receive your phone call.
You said something about a computer
connection, right?
That phone number was a personal
line she used for chat.
Where's Nozomi?!
You didn't say anything on the
phone, but what happened?
Well, Nozomi died.
She died about 10 days ago.
Nozomi was sick.
I didn't know anything about it until it was too late.
What sickness did she have?
Her mom wouldn't give me
the details of the sickness.
But it appears she couldn't sweat
if she went out into the sunlight.
I stopped by her house today.
And you see, Natori-san, the
reason I had to see you...
is because I wanted you to see this.
Our chat logs have been all about
you for the past two months.
It might be a bit of a burden, but I want
you to know how Nozomi felt.
Nozomi...
He might have been a little too
pushy with me at times,
but I think he's really kind person.
All of his college friends were kind people.
I drank alcohol. It made me feel grown up.
Natori-san sure can hold his liquor.
It made me think about how mature he is.
Natori-san's room was unexpectedly clean.
It made me really happy just to be surrounded
by all of the things he likes.
He said he loves me! I'm so happy!
It's really just by chance that we met!
But I really want to cherish this opportunity.
And this is the final message.
From the day before she died.
It may be that I have fallen
in love out of convenience.
But I'm fine with that. I love him.
I really love him.
I just wish I could be with him.
yosomi wo shitetara chansu ga nigeteiku
Your chance will get way if you don't focus
mou matenai yo sasso aoutte READY GO
I can't wait anymore, come on, let's meet, Ready Go
kotoba no uragawa mirai no yukue toka
Rather than thinking about words
that hold some meaning for the future
mendou na koto wo souzou suru yori
and other bothersome things,
suki wa suki de ii ja nai
Just like whatever you want to like
hottokenai yo karada no oku ni
I can let it go, and within me,
ima kanjiteriru atsui kurasshu honoo ni natte
The passionate crash I feel turns into flames
kokoro sae mo makikomu
and even my heart wasn't saved from it
Get you! Get you! ii kagen na kimochi
Get you! Get you! These half-hearted feelings
Get you! Get you! sonna mon' ja nai yo
Get you! Get you! No, it's not really like that
yowaki ke tobaseba ato ni kawaru
Kick those feelings of weakness
and change will come afterward
Hit me! Hit me! yuutsu-sou na kao ya
Hit me! Hit me! Those melancholic expressions
Hit me! Hit me! poosu nante shitete
Hit me! Hit me! Just get on with it and strike a pose
tsukamaeyou I can ready go!
Let's get it all I can, Ready Go!
hara hara shitenakya ikiteru ki ga shinai
I don't feel like living if there's no excitement
taikutsu yori mo suriru mezashite Ready go
Thrills will always be better than
boring things, so Ready Go
ashita no watashi wa kinou to nitenai
I am different from the person I was yesterday
mainichi umare kawareru kara
And if I'm always reborn everyday like this
mamoru mono wa nai ja nai
I have nothing more to protect
minogasanai yo karada no oku ni
I can let it pass, and within me,
ima todoiteiru kimi no biito ookiku natte
The beats from you become bigger
tsuyoku mune wo ugokasu
Invigorating my heart
Get you! Get you! chotto hazushite mo
Get you! Get you! Even if I let it off a bit
Get you! Get you! doutte koto nai yo
Get you! Get you! It won't affect me at all
naritai jibun ni watashi nareru
I can become whatever I want
Hit me! Hit me! ai toka yume ni wa
Hit me! Hit me! In love and dreams
Hit me! Hit me! ruuru nanka nai yo
Hit me! Hit me! There are no rules
dakishimeyou I can ready go!
Let's all embrace it I can, Ready Go!
isogu kimochi wo osaetakunai ima sugu
I don't want to hold back from the rush, it's now or never
Get you! Get you! ii kagen na kimochi
Get you! Get you! These half-hearted feelings
Get you! Get you! sonna mon' ja nai yo
Get you! Get you! No it's not really like that
yowaki ke tobaseba go ni kawaru
Kick those feelings of weakness
and change will come afterward
Hit me! Hit me! yuutsu-sou na kao ya
Hit me! Hit me! Those melancholic expressions
Hit me! Hit me! poosu nante shitete
Hit me! Hit me! Just get on with it and strike a pose
tsukamaeyou I can ready go!
Let's get it all, I can Ready Go!
When I told Nozomi loved her
that really was the first time I said it.
I said it from the heart, but it might have been
due to the state I was in at the time.
It was so easy to say,
but it wasn't the same for Nozomi.
I've been thinking this whole time about
when Nozomi came out that day.
I know why she did.
She wanted to see you, Natori.
I could see it in her eyes.