Today is a special day for me.
Today we take the measurements.
My work is great!
Alright, you're 139 cms tall.
Lift up your blouse.
Ok, stay still.
Waaaaah! Such small breasts!
They're 62 cms.
Akiyama is still flat.
Although, well, that's the way I like it.
Okay, next!
Sensei. Are you looking!
How perverted.
K-Kana-chan?
Look! These are undeveloped breasts!
W-What are you doing?
Stop bothering and continue.
That was great!
The only one missing was Kouda?
Yeah that's right.
She hesitated but
in the end she had to miss.
Kanae-chan, she said that she would come tomorrow.
Otani-san.
Coming!
This may just work!
Kouda!
Coming!
Please stay for a minute.
See you, Kanae-chan.
Bye-bye.
Sensei, what's wrong?
Yesterday you didn't come and we took measures.
So let's go to the infirmary to do it.
Okay, fine.
Now let's check your height.
Stay still.
Ouch!
Oh, sorry.
Let's see, 136 cms.
I grew up a little.
So we have your weight and height.
How, your waist, chest an a abdomen.
I want to do it properly.
Please undress.
But...
Yesterday everyone did it.
I'll turn around.
Please go ahead.
Don't get carried away!
Yes...
Peek.
Woah! A loli stripping!
This is bad! I'm getting excited!
Sensei, I'm already naked.
Well, now let's take them.
What a wonderful figure!
She is so white an small!
She is so sparkling!
I have in front of me the panties of a beautiful girl.
This isn't good! Not at all!
So...
Your waist is 69 cms.
This body is the best!
Now your abdomen.
What a soft belly!
It tickles
I'm almost done, endure it.
I'll do the same!
Well, it's 55 cms.
Now the chest.
Your t-shirt bothers me
Pull it up to the shoulders.
Eh, t-that's embarrassing!
If you don't do that, I won't
be able to take it properly.
Come on, hurry!
Kouda's breast!
There they are!
They still have no shape.
And her nipples.
They're still so pink!
This is great!
Sensei...
I-I'll take it.
It's rubbing.
My nipples.
By her voice, she seems to be enjoying it.
Could she be...
I'm going to touch.
Sensei...
Don't touch them.
Your breast are a little bit weird.
They are not!
They still have no shape.
They are soft and sensitive.
Sensei you are touching them too much!
It's because your breast are very odd.
Jeez... don't fondle me so much.
Small naked breast!
So addictive!
Seems that I went too far.
That felt great.
Sensei, idiot.
I would like to keep doing it!
How cute.
What happened? This place is wet.
Don't!
Girls get wet like that when they feel good.
By chance did it feel good
when I fondled your breasts?
You're wrong...
You are all wet there.
It's embarrassing...
Happens the same with all the girls.
You should't be ashamed.
Don't hold back.
Sensei is touching me...
With his finger there!
I'm cumming!
She is so wet.
Did she just cum?
I won't be able to resist.
So bad.
Sensei...
That felt really great.
I...
I want to have sex with you.
Can I stick my dick inside?
It is my first time.
I'm scared.
Also it can be painful.
Don't worry. I'll do it slowly and gently.
It's true, it won't hurt.
It's the truth.
Please. Pleeease!
You can trust me!
If you are gentle...
Then... okay...
If that felt that great...
Having sex must feel much better!
Sensei, this position is embarrasing.
A small butt and a small vagina!
How beautiful!
It's incredibly soft!
So tight.
Seems like It's going to crush me.
I'll stick in it...
Little by little.
S-Sensei...
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
It's a bit weird.
But it doesn't hurt.
I'll move.
This is too much!
It can't be compared!
It's so tight and warm!
My head feels weird.
Even suffering.
It feels good.
It's tiny.
And tight.
And soft!
This little pussy is too good!
You're starting to relax.
I'll do it faster.
S-Sensei. Slow down!
No!
I can't move.
She relaxed too much.
Did she cum?
Seems that I was very rough.
Sorry, sorry.
Kouda, are you okay?
I'm fine, sensei.
Seems that your pussy got tired.
And you got scared.
Let's stop using my dick.
And use this.
Recently you were using panties.
So you didn't feel it right.
But this way you can feel it well.
It will give you a lot of pleasure.
Sensei! There... don't...
Sensei! I f-feel weird.
Feels good?
Without moving she gets
wet, gets tight and gets soft.
This is really great!
Sensei...
You can cum.
Do it!
Again...
Your pussy is so wet.
Who would've thought it would be so sensitive.
I'll move again.
Sensei! So rough!
Slow down!
It feels great!
Kouda.
Can... can I cum inside?
Are you about to...
Yes, I'll cum.
I'll cum inside.
I'm cumming!
Sensei!
Kouda, it felt great.
I can't...
Achoo!
S-Sorry!
Yesterday I went too far.
Despite your physical state!
So... Can I reward you with something?
If it's not very expensive...
Then, when I get better...
Would you have sex with me?