Good morning to myself!
Let's work hard today!
Hey, don't you think school has gotten boring?
That's not even the issue.
My pops found out some of my lights yesterday.
Your room is bugged?
He said he'll reduce my allowance now.
What a tool.
I don't really talk with my parents at our place.
Same goes for me.
The entire family's going to
make dinner at our place.
But, your pops is quite an old guy already.
Yup, he does it at least once a week.
What kind of pops is that?
Oh, and speaking of your family, Yumi,
both your parents were totally into filming
the entire lesson during parent's day.
All three of us watched it that same night.
For real?!
But, I guess that's Yumi for you.
I totally agree.
Totally.
Is it weird?
Dear, would you prefer to have light liquor?
Okay.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Thank you, Yumiri-chan.
It's nothing, I got to taste that
wonderful stew, anyway.
No worries.
Where did you learn to make it?
I'm going to cook something even
more wonderful next week.
Now I'm really looking forward to it!
Umm, Mom...
What is it?
Later this night...
Are you and Dad going to,
have... sex?
Hey, mom.
Well, we're going to, but why ask?
M-Mom!
Yumiri-chan,
don't forget to always look at the person
you're talking to straight in the eye.
O-Okay.
Can you... show me how you two do it?
Yu-Yumiri?!
Alright.
Dear...
Don't... you have to look here.
Mom and Dad are amazing.
So you'll get there eventually
with mutual affection.
This is how married couples really are.
Dear...
Dear... my dear...
I'm cumming...
Yumiri-chan.
So, how was it?
U-Umm...
I learnt a lot, thanks.
Good night!
Learnt a lot?
Hey, Papa.
Let's do it again.
Mama!
So that's what sex is.
So you can do that if both of
you really love each other.
I guess you just want to do lots
of those things after all.
But, wasn't it surprisingly big?
My jaw kind of gets tired quite easily.
I don't really like that.
You two sure are nonchalant about it.
Don't you just get a real feel of it
when doing it with someone?
I'm not a kid anymore, you know.
Maybe you haven't gone to one yet.
Eh?
Oh, then somebody should get
this "expert" for me, please.
Nakata-senpai.
I have to sleep now.
I want to...
Oh no, I can't sleep with this!
My heart throbs just by thinking about it.
Good morning, Papa, Mama!
I'm already late so I'm going to skip breakfast.
Alright, I thought you'd be in a hurry, so
I already made a few extra sandwiches.
Thanks!
She's in love.
I'm sure she is.
Wait, isn't that bad?
With her having watched that and all.
And adventure.
Adventures are a part of romance.
I haven't slept for 25 hours,
and I'm now feeling sleepy.
Nakata-senpai...
His precise and gentle instructions for
the school festival were very cool.
It's all because of him that I was able
to give my all for the event.
And now I think us meeting together
there may have been fate!
His bold innocence is also what makes him good.
Hey, Yamada, are you still feeling sleepy?
Shut up.
Yumiri, good mornin'!
Mornin'.
Oh, he's there.
What's so good about that muddlehead?
I love you.
I'm at this district, so I'll be going first, okay?
I haven't even made myself known to him yet.
Well, my friend may have questioned my
preference over "that muddlehead",
but he's still the complete package, right?
Okay, now I've officially gone past 26 hours.
I don't think I'll even last a day.
She should have slept if she's really feeling sleepy.
You're damn right!
This person seems to be able to see us.
What a weirdo.
Ah, she must have done something
while she couldn't sleep!
Weirdo?
Well...
I guess I can just take it that way.
Hey, listen.
Is it really weird for a girl to be on the offensive
when it comes to the person she likes?
I think affection can also come
from a more solid expression.
Which means, sex would definitely
lead to love, I think.
Taking the actual process aside,
I've actually experienced how good it
is, and how amazing it is to be connected
to someone as one, anyway.
Also, girls asking out guys isn't really
that uncommon anymore,
so I can make the first move, right?
However...
No matter how I think about it,
I can't think of any situation where
we could be alone together.
Music Room
Umm... senpai,
I think this may sound rude,
but can you please teach me
how to play the piano?
And you are?
Well... I'm Hoshino Yumiri, First Year, Class 3.
Try to push a few chords.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Senpai!
Senpai, I've loved you for a long time!
Hoshino-kun...
Oh, is he associated with some kind of music dub?
Hmm... I think we might not ever meet there.
Art Room
Senpai,
please don't draw that, draw me instead.
My entire body!
A-And you are?
Gently, and with some paints, he proceeded to.
I go straight home after school, though.
My, my.
I wonder if there's any chance.
What about the infirmary?
There are even beds there.
That's right.
Like he was carried there because he was hurt.
Infirmary
Sensei, we have an injured patient!
He's bleeding profusely!
Prepare the emergency room!
Blood pressure is decreasing.
This is bad!
He's going into shock due to massive blood loss!
What's the patient's blood type?
Oh no, Nakata-senpai!
No!
No, no, no!
Senpai will die!
My my.
That situation is a bit too over the top, though.
When I think about it,
the way we met during the school
festival really was a whim of fate.
I never thought it'd be really difficult for
us to meet naturally on normal days.
Well, you don't really need to
think of weird situations.
See, I never got to sleep thinking
about these things.
You two sure have it easy, not ever having
to think too much about these things.
Well, when that time came we just naturally...
...met, and made out.
So... like pollen and hay fever?
Huh?
What? What?
Did I say something weird?
Not telling.
Sleeping in class isn't good, you know.
I'm sorry.
Now, now, everyone keep it down.
I've been dozing off for about two minutes.
About 29 hours and counting.
Minus two minutes.
Hey, no yawning!
And then, and then,
it was really amazing!
I must have been dreaming.
But it looks like I'm not as tired
after dozing off in class.
I also didn't get to see those two weirdos.
Senpai.
If we eventually manage to
have same privacy in here.
Bus to and fro school
Thank you, this is the last bus stop.
I've been waiting for us to be alone together.
You've been taking the same bus, right?
That got me curious.
Senpai!
Next stop, second district.
S-Sorry, I'm also getting off!
Please be careful.
Finally a contact point!
I'm sorry, I was in too much of a hurry.
Oh wait, it's like I'm introducing myself as a klutz.
Umm... senpai,
I need to talk to you about something.
Oh, the community hall is just straight ahead.
Senpai's really nice.
Wait, he's about to go!
The one road, currently being
walked on by this pair.
Though, some deviants might
spring up in this road.
Ah night in the park
I'll be taking this.
Save me!
Some weird guy is trying to,
is trying to rape me!
Umm... err...
You're...
Don't speak.
Please.
Here, little chicky.
Come out, come out.
He's gone.
Are you alright?
I was really scared!
I think that's really the only way!
Nakata
I'm home, Race.
I'm home.
Welcome home, you're quite late.
So this is where Nakata-senpai lives.
I'm sure that was his mother earlier.
Race, who are you barking at?
Oh, you're...
Hey, you're a student at our school, right?
I think we've already met before.
Do you need anything here?
Well, no, umm...
I just happened to pass by here.
Se-Senpai, may I ask what your blood type is?
What the heck am I saying?
I'm Type A.
Oh, you're Type A.
Do you need it for some fortune-telling?
Nope.
I asked just in case you'll need
a donor in the future.
I really need to know it beforehand.
Oh, and I'm Type AB by the way.
Th-Then, let's look out for each other
in case such a thing happens.
Okay, that's all I have to say.
Bye.
My voice finally reached senpai,
and senpai finally talked to me.
On top of that, senpai smiled!
Up close, a smile reserved for me!
I think, this is a lot better than any
of the scenarios I've imagined.
And so, I came home, without
knowing how or when.
So, what are you going to do next, Yumiri?
My heart throbs just by thinking of someone,
and I lose my nerve whenever
these feelings overwhelm me.
This is love, right?
Yup, that's what I think, too.
I think love is a one-sided pleasure.
It's not about what he thinks of me.
I think any experience I have
will determine how I'll act.
So it's more of a simple affection
than deep love, I suppose.
So actually,
I was planning on masturbating
tonight while thinking of him.
Can you watch me do it?
Ma...
Alright then.
...ma!
Thanks.
Oh yeah,
I was only able to sleep for two minutes in
the past forty hours and fifteen minutes.
Yumiri-chan.
Okay.
Senpai...
Nakata... senpai...
She seems to be exhausted.
She's sleeping so soundly
I'm getting worried from this point on.
Yumiri.
But, everyone marches toward adulthood this way.
Finding what makes them happy, one by one.
So we have to warmly watch over her.
yosomi wo shitetara chansu ga nigeteiku
Your chance will get way if you don't focus
mou matenai yo sasso aoutte READY GO
I can't wait anymore, come on, let's meet, Ready Go
kotoba no uragawa mirai no yukue toka
Rather than thinking about words
that hold some meaning for the future
mendou na koto wo souzou suru yori
and other bothersome things,
suki wa suki de ii ja nai
Just like whatever you want to like
hottokenai yo karada no oku ni
I can let it go, and within me,
ima kanjiteriru atsui kurasshu honoo ni natte
The passionate crash I feel turns into flames
kokoro sae mo makikomu
and even my heart wasn't saved from it
Get you! Get you! ii kagen na kimochi
Get you! Get you! These half-hearted feelings
Get you! Get you! sonna mon' ja nai yo
Get you! Get you! No, it's not really like that
yowaki ke tobaseba ato ni kawaru
Kick those feelings of weakness
and change will come afterward
Hit me! Hit me! yuutsu-sou na kao ya
Hit me! Hit me! Those melancholic expressions
Hit me! Hit me! poosu nante shitete
Hit me! Hit me! Just get on with it and strike a pose
tsukamaeyou I can ready go!
Let's get it all I can, Ready Go!
hara hara shitenakya ikiteru ki ga shinai
I don't feel like living if there's no excitement
taikutsu yori mo suriru mezashite Ready go
Thrills will always be better than
boring things, so Ready Go
ashita no watashi wa kinou to nitenai
I am different from the person I was yesterday
mainichi umare kawareru kara
And if I'm always reborn everyday like this
mamoru mono wa nai ja nai
I have nothing more to protect
minogasanai yo karada no oku ni
I can let it pass, and within me,
ima todoiteiru kimi no biito ookiku natte
The beats from you become bigger
tsuyoku mune wo ugokasu
Invigorating my heart
Get you! Get you! chotto hazushite mo
Get you! Get you! Even if I let it off a bit
Get you! Get you! doutte koto nai yo
Get you! Get you! It won't affect me at all
naritai jibun ni watashi nareru
I can become whatever I want
Hit me! Hit me! ai toka yume ni wa
Hit me! Hit me! In love and dreams
Hit me! Hit me! ruuru nanka nai yo
Hit me! Hit me! There are no rules
dakishimeyou I can ready go!
Let's all embrace it I can, Ready Go!
isogu kimochi wo osaetakunai ima sugu
I don't want to hold back from the rush, it's now or never
Get you! Get you! ii kagen na kimochi
Get you! Get you! These half-hearted feelings
Get you! Get you! sonna mon' ja nai yo
Get you! Get you! No it's not really like that
yowaki ke tobaseba go ni kawaru
Kick those feelings of weakness
and change will come afterward
Hit me! Hit me! yuutsu-sou na kao ya
Hit me! Hit me! Those melancholic expressions
Hit me! Hit me! poosu nante shitete
Hit me! Hit me! Just get on with it and strike a pose
tsukamaeyou I can ready go!
Let's get it all, I can Ready Go!
So, in 1192,
Minamoto no Yoritomo established
the Kamakura shogunate.
Sensei!
Oh, what is it, Hoshino?
Is it hard to get a boner with low blood pressure?
You dunce!