When I went back home for summer vacation,
my two older sisters and I kind of...
Well, I ended up having quite
a lewd relationship with them.
She's Megumi, the second daughter.
She's a bitchy gal just as she looks.
Having my cherry popped by her
was the best thing I experienced.
She's Ayami, the eldest daughter.
Her beauty and pheromone can attract anyone.
She still calls me "Boku-kun" up to this day.
Those sisters that everyone envied me for having...
I think that they'll be milking me dry again today.
I Want to be Squeezed by My Lewd Older Sister♥
Amply Squeezing Older Sisters
Just from thinking that I live under
the same roof as those two,
it won't settle down no matter
how many times I come!
Which sister are you fantasizing about
while stroking yourself, Boku-kun?
A-Aya-nee!
That's okay. Continue fapping.
I'm gonna help you.
Don't think about Megu.
Stroke yourself while imagining
my lewd appearance.
Until you squirt your baby batter
and spurt everything out, I'll give you a hand!
Oh no, you already got so hard!
I want you to feel good a lot from my hand!
Fippity, fappity, fap fap!
Hey, you can't shoot it out yet.
I'm going to catch it all in the end,
so shoot plenty of your healthy sperm out!
Wow!
Your dick looks like it'll burst any minute now!
That's...
His dick feels hot and hard!
His precum is splashing around!
I feel that he'll knock me up even from
my mouth if he comes just like this!
I won't last long with something like this...
Are you about to come?
Shoot it out! Make it squirt!
Spray it all over me!
Aya-nee...
I'm coming...
Boku-kun, your thick sperm feels hot!
I might end up getting hooked on Boku-kun's scent!
I'll come here again late at night, alright?
Toilet... I need to go to the toilet...
M-Megu-nee!
Let's drink more...
H-Huh?
What are you doing?
Making a move on your sleeping dear sister...
You've got some guts, huh?
You're wrong!
What do you mean I'm wrong
when this one here is all set to go?
Th-This is just a morning wood!
Let's see... Maybe I should
ask you down here instead!
Come on, I'll be gentle!
It's already rock hard!
Not having a fling at the club last night
might have been the right choice!
Ever since I had sex with you,
every other man started
to look unappealing to me!
Make sure to take responsibility for it!
Responsibility?
Thanks for the meal!
Yes, this is it!
I can't forget about this wild cock!
Megu-nee, you're being too intense!
I feel bad for Aya-nee,
but I'll get you off using my technique!
Until Aya-nee's portion is gone,
I'll squeeze your semen out down here!
Your cock tastes good!
Come on, shoot it out... Shoot it out! All of it!
Make me drink your semen!
Megu-nee!
I'm getting squeezed dry!
This smell is making my head spin...
It's making me so horny!
Dummy...
You dumped me with such thick semen...
Hey, don't you want to go further?
Here...
Ta-da!
Come on... Get on with it already...
Megu-nee, I'm putting it in!
It's going inside me!
The cock of my little brother that's left
under my care is pounding me deep inside!
Megu-nee, your insides feel hot!
Power pistoning me right away is too rash!
Don't!
You're kneading my tits!
They're getting disfigured!
Megu-nee, you're being loud!
What's the problem?
Doesn't it feel better when you
let your voice out during sex?
Won't Aya-nee hear us when you're too loud?
Huh?
Aya-nee has nothing to do with this!
Forget about that and focus on fucking me!
Oh gosh! Oh gosh!
My head is spinning from getting drunk!
I started having sex with my
little brother before realizing it!
Fuck me! Shake your hips harder!
There's no doubt that I'll go crazy from this!
Megu-nee, you suddenly got tighter!
Come! Come!
Make my pussy drink your semen!
End it by giving your sister a creampie!
I'm coming!
It's pouring in...
Your semen is filling me up inside!
You came too much!
Sorry, one more round!
No kissing! I don't want to!
But you grew up to be my type of guy...
I made up my mind!
You're thrusting so deep! The semen in my
baby room is getting sloshed around!
Megu-nee, I'm gonna come again!
More... Come a lot more!
Your intense pistoning is making me come!
Your semen is pouring in...
You're forcibly making me gulp it in!
I can't drink anymore...
Hey... Don't just sleep there!
I wonder if Megu-nee is still asleep...
Boku-kun, I'm going in!
H-Huh!?
Aya-nee, what are you wearing?
How are they? Do they look good on me?
Alright, come here.
I'll take care of you.
Whoa... It feels so slippery.
I'll make you feel so much good
that you won't be able
to think about anything else!
You've been having sex with Megu since morning
but you're still this lively!
You're amazing!
You knew about it?
If she moans that loud,
anyone will realize it!
That Megu...
She sounded like she's in heaven
with that lewd voice!
I was so jealous...
I get soaking wet just from remembering it!
What's inside here is your baby juice.
Too bad that Megu took some of them!
When I imagine them aiming at and
charging towards Megu's ovum,
I end up want the same too...
Thinking about how good procreative
sex must feel makes me horny!
The truth is, I want you
to shoot it out for me alone.
I want to drink all of your baby juice semen!
Boku-kun! Boku-kun!
Shoot all of them out for me!
I can't take it anymore!
I can't hold myself back!
I'm craving for sex!
Boku-kun, your dick is reaching deep inside me!
It's thrashing around in my pussy!
My pussy is saying that it wants
your dick to keep on scraping it!
Aya-nee, your insides are so slippery!
Your swimsuit earlier was so lewd!
That's because I thought that you might
prefer outfits like what Megu wears!
It was embarrassing and I got a bit jealous,
but I thought that it might
help you come even more...
When you say something like that...
There's so much pouring in...
Boku-kun's baby juice is squirting...
It's spilling out...
Let's do it one more time!
Aya-nee!
I love how deep it goes in!
I love your power piston!
You're digging into my baby room deep inside!
It's getting deformed!
You're venting all of your lust deep into me!
I'm supposed to be the older sister, but my
little brother's dick is making me feel good!
I can tell that you're close.
I'm gonna make you ejaculate!
It's okay, Boku-kun.
Come a lot and give your sister an orgasm!
Aya-nee!
Boku-kun!
You came so much!
It's kinda unfair that you
always get it good, Aya-nee!
Huh? Boku-kun woke up.
You're both licking my...
Boku-kun, your precum is awesome!
I'll end up losing my mind when I smell this!
Hey, that's not fair!
That's too much!
You're still so hard!
I'm gonna work hard to
make both of you pregnant!
No, you're being too rough!
Not there!
It's hitting a part where I
never knew it could reach!
It's pressing against my prolapsing womb!
You're turning me into your woman!
You too, Aya-nee!
I'll turn your body into something
that can't live without me!
Boku-kun, your feelings are
reaching deep in my womb!
We're becoming one through my pussy!
No, I'm gonna come!
I'm gonna come from being
turned into your woman!
Megu-nee, I love you!
Dummy! I feel the same!
No, you'll break my pussy!
I love you too, Aya-nee!
Boku-kun, I love you too!
Onee-chan, bear my child!
I will! I'll do it.
Give me a baby!
Shoot it out! Knock me up using that
little brother semen of yours!
Anyway, you're not allowed
to masturbate anymore.
Whenever you feel horny, your sisters will...
...squeeze it all out for you!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji