It's the summer of my first year
living at the school dorm.
Who waits for my return to our family's home
are my kind and lewd older sisters.
She's Ayami, the eldest daughter.
She's a relaxed, mild and soothing girl,
but she has such a potent pheromone
that gives any typical man an erection.
Welcome home, Boku-kun!
What's the matter?
Are you tired from your trip?
I-I'm okay, I'll put my baggage in my room.
Huh?
So, you came home.
She's Megumi, the second daughter.
She's a bitchy gal just as she looks.
I have these two as my older sisters.
For a virgin like me, they honestly are...
...temptations for my eyes.
Or rather, what are you ogling at?
N-Nothing!
That's a riot!
Are you peeking at your older sister's
panties just 'coz you're a virgin?
I
I-I
I-I-I
I-I-I-I
I-I-I-I-I'mma notcha virgin!
If you want to see them that much...
...I'll show them to you!
It can't be helped...
H-Huuuh!?
What do you think? Are you getting horny?
Look, this part is squishy!
So that's Megu-nee's...
Wow... He's gawking so much!
I might come a little from this...
Boku-kun!
Somebody is getting in my way!
Come here after putting away your baggage!
I wonder if I'll be able to withstand
the advances of my older sisters.
I Want to be Squeezed by My Lewd Older Sister♥
Gently Squeezing Older Sisters
What's wrong, Boku-kun?
Did Megu tease you again?
Uhh... Well, that's...
Huh? Panties?
Hmm...
So, Megu did that...
Hey...
Wanna see my panties too?
Huh? Can I?
But I'm sorry!
I'm not wearing any panties!
Huuuh!?
S-So this is a pussy...
So, were you surprised?
Oh... Boku-kun is horny from looking at me!
Today is a special day, so...
Here, you can touch my tits!
A-Aya-nee's tits...
Do my tits feel good to touch?
They're the best... This is my
first time touching them.
Oh, my...
Boku-kun, you're hard down here as well...
It's giving off a very lewd scent!
If you'll keep it a secret from Megu,
I'll do something more amazing for you.
O-Okay...
Good boy!
Oh my, that's amazing!
You became splendid down here!
It reeks of a strong masculine smell.
It's making me feel dizzy...
Alright, then...
I'm gonna rub it using my hands.
Wow, it got so hot!
It's so stiff and splendid!
I wonder if there were times when you used me
as a fap material while you masturbate.
I'm sorry, I did...
I see!
Fantasizing is alright, but isn't the real thing great?
Licking and touching you like this...
The smell and the taste as well...
Hey, let's kiss.
Aya-nee...
Is it about to come out?
Are you gonna squirt already?
It's okay! Come on, Boku-kun!
Shoot it out with all your might!
It's coming out!
There's a lot of your thick stuff!
If you can keep this a secret
from Megu just as I told you,
I'll do something even more
amazing for you, alright?
Hey, what were you doing
with Aya-nee earlier?
N-Nothing in particular...
Hmm...
Oh, whatever...
By the way, have you seen a pussy before?
Huh!? I-I-I haven't...
Of course, you didn't!
Then, as a special treat...
If you'll masturbate right here,
then I'm gonna show you my pussy.
Is that for real!?
You already have a boner! Hilarious!
Th-Then... You too, Megu-nee!
Don't get too impatient.
Here you go!
Whoa!
Megu-nee's pussy...
What do you think? Isn't it pretty
despite me fooling around?
Up here as well!
M-Megu-nee...
Doing something this pervy
is making me so horny!
You're looking at my body,
and it drips with precum as you rub it!
I think that I myself have gotten into this as well!
I'm already...
Yes!
Megu-nee, I'm still...
It can't be helped...
Don't tell Aya-nee about this.
It's my little brother's cock...
This could be dangerous!
Megu-nee, it feels amazing inside your mouth!
Oh, this really is amazing!
This erotic scent...
I knew it, this boy really did
something with Aya-nee...
He's my dear little brother
who I haven't seen for a while.
That's why I'll never hand him over to Aya-nee!
I'm getting milked out by Aya-nee,
and then followed by Megu-nee...
Megu-nee, I'm already...
You can shoot it out!
It's coming out!
Megu-nee is covered with my semen.
Your semen is so thick!
Doesn't my tit-pussy feel good?
You can have as much titjobs as you want.
I won't lose even against Aya-nee...
Huh?
It's nothing!
Come on, thrust it harder!
Your cock feels so hot!
Won't I get burned from this!?
It actually feels like you're raping my breast!
You're engrossed in shaking
your hips! That's so cute!
This feels too good!
It's coming out!
You'd definitely want to put it
in my pussy after that, right?
Come on, put that rugged
virgin cock inside me!
Hurry up!
I'll finally get rid of my virginity!
Boku-kun!
Can you come here?
Huh?
Don't go.
Megu-nee...
I'm telling you not to go to Aya-nee!
That's because I'll be taking your virginity!
And with this, you got rid of your virginity!
Gosh, Megu...
I wonder if she seduced him earlier.
So deep!
Aren't you glad to have your first time with me?
Your cock is too titillating!
No ordinary woman will be able to handle it!
What's happening!? It's making me feel so good!
Is my little brother's cock this incredible!?
It feels so good!
You're being cheeky for someone who was
still a virgin until a moment ago!
My insides feel like getting all mushed up!
You're turning it into your personal fuckhole!
No, this is bad! If you'll come inside me right now,
you'll definitely end up knocking me out!
Megu-nee, I'm gonna shoot it inside!
No... No, you can't!
Coming inside will be dangerous!
My little brother's semen
is actually flowing into me...
Megu-nee, thank you...
Having sex with my little brother is the best!
It's way better than all the men I had until now!
Oh no! Aya-nee was calling me earlier!
I finally got rid of my virginity!
Though my partner was my blood-related older sister.
Aya-nee, sorry for taking so long.
Huuuh!?
Boku-kun...
I got tired of waiting...
I got horny from hearing
you and Megu having sex!
I've been doing it by myself, you know!
The truth is, I wanted to be your first woman.
But you got along well with Megu now.
Aya-nee...
It seems that Megu and I
have been competing for you.
It somehow makes me feel fired up!
I think Megu is still in the middle of an orgasm.
What would you like to do?
I wanna do it! I wanna have sex with you, Aya-nee!
That's a very good answer!
Here's my pussy as a reward!
I'm going to gobble down your dick, alright?
Aya-nee, your pussy is already dripping wet.
Boku-kun, your dick went inside me!
I'm having sex with Aya-nee right now!
I finally became one with you.
I am so happy right now!
Your dick feels so good!
Forgive us for being such lewd sisters!
I never knew that you're this indecent, Aya-nee!
That's because your dick is amazing!
Megu might hear my voice!
I want to give you more pleasure, Aya-nee!
I love this!
It feels like you're raping me!
Be my woman from now on!
I'm happy!
I will! I will become your woman!
So shoot it inside! Fill my insides up!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
I'm about to become your woman!
Give me a creampie! I want your semen!
I'm gonna come, Aya-nee!
You're shooting your semen deep inside me!
It felt way better than anything I had until now!
Gosh, Boku-kun...
You've grown into a full-fledged
man before I even noticed!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization