This is the file of all the students at the academy.
l'll take that.
ln a vague educational system...
...it's impossible to show the world the talented students you have.
l will choose the students myself...
...and personally give guidance and a special education to gifted students.
Yes. You have become everyone's target of attention.
Do a good job.
l'll try my hardest not to be embarrassed...
...by all the attention that has been drawn.
For the details, please ask Ms. Honoka Sakura here.
l have done research on your working history.
The principal was all for accepting you, but...
...l think there is a slight problem.
And why is that?
When you used to work at Tenhouin Academy...
...you were cajoling a female student.
Cajoling? You use such an old-fashioned word, don't you?
Stop pretending you don't know anything.
l'm sorry, but the research is reliable. The proof is solid too.
Hmph! And?
Are you turning defiant?
Well, you can take it whatever way you like.
And what do you want to do about it?
We're going to hand you over to the police of course.
That's what l want to say, but...
...l want your teaching ability.
So l want you to pledge right here...
...''As a chemistry teacher, l will fulfill my duties.''
Oh, so you're going to overlook me, huh?
So for that l should do your favor for my own sake, huh?
lt's not for you.
lt's not only for this academy but the principal too.
l understand.
Ms. Honoka Sakura, it seems like you also need a special education.
W-What do you mean?
Ms. Honoka, l guess you're more perverted than l thought.
l-lt's not like that! That was...
l don't really want to hear your excuse.
Well instead, with that tongue of yours that was sucking on mine...
...let's have you lick this.
N-No, please stop Mr. Kagami.
lt's too late now!
l like those rebellious eyes of yours.
Even you, so cold but beautiful like an ice goddess...
...if you're sucking on a man's penis you only look like an obscene female.
lt's so big and soft, Ms. Honoka.
Even though you fight me so much your pussy is soaking wet already.
lt's so good... and deep...
lt's intense!
You, who is called the academy's goddess in this kind of appearance...
P-Please stop! Don't take it! Don't take it!
lt's payment for trying to threaten me.
lf you try to expose my past...
...l will post these images and scatter them all over the lnternet.
No... No!
First off...
l should start...
He seems wonderful... The new teacher...
He's in charge of chemistry...
Maybe l should join the chemistry club.
This is nostalgic.
This was a song l played back in the day...
You're even more beautiful than l imagined from your picture, Yuzuki.
Hello? What can l do for you?
The newly-appointed... teacher?
Yes, my name is Shin Kagami and l'm in charge of chemistry.
Really? l can't believe big brother is here at Shuka Academy.
Were you aware of me?
l was skeptical.
Because... Yuzuki, you had become so beautiful.
P-Please...
Y-You don't have to flatter a childhood friend.
lt's not flattery. You really have become so beautiful.
Ah... uh... um...
Thank you...
...very much.
Oh yeah, are you free after school?
Huh? Tomorrow?
l don't have club activities, so l'll be free.
Really. Then...
...would you like to go to a concert with me?
U-Um, l would love to go with you.
Big brother, today's concert was wonderful.
Yeah. l'm glad we came.
Well, shall we go have dinner?
Actually today, um, well...
...l want to buy some groceries.
Groceries? Why?
l want to cook something for you at your house.
Okay. Let's stop at the grocery store and then go to my house.
l'll take you on your way home.
Yeah!
Big brother, can l ask you a question?
What's up?
That time... Why did you leave without saying anything to me at all?
That was when l had to move to my uncle's house. He's the principal.
Huh? T-that principal of the academy is your uncle?
Okay. l understand. l'll believe it because it's your words.
Thank you. l'm sorry l didn't get to say anything to you then.
lt's okay. Don't worry about it anymore.
But l still can't forgive the fact that l didn't hear from you for so long.
Then how can l be forgiven?
Brother... we kissed.
You didn't want to?
Of course not. Actually, l want you to do more.
Brother, if it's you, l could give you everything.
For so long... l loved you for so long.
l see. l'm happy, Yuzuki.
Brother, l love you.
Your voice is so cute, Yuzuki.
l'm embarrassed, Brother...
You don't have to be embarrassed. You are so cute, really.
Brother... Brother, if you're pleased, l'm happy.
l love you, brother...
Thank you, Yuzuki.
l would do anything for you...
B-Brother?
Don't be that amazed, Yuzuki.
While l didn't see you, your body has turned so obscene.
No...
Brother, your eyes... They're scaring me.
Did someone massage them already?
W-Why...
No one massaged them!
That's good!
That's a nice face, Yuzuki. The face of falling into despair...
So, can l hear more of that tragic voice from before?
N-No!
You are being turned on by this abnormal situation, aren't you?
N-No, stop it. Seriously, please stop.
Why do l have to stop?
W-Why? Because it's like l'm being raped.
l'm actually intending to rape you right now.
Broth...
l beg you Brother, please stop!
Plea... Ah! N-No! No!
No, no, no!
lt hurts, it hurts!
Shut up! You can't run anymore.
Give up and stop being tense!
No! No!
l won't try to run anymore. So please stop putting your finger in my butt!
So you decided not to run anymore, huh? Then the front is okay?
Y-Yes. lt's okay, so please take your finger out of my butt.
Really, so it is okay? But l don't want to take my finger out.
First of all, you said before you would do anything for me, didn't you?
T-That's because... N-No!
lt hurts! lt hurts!
Yuzuki, is it turning you on?
lt's your first anal, right?
No, it's... not... Don't move... your fingers...
But your pussy is clearly soaked.
lt's a celebration!
W-What you are you doing, Brother!
Wait, are you putting that in?
lt's a rare occasion, so...
...if you can't drink, then l want you to be able to enjoy it from this side.
No! Wait, stop it...
...don't put something like that in!
No! lt's going in...
W-What is this? My body's... hot...
lt's hot...
Now, Yuzuki, l'm taking your anal virginity.
lf it's the backside's virginity then you'll let me hear a pleasant scream.
No! No!
lt hurts, it hurts...
Yuzuki, if you don't stop tensing it's going to split.
Come on, stop tensing up.
lt's impossible... to stop tensing... lt's impossible... impossible...
Whether it's impossible or not, l'm sticking it in till the end.
lt hurts!
lt's only the tip that went in.
lf you're suffering right now, if l start moving, it looks like you'd die.
l'm gonna... l'm gonna die!
l'm going to die!
Yuzuki...
l'm sorry...
B-Brother?
This feast is still...
...going to continue!
No!
The hole is so tight it's like it's going to be torn off...
...but how about the inside?
Yuzuki, the truth is you are turned on by your butthole, aren't you?
l'm not turned... on...
l'm not turned...
lt's moving so much.
lt feels so good...
l'm going to move more!
No! No!
No more!
Stop it... stop it...
lt's great... lt's great!
Please, l-l'm gonna go insane!
Sorry, but l can't stop now.
l'm about to come. So you gotta put up with it!
No! l'm gonna go crazy!
l can't... l can't anymore... My stomach's full!
lt's good... lt's so good!
l can't... l just can't!
l'm gonna come.
l'm gonna come, Yuzuki!
No!
lt's hot!
B-Brother...
l... l love you...
...Brother...