Wow...
So this is how the castle
looks like from the inside!
Laranoa...
What—
Hiroki?
Elf Student
and Teacher
Volume 1: The Secret Afterschool Date
One day, the world got connected
with what used to be a fantasy...
A parallel world inhabited by demi-humans.
The nation of Japan accepted twenty
young elven women as students,
all for the purpose of building
mutual trust and understanding.
The government requested for me,
Kobayashi Hiroki, to serve
as a guide and look over these elves
from another world as their teacher.
These elves are my students.
Laying my hands on them is out of the question.
However, for someone like me who never
even had a relationship with humans
and being a fantasy lover in the first place,
I always admired elves.
After a series of various coincidences,
I ended up being in a romantic relationship with
one of the girls, Laranoa Oreale Graz Elzumia.
I definitely can't let anyone find out
about this relationship of ours.
Aren't you being so sudden? You surprised me.
Sorry, I couldn't hold myself back.
I just wanted to embrace you already, Laranoa.
Hiroki, that kind of tickles...
This might be sudden, but can we do it?
Of course, I won't mind.
Isn't this a place for that sort of thing?
Then, umm...
Would you mind licking it first?
Okay...
You really got better on this, huh?
If you say so...
...it makes me very happy.
Doesn't it feel good here when I do it like this?
Hiroki, what are you—
I can't breathe, Hiroki!
I can't breathe!
I'm coming!
I'm sorry, did I scare you?
I sure am. It was a little hard for me.
Well, as long as it makes you happy...
Then, shall we continue?
Okay...
Wow, you got so wet.
Hey, look at this.
You're so mean.
Lick it up.
N-No... If you keep on doing that...
What do you want? Do you
want to come just like this?
N-No...
I want you inside me!
What are you doing?
Don't! Not there!
Hiroki... stop it already!
Don't lick me down there!
I can't!
Ah, that's...
Hiroki, this feels great!
Hiroki, this feels so good!
Hiroki... Come, Hiroki!
I'm gonna come, Laranoa!
Come... together with me!
That was a close one.
I ran into other students
right after I got off the car.
I ran into other students right after I got off the car.
Next time, maybe I should
get off somewhere farther
from the dorm.MMM
Next time, maybe I should
get off somewhere farther
from the dorm.MMM
I understand.
Let's do that next time.
Next time, maybe I should get off
somewhere farther from the dorm.
I understand. Let's do that next time.
Hiroki, doing this here isn't a good idea.
Isn't this very risky?
Isn't it fine? No one's around right now.
Our relationship will be found out
if someone comes here.
Can't we just lock the door?
Do you want to do it here that much?
I've been dreaming of this.
I wasn't able to do this
when I was still a student.
So you're more turned on than usual?
That's because we're inside the school.
Doing it in such a place would be...
But that's what makes this more exciting, right?
What are you...
I want to take your panties off. Won't it be fine?
If that's what you want, then do as you please.
Then lift your skirt up.
O-Okay...
What are you doing?
I want to check how wet you are.
Hiroki! Wait, it hurts!
You're being too rough!
Then...
Will it be alright if we do it like this?
No! You're being too rough on me!
Laranoa, look at me.
Hiroki, I've been on the edge for a while now!
It's alright, I'm also about to come!
I can't take it!
I'm coming!
I wonder where Laranoa is.
Wasn't that a close one?
We're not doing it in the
classroom anymore.
Wasn't that a close one?
We're not doing it in the
classroom anymore.
Wasn't that a close one?
We're not doing it in the classroom anymore.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization