Seems like you've gotten used to this.
That's not... true at all.
And besides...
And besides... In a place like this...
What's that? Aren't you excited from our battle today?
You're quite into it.
Who would be excited!?
I'm an elf!
I would never stoop so...
Oh, really?
Then, I guess I'll just enjoy myself.
So rough...
Incredible.
Your pussy is like a virgin's.
It keeps squeezing me no matter how long I fuck you.
Do you love my cock that much?
No! This is disgusting...
If it weren't for the Promised Rite, nobody would do this with you!
Even though you say that, you're about to cum, aren't you?
Go!
It's kind of fun doing it in a place like this, isn't it?
Esteemed Elf Princess.
Who would, with you!?
If only it weren't you, then I...
Elf Princess Nina
Vol.01
Princess Trapped in the Sex Castle
Long ago, there was a lone king.
A king possessing immense power, yet
obsessed with obtaining more power.
Though he was a king meant to lead the humans, he became
a demon king who ruled over other demon kings.
At that time...
A survivor from the Demon King's genocide and
descendant of the king once more appeared...
This person was a light of hope.
Seven people gathered to serve the good King.
Noble humans who hadn't forgotten to pay tribute to the gods.
The Dwarf tribe of the Soil Country.
The female Elf tribe of the Forest Country.
The young Hobbits of the Grass Country.
A sage possessing ancient knowledge.
And the Royal Family's Sorcerer of Darkness.
At the end of their conquest remained the Demon King.
A demon king who controlled all demons,
and sought control of all humans as well.
Warriors from various places gathered under our hero...
To take part in a war of the heroes.
At the end of this war, a new era awaited.
Dusk turned to dawn.
Thanks to the Son of Light and the friends aiding
him, the sun rose once more upon the planet.
Bring praise and honor to the seven heroes.
And as the planet was reborn...
Until the new era dawns...
The planet will once more fall silent.
While watching over the dreams of the esteemed heroes,
a brief period of fulfillment begins.
Nina-sama.
Princess?
O-Oh, what is it?
Are you unsatisfied with this journey after all?
I feel your pain, Princess.
F-Fear not. We need not worry.
This Promised Rite is for the future prosperity of us Elves.
And seeing it through is my duty as Princess of Holy Filheim.
Princess!
Seil...
Princess Nina Asraat Winvilia of the Holy Filheim Kingdom!
Make way!
So glad you could make it, Princess of the Elves.
Yes. I have come to undergo the Promised
Rite for the sake of my people.
No amount of thanks could express my gratitude.
In the name of my father, King Filheim, please accept my thanks.
Oh? With the breeding prowess of... never mind.
You possess intelligence superior to our Royal Family,
and a nearly eternal lifespan. It can't be helped if
the desire to keep your race pure has grown thin.
If the blood of our Royal Family could be of service to your
superior race, we'll put our best effort into doing so.
Thank you very much.
In exchange, during the month in which this
legendary Promised Rite takes place...
...can you pledge your loyalty to the Holy Seilhelm Empire?
Yes.
Then our contract is complete.
Beautiful Elf Princess, please raise your head.
Seil...
Welcome, Princess Nina.
Kyle!?
The hero who struck down Zeromuth the
Demon King, was Seil Van Ganossa.
And one of the heroes who fought beside
him was Princess Nina of the High Elves.
You came between their love, then took
your elder brother, Seil's, place.
What a bad man you are.
You're one to talk, being the Dark Elf that assassinated my brother.
But is this okay?
What will happen when that Elf princess finds out that
you're the one to perform the Promised Rite with her?
There'll be no problems.
I've already put the pressure on her.
Quite thoroughly, I might add.
Why, is he...
Seil should be the ruler of this land.
I was supposed to swear my loyalty to Seil!
If it were Seil, I would have gladly given myself to him.
Seil!
Princess!
Princess, Princess!
Good timing. Come in.
I have decided to withdraw from the Promised Rite.
My father's still in good health, so we need not hurry.
But Princess...
What's wrong?
Actually, a swift horse from our
kingdom just arrived with a message.
Your father...
The King has collapsed from the plague!
What!?
Cornering the Princess with such a lie?
What a horrible king you are.
Call me what you wish.
With this, you've created a situation in which she has
no choice but to proceed with the Promised Rite.
Yes, and what's more...
During the month in which the Promised Rite takes place...
...the Princess will be a vassal to our
kingdom, as the old laws decree.
The King of Seilhelm!
Sorry about that,
suggesting a plan to deceive your own princess.
N-Not at all. We appreciate your consideration
for our kingdom Filheim.
Thank you for your efforts, and please
take good care of our princess.
Yes. I promise the best treatment for your princess.
I would also like to reward you three for going along with my plan.
But you shouldn't.
We deserve no reward for our services.
I insist.
I'm sure in time, you won't be able to live without it.
King of Seilhelm, what is this?
Your reward.
That, and a new home... this room.
K-King of Seilhelm... How could you?
I think they should taste an elf's virginity
before meeting your princess.
It's just foreplay, after all.
N-No!
Help me!
Princess, help us!
Don't worry.
You needn't worry. You'll become more beautiful from this.
D-Dark Elf!
What a beautiful bottom.
I'd like to eat it.
You... vile Dark Elf, how dare you!
Not there...
Not in such a dirty hole...
And from an evil Dark Elf...
Oh, and here I was planning to be gentle with you.
Fine, then I'll give you something even more disgusting than myself.
What?
Something's coming inside.
Something wet... Coming inside...
No...
No further than that.
Don't push it in!
No... I told you not to.
I told you to stop!
Don't worry. The rest begins here.
What? Something's coming.
Spreading open... Inside my sullied hole, expanding...
Wh-What is this thing?
It's slippery and wet...
This is a meat stick. Cock. Penis.
A dick.
No, don't touch it.
It feels strange.
It's painful!
If it hurts, there's a way to make it feel better.
No...
Have mercy...
Hey, hey, hey...
My dick... My dick's throbbing.
So let me do you. Let me fuck you.
If I put it in your hole...
And thrust it in and out...
It'll feel better, she told me.
The hole in front is already occupied.
Then, this one... This hole.
This one's dirtier and more filthy than the front.
Let me rub my dick inside.
No! Stop, have mercy. Sto...
My dick feels good. So good.
I love this!
I love the way your butthole squeezes so tightly.
Let me go!
Don't...
If you do this to me, I'll never return to normal...
I'll never be able to face the Elf Queen!
Yes!
Even Elves are just bitches in heat.
No, please let me go.
No... Let me go... Let me go home... To my kingdom.
What? You're still talking about that?
So rough! What a big dick!
Too rough! I'm ripping apart!
Elvish bodies are every bit as tight as I've heard.
Now, accept the fine semen of royalty!
Taste plenty of it before your princess!
It's... your dick is shaking!
There's... so much inside.
So much royal seed... flowing out.
I'm gonna cum.
I'm also gonna cum.
Cumming from my dick!
I'm an Elf, but I'm going to impregnate you.
I'll get you pregnant through the butt!
No! No more! No!
It's still throbbing.
My dick's throbbing.
Throbbing nonstop.
I'm cumming again, cumming again!
Perhaps this was too intense for elves who have no interest in sex.
Don't tell me... You intend to do the same to our princess?
Rest at ease. She's special, unlike you girls.
Wh-What are...!?
Later.
When the time comes, I'll let you see your beloved princess again.
Penises... So many...
Kyle...
Is Seil really dead?
While on a quest to defeat the magic
dragon Skuhame, he disappeared.
How many times must I tell you before you understand?
But I...
Rest at ease.
If you and I can produce a child, the
Elven race's future will be saved.
Only the child will be mine, not my brothers.
I'll make it so you can't live without me.
Don't misunderstand.
I might let you use my body, but you will never have my heart.
If the Promised Rite didn't exist, I would
have nothing to do with you!
Seil is the only one I can confide in and entrust myself to.
Hey, wrehe are you going?
To bathe in the night wind.
I don't want to breathe the same air as you!
There might still be some rebels in the area nearby.
So be careful.
Seriously, you should be more careful.
Seil...
What?
That armor... Are you with the rebels?
Let go!
In our battle today, I thought I saw an elf in the empire's ranks...
To think that she was such a beauty.
Tied up like this, you can't use your magic, right?
It's not often a man gets an opportunity to fuck an Elf.
Wh-What are you doing!?
I hear you're different from human females.
I asked you a question! What are you doing!?
Don't talk down to us, bitch!
Do you realize the position you're in right now?
W-Well, I...
What is it? Esteemed Elf Princess...
Could this be your first time seeing a human penis?
Then, is she a virgin?
You hit a gold mine.
Unhand me!
Who do you think I am!?
It's obvious.
You sneak out in the middle of the night, to get raped.
A stupid, stuck-up elf.
Okay, here I come.
W-Wai...
It's coming inside.
A filthy human's dick is entering me...
What? What gives? She's not a virgin!
What the hell!? For such a high-and-mighty attitude,
you've been getting around, haven't you?
Well, I...
If that's the case, we don't need to hold back, then.
Take that!
Stop!
If you move... I'll feel it.
Isn't that the point?
Come on, I'll break your little pussy and fuck you silly!
No... A male... A human male is violating me.
If this keeps up...
It hurts!
It's in too deep... stirring me up...
What a sexy voice.
Take care of me, too.
It smells!
You're going to suck on that smelly thing, you Elf!
Don't you dare bite!
I love her mouth!
Just like a whore's pussy, it's sucking on me tight.
Her real pusses also perfect.
So even a slutty, whore elf is this tight?
Stop...
Right now...
What are you saying?
I can't hear you!
I'm going to cum.
With your mouth...
Taste how a human tastes!
Stop it!
If you keep this up...
What are you saying? The rest are holding back!
Look.
What?
What are you all doing?
Isn't it obvious?
They're masturbating to you.
T-To me?
Stop it...
Looking at me, holding your penises!
I can't believe you're looking at me while stroking your penises...
Stop masturbating to me!
No guy can watch a dime like you get raped and not get stiff.
Come on, come on, let them get a better view.
So, rough...
While they're... masturbating to me.
I hate this!
Don't!
Stop, stop it... Take it out!
This is strange, I feel so strange...
All this... even though I'm getting raped,
with people beating off to me...
Even though I'm getting raped by a filthy human... I'm going to cum!
That's great, I'm cumming too!
I'll bury my human seed deep inside your slutty womb.
No! I don't want human sperm... I don't want human children!
No!
He's cumming... lots of semen into my womb.
I'm pregnant.
I'm pregnant with a human baby...
Stop it.
I'm going to stink.
I'm going to stink like human sperm...
And yet, I'm cumming again!
Are you sure we should have done all that?
Orders from the Emperor, after all.
This way!
Shoot the enemy front line!
Your Emperor Highness, what is this!?
They ran away!
After them!
Didn't I warn you?
Here you are looking like this again.
Kyle!
They came inside me!
A whole lot.
With human sperm.
I'm... I'm going to...
Yes, at this rate, you'll become pregnant for sure.
With a lowlife human.
I don't want that!
I don't want to give birth to a human!
No! No!
I have this for that.
That's a... Purification Stone?
Correct.
With this, we can purify your womb.
Is it already over?
Yes...
But are you okay with that?
Since I purified your womb... the sperm
I gave you disappeared as well.
Looks like we've got more to look forward to, Nina.
Until we're sure you're pregnant, that is.
Listen, these feelings I could not abandon, strangling my heart.
nee suterare nakute mune o shimeru kono omoi
Listen, this love that resembles admiration is so heartbreaking.
nee akogare ni nita ai ga setsunakute itai
Please remember the courage received on that fateful day...
ano hi moratta yuuki omoi dashite
And always gaze only at the light.
zutto zutto hikari dake mitsumete
The light that shines on that place seen in dreams long ago.
itsuka yume ni mita ano basho e
And become stronger, stronger,
motto tsuyoku tsuyoku
So that my wish won't become impossible to grant.
hatasenai negai ni narete shimawanu you ni