What's wrong?
This is a parade to honor our bonds.
Conduct yourself more appropriately.
What is it?
Are humans not worthy of the Princess of Filheim's good graces?
T-That's not...
Princess!
You! First you ditch work, then you're out here drinking!?
That hurts, Ma.
Stop drinking so early in the day and get some work done!
Yeah, but it's in Elf princess!
I've never seen such beauty!
Well, I've never seen a drunkard as bad as you.
Oww.
Come on, Ma, that hurts!
Even if it's just once I want to do her.
Just get to work already, you worm!
Oww, come on, that hurts, Ma!
Elf Princess Nina
Vol.02
The Prostitute Princess in the Tentacle Suit
What's wrong?
Why don't you stop idling over there and come closer?
What exactly are you two doing?
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious?
Right?
Women, you see, have other ways besides
using their vagina to please men...
Like I'm doing here.
Although, I do suppose this would be impossible for you.
I don't do lewd things like Dark Elves!
But Kyle's...
I mean, once you taste royalty deep inside
your body, you'll start wanting more.
Don't you feel the same way?
U-Unbelievable! I...
Your duty for your Elven people is to have
a healthy child from royal semen, so...
It's only right to do things like this.
Hey, Miria, pay more attention.
Are you going to cum once before giving
the Princess her sex lessons?
A royal man's sex drive is limitless, after all...
So hard,
and throbbing.
Not to mention hot.
Rubbing against your hot thing...
I feel like my tits are melting.
It's not long now,
I can tell.
Between my tits, I can feel it inside your dick...
I can feel it boiling up.
Come on, I'll squeeze it out for you.
I'll make you cum with tit-fucking you can't get from the Princess.
Right? Let it all out.
Just like a squeezing pussy, I'm going to...
...wring out your man-milk with my tits.
A lot came out, I see.
Though there's still some left.
Now, Princess, it is your turn.
Take that offensive thing away from me.
Now, that's no way to talk.
Isn't it the dick you need to impregnate you?
You need to clean it first,
with your mouth.
W-With my mouth?
Put such an offensive thing in my mouth?
How could I do something so vile...
What's wrong?
You won't get a child just by looking at it.
I... I know that.
But...
Yes. That's the way.
Know the sensitive areas of the penis.
Lick it from the underside to the tip of the head.
Make him feel good.
What am I doing...
licking a man's genitals?
Does this actually feel good to have done?
Hey.
What's wrong?
It doesn't feel good at all.
Ah, you suck at this.
With that technique... no matter how long you do it...
You will never satisfy a male.
Now don't just watch, you help out, too.
You take near the base,
and lick his balls.
The balls?
Yes, right there.
The place where a lot of seed is.
If you stimulate that area, more semen is released.
That's... easier said than done.
Very good.
It seems she understands a bit of sexual technique.
I don't...
Even though she is a High Elf princess,
she is still a female.
She instinctively knows how to please a man.
Eww. This is so disgusting.
Perhaps you're ready to move on?
Here we go.
Wait.
Don't use your teeth.
Come on.
Piercing, my throat... Can't breathe.
I'm a bit jealous seeing the two of them having fun...
I'll just attend to this area here.
Miria...
Well?
Men do the penetrating often, but don't
get penetrated very much, do they?
Come on, don't stop.
So deep... He's ramming my throat...
Very nice. I like that face.
I'll cum plenty in your mouth now!
What a beautiful scene this is.
This is degrading.
Now then, foreplay is over.
To thank you, tonight I'll cum inside you until you go crazy.
T-Today, tonight is no good... Please pardon me.
Now, now, that's lazy of you.
Then I won't cum inside tonight.
However, I will take this hole's virginity!
That is...
Now is your chance to experience the thrill of anal.
Wait... That's the wrong...
Not bad if I must say.
That hurts... Wrong hole...
I'll do my thing, you just rest.
What thing?
Stop it.
That hurts.
Take it out...
What? You prefer the other hole, after all?
No...
Your... obscene thing is... entering my dirty hole.
Very nice.
This is pretty good for your first time.
Elf bitches are well known for their assholes as well as their pussies.
That hurts!
And it's so hot!
It burns!
My ass is burning!
You look like you need help.
This is a good opportunity for me to help with this hole.
Not there...
No...
If you do both at the same time... I'll...
Just by having your ass dug up, you're already so wet.
Stop...
Or was it the semen in your face that got you off?
Stop... Both front and back at the same time...
So hot... They're melting together...
This is too... This is just too much.
Oh? So you're turned on by anal?
No, I, not by anal... Never in the ass, would I be... turned on!
I'm cumming now. I'll fill up your virgin asshole.
No, if you...
If you cum now it won't go back to normal.
In my butt... My asshole will be broken!
No!
I'm cumming, cumming! From both
my butt and pussy, I'm cumming!
It's coming...
Gushing in...
So hot... Flowing into me.
No...
Aren't you ever going to get used to sexual service?
That's... I could never grow accustomed to these obscenities...
Huh, but at that rate, you will never be
able to house a child in your belly.
Oh?
Be pleased.
I have a nice training session for you that
should cure you of your lack of passion.
Drink more.
This should be a good place.
Right?
Dressing me up like this...
If you want to take it off quickly then do as I say.
Don't worry, it'll be over in no time.
However, if you happen to get into it, who knows?
Wh-Who would?
Well, do as you wish.
Hey, do that guy.
Who the hell would go back to that
loud-mouthed hag's house, anyway?
I'm a business owner, ya know!
Damn.
Hey, you over there!
Oh my?
Young lady, ya got some business with me?
W-Will you, buy me?
I think I've seen you somewhere...
Never mind that... Just buy me.
Hey, Miss...
No!
M-Miss, what a lovely costume that is.
Well, well, now that I get a better look, aren't you an Elf?
I've never heard of an Elf prostitute.
What are you doing in such a sexy getup?
Tell me.
I want...
No, I can't... I can't believe I have to ask a human something like this.
I don't want to!
But, if I don't this...
Never mind that.
Just... just buy me!
If I just say that, and this human agrees to buy me, then...
Please, please buy me, the Elf whore!
It's groping me there...
It's twirling around inside.
Hey, Elf Miss?
B-Buy me, please...
I'm an Elf whore...
Please fuck this Elf whore!
Buy me, fuck me, if you don't...
All right.
If you beg me like that, I'll bust two big loads for you.
There's a good, cheap inn this way!
Wait!
It was enough just for you to say you'd buy me.
That was enough.
Kyle! Where are you?
Now that I've got a good view,
you look just like the Elf Princess that was with
the Emperor in that parade the other day!
Is the Elven Kingdom full of those beauties?
Unhand me, human!
No, I hate this...
Inside... Inside my mouth, his tongue...
Miss, are you okay? Down from just a kiss?
I bet once I put this in you'll get fired up.
Now for the real thing!
No! No more than this.
Merging with a human?
I don't... I don't want to birth a human!
Hey, we've come this far. There's no backing out now, Miss!
If you still say no, then I'll just push you down and fuck you anyway.
I'd like to see a prideful elf screaming and crying for once.
Y-You can't...
If you don't want that then behave.
It'll be over soon.
I don't want to, let me go.
Not with a human...
Time to give in, Missy.
Or would you rather be forced?
F-Fine.
But... Don't do the front.
If it's like this...
Just... Just not the front.
An Elf princess's asshole, eh?
Elves sure are smaller than humans. This one looks really tight, too.
Very nice.
An opportunity to fuck an Elf's asshole is pretty rare, after all.
Awesome!
This is even tighter than Ma's pussy!
Feels great!
So... rough...
Even though you're an Elf, a bitch is a bitch!
It's sucking me in and won't let go!
Stop going...
...so deep.
Digging into me...
...all the way.
Please, have mercy.
My insides... My rectum will...
Turn into the shape of a man...
Into the shape of a penis.
I had no idea Elves were so slutty.
Take that.
Punishment time!
Stop!
Don't hit me!
The more I spank you, the tighter you get.
Stop, that hurts.
This... This is... painful, but it feels good...
Th-This can't be. It feels... good?
A penis in my butt... He's thrusting it in my butt...
Yet it feels good.
Hey, now you're giving me some good reactions.
You like it?
Even though you're an Elf, you like being fucked in your ass-pussy?
D-Don't say...
Don't call it in ass-pussy.
I... I...
Stop!
No... I'm going to...
Are you cumming?
Are you cumming from having a human cock in your ass-pussy?
Yes, I'm cumming!
Fucked in the ass.
Fucked by a human.
I'm cumming from my ass-pussy!
It's coming... it's throbbing and cumming...
My insides are getting covered with the scent of a human male...
I'm going to smell like a male.
Now, now, Miss, there's no time to rest.
Next, next!
That's impossible...
Then...
This time, I'll...
Guest, may I please enter for a moment?
Who are you guys!?
You were merely told to acquire a customer.
What are you doing?
M-Miria?
Could it be that you wanted to be impregnated by a human?
I would never!
Be at ease.
I have brought suitable partners for someone as lewd as you.
What?
What are these things!?
Aren't they cute?
Go ahead and satisfy yourself with them.
Wait!
Stop! It's coming in... Get offl
Get away from me!
Could it be that you didn't let the man
from before have your front hole?
Stop, not there!
Anywhere but there!
No, no, no!
No!
I said no, even though I said no...
Either way, Kyle will purify you afterward...
So have fun.
I won't... No...
Not with goblins...
Such filthy creatures.
Don't tell me you want...
Can't breathe... Dirty...
No... I'm getting off from goblins...
Oh my, oh my. An esteemed Elf princess
is procreating with lowlifes.
I'm not... I don't...
Oh my, oh my.
You're in such good condition that they've all cum already.
See? That one too.
No!
Don't cum.
Don't cum inside me.
I'll get pregnant!
I'll have a goblin baby! I'll have a monster baby!
No!
It's coming. Really coming.
Goblin semen, to make me pregnant... All the way inside.
No...
It's filling up...
I'm conceiving.
I really will get pregnant...
...by something so filthy.
No.
Don't spray it on me.
Don't make me, smell like goblins...
There's no turning back.
I can't. I can never return to Filheim...
Good grief.
Who would imagine a scandal involving monster sex here.
It's shameful to hear that it was the Princess of Filheim.
Preposterous!
You two planned it out that way, right?
Hmph! I would never.
It was just a coincidence.
But, how was it? Did the sexual training help?
That's not sexual!
You just humiliate me!
Easy there.
You jump to false conclusions.
I was only thinking of you.
No, I was only acting on behalf of the Elves' well-being.
Don't jest!
What you're doing is not only hurting me,
it's degrading to the entire Elf race!
Really?
Yet, withstanding that, if you don't birth
my child, your race will become extinct.
If only Seil were still alive...
You could never...
What? Identify yourself!
Y-You're...
Are you... Seil?
Wh-Who is he...
And that superhuman power...
He isn't human... Could he be of the Royal Family like me?
Guard! Is there a guard around!?
Deploy troops around the castle gate immediately!
Don't let anyone leave this royal domain!