Seil!
No... It's not you.
Who are you!?
As expected of the Elf Princess. You saw right through it.
That is Seil's empty corpse.
I have gathered dark souls to control him.
How dare you defile Seil's corpse like this.
Release him at once!
I will not.
He is my secret tool.
This is how the scenario will go...
The princess is rescued and returned home
by the true prince who actually survived.
Then the evil Kyle will be brought to justice,
and the couple will live happily ever after.
I won't play along with the plot of an evil Dark Elf!
I used Seil to absorb your magic power, Princess.
Resistance is futile.
I will train you well, my dear.
You shall become my tool as well.
Who would become your...
Oh? You could assist me in killing that fool Kyle.
Won't you be a bit more cooperative?
You're going to betray Kyle?
I have no memory of ever being on his side to begin with.
It is all for the sake of the Demon King Zeromuth's revenge.
Elf Princess Nina
Vol.03
Dark Descent End
That idiot Kyle has a puppet spell placed on him.
I will show the younger brother coveting the splendor
of his older brother in the castle for all to see.
I'm really looking forward to this.
Really? Is that so?
K-Kyle!
Hi there, brother.
Long time no see.
Kyle! When did you realize?
I trust no one.
Oh?
Then I have no choice but to kill you here and now.
You really are a fool.
Were you not listening to what I said?
I placed a puppet spell on you.
I can take control of your body any time I please.
You Dark Elf whore...
Now! End your own life with your sword!
Stop it.
Lord Zeromuth, at last you shall be avenged!
...Just kidding.
Sorry Miria, but puppet spells have no effect on me.
I wouldn't approach a conniving whore
like you without protecting myself.
You can't mean...
Curse reflect.
In other words, the curse is sent back to the caster.
You won't escape, Miria!
Damn you...
You inferior human!
This "inferior human" is going to train you thoroughly.
I'll kill you!
Shit, shit, shit!
I'll fucking kill you, I swear!
And now, the final touch.
Wh-What is...
What did you make me swallow?
Nothing bad. Just a little something to bring out your true nature.
What?
As promised, I will make you pregnant.
Stop it!
Who would want to birth your child?
Don't lie.
You always get off like crazy when I shove my big thing in.
You think...
I didn't... Don't want to feel it.
I don't want to be aroused by you.
Really? I see.
Then I will do as you wish.
What is this?
I don't feel anything.
I can't feel anything.
It doesn't feel good.
Yes.
You said you didn't want to be aroused, after all.
That drug I just gave you completely
shuts down pleasure until I say so.
It's a magic drug.
It can't be...
If you get pregnant without undoing the
spell, then the effect will last forever.
In other words, even if I give you permission,
the effect will not become undone.
You will never feel pleasure ever again.
A drug well-suited to a High Elf princess, don't you think?
I don't...
There, there.
Your pussy feels so good that I'll cum any second.
And when that happens you can birth an heir just
like you wished and be returned to Filheim.
Wait!
But if that happens, then...
Yeah. You will never attain sexual pleasure again.
A High Elf princess doesn't need that, right?
Yes, just a bit more. I'm going to get you pregnant!
Unbelievable...
N-No more?
I'll feel no more pleasure?
I can't imagine not being able to feel pleasure ever again.
It's coming.
Very soon, my semen will pour into your
uterus and make you pregnant.
This is the last one!
Wait!
What?
If I wait, you'll never get pregnant.
What's wrong?
It's our last time after all, so if you have a wish let me grant it.
No, I don't want that.
This can't be the end.
This can't be the end of my pleasure.
No!
I want to have more.
I want to be aroused more!
I want to feel pleasure!
This lack of sensation... When I should feel good. I don't....
So please... Please...
Oh? You said you never wanted to see me again, right!?
That's... It's not about that!
If I return to Filheim never being able to feel pleasure again...
No!
So please... Please...
As you wish.
Right now I will return pleasure to you.
Move as you please.
I-Is my pleasure returned?
Yes.
Try lowering your pelvis and putting it in.
Yes!
It's here! It felt really good.
Like a surge of pleasure.
Yes... I love this.
If you love it, then continue.
As much as you want.
Of course.
It feels so good.
I can't let go of something so good.
Yes...
This feels great.
It's so hot, and the inside of my body is tightening up.
Oh yes...
Your cock is so wonderful.
Yes. I love this.
I can feel your penis.
Your big penis is inside me.
It's coming.
Pleasure is coming.
And that pleasure will be your last?
Why?
Why last?
If you birth my child...
Then you will return to Filheim.
Then it will be over.
No...
I want more.
Let's fuck. Let me fuck you.
I don't care anymore!
About Filheim,
or the future of the Elves!
I want not.
I want for nothing.
If I just have pleasure, I'm satisfied with your cock.
This cock feels so good... Just putting it in and out is all I need!
What is this?
I feel something amazing surging through me.
When a High Elf who values their purity
falls, she transforms into a Dark Elf.
With the way you've become it suits you perfectly!
Amazing! This is amazing!
It feels so good.
After tasting this, I can't return.
No! I don't want to return!
Let's celebrate your new beginning.
Take that!
It's here. It's coming again.
I feel something incredible coming from your thrusting cock.
Fuck me more. Fuck me harder!
I want more pleasure!
Send your seed deep into my womb!
Wow...
I really feel you deep inside my womb.
It keeps knocking at the mouth of my womb.
My womb feels so good.
There!
Time to cum.
Catch it all and make a baby!
I feel it!
So thick... So much thick cum is rising up.
The thick cum is seeping inside, gushing
and swirling to impregnate me.
I'm full!
It's spilling out.
It's dribbling out as more comes in.
I'm going to get very, very pregnant.
As long as I have Kyle, Filheim...
The future of the Elves...
None of that matters.
Why are we coming to such a dark and gloomy place?
Let's just have sex, Kyle.
Sure, after this.
First I must show you something amusing.
No!
This is disgusting!
It's rubbing inside of me... Such a filthy thing...
Rubbing my insides...
No! This is gross!
It's so dirty... Take it out.
Take it out!
Oh? It's Miria.
What is she doing?
As you can see,
she's entertaining the infamous Orc sex-beasts.
Kyle...
How dare you do this to me!
You defied me.
It's only fitting you receive punishment.
Why, you...
Don't cum!
No...
Hmm... Miria's going to raise an Orc child.
Congratulations.
No. Anything but that!
This stinks... It's dirty.
No, let me go...
You! Help me at once!
Don't care...
So intense!
An orc dick really suits you well.
Hey, let's do it.
Let's do it while we watch Miria get pregnant with an Orc.
You sure did change.
That's because... I love this.
I love your cock.
If only you could be this obedient as well.
Stop this.
Stop him. Let me go!
I don't want to get pregnant.
I don't want to birth a monster!
No!
Stop it!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
I don't want to get pregnant...
You must be happy to receive sperm inside.
Where's your over-joyed peace sign?
Or do you still want to be fucked by the Orcs?
I'll do it.
I'll do the peace sign.
Hey, with a smile!
Make a face that says you're happy to have gotten pregnant!
I like this sight!
Kyle, that's enough!
Don't look only at Miria.
Ah, sorry about that.
Your titty-fucking and fellatio is the best.
I can feel it coming.
Delicious.
Semen juice is delicious.
No... It's still coming out.
So much... from my pussy.
That look suits you, Miria.
Kyle, save me!
I can't take anymore!
If I use the Purification Stone, the situation might be resolved.
The Purification Stone...
Give it! Give it to me!
Use it on me!
Make all the semen disappear from inside my pussy and womb!
Please!
Please! Please!
Then you need to become more obedient.
Surrender to me!
I understand.
Yes... I will become your slave.
I wish to become your slave.
My body and my soul... I entrust it all to you.
Is that so? Then lick my foot to prove your sincerity.
Surely you jest.
You think I would fall for that?
You fucking sow!
Kyle!
You bastard...
You have plenty of time.
After you conceive an Orc child, I will have
you thoroughly regret what you did.
10 Months Later
Kyle, Kyle, Kyle...
Master.
Yes, yes, yes...
Kyle, your huge cock... No matter how many times...
I never lose interest. The best cock there is.
Master... Master's nipples are so delicious.
It's coming.
So thick... All the way to the baby in my womb.
My pussy is being penetrated.
Yes! Yes!
Master, after this... after this, do me.
Put it in my pussy.
I want... Master's cock...
No!
This cock is mine.
It's only for me.
Oh no...
I'm feeling it.
I'm so aroused just from saying "cock".
No, no, no...
No, no, no, no!
Dick... Dick... Dick!
Oh no.
Just the thought of it is making me soaking wet.
Yes! No!
I'm gonna cum.
This feels so good!
Take that!
I'm cumming!
Wow, wow, wow!
There's so much coming into my belly!
I could make a whole new baby!
It's coming out.
Milk is coming out!
So much is squirting out, just like sticky semen!
Oh, Master!
That was very good, you two.
We've barely even started.
Please, Master.
It's not over.
I'm not satisfied.
This time my butt, or ass-pussy.
No, put the next one in my pussy... Or even my ass-pussy.
Just plow me hard.
I might actually... like this.
I might like it in the ass!
Do it... Harder, harder, harder!
It's inside.
Inside my ass!
Kyle!
I want your cock, too.
Cock, cock... Kyle's cock.
Don't fret.
Oh yes, yes!
Kyle's finger thrusting feels great.
My ass-pussy! My ass-pussy!
It's thrusting so hard in my ass.
It's here, here, here!
I waited for this! I waited for it in my ass-pussy!
Let's have some more fun, you two.
Okay!
So delicious.
Kyle's dick...
There's so much semen.
Master's... semen...
It's so warm.
Delicious!