His name is Naria Kusumoto. Just an ordinary student of mine.
But the casual movements of his fingers, his red tongue kept behind those lips,
and the light fragrence of hair gel accenting his lovely scent.
These things lit the flames of passion inside me, and evoked my lewd fantasies.
Naria...
He's using his tongue...
Naria?
I won't let anyone else have him.
I want him for my own...
Captivating Lust
FAKKU! Presents
What's the matter Ms.Awashika? I got stuff to do today-
I got stuff to do today-
Ms.Awashika, why are you...
No more questions.
You can do whatever you like to me.
In exchange, I want yours.
Incredible! The tip's completely wet already.
Can I please...take them off?
I'm mouthing his penis, making such lewd faces...
Give my other mouth a taste too, Naria.
Ohh, don't just stare like that.
Now I want you to thrust it into my pussy.
Plow it all the way into my womb!
More! Give me more!
Oh god...it feels so good!
Don't tease me, go deeper!
Oh God!
Don't stop!
Doesn't your teacher's pussy feel great?
Yeah, you're clamping down on my dick.
Ms. Awashika! I'm cumming!
On my face! Dump it on my face!
Delicious.
Staff Restroom
The way you stick your ass out's so raunchy.
Ohh, I need more. You move too, Naria.
Fine, if you insist!
You're quite the slut, huh teach?
I'm...sorry!
Come on, cum!
You're spraying everywhere, Ms.Awashika.
You satisfied?
Yeah...I'm so happy.
I'll be going then.
...okay.
What'd you wanna discuss?
Oh, I was just wondering who that girl walking with you yesterday was.
Why on earth would you ask me that?
Our relationship is based exclusively on sex, am I wrong?
Isn't it against the rules to meddle with my private life?
But if you want...
come to my place tomorrow.
I'll explain it to you.
Well?
Okay, I'll come.
Coming!
That's the girl...
Who the heck is that?
And who do you think you are?
So basically it's just physical.
Yep, that's how we are.
We only meet up for sex, that's it.
Just like with you, right Yukiha?
Hey, come on! I'm serious, you know.
And there you have it.
So the reason I called you both here was cause I wanted to have a threesome.
I don't like the idea of Naria having sex with another woman.
Oh yeah? Well then just sit there and watch.
No way...
I practiced all night thinking of you, Naria.
She's sucking his dick like it was a delicacy.
Even though I always do it for him too.
That hurts...
But it feels good too.
Was he doing me that way too?
You'd rather do it to her?
Just like how you do it to me?
I can't bear the thought of that.
Oh...shit!
I can't hold on!
It's okay! Cum, Naria!
Don't take my Naria from me!
It's unfair if only she can have it.
If it's her, I'm gonna blow right away!
My mouth, breasts, and ass...
My whole body exists for his sake.
Come on, I want more. I want you to come in me more.
I'll do anything if it makes Naria happy.
So please don't hate me.
Oh my god...
I'm gonna lose it...ohh!
Hot!
Naria's dick is so hot!
Don't tease me!
If you rub there, I'll wet myself!
Do it. Let me see you pee.
No...I can't...
Is it here?
It comes out from here?
Don't...not so hard! My pee'll-
So good! I'm really going to...
Let it out.
Come on and let it go!
H-here it comes!
So warm...It's so warm, Ms.Awashika!
Naria, what are you doing?
Hey, where do you want to do it?
I-in your ass.
Okay
Ah, I wanna jam it in.
Go ahead.
Ohh, my ass feels so good!
It's fabulous!
Awesome! It's gripping me!
It's so tight!
No way, right in her ass?
Is it really that good?
Does it seriously...
Good...This is great!
Amazing!
It's getting bigger! And so hot!
It's gonna break! I'm gonna break!
Gonna break! Gonna break!
Harder! Go rougher!
Oh god! Oh god!
If you're that intense, I'll cum from my ass!
Well in that case...
Incredible!
Yes! God, Yes!
Sindalf - School is out for summer!
ACF - Idunno what to put here.
Others - Didn't do anything