Good thing we were able to take out all of these before it rained.
Don't, Kentarou-kun.
Everyone's about to go home.
But, you're about to go back to the city, right?
Oh, are you missing me already?
Or maybe, this little guy's the one who's going to miss me?
Aunt Shizue, it's been a while since the last summer festival so...
I see, it has built up again.
Oh yes, the picture from the festival is here already, right?
Yeah, I think it is.
Then I'll go get it.
Please watch over the house for a while, okay?
E-Eh...?
Also, don't go letting it out on your own now, okay?
Oh crap.
Enbi
Myabi Tsuzuru
Part 02
Yumeno Photo Studio
Ami, move a bit to the left.
L-Like this?
Pull down the veil a bit more.
Make sure that your nipples are exposed.
Okay, that's fine.
Now, focus on the camera.
Good day, Nobuo-kun, seems you're doing alright.
Shizue-chan?
From high school?
Long time no see.
Wow, winning the prize in a contest is amazing.
Not exactly the perfect top model,
but Kyouko's in a completely different category.
Oh, but she seems like a fine and beautiful wife to me.
It's the photo that made it, not the model.
Our next stop is a photo exhibit that will be published by a newspaper company.
I'll make sure to take the top spot and get my photo featured for my debut.
I have confidence in my skills.
I'm not just going to manage this old photo studio forever.
Hey, can I be a model for you as well?
Eh?
This is a good chance.
Can you take a good shot of Ami-san and I?
Oh crap!
I forgot to take the other roll of film!
But this one is actually a secret extra.
What should I do?
Shizue-chan, get a bit closer to Ami.
Make it seem smooth and natural.
That's great.
Good.
Now, let's change the background.
You seem to be a bit gloomy.
What's wrong?
He's been taking pictures of me like this almost every day.
We don't usually do it anymore at night.
It seems that he's already had his "fill" of this.
Good grief, abandoning his gorgeous wife like this.
Nobuo-kun's such a helpless guy.
Then, why don't we show off to him?
Our primal beauty as women.
A kiss, huh?
Good.
No, great!
Your breasts are cute.
Hey, do you like it when your nipples are pinched?
Yes.
Oh my, your nipples have gotten hard.
How lewd.
Oh? You can't hold back anymore?
Is it not enough with just your breasts?
Well, I see then.
Why don't we start here as well?
TL note: fundoshi = Japanese loincloth
It looks like a fundoshi.
No, this is embarrassing.
Amazing, your clit sure looks big.
Look, it's starting to get squeezed in.
Don't...!
Your breasts are big...
Why don't you lick them instead of just looking?
You're good.
No way...
Okay, now we show off our aroused bodies.
You don't leave a woman's pussy like that.
Nobuo-kun, I have this wonderful thing.
That's part of the photo exhibit.
It feels nice and cool.
That's...
TL Note: Kokeshi - Japanese handmade wooden dolls
The kokeshi's going inside me!
There now, the kokeshi’s round head is now completely inside your pussy.
Lots of your love juices are flowing out.
Okay then, let's ask your husband now.
Say "please take my pussy."
Please... take my pussy.
Oh crap.
I can't just take pictures like this anymore.
You two just wait there.
Let me do it too.
Aunt Shizue should be here.
But there's nobody...
My mouth's been wanting some.
So first, let me have a taste of your dick.
This is great.
This is really great.
Nobuo-kun, your dick sure is big.
Next, Shizue-san goes on top.
No fair! Just because your breasts are big doesn't mean you can tit fuck.
I'm going to do this then!
No, that spot is...
Here, take this, and this!
Dear, help me out here.
Drill it, push it inside me.
Okay, I'm going to fuck you soon.
Your dick...
It's been a long time.
I can't be satisfied just by fingering.
Please lick me lots this time.
Ami, your lip service feels great
I think you two will have better expressions with these.
Okay, you two, put your asses out.
It's in my pussy!
Drive it deeper inside!
It feels so good.
Now, stick your asses together.
Like this?
Your thick fleshy thing and this vibrating sensation...
Oh yes, your penis is in between!
Oh no, I can't take it anymore.
I'm cumming...!
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!
Oh, good timing.
Kentarou-kun, come over here.
O-Okay.
It's coming out!
Me too...!
Me too, I'm cumming!
A young man's dick...
It's twitching wildly inside me!
It's really thick!
Shizue-chan!
Let's all...
I'm already going to...!
Me too, I'm...!
I can't hold it anymore too!
Me as well!
I'm cumming!