Every summer,
people from various places visit my town.
As if the place is naturally loved by everyone.
Shizue Oba-san?
How many years has it been since you
came back from Tokyo to visit?
I can't remember.
It's been a very long time I guess.
BEAUTY
Myabi Tsuzuru
It feels strange.
What does?
The scenery looks the same even though
I've been gone for so long.
This place never changes.
I think it's the same for you too, Aunt Shizue.
Oh?
Though you've been married for many years now,
your beauty still remains the same.
Oh my, so you can say such things now eh, Kentarou-kun.
Say, is your neighbor Rumi-chan coming to visit today?
I'm not sure.
She arrived yesterday,
but I've yet to meet her.
Is that so?
Oh, this looks fun.
What's wrong?
I think...my stomach hurts a little bit.
Are you alright?
Do you want to go to the restroom?
Here's a bit of cash and some tissues.
I'm going to rest for a bit, so just go and enjoy the festival.
Oh crap...!
I wonder where Auntie went.
A Shinto shrine?
Auntie?
Why is she...?
Hey, are we really going to do it here?
What's the point in asking now?
Don't be such a killjoy.
You're the one who's inviting us to
do it with your big ass, you know.
But...
I really love young men like you.
If you really love us, then we'll be glad to
fuck both your pussy and asshole, Miss.
You're going to kneel like a dog,
while I rub my dick on your clean face, spraying my cum all over it.
Look, all these dicks are now in front of someone as old as you,
so be thankful.
How terrible of you to say I'm old.
But, I'm happy.
Such a youthful dick.
I want everyone to release their cum on me, okay?
My beautiful auntie, actually makes such an expression...
She's all over it, she just can't seem to stop sucking.
She's so taken by all these dicks that
she's starting to look spaced out.
I'm going to take some in here as well.
You're going to insert your dick?
Oh wow, it just went all the way in.
Her tits are huge.
She sure has a slutty body.
This pussy wraps around me really well despite its age.
I'll be taking your ass too.
Your asshole feels quite tender.
Here, does this feel good, Miss?
Oh no, I'm losing it, I'm about to...
Then just cum.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Here's your cum milk.
Open wide.
Don't just rest there, squeeze me tighter with your ass!
Tease me more with your cock, please.
Your cumming expression looks very erotic, it looks so great.
Don't worry, I'll rub my dick real good.
A pussy being penetrated by something as dirty as a cock...
Make me into a woman that reeks of a man's cum.
She's happily sucking all that stinky cum...
Make me stinky with the cum of your dirty dicks.
She looks dirty...
But...!
Woah! It felt so good for her that she actually started peeing.
Lots of cum is overflowing from her ass too.
How dirty.
But, it still looks very beautiful!
Someone’s there!
Hey, come out!
Is someone there?
Dunno.
I see.
Aunt Shizue...
She was doing it with those boys...
Rumi-nee?
What are you doing here, Rumi-nee?
Is she really sleeping?
Seems so.
Rumi-nee...
Runi-nee chan's...pussy.
Her... nipples... and breasts.
It feels soft.
Why is there a dick in front of me?
Kentarou-kun? Our neighbor?
Oh yes, I dropped by to say hello to Auntie,
but I fell asleep while waiting for her to come home.
What should I do?
I can't talk to him in this situation.
Onee-chan.
Kentarou-kun.
He's...
I guess he's still a guy after all.
He became aroused at the sight of me sleeping.
Do you want to have sex with me that badly.
Wait, is he going to cum on my face?
Rumi-nee...?
You already had something for me
even when you were little, right?
I know about how you were fapping as you ogled my body.
I was always thinking about you...
Actually, I'm quite happy.
Now...
This feels really good.
Kentarou-kun, your dick looks amazing.
It feels really hard and sturdy.
Oh my, you two...
Kentarou-kun, you dropped this.
That's...
Aunt Shizue.
I see that you two are complete adults now.
I can teach you a lot more if you want me to.
Is this your first time tasting a woman?
Yes.
You don't want a dirty old lady to be your first time?
No, I'm okay with you Auntie.
How cute.
Me too.
Auntie’s tongue feels so amazing.
Me too, I'm about to...!
Not yet, don't cum just yet.
Okay.
Hey, I want you to go all the way inside with just one push.
I'm going to be on top this time.
Alright.
I'm about to...
It's okay, just cum...
Cum a lot inside of me.
I'm cumming...!
Hey, it's my turn now, hurry.
Okay.
I'm going to cum.
Not inside. Cum on my face.
Aunt Shizue, Rumi nee-san...
I'm already...
What are you saying?
This summer night is still young.
Auntie is about to show you even better dreams.