Your virgin cock is so tasty!
I'm not a virgin!
Whatever you say.
Seriously, her technique is getting better and better.
She was so innocent when she was little...
Kyouka, I'm cumming!
Look how much you came! It's not good
if you don't squeeze it out sometimes!
The only thing you wanna
squeeze out of me is my money.
Today's a freebie.
I'll help you out whenever you're in the mood.
Hm? Now that I think about it,
she seems to be doing well, recently.
Nukisapo Arc.
What?! All the girls caught a cold?!
Then that means... I'm supposed to
take care of all the customers by myself?!
There's only one reservation today.
I would like another girl to help, though.
You're a delinquent aren't you?
Don't you know anyone who might be able to?
Hey, Karin!
You weren't responding to any
of my mails, so I came to see you!
H-Hey, wait! Come on!
Sorry, but could you please not talk to me?
Huh? What's up with you?
You saw the text, right? It's a damn good jo...
I'm not interested.
The client is the owner of some big company,
and wants somebody
to play with his virgin son and
make him a man, or something like that.
I told you, I'm not interested!
I know we used to do stuff like that,
but I've put it in the past! I'll only study now!
Come on, don't be like that!
We used to be the two best prostitutes ever!
Don't stay stuff like that out loud!
I'm seriously trying to change my image here!
Come on! Let's fuck guys like we always used to!
Ugh, fine! Just this once, okay?!
Yay, Karin!
Yeah, yeah, I know, so get off of me already!
No doubt, this style suits you best.
Using my hairstyle from back then
is so embarrassing though...
Come on, don't be shy. Let your hair flow.
With a hairstyle like that,
whoever you do it with would get super horny.
You think so?
Oh, my! How splendid! Isn't she just wonderful?
Um, that's enough about me. Where is the client?
He's waiting in another room. Do your best, you two.
U-Um, I look forward to working with you.
– What?!
Wh-What? A girl?!
You're not a fat naked guy?
Ah, I'm sorry! Don't make that face!
Don't cry!
Sorry we frightened you.
We're going to teach you lots of lewd things now, okay?
Oh, looks like a switch flipped in you, Karin.
So, where are your soft spots?
You don't know? Let's take it slow
and figure them out, then.
Oh, he got hard, look!
It's not too big, bu it's still being covered, huh?
P-Please don't look at it so much...
It's just some slight phimosis,
nothing to be ashamed of. See?
My dick is starting to itch!
Let me in on the fun, too.
Even then, you'd always do that as soon
as you see a dick! At least give me half!
What was that for?
What if you made me bite down on it?
Ah...
Seriously.
What... is this?
N-No, I'm going to cum!
Oh, look at what you did. Now I'm all dirty.
S-Sorry.
Would you make me cleaner? Lick me.
All right!
Okay, I'm ready to go. It's time for round two.
It'd be a shame if you didn't get to shoot
your virgin cum into a pussy, right?
First, I'll lubricate it with my pussy juices.
Hey! Are you seriously trying
to pull ahead of me again?!
Fine, then. I'll take his mouth.
Your face is so smooth, it feels great!
I think it's about time...
All right, let's put it in, all at once!
Oh shit, it's bigger than I expected.
Can you see it? Your cock is all the way inside me.
I can't see anything.
Hey, don't talk, just use your mouth here.
That's great. Keep going like that,
stick your tongue deep inside me like a dick.
It's been so long since I've done this, I...
Karin, you're about to cum, aren't you?
You're gonna cum just from having
your pussy licked like that.
What? Look at yourself, your face and
pussy are saying you're gonna cum!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Aww, a dick that cums before a girl does is a bad dick.
S-Sorry.
Don't worry, your licking was perfect.
Sorry we made you do it
with us like that right away.
You're just so cute. Don't you wanna
make some good memories?
Don't baby him.
Okay, let's have lover's sex with my pussy next.
Your pussy is so pretty.
Oh, stop it... That's embarrassing. Thank you.
Right here?
No, a little bit lower.
Right there, and just go straight in.
It went in!
This dick is completely different from before!
Kyouka, you had this inside you?!
It's great, isn't it? When it's in you, it just gets
bigger and bigger. This kid's got potential.
Your pussy feels so good!
It feels like my dick is going to melt!
Yeah, move your dick rhythmically,
just like that. One, two, one, two!
Look at how much better you've gotten
since losing your virginity!
Thank you.
Kyouka, stop moving his hips!
I'm not doing anything anymore.
This is bad. I-I'm almost at my limit!
That's fine. Let's cum together.
It's my turn after you're rested, okay?
No, I'm next, right?
Why don't we just have another three-way?
Hey, Kyouka, where'd you go?
Happy birthday!
A very happy birthday to you, mister.
Come on, Kyouka. You too.
Oh my.
Um, care to fill me in on what's going on?
We heard that today was the birthday
of her brother from Ms. Shiraishi.
We have prepared a great celebration for you
since it is for a family member of our employee.
Hey, Kyouka, what is all this?
They said they'd pay me if you came,
so what choice did I have?
What the hell?!
Screw off.
You always do this! You just rope me into these
weird situation without even asking me!
It's just as I had discovered from my research
last night. He is a very good looking guy.
What's more is that he's somehow a virgin as well.
What a miracle! I'm ready to start this party
and execute my plan to take his virginity!
This girl's up to something again, isn't she?
All right then, how about we go and get started?
Let's start first with the master of this mansion, myself.
Wha... Why are you stripping?!
What?! What's up with those clothes?!
What are you saying? If I'm to entertain a guest,
this is perfect, is it not?
Huh? Entertain?!
Oh my, what a cute dick. I see you have foreskin.
Okay, then let's make you all clean and pretty.
It's so cute.
Your tongue's going under the skin...
He's definitely Kyouka's older brother. Even though
he's a good looking guy, his dick cheese tastes so strong.
It tastes great.
Their plan is definitely to take his virginity isn't it?!
Wait, why am I getting mad?
Why should I care who takes his virginity?
Oh, what's this? I only cleaned you
a little bit and look how hard you've gotten.
You're such a dirty brother for getting so hard
even though your little sister is watching.
All right, you're good to go, Leo-chan.
Thank you, Mama.
Would you like to pump your cum into
my tight, little pussy as much as you please?
Wh-What should I do?
The only reason I sucked him off
at home was to get some money.
He's only a piggy bank to me...
He doesn't mean anything to me...
It's gonna go in! It's going in!
– Oh my!
– What are you doing, Ms. Shiraishi?!
What are you doing, Ms. Shiraishi?!
K-Kyouka?
I don't want anyone taking your virginity except me!
Your dick's mine, isn't it? So it should be okay
if I take your first time, right? Right?
Wait! Wait! Calm down, Kyouka! Calm down!
Aniki! Aniki!
Kyouka!
Yes! I took your virginity!
It's okay if I move, right? Right?!
K-Kyouka!
What do you think you're doing, Ms. Shiraishi?!
That was supposed to be my virgin dick!
It's unfortunate, but we lost this one.
Mama...
Look at the way he moves his hips.
Those two seem like they're very compatible.
She's gripping her brother's dick so happily.
That's so nice.
It's unfortunate that you can't put
a dick in yourself, isn't it, Leo-chan?
How about you have some fun
with your Mama over here?
Mama!
Leo-chan...
Your pussy's sucking me in!
I can't believe your pussy feels this great!
Your dick feels so fucking amazing too!
Those two are finally together
with one another. How wonderful.
Why didn't you do me like this sooner?
My pussy's always been so wet and ready for you.
Mama! Mama!
You're so cute, Leo-chan.
You're going to cum, aren't you?
Mama!
Leo-chan!
Kyouka, your boobs and your pussy are mine right now!
That's fine. I'm all yours. So hold me tight...
Aniki, please, please kiss me.
I'm almost at my limit.
Aniki, just wait a little bit.
Just a little bit longer and I'm gonna cum too.
Kyouka, I'm gonna cum!
Give it to me! Give me your flood
of virgin cum deep in my pussy!
Kyouka!
Onii-chan!
Aniki, congrats on graduating from being a virgin.
Oh also, happy birthday,
but it looks like I got a present from you inside me.
By the way, just a minute ago,
didn't you call me onii-chan...
Hey, yeah, you're pretty good at sex, aren't you?
You're good enough that you made me
cum even though this is your first time!
I-I guess.
Let's do even more of this at home...
Kyouka, does this mean there's
something you want to buy again?
If you didn't, then there's no way that you'd...
What the hell's your problem?!
But you called me onii-chan after all these year...
Damn it! I'm gonna fuck you.
I'm gonna fuck you dry today.
Ms. Shiraishi, I won't let you do as you like anymore.
Your brother's anal virginity is mine.
Anal virginity?!
It only hurts at first.
Leo-chan, here's some lube.
It's so exciting to see a guy get off from his ass.
I will save this footage of Lady Leona
with a strap-on forever.
No, not my anal virginity!
Come on, aniki, give it up. It'll feel good soon.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч