Your virgin dick is so delish, bro!
N-No, it's not!
Don't lie now.
Though, her usual blowjob seems to be getting better.
Kyouka was really such a cute girl before.
Kyouka!
You came quite a lot there.
It's bad to keep it built up, you know.
You say that, but you're just nagging me for cash again.
Whoopsie.
That's for today's service.
Just tell me if you want me to suck it again.
What was that all about?
Also, she's been getting better at nagging me for this.
What? Boss and every other girl are down with the cold?
So, that means I have to attend to all the customers by myself?
No, we've already handled that.
We just have one small group for today.
Although we do need at least one more girl for the job.
You're always wild at night, right?
Don't you at least have someone you know that you could ask?
Hey, Karin!
You never replied to my texts so I came personally.
Hey, just wait a sec!
Sorry, but could you please refrain from speaking to me?
Huh? What's up with that?
You read my text, right?
It's a really good paying job!
Not doing it.
It's like, there's this one big wig company president,
he asks for his heir, who is his virgin son, like.
"This will not do. Could you please
teach my son the basics of sex?"
Or something like that.
I said I'm not doing it!
Sure, we did lots of shit together back then,
but I've decided to focus on my studies
after getting away from my parents!
Please don't say that!
Weren't we known as the "Greatest Compensators" before?
Stop saying that with a loud voice!
I'm trying to live a normal life now!
Come on! Let's fuck like old times please!
Aw, jeez!
Just once, okay?
Karin!
Alright, alright already, so get away!
This really suits you best, Karin!
This old haircut is so embarrassing.
Come on, don't be shy and let's get it on!
I bet our customer will get totally horny in no time!
R-Really?
Oh my, this is so wonderful, Rin-chan!
Very wonderful!
Forget about me... where's the client?
He's in the other room already, so you two do your best, okay?
Umm.
I hope we can get along.
Huh? Wh-What?
A girl?
His skin is soft and supple all over.
Oh, my bad. Please don't be sad like that.
Oh, don't cry.
Sorry for scaring you like that.
You'll have two big sisters teach you all about sex, okay?
Ohh, flipped the switch already, Karin?
So, where does it feel best?
Don't know yet?
I see. Then we'll slowly discover them one by one, okay?
Whoa, it's getting big now.
Not really that big, but it's still sheathed.
Please don't look.
I guess it's still not completely phimotic, but it's alright.
See?
My dick feels really tingly.
Hey, lemme enjoy this too.
You always get hyped up whenever you see a dick.
Gimme half of it right now!
You're terrible, Karin.
What if I had accidentally bitten his dick earlier?
Oh.
Jeez.
I'm!
Oh no, stop... it's coming out!
It's all soiled now.
I'm sorry.
Would you kindly clean it for me?
Good.
Alrighty.
Okay, I'm fired up now.
Time for round two.
It'd be a waste for your virgin dick
not to cum inside a pussy, right?
Gotta mix a bit of my fluids at the tip.
Hey, are you going to leave me out again?
Well, okay then.
In that case, I'll be taking his face instead.
It feels so great rubbing it on his cute face.
You're going with that, huh.
Alright, I'm taking it in.
Whoa, it feels a lot bigger than it looks.
Can you see it?
Your dick is all the way inside me.
I-I can't see it.
Stop talking and just keep using your tongue.
Your tongue feels really good.
Just extend it as deep as you can.
The sensation inside, it's been so long since I've felt it!
You look like you're about to cum, Karin.
Your mushy pussy is right at its limit.
What? Your face is just as sloppy as your hole.
It's coming out again.
Hey, a dick that cums before making the girl cum is a no-no.
I'm so sorry.
Both your tongue and dick did very well.
Sorry that both of us stimulated you too much so suddenly.
It's because you're just so cute.
Stop spoiling him.
Now, let's have some lovey dovey sex with my pussy.
Your pussy looks beautiful.
Oh stop that, I'm feeling embarrassed.
Thank you.
In here?
There, a bit lower than that.
There, you then push it straight in.
It's in.
What's with this dick?
It's completely different.
So you were getting fucked with this earlier, Kyouka?
Kinda surprising, right?
His dick just suddenly bulges when it goes inside.
This kid's really got some potential.
Nee-san, it feels really good.
It's as if my dick is melting.
That's great.
Just keep that rhythm up and go one, two!
One, two!
Good, good! Now you're completely out of the virgin stage.
Come on!
Thank you.
Kyouka, stop hitting him already!
Huh? I'm not doing anything anymore
Thank you, but it's coming again!
It's alright. Let's cum together.
We'll take a break, and then I'm going again next.
Of course you're going with me next, right?
Why don't we just have a threesome again?
Hey, Kyouka, where did you go?
Happy birthday!
Congratulations on your birthday, onii-sama.
Come on, you too, Kyouka.
Come on.
Hey, just what in the world is going on?
We've heard that Shiraishi-san's brother's birthday is today.
To celebrate one of my important
school friends' glorious occasions,
we, the Houjou family, have decided to completely go all out.
Just what the hell is going on, Kyouka?
She told me she'd pay me if I bring you over.
I had no choice.
What?
Like hell I know!
He is indeed a stud, as indicated when we
first had her run a background check.
And a virgin to boot?!
'Tis indeed a miracle!
It was totally worth having a big party for his virginity!
She's definitely up to no good again.
Now then, shall we begin?
Let's start with me, the master of this household.
Wait, why are you stripping?
Wh-What?
What else? We did say we'd go all out, didn't we?
A-All out?
My, what a cute dick you have.
And it's uncircumcised too.
Alright. Let's clean its insides now, okay?
So stinky!
My sheathed dick.
As expected of Kyouka-chan's brother.
A stud, yet his smegma reeks of inexperience.
We've caught a big one.
I knew they were planning to take my bro's virginity!
Wait, why am I so upset about it?
It's not really my place to decide how he'll lose his.
My oh my, it's already this big after cleaning it only for a bit?
Such a pervy onii-chan, even though your
sister is watching just over there.
Now all preparations are complete, Reo-chan.
Thanks, Mom.
Onii-sama, please use my very tight pussy,
and fill it with your virgin cum.
Wh-What should I do?
I only ever gave him blowjobs to get my allowance.
H-He's nothing but my source of cash.
Nothing else, but.
It's going in. It's pushing in!
What in the world did you just do, Shiraishi-san?
K-Kyouka?
I won't have it!
I don't want my bro's virginity to be taken away from me!
Your dick is always mine, right?
That's why I can take your first time, right?
Right?
Wait, just wait!
Calm down, Kyouka!
I said calm down!
B-Bro.
K-Kyouka.
I did it.
I finally got my bro's virginity.
I'm moving, I'm going to move, bro, okay?
Bro!
Kyouka!
What have you done, Shiraishi-san?!
My precious virgin dick is now.
It's unfortunate, but we're not winning this time.
Mom.
Look at how his hips move.
They have perfect compatibility.
Kyouka-chan's embracing his brothers dick very passionately.
So you want it.
It's indeed quite lonely without a dick, right, Reo-chan?
Now, let's have fun together, shall we?
Mom!
Reo-chan.
It's squeezing me very tightly!
I never thought it'd feel this good inside you, Kyouka!
Onii-chan, your dick feels very good.
Such a warm union. So wonderful.
You never once did it. Even though you're
always so close to my very wet pussy.
Mama!
My cute Reo-chan, looks like you're about to cum.
Reo-chan!
Your pussy, and your breasts.
Everything's mine tonight!
Okay, I'm all yours, bro.
So please fuck me harder!
Bro... kiss me.
I'm about to.
Bro, just wait a bit more. I'm about to cum as well.
Kyouka!
Fill me with your virgin cum, bro!
Onii-chan!
Congrats on ending your virginity, bro.
Also, happy birthday.
Though, I'm actually the one who's full of your present now.
By the way, did you just call me onii-cha...
Hey, you did really great there, bro!
You made me cum even though it's your first time.
Well, I guess.
Then we'll be doing lots at home from now...
Kyouka, are you planning to buy something again?
My cute Kyouka's definitely going to...
What the hell did you just say?!
But, after such a long time you finally called me onii-cha...
Damn!
I'll rape you!
I'm going to rape you all day today!
Shiraishi-san, I'm afraid I can no longer let you do as you please.
Onii-sama's anal virginity is mine.
Anal virginity?!
Onii-sama, it only hurts the first time.
Reo-chan, here's the lotion.
I'm quite excited to see a man get aroused in his ass.
I definitely need to record Reo-sama's
finest aggressive moments.
My anal virginity!
Give it up already, bro.
Don't worry, it will all feel good soon.