Let's do this.
I'm gonna gobble up your veteran cock!
Damn, veteran cocks are amazing!
If somebody told me yesterday that I'd be getting paid
to satisfy men's sexual urges, I never would've believed them.
Yeah, that's fucking great!
Energy Kyoukai!!
Jack Off Battle Are Episode 1.
Crap, I'm basically flat broke right now.
Being a high-schooler sucks.
Cleaning in
progress
A-Are you serious, Kyouka-senpai?!
One time raw costs this much.
That's a special price I'm giving you cherry boys.
Hell yeah!
What's the matter? Who's first?
Get your cocks out already!
You got a lot of cum backed up, don't you?
Y-Yes! I do!
Please, do me too!
M-Me too!
S-Senpai!
You guys aren't done yet?
I'm getting money from you guys either way!
D-Damn, this feels so amazing!
I'm cumming!
You're gonna suck me dry!
S-Senpai, do me with your mouth too!
Step off man, I'm first!
Hey!
Hey, what's the matter with you guys?
You just came but you're already hard again?
Is this what you guys want?
Looks like I guessed right.
Alright, let's switch this up.
Come on, you gotta make your partner feel good too.
– Come on virgins, do your best!
– Yes!
Got it!
What? That's how you use your tongue?
Yeah, just like that!
Yeah, yeah, keep it up!
Keep pulling on them like that!
This kid! What's he doing shoving
his tongue into me all of a sudden?
You fucking idiot! Who the hell goes
that hard with their tongue all at once?!
I-I'm so sorry! I didn't really know what I was doing!
How fucking long are you gonna keep sucking my tits?!
For fuck's sake.
Okay, whatever, I'll start with you, Ronge.
H-Huh?!
My dick's really inside!
How's your first pussy feel?
Well, um, it feels so good, I...
I came already...
You little bitch!
You're supposed to make the person
you're sticking it into feel good!
I-I'm so sorry!
He really came inside her...
What the hell are you waiting for? Get over here already!
I know where you wanna put it...
Right here, right?
Y-Yes!
Yeah, that's good!
Thank you very much!
S-Senpai, I'm at my limit!
The second round of cum is served!
For having such a cute face, you have a real monster cock.
Oh, thank you...
How many times does this make?
Six so far.
Oh really, then I guess your cock's all grown up now.
I'm going to cum again!
Do it! Shoot it inside me!
I'm gonna cum too!
I'm cumming!!
Y-You guys didn't do half bad.
– Th-Thanks.                                – Th-Thank.
– Th-Thank you.
You guys came 15 times inside me,
so that means 75,000 yen total.
Give me the rest by the end of the month, okay?
Shiraishi-san?
Just what were you doing inside the men's room?
Crap! The President?!
Just what did you mean by
15 times inside me is 75,000 yen?
Sh-Shit...
So because you were having difficulty paying off
your cell phone bill, you resorted to these tactics?
I wouldn't mind keeping this
matter a secret from the school.
For real?!
Why am I dressed like this?
It's to improve your worth.
Mama!
Nice to make your acquaintance. I'm Leona's mother.
So you're Kyouka-chan?
She's so erotic!
Are they really related?
Mama, we talked about this already,
but Shiraishi-san has agreed to help us out.
Oh my, is that so?
Hm? Help out?
Hm?
All right, let's make our way into the venue.
Venue?
Wh-What the hell is this?!
What are these guys doing inside your house?
This is a high-class gentleman's club that Mama owns.
This is our main trade... prostitution.
Aren't you honored that you
get to work here, Shiraishi-san?
Work?!
Th-There's no way I can do this!
You suck at making jokes.
What are you saying?
Would you rather me tell the school what you did?
Anything but that!
Of course, I won't be making you work for free.
Every time is 20,000.
Oh man, I guess I've got no choice
since I'm being blackmailed. All right then!
This is so sour...
Hey, can't you take a hint?!
Come on, you can't just do this out of the blue.
I just came buckets from another girl...
Don't run away, mister...
You're trying to tell me there isn't
any cum left in here? Don't lie to me.
I can smell your cum through your sack.
Just cum, okay?
Semen! Semen! Semen! Semen!
Amazing! I'm being sucked clean!
Calm down, I'll suck you all off!
Just wait your turn!
What the heck is her problem?
In just an instant she became the star of the show?
Leona-sama!
The young mistress from the
Ojou family is making her appearance!
Leona!
Leona-sama!
Let's have a match to see who can
make more of these gentlemen cum!
All right everyone,
please give me your stinky dicks.
I'll make each one of them feel ecstasy.
This is the first time I've seen
Leo-chan get so into her work!
Do your best, Leo-chan!
Mama!
Leona-sama! I never thought you were
the kind of girl to give a blowjob this vulgar...
You've really grown up, Leona.
Both Leo-chan and Kyouka-chan are wonderful.
They're making Mama so horny.
Oh no!
Wow, her mom is amazing.
You two are so wonderful.
I'm not gonna let myself be outdone!
This tanned girl's blowjob is really something!
– Ah, I'm cumming!
– Semen! Semen! Semen!
Yeah, I'm gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Your cum's so thick, mister...
All right! Cum on me more!
Please spray me with your cum, good sirs! Yes please!
Leona-sama, your pussy's so tight! It feels so good!
Y-You may cum in me whenever you desire.
L-Leona-sama!
Come on, just cum already!
You've got a lot backed up, don't you?
Y-Yes, I do.
You've really had to hold back, haven't you?
Come on, come on!
Give me lots of your thick cum!
Come on! Come on!
It's cumming inside me!
I can't get enough of this feeling!
Looks like we're dead even, huh?
This is where the true battle begins.
Battle? Whaddya mean by that?
How do I look, fine sirs?
This doesn't really fit my image at all...
Leona! You can do it! Go! Go!
– Leo-chan! Do it! You can do it!
– Your mom is amazing.
What're you doing, man?
It's my turn now.
Oh, if you want my pussy so badly
then just stick your cock in me.
Tan-girl!
Come on, if you don't hurry up,
my pussy's gonna dry up!
Hang on!
How unseemly of you.
You should be welcoming them with more grace.
Just. Like. This!
Your dick is so thick!
I will make you cum in an instant
with my wonderful pussy!
That's some amazing hip usage.
Hey!
What gives, old timer?
You're supposed to be feeling good from my pussy.
I'm not gonna lose! This guy's cum is all mine!
Your cock feels so good!
I'm cumming!
There it is! That's the cum I wanted!
I want more cocks in me!
More! Fuck me harder with your old cocks!
Give me more of your amazing cum!
These old guys really know their stuff...
They're so aggressive!
Having two dicks inside me simultaneously and one in my
mouth makes me feel like I'm going to cum any minute now!
Leo-chan and Kyouka-chan are so wonderful!
Mama's gonna cum too!
Are you trying to make me use my hips?
If this keeps up, I'm going to be the one who cums first...
Your pre-cum's really great, mister!
Kyouka-chan! I'm gonna cum inside again!
The last spurt? That's fine,
make me cum with your semen, baby!
Oh yeah, what about our competition? Who won?
Of course I won by a landslide.
Um...
About that...
You guys got so into it that halfway into it,
we forgot to keep counting...
What?!
Oh my.
Well, you know what that means.
"Our battle has only just begun", or something like that?
Oh my.
I will not accept this!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: akin
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч