Put your cock in my pussy.
Why is this cock so good?
I need money again so I have too have sex with these old men.
Until yesterday I never thought this way.
Good! Good!
Without a phone school is very boring.
I'm not like any other highschool student.
Do you really want to do this Kyouka-senpai?
Only cum inside once, ok?
For the three of you I'll charge a special price, 100 yen.
– Yes!
– What's wrong? Who will do me first?
Quickly get your cock out!
Do you like my mouth?
Ah... I do...
Please do me also!
Me too!
Senpai!
Still haven't cum? If you don't cum I can't take your money!
Great! Looks like I'll be cumming!
Cumming...
You're sucking my cock!
Senpai! Mine too!
I'll go first right?
Hey!
Wow! Wow! You came already?
Isn't THIS what you want!?
Hehe... Right?
OK. Now gentlemen...
Come on. Come on. Do not make me bored.
Fight your virginity.
Ok!
Who the fuck licks that way?!
Fuck yes!
Good, good! You're sucking so hard!
Hey! Don't put your tongue down there so sudd...
You idiot! Don't you know how to lick!?
Sorry! I don't know the right way to do it...
Also, don't you know when to stop sucking my breasts?!
Geez...
First, I'll give you a punishment!
My dick is inside her pussy!
How does it feel to feel a vagina?
Yes... It feels so good...
That I already came...
Idiot!
I told you not to cum inside me!
Ehh...
Forgive me.
He really came inside.
What! Come on! Who's next!
I know you want to stick your cock in...
Right?
Hm...
Ya... good...
Thank you!
Se-Senpai, I'm coming...
Fill me with your cum!
Your cock is so good.
Really?
Yeah! Are you about to cum?
No, I can last a little longer.
So yes, soon you will be an adult.
I'm going to cum.
Good... Cum inside me.
I... I'm also cumming!
Cumming!
You guys are getting better at doing this.
Th-Thanks...
By the way... you guys came over 15 times
each. That'll be a total of 75,000 Yen.
Make sure the money is there, you have till the end of the month.
Shiraishi-san, what are you doing in the men's room?
Council President?
What exactly is 15x total 75,000 yen?
Really?!
So you need money to buy a phone, why not get a job?
The Student Council will buy you a phone.
Seriously!
Why do I have to wear theses clothes?
For a reason.
Mama!
Greetings, I'm her mother Leona.
Kai Kyouka-chan, right?
She looks sexy...
Is this really her daughter?
Mama, like I said I would, I brought Shiraisi-san to help.
Oh... Oh...
Help?
Lets go to the Chamber.
Chamber?
What is this place!?
Is that the Student Council!?
This was arrangement was made by Mama.
They are both servants of the house.
Is it not an honor to work here?
What?!
I-It's not possible president?!
This is too much.
What are you talking about?
Do I have to spread rumors about the incident to school?
Please don't!
Of course, but if you want to work here.
You can do anything in Japan.
If I'm forced too, so be it!
I feel something strange.
Of course it would!?!
Don't do that so suddenly!
I just finished doing it with someone else!
Do it with me old man, you have not released your cum.
Smell can't lie, I can smell cum from here.
Come on!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
Great... blow job.
Don't push! I can serve 10 at a time!
What the hell, basic fat chest!
Taking it all!
Leona-sama!!
Leona-sama is gonna to use it!
Bloooomers!
Leona-sama!
Do you think you can beat me?! Let's fight Shiraisi-san!
Come on everyone, give me all your rotten cocks.
I'll make you feel good.
This is the first time seeing Leona-chan so motivated!
Get it Leo-chan...
Mama...
Leona-sama the way you suck it, is really graceful.
Already grown so big, Leo-chan.
Leona-sama and Kyouka-chan are truly amazing! Mama's so horny!
Noo...
Her mother is truly great!
Amazing!
I do not want to lose!
This woman is unbearable!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
I also want to cum!
I'm cumming!
The smell of cum is really great.
Yes! Cum more!
Quickly... give me all your cum.
Leona-sama, your vagina is great.
You can fuck me with your cock whenever you want.
Leona-sama!!!
Come on! Cum! Quickly cum in me!
You can't stand it anymore can't ya?
Right...
You're holding it, old man!
Come on, let it flow out!
Come!
Flowing cum is unbearable!
Looks like you lasted this long, but the fight has just started!
Fight? What fight?
Do you like it, old man?
This doesn't fit me.
You two fight!
Chairman's Mother is truly hot!
I'm amazed!
What are you doing, old man!?
It's my turn next...
If you want me, immediately beat me with your cock.
Black girl.
Come on, my pussy's waiting.
Yah... No problem.
There are more important things in choosing a cock.
N-A-M-E-L-Y.
Inside there are areas.
Where vagina fluid flows out...
and this makes them cum faster!
Really? Great hint!
What do you think, old man?
Do you feel my pussy?
I won't lose, all the elderly cum will be mine!
I can feel the cock inside me!
A-Amazing!
Cum flowing inside me.
I love longer cock!
Again... Again... Cum inside me!
Give me more cum!
Doing this with the old folks is great!
Ten years in japan, this is the first time
that my ass and pussy are both full!
Kyouka and Leo-chan truly amazing!
Mama is going to cum!
You're more wild than usual.
At this rate I will be first out!
Old man, stop holding it and cum in me!
Kyouka-chan I will cum in ya!
Alright old man! Cum inside me!
Oh yeah, didn't we have a challenge or something... Who won it?
I won... of course.
Umm...
Since you two came... we kind of forgot to count the rest.
Huh!?
Oh... Oh...
So that's how it is...
Hmm?
How about we start again right now then, ok?
Ok!
You have got to be kidding me!!!