Here we go, I'm about to eat some veteran dick!
This veteran dick is really the best!
For an energetic gal like me to be hanging out here
squeezing cash from all of these old geezers,
I never would have believed this yesterday.
Good, good!
My phone budget is really dire now.
Guess I'll just have to take drastic measures.
Really Kyouka-senpai?
Something like this, each time you guys cum inside me.
I'll even let you three virgins do it at my special price.
Aw yeah!
What's wrong?
Who will be the first to go?
Just take that dick out already!
So, keeping it built up lately?
Yes, I've been holding it a long time.
Please, me too!
Me too!
Senpai!
Still not cumming yet?
I'll still charge you guys even if you don't cum, you know.
Oh wow.
I feel like I'm about to!
I'm cumming!
It's clamping down on me!
Senpai, please suck mine as well.
Me, I'm first!
H-Hey!
Hey, hey, you guys just came and it's still lively?
Is this what you guys are really after, then?
Jackpot, I guess.
Alright, switch pitchers then.
Come on, you have to properly pleasure
your partner, you know.
Do your best now, virgin team.
O-Okay.
Hey, what's with that licking of yours?
So tingly.
Good, good.
Just keep sucking on it.
You... why did you suddenly use your tongue!
You idiot!
I never told you to suck and lick it hard!
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't know how to do it properly.
And why are you still sucking on my tits!
As punishment, I'm going to fuck you first, longhorn.
My thing is inside her!
Well? How's your first pussy?
Y-Yes! I mean... it feels so good that I...
that I came already.
Why you!
I told you earlier to make your partner feel good, didn't I?
Take this!
I'm sorry!
He really came inside her.
What are you guys waiting for?
Next, next!
You want to go crazy, right?
With this, I mean.
Yes!
Alright, just keep that up.
Th-Thank you very much.
Senpai, I'm about to!
Here comes the sudden cum!
You've got quite a huge dick despite being such a pretty boy.
I'm honored.
Say, how many times has it been already?
It's been six times.
I see, then your dick is already a full fledged adult dick.
I-I'm about to cum again!
It's alright, pump it all in my womb again.
Me too, I'm about to cum too!
I'm cumming!
That was quite great, you guys.
Thanks very much.
You all came inside fifteen times.
That'll be 75,000 yen total.
Don't forget to pay up the remaining
sum by the end of this month, okay?
Shiraishi-san.
What exactly were you doing in the men's restroom?
Prez?!
What did you mean by fifteen times and 75,000 yen?
C-Crap.
Your phone budget's in a pinch,
so you decided to hold an impromptu prostitution
session within school grounds, is that correct?
I'd be willing to keep this affair a secret from the school.
For real?
Why do I have to wear this?
You have to look your best for our guests.
Mother!
Pleased to meet you, I'm Reona's mother.
Kyouka-chan, I presume?
So busty.
Are they really related to each other?
Mother, as I've discussed with you, Shiraishi-san
is willing to assist us here.
My oh my.
Hmm? Assist?
Now, let's head over to the assembly hall, shall we?
Assembly hall?
What the heck is this place?
Hey, those are Prez's underlings!
This entire mansion is home to a
large social club built by mother.
Those two are our maid-type prostitutes.
Feeling honored now, Shiraishi-san?
For you to be able to work here, I mean.
What?
I-I can't do this, Prez!
Your gag is really hardcore.
My, I think it's a bit too late for that.
Or do you want me to report that incident to the school?
Please don't!
Of course, you're not going to labor here without due payment.
200,000 yen for each guy you cum with.
I suppose I have no choice in the matter!
I can't do anything about it since I've been blackmailed, right?
What's that sucking sound?
Condition: Red!
Hey, you can't just start sucking on my dick.
I just came a lot earlier with another girl.
Please don't run away, old man.
You say you don't have much left?
Don't lie to me.
Your balls still reek strongly of cum.
Just cum already, pops.
Cum, cum, cum, cum!
Amazing, I'm being sucked dry.
Hey, hey, no need to rush!
I'm going to make you guys cum one by one.
What in the world? How did she suddenly
become everyone's vixen here?
You unripe and immature novice pussy!
Whoa, it's Reona-sama!
Reona-sama has finally made her move!
Whoever can make the most men cum
will be the winner, Shiraishi-san!
Now then, everyone, let out your stinky dicks.
I'll properly service each and every one of them.
It's my very first time seeing Reo-chan so fired up.
Do your best, Reo-chan!
Mother.
I-I never imagined that Reona-sama
could do this kind of dirty blowjob.
You've grown, Reo-chan.
Both Reo-chan and Kyouka-chan are wonderful,
and I just can't help but get homy.
Prez's Mom sure is amazing.
So wonderful.
I can't lose.
This black gal's sucking is really hardcore.
Cum, cum, cum!
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Your cum's so thick, old man.
Alright, I'm gonna make those dicks squirt more cum!
Everyone, it's alright, please cum as much as you want now!
Reona-sama, your pussy feels superbly wonderful!
You can pump it all inside me whenever you want to, okay?
Reona-sama!
Come on, just cum already.
You've got it built up, right?
I-Indeed.
You sure are holding back, gramps.
Come on, come on!
This is the home stretch!
Here it comes!
I love getting fucked and cummed in by a raw dick!
Looks like it's a tie for now.
The fight is far from over!
Fight?
What crap is that?
Well? How is this gentlemen?
This doesn't really suit me, though.
You two... do your best!
Prez's Mom is really amazing.
I'm definitely a fan now.
What are you doing, mister?
I'm next.
Oh, if you really wanted me then you should
have just fucked me right then and there.
M-Miss black gal.
Come on, before my pussy dries up.
My, quite rough if I do say so myself.
Accepting a dick should be done with a bit more finesse,
and-style.
It's quite thick in here too!
I'll make sure, with my elegant and refined techniques,
to make you cum as quickly as possible.
Such graceful moves.
What are you watching other people for, mister?
Why don't you just caress my pussy?
I'm not going to lose!
I'm going to squeeze every geezer out here dry!
Your dick is hitting my very depths.
I-I'm cumming!
He finally came inside me!
Come on, fill it up more!
More, more.
All you geezers just shower me with all of your lust!
All of you gentlemen please give me
every last drop of your lewd fluids.
They're all so clingy that it actually feels great.
Being violated both in my ass and
pussy by these middle-aged dicks,
makes me want to cum already!
Reo-chan, Kyouka-chan, you two are wonderful!
I'm about to cum as well!
How long are you going to keep fucking me?
If this continues... I'm... I'm the one who's going to.
Your cowper secretions also stink, mister.
Kyouka-chan, I'm going to cum inside again!
Are you the last one?
Alright then.
Make my pussy cum with your geezer cum, okay?
Oh yeah, you said something about
a competition or something.
What happened to that now?
Of course, I'm the clear winner by a mile.
Umm.
Well.
We were kinda overwhelmed by both
your vigor that we already lost count.
What?
My, my.
So that's it, huh.
Fight's still not over, I guess?
My!
I cannot accept that!