It's been months now since I got
here in Tokyo from a job transfer.
Will the day I get used to this rowdy city ever come?
That can't be. Seriously?
Yeah... It was just something given to me.
I wonder if my wife is doing fine.
Isn't that great? Congratulations!
Hey, mister.
Wh-What?! What's with you two?
You look so gloomy, mister.
If you're free for today, how does
going with us to have fun sound?
Eh? Eh...
I love sex, and I get pocket money. It's the best!
I'm Ami-chan, a bubbly tan gal!
Let's get along, mi-s-te-r!
Compensated Dating
Highsch••l
Bitch Gals
Daily Life of Raw Sex with An Old Man
Part 1: Tanned Gal Bitch Ami
Shall we get started, mister?
You both look very used on doing this.
We're regulars in this hotel!
Well then, we'll be introducing ourselves!
I'm Ami! It's hobetsu yukichi 3 for me.
Comp. Dating Term #1
hobetsu yukichi 3:
Sex with rubber
for 30 000 yen
(Hotel fee not included)
And a rubber, okay?
My name is Nana.
Comp. Dating Term #2
kisunashi honnashi ichigo:
No kissing,
no penetration,
for 15 000 yen
It would be kisunashi honnashi no ichigo on me if you please.
Well then, you'll be starting with me.
You're so hot and sturdy down here.
It's like my fingers are gonna burn!
Wow... Your have a meaty cock, mister!
So Nana's mouth-pussy feels good!
This thickness, this stench!
You're incredible, mister!
I'm glad that you got this hard again!
Me and your dick...
We're in the same wavelength!
Please keep on shooting
plenty more of you semen, okay?
Pour you cock milk on my tit-pussy!
How amazing!
He shot a lot of semen on my tit-pussy!
I've waited long enough that I'm already on the edge!
Come on, hurry up!
Use that enormous cock of yours
to screw and make a huge mess
of my already dripping and well-prepared pussy!
Starting with foreplay? You're such a gentleman.
My tit feels good!
You're tongue is terrific!
No!
It started to feel good!
Don't!
You're being rough, mister!
Hurry up...
Hurry up, mister...
Put it in me already!
Mister... Your dick is too big!
Your cock is filling me up inside...
My pussy is choking up!
Oh no!
Oh my...
I've never been penetrated this deep before!
I can't... already...
Come already...
Your cock is one hell of a monster!
Having sex with you really is the best!
Both of you were the best as well.
Hey mister, can we get each other's contact info?
I want to meet with you again soon!
Wait... That's not fair, Nana!
Me too, mister!
Ah... okay, okay.
And thus, my daily life with these girls started.
The Next Day
On the next day!
Huh? You're alone today, Nana-chan?
It seems that Ami is confined home today
with aching hips from yesterday's sex.
I'm gonna do my best tonight
and fill in for Ami's share of workload.
Your dick is already sticky with pre-cum!
I'm glad that to see
that my feet are making you feel good!
Your dick is very hot, mister!
Please shoot a lot of semen out, okay?
Shoot a lot of you oldie semen
on my feet-pussy!
I'm gonna make your dick clean!
I'm sorry! This is bad!
I'm already... I'm already—!
Thanks for the treat, mister!
Your dick is terrific!
The head is rubbing my pussy,
and it's tip is poking my womb!
Give it to me! Give me your sperm!
Alright, let's take your photo!
Shoot your sizzling hot cock milk!
Three... two... one...
I love sex ♥
It's Ami ↑
Hey, mister... I'm totally not
gonna let you go home today!
I'm happy that Nana-chan came here too, but....
What's with that attire?
What else does it mean?
She's right, mister!
We'll pep you up as cheerleaders!
Hurray! Hurray! Oldie cock!
Hurray! Hurray!
I'm gonna cheer for both of you and Ami's raw sex!
Raw sex?
You'll be charged a separate fee for it but....
Let me have a raw sex with your oldie cock!
You're amazing, mister!
It feels so good that my hips
started to move on their own!
Oh no! I can't stop... I can't stop it!
This is too much! This oldie cock is too much!
I can't already...
Hurry... Hurry up and come!
I'm gonna make a creampie of
your pussy. Come on, cheer for it!
Hurray... Hurray... Hurray... Hurray!
It's not peppy enough! Go on, cheer me up properly!
No... No more... I can't anymore!
Hurry!
Hurry up and pump it all inside me!
His sperm is gushing into me...
I never had anything like this before!
Jeez... Jeez!
Compensated sex is the best!
Tomorrow, get together with both of us
and then let's have a lot of sex, okay.
See you next time!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization