Nana-chan, you look so good in bloomers.
Well, I had gym class today, so...
I thought wearing them for you might make you happy.
You're so big!
Your rugged animalistic dick is driving me insane!
Having fun while selling yourself
is a wonderful thing, isn't it?
I'm Nana. Let's have a good time.
High School
Prostitution
Slutty Gals
Raw Sex with Older Guys
Part 2
The Pure But Slutty
Nana
Train approaching. Please use caution.
It's been several months since I've been here in Tokyo.
But I've found something more fun than drinking
with friends and going to cabaret clubs.
Yeah...
I've been transferred here by myself to Tokyo.
And I'm having sex with prostitutes.
Here's a dirty photo of me as a present.
I'll be at the usual family restaurant, okay?
Yeah, the three of us! All three of us. Let's do it.
I thought you were dating that other girl.
Huh? Is that true...
Come on! Let's do a three-way!
Ami-chan?
You're even more intense than usual! I'm gonna...
My mouth-pussy feels good, doesn't it?
It's time for the main course.
Ami-chan...
We can't do this here!
Just seeing your dick made me want it so bad!
Oh god, I can't stop!
More!
Do it harder!
Cum! Cum, Mister!
Your dick milk...
Shoot out your milk!
He's too good!
I hope we can do this again!
Apparently Ami can't even move right now.
So it'll just be me and you again...
Your dick is really wanting it, isn't it?
My boobs feel so good!
You're acting pretty spoiled today.
But... But I...
I... I...
I...
I want your dick so bad, I can't help myself!
Please, Mister!
Nana-chan...
It's okay.
Please kiss me.
Please buy my virginity, Mister.
Amazing!
You came just from me putting it in!
What is this?!
It's so good!
Sex is so... amazing!
I'm... having sex!
M-My pussy is taking the shape of your dick!
I... I can feel your dick!
Mister, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
It's good... It feels so good!
Your dick... it feels so good!
It feels too good!
N-No, I'm...
I'm gonna...
Cum, Mister!
Cum!
Cum!!
Sex is... the best...
You're totally hooked on his dick, Nana.
Give me lots of your milk today too, okay?
Come on, Nana. You need to beg for it too.
B-But right now...
My boobs and pussy feel too good, I can't...
Come on, Nana.
Don't you have something to ask him?
Please, Mister...
In my pussy...
– Shove your dick into my pussy!
What am I gonna do with the two of you?
I guess I'll make both of you feel good.
What is this?! It feels too good!
My pussy and clit are being assaulted by your dick!
It's so good...
It's so good!
So good!
This is... This is so amazing!
I love it... I love this dick so much!!
I'm... I'm gonna cum!
Mister please cum!
Let's cum together!
– I'm cumming!!                              – I'm cumming!!
It's been a few months since I've come to Tokyo.
But I've found something more fun than drinking
with friends and going to cabaret clubs.
Yeah...
I've been transferred here by myself to Tokyo...
And I'm having sex with prostitutes!
I'm cumming!
It's so good!
Shoot out your milk!
Give it to me deep!
Thanks for today as always, Mister!
And as usual...
we got paid to get cummed in by you!
Raw Sex with Older Guys
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч