You look adorable wearing bloomers, Nana-chan!
We had P.E. today...
And I thought that you might love seeing this.
You're so big, mister!
It's rubbing on me.
My bloomers will get torn apart!
Getting supported and having fun
as well, isn't that fantastic?
I am Nana. It's a pleasure to meet you.
Compensated Dating
Highsch••l
Bitch Gals
Daily Life of Raw Sex with An Old Man
Part 2: Pure and Graceful Bitch Nana
It's been a few months since I came in Tokyo.
More than checking stock prices at mornings
and drinking parties with co-workers,
I found something to look forward to.
That's right.
I got transferred here in Tokyo,
and I pay for sex!
I sent this lewd snapshot of mine just for you!
I'll be waiting at the usual Family Restaurant!
This...
Ami-chan!
You're incredible, I'm already...
Isn't my mouth-pussy great?
We're just about to do the real deal!
Ami-chan, not in this place!
Whenever I see your cock, I end up craving for it!
No... I can't stop myself anymore!
More... More...
I want it rougher!
Come... Come, mister!
Your cock milk! Pour your milk in me!
You're too incredible, mister!
Let's play again sometime.
It looks like Ami is having a difficulty getting up because of her hips.
I'm gonna be at your service
again all by myself.
Hey, mister!
I'm looking forward for your dick!
My tits are feeling good!
You're acting desperately spoiled today.
That's... because...
I'm... already...
Already—!
I'm craving your cock more and more,
that I can't take it anymore!
Please... mister!
Nana-chan...
It's okay.
Please kiss me, mister.
Mister...
Please purchase my virginity.
Wow! I only put it in and you already came!
What's this?! Amazing!
Sex is...
Amazing!
I'm... having sex!
My pussy walls are taking the shape of your dick!
No... There...
I'm feeling good!
Mister... I'm already...
I'm coming!
Coming! I'm coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
So good! It feels so good!
Your cock feels good!
It's so intense!
No...
I can't... already...
No—!
Come in me, mister!
Come! Come!
Coming!
Sex... is the best thing ever!
Jeez, Nana!
You already got hooked on mister's cock.
But you have to give me some
milk for tonight as well, okay?
Hey, you have to beg for it, Nana!
Even if you say that...
Both my tits and my pussy
are feeling so good!
Hey, what is it? What is your request for mister?
Please, mister...
Here's my pussy...
Screw it with your cock!
I guess it can't be helped, girls.
I'm gonna make you both
feel good at the same time.
What's this?! It's so incredible!
Both my pussy and clit...
They're both getting rubbed by your cock!
This is amazing...
It's amazing!
Amazing!
Incredible! Incredible!
I love it!
I love your middle-aged cock!
I'm coming again... I'm gonna come again!
Mister, come too!
Let's all three come together!
I'm coming!
It's been a few months since I came in Tokyo.
More than checking stock prices at mornings
and drinking parties with co-workers,
I found something to look forward to.
That's right.
I got transferred here,
and I pay for sex!
Coming... I'm coming!
With this...
Amazing!
There...
Oh no!
Give me your milk! Pour it deep inside me!
Have you had your fill for tonight, mister?
We are...
We are always gonna let you
come inside us and get paid for it!
Compensated Dating
Highsch••l
Bitch Gals
Daily Life of Raw Sex with An Old Man
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization