Train approaching. Please use caution.
It's been a few months since I got
transferred by myself to Tokyo.
I don't know if I'll ever get used to
the hustle and bustle of this city.
No way! Really?!
– Yeah. It's basically a shotgun wedding, but...
– I wonder how my wife is doing.
– Congratulations!
– Hey, Mister!
Wh-What? What can I help you two with?
You just look so totally lonely.
If you've got nothing to do, wanna hang out with us?
Huh?
We love sex and we can earn money this way!
I'm the tanned slut, Ami-chan!
Please take good care of us, Mister.
High School
Prostitution
Slutty Gals
Raw Sex with Older Guys
Part 1
The Slutty Gal
Ami
Okay then, Mister, how about we get started?
You seem really used to this.
We use this hotel a lot.
Okay, let us introduce ourselves.
I'm Ami! Hotel fee separate. Three Yukichis. Condom must.
Prostitute Terminology 1
Hotel Fee Separate, 3 Yukichis, Condom Must...
With Condom 30.000 Yen (Hotel Fee Not Included)
My name is Nana.
No kissing. No sex. Total fifteen K.
Prostitute Terminology 2
No Kissing. No Sex. 15k...
No Kissing Allowed, No Sex Allowed, 15.000 Yen
So then, let me start things off.
It's so hot and manly!
It feels like it's gonna bum my hands!
Wow, your dick is really getting big!
Nana's mouth-pussy must really feel good.
This thickness... This smell...
You're wonderful, Mister.
You're still so big!
That makes me so happy!
I think... your dick likes me back, huh?
Please keep giving me lots... of your cum, okay?
Please give me your dick milk in my boob-pussy!
Wow, your semen is covering my boobs and my pussy...
You made me wait a while, so I'm gonna go all out, okay?
Come on, hurry up.
Shove your big dick into my dripping wet pussy.
It's ready for you.
Mess it up good!
You're starting from the top, huh? You're so nice.
My boobs feel so good!
O-Oh my...
No!
It's really turning me on!
No! You're being so rough, Mister!
Hurry!
Mister, hurry.
Hurry and put it in!
Mister, your dick is too big!
Your dick is filling my body up!
My pussy feels so crammed!
Oh god...
Oh my god...
I've never been nailed this deep before!
Oh no...
I'm gonna cum!
Wow, your dick was really amazing, Mister.
Having sex with you was really amazing.
You two were both amazing as well.
Hey, would you mind giving me your number?
I wanna meet up with you again already!
Hey, Nana, that's not fair!
Me too, Mister!
Okay, okay.
And just like that our days together began.
THE NEXT DAY
The next day!
Huh? Are you by yourself today, Nana-chan?
Ami-chan apparently couldn't even stand after yesterday.
I'll take over for her tonight.
I'm gonna give it my best!
Your dick's already becoming really wet with your pre-cum!
I'm so happy that my feet are making you feel this good!
Your dick's so hot, Mister!
Please shoot out lots of cum, okay?
Please coat my feet-pussy with your cum!
Mister, your dick...
I really like it.
I'm sorry... I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Mister, thanks for the treat.
Choose the frame that you like the most.
Your dick is too amazing!
Your glans is rubbing against my pussy and
your tip is pounding against my womb!
Give it to me! Give me your cum!
Alright, strike a pose!
Shoot out your dick milk!
Three, two, one!
It's Me, Ami
I Love Sex
Mister,
I'm not letting you go home tonight.
I'm glad that Nana-chan's here too, but...
What's up with your outfits?
Isn't that obvious?
It should be, Mister.
We're cheerleaders and we're gonna cheer for you!
Yay! Yay! Mister's dick!
Yay! Yay!
I'll help make your raw sex time with Ami more exciting!
Raw sex?!
А до этого презервативы были? Где?!  ಠ_ಠ
It's a little bit pricier, but I want your raw dick.
Mister, you're so amazing!
It feels too good... My hips are just moving on their own!
No! I can't stop!
My hips won't stop!
It's too good... Your dick is too good!
I-I'm gonna...
H-Hurry! Hurry up and cum!
I'm gonna cum inside you, Ami-chan!
Come on, cheer for me!
Yay! Yay!
I can't hear you!
Come on, cheer for me!
No... I'm gonna...
Hurry!
Hurry up and shoot it inside me!
His cum's gushing out inside me!
I've never felt this before!
I... I...
I love prostitution!
Tomorrow, both of us will...
Have tons of sex with you, okay?
See you next time!
translation: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч