Youth means possibilities.
Yukki! Long time no see!
Mako! You look a little different.
You think so?
I heard that you dropped out of school.
Yeah, I'm not too smart,
so I was never really good at studying.
What about you? How's track going?
I got injured, so I quit.
Oh, really?
So what do you want to do?
I want to go shopping!
Yeah, me too.
I wonder what Mako's doing now...
Would she respond to me if I texted her?
I wanna see her again.
Does she remember me?
Uh... what was Mako's number again?
Mako was never good at fitting in,
so I hope she wasn't bullied at all.
Yeah, no reply. I figured as much...
We've been out of touch for so long.
Do you think the clothes we bought were too revealing?
Isn't it better if it's a little more on the risque side?
This is so good.
Yeah, it's really popular.
Possibilities are hot born out of nothing.
They are things that are slowly built
upon until they finally burst out.
It's Ryui-san's birthday today.
Let's go.
Reido-kun, I'm hanging out with
my friend right now, so I can't.
What'd you say?
Also, don't these parties cost a lot of money?
You have enough money, don't you?
No I don't! I don't have any at all!
Don't lie to me. Today, didn't you...
Excuse me.
Oh, aren't you cute.
Let's take her with us.
It's half off for friends.
Well, I'm gonna head over there now. See you two there.
You can just drop me off here.
Okay. Thanks for hanging out with me today!
I'm glad we were able to hang out.
Me too.
Don't you wish you could go back
to when we were middle schoolers, Yukki?
Yeah...
We didn't really have anything special back then,
but what I have now isn't exactly what I want either.
See you later.
Y-Yeah...
Later.
Help me!
I could hear her distant plea clearly.
I'm sure I heard her ask for help
or at least, that's what I felt.
I'm home.
It says she read the message,
but she hasn't even replied yet.
Mako had that same look
on her face when she graduated.
What should I do?
What am I even doing? I guess I just can't leave her alone.
What should I do? It's not like I can just walk right in.
Mako, don't go embarrassing me like that!
I was being serious! I really don't have any money!
Don't lie! You got some yesterday from work, didn't you?
You're seriously pissing me off!
Ow! Ow! I'm sorry!
I have a lot of regular customers, so...
Hey, let her go!
Huh?
Yukki? What are you doing here?
If you do any more than that, I'm going to call the police!
Yukki, why did you come here?
I was just so worried, I couldn't leave you alone.
Pako is looking for action costing around 30k.
Condom required. Okay that should work.
What're you doing?
Prostitution.
Oh wow, I got a reply!
What? Really?
I'll give you 15k for a one on one service, Pako.
Are you talking about yourself?
Yep. I'm the girl who gives head anytime, anywhere: Pako.
That's a disgusting description.
50k for a three way?
What's a three way?
It means that there are two girls and one guy.
Yukki! Let's do this together!
Sorry, no. I can't do that.
I'm here...
– I can't really leave Mako alone.
– Hello? Yeah, we're at the usual place. Room 305.
– Prostitution... so were going to have sex?
– Oh, you're already here?
– I've never even had a boyfriend before.
– Yeah, we're both here.
But I can't really leave Mako by herself.
Yukki, the guy wants to have anonymous sex,
so use something to hide your face.
O-Okay...
Oh, there he is.
Hi there! How've you been?
You must've been surprised
when I contacted you, huh?
It's fine. I haven't had a three way
in a while, so it was perfect timing.
Oh wow, your friend's really cute.
Are you two from the same school?
Urn, please don't look at me so much.
This is Yukki's first time, so she's nervous.
So your name's Yukki-chan?
You're gonna scare her to death
if you just whip it out like that.
Well, let's take some pictures to start things off.
Get next to each other.
Try exposing yourself a little more, Yukki-chan.
Like this?
Make sure our faces aren't in the pictures, okay?
Spread your legs more.
Looking good. Very sexy.
Please don't look so much.
What size cup are you?
D cup.
I'm an F cup.
You don't need to hide your face!
I'll make sure your face isn't in the picture.
Eh, I don't believe you at all. Yukki, be careful, okay?
So how long have you been having sex for?
You really think I'd tell you?
You're not a virgin or something, are you?
Holy shit, really? You're getting me so hard!
Pako, can you suck it for me?
Okay! Pako'll suck it for you.
Oh, that's good. You're as good as ever, Pako-chan.
Yeah, right there feels good!
There's already pre-cum trickling out,
it must feel really good.
She seems really used to this.
Yukki, can you describe what's going on right now?
Mako's tongue is wrapping around it
and lots of erotic fluids are coming out.
It's called pre-cum. Is it your first time seeing it?
It's my first time seeing it pour out like this.
Why don't you lick it too?
O-Okay...
I'm really going to lick this?
I guess I have to do what I have to do.
What's this smell?
Yukki, try kissing the tip.
And now take it deep.
It's going too deep!
I feel like I'm gonna melt in your mouth,
it feels so good! Try moving your mouth now.
Holy shit, this is too hot.
There's something gushing out of his dick.
Yukki, you're doing so great. You're taking it
in so deep even though it's your first time.
I think I'm just about there. I hope you're thirsty,
'cuz I got a lot coming for you.
What? You're gonna cum already?
It's gushing out from the tip!
Yukki, swallow every last drop.
It tastes too weird, I can't swallow it!
Aw, what a waste.
Are you okay, Yukki?
Yukki's still not used to it. Don't be too hard on her.
S-Sorry.
Pako, are you ready to go?
Yeah, I'm soaked up and ready to go.
I expected nothing less from a prostitute.
Hurry up and put it in me.
Hey, put a condom on.
What? I really need to put one on?
Come on, just let me do it raw.
– No, you gotta put on a condom... it's the rules.
– They're really gonna have sex?
– I should have one around here.
Well I guess I did promise to use one.
Thanks. Your dick's gotten so big!
Yeah, it's rock hard.
I wonder if something that big would it inside me.
Make me feel good!
Yeah, I'll mess you up good with this.
It's really going to go in.
For some reason, I... Huh?
Yukki, why don't you kiss me?
Yukki?
Wait, are you crying? Hold on a second!
Yukki?!
S-Sorry.
You serious? That sucks.
I'll make up for her!
Nah, I'm done.
This isn't worth the hotel fee, so I'm just gonna leave.
What? That's not enough!
I was promised a three way and I only got
a blow job. This is more than enough.
I really need the money!
This isn't something to cry over.
Yukki, you're a virgin, right?
You wanna sell yourself to me tonight?
I'll give you 100,000... no,
200,000 yen for your virginity.
Reido-kun sounded really angry over the phone.
He's definitely gonna beat me!
Mako, you just go and rest. I'll do something about this.
Huh?
I'm so happy that you really came, Yukki.
You're pretty nervous, huh?
N-Not really.
Well, I guess you are giving up
your virginity, so it makes sense.
The way you phrased that is disgusting.
Wear this. You don't want to show your face, right?
If you don't put it on soon,
I'm gonna take a picture with your face in it.
F-Fine.
Okay then come over here and pose.
Good, good. Smile a little more.
Try raising your bra a little more.
Okay now, show me more of your panties.
I wanna get a good shot of your virgin pussy.
You're so gross.
I'll give it a little kiss as a reward
for being so cooperative.
Huh? You're gonna kiss me down there?
I can smell the virgin on you.
Don't say that.
Knowing that I'm the first guy to touch you
down here really gets my heart racing.
Okay, I'm gonna kiss it now.
Directly? No, you can't do that.
It's so disgusting, but for some reason
I can't help but be excited.
Your erotic liquids just keep pouring out, Yukki.
Stop taking pictures of it.
Why don't you try talking dirty too?
– It feels so good that my pussy's...
– I'm already so turned on!
– Come on, this is an important moment for you.
Let me have a better look.
I'm ready to give up my virginity.
I'm going to give you my virginity, mister.
– I'm so turned on I'm already about to cum!
– I really want him to put his dick inside me.
Your dick is drooling all over me, mister.
And it's okay if I thrust this drooling
dick into your virgin pussy, right?
Y-Yeah. You can put it inside my pussy. I promised.
Then let's go bareback.
Bareback? No, put on a...
Oh god! My raw dick is in your virgin pussy, Yukki!
No! It's inside me!
I felt him break my hymen.
I really had my virginity taken by someone like him.
Yukki, it's inside! How's it feel to have
your first dick go all the way to your womb?
It hurts so much and it's so hot! Don't move it!
I don't think I can! Your pussy's gripping
my dick so tightly! Your pussy's the best!
I never cared about my virginity in the first place,
so I'm kind of grateful to this dick for taking it away.
Do you like my dick?
Yeah, I love it!
Oh my god, it's reaching all the way to my womb!
This is the dick that made you into a woman, Yukki!
I became a woman. I became a woman with this guy's dick.
I can feel your dick hitting my womb!
Your pussy just go even tighter! This pussy is amazing!
I'm already about to cum!
Huh? Cum? He doesn't mean...
I'm gonna cum inside you!
No, you can't! You can't! You can't!
Oh god, it's just too tight!
I... My mind's blank... Did I cum?
Yukki, you'll be okay if you swallow this.
What is it?
Swallow it while you clean up my dick.
It has a really strong smell.
Yeah, your pussy juices and my cum
make for an interesting smell.
Okay, swallow it while you take care of my dick.
It smells so badly, but for some reason,
I can't help but feel excited.
Yeah, that's good. Now suck all the cum off my dick.
Oh wow, look at you go! Doesn't my cum taste good, Yukki?
I don't care.
That should be enough now, right?
Did you make this money?
Does it matter?
Yukki, let's go.
What's the matter?
I... I...
Mako...
I know how you made that money, Mako.
That guy's bad news.
If he ever sends those pictures out...
I changed my profile picture. Thanks.
Yukki!
I promised to meet the guy again so that
he could delete the pictures in front of me.
We decided to meet in front of the school.
So, about the pictures...
You really are in your uniform, as you promised.
It looks really great on you. You're turning me on.
Don't stare at me so much.
Hey, you can't go that way.
I'm a sports equipment salesman, so there's no problem.
Let's head over to the gymnasium.
You're kidding.
We're going to do indoor training today.
Okay!
N-No, we can't!
Hm? Thought I heard something.
Okay, pair up and stretch.
Don't do anything to make yourself stand out.
Hey, what are you doing?
You took off your jacket 'cuz you're ready to fuck, right?
No, I only took it off because it got wet from the rain.
I've been hard for a while now.
His hard thing is rubbing against me!
It feels so good that my dick's just pulsating.
It's so hot and so hard.
Your pre-cum's just running down me.
It's getting on my clothes!
Well then, why don't you drink it? Doesn't it look tasty?
You pervert. Why would I do that?
The faster we end this, the better, right?
That's true, but...
You're so cute when you're doing
something risque like this, Yukki.
Come on, keep it down. People are gonna hear you.
You're pretty turned on too, aren't you?
You've been moving your hips.
Keep dreaming.
– But it's true that my excitement isn't going anywhere.
– Oh yeah, just like that.
– By sucking it like this, I can't help but get excited.
I just keep imagining his dick in my pussy and I get so wet.
I'll put my dick into your perverted pussy,
so get on all fours.
Hurry up and do it before anyone outside finds out.
Give it to me!
You put it in all at once!
Please be more gentle...
No...
I know I have to stay quiet,
but he's going so deep inside me!
I'm selling myself at school! I'm letting a dick
shove itself inside me! My mind's going blank!
No, if this keeps up, I'm gonna cum!
What was that just now? Did you hear that?
S-Stop!
Senpai, I'll get the ball!
Where's the bat?
W-Wait! Stop! They're gonna see us!
We don't need it.
No, stop moving! I can't control my voice!
Not happening, I can't hold myself back!
No, stop! Not right now! They're gonna find out!
Oh god, it just feels too good. I can't keep my voice down.
What's that noise?
You say something?
No!
Can you hear something?
Uh...
Hey, what are you doing here?
Oh, sorry! We'll just take these and go.
Holy shit, Yukki! You're so tight!
No, stop! They're gonna find out!
I know I can't cum, but...
I can't hold back anymore, I'm cumming!
Hurry up and go.
Must've been hearing things.
My uniforms soaked now.
Sorry about that. It just felt so good, I couldn't help myself.
So, about those pictures...
Oh, you mean this right? Yeah, here you go.
Okay, see you around.
O-Okay.
Kawaragi.
C-Coach?
Who was that guy?
He was a sports equipment sales...
Salesman...
I see.
I know him through a friend of mine.
Kawaragi, you're gonna catch a cold dressed like that.
R-Right.
So, I just happened to see something interesting earlier.
– Did he find out?
– Come to the family restaurant at 9 tonight.
– Did he find out about everything?
– I wanna talk to you about your future path.
U-Understood.
Don't worry, I'll explain everything for you.
But...
Coach...
Hi there.
Kawaragi, who's this?
Nice to meet you. I'm Yukki's friend from middle school.
Yukki told me how cool you are
so I just had to see for myself.
I-Is that right?
Kawaragi, this is you, isn't it?
No, um...
It's all my fault!
I'm in a lot of debt, so Yukki being the nice person that she is,
offered to help me pay it off by prostituting with me.
So, it's true that you participated in prostitution then?
I-I'm sorry.
The man I introduced her to likes this kind of blackmail
role play, so he came to the school to blackmail her.
That may be the case, but she certainly
seems to be enjoying herself.
Th-That's not...
Kawaragi, you look like some kind of whore.
Hey, Yukki. This guy has a hard-on.
Huh?
Did you get turned on by imaging everything?
Wh-What are you doing?
Do you wanna know what me and Yukki did in more detail?
I'm glad that you're so understanding, Coach.
I understand that you two had
your reasons. So because of that...
It's my first time seeing a dick this amazing. Yukki?
Your mouth...
I never thought you were this perverted, Kawaragi.
Your nipples are erect already. They're rock hard.
Please, don't say that to me.
Whenever I saw you,
my heart always skipped a beat, Coach.
Really? Then I'll make sure you have a good time.
Touch me more!
I think Yukki's ready to go down here.
Get a good lesson from your Coach, okay?
Coach, you're so hard!
Okay, Kawaragi, let me show you the way.
Yes, please, Coach. Teach my pussy a lesson!
Your dick is so hard! I can tell just how turned on
you are from it! It's being shoved so deep inside me!
Thank you for this dick lesson!
So rough... You're being so rough, Coach!
Coach, you're thrusting it so much inside of me, I...
Kawaragi, your friend's soaking wet too.
I just started thinking dirty thoughts
and then I just kept getting wetter and wetter.
I love the way your big, strong dick
is shoving against my womb!
No! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum with your dick!
Coach, please pour your cum into my womb!
Give me your thick stuff!
I'm cumming!
I'm not done yet. I still got some
more lessons to teach you two.
Coach, your dick is still so hard.
There's still so much of your cum inside me.
Don't spread it so wide like that. It's so embarrassing.
I still can't believe that you've become so dirty, Kawaragi.
Please don't say that. My womb is still throbbing.
It's about time for your friend to get a lesson too.
Yes. Please don't take your time, I can't wait any longer!
Oh my god, your big, hard dick is inside me!
It's my first time having something this big!
It's hitting the end of my womb!
My pussy's gonna become the shape of this huge dick!
Coach, give it to me again too.
Give what to you again and where?
You gotta spell it out for me.
Please put your big, thick dick inside my perverted pussy.
Okay then. I guess I'll stick it into your horny pussy.
Thank you very much!
You guys are in debt, right? I'll do something about it.
I'll make you two into my mistresses.
You understand what that means?
You mean it? I'll become your mistress then.
Me too! I'll become your mistress, Coach!
Your dick feels so good!
Coach, I...
Get a good taste of my dick!
Your dick's twitching. I'm gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum! Keep thrusting your dick inside of me!
Holy crap, you're so tight. I'm at my limit,
I'm gonna pour my cum inside you!
Do it! Cum inside me! I'm your mistress,
so it's okay even if I get pregnant!
I want to take in your love more than anything!
Fill my womb with your cum!
Coach, I'm gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Yukki, you were the one who said you'd be his mistress.
Did I really?
But yeah, Coach's dick was really amazing, wasn't it?
Yeah, just thinking about it makes me horny.
I've already decided on the next guy.
Oh, poor Coach.
Oh, my customer's here, so I'll talk to you later.
Okay. Well then.
Um, are you...
Uh, last night...
At the family restaurant, I...
So, you saw that? I see.
Um, so...
Oh, what do you want to do?
Huh?
No, I just...
Then what did you come here for?
Tell me.
Yes, I want to do it with you.
Your dick's twitching.
How much money do you have?
Money?
Yeah, I'm not gonna do this for free.
Kawaragi-senpai, does that mean that...
Today's a freebie, okay?
Your dick has foreskin, huh?
I can peel it back like this, right?
This is my first time with a dick like this.
Kawaragi-senpai's sucking my dick!
It feels really good!
Having the senpai I've admired
for so long suck my dick like this... I...
Senpai, I can't... I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
S-Sorry, this is my first time.
It's fine. I was just a little bit surprised.
So you're a virgin?
That's so cute.
Next time bring a lot of money and a lot of cum, okay?
Owner, you have a text.
It's from Yukki!
It's been half a year since
you last spoke with her, hasn't it?
Apparently she graduated. She even sent a picture.
How does she look?
Look. It's the serious looking Yukki.
She looks very normal.
Did she give up prostitution?
Probably.
Yukki doesn't know anything about you, does she, Pako?
And it's fine that way.
She told me that after quitting track, she felt empty.
So that's why I gave her something to fill that hole.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupersent
editor: akin
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Graduate...
Advance to the next grade...
If even then...
I don't find anything...
If that happens...
I'll...
I'll fill that hole for you again...
Possibilities...
They come from nothing...
They aren't generated...
Not at all...
They will one day flourish...
But until that day...
You must nurture them...
Youth is...