Manager of a Small Convenience Store: Shimoda Yoshihiro
Yoshihiro is a single man who's reaching middle age soon, and who's worried
about his weight issue as well. He relies on his job as a store manager
which he got after being hired by the owner who's also his close friend.
His sole entertainment in life is using a hidden camera to peep on Yui,
his high-schooler niece, together with Shiori, her elder female cousin.
Both are working as part-time employees at the store.
But he has been laying his hands on the two lately, and with that
also comes its own luxurious set of problems for him.
Paranoid and Delusional High School Girl: Kusunose Miki
Miki is a stereotypical street-smart high school girl typically seen nowadays.
She is a ditzy girl who ironically carries herself with full confidence,
claiming that she absolutely never makes any mistakes.
Although she is dedicated at work, she pretends to not see
all of her own shortfalls.
She seems to have been raised by high-class parents with her
princess-like attitude of bitching on people she doesn't like,
even if that person happens to be an elder to her.
She is a cheeky high school girl.
A Scandalous High School Girl Cousin: Fuyutsuki Shiori
Shiori is a spitting image of a cheeky high school girl not only in her looks
but also in her way of speaking. With both of her parents dead, her elder aunt who also is Yui's mother took custody of her.
Shiori started living with the two for a few days now.
She feels that her being a free-loader is inexcusable.
She does not want to keep relying on them for her meals and other expenses,
so she puts an effort into landing herself on a part-time job.
She successfully acquires a scholarship for college. This shows that she actually
is a conscientious, praiseworthy, and hard-working high school girl,
far from what her appearance and way of speaking implies.
High School Niece: Nakaizumi Yui
Yui is a well-behaved, honest, cheerful, and diligent girl.
She is a bit of a klutz by nature, a twin-tailed girl who always gives
her best at work that can be clueless at times.
She works to help her mother on shouldering daily expenses and school fees.
She is exemplary for being a hard-working part-time employee,
and a sexy high school girl as well.
"Looks like I'll get hooked on Miki..."
The excessively self-conscious and cheeky part-timer Miki
filed a sexual harassment complaint against Yoshihiro.
He later forcibly strips her, forces her to suck him,
and took the opportunity to screw her and taking her first time.
Miki's face warped in agony as she complains
kindled Yoshihiro's long due arousal.
He does nothing but humiliating her by stripping her in public.
He uses his position as the store manager
to remove her skirt and order her to sweep the floor.
Miki trembles from shame and regret but won't drop her stubborn attitude.
But what's beyond her knowledge is the fact that her unfaltering attitude
of throwing impudent complaints and saying that she'll sue him
only fuels up Yoshihiro's lust.
"Those two have loosened up lately..."
Those two girls are now dying in boredom while the monster is away.
Meanwhile, Yoshihiro attains a new level of entertainment for himself
by rigorously humiliating the cheeky Miki right in front of her boyfriend.
Ero Konbini Tenchou
Lecherous Convenience Store Manager
Original Animation
Have The Dirt On Female Part-timer
And Do Her As Much As You Want
Last Time on Ero Konbini Tenchou
Huh?
What, you're just here as a fill-in?
You don't look like you have
what it takes to be a manager.
Thank you for coming!
That was quite something earlier.
Kusunose-san, do you have a moment?
Everything is taken care of, up to the orders.
Lots of the staff tend to quit so
I've been doing it myself.
That must have been hard for you.
Yeah, I already got used to it.
I'll teach you while I'm here.
You've only been here for half a year,
so you must've made mistakes at times.
I never make mistakes.
Here is today's report, manager.
Good job.
And one more thing...
Huh?
I filed a report about your
sexual harassment today.
I'll submit it to the main office.
What... After sexual harassment,
it's abuse of power now?
Your misinterpretation is terribly off.
What are you doing? This is sexual harassment!
My sexual harassment is on another level!
You're not making any sense!
P-Please stop touching me!
No!
Ouch!
It went inside!
A man's hot fleshy rod is scraping me inside!
You're not wet yet but bear with it.
You'll be drenched in no time.
Aren't you the liar here? Dammit!
No! No way, are you gonna come inside?
I'd get pregnant from that! N-No! No! No!
Don't! Seriously, you can't!
No! No! No! No!
If you put that thing inside me again
while there's still some stuff left...
No! Stop!
You really might end up pregnant.
Making me do something like this...
S-Something like this...
Huh, you're still there.
Yeah, I'll still have to put some stuff away.
Have you given a thought about last time?
Yes, I think I'll be able to get a day off.
His rock hard cock reaches so deep inside me!
Can you give me a little more time?
I understand but don't take too long.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Don't go that hard on me, he'll catch us!
Come on, it's morning already. Get yourself ready.
I still feel sleepy...
Jeez, making me come over
yesterday all of a sudden...
Hey, did something happen?
Yui told me to come here at once.
Whoa!
Huh?!
Hey there! What are you doing out of the blue?
Wait! Calm down, you fat-ass scum! Hey!
I can't, I've been longing for you.
Huh?!
That doesn't mean you'll just suddenly...
I won't run away, so just wait!
You're an idiot... Hey!
Wait!
You put it inside me while
we're in such a place!
You're an idiot!
Weren't you hoping for this?
You idiot! Yui said it's something urgent
so I wondered what's up!
Hoping your ass, you sleaze!
Oh, so you were worried
about me. That's cute.
Huh?! Shut up, you scum!
Pull it out already!
I'm going home if there's nothing
wrong with you, airhead!
Huh? Whoa!
Hey, that's dangerous!
Hey, stop!
You... I'm going home!
You're the only one for me, Shiori.
Shut up! You said the same to Yui!
You even said that to auntie not long ago!
How did you know that?
Never underestimate us
high school girls, sleazeball!
You won't be able to seal our lips!
Well, that certainly is true...
You... Are you planning
to come inside me again?
I don't want that!
I'm gonna come a lot.
Dammit! Learn some self-control!
Fat-ass!
Fat-ass! Sleazeball!
Fat-ass! Sleazeball! Airhead!
No... I'm coming! I'm coming!
You're coming too much!
Airhead scum...
Oh, the time!
Alright, Just put the key
in mailbox after locking up!
So she came.
Shiori has also been compliant lately.
If we'll talk about fresh, it has to be Miki.
She's fast...
He won't be able to do weird things to me here.
I'll definitely sue his ass off. No matter
how cute I am, he can't just...
She's being cautious.
I won't be able to do anything at the walkways...
Don't underestimate
a convenience store manager.
Kusunose-san, can you man the register?
Yes, I understand.
Welcome!
I'm glad to see you smiling today as well.
Thank you for always shopping here.
It'll all be 581 yen.
What is he doing? Don't tell me that he's
gonna do strange things to me here...
Hello, I'll have the usual again for today.
You're kidding! It has to be now,
of all times! What should I do?
He planned doing this here!
Will that be everything?
Umm... It'll all be 390 yen.
Thank you. Can we talk for a little?
Okay, yes... It's fine.
He's rubbing me... If we get caught here...
About the last time,
will your next day-off be fine?
O-Oh, right... Next day-off...
A-Are you okay? You look sick.
No, I'm alright! I'm just a little dizzy.
No, he's touching it directly...
Don't push yourself.
Yeah, I think we should be fine on my next day-off...
I'm happy that we get to talk.
Yeah, me too...
Seriously? I can't believe this!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Time's running so let's talk later.
Oh, you're right. I'll wait at the usual spot.
It's okay, take care.
Yes, see you later.
She hit me with her full strength!
I won't forgive that overly
self-conscious high school girl!
See you later.
Don't think that you
can just meet up with him.
I-I'm going home, so make way!
Should I sue you for physical injury?
Huh? Isn't that your fault for doing
dirty stuff on me... Don't give me that!
How rich, coming from a pervert who's
dripping wet while talking to her boyfriend.
I-I'm not! There's no way I'll ever be like that!
"I never fail", "I'm not like that"...
You're the exact opposite of what you say.
Th-That's not true!
It is, or won't you realize
it unless I show you?
What are you doing?!
Pervert!
Pervert! Molester!
Pervert! Molester! Sleazeball!
Pervert! Molester! Sleazeball! Scum!
Pervert! Molester! Sleazeball! Scum! Fat-ass!
What's up with this stain, huh?
Th-That's...
That's what?
That is, umm...
I-I just peed a little! It isn't what it looks like!
I-I'll be excusing myself!
I see... So that is pee!
Well, let me have a good check!
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop that, you don't need to check!
This isn't piss... More importantly, your ass...
Pervert! What the hell are you doing?
That's the wrong spot! Don't poke
your nose there, idiot!
It went inside me again!
No!
Yoshihiro-san
Is that your boyfriend waiting like a fool?
Are you planning to talk to him like this?
Scum!
Scum! Sleazeball!
Scum! Sleazeball! Brute!
Scum! Sleazeball! Brute! Pervert!
I'll never ever forgive you!
No!
What should I do? If I let him wait...
I won't be able to meet him if this goes on!
What, he could've been caught up
in an accident or something.
How cold of you.
Shut up! You should just die!
Pervert!
Pervert! Scum!
Pervert! Scum! Stalker!
Pervert! Scum! Stalker! Molester!
You're rude.
Besides, I can do proper work.
You're stupid in comparison.
Hey, what "stupid" are you saying?
Only stupid people call others stupid!
Can't you just message him?
Like, say that you left early.
Huh?
Yoshihiro-san
Help me!
You can't just go run to your
boyfriend looking like that.
Help me! If he keeps having his way on me, I'll...
Yoshihiro-san
It's already past our meet-up time.
I wonder if you're feeling ill?
Are you alright? I'm worried.
Please call me back.
Sorry for not contacting you.
I suddenly felt sick so I left early.
I
I fe
I feel
I feel a
I feel a lot
I feel a lot bet
I feel a lot better
I feel a lot better now.
I feel a lot better now. I'll
I feel a lot better now. I'll ca
I feel a lot better now. I'll call
I feel a lot better now. I'll call yo
I feel a lot better now. I'll call you
I feel a lot better now. I'll call you to
I feel a lot better now. I'll call you tomo
I feel a lot better now. I'll call you tomorr
I feel a lot better now. I'll call you tomorrow
No! Stop going any further!
Why are you doing this?
What did I do to deserve this?
Blame your own excessive self-consciousness.
That isn't true at all!
You're the one who should face reality!
Well, you being cute is a reality.
No matter how cute I am, doing such a thing...
This isn't something a human
would do! You brute! You're sick!
You can say whatever you want.
No, it's reaching deep inside me!
Are you gonna come again?
I don't want to get pregnant!
You can't! No, don't! No more!
No—!
It's pouring inside me!
Y-You're cruel!
Doing such a thing to me is too cruel...
You get what you deserve.
Alright, I'll be locking up so
fix your clothes and go home.
What's up, Yui?
No, that's fine.
Yes, that's it. Right there...
Isn't this good enough?
I became his comfort woman now.
Any further and my relationship will...
Please hurry up and come! I need to work.
This is part of your work as well.
It's called serving the store manager.
This man is way beyond help.
No, he's not even human. He disgraced me.
We can't do this! You have
to hurry up and come!
No, not that deep!
No, don't!
Please stop! We'll get caught here!
That depends on you, Miki.
Can't we just do this somewhere else?
Why does it have to be here?
So you never met up with
your boyfriend the other day.
I heard about it at the register yesterday.
There's no way that I could!
After getting raped and sullied like
a slave, there's no way that I could...
Just keep it a secret. Aren't you
good at putting up a front?
You're wrong! That isn't a front!
That's me being professional
at work! How rude of you!
Work, huh...
It's way beyond that, though.
People who work seriously
are capable of that.
It would be impossible for you, though.
Then prove it to me.
Umm... Are you busy right now?
Oh, umm...
I'm currently sorting some items.
I'll call you later, alright?
Wh-What were you thinking?
Won't you also get in trouble
if we get caught? You brute!
How about sending your boyfriend
a photo looking like this?
Say whatever you please.
Just hurry up and get this over!
Nothing I say will reach this man.
Any more than this and even I will...
No, it's coming...
Coming...
It's pouring in...
No way, why is he still here?
What's wrong? You look down.
Oh, no...
Sorry. I'm alright, thank you.
There's no way he'll come back.
What am I even doing?
It's obviously gonna end like this...
Miki has such a great body.
I'm gonna be hooked on her.
Those two have loosened up
as well, so it's about time...
Well, then. Nothing seems off
here so I should go home.
I'm gonna surprise him
since I got a duplicate key!
Oh, did he see my message
and dashed back home?
Yes! Welcome
Yes! Welcome home?
Huh?
Huh?!
Oh...
Wh-Why are you here?
Fuyutsuki...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization