Manager of a Small Convenience Store: Shimoda Yoshihiro
Yoshihiro is a single man who's reaching middle age soon, and who's worried
about his weight issue as well. He relies on his job as a store manager
which he got after being hired by the owner who's also his close friend.
His sole entertainment in life is using a hidden camera to peep on Yui,
his high-schooler niece, together with Shiori, her elder female cousin.
Both are working as part-time employees at the store.
But he has been laying his hands on the two lately, and with that
also comes its own luxurious set of problems for him.
Paranoid and Delusional High School Girl: Kusunose Miki
Miki is a stereotypical street-smart high school girl typically seen nowadays.
She is a ditzy girl who ironically carries herself with full confidence,
claiming that she absolutely never makes any mistakes.
Although she is dedicated at work, she pretends to not see
all of her own shortfalls.
She seems to have been raised by high-class parents with her
princess-like attitude of bitching on people she doesn't like,
even if that person happens to be an elder to her.
She is a cheeky high school girl.
A Scandalous High School Girl Cousin: Fuyutsuki Shiori
Shiori is a spitting image of a cheeky high school girl not only in her looks
but also in her way of speaking. With both of her parents dead, her elder aunt who also is Yui's mother took custody of her.
Shiori started living with the two for a few days now.
She feels that her being a free-loader is inexcusable.
She does not want to keep relying on them for her meals and other expenses,
so she puts an effort into landing herself on a part-time job.
She successfully acquires a scholarship for college. This shows that she actually
is a conscientious, praiseworthy, and hard-working high school girl,
far from what her appearance and way of speaking implies.
High School Niece: Nakaizumi Yui
Yui is a well-behaved, honest, cheerful, and diligent girl.
She is a bit of a klutz by nature, a twin-tailed girl who always gives
her best at work that can be clueless at times.
She works to help her mother on shouldering daily expenses and school fees.
She is exemplary for being a hard-working part-time employee,
and a sexy high school girl as well.
"I never make mistakes."
This particular store has already switched managers thrice
in a span of almost half a year. Yoshihiro has been assigned
to the said store as a temporary manager.
Here he meets Miki, the part-timer who's been working
for almost half a year as well.
Yoshihiro was taken aback by how Miki is way different compared to Shiori and Yui.
Miki is implying that she sees Yoshihiro as someone unreliable as she looks at him.
She obviously considers him as trash while her discerning eyes scrutinize him.
Miki verbally abuses Yoshihiro on each and every opportunity she can.
He angrily thinks about it as he watches her in a candid voyeur video recording of the locker room. However, he gets a call from the main office
while in the middle of what he is doing.
Yoshihiro plans to peacefully settle the issue with Miki,
but her outrageous self-consciousness has already reached the main office.
That, together with all of the bad treatment he got from her
made Yoshihiro snap and unleash his anger onto her.
"My sexual harassment is on another level!"
Miki trembled in fear as he showed her what real sexual harassment is.
Ero Konbini Tenchou
Lecherous Convenience Store Manager
Original Animation
Have The Dirt On Female Part-timer
And Do Her As Much As You Want
Last Time on Ero Konbini Tenchou
The view from up here feels so nostalgic!
It was my first time back then...
I had you pinned down to the floor, Yoshi-kun...
I haven't noticed that you
were in a daze at that time!
Hey, old man!
What?
Yoshihiro, lick.
Wait, stop!
You cheeky brat!
You scum! Where the hell are you licking?
Stop that!
Idiot, don't do that! Dumb-ass!
That's my ass!
No way, it's dirty!
Aren't you feeling it?
Scum! Fat-ass! There's no way I would!
Cut that out!
For an old man like you...
This place should just go bankrupt
have you get lost, sleazeball!
Won't it be the same for you if that happens?
Shit... This fat-ass!
I don't want this!
This feels gross, but why!
I'll play with you this time
but this will be the last, uncle!
Wait, Yui! Were you watching us all along?
Dammit! So, you saw everything!
It seems that mom at least never knew
about us being fucked by uncle.
And using that fact, I now have uncle...
Y-Yui, you're scaring me!
Even last time, I had no idea
that you dragged me along...
Men are no good for this girl.
She is a pervert who's only into other girls.
Well, umm... I...
I'll excuse myself!
Shi-chan...
Doing this while being penetrated
somehow feels amazing!
I'll be happy too if you'll get thinner!
Won't that be great, Uncle!
Having such a dysfunctional
lump will make you die early.
You really should go for a diet!
You'll be allowed to do it whenever
and wherever you want
if your diet goes well...
if your diet goes well... by Shi-chan!
Hey there, Yui! Don't make any weird promises!
Hey, uncle! That's good!
Do your best for me!
Oh no! Ah!
Did someone quit again? It really is a burden for me.
I have to get all of the orders done by myself.
Hmm? It'll be fine next time? Are you sure?
Okay, I'm looking forward to seeing you.
Hang in there, see ya!
Welcome!
Oh, you're working on day shifts
now? Where's the manager?
The manager's a little sick
so he's on leave for some time.
Welcome!
I'll be the new manager
starting today. I am Shimoda.
The door at the back is locked, so I went here.
Uhh, he looks anything but alright...
I'm Kusunose Miki, a part-timer.
I'll be under your care from now on.
I need to make a good impression.
Let's get along. I'll only be
here for a month, though.
I was assigned here temporarily.
Huh?
What, you're just here as a fill-in?
You don't look like you have
what it takes to be a manager.
Thank you for coming!
That was quite something earlier.
Kusunose-san, do you have a moment?
Everything is taken care of, up to the orders.
Lots of the staff tend to quit so
I've been doing it myself.
That must have been hard for you.
Yeah, I already got used to it.
I'll teach you while I'm here.
You've only been here for half a year,
so you must've made mistakes at times.
I never make mistakes.
W-Welcome...
It'll be 321 yen in total.
Umm... I'll call you later.
I'll be waiting. Hang in there, Miki.
Is something wrong?
Is that your boyfriend?
That's none of your business!
Here is today's report, manager.
Good job.
And one more thing...
Huh?
I filed a report about your
sexual harassment today.
I'll submit it to the main office.
Sexual harassment?!
Wait, I did?!
Are you playing dumb?
You abused your authority just
because I'm cute. You're the worst!
W-Wait, calm down!
It's late now so let's continue
this tomorrow, alright?
You can't just hush me up with some cash!
Did she treat my help as sexual
harassment? That high school bitch...
...he kept trying to seduce me as he guides me through with a naughty smirk on his face,
Wasn't I just guiding her through?
What is she, paranoid?
Her imagination is way so crazy, goddammit!
Yes, good evening.
Yes, that was today.
Huh, no... there has to be
some sort of mistake!
Yes, I'll check our inventory.
Looks like this will be one fun month.
The main office contacted me about your complaint.
I said we'll talk about it today, right?
Why are you ignoring your manager?
Of course, I knew that you'd just cover it up...
So, talking would be pointless...
We'll calmly talk in the office
after you're done with that.
Then we'll talk about how you shouldn't
sexually harass me, pervert.
He's just the same as all of the
past managers. What a creep.
Pardon my intrusion.
I read your report and I can see your paranoia.
Such convenient reasoning...
Men really are the worst.
You say that, but weren't you talking
with your boyfriend at the register?
Th-That was a simple greeting.
That's against company policy.
Fix yourself first before accusing me
of your one-sided harassment.
So, that's how it goes? You're
planning to cover this up, huh?
I'll never let you off with that!
Stubborn, aren't you?
Aren't you talking about yourself?
I'll ignore your violation of company policy as well
if you'll offer to write a written apology by yourself.
What... After sexual harassment,
it's abuse of power now?
Your misinterpretation is terribly off.
What are you doing? This is sexual harassment!
My sexual harassment is on another level!
You're not making any sense!
P-Please stop touching me!
No!
No way... Stop, no!
Shut up.
Write a letter of apology if you
don't want this to go further.
I-I understand.
I'll write one.
I'll just write it here, right?
Say that you were mistaken.
Wait, what are you... The locker room is over there!
You might use that chance to run away.
Don't mind me and go on writing.
I hate this... Why does a victim
like me have to go through...
What... Wait, what are you doing?!
I'm changing my underwear as well.
Even if you say that...
You're not writing?
We'll go all the way, then.
N-No need for that. I'll write it.
What was that? Is that how a man's thing is?
It's way bigger than dad's!
Those two instances of me getting harassed by...
dick
------------------------was a mistak...
That wasn't hard yet, right?
Huh? What am I writing?
But having something like that nearby...
You'll get it done faster if I'll read it beside you.
Go on, write it down.
It's reddish-brown with a peculiar
shape. What an atrocious thing!
What's with that thing?
It's way bigger than before!
This looks bad...
Wh-What... Wait, what are you doing?
No, let go of me!
Yeah, don't mind me and just write.
Stop fooling around! This isn't what
you said before! No, let me go!
No!
N-No, where do you think you're touching?
Wait, not down there! Stop!
Are you getting moist here with sweat, or rather...
Don't you stink down there?
Huh? That's harsh! You're being rude!
I'm sure that it stinks...
...despite having such a cute face.
No... Stop, you pervert!
Stop! Idiot! Scum! Molester!
You call yourself cute yet you stink down there.
Isn't that embarrassing?
You're wrong! You're just being weird!
That isn't true at all!
Then, let's check it out.
What are you doing? Please stop!
No, stop sniffing!
I knew it. You don't even
realize it yourself. That's sad.
No, you're definitely wrong!
I'm washing it properly and keeping it clean!
You don't smell your own odor, after all.
I'll bang this stinky pussy
of yours with my cock.
What... No! Wait, don't! I'm begging you, stop—
No—!
Ouch!
It went inside!
There's a man's hot fleshy rod scraping me inside!
You're not wet yet but bear with it.
You'll be drenched in no time.
No! Why is this happening?
This can't be!
Everyone will sexually harass
a cutie like you. It can't be helped.
This isn't sexual harassment!
This is rape, forced sex! You liar!
Aren't you the liar here? Dammit!
No! No way, are you gonna come inside?
I'd get pregnant from that! N-No! No! No!
Don't! Seriously, you can't!
No! No! No! No!
No! No... No!
No—!
I can feel your sperm soaking my insides up!
You impregnated me!
You won't get pregnant that easily...
...unless we do it more like this!
No! Stop, no way! Again?
If you put that thing inside me again
while there's still some stuff left...
No! Stop!
You really might end up pregnant.
No human can do such a thing!
You brute! Demon! Fiend!
Good, keep bawling! You're
squeezing me tighter that way!
What, you're done already? That's boring.
Should I get it done here as well?
No way, no! Is this...
Y-You're kidding, right? Are you coming again?
This can't be! Stop, I'll really end up pregnant!
You came again!
There's a lot inside me...
Why would you do such a thing...
This isn't sexual harassment, you just
happened to have a hole down there.
That's cruel! You're lying!
We both know that you assaulted
me because I'm so cute!
Fix that excessively sad amount
of self-consciousness of yours!
What? Why are you...
No! It grew big again!
It's inside me again!
No, no more! Let me off already!
No more! Forgive me!
Is this his dick? It's in my mouth, no way!
No... What's with this thing?
This is disgusting! It stinks, no!
That man turned me into a
woman right here yesterday...
Using that gnarly dick of his...
I'm taking a picture as well.
No! Wh-What is this? Are you
candidly peeping on me?
I'm just greeting you before work starts.
Good morning!
Good morning...
Wait, I'm changing right now! Please get out!
Even if you say that...
I won't be able to work at the register with this...
Making me do something like this...
S-Something like this...
I'll never ever forgive you!
I'm fine with that, so be sure to make me come.
You sleazeball!
You brute!
S-Something like this...
There's so much... It's disgusting!
You did great! Alright, it's time for work.
Please give my skirt back!
You have to hurry and get that done first.
Oh, you're cleaning here...
Hello... I just got done here.
Then, I'll be using the toilet.
Yes, feel free to...
P-Please stop, he'll find us out! I'm begging you!
So even you are afraid to be
caught by your boyfriend.
Of course, anyone would be...
Please don't!
Not here, he's about to come out!
That makes me want to do this more.
It went inside me!
Huh, you're still there.
Yeah, I'll still have to put some stuff away.
Have you given a thought about last time?
Yes, I think I'll be able to get a day off.
His rock hard cock reaches so deep inside me!
Can you give me a little more time?
I understand but don't take too long.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Don't go that hard on me, he'll catch us!
You're aroused, your body got so hot.
You're wrong! Never from
something like this, ever...
Doing such a thing in front of my boyfriend...
You're supposed to be a manager, an adult!
You brute!
I'll never ever forgive you!
Come on, it's morning already. Get yourself ready.
I still feel sleepy...
Jeez, making me come over
yesterday all of a sudden...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time on Ero Konbini Tenchou
You idiot! Yui said it's something urgent
so I wondered what's up, but you're waiting for this, you sleaze!
Oh, so you were worried about me. That's cute.
Huh?! Shut up, you scum!
Pull it out already!
I'm going home if there's nothing
wrong with you, airhead!
He won't be able to do weird things to me here.
I'll definitely sue his ass off. No matter
how cute I am, he can't just...
She's being cautious...
I'll need to handle her more carefully...
Don't underestimate
a convenience store manager.
Hello, I'll have the usual again for today.
You're kidding! It has to be now,
of all times! What should I do?
Umm... It'll all be 390 yen.
Thank you. Can we talk for a little?
Oh, I'm sorry!
I have no time right now, so later...
Oh, you're right. I'll wait at the usual spot.
It's alright, take care.
Okay...
What are you doing?!
Pervert!
Pervert! Molester!
Pervert! Molester! Sleazeball!
Pervert! Molester! Sleazeball! Scum!
Pervert! Molester! Sleazeball! Scum! Fat-ass!
What is this?
That is, umm...
I-I just peed a little! It isn't what it looks like!
I-I'll excuse myself!
It went inside me again!
No!
Yoshihiro-san
Is that your boyfriend waiting like a fool?
Are you planning to talk to him like this?
No matter how cute I am, doing such a thing...
This isn't something a human
would do! You brute! You're sick!
You can say whatever you want.
No, it's reaching deep inside me!
Are you gonna come again?
I don't want to get pregnant!