I always lose on the first round.
I'm a total loser...
That's not true!
L-Lemon-chan?!
I know because I've been watching you!
Our school's idol-like cheerleader
somehow knows about me?
Presented by
Maruwa Tarou
Even if I enter another tournament,
I'm just gonna lose again. I'm just...
I only use this club as a way to kill time.
I might as well just give up.
You shouldn't say things like that!
I know how hard you've been
practicing every morning!
It's really impressive!
I can tell that you really love tennis!
Lemon-chan...
Oh, I know! Will you let me cheer for you?
That way, you'll be able to continue!
I'll do anything for you.
Lemon-chan was so radiant...
Wait, did she say she'd do anything?!
"Anything?" Then if I win,
does that mean you'll do anything I ask?
Huh?
Well, I do want him, to try hard...
Yeah, no problem!
I know you'll win, Asagiri-kun!
She really thinks I'm capable of winning...
Okay then, your boobs!
Huh?!
If I win, let me touch your boobs!
Hell yeah! Let's do this!
Wh-What?!
In tough times, sad times, fun times and happy times,
ero-manga has always been by my side.
I, Okazaki, enjoy reading ero-manga.
As my graduation drew closer, I began to panic.
Suddenly, I came across an ad asking for an editor.
I read this magazine!
But...
Rock Bottom Comics is a fairly new ero-manga
magazine that barely makes ends meet.
If I get hired there, it'll be easier
to get my suggestions accepted.
And if that's the case, then it'll be the perfect place
to put my extensive ero-manga knowledge to use!
I was introduced to Miyahara Nao-san, the CEO,
who had no motivation, and barely understood ero-manga.
And then there was also her
sole assistant, Fujita Masakazu-san.
But Fujita-san went on to do greater things in the ero-manga world,
being chosen as a top-tier editor for Kami Magazine.
Because of that, I was hired even
though I had no prior experience.
Over the summer, Fujita-san helped me to
gradually learn how to do my job as an editor.
And then he left.
Now, it's up to me to determine
whether Rock Bottom sinks or swims!
I need to make a good impact on this magazine!
Or so I thought until I got an email from Fujita-san.
It was an invitation to come work
with him at the Kami Magazine
I'd be surrounded by top-tier editors and creators
in order to make top-tier ero-manga...
It's my dream job.
But to do that, I'd have to ditch Rock Bottom.
As it stands, I only have about six months
of experience, and that's all from Rock Bottom.
I'm in a pretty tough spot right now.
Kami Magazine or Rock Bottom?
What do I do?!
Original animation disk.
Ero Manga!
Stepping Up both Sex and Manga.
Stepping up drawing and being drawn?!
Ayato Haruru is Ready to be Served Arc.
Fujita-senpai
Want to come work with me at Kami Magazine?
Of course!
Thanks for the offer, but...
I actually turned him down...
But this might be a great opportunism for me
to make my ideal ero-manga with my own two hands!
This is the start of my path to making
Rock Bottom the best in the industry!
Look at you with your enthusiasm.
Editor-in-chief?!
I guess this'll do.
What will?
Wait... What are you...
It's not even fully erect and it's this big?
dick
Keep calm, keep calm, me!
slurp
lick
Chief?
suck
lick
I don't have any experience with sex!
This is the first time a girl has ever sucked my dick!
Don't push yourself too hard...
You really think I'm pushing myself too hard?
Don't make me kill you.
Just shut up and cum
with your big dumb cock already.
Chief, I'm gonna...
That hit the spot. See you later.
What the?!
What should I do to help
Rock Bottom stay in business?
Maybe I should start with the magazine's poster girl,
Hayabe Aruru, AKA, Ayabe Haruru-san.
Her drawings and plots aren't bad,
but her manga lacks presence, delicacy and sexiness.
Her work has that feeling of
a goody-two shoes. It feels too clean.
That definitely won't sell too well.
Then there's the girl I scouted at an event,
Shimshima Nekoto, AKA, Ichikura Miyu-chan.
Her work doesn't have nearly enough impact.
And then there's Otohime Lala,
AKA, Odagiri Kaori-san.
She used to draw regular manga for
another magazine, so she has the basics down,
but she falls totally short when
it comes to making things sexy.
For now, I really want to focus on these three.
Lastly, there's our operations manager,
Miyahara Nao-san.
She has basically no interest in erotic things,
so she hasn't been doing too well promoting our magazine.
Ayato
Haruru
Ichikura
Miu
Miyahara
Nao
Odagire
Kaori
Who will you choose?
Yeah, I should definitely start with our poster girl
today since she's the face of our magazine.
So my manga really is bad, huh?
No, it's not bad at all.
You can be honest with me, Okazaki-san.
Well, this is really lacking in erotic elements.
How do you want to proceed, Ayabe-san?
Well, you see,
I... I realty want to draw ero-manga.
Until now, I've been studying ero manga by myself
and then using images I think of myself to use in my manga.
Consequently, I just transmit
my inexperienced visions onto the paper.
But no matter how much I think about it,
I can't figure out how I can overcome this problem.
Urn, Okazaki-san, would you be willing
to use my body to show me how real sex works?
My body's so hot! These...
These small things are making me so hot!
Let's put on the finishing touches, then.
It's so strong! My clitoris!
No, stop! Please stop!
It's coming... It's coming, it's coming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Wow, you're so sexy. I'm sorry to say,
but you're more erotic than your manga is.
Okay then, let's set up her lecture days like this.
Were going to go down the stairs,
so please watch your step.
Okay. Let's go down slowly.
I think I hear something.
You're sure no one else is around, right?
Yeah, right now there's no-one around,
but if you don't hurry...
I'll hurry up then.
Editorial Department Meeting Room
Are you okay?
Don't overdo it.
I'm fine. In order to understand males...
to understand the cum of men better,
I need to taste your cum.
Otherwise I won't be able to draw it.
I think I might cum soon.
Please, right now, don't hold anything
back and cover me with your cum.
Just cum. Please cum.
suck
squeeze
Please let out your cum from your big, hard dick!
slurp
suck
drool
I'm cumming!
Your work is constantly improving month-on-month.
You really mean it?
I think we can go ahead with this chapter.
But...
But?
She still needs to learn how to draw sex scenes.
But I can't have sex with her
for work reasons alone.
Yes, you have a point.
I realize that something is still lacking.
So, I thought that maybe this time,
I could bring something to the table.
Would you mind using this?
Rope?!
I've been wanting to try this.
Take this!
It's all in my hair!
Suck it! Suck it good!
Here comes another one!
You came so much, but your dick is still so hard.
Why are you stopping already?!
W-Well that's because...
Why can't you take a hint?
Haven't I already set everything up for you already?
Better brace yourself.
I'm gonna make your womanhood into a mess.
Please, don't!
I'm sorry...
Dummy.
Don't rub it, it's making sounds!
You're so fucking wet. Here I go.
So I guess the first time really does hurt?
I'm gonna make your pussy feel good in no time.
So this is... This is sex?
Hey, so how is it?
My cock feels good, doesn't it?
No, not at all! It still hurts!
Don't thrust your dick
in and out of me like that!
This is my first time...
My first time is here in this office?
And it's with this guy fucking me!
Oh? So you really do feel good, don't you?
I might be...
But your dick is...
It's stirring up every last corner of my pussy and it's
making me feel good in places I didn't even know I had!
Your pussy feels really good for me too, Haruru-san!
Your dick! I really like your dick, Okazaki-san!
I love how your thick cock is throbbing
so hard and going so deep inside me!
Haruru-san! Haruru-san!
I feel like I'm melting!
I don't know what's wrong with me!
I'm about to cum!
Please, cum like this!
I want to take your big explosion inside me!
Fill me to the brim!
That's how I want my first time to be!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My first time having sex is with us
doing it like beasts, like animals!
It feels so good!
It feels so good! I'm so happy! I love this!
I can't hold on, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum a lot!
I'm really going to cum! I'm really going to!
I'm cumming! Wow, there's so much!
I don't think I'll be able
to get any work done today.
That's fine. First thing tomorrow,
you'll get right to it.
Yes.
Ero-manga!
Yeah, I really don't get this stuff at all.
Like, I can't really understand the characters.
Maybe it's more that I just want
to see for myself what gets guys off!
What?!
Wow, so this is what's under the hood.
I feel like it's bigger in manga though...
It's not fully erect yet.
Okay then, please get it fully erect ASAP.
It should be arousing to
jack off in front of a girl, but...
Looks like it's a lot of trouble.
Oh, I know! Wouldn't it help if a girl
started talking dirty to you?
Yeah, I guess...
"Hehehe, what's the matter? You're pointing your
hard dick at me like you want to put it inside me."
"Sorry, but you can't. I'm going to have you hold back
and make that pent-up cum inside your balls even thicker!"
"After you do that, I might consider letting you shoot all of that sperm
from your swelling balls into my womb through your thick, hard dick."
The lines themselves are erotic,
but she's butchering them so badly!
I've got an idea. This'll do the trick.
I'm gonna cum all over her face!
Okay, that's enough.
Just get close and look at it.
No problem at all.
W-Wait a sec...
This stuff is so hot, huh?
I didn't think it'd shoot out like that!
Welcome back!
Nao-san, what are you doing here?
Isn't that obvious?
I'm here to deepen my knowledge about dicks.
It's already getting hard!
Pardon the intrusion!
Something wrong?
Well the girls in the comics always suck
these things like they're candy or something.
Yeah, they do...
But it doesn't taste good and it kind of stinks.
Maybe that's because you just
aren't trying hard enough?
Even though I'm being this aggressive?
Yeah, you're definitely not trying hard enough.
I can't believe they want their junk
in a girl's mouth! Guys are so perverted!
Oh, shit! I think the Chief is waking up!
Hey! Wait, Miyahara-san...
Everything going fine?
What are you up to now?
Yeah, right now I'm going over the surveys
and polls from the readers. Ugh...
Ugh? What's the matter?
Nothing at all!
Need some help?
N-No, I'm f-fine.
I'm just about to head out.
But wouldn't you be able
to go home sooner if I helped?
Dick... Dick...
I think I'm just about done, so I'm okay.
Really? Okay, I'm going home then. See you later.
Yes, see you tomorrow.
What is it?
This big, hard dick!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! Cumming!
Your cum is...
How'd you like it? That's what cum is.
Let's move on to the next stage!
Next stage?
Oh, come on. You know I mean sex!
Um... are you being serious?
Of course I am! There's no faster way
to learn about sex than to do it!
If I say no, I'd just be embarrassing her...
I'm sorry, Haruru-san!
Okay, here I go.
Yeah, do it!
I'm getting kinda nervous.
Oww!
Are you okay?
Please take it out! I've been duped by ero-manga.
They make it look like it feels so good, but it really hurts!
No, the girls in the manga were
putting up with the excruciating pain!
Actually, don't take it out.
I'll see this through until the end!
This... This is a breeze!
If you really claim that sex feels good,
then make me feel good, Okazaki-san!
No problem.
Is she getting wet?
I think it's starting to hurt less than before.
Does it feel good, Okazaki-san?
Y-Yeah...
This girl's an idiot, but she's so cute!
My boobs are bouncing around like crazy
every time your dick moves inside me!
Good work...
Okazaki-san, please don't stop!
Goodbye.
The next day, we learned that Haruru-san
wished to cancel her serialization in the magazine
via a single fax message she sent.
She disconnected her phone, moved out of her apartment,
and so we had no means of contacting her.
Losing our poster girl really hurt Rock Bottom
and we started seeing a huge drop in sales.
And then a few months later...
Well, I guess this is the end.
We had a good run.
And with those words,
Rock Bottom closed its doors.
bad end
replay
"Hehehe, what's the matter? You're pointing your
hard dick at me like you want to put it inside me."
"Sorry, but you can't. I'm going to have you hold back
and make that pent-up cum inside your balls even thicker!"
I've got an idea.
I'm gonna cum all over her face!
Meow!
Welcome back!
Nao-san, what are you doing here?
Isn't that obvious?
I'm here to deepen my knowledge about dicks.
How's it going?
What... are you doing?
Well, that's...
Oh, well, I dropped my contact lens.
Please pardon my intrusion,
Okazaki-san. I'll be off!
So, do you want me to look over your draft?
Y-Yes...
Haruru-san's skill grew,
drawing in even more devoted fans.
Even so, she was worried about
the fans she lost by her change in style.
I'm pretty sure the draft
you showed me is ready to be published.
No, please let me review it some more.
Got it.
Her quality has improved,
but the eroticism hasn't so much.
It's seemed to have
a reverse effect on her fans.
Could you wait here for a second?
Something wrong?
What's taking her so long?
H-Haruru-san?
What are you doing?!
Haruru? Who's that?
Forget about that,
wanna do some fun things with me?
Is this some kind of act for the manga?
Look at how big you've gotten.
Let's feel good together.
You little slut!
Just watch!
Please give me your dick.
This time, put it in my other dirty hole.
It's so hot! Your big, hot, thick, dick
is throbbing and going so deep inside me!
It's going so deep!
The feeling of it being thrust
in and out of me is amazing!
We might be found out,
but I'm only getting more and more turned on!
She got even tighter!
Cum in my ass!
Melt my ass with your hot cum like it's my pussy!
It's coming, it's coming!
I don't know what's going on anymore!
You have to keep going until
your dick has nothing left in it!
So good! It feels so good!
It's so hot! I'm covered in cum!
I'm gonna cum!
This may be for the manga,
but this is kinda...
Look, people are watching through
the glass and the camera!
I'm being watched! People are watching me
get off from these big, hard dicks.
Yeah, show them that cute face
of yours filled with depravity and lust!
I love it! I like it when they look at me!
Look at me! Look at how dirty and shameless I am!
I'm gonna pump this pussy full of my cum now!
No, please, don't cum inside!
It's coming inside! Your dick exploded in my pussy
and now your seed is pouring inside me!
It's heavenly! I can feel it pulsing inside me!
I love it so much! It's just amazing!
Okazaki-san, we have a problem! A big problem!
I'm a bit busy right now...
Just take a look at this.
"Hayabe Aruru is a plagiarist!
That's the only reason she sells?"
A lot of letters like these have been
coming to the editorial department.
This is it!
A site for anyone against the vulgar
ero-manga artist, Hayabe Aruru.
Haruru-san? Haruru-san, please open the door!
Please, stop. You're bothering my neighbors.
Kazuya-san, I can't draw manga anymore.
I just don't know what to do now.
I brought surveys.
There's hate mail and other fan letters.
Why'd you bring them?
It's so that you can decide what to do next.
I like your current manga style.
The difference between me and them
is how much we liked your previous and current style.
I want you to read these letters, get a feel for
what your readers want, and get back on track!
These postcards are to get you started.
After that, it's all up to you.
Up to me?
I'm going back to the office,
I still have some work left.
One week. If she doesn't come back
in one week, you need to give up on her.
That week's almost up.
Good morning!
I've decided to keep drawing
ero-manga from now on.
Haruru-san!
I won't falter anymore.
I want to draw ero-manga!
H-Hey, Haruru-san!
half a year later
Here it is.
It's Ayabe Haruru's first manga volume.
There are so many pre-orders,
Nao-san's having trouble keeping up.
You wanna sit on a bench or something?
How about we sit over there
if you don't mind?
Kazuya-san, a lot's happened, hasn't it?
Yeah.
Actually, there's something I need to do.
What is it?
Yes.
It's something I decided I'd do if my
manga volume was well-received by the fans.
Half a year ago,
I felt like it was impossible to regain my fans' trust
after they all began saying that I'd betrayed them,
when I thought I was actually making them happy...
You helped me through that.
You believed in me as a manga artist.
That's why on that day,
I yelled out that I wanted to draw ero-manga.
I said the same thing the day I met you.
The only reason I was able to
come this far is because of you.
Thank you very much for really,
truly caring about me until now.
"Until now?" That makes it sound like
I'm gonna stop caring about you.
We're going to keep making
ero-manga together, forever.
Yes, you're right.
By the way, about my pen name...
Wh-What about it?
I was planning on having
my last name changed.
Wait, does that mean...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: fyurie
quality control: fyurie