In tough times sad times, fun times and happy times,
ero-manga has always been by my side.
I, Okazaki Kazuya, love reading era-manga.
Just as I was about to stop doing that, I saw a job notice
for an editor's position at an ero-manga company.
I read this magazine!
But...
I was introduced to Miyahara Nao-san, the CEO,
who had no motivation, and barely understood ero-manga.
There was also her sole assistant, Fujita-san.
But then, Fujita-san was headhunted to be
an editor for the top-tier Kami Magazine.
Because of that, I was hired even
though I had no prior experience.
Over the summer, Fujita-san helped me to
gradually learn how to do my job as an editor,
and then he left.
From now on, the only one I can depend on is myself.
But this might be a great opportunity for me to make
my ideal ero-manga magazine with my own two hands!
This is the start of my path to making
Rock Bottom the best in the industry!
So now to figure out what to do to save
this magazine from going out of business...
Maybe I should start with the magazine's poster girl,
Hayabe Aruru, AKA, Ayabe Haruru-san.
Her drawings and plots aren't bad, but her manga
lacks presence, delicacy, and sexiness.
Her work has that feeling of
a goody-two shoes. It feels too clean.
That definitely won't sell too well.
Then there's the girl I scouted at an event,
Shimashina Nekoto, AKA, Ichikura Miu-chan.
Her work doesn't have nearly enough impact either.
And then there's Otohime Lala,
AKA, Odagiri Kaori-san.
She used to draw regular manga for
another magazine, so she has the basics down,
but she falls totally short when
it comes to making things sexy.
For now, I really want to focus on these three.
Actually, there's also our operations
manager, Miyahara Nao-san.
She has basically no interest in erotic things,
so she hasn't been doing too well promoting our magazine.
Ayabe
Haruru
Ichikura
Miu
Miyahara
Nao
Odagire
Kaori
Who will you choose?
I'm...
Who do I choose?
Okay, let's start with the one who
has the basics down, Odagiri Kaori.
She definitely looks the part of
a manga artist, but not really an ero one.
She looks more like a
married woman or something.
She's single, though, if I remember correctly...
Drawing Ears, Bloomers, and Naked Apron <3
Odagiri Kaori's Delicious Eating Methods <3 Arc
EROMANGA! STEP UP THE H AND MANGA!
I see. You're very capable as far as raw talent goes,
but you still lack that ero feel to your work.
Just as I thought...
Also, your depiction of the ero scenes are very weak.
Yes... Yes... You're right...
So, with that said, let's try to fix up
the errors in the art this month.
Yes. Thank you for your help.
I believe you're having trouble drawing the guys,
so I think it might be easier if you just
used a real life one as an example.
A real life one?
Fortunately for you, we have reference materials.
I know that.
If I remember correctly,
there were real vibrators here...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Hey, wait...
Oh my. Goodness gracious.
I can't tell her that she misunderstood me now, can I?
Oh, I see. This is quite difficult.
It's kind of like the shape of a mushroom
or an inlet of water, or just one big muscle.
Oh, something came out of the tip. It's getting so wet.
You're doing great. Just like that.
Sorry, Okazaki-san. I'll make sure that
I'm able to draw your dick perfectly!
Great, but I'm getting really close to cumming!
Watch closely.
Yes. I'll burn this real life example into my memory.
Your dick is going crazy.
It's so hot! There's so much thick stuff all over me!
It's getting in my mouth!
Yeah, she's totally like an older, married woman.
She's really cute though.
This feels really good.
I can understand why that porn actress looks so happy.
This is what ero is.
It's all about getting aroused,
releasing your lust,
being very physical with each other,
and feeling good together!
Yes, I completely understand.
This is what it means to have sex.
This is what it means to do something dirty.
This is what it means to feel pleasure, right?
I can feel something inside of me. That something
feels good. It's welling up and getting ready to explode!
Yeah, me too!
Your dick! Your dick let out
so much hot stuff! I'm going to cum!
Come on, Odagiri-san,
you're not masturbating properly.
Sorry.
Odagiri-san, masturbating and sucking on a guy's
dick shouldn't take two parts of your brain to do.
It should just be one smooth action in your mind.
It should?
Pleasuring yourself while trying to pleasure
your partner should be done simultaneously.
I want to feel good.
I want to make you feel good, too!
I think I understand now! I'll do my best!
Just like this! I'm gonna...
I can feel it! I feel so good!
More! More! I want to feel more!
I want you to feel more!
Please, let your dick unload its juices into my mouth!
It feels so good!
I can feel it! I'm about to cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I think I need to actually do it.
You know, have real sex.
But even if it's for work, I'm against
you having sex just for the sake of it.
If you're trying to sacrifice yourself for the sake
of ero-manga, I definitely can't let you do that.
Thank you. I don't want my
first time to be for that sake either.
After everything you just told me,
I'm sure that you're the one.
Um, so, will you let me do it now?
Well, I... Yes!
Here I go.
Okay.
Wh-What is this?
Does it hurt?
Yes, it hurt at first, but doesn't
this just feel really, really amazing?
What? Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
Could you move around more?
If that's the case, then I'll give it my all.
So this... this is sex?
Your dick is moving inside me.
The sensation of your dick
stirring up my insides is sex, right?
This feels so good! I can't stop moving my hips!
I'm so happy. Your dick is treating me like a woman.
Please use me as you wish!
Um, Odagiri-san, I'm about to cum!
Me too! I can't believe that your dick is making me
feel so good that I'm already about to cum!
Please cum inside me!
I'm cumming!
So this is semen?! This is what it feels like
to have someone cum inside you?
It's overflowing! There's so much
of it that it's flooding out of my pussy!
Odagiri-san, this is great. You just keep on
getting better at drawing ero scenes.
Thank you. It's all thanks to
everything you've taught me.
The only thing lacking in your manga
now is variety in your scenes.
Right now, you are a housewife
who is filled to the brim with lust.
And I'm a twenty year old college student
who's always admired you, but gave up
on you after finding out that you got married.
I want you to seduce me with your womanly charms.
Kazuya-kun?
Y-Yes?
There's something I wanted to show you. Come in here.
Wha... How? Why?!
Is it really that hard to figure out
why I'm dressed like this?
Why you're dressed like that...
Am I doing this right, Okazaki-san?
If I'm doing anything wrong, just let me know.
Y-Yeah, you're doing great.
But try using dirtier words
that would make any guy horny.
Look at me, Kazuya-kun. Can you see my pussy?
Don't look away.
My body is reaching it's limits, it's so hot right now!
You can see the juices coming out already, can't you?
W-Wow. Even though nothing's
touching it, your pussy is twitching.
I can't get enough of you looking at me.
It's getting me so hot and horny!
Kaori-san, I...
I'm sorry, Kaori-san!
Your big, hot, young dick is entering inside me!
This is all because you tempted me without
even thinking about the consequences. Over there!
No!
This is exactly what I wanted.
The dick I always wanted is finally inside of me!
No! I'm getting turned inside out!
Your dick is so intense!
Give me more! Do me harder!
Hit me with all of your feelings and your lust!
It feels so good!
My body feels so good inside and outside!
I'm about to cum!
Do it! Cum inside me all you want!
Ero Manga! Stepping Up both Sex and Manga.
Odagiri-san, let's try increasing
the diversity in characters this month.
Okazaki-sensei...
What's up, Odagiri?
Why'd you call me out here?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Isn't it obvious? No matter what I did,
I never could get you to look my way.
S-Stop fooling around and close your legs.
I'll not fooling around!
I really want to, have sex with you, sensei!
I'm not a child anymore.
I want you so bad.
I want you to pour your semen
into this dripping wet pussy of mine.
I understand.
Finally! Sensei's dick is finally in me!
I can hear it making weird noises inside me!
It's so intense! It's amazing!
It feels so good!
I've never felt this good before!
It's going so deep inside me! It feels so good!
I can feel it reaching into my womb!
You're doing me so hard!
You owe me money,
so I can do whatever I want to you, right?
It's entering inside me!
Your big thing is entering inside me!
You're the one who said I could, little girl.
My butt! My butt!
I-I can't stop it! It feels so different than when I do it alone!
So you play with your ass, do you?
I just wanted to try it, but before I knew it...
Please fuck me harder!
Fuck me with everything you have!
Pleasing Master is Meow's dyuuty.
I need to try harder.
Oh my god, your tongue is going in and out of me.
It's really stimulating my clitoris! It feels so good!
Hey, what's your mouth doing? It's not sucking,
is it? What happened to you servicing me?
Yes, right away.
Nya! Nya! Nya! It feels so good! I can't stop!
Good, 'cuz I'm not stopping
until your face is filled with ecstasy.
N-Nyoo way!
This feels so amazing!
I can't hear whatever you're trying to say,
but don't worry, I know that you've
wanted to do this for a long time now.
You don't have to lie. I'll keep you with me forever.
Look, onee-chan, both your mouth on your head
and your mouth down here are squealing with pleasure.
You must've really wanted this too!
N-No! Stop! You don't have to do this!
I'll always be on your side!
You will? I'll make your body into one
that can never lie to me again!
I'll make you feel pleasure like this every day!
N-No! Don't!
You don't have to do anything anymore.
Just feel good whenever I touch you.
It feels so good! Your dick is making
such a mess of my pussy! It's amazing!
Wow, onee-chan, I can't believe your pussy makes
so much noise whenever I move my dick inside it!
No, stop! This is too intense!
I'm going to lose my mind!
You're being too rough!
You're making great progress.
Your manga's eroticism is improving so much.
You're slowly moving up the rankings of the readers.
So what should we work on this week?
I'm thinking about doing it by myself this month.
By yourself?
From now on, please let me make the
rough draft, no, the script too, by myself.
Was I just being full of myself
when I thought that she needed me?
That was a pretty big sigh.
Something bothering you?
Shiraishi-san?
You look like you're shouldering
the weight of the world.
You wanna have our own drinking party here?
I bet you'll feel better!
Kaori-san is the one who said she wanted to
work alone. She's the one who rejected me first.
So...
Yeah, sure. I'm in.
I was of use to someone.
She was happy with the help I gave her, but...
Sorry for ruining the mood.
Hey, sit over here.
Your dick is so hard.
I can tell that you're aroused.
Can you tell how horny I'm getting?
Well, don't just look. Use that dick
of yours to fuck me! Drill a hole into me!
Oh my god! You're stretching my pussy so wide!
All we need to do is just go crazy,
have sex with each other, and forget about everything else!
It's so good! It's going so far in!
I can feel it reaching into the depths of my womb!
N-No! Calm down!
If you do it that hard, I'm going to lose it!
Oh, no! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Odagiri-san?
Did you just have sex with Shiraishi-san?
W-Well...
I don't think I can draw anymore... Goodbye!
Odagiri-san!
After that day, I was never able to contact her again.
She was never at home
and she changed her phone number.
It's all my fault. I hurt her. I emotionally scarred her.
When did I start to not like ero-manga?
This job is one that you have to enjoy to survive at.
Rock Bottom closed its doors soon after.
Even though I knew that beforehand,
I felt no emotion whatsoever.
BAD END
REPLAY
Was I just being full of myself
when I thought that she needed me?
That was a pretty big sigh.
Something bothering you?
Shiraishi-san?
You look like you're shouldering
the weight of the world.
You wanna have our own drinking party here?
I bet you'll feel better!
Kaori-san is working by herself now.
I bet even right now,
she's working hard to fix her script.
Thanks for the offer, but I'll pass.
I still have work left to do.
Really? That's too bad.
Call me if you ever feel lonely, okay?
Odagiri-san? What are you
doing here so late at night?
I'm sorry I'm late. Here's the script for this month.
I wanted to give it to you as soon as possible.
Okay, here goes.
Wow, this is great!
This is your best work yet!
But why do you think this script has problems?
This script is just a manifestation of my frustrations.
Huh?
I need you and I want to support you from now on.
Kazuya-san, I'm in love with you.
More than anyone in the world.
Your dick is entering inside me!
I can feel it pushing its way in! It's rubbing against me!
It's because I want you so bad! I can't help myself!
Your dick! I want your dick!
I need your dick! It feels so good!
Touch me more! Taste more of me!
Your dick! It feels so good!
Your dick feels amazing! I'm in ecstasy!
I love it when you touch my boobs!
I wish you could touch them all day!
I love the taste of you.
Let me taste more!
So intense! It's too much to handle!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I love it when your hot milk shoots out
inside me and splatters all over my womb!
It keeps hitting all of my sensitive spots!
No person under the age of 18 or high school students allowed in this shop.
This, that... Oh that too.
Oh and this... And also...
Please give me an eggplant,
a cucumber, and this really big goya.
She's not going to use them
for anything kinky is she?
Now we're set for tonight!
What's the matter?
Your face is saying that this isn't enough.
Don't worry, it'll feel good soon.
If even one of these things comes out,
I'm going to punish you.
This is amazing! Like, really amazing!
You could aim for the top of the charts with this!
Are you serious?
Why would I lie to you?
Well, that's because I mixed more elements from
different areas than I usually do, so it's difficult to be objective.
Well, then I'm not too objective, either.
Why's that?
Well that's 'cuz...
The guy who keeps raping this housewife
all day is obviously me and the housewife is you.
It's great that she's not embarrassed
by the characters doing sexual things anymore,
but now we're just back to square one.
Well, I guess it's more embarrassing to know that
your entire audience is getting off to your fantasies.
By the way, were those your
only thoughts on the manga?
Tell me anything,
no matter how trivial it may seem.
Well...
I wonder if she really wants me to point out
that the characters were based off of me and her.
Kazuya-san, you're such a meanie.
It's not too fun to be blatantly
influenced to answer a certain way.
Geez.
I told you, didn't I? Every time I draw anything perverted,
I have to hold back my desire to have sex with you.
Yeah, you did.
The script was supposed to be a message of hope.
Hoping that we can do that sometime in the near future.
What?
Being this kind of ero-manga artist isn't bad, right?
I just thought of another idea.
Do you mind waiting for me to make a memo of it?
Yeah, take your time.
Sorry for the wait.
Kaori-san?
I love you, Kazuya-san!
I look forward to working with you from now on.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: fyurie
quality control: fyurie