Previously on Ero Konbini Tenchou.
hanime.tv
Presents
This view makes me so nostalgic.
That time, it was our first time, and I did it
without realizing you were unconscious.
Hey old guy! Over here!
What!?
Yoshihiro, lick.
Wha...!
Sto...!
You fucking bitch!
You trash, where do you think you're licking?
I said stop it, you idiot, dumbass!
That's my asshole!
Stop it, it's dirty!
I know you're feeling it.
Trash, fatass!
Stop making stuff up!
Stop already!
I hope you become homeless after this place goes under!
You're on the same boat.
Am I right?
Fucking fatass...
Stop it already, it feels disgusting...
I'll play along this time, but there won't be a next time.
Yui! You were watching the entire time!?
You're shameless!
It doesn't seem like Mom knows that we've been fucked as well.
This will keep him satisfied in the meantime.
Yui, you scare me...
What happened last time was just in the mood and I...
Sorry, she doesn't go that way.
She's a perv who's only interested in girls.
Um... I'm gonna...
Sorry for bothering you!
Shii, this feels so nice while being fucked...
If you slim down, that'll make me happy too, so why not.
You'll eventually get some disease
at this rate and bite the dust early.
You seriously gotta get on a diet.
You get to fuck however much and
wherever you want if you succeed.
Get to fuck Shii that is.
Yui! Don't go making weird promises!
So good!
Do it for me!
Another one ran away?
What a pain in the ass.
That means I have to do everything, starting with deliveries.
Hmm... The next one will be fine. Are you sure?
Okay, I look forward to it then.
Talk to you later!
Welcome.
On the morning shift today?
Where's the manager?
He's a bit under the weather, so he's out for a while.
Welcome.
I'm Shimoda, the new manager.
The backdoor was closed, so...
Ugh, this one doesn't look fine at all...
I'm the part-timer, Kusunose Miki.
I look forward to working with you.
Gotta make a good first impression.
Same here.
But we'll only be working together for a month anyways.
I'm the manager at a different branch.
I see, just a filler.
You don't look that capable even though you're a manager.
Thank you very much.
Just look at her go...
Kusunose, may I have a moment?
Everything, even orders, is fine.
Everyone keeps running away so I did their functions as well.
It must have been hard.
I'm used to it.
I'll teach you the ways while I'm here.
You've only started about half a year ago,
you must have made some mistakes.
I don't make mistakes.
Welcome...
That'll be 321 yen.
Um... I'll hit you up later.
I'll be waiting. Keep it up.
Can I help you?
Boyfriend?
It's none of your business...
Manager, here's the daily report for today.
Good work.
Also...
Hm?
I put down all the times you sexually harassed me too.
The report will be going to headquarters.
Sexual harassment?!
Me?!
Are you going to play dumb?
You're the worst for abusing your authority just because I'm cute.
H-hold on...
It's late too, so why not talk about this tomorrow?
Just to let you know,
I won't just let you settle this with money!
I'm just helping and she accuses me of sexual harassment...
That fucking bitch...
I was just instructing you on how to interact with customers...
How self-conscious can you be... Get over yourself.
Fucking crap...
Hello.
Yeah, I just started...
Wha... No, there's a misunderstanding going on.
Of course. I'll get things straightened out immediately.
Heheh... This will be one fun month...
I got contacted by headquarter about sexual harassment.
I told you let's talk about it today.
How could you just ignore me and do that?
I knew you'd just cover it up anyways.
Guess words won't work...
Let's talk about this peacefully in my office after you're done.
How about you not sexually harass me in the first place, pervert.
Hmph, he's no different than all the other managers.
Disgusting.
Pardon the intrusion.
I read your report,
but I think you're just being too self-conscious.
What a handy excuse.
God, men are such scum.
What about you? You were having a
private conversation with your boyfriend or whatever that time.
Th-that was just me interacting with a customer...
It's against the rules.
Before you go running around accusing people of sexual
harassment, make sure you're doing your job first.
I see.
So that's how you plan on sweeping this under the rug.
I'm not going to let that happen.
Trying to make things hard?
That's you right now!
I'll let you off now if you just write an apology letter.
Wha... I can't believe you're going to
perform power harassment as well...
How off can you be.
What are you doing?! This is sexual harassment!
My sexual harassment is on a whole other level...
What the hell are you saying...
You're hurting me! Stop touching me!
No... stop it...
Stop shouting.
Write the apology letter if you don't want things to escalate.
Understood.
I'll write one...
I just have to write it here right...
Make sure to write that it was just your misunderstanding.
What are you...?! This isn't the changing room!
Just in case you try to run away.
Just keep writing.
Why am I, the victim, being forced to do this...
What the hell are you doing!?
I change all the way down to my undies.
Even so...!
Not gonna write it?
Then it's time to get serious then.
You don't have to! I'll write it...
What is that...
That's a man's...
It's bigger than Dad's...
It can get harder than that...
What the hell am I writing...
That thing is near me...
This will end sooner if I read it with you.
Come on, write.
It's so red and dark and grotesque looking...
How can that even be...
What's with it?
It's different than before...
God damn...
Wh-what are you...! What are you doing?!
No, let go!
Don't mind me. Keep writing.
Stop playing around!
This isn't what we agreed to!
No, let go!
No!
Where do you think you're touching...
Sto... That spot is... stop it!
Are you wet down here from sweating?
Or could it be...
Hm, yours smells.
What? How rude!
It definitely smells.
Look at you with your cute face...
No, stop it... you pervert!
Stop it! Idiot! Scum! Don't come near m...
It must be embarrassing when you
call yourself cute and yet you have a dank ass pussy.
That's not true!
You're just weird!
My pussy isn't...
Then let me confirm it then.
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
No, don't sniff it...
Heheh... I was right.
How pitiful that you don't even realize it.
No, there's now way that's true...
I make sure to keep it clean all the time...
You can't tell your own scent anyways.
I'll plug your dank pussy with my dick.
Wha... Wait, no! Please sto...
It hurts...
It's going inside me...
My pussy is getting rubbed inside by his dick...
It's not that wet yet, but deal with it.
I'm sure the juices will start flowing soon.
No!
Why is this...
This has to be a dream...
Everyone sexually harasses you because you're so cute, right?
You had it coming.
This isn't sexual harassment...
It's just rape!
You freaking liar!
You're one to call me a liar...
Don't tell me you're going to cum inside...
That'll make me pregnant.
No, no, no!
No, seriously you can't!
No...!
I can feel your cum inside me...
I'm pregnant now...
As if you'd get pregnant that easily.
This'll do it for sure though.
Stop it...
You can't be going again...
If you put it in with cum already inside...
No... stop it...
This will get the cum where it needs to go.
This is just inhumane!
You brute, ogre, demon!
Very nice, keep crying.
It makes your pussy nice and tight.
What, finished already. What a party-popper.
Let me finish too then.
No, no... Don't tell me you're going to cum again!
You're joking... Stop it...!
I'll really get pregnant!
You're cumming again...
So much inside...
Why did this happen to me...
It's not sexual harassment.
There just happened to be a hole.
You're terrible...
You're lying. You assaulted me because me I'm cute!
If you're gonna cry just stop being so self-conscious.
What!? Why!?
No... It's getting big again...
It's inside me...
No... forgive me already...
This is his dick...
He's putting it in my mouth...
No... what is this...
It's disgusting. It smells! No...
I was made into a woman here yesterday.
By that guy's big dick...
I'll take a picture for the occasion...
What do you want?
Are you just gonna peep like that!?
I'm just greeting you before work.
Morning.
G-good morning...
Not! I'm changing!
Get out!
Even if you say that,
I can't stand at the register like this.
I can't believe I'm being forced to do this...
I'll never forgive you...
Whatever rocks your boat, but make sure to make me cum.
You trash... you're lower than an insect...
So much...
It's so disgusting...
Well done. Now time for work.
Give me my skirt back!
You should hurry up.
Oh you were cleaning.
Hi, I was just about to be done.
Then if you don't mind.
Of course, go right ahe...
S-stop it, he's going to find out...
Please...
So even you're scared of getting busted.
Anyone would be...
No, please...!
He's going to come out soon...
Even more than the reason then.
It's inside me...
Oh, you're still here.
Yeah... I still have some tidying up to do...
Did you give some thought to what I said last time?
Yeah... I might be able to the next time I have a break...
His hard dick is going all the way inside...
Can you just wait for a bit longer though?
Got it. But don't make me wait too long.
Of course... sorry...
We'll get busted if you're too rough...!
Looks like someone got aroused.
Your body is getting hot.
That's not true...
This is definitely not...
You're an adult and yet you made me do this in front of him...
You savage!
I'll never forgive you!
Come on, it's morning.
Get ready already.
I'm still sleepy...
Gosh, you called me out of nowhere yesterday too...
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Next time on, Ero Konbini Tenchou.
You idiot...
Yui told me to hurry, so I thought something happened and...
Like hell I was expecting this!
Oh, so you were worried about me. How cute.
Shut the fuck up, you trash!
Pull out already!
If nothing happened then I'm leaving!
You jackass!
He can't do anything to me here.
I have to tell someone...
Just because I'm cute doesn't mean he can just...
Looks like she's guarding herself.
Doing it in the aisle is bad no matter how you look at it.
Don't underestimate the manager...
Hi, the usual.
You're kidding...
Why right now...
Um... It's 390 yen...
Thanks.
Is it okay to chat for a bit?
Sorry... I don't have much free time
anyways so how about later on...
Yeah, you're right.
I'll be waiting for you at the usual place.
It's alright. Take care of yourself.
I will...
What are you doing you perv! Molester! Scum! Trash! Fatass!
What's with this mark.
That's from...
I just peed myself. It's not what you're thinking!
Excuse me!
There it goes again...
No...
Must be from your boyfriend who's waiting in vain.
Are you going to answer while in this situation?
You can't just do this because I'm cute...
You savage! Devil!
Call me whatever you want.
No... it's so deep...
Are you going to cum again...
I don't want to get pregnant...!