My boobs...
They're rubbing your dick and making really dirty noises.
Please give me lots of guidance with your cum!
Yeah, I'm gonna give you lots so make sure you take it all in.
Wow, it has such a strong taste.
In use
Just let your body fall into pleasure.
Let everything go!
But it's so embarrassing!
I want you to pass!
You really care that much about me, sensei?
Good, keep it up. Let people in the store hear you!
Let them hear your dirty climax!
Y-Yes! Give it to me!
I'm gonna cum with your hot dick, sensei!
Sensei... this is so embarrassing.
Beat with it until your shyness disappears.
I'm starting to twitch so badly down there.
Be more specific. Say "my pussy".
Be dirty.
My pussy feels good!
Stick my pussy with your hot dick!
Please mess my insides up!
Sensei, you're the only one who makes my pussy this wet.
Perverted Seminar
The ABC's of Sex and Motivation
Are you Kusukuni Kyoji-kun?
Nice to meet you, I'm Monica.
I never thought that the headmistress Amakamihara
would personally come to me.
So how about it? Wanna take up
the job at our Summer Camp?
And maybe you want to try challenging
yourself to take my virginity as well?
Hull?! Headmistress?!
There don't seem to be any lies
in what you just said. I can tell.
There's no way I can take your virginity in
the short time frame of a single OVA!
Don't start being logical all of a sudden!
You're quite a clever one.
You're exactly right.
I'm not one of the targets this time.
It's quite unfortunate.
Take my apology.
Wait, Headmistress,
you're really coming to this guy to ask
him to teach girls at your prep school
then asking him to have illicit sexual relationships
with them as well as make them all pass?!
That's a crime! It's illegal! You can't do this!
I'm not going to be teaching just girls though.
And I'm sure that you're a virgin just
like the headmistress, aren't you?
Good eyes.
I do recognize that it's a tall order to ask you
to make all two hundred students pass.
But will you still take the job?
Is this...
I think general admittance starts next week.
Are you one of the girls going to the summer camp here?
Wait, does that make you...
I'm Kusukuni Kyoji.
I've been assigned as the instructor
for the courses taught here.
Kusukuni-sensei?
Wait, are you...
What? Do you know me?
W-Well...
Don't be so shy.
I don't force my students to do anything.
If you don't want to be near me, then I won't force you to.
But I'll tell you now that I make
anyone who comes to me pass.
Without fail.
Without fail?
You really are...
The rest is up to you.
I...
The ones I met today were Sagisawa
Karen and Nagaoka Satomi.
And...
This way please.
Hey there, I've been waiting.
You're not hiding too much.
I'm not trying to.
So how about it? Do you want me?
Don't think badly of me.
I just want to let you know that asking you
to take my virginity was a real request.
After saying that yesterday, it's been
non-stop pulsing down here.
I'd just like you to understand my feelings.
So why did you really call me here?
Well you're no fun.
It seems that you've already set your eyes on those three.
You picked the most interesting three girls too.
I'm not surprised.
Surveillance cameras, huh?
Failure has been so common when it's time for
the real deal. We want to see how you teach.
They're the ones who decide if I teach them or not.
That guy's a fool.
There's no sane student who'd
come to him after that speech.
Kusukuni-sensei!
You decided, Narumi Kaede?
Wh-What?! N-No way!
Love, play, sex... These are the three themes of my course.
Especially in regards to the proper progression of sex...
the latent sexual knowledge within
yourselves will be greatly improved!
Failed Students
The only students who should come to me are those who
are serious about getting into the school of their choice.
That's all.
What kind of lessons are you thinking about giving me?
I'm going to have you fall in fake love with me.
Narumi... you're the lost princess, Orihime,
from the seventh of July.
On that one day every year, she was able
to reunite with her love, Hikiboshi.
But her heart would begin to cloud up and she'd
miss her chance to cross the bridge to meet him.
That's what you're like right now.
With me, I'll make it so you can cross
that bridge called an exam
so you can get the ticket to meet Hikiboshi,
the school of your dream.
You just have too much confidence, sensei.
Please allow me a little more time
to get ready for your guidance.
They're all basically perfect scores.
But I can't seem to translate this success to the real thing.
My hands shake.
I start thinking "what should I do if I fail?"
That's where my guidance come in.
Your biggest weakness is your mentality.
I'm going to make you conquer that mentality.
Y-Your face is too close.
Hello, sensei.
Thanks for coming.
Yes, I've made up my mind.
Don't worry. I'm not going to do anything
extreme like what you're thinking of.
I-I'm not thinking of anything extreme!
We're going to kiss today.
And then we're done.
Entrust all of yourself to me.
Loosen up more.
Loosen up the defenses of your body and mind.
Sensei, I... My breathing is...
Sensei, my body feels weird.
Right now, I...
It doesn't seem like you understand
what's going on in your body.
Let's change gears here a bit and try
something a little more drastic.
Kaede, this is a special regimen only for honor students.
Sensei, this is too sudden!
If you keep playing with them like that,
my boobs are going to go numb!
You can't...
You can feel something hitting you down
there, right? Right around your pants.
It's so hard.
It's so big too.
Why?
Why? Seeing you writhe in pleasure
is just so cute, it got like this.
Cute?
That's not...
It's so hot!
It feels so good!
Sensei... My stomach is getting really hot!
It hurts... It hurts, but...
Now that I've taken your virginity, let me promise
that I'll do everything in my power for you.
Your dick is rubbing against me,
it's making my mind go blank!
I'm starting to feel really weird!
Don't be afraid.
Just take it all in.
I won't give you anything but pleasure.
I never knew sex felt so good! I'm so happy!
I'm...
Your dick is really big even in my ass!
Is it too tight?
No, it's perfectly fine.
I'm gonna cum with my ass!
I could really get hooked on this.
I'm gonna become an even dirtier girl.
I'm about to cum again.
Sensei, I love you.
You okay?
Um, sensei? I want to do it one more time.
Okay, Kaede.
Looks like this will go well as usual.
I heard that the mountains were off limits, but
I didn't think it was a spot for celebrities.
Sorry but I'll have to ask that you stay away from this area.
Good work discovering where the camera is.
I shouldn't be surprised considering
you're a person I truly respect.
Only the one who has conquered both
my heart and mind can enter here.
You don't have that right yet.
I like how you understand when to give up too.
Is this seat open?
Oh, Fuyumi?
Go ahead.
Thanks.
This woman was pretty uptight at first, but after
learning about sex, she wound down a lot.
I shouldn't be surprised by the results of the mock exam.
Narumi-san took first place and both Sagisawa-san
and Nagaoka-san are also at the top.
I think the way you are now, you could
give me a run for my money.
I'm sure Monica would be happy about that.
L-Let's not talk about onee-sama right now.
Are you still going to try and take her virginity?
Yeah, we go back home tomorrow.
I don't have much time.
Excuse me.
Need something?
Yes, the Amakamihara owner asked me
to give this to you, Kusukuni-sensei.
A reward for success, huh?
What's happening?
My knees are giving out.
Wait...
That dessert...
I'm really not one of your targets.
But I can't wait any longer.
You already made all the other women wet.
You're such a mean man.
Oh? Looks like you're awake.
I got a good look at how you work.
You did so much better than I expected,
you made my heart flutter.
This is the first time I've felt like this.
You really are special.
I didn't think you had emotions like that.
I'm a woman too, you know?
That's why I wanted to give this a try
and employed such forceful methods.
To see if you're a man who can accept everything about me.
And you passed.
Your mental fortitude is like a fortress.
You'd really make a great addition to the Amakamihara
Prep School. You'd make a great husband for me.
My lady part has just been drooling
hot liquid for a while now.
I can tell that your dick wants to cum.
It's quivering and the tip is twitching.
The tip...
Do it. Cum!
So this is what your cum tastes like?
It really smells.
I'll give you my first time.
Give me your baby tonight.
So that's it, huh?
If I get you pregnant here and become an instructor
here at the Amakamihara Prep School,
the Prep School association would be heavily
favored towards Amakamihara,
and you'd be able to charge even more for classes.
It'll become a system where only paying
students are allowed to be taught.
That's not something I can agree with.
If you keep being this sharp, you're
gonna make it hard to like you.
I told you not to call me unless it's an emergency!
What? Forget it, I'll go by myself to confirm.
Sorry, something came up.
We'll have to postpone this virginity losing
and baby making for another time.
At any rate, I need to do something about this.
Sensei, are you okay?
Hyoudou-sensei saw you being taken away by the headmistress
and found the room by looking at surveillance camera footage.
I see.
So Monica leaving in a hurry like that
was also Fuyumi's doing, huh?
Yes. Probably.
What's the matter?
No, it's just that...
You really are naked.
This might not be the time, but...
Right? Can't we? Give us guidance one more time.
Where is he?
Where'd he go?!
Kusukuni...
Wait, could he be on this island?
Surveillance room, did Kusunoki enter this area?
Yes, he did...
I was careless. He could already be...
That took you a while.
But now it's checkmate.
You awake?
Where is... What are you planning to do to me?
I'll tell you this now, but if you do anything that leaves
even so much as a scratch on me, your life is over.
I'm not going to do anything like that.
In fact, I'm sure you'll be happy with what I'm about to do.
Happy?
This is typically something I take my
time doing, but today's special.
I'm gonna cram my full teaching
course into you in one night.
Fine. I understand that you aren't
happy with my forceful methods.
I'll apologize, so...
Wait, did I... did I cum from just being kissed?
It's the basics of my lesson.
Your body should have loosened up considerably and
now you should understand what that leads to.
Basics? Plural? So you're going to do more?!
Untie me!
Just how long will you be able to act like that?
My next lesson is...
This isn't enough to...
Yeah, but your nipples are rock hard.
I'm Monica from... Amikamihara...
Monica! Amikamihara's...
You monster. You just made me cum.
Now we're up to the most important lesson.
No, stop! My body's melting... My
body's being filled with your dick!
My stomach's going numb!
– No! It feels good!
– Don't worry, your hymen definitely broke.
– Your dick is mixing up my stomach... I'm melting!
– I took your virginity in all aspects of the word.
That's good. Let all reasoning melt away!
Why didn't you give it to me inside?
I mean, why didn't you give it to me inside, sir?
I don't mind doing that.
But first, I need you to promise me a few things.
Promise?
You won't force me to stay at your prep school.
You won't interfere with my lessons.
You won't pull any underhanded
tricks to fulfill your desires.
And lastly, you'll never refuse any request of mine.
That's...
If you can't agree to those terms, we're done here. I'll
untie you and you can just masturbate on your own.
You've made me feel so much, there's no way I can...
Please!
I'll listen to your... I'll listen to any request of yours, Master!
So please make me cum more!
Good answer.
Master, please put it in. Can you put your dick inside me?
Fill my insides with it!
Yeah no problem. As an apology for playing with you so
much, move as you like. Consider it as helping yourself.
I understand. Well then...
I'm sorry for saying that I wasn't a target, Master!
I have a dirty, perverted pussy!
Your dick is already inside me!
Not enough... This isn't enough!
Stronger... Deeper...
I want to make this colossus of a dick ravage me so badly!
I guess I'll start moving then.
Please.
Deep! It's hitting me so deep!
You devoured my dick and now everyone's
waiting for you to cum!
Show off your hard nipples and your no longer virgin pussy!
Make me cum! Please make me cum!
Your dick's so deep! It's hitting so deep!
Cum everything you have!
Everything! Everything! Make me yours, Master!
The summer camp ended without problems and
all my students got into their dream schools.
As for me...
Monica contacted me saying that
she wanted to report something.
I didn't expect to have gotten her pregnant
and be forced into marriage, but
if it's with Monica, I have no regrets.
Since Monica entered maternity leave,
her days were filled with love making.
Seeing her face mixed with shyness
as we made love was very cute.
And also, her body started to lactate just
by imagining married life with me.
Master, are you watching my face as I cum?
Yeah I am.
Sheesh, you do work perfectly, but when it
comes to bed, your face just gets so messy.
You're the one who made me that way, aren't you?
translation: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч