Alright, I'm done!
I'm not doing any more of this stuff for today!
Now then, I'll be going home now.
Momo and Iori, you two should go home as well.
You're right, I think this is enough for today.
Okay then, it's been a while so why don't we all go home together?
You're not going home yet?
You're always going home late, right?
Well, I'm still the newbie here you know.
Newbies should traditionally arrive earliest and go home last.
Oh, that's nice of you then.
You still need to fix that "arrive early" part though.
Well that's...
I guess you're still not going home exactly for that reason.
Okay, just say hi to Nene-chan for me when she gets back.
I understand.
Original Animation Disc
Eroge! The joy of sex and game development
~ We're doing this stuff in front of everyone?! Nene is already a fine lady~ Chapter
It's so late already.
Oh, boss.
It's late, you must be tired.
I see everyone's gone home already.
Yeah, you got here just after they left.
Well that's quite convenient.
Here, how about some drinks?
Mochizuki-kun, let's drink these up quickly.
Actually, I'm extremely in the mood to drink today.
Well, it's true that we can't drink beer when everyone's here.
Something must have happened earlier I suppose.
So, what exactly happened?
Will you listen?
I... I did agree to drink with you.
I don't think I'm really fit for a corporate job.
Crap, she's starting to get drunk.
I guess this really isn't for me, huh.
That's why this formal outfit doesn't even suit me, see?
Even when I tried lots of things during discussions,
everyone looked like they were about to burst out laughing.
No matter how much I try to be serious,
they simply treat me like a child,
and the discussion never progresses as it should.
Well, I guess that was really troublesome.
Reina-chan's especially good at these things by the way.
I could really see her doing well, doing these kinds of things.
With her pushiness and persuasiveness,
she could control the pace any discussion on her own!
What should I do to look more mature?
Please tell me Mochizuki-kun!
uhh...
If it's something to do with the eroge, why don't
we wait until the next trial distributions?
Man, there sure are a lot of people.
Huh? You're the eroge expert and you
haven't even come to this event once?
Sorry about that...
Ki-Kisara-san's cosplay outfit looks really cute!
Well, it's quite hot and I'm already a bit tired so,
I'd like you to work really hard for our game promotion, okay?
Please...
Thank you very much.
Please try our game out!
That costume looks cute.
Th-This costume?
Th-This costume is worn by the characters in the game.
Oh crap.
I totally forgot about the boss.
I'm going to Momo's place, so help the boss out for a while.
Ah, okay.
Boss, sorry I'm late.
I'll help out here so lets do our best together.
Oh Mochizuki-kun, so you finally came.
Yeah, I even wore t-this outfit for today,
so we really need to work hard.
Please check out our booth!
We have leaflets here that you can get!
Here, take this one please.
Also, that'd be only one per person.
Do your best, do you best boss.
N-Now I can finally rest a bit.
Yeah, I think I now have time to do that too.
A-Are you really going to do it?
Really?
Well, I did prepare this just for that you know.
We'll start real soon, so prepare yourself.
U-Umm, please do it gently, okay?
I'm having a hard time with this outfit already you know.
Mochizuki-kun!
Don't turn it on suddenly like that!
Look, we have a customer.
You have to attend to him properly.
Sorry for the wait.
Here's the trial version for our game.
I think we're still okay here.
My pussy...
Something's welling up inside.
Got your pussy wet already?
B-But, it's quite deep inside.
You told me to put it so I just...
This is the t-trial version for our game.
Please enjoy it okay?
Let's play with her ass as well.
My ass...
It feels...
In this position, your skirt perfectly covers you.
So, tell me exactly how you feel.
The finger like thing inside my ass is
trying to wiggle and swirl around,
and can't take it any longer.
I-I'm about to cum with this already.
It's moving and pushing inside like the real thing.
I can’t hold on anymore Mochizuki-kun.
I'm about to cum.
Any more and I'll...
I'll really cum...
Huh? Did it run out of power?
We still have time, it'd be boring if I let you cum too quickly.
Yes, this is Flower, it's nice to meet you.
Please try out our game.
Let's give our cutie here a nice erotic reward.
T-The trial version already includes some of the deeper scenes.
It's contents will surely stimulate your thing...
Mochizuki-kun, please let me cum.
Let my ass and pussy cum already.
Hmm, not yet.
Wait just a bit more.
No way...
We're doing this to get your courage up you know.
You can't just let your sexual pleasures take over you.
I... I understand but...
But I'm already doing this embarrassing cosplay, and this is just...
M-Meanie.
Please don't tease me any longer.
My pussy... My pussy... My ass...!
My asshole, and this dick...!
Thank you v-very much.
This is the last copy.
Thank you very much.
Hey, I've brought the other discs!
I... I can’t take it anymore.
Boss, take it easy for now.
Just leave the rest to Kisara and me.
Please do, sorry about this.
Our trial version copies are now restocked.
One copy per person please.
We're also selling related original items,
so please check them out!
One soundtrack CD,
and two of these shirts!
Thank you very much!
She's faking it.
She's totally faking it.
Really faking it.
I'll be fine here on my own for a while.
Why don't you try to have a look around.
Huh? But I don't exactly know what to find or where I would go.
Here's the change for 500 yen,
thank you very much.
What? You already have me and you're still
putting on a big smile for these guys?
I know, I totally understand.
It's just her way of dealing with people.
But I'm still getting pissed off nonetheless.
Okay I'm free so let's just do it.
Let's tease her a bit.
Ah, you dropped something.
It's okay, I'll pick it up.
She's completely open.
Defenseless!
Thank you very much!
Yes, we'll be releasing a new game around this fall.
Please look forward to it!
Not even the least bit aware.
Kisara-san, you're panties are totally exposed to me!
We really improved on a lot of things this time.
We also worked quite a lot on the sex scenes.
We hope that you enjoy playing it!
She's even acting cute like that.
Normally, she would...
Hmph, you should be thankful that you can buy my goods, you pig.
I'm going to step on you as a reward.
You like being stepped on this embarrassing part?
What are you getting a boner for? You pervert!
As punishment, buy three more of each of our shirt designs!
You already have them?
Oh shut up.
You need extras right?
I'll step on you now,
there, there, there!
She would most likely treat customers like that.
What's wrong? Still can't find it?
Well, I think it went inside a crevice or something.
Jeez, you're in the way so find it quickly, okay?
R-Roger.
You don't have to say it that way you know.
Now I really need to discipline her.
One shirt yes?
Thank you very much.
Slowly, slowly.
Having your pussy exposed in a public place like this,
how slovenly.
Yes, all three badge pins will cost a total of 1000 yen.
It'd be bad if she notices.
But then, it'd be boring if she doesn't.
H-Hey, can't find it yet?
Yeah, I found it,
but it was inside a small gap so...
Sorry, I think it went into a corner.
You're not just after my panties, right?
I've already seen what's in them many times, so what's the point?
Though I still plan on looking at it again later.
W-What are you saying?
Stop saying stupid things and just get to work!
Okay, okay.
Anyway, this sure feels really soft.
This isn't sweat right?
Getting wet just by getting between her legs like this...
How about we expose the faker she is, eh?
One shirt please.
Okay, that would be 1500 yen.
Is something wrong?
N-No, nothing, that would be 1500 yen.
Thank you very much.
O-Our shirt's d-design is original.
We hope that you appreciate it so p-please
take a look at some more.
It's starting to get wetter and wetter.
Never thought it'd get like this by just touching.
Thank you very much.
Hey, w-what are you doing?
That's way more than just looking at my panties!
Well, I don't have anything to do anyway.
There must be something that you can do that's better than this!
S-Stop...!
Do you think it's okay to play with my pussy here?!
Look, there are more customers coming.
Just ignore me and concentrate on serving.
H-Hello there again.
Would you take these? If it's okay with you.
O-Oh extras? Thank you very much.
Th-Then please, take our trial version and a leaflet as well.
Thank you, I'll try to come again.
You did well in resisting your pleasure.
Hey!
I-If you continue do that, I'll really get mad you know?
Continue? Like this?
St-Stop that!
I'll really be mad!
Oh, you won't get mad just from licking?
Then, how about this?
Mo-Mochizuki!
D-Don't insert you finger into my pussy!
Your juices won't stop flowing.
A customer is here again.
Okay, one hugging pillow right?
Thank you very much.
Don’t worry, I'll lick every single drop that comes out of your pussy.
Hey, there are lots of people out here!
You think I'd really let you do that?!
Are you nuts?
Stop, I really won't be able stand anymore.
If you let your voice out like that...
Hey, there's another customer.
Oh, you visited our website?
Thank you very much.
How about I let her cum already?
Hey, your finger's going into, into my...
Look, I got my finger way up inside you ass.
No, no...!
I don't want to cum here!
Oh no, oh no...
Hey!
There's another customer coming!
A-At least do it when nobody else is around.
One soundtrack CD right?
Umm... The soundtrack... how much is it again?
S-Sorry, we're having a bit of trouble with our change,
we don't have enough anymore,
so please just take it.
Th-Thank you very much...
No more...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
My pussy came.
My ass came.
I just keep on cumming...
Kisara-san, I found it!
The 100-yen coin!
Shut up!
What are you doing?
This is for being a stupid pervert monkey!
What the hell were you thinking?
Pervert!
But, your custom maid outfit is just so cute.
What are you saying, stupid!
You expect me to feel h-happy about that?
Stupid!
S-Stop acting violently, you're going to bother the other booths!
You're one to talk!
Sorry, I need to go to the toilet!
I'll be back soon.
Alright, I've escaped somehow.
Iori-san?
This is the men's toilet.
And you're wearing a school swimsuit?!
T-This is bad,
Iori-san, I'm sorry!
Iori-san, weren't you helping out in Momoka-chan's doujinshi?
Well, the number of customers went down after a while,
so I've got nothing to do.
I see, so you were dealing with customers wearing that.
I wanted to have some direct material for my work.
We have this kind of scene in our game, right?
Yeah, I think we have at least one.
So, the part where the image of the
character defecating comes up.
I already had it colored, but it still doesn't look right.
Defecating...? But right now...
I think I can help tomorrow with that.
Actually, I just ran from Kisara-san and
planned to take a short break here.
I never planned to use the toilet.
But you were totally cooperative with the other three.
Ah...
So you were watching...
It's not fair that you're not willing to cooperate with me.
W-Wait... Iori-san?
And there's no better model for my own material than me, right?
I-It's okay for me to just provide instructions, right?
Nope, I need you right here.
Why?
I feel kind of constipated lately.
I want you to help me out.
T-Then...
Then that means "that thing", right...?
Is it okay?
Is it alright?
Here, please hurry up.
Someone might come in.
I guess it's okay with Iori-san?
Then, Iori-san, here I go then.
T-This is...
It feels too tight!
I... I think I can let it out quickly with this.
T-That'd be good and all but...
It will turn out okay... though of course
that still depends on your effort.
I'll do my best.
I... I want you to push your dick deeper inside for this.
Eh? Something's hitting the tip of my dick.
That's my poop of course.
But it doesn't even look like it'll move soon.
That's why I'll widen it up so that it comes out then.
P-Push it in harder.
It's so tight.
Your dick... Your dick is...
It's pushing as if it's trying to stir my insides.
I... I think I'm about to cum.
Yeah, I can really feel it, like it's about to rip my anus apart.
It's stretching my asshole as it pushes deeper.
Your poop is going to be lubricated by my cum.
Then let it out.
Lubricate my poop with your cum.
Make it my asshole's lubricant!
I can feel it.
The hot thing, your cum...
It's filling me inside.
We're done.
How was it, Iori-san?
Something is starting to push down inside my ass.
I'll pull it out then.
I-It's coming out.
It's coming out!
My poop's coming out!
My poop is shaped like a dick!
And this dick is starting to flow out inside me.
I've just had sex to defecate!
This is amazing.
More than just poop, it kind of makes
you think of a very long dildo.
It finally came out.
S-So the big thing finally came out.
Thank you, Mochizuki.
It's okay, I think I can handle this on my own now.
I'm grateful for your cooperation.
D-Don't mention it.
Eroge! I he joy of sex and game development.
I've wasted too much time!
I have to hurry back, or Kisara-san will kill me.
Hey, Tomoya-san!
Tomoya-san, I've been looking for you.
Now, let's go out on a date.
What? What?!
Is it okay to leave Kisara-san alone to attend the booth?
T-There's just a few trial version discs right?
Then, I think it's fine.
You're... right.
Anyway, I want you to concentrate on our date.
Don't you think this is nice?
It looks quite cute.
Cute? But this is...
B-But, there really was something there earlier.
Our date's being ruined by absent-mindedness.
And because of that...
This bad girl needs to be disciplined from both sides!
N-No... Stop...
Not both at once...
My pussy and my ass are both plugged.
They're already pushing into me as I walk.
Then why did you prepare two?
W-Well that's...
Because... Because...
It's a lot better if I use both at the same time, right?
I'm not just going to let myself be done like this you know.
I'm not about t-to lose just to this...
You're voice is clearly trembling.
Then I'll set it higher.
Wait, can't you make it more gradual?
I can't.
You just have one vibe over there.
I'm the one who has the bigger handicap here.
No way...
What are you doing walking that way?
You look really weird you know.
We're on a date, so why don't you try walking faster?
Even if you say that...
Umm, Momoka-chan-sama.
I'm at my limit.
Let me cum already.
You can't just cum with a sex toy.
I want you to give your cum only to me.
Th-Then let's use it already.
I can't endure this any more.
You're dick looks pretty big already.
It's drooling lewdly as it stays stiff.
What a helpless man.
Then, here!
Gimme some of that wet boner of yours.
It looks like it's about to shoot loads of sticky cum.
Now then, I'll put it in.
Your dick feels really thick.
Me too, your wet pussy feels really good.
No, you can't just cum yet.
I still have to enjoy your dick more.
Thanks to you, not just once,
but I came twice with the one inside my pussy,
once with one inside my ass.
And four times with both on!
That's a total of seven times!
As punishment, I won't let go until this
thick dick makes me cum way more.
I really want to do that but,
I-I'm about to cum already,
I don't think I can hold out for long.
Nope.
You need to concentrate while fucking me.
I want to cum.
It really wants to let it all out inside her tender flesh already.
What's wrong? Making such a cute face like that.
Keep that face, and I'll soon feel like teasing you more.
How about I tease you right now already?
Tease this very sticky and lewd dick I mean.
N-Now I feel like teasing you too.
N-No, not my nipples.
I'll feel weak from being too aroused.
Anyway, this dick is really amazing.
I already came lots with the vibrators but,
yours is still thicker, hotter,
and feels way better.
You're gritting your teeth, trying to endure...
Does it feel really good for you dick?
Is my pussy giving you lots of pleasure?
Y-Yeah, I'm actually giving it all just to hold it in.
You can't do that just yet.
I still have this you know.
No, don't turn that on now please!
Why don't you fight back then?
Try switching mine on too.
Okay...
M-My asshole, my anus, its being drilled!
This feels great.
I think I'm about to cum from both sides again.
If you think about it, there wasn't any
use trying to get back it after all!
Fuck me more!
I want you to stir me deeper inside.
Umm... I'm really at my limit now!
Your dick wants to cum inside your own personalized pussy?
I want... I want to cum.
Okay, you can cum then.
This raw and totally concentrated semen,
that's made from this teased and played with dick,
please pour it all inside my pussy!
I-I'm cumming.
There it is,
all of that semen you've built up for me,
it's all coming out.
Oh wow, what is this?
Your dick, your dick....
Your dick...!
Is this real?
Wow...
Recreating the way it is mixed in with semen...
Can I really draw it perfectly like this?
This dick looks big...
It's very thick...
Jeez, how long does that sex maniac plan to stay in the toilet?
I really am going to kill him once he comes back.
Are there still trial version copies left?
It's ok.
we still have some to hand out.
Thank you very much.
Yes, that's right.
We will be releasing a new game this fall.
Please look forward to it.
We really improved on a lot of things this time.
Oh yes, we also worked quite a lot on the sex scenes.