Thanks to your efforts, that was our best selling game!
I want to thank all of you for your hard work.
I'd like for us to go on a trip together,
and gather ideas for the next project.
If you have any places you'd like to go,
please let me know.
What about camping or hiking?
I think going outside would
give us some fresh ideas.
No way, that's too much effort.
It's also too hot.
Rejected.
How about going to the art museum?
It's nice and cool there.
The art is nice to look at, too.
How would we use that in a game?
It has to be something we can use in a game.
Aw...
Hey, what about a resort in the south?
That doesn't sound bad, we'd definitely
be able to come up with lots of ideas there.
I... I don't think we have enough money to do that.
Onsen.
An onsen?
Agreed!
Its decided!
Developing sex and games!
Original animation disk.
Feeling good in the outdoor baths. Late outdoors test of courage arc.
Eroge! Developing sex and games!
Feeling good in the outdoor baths.
Late outdoors test of courage arc.
Uwah! I'm falling! I'm gonna fall!
Murano
Come on, just a bite!
No, there was a limit on how many of these were made!
Wow, the onsen smells so good.
I like this aroma.
There we go.
Off they come.
I'll see you guys there.
Oh, okay.
Um... this way, right?
Men's bath
Oh man, this is great.
Oh, this place had mixed bathing?
I-Iori-san?!
No, this is the men's bath!
There's no mixed bathing here!
Oh, I couldn't really see that well.
Well, there's nobody around anyway.
This feels amazing.
Okay, I'll just get out now then.
Wait.
This is the color it goes when you soak it in hot water?
Iori-san, what are you going to do if somebody comes?!
Hm? We'll deal with that when it happens.
I'm so excited for the outdoor bath.
I can't wait to get in!
This is a beautiful view.
Yeah, it's the best.
Let's get, out for now.
Yeah.
Iori-san, you can't make any noise, okay?
Iori-chan's really taking her time.
I bet she actually went to the men's bath.
Yeah, I can totally see that happening.
Cumming... I'm gonna cum!
I... I can't...
Did you hear that?
Yeah, I heard something...
Maybe it's a bird?
Right, I think I'm about done.
Yeah.
Iori-san, if you get out of the men's
bath now, nobody will notice.
Are you okay?
I don't think I can stand right now.
Cheers!
Good work everyone.
Pres, don't be so pouty.
Pout.
It looks really good on you!
That's the problem!
Kisara-san, here you go.
Thanks...
S-Sorry!
Jeez! Look at what you did!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
Oh jeez, you're soaking wet now.
What a waste of a meal, Mochizuki-kun.
The smell of beer isn't too bad either.
Mochizuki, you have a spare yukata
in your room, right? Come with me.
O-Okay.
Of all the things...
Huh? What happened?
Hey, Mochizuki?
Yeah?
The water stopped running all of a sudden.
I wonder why...
What's wrong?
It's so cold!
God, I can't believe you!
Yeah, I'm sorry, it's really just one thing after another.
It's coming inside me!
Mochizuki's big dick is coming inside me!
So good!
It feels really good!
My pussy feels so good right now.
No, if you move so quickly right from the start, I...
Sorry.
I-If you feel even a little bit sorry for
the trouble you've caused me, be more gentle.
O-Okay.
Does it feel good for you, too?
Yeah.
Say it. Say that it feels good.
Sure. Kisara-san, your pussy feels so good!
I know, right?
Of course it does.
Hold my boobs.
Okay!
My pussy is being fucked so good
by your dick, I feel like I'm gonna cum!
No! I don't want to cum yet! I don't want to cum yet!
Why'd you stop?
Wait, Mochizuki, what are you doi...
What is this? This is amazing!
It's going all the way to my womb!
Your dick is touching every last corner
of my pussy! You're making me go crazy!
If you keep doing this, my pussy...
my pussy's gonna melt!
It's so intense! It's going wild inside me!
Oh no, I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm really cumming!
Yeah, me too!
Just cum like this! I want your cum inside me!
I want it dribbling out, filling me up inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
This might be the first time that I've cummed like this.
When I was walking in the pitch dark woods by myself.
I began to hear a pair of footsteps
slowly drawing closer and closer to me.
Splash. Splash.
The wet footsteps matched
my pace as they closed in on me.
When I stopped, the footsteps stopped.
I turned around, but there was nobody there.
When I started walking again, the footsteps continued.
I looked up ahead and saw a small light coming
from a cabin window not too far away.
I quickened my pace, wanting to get
to that cabin as quickly as possible.
Trying to catch my breath as I peered into
the window, I could no longer hear the footsteps.
I looked behind me again and still, I saw nobody there.
I calmed myself and slowly opened
the wooden door in front of me.
And then suddenly...
Hey guys, you need to get out soon.
It's almost time for the men to bathe.
Why did you have to come in, then?!
We'll follow this path,
do one lap and then meet back here.
Mochizuki will be hiding around
the trail, trying to scare us, okay?
Okay, I'll go first.
I can't do it! Iori-chan, let's go together?
Okay...
Don't let go of my hand, okay?
Eroge! Developing sex and games.
If you're so scared, why did you suggest a test of courage?
There's no point in doing a test of courage if it's not scary.
Walking around with a kitchen knife is against the rules...
Oh, finally. I'm finally at the end...
Ooga Booga!
Ghosts should just stay dead!
Don't you think Mochizuki is trying too hard?
Is it time to use this?
Tomoya-san, sorry!
I forgot that we were in the middle of a test of courage!
I'm so sorry.
Wait, that's...
Tomoya-san, wake up!
The pain from the top and pleasure
from the bottom are mixing together...
There's only one part of him that's conscious.
All right.
Oh man, I'm so lucky!
Come on, come on, wake up.
Tomoya-san, wake up!
This is great.
It's moving. Okay then, next up is...
How's this? Is this still not enough?
I can't do this anymore!
Tomoya-san?!
Momoka-san, I'm cumming!
Wow...
They're so pretty...
When I stopped, the footsteps stopped.
I turned around, but there was nobody there.
Oh jeez, I'm getting so cold, I need to pee.
Huh?
Mochizuki is really doing his job.
I guess Kisara-san was really scared too.
Sure looks like it.
You don't have to hold it in, Kisara-san.
No, it's dirty! Let go of me!
Holding back my pee feels really good!
Come on, just let it out.
No...
It's really going to come out!
No! Let go of me! Let go of me!
No, this is so embarrassing. So embarrassing!
Kisara-san is a big scaredy cat, huh?
That's surprising.
Let's head over there.
You jerk! What the hell were you thinking?!
But it felt good, right?
Kisara-chan! Where are you?
It's time to go back to the inn!
Kisara-san, this way!
H-Hey, wait.
Wait a second!
Crash
They're so pretty.
Fireflies!
There are so many of them!
How beautiful.
Maybe Kisara-chan already went back?
That's possible.
Let's go back then.
Agreed.
Kisara-san, how about a lesson about yukatas?
About yukatas?
Female yukatas have arm holes
called Miyatsukuchi on them.
My boobs feel so good!
It feels good! Play with my nipples too!
So hot! My nipples are on fire!
My boobs and my pussy feel so good!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Wow! Oh my god. Oh my god!
This feels so good!
Your dick... your dick is bulging inside me!
It's so thick! It's messing me up!
My ass... My ass feels so good!
No! No! No! No! No!
I'm going to break!
Cum... I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Why am I in this kind of position now?
Kisara-san, you look so sexy.
Mochizuki... remember this.
It looks like you don't mind this too much.
I... I'm just still wet from before.
No, don't lick it with your tongue like that!
If you lick my pussy like that, I'll...
I think I'm gonna cum!
Wait, what are you going to do?!
Here I go.
This is amazing!
It's getting bigger!
Do it harder!
Go deeper! Go all the way inside!
I'm gonna cum!
My pussy's being messed up so badly, I can't hold it back!
It feels good! It feels so good!
Shove it in harder!
Make my pussy crazy! Make it a mess with your dick!
That feels so good, Mochizuki!
I want you to... I want you to keep
thrusting your big dick in me forever!
Okay, here I go!
Yeah, that's good! That's so good!
It feels so good!
You came so much inside me!
There's so much...
I can't stop cumming...
Fireflies...
Unable to resist his urges,
he shoved his cock in between my breasts.
Okay everyone, time to go home.
Oh, looks like you two are filled
with ideas for the new game.
Everyone is really motivated now.
It was worth it to spend all that money on the trip!
Right, Mochizuki-kun?
Yeah, seriously. It was a great idea.
Tomoya, take a picture of us.
Sure.
Okay, ready?
Say "cheese".
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality check: fyurie