MuchoHentai.com
Thank's to everyone the game sales
reached an unprecendented high!
This is all thanks to the efforts of
everyone. Thank you so very much!
As a prize, I'm going to use some of
the earnings to go on a vacation!
Now the question is where do we want to travel?
How about a camping and hiking trip?
I think it would be really fun!
No way, I don't want that.
It would be very hot...
Nope.
How about we go to Kogen no Bijutsu?
It's cool and the scenery is beautiful.
How about we visit the sex museum?
The game didn't earn enough for that.
Awww...
I know! Why don't we go to the Nangoku Resort?
That sounds good!
We really don't have the budget for that either...
Spa.
Spa?
Spa??
LOVE IT!!!
So be it!
I'm falling, I'm falling!
One more, leme have one more.
No, these are for later!
Wow, the smell of the springs is so good!
I love the taste of it.
There.
I'll go on ahead.
Ah, ok.
Hmm, maybe they went over there.
Ahhh, so good, so good...
What? It's a mixed bath?
No Iori, you went to the wrong bath.
Ahh, I couldn't see clearly.
Oh well, not like anyone minds.
Ahhh, feels really good.
Umm I'm gonna go.
Hold on.
Hmm, together we could make this go away.
Iori, what if someone comes?
We'll see if that happens.
Open air baths. Let's go!
Hurry let's go soak and relax.
Man what scenery...
Ahhh, it's the best.
Let's wait a bit to do it.
Wow...
Iori, please be really quiet.
Man, Iori is so slow.
I think she went to the men's bath.
Ahhhh, my oh my.
I'm gonna... cum.
I want... more.
Did you hear something?
I heard something too.
Could that be Iori-san?
Alright, It's time to go.
Yeah lets.
Iori, let's go back to the men's bath. No one's there.
Are you ok?
Ahh, my legs wont be moving for a while.
Cheers!
Otsukaresama desu!
Hey manager, why are you in that mood.
Ughhh. (O'3'o)-3.
You look very cute.
I didn't want to wear this!
Kisara-san, here.
Thank you!
Ahhhh, I'm sorry!
Arghh! You've really done it now!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Aww, you're all wet.
Aww, such a good mood we were
having and you ruined it Muchizuki.
– I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
– Aww, such a good mood we were
having and you ruined it Muchizuki.
– I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
– The beer wasn't bad either...
Mochizuki come on, you have a spare yukata in your room.
Come on, let's go.
What, yes.
Geez...
What... that's strange.
Hey, Mochizuki.
Yeah?
Suddenly the water stopped.
Hmmm, I wonder why.
What happened?
It's cold!!!
Geez, I cannot believe this.
I sincerely apologize for this...
Ahhh! Your mega dick is in me!
Incredible!
It feels so good.
My pussy feels so good!
Careful, if you keep moving that fast...
I'm sorry.
If you really feel that guilty, be a little more gentle.
Ah, ok.
Hey, does it feel good for you too?
Yeah.
Come on, say it clearly. Say it feels good!
Yeah, Kisara-san's pussy feels good!
Really, I knew it!
Ahh, rub my boobs!
So good, my pussy feels so good!
Not yet!
I don't want to cum yet!
What? Why did you stop?
Wait Mochizuki, what are you?
This feels amazing!
It feels so good on the inside!
Your dick is so hot and moving so fast.
It's making my mind go all blank.
This!!! This!!!
It's making my pussy, my pussy!
I'm gonna cum, go faster, I'm gonna cum.
I can't hold out any longer. I'm gonna, I'm gonna.
I'm gonna cum!
I'm also, I'm also gonna.
Keep going.
I want your cum!
I want a lot of your sperm!
I'm cumming!!! (x9)
This is... probably the first time... I've cum so hard... Ahhh!
I'm the dark forest...
Walking alone...
You hear footsteps coming.
Bang... Bang...
The sound of the foot steps is getting louder and closer.
But then suddenly the foot steps stop.
You stop and turn around, but there is no one there...
And then you start walking and hear them again.
You look ahead and see a small visible light from a window.
You quickly run towards the light.
You look at the light again.
Suddenly stop hearing foot steps...
I looked back at the light and there was nothing there.
I was able to calm down.
I look ahead and see the gates.
Then suddenly...
Everyone! You have to get out. They're
gonna change it to the men's bath now.
Why did you come in to take a shower
during the women's bath then!
You start here, make a turn there and then lap over there...
Mochizuki is somewhere around there to scare us.
I'll start ahead, see you!
Iori, it was really scary! Let's go together!
Ok let's go.
Please don't let go...
If he's not a coward he'll come...
If he doesn't try it's not as fun.
I'm sure holding kitchen knives is against the rules.
Ahh, it was just a dog.
WAU WAU!!!
DIE YOU MONSTER!
I hope Mochizuki isn't taking too seriously...
This seems like the best option.
I'm sorry Tomoya!
I forgot this was just a test of guts.
Sorry!
Is this...?
Tomoya please wake up!
Ah the pleasure of my penis but the pain of her slaps.
It's no use, I'm only making it worse.
Ok.
Oh I am getting so lucky...
Tomoya please wake up, wake up!
Tomoya please move...
This... it's incredible.
This is moving! In that case...
How is this? Is it working?
Ahhhh, I can't hold any longer!
Tomoya!?
Moka, here I go!
Amazing!
So beautiful.
But then suddenly the foot steps stop.
You stop and turn around, but there is no one there...
Oh no, I have to pee.
What?
He did it.
I knew Kisara was gonna be afraid.
It seems like it.
Kisara, you don't need to hold the pee back...
No! Let go, the clothes will get dirty!
God I'm dying to pee!!!
This feeling...
Come on, let it go...
No, it's getting wet!
No!
Let me go, let me go!
No, this is shameful!
It's embarrassing, very embarrassing!
It sounds like Kisara is really scared.
Very unexpected...
Isn't it time to pick him up now?
Idiot! Why did you do that!!!
But... it felt good didn't it?
Kisara! Where are you?
It's time to go home!
Kisara, come.
Wait!
Hold on!
So beautiful.
Wow... fireflies!
Wow! There are so many!
Beautiful!
Did Kisara already head back?
Perhaps.
Let's go back.
Kisara, let's learn about the yukata.
The yukata?
The women's yukata is nothing really special...
My boobs, they feel good!
Yes!
Play with my nipples too!
My nipples! My nipples are so hot!
Yes! My boobs and my pussy feel so good!
I'm gonna cum soon!
Amazing! (X4)
Mochizuki, your hard cock is inside me!
I can't! I give up!
Oh my ass! (X5)
Don't! (X9)
I'm gonna break!
I'm cumming! (X3)
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!! (x6)
Outside... dressed like this.
Kisara... you look so lewd.
Mochizuki... I'll remember this.
You seem to be enjoying this aren't you?
No! I want to go back!
Don't!
Lick my pussy!
My pussy is being licked!
I'm gonna cum!
Wait... What are you gonna do?
Here I go!
So good! Your penis is getting bigger!
More! Give me more!
Deeper, deeper, go deeper!
Give me your semen!
My pussy can't hold it anymore!
So good, so good, so good, so very good!
My pussy is getting treated so roughly!
Treat it rougher into my abdomen!
Mochizuki! Give me all of your semen! Give it to me!
Cum in me! (X4) Ruin my pussy!!!
Yes... Here I go!
Shoot loads, loads... loads.
Fireflies...
An excited man...
then places his penis between my breasts.
Alright everyone! It's time to go home!
Ohh, you seem to have gotten hew ideas for the next game.
Everyone looks so happy now.
Everyone got good memories...
Right, Mochizuki?
Yeah, good, really good.
Tomoya! Let's take a group photo!
Ok!
I'm taking the picture!
Ok? Cheese!