What do you think? It's got a lot better, right?
Sure!
That's right!
Praise me more! I'm allowing you to praise me.
Well, it's not like I want you to praise me,
but I don't want to lose against Kisara-san.
Is that so? If there's no problem, I'll keep on going.
The erotic game nut who's joined our company to help us, Tomoya-kun.
Then he helped Kisara-chan's erotic development,
for Flower's last chance to avoid bankruptcy.
I hope it will succeed!
I hope it will sell out!
I hope we can avoid bankruptcy!
I'm sure we can manage it!
We're close to finishing development, bug testing, then the game will go gold.
Let's do our best, Game Nut Tomoya-kun!
I'd rather you called me Erotic Game Nut!
W
Eroge!
H & Game Development with the Three Sisters
~Sopping Wet!? Beautiful Girl Creators Chapter~
It's been three months-
-since Mochizuki arrived.
It's been that long?
It feels like it was just last week.
That's true.
Even I can tell that there's still four of us in here.
That's mean.
Okay, okay... But Mochizuki-kun's doing good work with project management, as well as gathering data.
We have a lot of work to do, so let's do our best together!
Okay~!!!
There's a cute aspect to Kisara-san's artwork,
but now she understands how to make it erotic as well, and has moved beyond the standard erotic game level.
Momoka-san's story wasn't suitable for an erotic game at all,
there were just a lot of romantic scenes in flower gardens,
but now she's able to write harsher, more diverse scenes as well.
And Iori-san.
In the previous project, her coloring style was pretty flat,
but now she's able to bring the characters and scenes to life.
The president is, well,
still getting hugged and caressed by everyone as the company mascot,
but now I can say that she's able to be a good director for our projects.
Don't think that you'll be my boyfriend because of this!
Mochizuki, will you check... my coloring?
Y-Yes.
That's right, it's not all about Kisara-san.
Eroge.
Momo, I'm leaving first! Don't stay for too long.
I'm first.
I'm going to take a bath!
Okay!
It's wrong, It shouldn't be like this.
Um... What's the matter, Momoka-san?
It's nothing! I'm just thinking about this script.
I can solve this kind of problem by myself, you don't have to worry.
Right... But if you need help with something, you can ask me.
Really? Ok then.
What's with that dismissive look?
You should be grateful to me.
This high class lady wants to use your filthy thing for reference!
There's no line like that!
Shut up, just be useful this time!
I'm not a masochist!
I wonder, how long can you keep saying that?
Controlling men's desire is easy for me.
I'll prove that... to you.
What's that? You're just looking at my breasts.
Do you want these?
You're just like an animal, huh? You're really groping hard.
What?
Do you want to put your masochist penis inside me?
You're the one who wants it inside, right?
Well... Well... You're still able talk back to me.
It's getting hard, right?
Do you want to have sex with me... with your big penis?
I want to.
What? I couldn't hear you.
If you don't say it properly, I won't let you have sex with me.
Please let me put it in!
My penis is inside Momoka-sama's pussy!
Well said... I'll let you put it in.
But in exchange... If it hurts, you have to stop.
Th-This is your penis? Something that size can't possibly satisfy me!
Don't think so highly of yourself just because you have bigger breasts than the others!
What's with the way you're talking to me?
It seems your penis needs to be taught to be obedient.
My pussy will teach your penis a lesson.
Until it turns into a masochistic penis that begs to be abused!
It's getting tight!
It's not bad... being held like this.
You like my pussy?
Penis...
I'm going to make you feel good,
then you and your penis will serve me forever!
What's the matter? You came this much already?
Your pussy is soaked as well!
What're you saying? There's no way I'd get wet from your filthy penis!
Very well... I'll punish your cock with my pussy so you won't ever talk back again.
It's out... I can feel your juice flowing out inside me.
It's unfair that only you get to let it out like that.
Open your mouth.
Very well... Since you dared to put your hard and filthy penis inside of me, I'll give you this.
Hey, who told you that you could touch my tongue?
Know your place.
How is it? I'm tasty, right?
What? What?! Y-Your penis is...
You're really simple minded with a pig-penis, aren't you?
You got carried away since I let you drink my saliva, now you dare to stir up my insides with your penis.
You're so deep inside my pussy!
It really irritates me when I hear the noise from my breasts hitting your chest.
This thing...
Don't... That part is...
What's this? It's so embarrassingly hard!
I'll do something like this with your masochist nipples.
Th-There's a lot of it!
So much came out...
You... You're not that bad, you sadistic penis-loving Ojou-sama.
You're not bad either, you masochist pig.
Yes, this is...
I'm the queen who's getting filled with cum.
I'm finally able to understand!
I... I'm glad to hear that.
Not like that... Not like this.
Um...
No-No! Not that!
This shouldn't be happening.
Everyone, could you stop for a moment?
What's the matter? Did you go crazy from the heat?
Do I look crazy to you?
You do, that's why she said it!
I can see that.
Wh-What's the matter, Mochizuki-kun?
You're not working very effectively.
Shouldn't we go out to refresh and have some fun?
Have fun? Where should we go?
What a great scene!
Be grateful to Reina-sama for driving us here.
Thank you very much!
Reina-san, let's play beach volleyball!
Hey, Mochizuki... If you're not doing anything, join us!
I'll pass for today. I'll get covered in sand.
Me too, I'm not very good at sports.
Hm.
A cicada flying around in the heat of the sun.
I'll teach you manners in beach volleyball.
Mochizuki-kun, you were a nice employee.
That's cowardly! Is that how adults play?
Adults should use their heads instead.
Here I come, I'll make you regret making me your enemy!
Such a weak shot,
I could dodge it with my eyes closed!
Even your head is empty!
So stupid.
A-Are you all right?
If it's come to this...
We have to run away!
Why me too?!
Wait!
Adults don't run away!
Then why are the adults doing that?
What are they doing?
It doesn't look like beach volleyball.
There you go!
It's fabulous!
This is one big hole.
Excuse me, where's the toilet?
Ah, this way.
Eroge.
Um... Iori-san, where's the toilet?
In here.
Eh?
In here, my mouth is the toilet.
We've been working on peeing scenes, I want to know more about pee!
Come on, it's all right. Don't hold back.
Wh-What's wrong with her?
Is she serious? There's no way...
This is bad...
What's wrong? You won't do it?
That's because... I'm like this...
You can't do it if you're that hard?
Yes.
Then I should just make you cum.
Your penis is getting hard.
Iori-san, I'm...
It's okay, you can cum.
I already know the taste and smell of semen.
Now I want to taste it... with my pussy.
Look.
Inside here.
Th-This is bad, Iori-san.
Amazing!
I never thought that it would hurt like this.
Your penis is so big!
It feels so good!
Let me touch you more.
Let's rub each other!
If you make so much noise...
It's not a problem, besides...
I want... I want a stronger smell than this!
Smell?
I want it! I want it!
So intense!
I can't hold it!
This is... the strongest smell I've ever known.
It's so sticky, I can't get it off easily.
Now can you let it out?
I... I'll really do it, okay?
Sure!
She likes this kind of thing?
Hey, Nene!
If you don't hurry up, the crabs will eat you.
Don't just stand there, help me!
What are they doing... exactly?
It's getting late, we should go back now.
L-Let's come again! With everyone! Next year too!
Yeah, you're right.
Eroge.
Good work today!
Good work!
We're gonna start tomorrow!
Debugging, right?
Let's do our best.
You're going home too, right?
Yes.
I have something to ask you.
Come in.
It's a bit small, but it's all I can afford from my part-time job.
This is from back then... I want to see it again!
Th-That's enough! There's no time for that!
Just hurry up!
So you also draw doujinshi?
Right, since we're getting pretty busy now, I want to get it done by tonight.
I see.
Um... This is... Where should I fill in this one?
Um... How was this one gonna be?
What do you think of this?
I asked because I don't know.
I was joking.
Um... Let's... Maybe it's the hair... Yeah, the hair.
The rest is... Supposed to be in black...
I'll write in the directions to make you...
H-Hey, what are you doing?!
That's enough! I'm sorry, I didn't realize you were trying so hard to invite me in here.
Huh?! What are you talking about?!
Kisara-san!
No!
D-Don't!
It's been a while since I've seen your ass.
Don't grope...
W-Why are you so hard already?!
It's because I've been looking at you!
You smell so good, it's like you're attracting my penis to you!
I'm not attracting it! Not attracting it at all!
Then why is your pussy soaked?
It's not... It's just a bit wet.
Also, there's no scene like this in the game!
Don't just take out your penis like that!
Your pussy is soaked.
If I don't do something, the floor will get stained.
Your penis is inside me! In my own room!
If you do it so hard, I won't be able to use this as a data!
It's alright! Use your head to focus on the drawing!
And use your pussy for sex!
As if I could do that when your penis is so deep in me!
Don't go in so deep! My neighbors will hear me!
Who cares? Kisara-san is already a fine adult woman with adult needs!
No way! I don't want my neighbors to hear me having sex!
You're rubbing me so hard!
My insides are going to melt!
You just want to enjoy this as much as you can, right?
Not at all! Not at all!
But I can't resist this! Your penis is taking me over!
It's all right, you're gonna feel better after this.
Your stupid penis...
Really... Your stupid penis is the only good thing about you!
Don't grope my breasts!
I'm about to cum.
Don't... I don't want you to cum inside me in my own room!
Your semen's filling my pussy!
You're filling me with semen!
I'm cumming too... Your animal penis is making me cum...
Don't! I'll cum too much...
Just leave it to me, I won't let your perverted pussy rest!
A filthy, hard penis is penetrating my pussy!
M-More... Do it harder!
If you move like that...
Shut up! Just because you're an animal with a big hard penis,
I'll take your penis inside me!
Hurry, move more and stir up my pussy harder!
If you want it that much, I'll tear apart your perverted pussy!
Your penis is amazing! It feels so good when you move in and out!
It's thrusting so deep, the tip of your penis is hitting me so hard!
No!
I can't...
My ass... My ass is being raped by a penis!
You're rubbing so hard, I'll cum from my butt and my pussy!
My neighbors will hear the noise from you teasing my pussy...
I love penis...
What's wrong with you? Now we left early for nothing!
I'm sorry.
As a punishment, you won't get your payment!
Well... That's... I already got my payment... a while ago.
You're really a monkey!
Idiot! Stupid, stupid, idiot!
We're done.
Now I only need to edit it, I'll do it by myself.
Good work.
I'd rather have a beer instead of juice.
You can't have any beer, right?
You'll do something weird again.
Hey...
You... You like me, right?
Y-Yeah.
You really worked hard today... So...
If you're fine with it, I might agree to go out with you.
Huh?!
She refused me once already, so why now...
Did Kisara-san do something like that only for today?
Come on, say something already!
I-It's not like I care about you or anything!
Not at all.
Of course, it would be my pleasure.
What's with that face? Are you making fun of me?
It's not like that.
You are, I know you are!
Idiot! You idiot!
She's one troublesome girl.
Say something already.
You're so cute, Kisara-san!
You don't have to be shy!
I'm not! Not at all!
Let me go, you idiot! Stop it!
I won't go out with you then!
Don't go pushing yourself.
Geez... Idiot.
Eroge.
Debugging.
Saving electricity!
Iori-san, the penis is already in her here, so you should add some juice!
I'll do it, but the pussy would be sticky as well.
Who put this in the script?
'If you put your penis inside, my pussy will explode'?
'My pussy will explode'? Where's that?
That was me! I edited it, did I do wrong?
Penis
Pussy
Penis is... Pussy is...
Penis
Pussy
All the innocent Flower girls have matured since then.
Penis
Pussy
But when are we gonna finish?
Debugging
Master Copy
More... Give me more penis! More semen!
Cover me with your hot semen!
There shouldn't be any problems, right?
With this, we've finished the game.
It's all right! Everything's okay!
We did it! We managed to do it! We did it!
We really got it done!
I'm really tired after all.
Finally! Finally...
The new Flower game is complete!
Eroge.
Everyone, thanks for your hard work!
Thanks to you, we finished the game!
Thank you so much!
Cheers!
I'm glad I could join this company.
I'm also glad... Come here.
Me too, this place... This place is the best!
Yeah, that's right.
I'm so happy!
Congratulations! You're done with the master copy?
Reina, why are you drunk already?
We should celebrate! I can't resist drinking now!
Let's do the usual!
But that would be too much...
You're so sexy.
I think we should reward him for his hard work.
There!
One more!
What are you doing, Reina-san?
Then me too!
Nene-chan, you can't!
It's still not over!
You woke up? Good morning!
What's with that getup?
You put it on?
You said... you wanted to see it.
No... Your penis is getting hard inside me!
We're on break until next week, so we can...
Let's do it a lot!
Sure, I love you Kisara.
I love you too, I love you so much... Tomoya!
Again... Come again, Tomoya.
Don't ever... Don't ever let go of me, okay?
Of course.
I love the feeling of you cumming inside me!
Your penis exploded inside me!
I'm cum.... Cumming... Cumming!
Tomoya...
Kisara...
Wh-What are you doing?!
I told you!
I'm here to stop them!
Nene said we could use it as reference for our next game.
So nice to be young, doing it in the middle of the day!
Even Reina-san?!
Idiots!