Let's Fall In Love, The Ero-manga: Page 2!
It's just a big, good event.
Good morning, Mom.
Good morning, Hiro.
Huh?
Where's Sis? She's still sleeping?
It's "that day" for Azusa, so she's taking the day off.
I see, today is "that day"...
That's why you should take the day off, too.
Huh? Why do I have to take a day off, too?
It can't be helped. We can't leave Azusa home alone, right?
I can't take a day off today; I have to work.
So make sure to take good care of your sister, Hiro.
Eh? W-wait... Mom!
Well, I'll see you later.
Why me?
Every month around this time,
my step sister...
...will fall into heat.
What are you doing, Sis?
It's time for breakfast! Your morning wood...
Here I go!
Hey- Sis!
Delicious!
Doing something like this in the morning...
It's fine, let it out.
Let it all out into your sister's mouth!
I'm coming.
Sis!
Hiro's cum is so thick and tasty.
Thank you for the meal.
Ah, um... sorry there wasn't more.
It was so good, I'd like seconds.
This time, let me taste it with this mouth...
Go ahead.
Ah... yes...
Even though you just woke up... why is it so easy to move?
Hiro's jumbo sausage tastes so good!
More, let me taste even more of you!
Sis!
It feels good, Hiro.
Hiro!
Sis!
More.
She got so tired that she fell asleep.
Even though I'm even more tired...
Ah, I'm hungry.
Thank you very much.
Not good... I originally planned to go back as soon as I bought a lunch box.
I got caught up in those books without realizing it!
I'm back.
Sis, I bought food.
Huh?
Is she in my room?
Hiro...
Hiro, more... do me more...
Don't leave me alone!
Hiro, I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Um...
S-Sis...
I brought a lunch box.
What's wrong Sis?
Don't cry.
But... when I woke up, you were gone...
I thought you left because you hated me.
Idiot, how could that be true?
Really? You like me?
Yeah.
You love me?
I... love you.
Thank goodness.
Leaving that aside, here's your lunch box.
You're hungry, right, Sis?
Yeah, I'm really hungry.
That's why...
Eh?
Use your dick to fill me up.
As I thought, it's turning out like this again.
Hey, look.
Our special places are rubbing each other...
You're already so wet.
No, this is...
...so hard to bear...
I want your dick.
Sis, you don't need me. Won't a vibrator be fine?
No!
I only want yours.
It has to be yours.
Sis...
Your dick is amazing.
You just put it in, and I already came.
Yours is amazing, too.
It's so wet, and so tight.
Hiro.
You're amazing.
Sis, I'm already... gonna come...
Let it out, Hiro.
Fill me up with your sperm!
I can't hold on anymore, Sis!
You came outside...
That's a given.
How could I have come inside?
Geez...
What are you doing?
My stomach isn't full yet.
Huh? Wa- I just came.
Wait, Sis!
It got big again.
S-Sis, you're going too fast.
I-It's going all the way in.
Sis, I'm coming again...
Let it out, Hiro.
This time you have to come inside.
Sis, that's not possible.
You have to come inside.
This is your sister's order.
No way, Sis.
Sis, I'm coming!
Sis...
Hiro, I love you so much.
More!
I'm back.
I brought some eel.
You've gotten quite pale since I left you this morning.
Well, how was it?
I don't remember anything after the 20th time.
My kid's sex drive sure is strong.
She's just like me when I was young.
"When I was young"...
You would fall into heat, too?
Didn't I tell you about it before?
This runs through our family.
Though that phase ended for me a long time ago.
Then Sis' will end in the near future too, right?
After giving birth to Azusa, it ended naturally.
After giving birth...?
Look, it's your dad.
Although he's your dad, he's also your uncle.
This is bad.
I have to hurry up and find another breeding horse for her.
It'll be fine.
As long as you have love, you'll easily be able to overcome any obstacle that comes your way!
Don't say a bunch of impossible stuff and change the subject!
My stomach is so full.
Hiro...
Let's Fall In Love: The Ero-manga!
It's been a while since you've come to my room, Mayo-nee.
Ah, yeah... That's right.
Then, what is it?
Aside from lending you money, I can help you with anything.
Actually...
I'd like to request something of you.
A request?
Um... my boobs...
Can you caress my boobs?
Oh, boobs! Tits.
That's right.
What, just that?
T-T-Tits?!
Wah! Satoru-kun!
I burned. I burned until nothing was left but white.
Hey, Satoru-kun?
Have you calmed down?
Well... somewhat.
Anyway, why are you suddenly asking me to do something like that?
That's because... um...
What do you think of my boobs, Satoru-kun?
Even if you ask me what I think...
Like I thought, they're huge, useless and unseemly; it's really shameful, right?
T-That's not true.
As a man, you wouldn't understand, but...
They're heavy and make my shoulders really sore,
and when I'm running they rub against my clothes, and it's really painful.
The opposite sex looks at me strangely.
The same sex is jealous of me.
There's a lot of other downsides, too.
Ah... The man's romance continues to collapse.
That does sound pretty tough.
And then I talked about it with my friend.
You wanna die!?
Just let a man rub your "Cameron Legend" tits this way and that way!
Let him rub them until they disappear completely!
And so she gave me this valuable advice.
That counts as advice?
I've also asked a lot of other people,
and they all said the same thing.
It seems like it's really effective.
It looks like everyone's had their boobs rubbed by a man to make them smaller.
It looks like the same sex really is jealous of you.
Mayo-nee, you should choose some better friends.
And then, I thought about giving it a try...
...but you're the only member of the opposite sex I'm close to, Satoru-kun.
And so... um, Satoru-kun.
I want you to... rub my... t-tits...
Well, if you're going this far, then...
Um... is it really okay?
Yeah.
I'll leave it up to you.
Wait, why do you have to take off my clothes?
Well, I was just thinking that it might be more effective if I touched them directly.
Yeah... That seems be... reasonable.
And so... here I go, Mayo-nee.
Yeah.
How is it, Mayo-nee?
Is it working?
I don't know, but...
...my body is getting hot.
My head is going blank.
I want you to keep rubbing... for a bit longer.
Mayo-nee...
Y-You don't need to rub the nipples, do you?
But these are a part of your breasts, too.
Indeed... That's true.
S-Satoru-kun, after you started rubbing there...
...it's gotten hard to breathe.
It's unbearable.
Mayo-nee, who's always so cool, is showing an opening.
It's too cute!
Um... if two people aren't in love, isn't it wrong to do something like this?
I-I-I'm Sorry!
You were too cute, so I unconsciously...
I-Idiot! How can a woman like me be cute?
This insistent part of you too...
Always serious, but a bit air-headed. That part of you...
And that huge pair of tits; they're all cute.
Because of that, Mayo-nee...
I've always loved you.
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean to make you uncomfortable.
Um...
Now we're even.
Mayo-nee, you really are cute.
Then, what are we going to do next?
By "next", you mean...
You've confessed, and we've kissed already.
Aren't we going to do it?
Sex.
You're going too fast, Mayo-nee.
Am I wrong?
I heard from my friend before that this is the way things should work.
Don't tell me you don't want to have sex with me?
Of course I want to!
Don't cry.
Um... I don't have any knowledge or experience with this.
Anything you want to do... it's all up to you.
Then... I'll take you up on that offer.
You're starting there?
Mayo-nee, you're really wet.
You became this wet just by having your tits rubbed.
You're unexpectedly perverted.
I-Is that so?
Do you hate perverted girls?
I love you the way you are; cute, big-breasted, and really perverted.
Idiot.
Mayo-nee, it's about time...
G-Go ahead.
Then, I'm going in.
Mayo-nee, are you okay?
I'm fine, so...
It's so wet and tight inside Mayo-nee, it feels too good.
This is...
It's so intense.
Don't lick my tits!
Mayo-nee's tits are so bouncy and delicious.
No.
Idiot.
I love every part of Mayo-nee's body.
No!
It's coming!
Ah, don't!
I'm going to come!
I'm coming!
I've always wanted to do this one.
Idiot.
Mayo-nee~!
Geez, you're just like a baby.
You like my tits that much?
Yeah, they're so big and soft; they're the best.
This might be a problem.
Why?
Because you like big breasts, right?
Which means you dislike girls with small breasts.
In other words, I have to maintain my current breast size for you.
Actions that make my boobs smaller must be strictly controlled.
And so, I forbid you from rubbing my breasts from now on.
Awaken, Ero Tits!
Rub, rub~.
What are you doing?
And going "boobs, boobs" like that...
You aren't a baby.
Didn't we do a lot of other things already?
Is this okay, nya?
Yeah.
Nya!
It hurts!
Nyah!
Ah! I hate not being able to grope your tits! I hate it! I hate it! I hate it! I hate it! I hate it!
Geez, it can't be helped.
Today is an exception.
Mayo-nee's tits taste good.
No matter how hard you suck, nothing's going to come out.
But a lot of juice came out of this place... it's all wet.
Mayo-nee, I'll leave my thing up to you.
Use your tits, of course.
Geez, you really like that, huh?
Amazing, it's throbbing.
It feels good, Mayo-nee.
I'll make you feel good, too.
I'm coming, Mayo-nee. I'm coming on your tits.
Amazing, this much...
This makes it look like your milk came out.
Idiot.
Well then, Mayo-nee.
Yeah.
Take this!
Amazing, Mayo-nee. Your tits are bouncing up and down.
It's because you're doing it so intensely.
Your hips are moving on their own, too.
Because... it feels good!
Mayo-nee, I'm... gonna come soon.
I'm already...
I cant, I'm gonna come.
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
So much went in...
I came this much, so it's about time for you to be able to produce milk, right?
Idiot, what if I really do get pregnant-
I know, Mayo-nee.
I'll take responsibility.
Before I give birth, tits are a given, but all other perverted things will be forbidden, too.
I've only just begun my journey down this road...
This road without end, the road towards the distant tits!
Unfinished
It's just a big, good event.