This video is brought to you by NotSafeForWork. For more of our releases, visit http://sfw.omni-downloads.com or #NotSafeForWork@irc.rizon.net. This video is not safe for work. Do not redistribute this video for any commercial purposes.
This is amazing...
It's so big and hot, and it's throbbing...
It's okay to feel good... let it all out into my breasts!
So much cum... such a waste!
Now it's your turn to make me feel good.
It's going in, it's going in... your big penis is going in!
Amazing, it feels good! My p***y feels so good!
I'm coming!
Let's fall in love, like in ero-manga!
[Let's Fall in Love the Ero-Manga]
Alright!
It's not alright!
That hurt!
Mizuki, when did you...
It's not "when did you"!
Daisuke, what are you doing skipping school?
What, you ask? Well, as you can see, I'm drawing ero-manga.
You don't have to show me!
Eh? But it's a color page drawn with my sweat and blood!
Geez, I know you're busy with work,
but if you can't graduate because of that, won't you be putting work before school?
But, you know, there were a lot of exams and stuff this month,
and before I realized it, the deadline was here...
You're a man, so don't make excuses!
You're the one at fault for not planning ahead!
Don't get so angry. I'll make you some tea.
So drink it and calm down- Ah!
Wait! Mizuki, it's a misunderstanding!
I pulled an all-nighter, I haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
My legs don't have any strength, so...
Idiot!
Geez, this guy has always overworked himself without thinking of anything else.
Wait a minute.
Thank you for the food!
I'm full.
D-Don't get the wrong idea! I was hungry, so I just made your share, too.
Yeah, curry tastes better if you cook a lot at once.
This idiot writes ero-manga and can't even tell when I'm being tsundere?
Well then, I guess I should get back to work.
I'll help you.
Is it okay?
The sooner you finish your work, the sooner you can get back to school, right?
Well, I'm counting on you.
Crap, Daisuke draws ero-manga...
At any rate... this woman is me, no matter how you look at it.
What is he thinking while he's drawing?
Don't tell me he looks at me like this...
D-Daisuke...
Um...
Hmm? What?
Is this heroine possibly...
Ah, you could tell after all?
Yeah, she's modeled after you.
Because you fit the heroine perfectly.
Having someone like you as a childhood friend really helped me out.
I didn't have to think about the character design this time.
Since I'm familiar with your face, it was really easy to draw!
I see...
I finished the part you assigned me.
Next is...
Hmm, wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Well, I just can't seem to draw this right.
Mizuki, could you do a pose for me?
Sure, but what kind of pose?
Masturbating.
You bastard... If you don't cut it out already,
you might lose something other than that manuscript... like your life.
If you happen to pick it up, could you return it to its owner?
It can't be helped. I'll search through these videos for a reference.
What is that? I don't believe it!
Is it normal for someone to look at adult videos in front of a girl?
Which one should I look at?
On top of that, we're alone in the same room.
Doesn't he see me as anything more than a convenient helper?
Alright, I'll look at this one.
Mizuki?
I'll do it.
Like I said, I'll do it. That... masturbating... pose.
Is it alright?
Yes.
W-Well... get on the bed.
Is this fine?
Yeah... that's the idea.
Hey, Mizuki...
W-What?
Do you always wear your clothes when you masturbate?
Why am I doing this... it's so embarrassing!
Idiot! Don't get so close!
But I need to see the crease properly...
If he moves so close... the smell will... I haven't taken a bath yet!
Daisuke will think I smell for sure.
Mizuki... is wet.
Don't look! Idiot!
Daisuke's breath is hitting it... I feel strange...
If I didn't watch, there wouldn't be any reason for you to model.
Daisuke is watching me! It's embarrassing, but...
This... clitoris. It's getting big enough to see it, even through the panties.
Idiot! Don't touch it!
Don't play with it!
If I don't know what this place tastes like while you're masturbating...
No way!
No, don't lick it! Don't!
It's dirty... to lick it like that!
No!
It's making strange noises...
Daisuke's licking my pussy... it feels so good!
No!!
I came.
Just like in a manga... I came.
Mizuki, you came?
Hey, what does it feel like when a woman comes?
Mizuki?
Let me see your naughty place in return!
So this is a man's... It can turn this hard...
It's hot and throbbing, just like it's drawn in manga.
Um, Mizuki-san, it's about time for me to start my work...
My childhood friend is giving me a blowjob. This is just like...
I did something like this in the manga, right?
If I remember correctly... I used my boobs to squeeze it and moved them up and down.
How is it, Daisuke?
Your tsundere childhood friend is giving you a titty fuck!
Amazing, it feels good! Eh, tsundere?
I didn't say that!
Ah? Something came out.
Ah, Mitsuki. This is bad!
What is this?
This is cum?
So Daisuke came, too.
And all over my face, too.
Now we're even.
Not yet.
Mizuki, I want to go all the way with you.
All the way? Sex?
Yes.
For your manga?
No.
I love you, Mizuki. That's why...
Alright.
If it's like that, I don't mind.
I'm going in, Mizuki.
Daisuke is coming in... he's coming in!
Amazing! We're doing it... just like in manga...
Mizuki, does it hurt?
I'm fine, so...
Then I'm going to move.
Okay.
What is this?
Even though this is my first time,
it feels so good!
It's so wet and tight...
It feels so good inside of Mizuki!
Daisuke... good, amazing! I feel so good!
My breasts feel good, too...
Daisuke, I love you!
Me too, Mizuki.
Ah, my first kiss came after I lost my virginity.
This position is so embarrassing!
Mizuki, Mizuki!
Daisuke, I'm coming, I'm gonna come!
Me too.
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Mizuki.
Daisuke.
I love you. I love you so much.
Hey, do I really have to do this?
Please, Mizuki. I'll be finished after this last page.
Geez, I guess it can't be helped.
It's here! This is it!
No, Daisuke is watching me pee!
I...
Thank you, Mizuki.
Now I'll be able to make it in time for tomorrow's deadline.
He really only thinks about ero-manga.
He'd better thank me properly later.
Hey, what are you gonna do with this?
Uh, just pour it down the toilet.
I'm the one cleaning it up, too?
Well, it's better than letting Daisuke smell this pee.
[Ojou-sama's Special Attack]
In other news,
new developments regarding the Tokinomiya Group president's recent embezzlement scandal...
This news again?
Reports keep coming in one after another; it's getting pretty serious.
It's a good thing I quit working there before this happened.
I wonder how Ojou-sama is doing?
Sebastian, refill.
My name is not Sebastian.
I do not have the time to remember every one of my servant's names.
This spoiled girl...
Who is it at this time?
Shut up! What time do you think it is?
You're late!
How long were you planning on making me wait?
Ojou-sama!
For now, have some tea.
Is this the time for that?!
Hot-
But you're drinking it...
Well? Why did you come all the way out here?
Because you didn't come to pick me up!
You didn't come when your master was in a pinch.
You're a disgrace to servants everywhere!
Even if you say that,
I already quit.
To be blunt, we're not related at all right now.
What about loyalty?
Where is your loyalty towards your master?
Asking for loyalty from a part time servant is a bit...
Anyway, it's already this late.
The Missus will be worried.
Mother already ran off with her young lover.
Tsubasa~
Come with me.
Aren't there a lot of servants back at the mansion?
They all quit.
I don't want to return to that mansion.
Leaving that aside, this room is quite small and dirty.
You're annoying, so go back already, you spoiled brat!
Please stay at my home for tonight.
Well, if it's only this much, it should be fine.
It's not like this is the first time I've experienced Ojou-sama's selfishness...
H-How rude!
Unlike people like you, who don't repay people's kindness,
I'll thank you properly.
Well then, how are you going to thank me for the night's stay and the free meal?
Well... I came here in a hurry, so I didn't bring anything with me.
I'm kidding, I don't really need anything.
I don't have money on me, so I'll pay with my body.
Like I said, I don't need any...
Eh? Your body?!
Ojou-sama.
You hit my teeth, it hurts...
T-This was my first time, so it can't be helped.
Eh? First time?
What's so funny?
Nothing. You're only doing this much to pay with your body?
T-That's... um...
That's why you're a spoiled girl who doesn't know how the world works.
What are you doing?
Let me teach you what it means to pay a debt with your body.
No!
Just kidding.
That was an act.
But if you stay here, I might really make that mistake.
So be obedient and return to the mansion.
I'm... not going back!
If I go back, I'm going to be...
Eh? You're getting married?
To who?
Someone I've never met before...
Some rich man from another family.
So this will be my last selfish request.
At least let me give my virginity to the person I like...
Ojou-sama...
For a master to fall in love with her servant...
It really is ridiculous.
Ojou-sama.
You're really good at kissing.
Well, compared to you, I have much more experience.
How arrogant... even though you're only a servant...
That's why you should leave everything to me.
All you need to do is relax.
E-Even if you say that...
My breasts are being sucked by a man.
Don't! It feels too good.
Any more, and I'll...
Don't! No!
Don't think too much, and just feel it.
It's alright, just let your body follow your feelings.
You're already this wet.
That can't be... no!
The shape and color of your pussy is really nice... it's really erotic.
Wait- No!
Erotic juice keeps flowing out.
It's delicious, Ojou-sama.
No!
Don't drink it!
It's about time.
Are we really going to do it in this dog-like position?
It seems that this position doesn't hurt as much for virgins.
And I can see your asshole clearly, too...
I'll be able to stimulate it.
Idiot! Don't look at that!
It's too late to hide anything now.
This can't... It's coming in! It's coming in!
Even though it's your first time, you're enjoying this by swallowing and squeezing my dick.
Don't explain every little thing.
You've matured well. It feels great inside of you, Ojou-sama.
Ojou-sama, even though this is your first time, you're still really sensitive.
Please tell me where it feels good.
No!
If you don't tell me, I'm going to stop.
How can that be...
Pu..ss..y
Puss... what?
Pussy...
I want it... in my pussy...
I can't hear you.
It feels good.
Amazing! Your dick is going in deep.
I'm already...
My breasts are... being groped by a servant.
It feels good.
We're having intercourse like dogs...
The dogs we raised in the mansion, Richard and Elizabeth,
they had sex like this too, right?
No! It's embarrassing!
No, that's not it!
I'm Tokinomiya's only daughter!
To be doing dirty things like a dog...
You've already given your virginity to a servant.
It's too late to pretend to be a dignified lady now.
I'm already at my limit... it doesn't matter if we're doing it like dogs.
I want to come! Use your dick to...
Make me come! Make me come! Make me come!
As you wish, Ojou-sama.
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Amazing, it's so hot...
Ojou-sama.
Father, Mother, don't abandon me...
Where are you going, Ojou-sama?
I'm returning to the mansion.
Wait a second.
I'll be a problem for me if you move around as you wish.
But if I continue to stay here, I'll only give you trouble.
I've finally gotten together with you.
Using this to become the successor to the Tokinomiya group...
...might not be so bad, I think.
Then, that means...
For now, would you like to hire me again?
T-That's right.
I can think about it.
Then let's start by making it a reality.
You're only a servant, yet you want your master to do perverted things...
How arrogant.