It's a Christmas night,
and there's a real santa right here in my lonely apartment.
I'm your Christmas present.
I'll work hard so that you can completely accept me.
A-After my first kiss,
I want you to take my first time here as well.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum.
Oh no, it's overflowing.
My pussy is still wide open, in the shape of your dick.
Santa Foundation, Japan Branch
Sex with a santa girl?
Do we accept these kinds of requests?
Alone with my Santa Clause
It's a Christmas night.
I'm the pure-hearted Santa-san who's
about to give presents to children.
Designated by Santa Foundation's Japan Branch.
It's also the first year of my service.
That's how it's supposed to be, but...
It's here.
Good evening, I'm Santa.
I'm here to give you your present.
I'm coming in, okay?
S-Santa? A present?
Wait, I don't really get what you're saying...
What's with this girl?
She's really cute!
Your request has been accepted by the Santa Foundation.
You placed thi linside a stocking.
I want to have lovey-dovey
date with Santa girl
on Christmas night
Oh yeah, I remember doing something this childish a while back.
I'm still a newbie, but I'll do my best
so that you can come to accept me.
Here, say "ah".
U-Umm, did I do something wrong?
You're just so cute, it's love at first sight, Santa-san.
I can't hold back anymore.
Suddenly doing something like this...
This is embarrassing.
Please just wait.
My heart isn't ready for this.
I can't wait.
Because this offer stands only for this night, right?
I understand.
Just for this night,
I'll give my everything to you as a present.
So please, do what you want with me.
Your pussy is also cute.
Santa-san, you're really cute.
No, please don't stir it too much.
Santa-san, your pussy is totally wet now.
I can put it in already, right?
Okay, I'll give my virginity to you.
Santa-san, your insides feel hot, I'm about to melt.
It feels too good.
Thank you very much.
Oh crap, I'm being squeezed tightly by this virgin pussy.
I'm going to cum.
You also seem to have cum.
I'm happy.
It felt great for me too.
Oh yeah, are these presents mine, too?
Yes, these are some of the presents that you requested.
What are these, anyway?
Oh, this looks quite fun!
Alright, let's use these toys and play.
S-Sure.
I'm a bit scared.
Santa-san, say "ah".
This is...
The thing that was inside me earlier.
So this is how men taste?
It feels wet and soft, this is great.
Her blowjob is going to make me cum again.
Cum it all inside my mouth.
I'm going to cum.
I'm about to cum while he cums inside my mouth.
Take it off.
T-Take this toy off, please.
So you came while sucking it.
How cute.
This means you want my dick, right?
It can't be helped then.
I'm going to cum if it keeps on rubbing me hard like this.
I'm cumming.
My pussy is going to cum!
No, don't play with my nipples using that toy.
This is fun.
Do your best, Santa-san.
I just keep on cumming.
I'm about to go crazy.
I'm supposed to be the one getting the present,
but you're the one who keeps on cumming.
Here's a little punishment for my erotic Santa-san.
That place is...
Your pussy is clenching me tightly as I play with your asshole.
Please don't...
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming in the depths of your pussy!
I'm cumming!
It's pumping inside me.
For my last round, please let me do some
lovey-dovey sex as I cum inside you.
Okay, I'm happy.
Just keep on pushing...
I want my pussy to remember your dick's taste.
I like you, I love you.
I'm going to cum.
Let's...
Me too, I love you too.
Here I go!
Cum inside me.
I'm cumming...
Let's cum together!
Santa-san...
One year later
Thank you.
You requested for me again, right?
We'll be together from now on.
I love you very much!
Give me a Santa Girl
as a wife
Huh? Did we really accept this kind of request?
Our captain sure is cool.
She really is.
I want to start shooting arrows already.
Yeah.
Kohinata, enough blabbering over there!
We'll start doing some running once the first
years are done with weight training!
Understood, I'm sorry.
Love-Bow
The Love-Shot Maiden
~How to aim to captivate her~
No, no!
I mustn't think of anything unnecessary.
I need to focus.
As I thought, you're still here practicing.
Wh-What's the matter, Kohinata?
Did you forget something?
Well, I just thought I haven't been lovey-dovey
with my girlfriend lately.
No, what if someone sees us here?
Everyone already went home a while back.
Just a little.
Oh yeah, that girl is just a classmate, okay?
Wh-What are you trying to say?
Just making things clear since you seem to have misunderstood.
The one I love, is only you, Yumika.
Saying my name so informally like that is unfair, Kohinata.
How cute.
It's completely the opposite of what
you usually show during practice.
I really think this isn't the appropriate place for this!
Should I really stop?
N-No...
Don't stop.
Please, go all the way.
I was actually only thinking of you the whole time I was practicing.
When you start talking to other girls,
I start to get jealous, and my mind starts to go crazy.
The way you beg for it like that,
and how your pussy is already wet and exposed,
there's just no way for me to hold back.
I think I left it in the clubroom.
Are you for real?
The lights are still on in the shooting hall.
Is someone there?
H-Hey!
Sorry, but your breasts are really bulging, so...
Huh, it's not here.
Was it in the classroom?
Your locker is a total mess.
Please leave already.
If you don't, I'm going to lose my mind.
Hurry, I'm already starting to crave his dick.
My pussy wants to be fucked already.
Yu-Yumika, you can't move like that!
It's in!
More... it's still not all the way in.
Ko-Kohinata...
You can't, Yumika!
Hold it in!
Or I might start fucking you.
You've already made things worse.
And this is all your fault.
My womb is being pushed inside...
Your insides are rubbing me slowly.
This is bad...!
Hey, did you just hear someone over there?
Go and take a look yourself.
No, I'm scared.
Sorry, I'm about to cum.
I can't hold it in anymore.
My club members might just see me cum as I get cummed inside.
Oh, there it is.
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
That was scary.
I guess we really can't have sex at school.
Let's just go home already.
Yumika?!
I won't just let this end.
Sorry, Kohinata,
but I really don't think I can stop myself at this point.
Just let me have another taste of your dick, please!
I-It's going to get hard again if you keep sucking me like that.
Th-This is intense.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
She's going to squeeze out all of my cum!
Deicious...
I just came twice.
Yumika, has your horniness subsided already?
It hasn't even subsided a bit...
Sh-Should we really go home first?
The combined smell and taste of his dick and cum,
just made my pussy want it more!
I might just fuck you real hard,
depending on how you plead to me.
I beg of you!
Fuck me once more!
I want it inside my pussy!
Please make a complete mess of me with your dick!
Then I shall do as my captain says.
I'm not your captain right now.
I'm, I'm completely yours, Kohinata.
So please call me Yumika.
Sorry about that, Yumika.
Whenever I call you Yumika,
your pussy seems to squeeze me even tighter.
You're cute, Yumika.
The cool Yumika during practice,
and the erotic Yumika who doesn't want to let go of my dick,
I love them both.
I'm happy.
My pussy just keeps on cumming with your love.
Your cumming pussy is so wet, and if feels so good.
I'm happy, just keep on stirring me.
I'm cumming, I feel like cumming as you push inside.
I love you, I love you!
I'm going to cum already.
Cum, just cum!
I'm going to take everything inside me!
His cum is filling me inside.
And it feels so warm.
I love you.
I love you very much.
I just keep on cumming.
It just won't stop...
Yesterday, right here, Kohinata and I...
Are you remembering it?