I don't understand this question at all.
This makes me sick.
It's useless for me to plan a future when I can't
even do basic math and writing.
I wonder if my friends are enjoying Karaoke
now? How nice!
What am I doing here in the classroom alone?
I'm wasting my time.
How boring this textbook is!
Why not an animation textbook?
What? I saw something moved.
Maybe I was wrong.
I don't want to stay here... ...but I need to answer
these questions. I don't feel good.
I should keep going.
Something is here.
This power... but...
Oh, shit...
This might be...
Maybe...
Is it an evil spirit?
Oh, shit... it's coming to the school.
I hope it is not a pervert.
No... It looks like a man.
... and his eyes have erotic nature.
I don't like this.
No...
Hey girl... what are you saying to yourself?
I didn't come here to hear your opinions.
These days many young girls are so willful.
Shut up. Don't preach to me, damn it.
Like my teacher... You don't study at all...
You don't understand high school math,
do you?
High school math?
If you are good at studying,
why were you kept after school? Alone?
You look stupid, like a little stupid shit.
Yeah... you don't need to study?
...you can use your skills to get good grades.
Well, you won't see my skills. You're ugly...
Shit, what the fuck are you talking about?
I'm getting mad...
When I'm in a good mood,
I can have a conversation.
But... cause of you,
I'm going into attack mode now.
I'm gonna destroy an evil spirit.
Hey, girl. I know your attacking patterns already.
I have your energy in my body. I'm energy itself.
I'm like a big condenser.
...so, I can release my energy all at once.
Take this, girl!
What happened?
It's not the same energy...
You are not used to getting this, huh?
Take it more...
No... I'm losing my power...
I cannot hold in any longer...
Even though you have ESP, without a shield,
you are just a regular girl.
That's it...
Pray for yourself.
Good, that's it. You could have saved your clothes,
but you were against me in the beginning.
What a view! You are all naked.
I like it this way better.
Nice.
Even though you've got ESP, your body is just like
a regular girl. You got long legs and nice breast.
S-Shut up.
Are you still a virgin?
I don't think so.
...but your pussy is still pink, like a virgin color.
S-Shut up!
Coward! You don't fight fair?
What the fuck are you saying?
I'm the one with ESP.
What's wrong with me using my power?
Because you are so weak, you cannot move.
You shouldn't do this to a girl.
Pervert!
Let me get down. This is foul.
Are you damn? Don't be so cute, girl.
How many men have you beaten so far?
Don't be overconfident in your powers.
No good... what should I do?
This fucker may molest me later...
No... His cock is getting bigger...
he must be thinking something nasty...
What a fucking Pervert!
I can hear what you are saying.
Oh, shit... He can understand me.
Fuck, yeah. Let me play with you a little.
No...
I can change my own body, and I can remove
my body part and control it.
No... So ugly...
What a nice body!
I have been wanting a schoolgirl.
No, it's coming! It has a face and it's speaking.
No... it's so ugly...
Shut your mouth.
I'll make you fell good.
No... Don't come closer.
No...
It looks so delicious.
If you touch it, I'm going to kill you, damn it.
I won't touch it... just lick it.
No... Too wet... No... No...
What... what a heck...
I told you. I can make any shape.
Your nipples are getting hard.
Are you getting horny now?
Do you feel good now?
No... No... Stop it... Not so hard... Ah...
No... Not yet... Be ready...
I'm going to show you a new world
you have never experienced...
No... No... It's pulling my tits!
I thought so... you like it so much...
Ok, now... Take this... So much joy may bring
your death!
Go for it, my spirits.
Make her so crazy, she will die...
What a nice pose!
Do you like it? You may be fainting.
Woof... You like it so much, don't you?
You want it in your hole, don't you?
One of us is trying to get in.
Do you like it?
It smells your hole.
You're so wet, almost too much.
Here you go...
What a dog!
Your cum is everywhere.
How nasty...
Going, going...
Going into your pussy...
Is it a joke that you are the most powerful ESP,
who has beat us for a long time?
How do you like it? You have never felt an
indescribable pleasure like this before?
Your body is shaking.
I'm going to give you something harder now.
You are going to die now.
Going to die in pleasure is your destiny.
This girl is shaking, dribbling.
No... Ouch... No... it's still inside...
I'm going to fuck you with it.
Come here.
Please stop it. Forgive me. Please...
Super power on. Miracle Junction!
No...
Come on. Bigger and bigger...
Come on. It becomes double now.
It's going to stretch me... it's going to get big.
Come on, come on, come on...
It's getting bigger... It's going to cum...
It's going to cum...
No... No... No...
Come on... Ok... Suck me now.
Hey, do it better than that, bitch.
Good, good... Like that...
How do you like it in your other hole? Good?
Well... Need more? Ok...
Here you go... Super Giant Spin!
Don't moan. Just suck this, bitch.
Suck it...
Good, good.
I'm cumming... Take my cum...
Please forgive me...
What the fuck are you saying?
I haven't finished yet. Hey, moan...
Ah... No more...
Oh, I see. You want more...
Ok... You want my dick in your ass, uh...
No... I don't want it...
You have a small ass hole...
It'll be stretched out when I'm through with you...
Please stop it. Please.
I don't like it. Please...
Damn girl...
It's a rare for me to fuck a schoolgirl's asshole.
Here you go.
My 1st asshole... What a tight...
So tight... good...
Good... I cannot stop...
Too tight...
Cumming...
I haven't cum yet, bitch. Ready?
No... Stop it... It's enough...
Fuck you.
I have my extra super power and it's growing.
...but you have become skinny.
Shut up.
...like she says,
I have power but it is at its limit.
I cannot hold it longer, but I have to finish this.
Ok... I need to end this.
W-What's that?
How do you like it?
I told you I can change my body.
No...
Do you like it?
Do you like to get fucked by yourself?
No more... Forgive me...
I don't remember how many times I came but...
I like your tight pussy.
You are going to destroy yourself.
You are going to die.
Finally I am going to win after such a long battle.
How do you like it?
This is your breast. Can you feel it?
My breast...
Yup... Your breast... Is it not soft?
Soft...
...and who's dick is in your pussy?
Say it.
That's me.
That's your dick, uh...
Well, so you are playing with yourself?
No... That's not... No...
You going to die...
Come on... Die...
You are getting fucked by your dick.
You get it?
I don't know... No...
I'm asking you...
No... No...
This is Manami.
I did it. She is insane now.
I won. I did it.
It's over. I did it.
I have become the strongest ESP!
Someone is here.
I need to change...
Wow... I cannot...
Oh... I see... I used all my power...
Shit, what should i do?
Manami, what are you doing?
No... Oh... No...