Leave me alone already.
Are you sure that's what you want to say?
Itsuki-chan...
Hi-Hiyori-chan...
Look, there's more than ten rounds left.
Ow, ow...
Oh, you're there.
Non-existent person.
I'm so sorry about that.
I didn't really notice you.
Hmph.
Itsuki-chan.
Hiyori-chan.
This is strange.
Eh?
I completely lost.
I love you.
I was really happy when you also told
me that you loved me, and yet...
I still lost.
Me too.
Eh?
Love can be so painful, right?
Yeah.
Touch mine too.
Itsuki-chan.
I'm cumming.
Oh no!
Hiyori-chan, Hiyori-chan!
Hiyori-chan...
It's alright.
You, and even your tentacles,
I'm willing to accept you both.
I'll accept them so that they'll never
attach themselves to another host.
Hiyori-chan...
Why do I have to be the one to get it?
Is someone there?
Must be my imagination.
What is this?
I've been waiting, Terashima-san.
Nonohara.
Nonohara Rena.
That is my name.
The one who will rule over you from now on.
What are you saying?
That thing you are stepping on,
that's my tentacle.
What's happening?
Hey, let me go!
I really want to see,
that face of yours twisted in humiliation.
What?
I wonder how it feels to be taken over by someone
who you're so used to making fun of.
Now then, let us enjoy this.
Stop this...
What a lovely expression.
My tentacles have become really lively.
It's thick, too thick!
It's getting torn up, it's getting ripped apart!
No, no...!
No!
That looks fantastic.
Pleasure, is the one thing that all humans bow down to.
You want me to do more pleasurable things... right?
Yes.
I want you to help me, okay?
Just who sent this?
I wonder what this is?
Fujimori Hiyori, Murasawa Itsuki, I know your secrets.
If you don't want me to tell anyone,
then go to the old school building.
I've been waiting.
You...
Nonohara-san?
A tentacle, this can't be...?
Itsuki-chan!
You two are so unfair.
Trying to keep these wonderful tentacles to yourselves...
Th-That's...!
Try not to resist, okay?
If you do...
...Then Murasawa might just break down.
What should I do?
Now that's ten.
You did really well, Fujimori-san.
That's too bad.
You're now part of us.
You came that many times.
It felt really good, right?
Fujimori-san, your insides feel amazing.
Fujimori-san looks like she's having a great time.
Let's pleasure ourselves too.
Pleasure will slowly creep into your mind,
and pretty soon, your brain will just stop thinking.
Look carefully.
Love is nothing in the face of pleasure.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
It feels good, it feels good...
More... more...
Give me more!
I can't hear you.
Say it louder.
No...!
Give me more!
Rape me more with your tentacle dicks!
Sad?
But, you got horny with them.
And you're really wet.
No, no...!
It, it feels good!
Now, let's all let ourselves give in to the pleasure.
Pleasure's offspring
Tentacle dicks, tentacle dicks!
Give me more of it...
Pleasure will slowly creep into your mind,
and pretty soon, your brain will just stop thinking.
Everything will just melt into the pleasure's offspring.
Forever, and ever...
I don't want to be human anymore.