Oh God!
It feels so good!
More!
I'm scared!
Save me!
Kei-chan!
What's the matter all of a sudden?
As soon as someone got back, you...
But thank goodness.
I thought that you might never wake up again.
No, not my boobs!
Ow! Kei-chan, that hurts!
No, don't do it like that!
My pussy is so happy that it's filled with
your cock that it's twitching with joy!
They feel so good! My boobs feel so good!
You're stabbing into my nipples the same
way your dick is stabbing into me!
I can feel your dick getting bigger inside me!
I can tell you're gonna cum!
Stop!
Please, stop!
S-Stop!
S-Save me!
Your cum is pouring into my pussy!
There's so much semen coming out.
With this, I'll become the savior's...
Kei-chan...
I really love you!
Awake now?
Rinne?
Where have you been all this time?
Where's Nemu?
When Manaka-san went to go get help...
She never came back, so I went out to look for her.
What about Kanae?
When I came back, she was nowhere to be found.
She was following me, and then...
Does it still hurt?
That memory hurts.
The paradise we desire is only a holy ritual away.
The mother of the savior is... Byakuya Rinne?!
Somebody, help me!
Let me go!
P-Please, take it out! Take it out!
My insides are already full!
Please, no more semen!
Good God...
What's going on?
Help me!
Mom! Dad!
I like those looks on your faces.
I'm going to take everything you've been working
so hard for and crush it right before your eyes.
Nemu... No way...
That's right. It was all my doing.
The game in the underground facility...
And this hell on the surface as well.
I... I don't believe you.
So, how do you feel now that you know the truth?
Hate me? Want to kill me?
Don't give me that crap!
That wasn't a game! People died!
And you took advantage of it
to get "close" with the victims.
Am I wrong?
That's why I like you.
There's no "normal" life for you to return to anymore.
But don't worry, there's a new world, right here.
The world you yearned for in your heart.
A world where all of your desires can be fulfilled!
I made this world just for you, you know?
And what makes you think I'll just go along with this?
You're cute even when you're angry.
But unfortunately, you're in no position to defy me.
Kei-cha'n, run!
Kanae?!
Don't!
Wait.
Rinne?
You think you can go against these numbers?
Is Hokari-san really that important to you?
If you want to save her...
Let's see...
Rape Byakuya-san.
Right here, right now.
Here, I'm the law.
All I want to see is someone in pain.
I can have Hokari-san raped instead if you like.
No!
But I can't just...
It's fine...
All you have to do is rape me.
I don't mind.
What's with that pathetic excuse of a penis?
You won't get it done like that.
Rinne?
Don't worry. We'll figure something out.
Rinne...
All right, that should be good.
So he'll rape one of his friends if it means saving you.
How fitting.
It's making such dirty noises.
Your dick is reaching all the way to my womb!
It kinda hurts.
I'm about to...
Don't worry. Just cum inside.
B-But...
It's fine. This way, I'm sure she'll be saved.
Cum! Cum in my pussy!
Fill me to the brim with your hot semen!
Make me pregnant with your semen!
That was great, Keisuke!
You're nothing more than a beast
that only knows how to fuck!
My pussy is overflowing with your semen.
Okay, now let her go.
All right, I'll let her off easy.
I'll let her off with just being cummed in once.
No!
Stop it!
What's going on?!
Who the hell are these guys?!
Get 'em!
The pain of the earth is our pain.
The pain of the earth is our family.
The pain of the earth is our family...
Kei-chan!
Kanae! Thank God!
I've planned and waited so long for this day.
This school...
No...
The whole world shall be freed.
We've waited and endured for so long.
We welcome this day of reckoning with open arms.
The fearsome tyranny has ended.
We have been freed.
However, this is not the end.
We now aim for something much higher.
We have nothing left to fear.
Now, let us go forth!
The pain of the world is our nourishment!
From the pits of hell to paradise!
– What the hell is going on? This is almost like a cult.
– From the pits of hell to pardise!
From the pits of hell to paradise!
Manaka Nemu...
Your reign of fear has been deemed as sin of the Devil.
We are going to pull the Devil inside you out.
Stop it! This is just abuse!
You're wrong. This is a purification ritual.
This is our faith's beliefs. My mother's beliefs.
Once she admits her sins and receives
divine punishment, she will be purified.
We can expel the Devil inside of her.
It hurts! The semen is soaking into me!
There's no time for rest.
The purification ritual lasts for three days.
The time has come.
We shall now open the first door.
And now, the second door.
This is my mother, Kyousa-sama.
I've inherited my mother's will
and will guide my people to paradise.
Takato Keisuke, you were brought here by my mother.
You are to father the savior.
What?
When I saw the mark on you,
I immediately understood.
I understood that this was the will of God.
I-I have no idea what you're talking about.
It's okay if you don't remember.
You're necessary...
to me.
I am going to fulfill your destiny
as the herald of the new world.
Now let us begin the holy ceremony!
No! Kei-chan! Kei-chan!
No! Stop!
Stop!
I-I'm...
Finally remembered?
You also did this with my mother long ago.
Yes, my mother raped you and bore your child.
And then I was born.
Th-That can't be true...
But I couldn't become the savior.
The child my mother bore was supposed to be male.
If I was born a man, I would've been
the savior, and no one would have died.
We all would have gone to paradise.
I'm nothing but a failure! An incomplete mess!
No, you're wrong.
There's no such thing as a savior!
All you're doing is just repeating what your mom did!
I'm repeating what my mother did?
This isn't right.
Come with me.
I'm sure we can find our own paradise together.
I'm different than her!
I'm definitely going to give birth to the savior!
Rinne...
So, get me pregnant.
Let me do what mother couldn't.
Let me bear your child.
I'm going to become the mother of the savior!
It feels so good! Your dick feels so good!
What about you? Does my pussy feel good?
Your dick is so big, hard, and hot.
It's so wonderful!
More! Thrust it in me deeper! Fuck me harder!
Mess my pussy up!
I...
Do it. Cum inside my pussy with your dick!
Cum! Cum!
Spray all of your cum into me!
Make me pregnant!
Please impregnate me!
I can feel it! I can really feel it!
I can feel your cum...
flowing into my womb.
Your child... The savior...
I don't know if I can reason with her...
In any case, you should run.
But, Kei-chan...
I promise I'll find you once this is all over.
Manaka-san's gone now.
I thought you were busy punishing people.
You're purifying Nemu of her sins aren't you?
It's not that important.
You're all that matters.
It's your duty to become the father of the savior.
And also...
It's okay if we have more than one savior...
Please let me bear a savior as well!
Open your eyes! This isn't right!
There's no such thing as a savior or paradise!
This is amazing! My pussy's being stirred up!
I can feel the life of the savior pouring inside of me!
Congratulations. Now, you too are the mother of a savior.
Please give me a savior as well!
The children will lead us to paradise.
Please let me bear a savior!
Thank you very much.
So good! It feels so good!
Your dick is reaching all the way to my womb!
It's spreading my pussy so wide!
I-I'm cumming...
Cum inside me already! Cum! Cum! Cum!
Hurry!
Let me bear your child!
You're cumming! You're gonna cum, right?!
What a waste...
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much for your seed!
I will definitely bear a child!
Byakuya-sama! Byakuya-sama!
Apologize like you mean it!
We are the scum of the world!
Please cleanse us of our sins, Byakuya-sama!
In order to enter the holy grounds,
you must be purified of all sin.
Through the punishment called pain,
you shall be purified!
Thank you very much!
This is fucked up.
No...
Maybe I'm the one who's fucked up.
I heard that Kanae managed to escape.
I want to save you, Rinne.
I want to give you a normal life,
away from this messed up cult!
I don't care about paradise.
Even less about a "savior".
I just...
I really love you.
I loved how you'd never give up,
even when you weren't sure what to do.
And even now...
I still love you.
It's time. Stick out your arm.
That's not necessary.
What's gotten into you?
I want to live my life with you!
You've finally accepted your role
as the father of the savior?
This is so different than usual!
This is amazing! Your dick is so amazing!
Your semen is flooding into me!
There's so much that it's overflowing!
So good! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna keep cumming in you!
Does it feel good for you too?
Please give me the mark of my sin!
Please mark me too!
I-I'm so happy, Byakuya-sama!
More! Repent from the depths of your heart!
She's been purified!
That's so beautiful!
Please purify me too, Byakuya-sama!
It's soaking into my womb!
The cum that will create the savior...
It's flowing inside me, swimming all around!
You just can't wait to be born, can you?
I'm definitely going to get pregnant now!
I'm going to bear your child!
I love your dick.
I love how hard and hot it is.
I love the way the tip twists up my insides.
It makes me feel so good.
It made me pregnant.
I wonder how many times it has cummed?
I love how it's a bottomless well of cum.
Cum. Cum more!
You can cum more, can't you?
You can cum enough to drown me, right?
This is wonderful! Your dick is so wonderful!
My mother was right to choose you.
I wonder if she made the noises
I'm making that day as well?
This is great!
It's reaching all the way to my stomach!
The baby's surprised too!
Your big dick is going all the way into my womb!
It feels so good!
I'm going to cum!
You should cum too! Cum!
Cum!
Fill my womanhood with your holy seed.
Pour it in me and fill me up!
Let him drink it! Let the savior drink your cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
A little longer... Just a little longer.
Just a little longer and the savior
will be born to this world.
Nobody move!
Nobody make a sound.
If you try alerting anyone that
we're escaping, I'll cut her head off.
If we stay here, history will just repeat itself.
I need to take Rinne to the outside world.
What's wrong? Is it that thing again?
My wish...
My true wish?
What? Are you back to normal?
It is my duty to give birth to
the savior and guide my people.
H-Hey!
My true desire...
I...
I might be able to become one...
I might be able to become one.
With you, I can...
What is this?
I found it!
This is it! The door to paradise!
Paradise? You knew this was here?
I was chosen!
You and I, we were both chosen!
Beyond this door is paradise!
And we will be the first to inhabit it!
We'll be Adam and Eve!
I've been chosen as the savior!
I can lead everyone to paradise!
My true wish is right here in front of me!
Is this some kind of facility?
It looks like it was recently abandoned.
Th-This can't...
I was supposed to be chosen.
Are you telling me that there's no paradise?
Oh no...
That's right, we still have hope!
Even if I can't become the savior...
This child can!
It's a girl...
There's no such thing as paradise or a savior.
I couldn't become the savior or even give birth to him.
What did I do this all for?
It's over. You're free.
Now you can live a normal life.
Right there! That feels so good, honey!
More... Kiss my pussy with your dick more!
Hey...
If our next child is a boy...
It will be another girl for sure.
So good! I'm going to cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
There's so much of your raw seed
flowing out from my womb.
Hey, you know what?
I'm really happy now.
translator: hikarucon
timing: cockslider
typesetting: cockslider
editor: cockslider
encoder: penisthruster
quality control: fyurie