The Master has to select a keyhole within 30 seconds.
If I don't choose someone... everyone dies.
Just like what happened with the council president.
17,
16,
What should I do?
15,
14,
13,
Who should I choose?
Makiba Rika.
Eh?
Huh?
Me?
No, I don't want this!
Even if you're my senpai...
I'm, I'm...
It's my first time.
Aoi Natsuki.
I-It's alright.
I can't let the other students do this, anyway.
This is my job as their teacher.
Besides, you too, are also the victim here.
Right, Takato-kun?
Yes.
Makiba Rika, Aoi Natsuki and the Resurrected Visage of Hell - Chapter
Se-Senpai, I know you're kind so...
You're not going to do anything bad to me, right?
Senpai, you would never choose me, right?
I believe in you, senpai!
The meaning hidden behind those words,
was something that Makiba never understood.
That it was okay when it came to everyone
else, so long as she didn't get violated.
No...
...no...
Please spare me!
I'm... I'm going to die!
I'll do anything else...
So please..
Is she seriously still hoping to be spared at this point?
She's...
Se-Senpai, I beg of you!
I beg of you, please!
I want to...
...really see you suffer in pain underwater.
Keyhole: Vagina, Number of Ejaculations: 1, Note: Hard
No, no...!
My...
My virginity is gon-
This is terrible...
Makiba... so it is true that this is your first time!
It hurts...!
I'm, I'm going to die!
You won't die from just this.
It hurts, it hurts!
It hurts so much, please don't push it in anymore!
Don't call this 'it'.
It's my dick.
My dick is pushing inside you.
Please pull your dick out, it really hurts!
My pussy is... it's going to break...
It's going to break!
It's going to...!
I'm going to drown, so please don't push me too much!
I can't stop...
Raping women sure feels great.
Even fucking this rather young pussy,
is justified because after ail, they're simply made to be fucked.
It's getting even bigger...!
If it gets any bigger...
I think I'm really going to be ripped apart!
It's gotten bigger? You know what that means, Makiba?
It's about to blow its entire load inside you!
No!
If you cum inside me, I'll get pregnant!
Well, you're right.
But I'm doing it anyway.
I'm going to cum inside you!
No, please no!
Please don't cum!
I don't want to get pregnant!
We haven't completed the condition yet.
Keyhole: Vagina, Number of Ejaculations: 1, Note: Hard
Note 2... Push her head into the water until ejaculation
I'm cumming!
I'm getting cummed inside...
It's, its really pumping cum into my pussy!
No way, no way, it's really inside me!
It's hot, it's hot! I don't want this baby seed inside me!
Decision: Clear.
Makiba.
Why?
Why me?
Please don't do terrible things to me.
If you like me even a little, then please...
I...
...won't say anything like that.
If you had said that you loved me before that,
I would have been able to bear all of those things.
So you say that our mutual feelings would
have brushed aside what I'd done?
I don't know at all!
I don't understand these difficult things!
Because I... I...
I don't want to think of you as a terrible person, senpai.
We shall now have an intermission.
How good for you.
Making your own desires come true.
You've always wanted to do that to her, right?
And wanted to do even more terrible things than that.
So what then?
Looks like I'm about to see even more interesting
things as this game continues.
To think that such things,
are actually part of this terrible game.
How would you think things would turn
out if someone else was in your place?
So, having fun?
It indeed is fun, right?
I for once, am having fun, you know.
Which is why I won't spill it.
In exchange...
I'm not going to be your puppet.
I'll choose whoever I want to choose next.
Turn 2:
We shall now commence the setting phase.
The Master has to select a keyhole within 30 seconds.
I'm going to choose who I'm going to violate next.
To end this game once and for all.
17,
16,
15,
14,
What should I do?
13,
Who should I choose?
12,
11,
10,
9,
Jeez, are you listening to me, Takato-kun?
Sensei, are you the sweaty type?
I just got a whiff of your scent.
The scent of your wet panties, that is.
Please don't... don't sniff them...
Your dick is now inside my puss-
P-Please...
I'm still not that wet yet.
So, so...
Please do it more gently.
So, you're hymen's gone already.
Who was it?
Who was your first time?
No, no...
Don't ask me that, please...
Sensei,
your nipples are inverted, eh.
That's unusual.
I see that it's been bothering you.
It... hurts...!
Don't grab them too tightly.
My breasts are going to get ripped off!
Sensei, I'm about to cum!
No, you can't!
No, no...
Your dick is bulging,
I'm going to get cummed inside,
his cum is going to fill me up!
I'm going to have your seed poured inside me,
while you roughly fondle my breasts!
You're cumming!
I'm getting impregnated with your hot cum!
You really cummed inside...
Your cum is seeping deep into my pussy.
Cum inside While Bound Concentrate on Breasts. Number of Ejaculations: 2
We're not done yet, sensei.
I still have to...
...get cummed one more time, right?
While bound, as if I'm some wild boar that's about to get roasted...
While my breasts are fondled, as if I'm some cow...
I never Wanted to show myself to you
in such an embarrassing manner.
But, I want to see more.
Cum inside While Bound
Concentrate on Breasts.
Number of Ejaculations: 2
Your dick is pushing really hard!
My pussy is getting ripped apart!
No, not yet...
I want to see more.
I want to see more of sensei's pained expression!
No, d-don't do that!
I'm being violated...
My inverted nipples...!
They're being played with by his thumb!
Sensei, I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum directly into your womb.
Your dick is getting bigger inside my pussy!
It's going to burst out.
Lots of his milk cum is going to be pumped inside me!
It's coming out, it's coming out!
My womb is being turned into a cum tank by your dick!
It's filling up every last spot!
You cum feels hot!
My breasts are going to burn!
And it's even seeping inside my nipples!
I...
I was just impregnated by one of my students.
Even my breasts were raped...
What should I do...?
Decision: Clear.
Turn 3.
Choose a keyhole.
Makiba Rika.
Wh-Why does it feel this hot?
And its shape, it really feels gross!
You're going to give me a handjob, Makiba.
But I don't know how to do it.
I'll tell you how.
Also, you do this while saying this...
Do I really have to say that?
No way.
It’s your choice, Makiba.
You'll die if you don't.
No... I don't want to die...
I'm...
But...
I, I can do this handjob...!
I lubricate it, and then rub its tip with my fingers...
Something wet came out...
Is, is this what's call a Cowper secretion?
The smell is very strong.
Oh, the liquid is very sticky, what is this?
My hands are now very slippery.
The smell might be permanent and never get cleaned.
Now, say it.
I, Rika, with your dick, am...
...am very happy to be able to service your dick like this.
It's seeping through!
It's starting to stick to my skin...
I won't be able to clean this anymore.
We're not done yet.
Number of Ejaculations: 2
We still have to do this one more time.
Your dick is drilling me inside.
My insides are molding themselves to your dick up to my womb!
My, my delicate baby holding part is going to brea-
Please don't cum.
I don't want cum!
I don't need this milk cum!
It's hot, it's hot!
I don't want to get cummed inside.
Don't soil my womb any further...
I hate you, senpai...
Decision: Clear.
I don't understand.
I don't understand at all.
Why?
Why are you both good and bad to me at the same time?
I really hate you now senpai, but...
I already decided to loathe you,
I never wanted to exert myself.
I never tried thinking on my own.
I simply laughed, cried,
and asked people for help all the time.
Senpai never allowed me to do so.
He confronted me and was honest about it.
He was the only one...
Turn 4: Please choose a keyhole.
Aoi Natsuki
Muscle Relaxant
Please, I beg of you,
Don't do this...
Semen milk
Can I rest for a bit?
I am sorry about this.
Why are you apologizing?
If I put up a pained expression, I'm sure everyone will...
No, I'm sure it'd also be troublesome for you as well.
Semen milk
Please, let me go to the toilet.
Babies don't talk, you know.
It's alright.
You're doing well at what you should be doing.
You're working hard to save everyone.
Isn't that right?
Sensei,
sensei, you're just too kind.
The fact is that l am doing these terrible things.
It's okay for you to get mad at that.
But...
How can you be so kind?
I am yet to be taken down by just this.
I'm much older than you.
And I am your teacher as well,
which is why I want to protect everyone.
Especially you.
I'm not really worth protecting.
Having favorites isn't actually allowed, though.
So it might just mean that I am also a woman.
Okay...
It's okay.
You can rely on me more.
I want to heal your pain and suffering someday.
Sensei,
will you forgive me someday?
And now, we shall have an intermission.
There's a hidden passage on the other side of this hole.
We can get out through here?
L-Let's go now!
You're right, we don't have much time.
I'll stay here.
Eh?
I feel like I've been here before.
I want to reclaim my past, and confirm this place's true identity.
Ouch... my legs...
I'll draw their attention, then escape.
Kanae!
Wait, don't do something so foolish!
She'll be fine, let's go.
So this is the exit.
You can't.
You won't escape.
You must all be crazy if you want to let yourselves
be captured here and let the game end.
You can still turn back.
Don't move!
Capture everyone!
I won't let you interfere.
So you are part of the organization after all.
Sensei, just what are you...?
I've been investigating this place under special orders.
You're also the one controlling these chokers, correct?
What kind of joke is this?
It's no use trying to lie.
These are your brainwaves, right, Manake Nemu-san?
Out of nowhere,
aircrafts and ground vehicles just started appearing one by one,
and when I'd regained consciousness, we had arrived here.
Hokari and Byakuya have been safely rescued.
Well, let's just lay down and relax as they clean things up.
What happened to Nemu?
Knowing you, I knew you'd ask that.
It may not be easy,
but we should at least have her own up to what she did.
She never revealed any other details, simply
dodging the subject altogether.
Who was she really?
It's payback for playing with my body a lot back there.
Prepare yourself.
Rika, you see...
Can no longer live without you, senpai.
Please take responsibility.
Senpai, your dick, it feels really big.
My mouth can't take it all in.
This is the dick that stole my virginity.
How is it?
Am I doing well?
Your secretions are getting thicker inside my mouth.
The inside of my mouth is ready now.
Please squirt your milk cum already.
Pour it, pour it... pump lots of it inside my mouth!
See, even I can do it.
I drank all of your cum milk.
My, your big and stiff dick is such a...
I know how much you love my breast pussy,
but this cum is just too much.
You're not getting away from my breast pussy just yet.
Oh wow...
I feel like putting a tough stick in between.
More, more...
Let me slurp all of this cum milk over my breast pussy.
I want so much of this thick cum, that I might
even get my own breasts pregnant.
Let it out, let it out... let all your cum milk out!
Let it out, let it out!
My womb is being wetly penetrated.
It's deep, going inside my soft spot.
My pussy's being opened wide by your dick.
This outrageously thick dick feels amazing!
My pussy feels so horny from my student's big dick!
It's rubbing the insides of my pussy really hard.
My pussy is trying to suck your dick in.
Senpai, please, please give it me!
I can tell that you're about to cum,
it's okay, just cum.
Let out all your impregnating cum from your thick dick!
Cum inside me.
I'm going to squeeze all the cum out of this scorching hot dick.
Oh no, I'm cumming.
Cum all you want inside your sensei!
My womb, is happily drinking all of your cum, senpai.
This is the first time I've cummed like this.
My insides are already completely filled with your hot cum.
I'm still not sure what'll happen from now on,
well, I think things will turn out just fine.
So long as I'm with them.