What's this place?
No idea.
It's the closest place from the underground exit.
It looks like a storage room.
There weren't any other places to hide.
I see. I...
Keisuke!
So you guys carried me here.
Yeah.
You seemed fine though, so they
went outside to look around.
They haven't come back.
We weren't followed, though.
I don't think the one behind the game would just let us go.
Yeah.
We have to find the others.
Seriously.
It wasn't easy. I mean I got beat up
that time, you know.
And the person at fault was fast asleep
for a whole week.
It's been three days since the others left.
That doesn't sound good.
We'll apply disinfectant once more just to be safe.
The wound should be closed by now, though.
Thanks.
Wh-What's this all of a sudden?
Why are you getting aroused right now?
S-Stop.
Keisuke...
You took care of me by yourself, didn't you?
It didn't seem like anyone was coming back.
I thought it wouldn't be good to just let you die here.
And why's that?
Th-That's...
You were just on the brink of death, how
come you're so full of energy now?
It's all thanks to you.
Your dick is going in...
I-It's really all in!
What are you thinking?
N-No...
Don't move...
You beast! Not even choosing a proper place...
This is not the time for this...
Then why did it get in easily?
Th-That's...
It's not what you think!
I really was a virgin when we got to that room.
You turned me into this.
S-Stop! Not my boobs!
If someone comes back...
Isn't it a bit late for that? Everyone
has already seen you like this.
But your hard cock is rubbing me so hard...
If you keep thrusting it in like that, I'm...
It's coming out. Semen is pouring into my pussy.
S-So hot...
If you can spurt out this much, I guess you're all right now.
Goodness.
The dreadful games in the basement, the scatology hell on the surface.
The mastermind is... Our childhood friend!? Arc.
Help me! Help!
Please forgive me!
Please take it out! Take it out!
I-I'm full! Too much semen!
What's this?
What's going on?
Is this our school?
Help me! Dad! Mom!
I rule this world.
I implemented a new system in this
school and I'm its supreme leader.
K-Kanae?
Hokari-san?
That's right. I was behind everything.
The game underground,
and this hell on earth.
Th-That can't be...
Keisuke...
Kei-chan.
The normal life you're looking for is nowhere to be found.
Stop.
Stop this nonsense.
Please turn back to the kind Kanae I knew!
Hokari-san, why are you doing this?
You want to save everyone?
Okay, I'll give you a choice.
Me or Manaka-san. You have to kill one of us.
What the hell?! Like I can ever do that!
If you kill Manaka-san, I'll let everyone, including you, go.
If you kill me, the school will be free and you'll both be safe.
I wonder which one's better?
I'd rather die than kill you!
I thought you'd say that.
But then, nothing would change.
The school will remain as is,
and Manaka-san will live her life as the guys' plaything.
Hokari-san, Keisuke can't bear to make a choice.
You're the only one who can choose, Kei-chan.
I-I can't. You're both important to me.
Okay. Let me tell you something good, then.
Your memories about Hokari Kanae...
are all lies.
An affectionate, cute girl who only loves you.
It was just an act anyway.
Keisuke...
I'll ask you again, Kei-chan.
Me, or Manaka-san. Who will you kill?
What's going on? Why would Kanae do this?
Not all of the students are here, but there
are still around twenty or thirty of them.
We can't force our way out.
We can't run away either.
Not as long as we have these collars.
Damn it.
Do you hate Hokari-san?
I don't know.
What about me?
If you kill me, the whole school will be released.
You'll be safe too.
At least you'll be able to try and
find the normal life you crave.
But still...
Why are you having trouble choosing?
You hate me, don't you?
The answer is simple.
Then...
Then why...
did you look so sad?
Why the hell did you look so dejected?!
I don't even know what's the truth anymore!
Wait! I'm not wet!
Keisuke, it hurts! It hurts!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Wait! Stop grinding me with your dick!
You're too rough. If you keep on scraping my insides...
You're gonna rip it out!
You're gonna mess up my pussy for real!
No, stop. No!
Your semen is flowing in...
So? You still want me to kill you?
Good morning, Kei-chan. Did you sleep well?
I guess you were too shaken up last night. Or...
After all you said, maybe you actually
like Manaka-san's body?
If you've got that much energy, I take
it you can make a proper decision.
Every time you don't answer, I'll kill one of them.
Stop!
They have nothing to do with this, Hokari-san!
It'll all end if Kei-chan would just make his decision.
Well then...
Me or Manaka-san. Who will you kill?
Keisuke...
You can't choose, huh? Pity.
Say goodbye to the first one, then.
I'll ask you again.
Who will you kill?
S-Stop!
Geez, that's not an answer.
Once more.
Are you really that Kanae?
– Stop!
– Hokari-san!
We'll stop here for today.
Make sure you choose tomorrow.
Choose who will walk with you in this hellish path.
Why did it come to this?
I didn't expect them to be captured.
She probably wanted to use them as bait to lure us in.
Sensei was still alive too.
What was the point of surviving that game, then?
I killed them.
Entrance Ceremony
Huh?
I feel like I've seen you before.
Uh, I'm not hitting on you or anything.
Um...
Nemu?
Kei-chan...
You still can't decide?
Fine, then.
I guess I'll have Manaka-san do some work.
Hey!
You know what happens if you use
laxatives and diuretics, right?
A perfect poop-spewing, filthy human ring!
I know very well.
It was the same back underground.
You get turned on when you see girls suffer, don't you?
That's something about you I really hate.
You haven't seen stars before?
My name's Takatou Keisuke.
Yours?
Mine?
I'm...
My name is...
Looks like I'll have to punish you today as well.
Hey, what are you doing?
S-Stop. No! Let me go!
That hurts!
You're gonna rip my tits off!
S-Stop...
You're rock hard. Does seeing Manaka-san
get raped excite you that much?
Who am I?
Who exactly am I?
No! Help me!
You're gonna rip me apart!
Somebody, help! No!
No! You're breaking me!
You're breaking me!
My pussy has had enough. My body is tearing apart!
My ass is so full...
You can still get hard even in this situation, huh?
Yes! Your cock is great, Kei-chan!
It's rubbing against my womb! I love it!
I can see why Manaka-san became your slave!
In the end, you're just some pathetic
scumbag that likes raping girls.
You should just die.
Kanae wouldn't ride on me like this.
The Kanae I know would never do something like this.
It's coming out. Thick semen is flowing into my pussy!
Stop! You're killing him!
I didn't think he was such a bore.
Keisuke!
It's okay. Everything's fine.
Which one's the real one?
Give me back my memories, Kanae.
Keisuke...
She's not Kanae.
If she's not Kanae,
then I should just kill her.
I see.
But I don't want to lose you too.
Nemu, I...
Keisuke...
I'm sorry...
Huh?
It's fine if you don't remember.
I'm probably the one who dragged you into this.
What are you talking about?
What are you saying?
Listen, Keisuke.
The one making you suffer is me.
But I had to do something.
I know it was selfish of me.
That day, I obtained something for the first
time... something that I didn't want to lose.
I met someone who cared for me.
That's all I needed.
You're the one who, taught me about what's important.
I won't forget.
I'm sure I won't.
I can never forget.
I don't care who Keisuke will choose anymore.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
You two should be at your limits already.
If you don't cut this out, you'll both die in vain.
Well, if that's what you really want,
I won't mind, you see?
That's it!
Your hard cock is coming into me!
It's messing up my insides!
Ahh, cocks! I love cocks!
Cocks, cocks, cocks!
My pussy's being wrecked by your hard cock!
You came! I can feel your cum inside!
Your hard cock is tearing up my pussy!
I'm being ripped apart by your dick!
I'm cumming! It feels amazing!
I'm melting! I'm gonna go nuts from this pleasure!
It's coming out!
Your dick is scraping up my insides! I'm cumming!
Your hard cock is hitting my womb!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!
No...
No! If this goes on... If you keep tearing
me up like this, I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die!
Mine? My name is...
Manaka Nemu.
Why didn't you kill me?!
Cum! My womb is burning up! Amazing!
Thank you, Kei-chan.
I hate to admit it, but fine. You win.
You can have him back.
3 Years Later.
Did you save me, Mister?
Where are we going?
I don't know.
A place where the stars twinkle would be nice.
I love stars!
How do you know about what I like?
I just do.
I'm Takatou Keisuke.
Then can I call you Kei-chan?
So there are places we don't know about in this world,
and they're all bright, sparkling and filled with fun things?
Yeah.
Let's go together, the both of us!
It's in.
Your dick is in my pussy.
Does it hurt?
No. I'm actually happy.
I wonder why. I feel like I've always wanted to do this.
Nemu...
It's weird, huh?
But I wanted you to do it.
I'm gonna move.
It's moving.
Your hard thing is gently moving its way in.
Amazing!
We really are connected!
What's this? I feel strange.
Wh-Why? Your dick feels so good!
So good! Your dick feels amazing!
Does it feel good because it's yours?
Huh?
My hips are moving on their own!
Why won't my hips stop? No!
I don't want this!
It's like my body is already used to your dick!
Your huge, hot thing is too good!
I feel strange.
You're rubbing it against me...
It feels weird inside!
No! Don't do that!
I... I'm gonna go nuts!
Pee? I can't stop!
What? Something is... Something is coming!
No! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Hold me, Kei-chan! Don't let me go!
I won't.
Here I go.
Kei-chan! Kei-chan!
Something hot is flowing in from you.
It went inside.
This is somethings lovers do, right?
That means we're lovers!
I'm so happy!
Kei-chan! Kei-chan!
You might've forgotten about me,
but I haven't forgotten about you.
I won't let go of your hand this time.
Kei-chan, I love you!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: bis