I wonder what would have happened,
had you opted for a different choice?
~﻿Byakuya Rinne - The Cycle of Life - Chapter
30, 29, 28, 27, 26, 25, 24, 23, 22, 21, 20...
I have to choose.
Or else everyone dies.
Kouseku Keisuke
Makiba Rika
Hokari Kanae
Aoi Natsuki
Manaka Nemu
Byakuya Rinne
Kei-chan, I don't want this anymore.
Someone please save me.
Oh, it's only the monitor that came on, you know.
No need to be scared.
Umm...Rika-san?
Okay, th-thank yo...
Anyway, if we die, then we die.
I feel like teasing you even more when you show me that face.
That's enough.
Oh, you.
Rinne. I'm Byakuya Rinne.
I can't help it but feel like teasing someone like her.
Don't you get it?
I do not, and I do not plan to.
Oh, then why?
The capable ones should uphold forbearance to the meek.
She is the girl from the other class, right?
So that's her name.
Setting the keyhole.
The keyhole...
That refers to each and every one of them.
26, 25, 24...
I have to choose,
or else everyone will die.
Everyone will die.
What should I do? Who should I choose?
Nemu,
Kanae,
Makiba,
Natsuki-sensei,
and...
How can she stay calm at a time like this?
One wrong step and it will be over for us here.
Can she not feel anything in this dire situation?
She could be violated at any time.
Or maybe, she's thinking that she won't be chosen?
My pussy is being fucked wildly!
It hurts.
My pussy hurts, Kei-chan.
Yeah, I definitely want to see it.
I definitely want to see her doll-like expression
transform into that of fear and pain.
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2...
Byakuya Rinne. ﻿
Action: Keyhole and room designation confirmed.
Keyhole: Vagina
Why don't you look the least bit scared?
Number of ejaculations: 2
You're about to get raped you know.
Note: Hard
By a man you barely know.
I... want to rape Byakuya-san!
She still doesn't look the least bit scared.
Does she even understand what's about to happen to her?
Hard
Hard, eh?
That means I have to do something horrible to her.
I'll do it then.
I definitely want to see it.
Byakuya-san's...no, this woman's face as she cries and screams!
Why won't you cry?
Show me more of your pain!
Show that you are in pain!
This is it.
This is t]he expression.
I finally changed her expression, took her virginity away,
and raped her.
I just can't stop...this is her pussy!
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum.
I did it.
I came raw inside Byakuya-san.
Byakuya-san.
Kei-chan.
Action confirmed.
Analyzing verdict.
Verdict: Clear.
Clear, huh?
Of course it is.
How else would it turn out with that level of violence?
I'm fine. I can walk on my own.
What?
Well... it was taking a lot longer than I thought, so...
Are you worried about me?
Guess that's none of my business.
It is.
You are hiding a beast inside your heart.
Huh?
But, you are fully aware of it.
I am grateful that you have been paired as the chosen key with me.
That is why...
I do not care if you violate me more from now on.
Why are you saying that?
This game...
Byakuya-san?
No...
Confirming the completed actions and the participating keyholes.
Phase one complete.
Commencing break time.
Are you okay, Kei-chan?
You look tired.
It's all right, I'm fine.
Don't push yourself too hard, Okay?
Umm...if you’re okay With it...
I'm thirsty.
We have to find something to drink.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
How do you feel?
How does it feel to rape a woman?
What are you saying?
It feels good to fulfill your desires, right?
You've been wanting to do it, am I wrong?
And, you want to do something even worse.
I want you to choose the same girl the next time.
Why?
The show will get more and more intense,
as you choose the same person each time.
Senpai! Senpai! This room is amazing!
How wonderful.
I wish I could enter this room.
Drinking Water
Toilet
That rule, and these things,
everything was set up to have us throw away our dignity.
It was designed in such a way that we would
lose our reasoning and judgment.
How terrible.
We're already in this totally messed up situation.
That's right, but I'm alright.
Assemble in front of the gate within 10 seconds.
Please choose a keyhole.
What should I do?
Who should I choose?
True, I've wanted to break down, even violate a certain someone.
I want you to choose the same girl the next time.
I do not care if you violate me more from now on.
7, 6, 5, 4, 3...﻿ ﻿
Byakuya Rinne.
Thank you for choosing me.
I wonder what would happen if I insert this very large vibrator.
You don't have to turn it on.
Is it painful, Byakuya-san?
It's not completely inside yet.
It's...
I'm going to die!
I'm going to die!!
Prepare to widen
the womb for fisting
It hurts, it hurts...
My pussy is...
So you've awakened, Byakuya-san.
But we're just getting started.
Here we go.
My womb, my womb is...!
It's getting opened wide!
Verdict: Clear.
I think of this game as a trial.
Which is why we just have to move forward and go deeper...
Which is why I thanked you.
I see.
You are hiding a beast inside your heart.
Can you forgive me?
For the things that I have done,
and for the things that l am about to do.
Of course.
The beast that resides within you,
must have been putting a lot of stress on your conscience.
However, you must not forget.
The pain that your beast will inflict,
will be important to me.
I'll be expecting all those things from this point on.
More....!
More!
If you want to make me suffer,
then that suffering shall become my pleasure.
I want you to inflict pain on me.
Make me suffer, push me around.
Just like I wish to be.
If by any chance, you are ready to completely accept me,
then at that time,
I will request something of you.
I want you to come to the shower room.
I think there's something on its floor.
Something?
I've been to some place that's similar to this place once.
You mean you were here before?
I'll talk about it soon.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to hear it...
It's okay.
This is nothing.
There wasn't anything on the floor.
Did you really look hard before?
At that time...
If my memory serves me right,
then we might just be able to get out of here.
Outside, huh?
If you are able to complete the bonus game,
permission to use the big room will be granted.
What? That room?
The members allowed to participate,
are Byakuya Rinne and the Subject.
Will you accept?
I accept.
How do you want it to be called?
Penis? Dick? Cock?
It tastes weird. Like stinky cheese.
So this is the dirt surrounding the dick.
Dick dirt eating
I drank it all.
Golden water drinking
You feel aroused with my hair and hands. I'm happy.
Hairjob
This bonus game uses all physical
methods available to the subject.
Semen chewy gargle
I like this.
His entire dick is starting to feel hot.
The smell is starting to reek.
Release it.
You can cum.
Squirt it all on me.
Cum ﻿squirt
This is my thick semen shampoo.
Verdict: Clear.
Use that room with Byakuya-san.
Yeah, you two were the ones who worked hard for it anyway.
I don't feel calm at all.
Me too.
How did they manage to bring this food, and all those things here?
From outside, unseen by us.
Then there's definitely an exit.
Look.
I was watching the whole time.
The utensils disappeared before my eyes.
They're using this to switch our consciousness off...
I guess they really can do as they please.
We're being observed by whoever designed this game.
There is one game left.
If we've come this far, then clearing the game is almost certain.
You're right.
But I want to look for it till the end.
I thought you'd say that.
Now that we know that you've been held here before,
what do you plan on doing?
I want to confirm something.
About the outside.
Outside.
Is there something important that concerns her?
I am just full of secrets, aren't I?
Totally.
At first, we didn't really care about each other.
But halfway through, we started to
appreciate each other's company.
I wanted a new setting to be realized.
And I think I can, with your help.
Byakuya-san.
If you accept me as not just a carnal piece of flesh...
Of course I don't think of you like that!
Byakuya-san, you're actually...
I...want to know more about you.
The things that you like,
the things that you read,
the shows that you watch.
I want to know and do lots of normal things like that.
And,
this game has nothing to do with that.
The opportunity is exactly in our hands right now,
so I want to touch you.
Are you nervous?
A bit.
It's okay.
I am ready and waiting.
I want to be touched as well.
Byakuya-san.
So you really can be nice, eh?
Is it better if I am not?
No, I want you to stay that way.
My pussy is filled with the happiness of your affection.
Byakuya-san.
Oh yes...!
This feels good!
So affectionate sex feels this good.
My pussy feels aroused.
It feels like melting with your dick inside it.
I never knew I'd get aroused by being licked.
Me too, I never thought you could get easily aroused like this.
I think you already know more about my body than I do.
Yes, this feels good...
My pussy feels great.
It doesn't hurt.
Not at all.
It feels good.
Your dick feels good.
Your dick is rubbing my pussy hard.
I'm really feeling horny with it.
It's rubbing in and out, going deep inside my pussy.
Something...something is welling up inside me.
What is this?
That's an orgasm.
Your body is about to climax.
Orgasm? I his intense throbbing feeling?
I'm going to climax with your dick?
Are you about to cum too?
Yeah, I'm about to.
Then, I want your cum.
I want to experience my first orgasm with you cumming inside me.
Your dick is getting even bigger inside.
I can tell.
I can tell that it's about to cum, isn't that right?
Yeah, I'm about to cum inside.
It's coming, it's coming!
Something's coming...!
My mind is going blank!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum!
I'm really cumming.
My pussy is cumming...
While it is also being cummed in.
I'm reaching my climax!
Lots of it is coming out.
Lots of cum is coming out, and my pussy came for the first time.
It really feels good, the feeling that cum
is being poured inside your pussy.
This is the first time I was nice to you, lately I've been...
Don't say another word.
You taught me both pain and pleasure.
Byakuya-san.
Move more, I still haven't had enough.
Keep it inside.
I want you to fill me more.
Byakuya-san...
Oh yes...
It's making sloppy sounds.
Your cum and my secretions are mixing together.
I'm cumming again, I'm going to cum again!
My pussy is about to reach its climax again!
Is it this easy to cum after the first time?
Or maybe I just get horny too easily.
Me too, I'm about to cum.
Please cum!
I want you to cum inside me as I reach my climax!
I want your thick milk inside me.
Make my pussy really horny as I cum!
It's pouring inside me, flowing inside as I cum.
I'm being cummed inside as I cum!
Your thick cum is mixing in with the cum you just released.
It's trying to seep in inch by inch inside my cumming pussy.
We already did it two times, and yet your
dick is still hard inside my pussy.
I can't stop, I just want more of you.
I also want you.
I want you too.
Move more inside me.
Do it more.
My insides are being messed up.
Everything's being mixed inside.
It wants your dick even more,
and I'm about to cum again.
I'm going to cum again!
I'm going to climax again!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Your cum milk is pouring inside.
It doesn't stop flowing inside my horny pussy!
More, push it in more.
Rub it inside.
Fuck me harder,
penetrate through my pussy!
Your dick feels great!
More, do it more intensely!
I don't care, just let your dick go wild inside my pussy!
It hurts, and yet...
The sensation while you're pinching and pulling my nipple is...
My pussy is trying to squeeze even more!
I'm going to be deeply stained with your cum!
I'm cumming! ﻿I'm cumming!
My womb is already completely filled!
My pussy is getting completely filled!
It's tight!
Your dick just became bigger!
It's coming!
I know you’re about to cum hard already!
Please, release it!
Release it!
Release all that thick stuff from your sturdy dick!
Cum all your dick milk inside my pussy!
It's coming out!
It's still pouring in.
Your milk cum inside my womb feels so hot.
Your thing just kept impregnating my horny pussy.
Lots and lots of it came out.
My womb wants to take it all, but it just keeps overflowing.
No...
Byakuya-san?
I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear it right now!
Byakuya-san!
Byakuya-san, get a hold of yourself!
I wonder what would have happened,
had you opted for a different choice?
I am now the mother of the savior.