Fairy of the Forest
Whew.
I'll take a rest.
No!
What was that?
A girl screaming in the forest...
What happened?
I'll check it out.
After the decision is the act.
Damn, right when I was about
to ease my sorrow.
Too much drama.
Whoa!
What is this?
No...
What's happening?
She's hanging from the tree.
No...
Aah... no, no!
She's cute.
Looks young, but very
attractive.
Is this a bondage?
Maybe she's a masochist like I
dreamed of.
No! Mosquitos!
Mosquitos?
It itches! I'm so itchy!
Oh, she's itchy because of the
mosquitos.
I'm so itchy!
Um, excuse me.
I got my foot bitten. Will you
scratch it?
Huh?
It's so itchy I can't stand it!
Want me to scratch?
Yes, please hurry and scratch!
Oh, I see the bites.
Please hurry!
Her leg's so skinny, it looks
fragile.
Hurry!
Can I really touch it?
Like this?
No, stronger.
Ah... right there!
This one too?
That's good too!
Feels so good!
Then, this one.
Feels good!
Thank you very much!
No, it's okay.
Did your itchiness get better?
Yes, it's much better.
That's good.
Ouch!
No!
What's wrong?
A mosquito's on me again!
What?
No! Why did it land there?
Oh man, it stopped on her tits.
No! It's sucking!
It's sucking my blood!
Aah, it's getting itshy!
Shit, I can't just lay my hands
there.
I don't like this!
What should I do?
Should I jump and swat it?
Or should I stay here and
watch?
No, if I do that, she'll be itchy
and irritated.
No, it's getting itchy!
Oh man, I don't kncw what to
do!
Hurry! Don't be sluggish!
What?
Coffe is heavy for my
stomach, and $4 is expansive.
If it's $3.80 plus tax, it's
reasonable.
But with tax, it's $4.20.
$4.20 for coffee is out of my
mind .
Then for cocoa... What! $5?
This is expensive?
Wait a minute.
There always is whip creme in
cocoa.
The cost price of whip creme...
Hey, can you hurry?
You're so sluggish!
No, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
I'm going to change. Wasn't I
going to change?
I'm not me like before.
That's why I took my days off to
come to the mountains.
Umm...
It's the same like before.
Shit, I haven't changed at all!
Umm, excuse me, but...
Will you scratch for me again?
It's so itchy.
You got bitten already?
Please.
It's so high up there.
It's so itchy! Please scratch!
I guess I have to jump.
It's itchy!
Okay.
Right there!
Good!
How is it?
Thank you very much.
I feel much better.
That's good.
Yes.
Huh? Mosquito?
No, no, no, no!
Whoa!
No, I'll get stung and bitten!
I hate being itchy!
Help me, ah!
Go away, go away! No!
Help me. Help me.
Please.
She's cute. She has the charm.
A branch?
Oh yeah, I can use this.
All right, I'm coming to save
you.
Huh?
One more!
How's this?
For good luck!
Damn mosquitos. That'll work
on them.
Oh no!
I got a little too excited.
Wake up! Are you all right?
Hey yuo!
I'll get you down right now.
Shit, I should have done this in
the first place.
Hey! Hey!
Are you okay?
Damn, sne's so hot.
This is too much for a guy like
me.
Good thing we're deep in this
mountain.
I bet not one person come
here.
What should I do?
I wonder how old sne is.
Hmm, I guess I'll just look.
Just to look isn't too harmful,
right?
Gently, gently face her up.
Oh yeah, yeah.
This girl in front of me is
defenseless.
She's passed out.
You're the worst loser.
I can't hang with you.
Fucking shit. Girls are just girls.
Look at this unconscious girl.
In a few years, she'll become a
gold digger.
Before that happens, I'll teach
her about men.
She'll be aware of the power of
men.
There, let's spread your legs.
It's spread open.
No hair. She has no hair.
There, let me see it nore
closely.
Oh, wow it's so small.
I wonder if her small hole would
fit.
It'll sure feel good!
Let me get a taste of her.
She has a nice pussy.
No!
What are you doing?
You're asking what I'm going?
Who do you think you're talking
to?
Uh, umm...
You're a thousand years too
early!
What?
I said you're a thousand years
too early!
No!
You gold digger!
Take this!
This! This!
What you got? What you got to
say now?
What do you mean?
What? What you got?
What? Say something!
Umm, I don't know.
What, bitch?
You suppose to say I'm sorry!
You're in a good position.
I can see your ass hole.
No!
No, no...
Serves you right!
Girls take a piss and shit too.
From here. From here right?
No, don't touch me there!
Is this where you take your
nasty shit?
No!
There, it went in.
My finger is going in your ass
hole.
Right in the girl's ass hole.
Stop it, it hurts!
How this one?
No...
Huh? What? How old are you?
You're a thousand years erarly
to get wet, damn kid.
She's feeling it, must be feeling
it.
Damn kid!
You really want it? I can sure
give you it.
There, how's this? I'll give you
something good!
Please, stop it...
Sorry, I can't do that.
I give you good stuff!
Ouch, it hurts...
It's in, going in.
Ouch...
This is what you get! Show me
what you got.
How is it? Huh?
This is great. Feels good.
Yes, this is how girls should be.
All girls should suck on my dick
like they love it.
How's your master's dick like?
It's tasty.
Really? Suck, suck on it more.
Oh, you're good. I'm feeling like
cumming.
Your tail's swinging like a bitch.
Oh, shit, I'm cumming.
Hey, face toward me and
spread open.
Huh?
Just sit down and spread your
legs.
Yes.
Like this?
Okay, yeah. Now masturbate
there.
Huh?
Use your tail to fuck yourself.
I can't...
Hurry up, you dullard!
Yeah, you're a dumbass! The
worst loser ever!
How cruel!
I'm not cruel for shit!
Just hurry and masturbate.
You're going to fuck until the
stick becomes bloody.
You fucking slow ass bitch!
Ouch...
Move it faster!
It hurts.
I know it hurts, dumbass!
No, I can't do it.
Bitch, who do you think I am,
huh?
I didn't mean that.
I'll do my best.
Damn, look at her eyes.
I'm doing mv best.
Move it more faster.
This is the most I can do.
Fool! Stop whining.
No, it hurts...
Does it really hurt?
I can't do it anymore.
Little brat!
There, now it's all the way in.
Come on, now is not the time to
sleep.
Now the stick's in, the fun
masturbation show's starting.
Doesn't it feel good?
It's going in and out, see?
Say that it feels good.
It feels good...
Oh really? It feels good?
Then I have to do this more.
How's this?
So you like this?
I can do this faster.
It's going to even get faster.
I'm going at turbo speed!
It's gong in.
My dick is fucking a girl.
I can barely stand this!
Good, good, good.
You're so tight.
Are you having fun?
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
Good, good, I'm cumming...
Suck on it harder.
I'll cum all over you.
Oh, good. Feels good.
Suck with your effort.
You're good.
You're doing great.
The tongue wraps around...
Good, that's the way. Move
faster.
No more, I'll go crazy!
What are you talking about?
Come on, move your hips up
and down.
Shit, this feels too good.
Come on, move more!
Oh, there it is again.
And again!
It's cumming, cumming! I'm
cumming again!
No more, no more...
It's cumming, cumming!
Hey we're not finished yet. The
fun's about to happen.
I'm sorry. Please spare me.
I can't take it anymore.
What are you saying?
No more! I'll go crazy!
Shut up!
Now it's your asshole. Turn
your butt up.
No!
There, good. You butt is politely
facing this way.
No!
You have a tight asshole.
I don't like that...
Look, no matter what you say,
my finger's in.
I bet you want something
bigger and fatter.
Right?
I don't want it!
What? Are you denying my big,
fat cock?
No, no, never!
You little brat!
I'll spread your little asshole like
this!
No! It hurts!
How is this?
It's spreading! Spreading!
My dick won't fit in this still.
Ouch...
Ouch.
Like this! This!
Ouch!
Okay, it's going in.
No, no!
Stop moving around!
No!
It went in.
Shit, it's so tight!
No, no, no...
Cumming, cumming...
Are you finisned?
Huh?
Is it over?
Fool! It's going to start from
here.
No...
Come on, suck more.
Suck all over my dick.
Good, that's the spirit.
All the girls just come to me.
Bitches are shit.
I am the best.
You're thousand years earli to
go against me.
It's cumming.
I can fuck anytime.
I cummed again.
But, I'm not yet finished.
Hey, don't be resting. Get busy
sucking!
My next load is already ready,
you dumbass!
Nope, we're done.
What? You fucking bitch!
I said that your lifetime amount
of sperm is depleted.
What you bitch? You think you
can scare me?
I have it all.
This will last me another 60
years.
What? What are you saying?
Thanks for the meal.
You're were pretty strong, so I
was surprised.
Wha, wha, what?
Guys with no girlfriends have a
lot build up.
What? Who do you think you're
talking to?
Are you going to say that I'm a
thousand years too early?
That's my line!
What the fuck!
I am the fairy of the forest.
A fairy? A fairy?
I look young, but I'm turning a
thousand.
Thank you.
Oh yeah, you were going to die,
right?
Then, I'm out. Bye bye!
I can't handle girls.
Okay. I'll make trap another
60 years later.
Next time, I'll be bitten by bees!