I fell in love with her.
Friday, at the usual time,
at the usual flower shop,
she picked a few flowers, and bought them.
I wonder who she will give them to?
I instantly became envious of the lucky
man that would receive those flowers.
Watching her surrounded by all the flowers
as I walked home, was a treat for me.
When I saw her, at that moment I became so happy,
that I fell in love with her.
And she...
Panty-butt!
Umm... Shuu-kun.
It's really embarrassing for me to be
exposing myself like this every day.
Wow, this angle is really something!
I was hoping that you'd consider my situation, you know...
Nope, no can do.
What?!
This is the daily nourishment that keeps me alive.
I'd die without it!
You're overreacting.
You really have a fetish for butts, don't you?
Specifically, I have a fetish for female
butts that are wearing panties.
Hey...
My fetish is for panty-butts!
That doesn't really sound different, though.
No, it's completely different!
The panties allow this string-eating-pussy to exist!
For me, this is everything!
Stop, if you keep pulling it like that...
It'll enter my pussy...
It's being "eaten" by your pussy very nicely.
I can't get enough!
This line that shows the part "eaten" by the pussy...
Wonderful, wonderful!
It ended up like before after all...
Oh no, I'm...
Don't lick it like that...
Stop... I said stop...
No...
Then,
let's do this.
Ooh, this is...!
No way... It feels hot.
Your dick feels hot.
It's rubbing against my butt as it hits my asshole.
Oh yes...
Me too, its skin is hitting your panties.
More, rub it more!
This time, I'll be the one to rub it.
Oh yes, that's it!
The sensation of your panties rubbing
against the bottom is the best!
It feels good for me too.
That's why, I can't hold back any longer.
I’m putting it in.
Amazing... this hard dick feels really hot.
It's rubbing inside and hitting me so deep.
It's really amazing.
Yours is amazing too.
Your panties are still getting "eaten" by your
nether regions as it grazes my dick.
This sexiness that cannot be put into words.
I wonder what this is?
It feels even more lewd than being completely naked.
Yes, correct!
I can feel it too!
My arousal just keeps going up.
No, don t lick my breasts too much.
It feels great.
Oh no...!
I'm almost at my limit.
I think it's better to end this from behind after all.
No...!
You shouldn't do that...!
If you put it in too much...
This is too intense...
Shuu-kun.
My panties, my panties are going to get soiled.
That’s my favorite.
But it feels great when it rubs... oh no...
No, it feels too good.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, as it's rubbing, as it keeps on going into my flesh.
Oh no...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I just had sex while my panties were still on.
Now it's drenched with cum and pee.
I was pushed around till the end.
I thought about asking him to stop.
The dreadful butt-panty fetish...
Oh!
Oh yeah, that's it!
I just have to remove my panties from the start!
He won't be attached to his butt-panty fetish anymore,
so the matter will be settled.
No, I think that's still embarrassing in another way.
Ehh?!
No-panties!
Umm... Shuu-kun.
Aren't we going to strip first?
No, you're pushing too hard...!
If this keeps on my lewd juices will...
...will soil my clothes!
These are my favorite, you know!
Nope, you're not stripping, it's fine like this.
If you take off your clothes,
that'd just be plain nude, and not no-panties.
O-Oh no...
I really love this!
We really shouldn't be doing it like this...
This angle!
...and yet it feels very good!
Shuu-kun...
There, it feels very good there.
Shuu-kun, Shuu-kun...
Your butt is the best!
Y-You have started pushing hard again!
No... not this hard.
Not this hard...
If you keep pushing it this hard...
Oh yes!
Shuu-kun, it feels good.
It feels good, it feels good, it feels good!
I'm cumming, I’m cumming!
I'm cumming!
He did it to me again today.
I thought about asking him to stop doing weird things to me.
The dreadful no-panties fetish...
Oh!
Oh right! I just have to wear panties again.
He won't be attached to his no-panty fetish anymore,
so the matter will be settled.
No, that actually makes me really aroused.
*Pop*
Eh?
So you finally understand.
No, I didn't really mean...
Okay, let's do it!
Let's do it now!
Let's go!
Kneesock!
Umm... Shuu-kun.
It's really embarrassing for me to be
exposing myself like this every day.
Wow, this angle is really something!
I was hoping that you'd consider my situation, you know...
Nope, no can do.
What?!
This is the daily nourishment that keeps me alive.
I'd die without it!
But... it's really embarrassing.
Well, how about this?
I shall etch it into the wonders that are kneesocks!
T-That's...
It's a lot faster if the body remembers it.
First, we'll tackle the proper absolute thigh line.
The absolute thigh line, is the small line of exposed
thigh that is between the skirt and sock.
It tickles...
The exposed spot... here.
This, this spot is important.
Yes, this raw spot where the skirt and sock almost meet but don't.
I really love it!
Stop...
If you lick it like that... I'm going to start feeling weird.
Then just give in to your desire.
Your body is going to go crazy with this anyway.
This small area of pinched flesh is the absolute thigh line.
The absolute thigh line, it's really pretty deep.
Correct.
And those are just the basics.
From this point on, kneesocks will...
Kneesocks will...?
Will be our topic for applied sex.
Huh? What are you...?
You're putting your dick in weird spots again...
Oh yes...!
A-Amazing...
Your dick is as hard as metal, and feels so hot that it could burn me.
Yes, this is the excitement, the sensation
between the kneesocks and the thighs!
I even dare say that my dick would be
crazy if it didn't get hard with this!
Kneesocks are the best!
Oh crap, I really want to go crazy now!
It's okay, keep moving like that.
Just go on, and cum.
Cum and give it all to me!
The hot stuff is seeping inside my kneesocks.
A-Amazing!
Shuu-kun, you came all over my kneesocks.
I'm covered in thick cum.
It felt great, but it's not enough,
I still want some more.
Oh, but your dick...
I think I may have gone wild a bit too early.
But I'm okay.
I already have a way to get it back up.
Hime, please assist me.
T-This is...
I wonder,
it feels more lewd than just being naked.
That's right, that's what I feel too.
And I'm about to increase the lewdness!
I can't wait anymore!
Amazing, your dick became this big already...
Kneesocks are amazing!
It feels so thick!
See? And it's all thanks to kneesocks!
The smell they give off is drifting its way towards my nose!
Oh wow, oh wow...
Kneesocks are really amazing!
I know, right? It feels great.
Your dick is getting even bigger.
Oh yes...
Shuu-kun, you're penetrating my insides intensely.
I'm being fucked hard!
Your kneesocks-boner dick is making me crazy!
Yes, you're wrapping around me quite nicely.
It feels as good as when it was still inside
your kneesocks... no, it's even better!
You're moving intensely again!
Yes...
Amazing...
A-Amazing...
Hime...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum all over your kneesocks!
Cum, just cum!
Give me all of your thick cum!
I'm going to cum too!
Let's cum together!
I'm all drenched in pee and cum, but if feels good.
Sex with kneesocks...
I think I'm starting to like it too...
Oh yeah, it seems you’re only wearing kneesocks nowadays.
Huh? That's because I already threw away
my stockings and other foot clothing.
You said you didn't like the other ones.
What?!
No, no, no, I love stockings too, you know!
Eh? But kneesocks seemed so amazing, so I just thought...
Okay! We're going to buy stockings today!
I'm going to buy them for you!
Th-Thanks...
Stocking!
Shuu-kun, can we at least take the stockings off?
No, you're doing it too intensely!
The stockings are getting soiled.
They're getting drenched in love fluids.
But you still can't take them off.
This is what makes it great!
It's great because you get to soil these beautiful stockings!
N-No way...
I can't get enough of this!
I really don't think we should...
This angle!
It feels good...
Shuu-kun...
Oh wow,
it feels really great.
Shuu-kun... Shuu-kun...
Your butt combined with stockings is the best!
You are starting to move intensely again...!
Oh no...
Not this hard...
Not this... hard...
If you keep pushing this hard...
It'll feel too good!
Your dick...
It's getting bigger.
Oh wow...
I can't hold back anymore!
Your dick is amazing.
It can even get this big.
Your dick feels thick inside me.
Oh yes...
Your dick is rubbing really deep inside my pussy.
My pussy is, my pussy is...
Shuu-kun, no... I'm going to go crazy.
Shuu-kun.
Don't don't do that...
If you go all the way in I'll...
Shuu-kun, Shuu-kun...
Hime, I'm going to cum.
I'm about to cum!
I'm going to cum all over your stockings!
Just cum, please cum!
Give me all of your thick cum!
I'm cumming too!
I'm going... I'm going... Together...!
I'm all drenched in pee and cum, but if feels good.
Sex with stockings...
I think I'm starting to get attached to this too...
Oh yeah, it seems you're only wearing stockings nowadays.
Huh? That's because I already threw away
my kneesocks and other foot clothing.
You said you didn't like the other ones.
What?!
No, no, no, I love kneesocks too, you know!
Eh? But stockings seemed so amazing, so I just thought...
Okay! We're going to buy kneesocks today!
I'm going to buy them for you!
Th-Thanks...
Oh yeah,
before we started dating, you usually went
out to buy some flowers at the shop.
Who were you giving them to?
You see, those were flowers that I bought for myself as a present.
I always felt happy whenever I looked at them.
But you're not buying them as you used to now.
That's because of you, Shuu-kun.
You're the one making me happy now, Shuu-kun.
Eh?
Shuu-kun, can we do it again?