Hey Megumi, you know?
What do you think?
Hey, do you think that's...?
Ahh!  It is!
Kyaah it's the student council-
Ah it's true what should I do?!
You're such an inspiration!
That we'd get to meet you here is incredible!
Please let us talk to you!
O-okay...
You really are beautiful!
This is my older sister, Mitarai Keiko.  She's the student council president.
But, before she's the president...
You fools, I'm confiscating that!
No objections, right?
Y-yes!  We're sorry, president!
These disobedient students call her the Demon President
but on the contrary, there are many girls who adore her
and these girls support her everyday.
But, nobody knows Mitarai Keiko's true nature...
Ah, president...
will you tell us what food you like?
Food?  Hmm...
I love a large, thick wiener!
Eh, ah, that's kinda cute, huh.
Like an octopus cut wiener?
No, not seafood
a ferocious wiener...
Ferocious?  You mean like minced meat?
I-I like that, too!
It's delicious when it's nice and tender.
Right right, that texture is the best.
I can't hold on...
S-sempai?
Yes, I want to gobble it up, Noboru's wiener...
Yes, this is...
Noboru's Personal Gloryhole
Fella Pure:  The Animation
N-nee-chan, you're too rough-
Yes, this is my sister Mitarai Keiko's true self.
By the way, this is me, her little brother Mitarai Noboru.
Your penis is delicious as always.
Ah, Nee-chan!
Ever since Nee-chan learned the taste of my cock,
her all-time favorite hobby has been blowjob research.
We've been living together for some time and I've become her guinea pig.
Yes, both our parents are working away from home.
So it turns out like this every day.
As I thought, this drippy precum is...
When I lick your frenulum, my tongue feels rejuvenated.
Nee-chan!
She knows all my weak spots!
Your manly scent's filling my head!
This deepthroat blowjob's...  rubbing my throat...
Nee-chan!
His powerful ejaculation in my throat...
His thick cum's clinging to my mouth...
In view of the foregoing, I'll have to taste your penis over and over.
Onee-chan!
Lately the amount has increased, and the taste...
Ah, I think it's the same as usual, but
that my own sister would do this, it's definitely weird...
Noboru, can you cum again?
Hey, that's not... anyway you're always doing it yourself...
Don't get so flustered.
Today there's something I want to try out.
Nee-chan
Until now he's only cum in my mouth,
afterwards, if he caresses my mouth...
Caressing your mouth...
Nee-chan's tongue is warm
it's long and a little sticky
it's lewd.
Her lips are squishy and kind of stretchy
Was this mouth really devouring my cock just now?
What is it?  Nee-chan...
N-no, that's...
Don't laugh.
It's because this is the first time you're touching me there...
I'm happy.
I'm feeling it really strongly...
What's with Nee-chan?
She's super cute!
Certainly...  I'd never done this, so I didn't know...
I want to see more of Nee-chan's sensitive spots!
You're licking...
Look...  when you rub my chest
my love juices...  when you use your bare hands...
to rub me, my tongue comes out, and it feels so good
Nee-chan, you're rubbing my cock again, this is!
Stop it, you're rubbing me there, stop
Stop it...  wow...  this is...
you're rubbing me so deep, oh no
Noboru!
Nee-chan, are you alright?
Too rough...  even though I told you it was my first time...
Sorry...
Thanks to that, my mouth's all wet...
Take responsibility, and go deep in me like that...
I, Nee-chan's wet mouth-pussy...
I want to see more of Nee-chan's reactions...
the place I want to do Nee-chan the most
Is here!
You said it, you said it, didn't you, Nee-chan.
Nee-chan, too cute!  Make me feel even better!
Next I'll fill your throat with my cum.
But this isn't the end, Nee-chan!
Take my piss, too!
How is it?  Taking my piss feels good, doesn't it?
My cock's gotten a little weak, huh.
It feels good...
It feels good...  it's overflowing...
Nee-chan!
Th-that felt too good...  my pussy's gone stupid...
I can't be satisfied with just my mouth any longer!
Nee-chan
I want to see more of Nee-chan's pleasure!
I want to fuck her up and make her my woman!
It's inside.  Noboru's thick penis...  inside me.
Here I go...  Nee-chan!
Wait!
Wow!  What is this?  It's totally different from my mouth!
You're right, it's totally different from a blowjob!
W-wow!  Your penis is directly, directly touching my womb.
I'm going to cum again, Nee-chan!
Don't, you can't like this!
I can!
Noboru!
You don't have to push yourself, you can wait a bit...
I'm not pushing myself, I can't hold back, I'm going deeper.
I'm breaking!  I'm going weird, I'm going weird!
Here, I'll put more power in.
I'm cumming!  Even though you shouldn't fuck me there, my womb!
It feels, good.  Here, in my lower mouth, cum inside!
Deep inside, don't stop!
Th-the next time you cum, fuck me 'til you drop, since it's your fault.
You're the one who gives me blowjobs every day, now I'll fuck you with all my strength!
I've been coming since before, cumming so much!
I can't hold on anymore, a big one's coming.
I don't know what's coming!
I'm cumming, too, inside you Nee-chan!  Take it all!
Cumming!  Cumming!
Noboru fucked me...  where I shouldn't be fucked...
Fella Pure
Ah, it's Student Council President Mitarai
Even when she looks troubled she looks great!
She's the president, she's certainly worried about everyone's concerns!
Yes.  Today Mitarai Keiko has another experiment.
Tonight, sex with me!
How should I do it with Noboru tonight?
Should I use...  that.
Huh?  Mom's coming back home?
She called me at lunch.  She forgot something.
She said she'd be back later tonight.
Well, since it's Mom, she'll probably leave again right away to be back with Dad.
Why would she come back from Paris for something she forgot?
Hm?  What is it Noboru, are you worried?
I'm not really.  It's just
Ah, I see.  You're bummed we can't have sex tonight, huh Noboru?
Y-yeah...  That's right...
It's alright.
Since Mom's coming home, I know what we'll do.
Just leave it to me.
Wait, what's this?
There's seriously a hole here...
It's as it says.
It's a place for you to put your penis.
Since when has this hole been here...
Well, since our rooms are right next to each other, it wasn't hard to make.
And whenever you put your penis in the hole,
I'll take it in my mouth.  Isn't that convenient?
Even without this hole, don't you always do that anyway?
Wai-  Nee-chan...
But lately you've backed up, right?
W-well...
So from now on, whenever you want to cum, don't hold back and feel free to use me.
N-nee-chan...
I think you might get addicted to it...
And, being your toilet might be an interesting experiment, don't you think?
Despicable Mitarai.
No matter what you say with your mouth, I understand, Noboru.
You shouldn't be able to hold back anymore, so...
Now I'll become Noboru's toilet!
If there's this mouth pussy in my wall, I'll...
I'll...  of course I'll use it!
How's that?  Even just putting the tip through is unbearably good, right?
What is this?
Even though I know it's Nee-chan, just because I can't see her face it's like I'm using an Onahole.
If I use this hole, I'll want to feel her on my cock more!
I want to cum...  inside her!
What is this?  Even though it's Nee-chan's usual mouth, just thinking of it as a toilet
I can't stand how good it feels!
Nee-chan, this toilet's amazing!
I want to put my cock in more!
If you put it in, I'll keep making you cum~
She's teasing my cock however she pleases!
It's no good, I can't hold back!
I want to tease Noboru's cock more!  I want to squeeze out all his cum!
This hole's amazing!
Can you tell, Noboru?  How amazing this hole is?  Being your toilet is making me so wet, too!
I've already cum so many times.
I can't stand it.
S-suddenly you're sucking so hard!
You're going to make me cum in your mouth, you're sucking it all out!
Nee-chan!  Nee-chan!
I can hear her vulgar fellatio through the hole.  I can't hold back!
Nee-chan!  It's cumming.
My cock's gonna cum!
Cumming!
I really did it...  this hole...
Thanks!
I want to cum!  I want to cum in this toilet more!
This is...
Can you tell?  What this wet feeling is?
This is Nee-chan's pussy!
That's right...  this is another toilet for you to cum in, Noboru...
Let out lots of your cum in here, too.
Do as you like...
Look, hold on a little more, and you can put it in another toilet.
I'm home!
Keiko!  Noboru!
I just got back!
What?  The day your mother returns you're both asleep?
We've gotta hide the hole!
Oh no, I forgot to lock the door!
Older sister!
Long time no see!
L-long time no see...
Ara, what're you doing?
Just, rolling around a little...
Ara, is that so?
Rolling...  rolling rolling...
But your face is pretty red...
Are you sure you don't have a fever?
N-no, I don't...
It's because the sheets are warm...
Really?  That's fine, but take care of yourself, okay?
I-I'm fine...
Come to think of it, Noboru's door was locked, is he sleeping?
Is that so?  Even though his mother came home, how cold.
No, it's because you called on such short notice...
M-my toilet...
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing...
Noboru...  Noboru is...
Noboru, hey, Noboru, what're you doing?
If you do that now...  Now's not the time...
More importantly, how's Dad?  Is he doing well?
Your Dad?  Listen, before I came here we were downtown and ran into these punks
Your dad got so excited and beat them up...
Kyaah!  He's so wonderful~!
Is that so?
It made me fall in love with him all over again!
If I can somehow keep her from noticing...
Oh no, silly me, I got caught up talking about your father...
You're getting sleepy, huh?
Y-yeah, probably...
But, I'm sorry
We're just so busy, it's keeping our family apart...
It must make you both feel so lonely
Ara, oh no, it's already so late
I have to be back in Paris tomorrow
It's about time for you to go to sleep, huh.
Ah, yeah...
That's right.  You and Noboru don't fight now, get along with each other!
Y-yeah you don't have to worry about that, we get along super well.
We get along as well as you and Dad.
Good, thanks!
T-take care...
Idiot, Noboru you idiot!  Fucking me the whole time!
Without stopping!  Rubbing me inside...
W-well, I was holding on this whole time...
Noboru!
I just wanted to make you cum!
Just now, when Mom was here, I just wanted to do it!
Just now, you said to use you whenever I wanted to cum!
Nee-chan.  Nee-chan!
Doing me so roughly, even though I feel like he'll break me
it, it feels so good!
D-don't cum!
You're my personal toilet, aren't you, Nee-chan?
That's right, Noboru's penis' sexual desire!  I'm the place for his semen and his piss!
Then, I'll let it all out!  I'll let out all my semen in you, Nee-chan!
I'll show you my true colors!
Fill me up, anywhere you like, give me everything, give all to me!
Being a toilet's the best~
Thankfully Mom didn't notice anything and she went back to Dad, but...
This hole's dangerous, huh...
Yeah...  filling it might be for the best...
It felt incredible, though...
Eh?
Want to try using it one more time?
Y-yeah.
In the end, we couldn't go back to how things were.
N-Noboru...
Thanks for your patience!  This was my first attempt at fansubbing.
Thanks to [biohrd] for the raw.  Sorry for any timing or typesetting problems!
I hope everyone enjoyed!  Through penis, UNITY!
Mouth is the best after all!  -Fue