Did you watch that show last time?
I gotta get off at the next station...
So then Megumi you know,
Guess what she said!
Hmm what should we do...
Hey, could that person be...
Wow! Like I thought!
It's the student council president!
Mitarai Senpai, it's really her! What do I do!?
This is awesome!
I am so honoured to be able to
meet you at a place like this!
Please tell us about yourself!
You're really beautiful!
My elder sister, Mitarai Keiko, is the talented
student council president at school.
In addition, at school she is...
Ridiculous! This is now confiscated!
Cum in Mouth Festival - All the Idols are Licking and Sucking
No objections, right?
No... We're so sorry Prez!
With such overpowering presence,
she is called the demon-president,
and feared by the guys,
while on the other hand she's
looked up upon by the girls.
Either way, there is nothing common about this lady.
But other people don't know...
About the true nature of Mitarai Keiko!
Oh, Prez! Is there anything you
like to eat? Could you tell me?
Food? Let's see...
I love thick and larger wieners!
Huh? Uh, that's kind of cute...
Like the ones cut into an octopus shape?
No, not seafood, but, you see, the vicious kind of meat.
Viscous? Like the coarsely ground sausages?
I love those too!
The skin is crispy and it's really good!
That’s right, the sensation to the tongue is irresistible...
Oh, I can't hold back...
Senpai?
I want to eat it right now, I want Noboru's wiener...
That's right This is...
Noboru's Personal Toilet
Presented by Erobeat | http.//www.erobeat.net| #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Fella Pure
~Stories of the Mitarai Family~
Sis... you're too rough...
That's right. This is my sister, Mitarai Keiko's true form.
By the way, that's me, her brother, Mitarai Noboru.
Your penis is tasty like always, Noboru.
Nee-chan...
After knowing the taste of cock, her hobby
for life because studying fellatio.
And conveniently living with her,
I became her experiment subject.
Plus, with the parents away travelling,
We've been like this every day recently.
This wet tip is great of course,
But the sensation when the tongue rubs
against the sinews on the back is...
Nee-chan...
Damn, she knows all my weak spots!
This is wonderful...
I want it in deeper...
Your tip is rubbing... against my throat...
Nee-chan...
The ejaculation that hits hard on your throat...
The semen so thick it's gluing your mouth together...
In conclusion from those points, one does not get tired of
Noboru's penis no matter how many times you have it!
Nee-chan...
You've even been ejaculating more and more
recently. There's nothing to complain about.
I've always been thinking, it's definitely
wrong do have your sister do this!
Hmm? Noboru? You asking for more?
That's not it...
Besides, it's always Nee-chan who's forcing it!
Don't panic.
I have something I want to try today.
Nee-chan...
From now, treat my mouth as genitals.
I will open my mouth,
and Noboru will go from foreplay to intercourse with it.
Foreplay with the mouth?
Nee-chan's tongue is really warm...
It's quite long... and sticky...
it's really lewd.
Her lips are soft, and stretchy...
This mouth was sucking on my dick until just now...
What's wrong? Nee-chan?
No um... I mean...
Don't laugh at me but...
It was the first time Noboru did that for me...
I was so happy...
and really turned on...
What with Nee-chan today?
She's really cute!
It's true... I never did anything, so I didn't know...
I wanted to see Nee-chan turned on more!
My chest...
You'll touch those for me, too?
I'm so happy...
The stimulation might be a bit too strong...
Your tongue is rubbing against mine...
All the way...
My tongue feels good!
It feels good!
Nee-chan, my dick is rubbing against her pussy, this is...
Noboru... don't rub there...
No...
I can't...
Lick inside...
Inside... Noboru...
Nee-chan... are you alright?
Way too rough... I told you it was my first time.
My bad...
Thanks to that, my mouth is drenching...
You'd better stick it all the way in properly.
I... had soaked Nee-chan's mouth-pussy...
I want to see more of Nee-chan's reactions!
The part of Nee-chan's body that I know the most is...
Here!
You're cumming. You're cumming, aren't you, Nee-chan?
Nee-chan is really cute when she's cumming!
Feel more! Get more and more excited!
Next, I'll violate Nee-chan's throat with my semen!
But this isn't the end, Nee-chan!
Take my, take my urine!
How is it? Drinking piss is great, isn't it?
Although my dick will get softer...
It's great...
Nee-chan!
It's so good...
Monthly Oral Journal
My pussy went crazy...
I can't stand only having my mouth anymore...
Nee-chan?
I want to see more... of Nee-chan as she is happy!
I want to mess her up and make her mine!
It's inside...
Noboru's thick penis is...
coming inside...
Here I go, Nee-chan.
Wait!
What is this... it's completely different from the mouth...
It's true... it moves completely
differently from the mouth...
Amazing... it's coming directly...
Your penis is coming in directly....
It's hitting directly on my womb!
I'm cumming again, Nee-chan!
No, there simply can’t be anymore...
Yes there can!
No, Noboru... you idiot...
Stop forcing it on a person who
just can't take it anymore!
I can't stand up, I'm losing strength!
Then don't force yourself and relax, Nee-chan!
I'm trying to get in deeper!
I'll break!
I'll go crazy... I'm going to go crazy!
C'mon, I'll make you lose even more strength!
Cumming!
All the way to places you shouldn't go...
My womb!
It feels... good!
Even the mouth on the bottom love raw fellatio!
I won't be able to stop this...
It'll become a habit!
If my grades drop on the next test,
it's definitely Noboru's fault!
How can you say that after grabbing
me for fellatio every day?
I'm going to make you cum hard!
I'm cumming. I've been cumming lots!
No, I can't hold back anymore.
Something huge is coming! I'll go crazy!
I'm cummming, too! I’m cumming inside Nee-chan!
Cumming!
This is great...
I won't be able to live without Noboru's penis anymore...
Oh, the Student Council President
Mitarai deep in thought!
She's so beautiful even when she's troubled!
Of course! She’s the student council president, she
must thinking about many important things!
How wonderful!
That's right, Mitarai Keiko is serious
in school just like always.
Serious about having sex with me tonight.
Hmm, what kind of sex should
I have with Noboru today...
That's pretty good, too...
Mitarai - Mother
Huh? Mom is coming back today?
Yeah, she contacted me today.
Says she forgot something.
It'll be late at night when she gets home though.
Well, it's mom, so I guess she'll be flying
back to Dad in Paris right away.
Why does she have to fly back all the way
from Paris just for something she forgot...
Hmm? What's wrong Noboru? Are you dissatisfied?
That's not true but... um...
Oh, I see.
You're disappointed you can’t have sex with me tonight.
You're right, you're right, okay!?
It's fine.
With mom coming back, I've decided
on what to try tonight.
Huh?
Leave it to me.
Wait, what is this?
What??
There's really a hole here...
Quite self-explanatory here,
it's where Noboru should stick his penis.
Noboru's Personal Toilet
When did this hole...
Well it’s be a waste not to since our rooms
are next to each others anyways.
Besides, if you stick your penis in,
I'll always be there to suck on it!
Convenient, right?
You're always sucking on it even without the hole!
Wait, Nee-chan...
But you've been quite eager about it recently, too.
Well...
So from now, if you want to cum, go ahead and use me.
Nee-chan...
It could be surprisingly addicting.
Besides, doesn't the phrase toilet strangely attract you?
Just from the pun.
Whatever you say, I understand what
you're actually feeling, Noboru.
You're probably at your limit right now, so...
Right now, I become Noboru's toilet.
If there's a mouth pussy attached to my wall like this,
There’s no way...
There's no way I wouldn't stick it in!
How is it?
When only the tip is teased like this, you're
urge to stick it inside become irresistible!
What is this?
Even though I know it's Nee-chan,
just because I can't see her face,
it feels like I'm using a toy...
Using this hole... I need to use this hole to feel good!
I want to cum inside this!
What is this? It's just Nee-chan's mouth like usual,
but thinking of it as a toilet... makes it so good!
Nee-chan, this toilet of yours is amazing,
I just want to leave my dick inside now!
It feels like you could cum again and again.
She’s starting to tease me now!
No... I can't resist anymore...
I want to tease Noboru's penis more!
I want to milk out all the semen!
This hole is amazing!
I know, Noboru. I know the greatness of this hole.
Thinking of being used by Noboru as
a toilet is making my pussy soaked!
I've already climaxed several, times.
It's just amazing...
You're sucking too much so suddenly!
Your mouth and tongue are wrapping around...
Nee-chan, Nee-chan!
The vulgar sounds of fellatio I can hear
from the hole is exciting, too!
Nee-chan...
It's sucking... my dick inside!
Cumming!
This hole... is really dangerous...
Thank you very much!
Noboru's Personal Toilet
I want to cum...
I want to cum more inside the toilet!
This is...
Can you tell? This soft, slippery sensation.
It's Nee-chan’s... pussy...
That's right...
It's the other toilet, Noboru.
Let out lots of semen in here, too.
Do as you wish!
C'mon, just a bit more.
You're about to get to your toilet, Noboru!
I'm back!
Keiko! Noboru! I just got home!
What? On the day your mom comes
home, both of you have slept!?
Woah, she's upstairs!
No way, I didn't lock my door!
Big sis!
Long time no see!
Uh, long time no see...
Huh? What are you doing, Big sis?
Um, I'm just rolling around...
wee...
But your face is red...
Do you have a fever?
No, that's not it...
The blankets are really warm, so...
Really?
Well if you say so... but take care of your body, okay?
Yeah, alright.
By the way, Noboru's room is
locked, did he sleep already?
Really? Geez, even though his mom
is coming home. How heartless.
Well, you only told us last minute...
My toilet...
Are you alright, Big sis?
No, it's fine...
Noboru... this is... Noboru...
Noboru this is...
What are you doing?
Now's not the time to tease...
More importantly, how's dad?
It he doing well?
Dad?
Oh, you've got to hear!
I was shopping downtown and got into
trouble with a bunch of thugs, and...
Your dad just appeared like magic!
Dad is wonderful!
I see...
I fell in love with him all over again!
If I hold this off for now...
Oh my! I got carried away talking about Dad!
Big sis is tired, too, right?
Yeah.
But, I'm sorry... that we're always so busy...
and we're always separate, leaving you guys all alone...
Oh my, look at the time!
I've got to back to Paris on the morning flight.
I think I should go to bed.
Okay...
That's right, don't quarrel with
Noboru, and be good friends!
Don't worry about that We're really close.
You be good with Dad, too!
Alright, thanks!
Have a safe trip!
Idiot! Noboru you Idiot!
You were thrusting all this time!
How many times do you plan on cumming!
Until I can't cum anymore, of course!
Noboru!
I'm just doing what Nee-chan said!
Even just now when Mom was here,
I just really wanted to do it!
Right now, too!
You told me to use you until I was
satisfied whenever I wanted!
Nee-chan, Nee-chan!
Even though he's going crazy on me...
Even though I feel like I could break from this...
It's really...
It’s really good!
It’s coming...
Nee-chan is my person toilet, right?
That's right, personal for Noboru's penis.
Dump all your semen and pee inside!
Then I'm letting it all out!
I'm letting out all of today's semen inside Nee-chan!
I’m a toilet!
You can do it wherever you want
from now! Just give it all to me!
Cumming!
The toilet...
is the best...
The next day, Mom went back to Dad without
noticing what happened, but...
This hole is really dangerous...
Yeah... maybe we should seal it...
Even though it felt really, really good.
Wanna use it just one more time?
Yeah.
It turns out, we can't go back to before.
Noboru...
As expected, oral is the best!