Wet.
Explosive.
Welcome your body to a new zone
that will leave you stunned.
Various options to suit your desires.
It's the age where your preferences are easily matched.
If you're going to cheat, do it with an onahole.
The New Age Onahole: Type FLA 4545.
You in?
Orient Industrial.
Damn, I wanna buy one.
I'm Shijima Tarou, a college student.
I'm quickly heading down the path to living
a single life since I have no girlfriend to speak of.
This isn't bad, but... today,
I'm gonna make a revolutionary purchase.
Thanks for everything.
Just wait a little longer.
It was either work hard to get one or give up. That's just
how great this new item, New Hole Generations, is!
Fall in love with an onahole
The revolutionary, new onahole that the
Orient Industrial company introduced to the world
ten years ago was touted as being
one of the most lifelike experiences ever.
Some people called it one of the miracles of the century
and it instantly gained much
acclimation and enthusiasm across Japan.
Using the catchphrase, "If you're gonna cheat,
do it with an onahole", their popularity blew up.
Right now, it's not even that rare
to see people with onaholes.
Could I...
With the money I saved from
my part time jobs over two years...
Yeah, need something?
Yeah, give me the new generation onahole please.
Oh, thanks for your business!
Now you can buy it with the swimsuit seen on TV and a knitted sweater of your choise (limit are per customer)
Would you like it mailed to you?
Yes, please. The address written on my card
is the same as my home address.
Oh, do you think you could mail it immediately?
Of course, no problem.
Wanna use it as soon as possible, eh?
Man, I'm jealous. I need to save up money
to buy one too. You're so lucky.
Oh, well thanks.
But buying one for a college
student is a very huge hurdle.
Oh, sorry, I'm taking up your time.
Let me know if you need anything else.
So, why did I work so hard to save up to buy one?
It's because it's every man's dream! Isn't that obvious?!
Hey, Tarou-kun, come on, hurry up!
Also, she's really similar to the lady next door
I used to hang out with when I was little.
Hey, Tarou-kun, don't look!
If that doesn't make me want to strip
her naked, then who'd buy it?!
For personality, I'll make her kind and homely.
Her speech will be gentle.
All right, set-up's almost done!
Just a little more! Just a little more!
I'm gonna be so happy...
Sucks. Error~
Nope!
What am I supposed to do now?!
What do you mean by "sucks"?!
It's not every day I get started up with an error.
You're my master, right?
It sucks that I wasn't set up all the way.
Uh...
Well, hello. I think you've already met my body,
but it's nice to meet you, Master.
I'm FLA model number 4545, Naoko, the onahole onee-san.
Let's have fun.
What's the matter, Master?
You're a little different than what I set up...
Well that's because of the error.
Then let's fix it!
You can't do the setup again for another hour.
One hour?!
Yeah, it'd, overload the servers otherwise.
What kind of hell am I living in where I have
no wait an hour before I can use my onahole?
Don't cry, Master. Onaholes can understand feelings too.
But I guess you could still use me.
Are you... are you serious?!
But right now...
Both my pussy and asshole are out.
The adjustments for those two holes aren't completed yet.
Well, they're not particularly broken
or anything, so it might be okay.
I think it'd be better if you used them later.
So, for right now, you should...
Master, are you listening to me?
Doesn't look like it.
You can use me properly in an hour.
If anything were to happen, I'd be returned because
I'd be faulty, so you can't use those holes right now.
Okay... okay, I understand.
But, I'm happy, Master.
As an onahole, that really does make me happy.
Why?
You didn't even hesitate to try and use me.
You must have really wanted to use my holes to cum, huh?
All us onaholes love people like that.
We like people who think that
"It's okay as long as I feel good."
I'm a tool that was made to help you cum, Master,
so I like that kind of attitude so, so much.
Oh, I know. How about you put that on, Master?
The wireless headset?
Yes.
Okay, I put it on.
Hello, Master. Can you hear me?
Is this...
It's a listening device for when
I can't use my mouth to talk.
Is there really a point to this?
Of course there is! Didn't you want to have
a conversation with your onahote?
What's up with that?
There are guys who just tell onaholes
to just suck their dicks over and over again.
Onaholes have it rough too, I guess.
But really, you don't have to hold anything back.
I'm your tool, so I'll do anything you want.
It's better for the onahole too that way.
Please put it in your mouth-pussy.
Okay.
Oh my god, it's so warm!
Welcome to my mouth which is set
at 42 degrees Celsius, Master.
It feels like a bath!
Should I make it warmer?
No, this is fine.
I'll stroke your dick with my mouth-pussy now, okay?
This is amazing, my dick fits so perfectly.
That's because my mouth-pussy
is being made to it your dick, Master.
It'll feel good no matter when you put your dick inside.
I can use these big tits, right?
Of course you can. They're pretty warm too.
Here I go.
You weren't kidding. They're so soft too.
See? Now try sticking your dick out.
Like this?
This feels so good!
I can't get enough!
Now touch my dick with your lips.
That's an onahole for you.
I'm getting so hard just from putting it inside.
This is worlds different than any other
onahole experience I've ever had!
Being able to masturbate like this
even though I'm a virgin is...
So fucking great!
I'm cumming!
Keep your head raised like that.
But I want to drink your cum, Master. Can't I drink it?
This is awesome. This is so awesome!
I've still got more left, so take care of it, okay?
I can't stop myself!
It's not my fault, I just want to cum!
People might say I'm stupid for trying to make myself
feel good, but I wonder if onaholes are like that too?
I might've been a bit demanding before, but can I help it?
If she says I can do whatever I want,
I'm gonna do whatever I want!
She's an onahole, I should be able to use it as I want.
If the onahole wants to be used, isn't it better that I use it then?!
Oh god, I sound like some kind of bad guy now.
Do you have any other functions?
Hint: Onaholes don't breathe, so it's okay.
Got it!
What is this?!
This is one hell of a vacuum!
I'm cumming. Drink it up!
Please, I want more, Master.
Again!
It's your master's dick. Does it taste good?
Master's dick... so much.
This is great! This is so fucking great!
Master, I'm so happy!
Man, you really are an amazing onahole!
You're the best source of pleasure ever!
Please give me your cum, Master.
You're so cute!
You make me cum without even realizing it.
I want to do it with your pussy now.
Here comes the last one!
Aw man, you cleaned me up,
but looking at your face just turns me on again.
I'm so happy. You weren't even done yet but you
made me clean you and now you want to cum again?
That makes me happy.
You can cum inside me as much as you want, Master.
You don't have to tell me twice.
I'm gonna use this.
Huh?! Wait, Master!
What's the problem? You're wet down there, really wet.
No, I do get wet when I'm aroused,
but that's not why you can't use it yet!
But it's not broken, right?
Also, you're already really turned on.
Yes, but my pleasure experience
settings aren't complete yet, so...
If you use that hole, I'm gonna...
Hearing that makes me want to do it even more!
It's so tight down here too! I just wanna pound it so hard!
Let's see how far we can go!
What is this? Pee? Water? Cum?
I'm sorry for feeling good, Master.
No, this is the best thing that an onahole could ever do!
Your face looks really hot right now.
Do you mean it, Master?
Yeah, I do. It's the best!
Here I go!
Master, it feels so good!
I'm sorry for getting turned on too.
It just feels so good that I can't help myself!
So good! Master, I'm gonna cum!
You're cumming! There's so much
of your cum shooting out into me, Master!
Cumming in the womb Registration Complete
Confirmed cum inside onahole.
By utilizing the user's usage, the registration has completed.
Setup of the body has been completed
and no further changes can be made.
What the hell's up with this shitty piece of software?!
That's why I told you to use my pussy later.
You could've told me this was gonna happen.
Maybe it was all planned.
You serious? But, oh well, whatever.
Master!
I'd like you to take responsibility for the errors
that you made while setting me up.
Right.
Take good care of me, okay?
Y-Yeah.
You're so cute, Master! So cute!
Ah, shut up, you're nothing but an onahole!
From today on your name's gonna be Onako!
Onako? That's such a good name!
No it's not! Why do you even like it?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: akin
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч