Wet.
Explosive.
Welcome your body to a new zone
that will leave you stunned.
Various options to suit your desires.
It's the age where your preferences are easily matched.
If you're going to cheat, do it with an onahole.
The New Age Onahole: Type FLA 4545.
You in?
Orient Industrial.
I'm Shijima Tarou, a college student.
I'm quickly heading down the path to living a single
life since I have no girlfriend to speak of.
It's hard to throw this away.
The new onahole is almost indistinguishable
from a real human being.
Fella Hame Lips.
Getting your onahole to say the "L" word
Master, I'm home.
Hey, welcome back. You're later than
I expected. Something happen?
Today was the special sale. Don't you remember,
Master? It was so crowded.
What? Were you stopping yourself from
masturbating while I was gone?
Yeah, something like that. But you
were kinda taking a while, so...
I couldn't wait any longer and I let one out!
M-Master, you cheater!
Huh?!
Well, you see, Master, the second generation
onaholes are something like heroes to us.
They were able to remove so much semen
from men all around the world!
New model Small Size: Christie
New Model Middle Size: Cindy
They really paved the road!
New Model Big Size: Betty
They're really important.
But what just happened here is a different story.
Don't you ever think that you did
the same thing to that onahole?
That's right! That's why it really surprised me to know
that you were cheating on me with this squishy thing!
I wasn't really cheating on you.
But yeah, you know what? You're really the best, Naoko.
Master!
But you know, the low-tech, warm ones?
It's always fun to try out the older stuff. Trying
and comparing different ones was fun!
Before I got you, I used that onahole
more than I've ever used you.
In a certain way, we're kinda like soul buddies...
It's like Peter Pan flying through the skies of
fantasies with his trusty friend, the onahole.
It's just something that every guy
needs in his life, you know?
Huh? Seems like you have quite the opinion on the topic.
Uh, no, I...
So basically as long as there's a hole,
you can get off. Is that how it is?
Well, uh, yeah, basically.
You honest monster!! Onahole user! You're
just a virgin who uses onaholes to get off!
Aren't those all compliments?!
If you like my predecessors so much, I'll just do the same.
I won't move anymore.
What?! You're an onahole though!
I'm good as long as I can get you off.
You can just get off by yourself like you just did.
Is this the onahole role play with an onahole?!
What an extravagant way to play.
It's not something that most people just think of.
Wow, my onahole is a genius.
I'm still not moving even if you compliment me, Master.
Oh, that's fine. You don't have to move at all.
Now that I think about it, as long as I have
this hot body, that's enough for me.
That kind of makes me sad to hear.
But yeah, even if you don't feel like moving, Naoko...
You still react anyway.
I'll never get tired of that.
My boobs feel so good.
It's just like you said, you're made to make guys happy.
You're really sensitive aren't you, Naoko?
But since you said that you have to make me happy,
you'll need to hold back on your desires.
You're kidding! Usually you just
give me your dick immediately.
This is the first time with the tongue.
I'm not good with this kind of thing.
I'm happy he's being so nice to me,
but I need him to mess me up!
What's this? You look like you're craving more.
That doesn't look like the face of someone who
told me that I could do whatever I wanted.
Here, look. It's the dick you love so much.
It's been sitting idly until now,
but look how ready to go it is.
Usually I'd just have you suck me off
the instant I take it out of my pants.
Master's dick is aroused.
It's so hot.
Oh crap, she's so cute! I never knew teasing
Naoko would turn me on this much!
The way you can't even take your eyes off my dick even
though you're trying to hold yourself back is just the best!
Now then, let's see what's going on with
the mouth that I've been teasing.
Oh, there's steam coming out!
Your drool isn't stopping.
That's right, Master! My mouth is ready
for you to cum in at any time!
Looks like your body's starting to turn on.
You don't need lotion unlike the older onahole models.
You fourth generation onaholes are the real deal.
Are you gonna? Master, are you gonna put it in me?
You're originally designed to give blowjobs, right, Naoko?
You want to suck it so badly, you can't help it.
You look like you want it so bad.
Hey, Naoko, your breath is getting hotter and hotter.
You're completely in blowjob mode, aren't you?
I thought you weren't going to move?
Your pussy's starting to tremble too.
Your tongue's even wetter now.
I'm covered in it.
Well, I guess...
If you keep looking at me like some
kind of dog, I have to give it to you.
It's inside!
Holy crap!
Not doing anything feels good, doesn't it?
I can feel the sensation of your lips all across my dick!
It really makes me know that my dick is
being sucked inside this erotic mouth!
It's Master's dick!
Let's go deep again!
So warm!
It's so hot and tasty. It feels so good!
Now that his dick's so far inside me, I can rest easy.
But I guess I can't just keep my dick tike this forever.
I gotta cum!
Please, mess me up!
If you're not going to give me a blowjob, I guess
I just have to use your mouth to do it myself!
Yes, that's tight, Master! Rub it!
Rub my mouth pussy!
Gotta force it deep down your throat!
Gotta bend your neck back...
My dick is being squeezed! This is great!
Your mouth feels so good, Naoko!
My mouth pussy is filled with Master's dick! It feels so good!
Hurry! Your cum! Cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum just like you
wanted me to in your mouth, Naoko!
Hurry! I want to drink your cum, Master!
Oh can't hold on anymore so you started moving, huh?
That deserves some punishment!
He's pointing it upwards?
I came so much.
Aren't you happy that you get cum
in a different hole now, Naoko?
Maybe you're more similar to your predecessors
than I thought. You look just like them now.
Seriously, it's amazing how you move like a vibrator.
How do I put this? I just gotta put it to good use!
Looks damn delicious!
Master's dick is coming again!
Now he's giving it to me in my pussy!
It's coming again!
His dick! His dick!
Damn, it's so tight!
Your insides are squirming so much!
Don't cum just because I put it in!
I thought you weren't going to move?
I'm not moving. I'm pretending.
Just pretending it feels good.
I'm an onahole, so I want you to help you cum, Master.
I don't know why you're playing tough. I'm
just gonna make your pussy go crazy!
The more you look like you're enjoying
it, the better it feels for me.
With that in mind, you're the best!
I said it at the beginning, didn't I?
Your hole feels the best!
Come on. If you understand, then
show me your dirty face now!
I haven't seen it all day.
Master! Master!
I like that face.
It's your usual erotic face, lost in ecstasy.
I knew it! Unless I see this erotic
face, I'll never be able to cum!
Look at it!
Your dick made me make this face!
Then let's try to make an even more erotic face!
That's no problem, Master!
This is rare. Are you making up for all the work I just did?
Yeah, I'm going to make up for the time that I stayed still!
Master, keep looking at my face, okay?
Look at my face wrought with ecstasy
and make your dick even harder!
It feels so good!
Wow. That's some face you have on right now.
It's so loose.
Can't move anymore, Naoko?
Then...
Let me do the rest!
Let's go!
It's so hot to see you like this even if you
can't even breathe properly right now.
You really are the best, Naoko!
Na-o-ko!
I can feel your entire body tensing
up! You're so cute, Naoko!
Here I go!
Here I go! Here I go!
Here, Naoko. Leftovers.
That's good. Suck more!
Yeah, this is the best way to end.
Maybe it's better if you don't move, Master?
Of course. How much do you think you cost me?
Onahole Daimyoujin
Why are you enshrining it?
Well, I'm just so impressed at how our predecessors
could just sit still and take it like that!
I'm never doing that again though.
You're making fun of your predecessors, aren't you?
But I just want to stick around and play with you, Master,
I think it's better to be used anywhere, anytime.
Well, yeah...
Just by saying that, you already got so hard. That's why
I need to be around or you'll be in trouble, Master.
If you keep this up, you'll never get a girlfriend, Master.
You're the one who made me hard!
Now you're gonna help me cum!
Okay, Master!
I'm gonna let out even purer cum next time, okay?
Prepare yourself!
Pure?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality check: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч