Are you okay?!
Hang in there!!
I'm here to rescue you!
We've got to get out of here, can you walk?!
Well well...
What have we here! If it isn't Ashe from Dalmasca.
I'm honored to meet you in person.
What business do you have with us, so late at night?
Don't play dumb!
Oh dear... such a threatening attitude. You seem ready to bite me.
Ha ha ha, I suppose that's not surprising considering the bad rumors about me in the city.
That's right,
I hear that you capture and imprison woman.
Ba'Gamnan.
Come on, let's go.
Now now.
Why don't you take it easy for a while?
Come to think of it...
I heard some rumors as well.
They say that Dalmasca has a valuable treasure that's been handed down for generations...
... The Dusk Shard...
I'd like to have a nice little chat about that...
Back off Ba'Gamnan!
Or else!
Oh dear... go ahead.
If you have the strength, that is...
Uhh... ahh... wh,why...?
Oh, what a shame.
Now, let's get down to business.
Heh heh heh.
Oh, you're awake.
Though from your point of view,
not waking up might have been more preferable.
Okay...
Let's start the interrogation. Answer my questions, and I'll let you go right away.
... Where is the Dawn Shard?
How does he know about the Dawn Shard...?!
I think it's better for both of us if you cooperate, you know?
The Dawn Shard has become powerless since it created the Mist.
What good is it to you now?
Vayne was looking for it.
That's more than enough reason for me.
So you're nothing more than a little bandit who's trying to suck up to his boss.
Shut up!!
Oops, sorry about that.
I should always interrogate ladies gently.
Oh yes.
You seem to think that I imprison those women,
but that's completely inaccurate.
Bullshit!
They just won't leave.
Because of my training! Heh heh heh!
D... do your worst.
It takes more than the likes of you to make me talk!
Oho, that's not what I'd expect to hear from a girl in chains.
But you know,
I kinda like spunky girls like you, girls who act all aloof.
... You better make this fun for me.
It's okay. I can take this.
I've got to get out of here, no matter what...!
Come on.
Heh heh heh!
Look at that, your nipples are hard!
You're pretty honest, after all.
That... that's a lie!
Well now... Is it really...?
No... no...!
Nooo...!
Ohhh. Well well well...
Let's see...?
Cut it out!
Ooh, lookie here.
Your panties are kinda moist.
No they're not...!
Shut up for a moment. Can you hear that sound?
Aww man! I want to fuck you already!
You better not start talking too soon! Heh heh heh!
Oh, way to resist that.
I totally figured you'd moan in pleasure from that one.
Like hell!
Th... this is nothing...!
I'll never... make... make that kind of noise...!
Yeah, you're right.
You wouldn't break just because I'm stimulating your clitoris.
R, Rasler...!
No need to hold back, you can make as much noise as you like...
It's... it's okay...!
I can still take this much...!
Well, I guess I should say that's a queen for you?
You're cut from a different cloth than your average straggler.
Too... too bad... for you... guh...
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot to mention, this vibrator has 5 power settings.
And... this is only the first setting.
N... no way...!
... And this is the highest one...!
Ahhhhhhhh! Aughhh! Noooo! Ahh! Aughhh! Nooooh! Nooo!
Heh heh heh!
You're finally singing a nice tune! Huh?! Well?!
Heh heh heh... ha ha ha!!
A queen! Writhing under a vibrator, huh?!
Ahhhh...! Oh no... It's... it's too strong...!
It's pulsating... all the way to my womb...!
Aaaaahh! No, no, no, no...! I can't take it...!!
Did you just come...?
Heh heh heh...! Even though you're a queen? Ha ha ha!
But did you know this?
Even when a woman comes, she can keep on coming if you keep stimulating her!
Aaahh...! The orgasms... they just keep on coming...!
I'm coming... Aahh! Over and over...!
I can't... take... it... anymore...!
Do you feel like talking yet?
Heh...! That's what I expected...!!
... Do you know the Urutan-Yensa race?
They live in the great desert to the west...
They're pretty scary things...
Their tortures are so brutal that even we Bangaa spill the beans.
There's a kind of aphrodisiac we get from them that we use on our sex slaves...
It must be like hell for them.
Anyway, they positively need something shoved into them, or they go crazy.
Most women end up insane in the end anyway...
... Let's see how you handle that stuff!!
Heh heh heh...!!
R... right now, there are people out there looking for me!
It's a matter of time before they find this place!
Ohh, now you've got me scared.
Well then, let's not waste any time with this!
What have you been doing ever since that Rasler got what he deserved?
With this, I mean.
Have you been masturbating all by yourself?
I... I would never stoop so low...!
Wow, looks like I was right.
No way... I... I don't do that!
You're so entertaining.
Well then,
it's finally time to look at Her Majesty's important bit...!
... No... Anything but that...!
Wow...
Where did your spunk from earlier go all of a sudden?
No... nooo...
Noooooooo!!
Mmmm?
Wah hah hah hah!
Well, I never!
With such a pretty face, you've got quite the nasty thing attached down there!
Heh heh heh!
Don't tell me you rub your own clit twenty-four seven!?
Heh heh heh...
You just can't judge a book by its cover, can you!
N... no... no I don't! I don't... do that!
This is getting more fun by the minute...!
Alright,
now suck it all up without spilling a drop!
... I can feel it pouring into my bowels...!
Come on!
There's still more where that came from!
Don't let it go just yet.
Why...?
This is so... humiliating, and yet...!
I feel... hot...! Ahhh... My body...!
Come on... You can feel it, can't you?
You can feel the heat...!
It's as if a thousand bugs are crawling around inside my womb...!
Ahhh! Nooo!
My butt is going numb... It... It's going to come out...!
Wow, you're really making an effort.
How does it feel?
Having your shit hole exposed to a lowlife like me?
Heh heh heh...!
It's... it's coming out...!
I can't keep my butt closed anymore...!
But I can't, not in front of him... Aahhhh...!
Ahhh... Oh no... I can't hold on anymore...!
I... I can't...! I can't...!
Aaahhh! Noooo...! I can't hold it...!
D... don't look!!
... How's it feel? The Yensa aphrodisiac?
Did it fry your brain...?
Heh heh heh...!
... Your pussy is itching, isn't it?
You want something to go in there, don't you...?
Aahh... What would happen if he skewered me with that thing...?
Ahh... I... I want it... My pussy wants it...!
... Nobody's going to see.
It's okay for you to beg for it...
... I... I want it...
F,fu... fuck me! Fuck me...!
Heh heh heh!
You've fallen from grace...!
Right, time to make you fly...!
I'm coming! I'm cominggg!
Ahh, I'm coming... coming, coming, ahhh, I'm coming again!
... Oh... This... this is amazing... Haaaaahh... Ahhh...!
Ahhhhh...aahhhhhh! I'm commmming!
Ahh, I'm comng... coming, coming, ahhh, I'm coming again!
... Uh... uhh... or... more... I want more...
Heh heh heh heh...!
Come on... Put up your ass, like a dog...!
... F... fuck me!
... It... It's inside me... Aahhh...
We Bangaa have much more stamina than you Humes, and don't you forget it...!
Oh yes! This... this feels so good!
Your cock! Your cock! Aahhhh!
Ohhhhhhh... More...! Fuck me more... Aahhhh...!
Ohhhh yessss! It... it feels so good...!
My pussy... Ohh...
Heh heh heh...! You're a such a little bitch...!
A... anal... too...! Oooah... It's... great... Ooh!
I want mooooore...!
Amazing... Ahhh...!
My... my belly... So deep... It's coming...!
I'm... coming... I'm coming... Aahhhh!!
I'm coming...!
Heh heh heh! What a mess!
Again... I'm going to come again already... Aahhhh...
I'm coming...! I'm... coming...
Come on!
It's too early to give up!!
Aaahhhh... No... no more...
Aaah... I... I'm going to die...
Noo... Again... I'm coming again...
Damn it...!
She's already at her limit... She sure broke down fast...!
Oh well... Here we go... Take it all in...!!!
In the end I didn't get my hands on that nethicite.
Oh well, it's just a rock now that Vayne is dead anyway.
Also, those fools in Dalmasca.
I bet they're going to be pretty upset when they see their princess like this.
Heh heh heh...
... Right?