In a town with a long history, standing at the botton of a hill.
Where people go for education up and including university.
Private school Seiohkan academy.
Wishes that could not be granted.
Cute scool uniforms.
Liberal scool philosophy.
A campus with greenery.
Feelings of love...
...that could never be fulfilled.
Where do those emotions go, once lost?
Minoru Hatsushima (Age 20) attends this campus
along with his good friends,
and they're enjoying their
carefree school life...
Miki Katou (Age 20)   Naoya Kamata (Age 20)
That which was clasped tightly
in their hearts were feelings of
Tatsuya Futaki (Age 20)
"Someone other than myself", "My treasure".
Anzu Hatsushima (Age 20)
Something was forgotten somewhere along the way,
but they can't even remember what it was.
Minoru Hatsushima (Age 20)
Lost in feelings of anxiety...
Komomo Sakurai (Age 21)
...they then remember.
"Your voice". "Your figure".
Yes, all is connected.
Nothing had changed.
The ungranted wishes never went anywhere.
They were always, always right there.
Indeed, feelings of love will never change.
The miracle of meeting you once again.
This time, don't ever let me go.
Episode 2: Promise
"We will always be together..."
Minoru-chan...
Senpai...
A dream...?
Senpai!
Good morning!
Good morning, Minoru-chan.
You seem in high spirits today.
They're sky-high!
So why do you look so glum?
It's just... yawn...
So you're sleepy...
What-could you have been up to?
Nothing, really...
Have any strange dreams?
Oh! Speaking of dreams...
...what kind of dream
do you think I had last night?
This is an easy one.
Was it about rice cakes?
I should've seen that one coming...
I just said the first thing
that came to mind.
No, it's okay.
But I don't get it,
I thought it would be easy...
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize for it.
Last night... I had
a dream about you, Minoru-chan.
You dreamed about me?
Yes, that's why I couldn't wait
to see you this morning.
S-Senpai...
Minoru-chan, if we don't hurry up
and get to school, we'll be late!
Y-yeah.
M-Minoru and Senpai are together?!
Ah, good morning, Tatsuya.
Good morning, Futaki-kun.
C-come here a sec.
What's your problem?
D-did you get lucky?
Uh... yeah.
You mean you scored?
You got some?
Yeah.
And you even did that??
Yep.
WHAT YOU SAY????
How did you move so fast?
There must be some trick to it!
Tell me, tell me!
Tell me the first step!!
I'm not sure how to answer that.
I'll get you next time!
NEXT TIME!
Minoru-chan?
Senpai, I'm leaving Minoru in your care.
Good luck.
Isn't Futaki-kun such a nice guy?
I... guess so.
Bye for now, Minoru-chan.
See you later!
Right.
"Bye for now, Minoru-chan!"
Why the imitation?
She called you "Minoru-chan."
And is there something wrong with that?
Not exactly...
Senpai's older than I am,
so it's perfectly natural.
Oh, not at all. It's so nice
that you get along so well.
Isn't it, though?
Still, I'm a little surprised that
you captured Senpai's heart.
Ah, I'm not saying you're not good
enough for her or anything.
That's not helping, Miki.
Well, he's better for her
than you are, anyway.
And what do you mean by that?
That I want you all
to myself, Naoya-kun!
What does it matter?
Youko-chan...
W-what is it?
Nothing at all.
Really? It looks like
something's on your mind.
Well, I owe a lot to Komomo-senpai,
so I can't help but feel something here.
If you're referring to the age difference,
it's occurred to me, too.
Nobody brought that up!
That kind of thought would never
occur to Komomo-senpai.
That is true...
Then where's the problem?
You said it! She's probably thinking,
"He's so cute, and sweet,
and rice cakes are delicious!"
Do you ever shut up?
What's with Youko-chan?
Youko-chan, you can't keep on
acting like you did today!
What do you mean?
You know full well what I mean.
I can tell you're in a bad mood
just by looking at you.
If you keep that up, even my
brother will be scared of you.
Did Hatsushima say somethirfg to you?
"What? Did I do something
to make her mad again?"
"That Youko-chan is one straight arrow."
Is that how he thinks of me?
I can always tell when you're
feeling down, Youko-chan.
So, Youko-chan, you have to say something
to him before it's too late.
And just what should I say to him?
Sheesh, do you really think that innocent
act is fooling anyone at this point?
But, it really is too late...
I never thought there'd be
competition for him.
He just carried along, never making
anything clear, never being cool...
But it's my fault for being complacent.
If you use sneaky tricks to take my
brother, there'll be hell to pay.
You should be worrying about
yourself too, not just me.
Are you okay with this?
Well, we're up against Komomo-senpai
here, and she's not to be taken lightly.
It must be hard for you, too.
Your brother won't have any more
time to dote on his kid sister.
That's an awful thing to say, Youko-chan.
But it's the truth.
That's why we can't keep my brother in the
dark about this any more than we need to.
Won't it eat away at you if he never
finds out how you feel?
Big Brother...
Ah, so you were still
hanging around here.
Yeah, I was just talking
with Youko-chan.
Why are you still here?
I thought I'd ask if
we could go home together.
So you're walking home
with Komomo-senpai.
Aw, come on! That's something
Anzu would say, Nishimura.
What do you mean,
"Something I would say"?
Huh? Nishimura?
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Just the fact
that I like you too.
Eh? What do you mean by that?
You just never learn
when to keep your mouth shut.
Aaaaah!
W-what are you doing to me?
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
K-Komomo-senpai!
S-Senpai!
Sorry about everything, Nishimura...
- Never mind, just go after her!
A-all right!
I'm so stupid...
I'm meddling in his life even when
he's already got a girlfriend.
That's for sure.
Anzu, will you treat me
to some comfort food?
Okay... hey!
S-Senpai!
Senpai...
So Youko-chan likes you...
Seems like it.
I'm a little shocked.
It was news to me, too.
If you think about it, Minoru-chan, there
are cute girls all over the place.
Why would you need me
when you've got them?
I'm older than you...
Senpai, why are you
bringing that up all of a sudden?
And I thought you were my destined person
at the other end of the red string.
So just because
I'm not your soulmate, I fail?
I'm still looking only at you
with everything I have.
Or are coincidences
more important to you?
It's not like that, Minoru-chan!
Because now that I have you, Senpai,
nothing that Nishimura or even
Anzu does will matter.
So please don't talk like that.
If you do, I'll lose my confidence
that you're only looking at me.
I am looking only at you!
You're such an idiot,
Minoru-chan!
It's... it's like I don't
even know you anymore!
Senpai...
Big Brooother!
Hey, the bath's open.
You alive in there, Big Brother?
Senpai...
What do I do after
saying such a horrible thing?
Minoru-chan will hate me now.
Minoru-chan
I'm so sorry, Minoru-chan.
I'll apologize, so don't hate me.
I don't want
Minoru-chan to hate me!
Minoru-chan...
I like you...
I love you...
I wonder if he'll forgive me if
I give him some rice cakes?
I mean it, Minoru-chan,
I'm sorry...
Senpai!
Minoru-chan?
How are you talking to me?
Um, on the phone.
Eh? It connected.
Call in progress
So... you heard
what I was saying just now?
Y-yeah.
No fair, Minoru-chan!
No fair not telling me
you were on the line!
But... I couldn't have.
Senpai...
I'm sorry about today, Minoru-chan.
For what?
For what happened today.
Don't be, I was the one
to blame this time.
Minoru-chan, I'm so glad
to hear your voice!
Ah! Senpai!
Not hearing your voice today
made me so sad!
Senpai. I want to see you, too.
Minoru-chan!!
Senpai! Keep your voice down!
Minoru-chan...
Senpai...
marshmallow hell...
Minoru-chan, I'm sorry.
I never meant to say
those awful things.
I understand, neither did I.
Well, Minoru-chan, how about
a little make-up sex?
Make-up?
Yeah. It's okay as long
as no one sees us.
So, Minoru-chan,
what do you want me to do?
I'll do anything you want.
Today, I want to return
the favor from yesterday.
Is that okay?
Minoru-chan...
Are you sure?
I'll have high expectations.
I'm sure.
Minoru-chan!
The scent of my woman.
I remember it well.
Really, Minoru-chan?
Yes.
You smell wonderful, Senpai.
Don't say that, Minoru-chan.
More... more..
you can have all you can eat.
Um, Senpai, does it feel good?
Yes, because you're being so gentle.
Yes, Minoru-chan...!
Yes, it's so good...
More, eat till you're full,
Minoru-chaaan!
Okay!
Senpai?
Your skills have improved,
Minoru-chan.
Senpai, did you already...?
I wanted to hold out
so that we could cum together,
but you were just too good.
So how about this time, I do
all the work, Minoru-chan?
I'm linked with you, Minoru-chan.
Senpai, if you keep that up...
Doesn't it feel good, Minoru-chan?
I sure don't feel bad...
Minoru-chan...
I'll make you feel really, really good...
Together...
Senpai!
Minoru-chan, you liked that, didn't you?
Yes. I'm sorry I couldn't
last any longer.
It's all right.
We're just getting started.
Senpai...
Minoru-chan,
I'll make you feel great...
Minoru-chan, go ahead...
Okay...
Minoru-chan...
Senpai...
It feels... so good...
I feel great too...
I'm... gonna cum...
Minoru-chan, I'm cumming!
Minoru-chan...
Senpai...
You were amazing, Minoru-chan.
You were too, Senpai.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
We'll keep doing it again and again.
Senpai...
Minoru-chan...
We just went our separate ways,
but I still want to see Minoru-chan again.
Texting time.
I'm already feeling lonely, even though
I was all over him a little while ago.
Am I just lost in lust?
Tomorrow, and the day after...
...we'll always be together.
Wait for me, 'kay?
"Let's be together, 'kay!
Wait for me <3"
Transmission Complete!
Big Brother?
Let's go home, Big Brother.
How could this happen to him?
Say something to him.
He's suffering so much.
I'm... about to cry, myself.
I can't do that in front of Minoru.
So there's nothing I could
say to cheer him up!
Futaki...
Naoya-kun...
Sorry, Futaki.
We're going to go on home now.
O-okay.
I'm gonna head home first, Big Brother.
Seeing her brother in a state like this
makes me feel sorry for Anzu.
Why aren't you going home, Nishimura?
I'm not going home yet.
Not when Anzu's put me in charge.
She cares about you more than anybody else.
In charge of what?
Comforting you.
I can see how you'd react badly to this.
I couldn't do that.
Then you need to stand up
again on your own.
Otherwise, you'll make Anzu sad too.
Whenever you're depressed,
she blames herself.
Does she...?
I won't tell you to forget
about Senpai, but...
...she's gone.
You have to think about how you'll
live your life without her.
It's way too soon for me to do that.
Then what are you going to do?
Komomo-senpai's dead, isn't she?
Nishimura!
Why are you crying?
Senpai! Komomo-senpai!
Nishimura...
What? Is it so wrong for me to cry?
Hey! Don't try anything funny!
Anzu would always stop crying
when I did this for her.
Stop it. You'll make me
cry even harder.
I'd been thinking that I was
the only one who was sad.
Hatsushima! Hatsushima!!
Nishimura...
N-Nishimura, wow...
I never knew you could do this.
Do you not like busty girls?
No, I don't dislike them...
Good answer.
N-Nishimura...
I don't know if my body can take it...
It's okay, as long as
I can make you feel good...
I'm sorry, Hatsushima...
I was only able to swallow a little bit.
You don't have to go that far.
I'm sorry I made you do
something this crazy.
It's not that bad.
I don't hate it at all...
...since it came from you.
Nishimura, do you...?
I'm fine with being a distraction.
Let's do it.
You're the only one for me.
Go out with me?
Are you sure?
I'm sure. You can do
whatever you want with me.
Nishimura...!
Hatsushima...
Does it hurt, Nishimura?
No, I'm all right.
Nishimura, I...
Hatsushima...
Hatsushima, this is incredible!
Are you okay?
I never thought it could be this amazing...
...but I'm glad it is!
Go ahead, Hatsushima. Keep going.
More... give me more!
Nishimura...
You did it with Senpai too, didn't you?
I don't mind, Hatsushima.
Think of the times you did it with her.
Pretend I'm her!
Senpai...
Komomo-senpai!
Hatsushima...
I... can't... last any longer...
Hatsushima, I'm cumming too!
Hatsushima... Hatsushima!
Nishimura!
Hatsushima!!
Nishimura...
Hatsushima...
I feel so refreshed, Hatsushima.
Sorry... and, thank you.
You knew I liked you, didn't you?
I heard you that one time.
How about an answer for me?
Sorry.
I see.
I was rash, and did
something I shouldn't have.
It's okay.
I had an impulse,
and I just went for it.
Sorry.
I said it's okay.
I hope that someday,
you'll be able to accept me.
- Sensei, good morning!
- Good morning!
Good morning.
I'm so sorry!
I was in a hurry because
I forgot something!
I wasn't paying attention, either.
It's not broken, is it?
Main message
Let's be together, 'kay!
Wait for me <3
Can I have it back?
Ah! Sorry about that.
Here. Please don't drop it again...
...Minoru-chan.
Um...
I'm back!
The wind from the east...
...sounds like your voice.
In this big, big sky
under many, many clouds.
Everything is connected.
The things I wished for
all came true.
Can you hear my heart racing?
Can you feel my excitement?
Everything's still the same.
When we meet again someday
we'll keep drawing our own path.
Feelings of love
will never change
now and forever.
I met you again!
It's a miracle!
Don't you let go of me this time.
I was born to love you, so
let's take this first love...
...and start all over again.
If I stand on my tiptoes...
...can I reach you?
To give you lots and lots of kisses
and lots and lots of love.
I'm just too shy to do it.
Keep looking at me forever
no matter where we are
You'll be the happiest guy...
...in this whole wide world.
I'm so glad I could
meet with you again!
I've just returned.
A new spark was born.
And your frozen seasons
will start to change again.
I met you again!
It's a miracle!
Don't you let go of me this time.
I was born to love you, so
let's take this first love...
...and start all over again.