The season when cherry blossoms fall.
In a town with a long history, standing at the botton of a hill.
Where people go for education up and including university.
Private school Seiohkan academy.
The soft rays of sunlight.
Even the colors of the wind are warm,
and they gently envelop everything.
Private school Seiohkan academy.
On such a spring day, the two meet.
Cute scool uniforms.
Liberal scool philosophy.
Later, they would realize that
it was a meeting of first love.
A campus with greenery.
"First Love." To fall in love for the first time.
Minoru Hatsushima (Age 20) attends this campus
along with his good friends,
and they're enjoying their
carefree school life...
Perhaps they didn't realize it at the time,
Minoru Hatsushima (Age 20)
but it was a memory to be treasured.
They might not have known it before,
Anzu Hatsushima (Age 20)    Youko Nishimura (Age 20)
but in that instant, they felt those feelings
Miki Katou (Age 20)
for the first time.
The feelings of "that person is precious."
Tatsuya Futaki (Age 20)   Naoya Kamata (Age 20)
Those will then become unforgettable feelings.
Komomo Sakurai (Age 21)
The season when cherry blossoms fall.
They would come to know that
it was a meeting of first love.
This is a story of such a spring day.
Episode 1: Confession
"I like you..."
Go, go, Sakurai!
Big Brother!
You gotta cheer for her!
Do I have to?
Anzu! Don't wander away from the cheering!
Youko-chan, listen to me!
Big Brother isn't cheering for Komomo-senpai!
What? Is that true, Hatsushima?
Just why did I have to come here, anyway?
I know she's your senpai and all, but still...
Well, you have a point...
But you do get to see
Youko-chan in cheerleader gear.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're wearing the same thing I am!
To me, she's just Sakurai-senpai...
I don't have any reason to cheer for her.
C'mon, Senpai's wearing a mini-skirt, too!
Anzu, seriously...
why'd you try to bring a guy along
with such dirty tactics?
Well, I'd have to say...
...it's a trap!
Senpai's about to hit it!
B-big Brother!
Sorry!
Brrr!
What happened to me?
Big Brother, are you all right?
You know who I am, right?
Umm... what happened to me?
Um, it's because I smashed the ball...
...and then it hit you.
You'd better keep the area cool.
Senpai!
Senpai, that won't cool him down!
Is that right, Youko-chan?
Big Brother, if only your face hadn't been in the way!
Senpai lost the match because
she was worried about you!
Wha? You lost, Senpai?
Sorry.
Eh? Why are you apologizing, Minoru-kun?
I should be apologizing.
I'm really sorry for hitting you with the ball.
Ah, don't worry, I don't think
this'll be too serious.
Probably not.
Thank you, Minoru-kun.
Ah! I sense a good mood between
Big Brother and Senpai...
- Some things you just don't say...
- Oww! I didn't mean it!
Hey, why did Komomo-senpai act
like she knew you back there?
That's just crazy talk.
Oh no, not crazy talk!
She totally knew you!
I can't help it!
Komomo-senpai's an old friend of mine,
just like Youko-chan!
Of course I'd want to talk about them.
So why do we have to talk about me?
Because it's interesting, duh!
Noo~! I hate noogies!
Let up on the crazy talk when we're
around other people, okay?
I get it.
Miki-pon told me something interesting
about your friend Kamata-kun.
Next time, you'll want to listen to me.
Kanata?
Oh yeah, he and Miki-chan started dating.
But what's so interesting about that, Anzu?
I'll tell you next time.
Oh yeah, Miki-pon and Kamata-kun
are having a party tomorrow.
What are we doing for that?
Making fun of them.
I feel sorry for Miki-chan
and Kamata. Bigtime.
Miki-pon was all for it.
I'm home!
There's something weird
about all of Anzu's friends.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
And now, why don't we have a few words
from today's main attraction?
I've been waiting for this!
You got a girlfriend; good for you.
C'mon, speech!
Kamata, you gotta stand, too.
Ahem. I, Naoya Kamata,
and Miki Katou to my left
do here declare in everyone's presence
that since last weekend,
we have been officially involved
in a romantic relationship.
Please treat us well.
Way to go, you lucky punk!
Please don't tease me.
I can't help myself.
Getting a girlfriend for the first time
is a once-in-a-lifetime cleared event.
It's something that comes along naturally.
His confidence is astonishing.
Question! Be honest, how was this decided?
I want to know!
Yes, yes, as fellow members of the
Maiden Society, we have a right to hear.
Go ahead, tell us everything!
C'mon, it'll be easy, just get it over with!
Well, it's like this...
онто нэ
After he confessed to me, I said "okay"!
That's too easy!
You made the decision to date him just from that?
Once you receive a confession yourself,
you'll understand, Youko-chan.
Miki-pon is sooo in love!
I'm jealous... I want a girlfriend, too.
Right, Minoru?
Even you want a girlfriend, right?
Well, yeah, I suppose so...
Minoru-kun...
Does the place where you got hit yesterday still hurt?
Oh, you mean that place? It's
just fine, never been better.
Oh! Minoru! Did something happen
between you and Sakurai-senpai?
Ah, no, just a little incident... yesterday.
It's like this: I hit him with a tennis ball yesterday.
A tennis ball?
Get out of town!
You went to peep at Sakurai-senpai
in her tennis outfit?
You undressed her with your eyes, didn't you!?
N-no, it wasn't like that at all!
He went with us to cheer at Senpai's
practice match yesterday.
Say what!?
Why didn't you invite me, too?
Way to look out for your friends!
Hey now, I got dragged along by Anzu,
I had no choice in the matter.
Anzu-chan, drag me along next time too!
Quite the social parasite, aren't you?
But it really bugs me...
You really were "struck" by Senpai too, am I right?
H-hey, Nishimura!
Be careful what you say!
Don't worry. It seems like
Senpai doesn't get it.
I'll come with you.
I'll be fine by myself.
I worry about you...
And whether it's all right to leave you alone.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Eh? It's Miki-chan and... who was that again?
It's Kamata.
What could they be up to?
Beats me.
Umm... Minoru-kun?
Yes?
We're alone, aren't we, Naoya-kun?
Don't shout.
You never know when someone might come by.
As long as you don't do anything weird, I won't shout.
But I can't get enough of your cute voice, Miki.
You're the only one who ever called Miki cute.
You ready already?
We'll be discovered if we take our time.
You're right. Then the fun starts now.
Miki, you look so embarrassed... but
I like that about you.
Naoya-kun... don't spread me too much now.
Even you have a shy side... especially right here.
Mind if I get started now?
This time, I'll do it for you.
Naoya-kun, we're short on time today,
so we'll have to make this a quickie.
Are you going to do the usual?
No. Miki will be on top.
Take it slow... it still hurts, right?
I've passed that stage, Naoya-kun...
having sex feels good now.
I see.
Well, don't overdo it.
- We saw everything... what if they find out... oh no...
- Senpai, if we stick around, they'll know we're here!
Oh yes, that's right.
Sorry for being such a voyeur, Miki-chan.
S-Sakurai-senpai...
Does what we saw bother you?
I can't say it doesn't bother me, but...
I wonder if those two are bound
by the red string of fate?
And I wonder if something like that
exists for me, too.
Um, well... I would think it exists.
Cause you're so pretty.
Thank you, Minoru-kun!
Oh, and our little peepshow back there...
It's our secret, right?
You wouldn't think Miki-chan would
get mad, but she would.
Yes.
It's a pinky promise, then.
It is.
If we don't head back,
they might worry about us.
Good point.
Things may have gone well for you yesterday,
but I won't let you get a single step ahead of me.
What do you mean?
You and Komomo-senpai
disappeared yesterday...
...did anything happen, Big Brother?
Nothing happened. Noth-ing.
Relax, Anzu, there's no way
your brother has that kind of courage.
That's true, he doesn't.
This is where I turn my losing streak around.
If you hate losing so much, what're
you gonna do about it?
I'll be requesting relations with
Sakurai-senpai, of course.
You're heading for disaster with that approach.
Minoru...
So, you're really going to ask her out?
Yeah, the only thing I can do is try.
After seeing Kamata yesterday,
I'm really jealous.
Even if it's hopeless, I have to make my move.
So, um... I know it's
impudent of me to ask, but...
I was thinking,
"If Senpai doesn't have a significant other..."
"...maybe I would be good enough?"
Ah... if you say you don't want to,
I won't hold it against you.
Futaki-kun...
I'm sorry, I really am!
So... like I said...
I can accept that!
Senpai, you don't need
to worry about it.
I... should just leave now!
Minoru?!
Were you spying on us?
Sorry, I was just getting something to drink.
I never thought you'd be
confessing to her back there.
So that means...
you saw me getting rejected, too??
Tatsuya...
Well then, I'll be looking for a new target.
I leave the aftermath to you, Minoru.
What do you mean, "aftermath"?
You go in there and succeed where I failed.
But I...
Give itryour best shot!
Ah, Minoru-kun!
S-Senpai!
Don't tell me you saw...
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to spy on you.
I was in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
I heard everything.
So you did...
Please excuse me.
As punishment for eavesdropping,
come with me for a chat.
All right.
Even though Futaki-kun went and said
he liked me, I turned him down.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Futaki-kun is your friend, isn't he?
Yeah, I suppose he is.
But Tatsuya's the kind of guy who
doesn't regret trying things.
I'm sure he'll survive.
He won't think badly of you at all, Senpai.
Really?
Well, it's pretty unlikely, anyway.
Minoru-kun, you're not looking
at me when you say that.
Well, you know how it is...
So why did you turn Tatsuya down, anyway?
He's smart, a bit of a flake,
but he's cool enough overall.
Just why was it...?
Minoru-kun... um...
"I like you."
Did your heart skip a beat?
Were you... just testing me?
Yeah, just a bit. Sorry.
But your heart did skip a beat, right?
Yeah, it did.
I'm happy to hear that.
You are?
Hey, Minoru-kun,
how would you react?
How would you react if I said I liked you?
I guess I shouldn't... you don't want to
hear that from girl you don't like.
T-that's not true!
Um, uh... "I like you."
Wha? Umm, Minoru-kun, it skipped...
My heart skipped several beats.
Minoru-kun, I do wonder if you like me,
but that was a test, wasn't it?
I wouldn't mind if it were true, though.
Say, awhile ago we saw something amazing...
...did you smell anything strange?
"Smell"? Smell what?
Um, when we were watching
Miki-chan and Kamata...
Yes?
Did I... smell strange to you?
I couldn't help noticing it afterwards.
Back then, my attention was on
other things, so I didn't notice.
Then... I just revealed something
embarrassing when I didn't even have to!
I'm so sorry!
You must think I'm a naughty girl.
Only a little...
There's no way you wouldn't...
You must be so disappointed...
and disillusioned.
I'm really not!
Really? I'm much naughtier than
I look... are you okay with that?
Yes.
Thank goodness!
Thank goodness for what?
Didn't you give the "okay"
when I said I liked you?
What about you...
are you okay with me?
Yes! Though I am unworthy, please take care of me.
I-I will.
Senpai, did I make you wait?
Yeah, I waited for about fifteen minutes.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to be late.
It's because I got here fifteen minutes early.
Say what?
But I liked watching you rushing to meet me.
You did?
Yeah, it really gave it that "first date" feeling.
Shall we go, Minoru-kun?
I had so much fun.
Are you tired, Senpai?
Maybe I ran around a bit too much.
I'll go get something to drink, then.
Please wait here.
I will.
Minoru-kun's so late...
Maybe I should go look for him.
He went that way, didn't he?
Eh? Huh? What the?
I should head back, shouldn't I?
Where am I?
Minoru-kun... I'm sorry! I got lost!
Senpai!
Senpai, is that you?
This is Hatsushima.
Mi-Minoru-kun?
Where are you now, Senpai?
Right now? I'm next to a park info map.
A park info map?
Which way is the Ferris wheel from where you are?
Um, I think it's to my left.
I understand. I'll go look for you.
Please don't go anywhere.
Okay, I won't. I'm sorry, Minoru-kun.
Are you crying, Senpai?
I might be.
Don't hang up the phone; my heart
can't take it, Minoru-kun!
I understand. I'll be right there.
I sort of recognize this area. I should be there soon.
Really?
I just passed the Ferris wheel, so it should
be straight ahead from here.
Minoru-kun!
Senpai!
I'm so happy to see you!
Same here, Senpai.
But how did you know my phone number?
I called Anzu as a last resort,
and she gave me the number.
Your phone is red too!
Yeah, Anzu said this one was too hard to use,
so she forced me to trade phones.
Check it out, my phone is also red.
So maybe we're joined by the red phones
of fate, rather than the red string.
Sorry about today; it was my fault.
No, I had fun.
Did you really?
Yeah.
Good.
We finally had our first date, and I
would've been sad if I'd ruined it.
It was a bit of a shock, though.
Ah! You are holding it against me.
No two ways about it,
it certainly was my fault.
I know! I'll do something to raise your
spirits, so that you feel better.
So, kiss me.
We're gradually catching up to Miki-chan
and Kamata, aren't we?
But, catching up to those two would involve...
It's too early, isn't it?
And you already know I'm a horny older girl.
Rather than "too early",
I'd say we're not ready...
Actually, I'm not quite ready either.
I wonder if anyone can see us...
Are you worried because we
spied on Kamata and Miki-chan?
You can never be too careful.
That felt good, didn't it?
Sit down, Minoru-kun.
S-Senpai...
Because I'm older,
I'll go first.
Wow, you're so big, Minoru-kun!
Senpai!
Does it feel good?
I'm so glad. Somehow,
this makes me feel good, too.
How mysterious.
S-Senpai!
It's okay.
Minoru-kun, that was incredible.
I'm sorry...
I got it on your face.
Don't worry about that,
it's your turn now.
So this is what you meant by your "scent".
Minoru-kun, can you smell it?
It's really strong.
I'm sorry, it must be so weird.
No, it isn't bad at all.
Minoru-kun...
Yes...
Keep going, Minoru-kun...
Yes, harder...
Minoru-kun!
When I was able to say "I love you"
That was a little fast, wasn't it?
Yeah, a little too fast.
it was the beginning of a miracle.
Miki-chan and Kamata will be surprised for sure.
Now we can start dating
without debate or hesitation.
I guess we can.
Minoru-kun, are you okay with sharing lots
of embarrassing and exciting experiences,
as well as happy and sad experiences, with me?
Of course I am.
Lots and lots of them?
Yes. Lots and lots of them.
Hurry up and kiss me then.
Even when we pass each other by
I don't want anyone to find out.
Please let us be lovers from now on.
With all the voice I have
I trick you with a "Good Morning".
I feel like sighing over
these lonely, unspeakable, tangible emotions.
Underneath this uniform
my heart is lost in its first feelings.
When I realize you're always on my mind
that's when I know it's love.
Lying awake in my bed
the words I want to say keep
floating back to me.
Will I be able to say "I love you"
as if it were just a greeting?
Gazing from far away
I want to stop, change, and shout out
these emotions...
My heart beats under this uniform
I can't control it any longer.
When my small body feels this powerful
that's when I know it's love.
I can't stop trembling.
Please, God,
won't you make me brave?
Underneath this uniform
my heart longs to express its first feelings.
You stood there with a smile
as you waved your hand goodbye
to my old weak crybaby self.
The two who had expressed their feelings.
That was the moment they realized their love.
Thus followed a miraculous occurance.
Their feelings were pure,
grand, and also clumsy.
Therefore they sometimes disagree
and misunderstand each other.
However, their bond was
a thing of certainty.
Grasp it strongly and never let go.
Next time on First Love: Promise.
Those were precious memories
of a precious girl...
...and a precious promise.