Mother! Mother!
l'm coming. l'm coming soon!
Stop! Stop it!
l don't want this!
Don't look.
No! No!
What have you been doing?
Don't worry about it.
That's better.
Matsuura! l want you to stop filming for now.
Are you sure?
lt's okay...
...nobody wants to keep watching
the suspect's disgusting ass.
You don't want to keep filming his ass, right?
Please standby
Foxy Nudes Vol. 2
No!
Shut up!
No! No more!
Come back here!
No!
Let me go!
Come here!
Great job you two.
We caught it real good on camera.
Well done!
Huh?
Why are you crying?
Well, anyway, you have to act like a hostage!
You were excited a little, weren't you?
They watched you get
raped and you were excited!
l wasn't excited!
l don't want to become a star like this...
You're right, l came here to save you.
Go wear those clothes.
And what are you going to do?
l'm sorry.
Maybe it's the booze, it's hard for me to climax...
What do you mean?
Your cock is getting soft?
Yes...
You were going to get your revenge like that?
You should turn yourself in!
Turn yourself in right now!
You can't even do your job right.
You're a stupid worthless scumball
who can never get anything done!
Give up and turn yourself in!
You're just a pile of trash.
That's why you were dumped.
An idiot who's satisfied with something like this...
...should turn himself in!
Your name says it all!
You stupid!
No! You're wrong!
l'm not scum!
l'm just a born loser!
Pit Viper Juice
What?
Don't you know what's going on?
According to Etsuko's orders,
our crew can't go near the scene.
What is Etsuko trying to show us?
We got visuals.
Finally!
This is Yamanobe of Flower TV.
We were in a dangerous situation before...
...we apologize for going off the air.
Don't shoot.
Understood.
No!
Take a look at this, folks.
Male enhancement drug!
There's also an aphrodisiac as well!
We thought he was doing this in a fit of anger.
But it looks like he had plans to
seclude himself from the beginning.
l'm coming!
l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
l'll release it inside!
Stop it!
No!
Don't release it inside!
Ladies and gentlemen, did
you just see what happened?
He released it inside!
He released it inside on live TV!
Things are getting worse.
The suspect's cock is still rock hard!
No!
Shut up!
l'll stick it up your ass!
Stop it! Not there!
Shut up! Just do as l say!
No! No!
lt feels really tight!
My ass will tear!
Shut up!
Sir!
Wait.
While he's doing that, the hostage is safe.
But l can't watch!
Don't be provoked!
Just wait!
Yes.
That bastard! He thinks he
can do whatever he wants!
lt hurts!
l'm coming again!
No, no, no!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
lt looks like he released it inside her anus this time.
But he's still thrusting his hips!
Will there be an opportunity for me to intervene?
Shut up!
Shit!
When did you put on these clothes?
Take them off!
No!
lt looks like there's plenty
of bodily fluids being released...
...from the crotch of the
victim, Mayumi Wakabayashi.
l believe that's a type of toy used in S&M play.
ls he going to stick it in her ass again?
Stop! Stop! No!
lt hurts, it hurts!
Matsuura, l'm heading out for a while.
Heading out? Where on Earth are you going?
A job.
Bingo!
We have our sixth winner.
What's the prize?
A car navigation system?
You won a car navigation system. Congratulations.
Miss Yamanobe! You look beautiful!
Thank you very much.
Weren't you reporting live
from the scene just a while ago?
This is Yamanobe live right before your eyes.
l just came here to make some extra money.
l'm a little bird.
l'm singing all alone everyday...
The way a river flows.
But to the huge sky...
Somebody will find me.
My wings will...
Receive love and...
Money! My money!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
l'm just here to make some money.
Excuse me.
My money!
Mine. Mine. My money!
This is just perfect!
Actions taken by the suspect in
this case just keep escalating...
He's really showing off.
Welcome back, Etsuko.
How's it going?
How? lt's out of control.
l was hit by a Molotov cocktail.
Not bad.
What?
l thought he was no good,
so l helped him out a little.
Then the male enhancement drugs
and Molotov cocktails were...
That's right.
lt's a toy.
Just a small prop.
l want you to start filming on my cue.
This case is clearly the current...
Looks like we have visuals from the scene.
Shut up!
Don't do it! You're making a big mistake!
Shut up! l don't care what happens to me!
ls he going to do it?
You perverted killer!
He's going to kill Mayumi!
He didn't kill her yet!
Our son would never do such a thing!
Reporting from Anan to all officers.
lt looks like the suspect has a gun.
Be extremely careful!
Our number one priority is to rescue the hostage.
l wish you all the very best.
l couldn't talk him out of it.
The suspect was planning to
commit suicide with the victim.
The suspect's ferociousness
is way beyond my imagination.
The victim's life is hanging by a thread.
What is he trying to prove by doing all this?
Etsuko is crying!
l can't believe he made her cry!
Kill this suspect!
lt's me. Are we ready?
We'll go in when we catch him off guard.
Fine. Do it carefully.
l see.Thanks for telling me.
We can finally capture the decisive moment.
Get up!
Now!
Search warrant!
Don't come any closer!
lt's a real gun!
Stop trying to resist and let the hostage go!
Mayumi...
Damesuke! Don't do it!
Stop resisting!
Got him.
We've captured him!
Mayumi!
Sir, we did it!
You're unbelievable Etsuko...
l was deeply touched! This is television at its best.
Great job Etsuko.
Amazing! You're amazing Etsuko!
l'm deeply touched!
Since the suspect wasn't sniped,
l can't give you this money.
l see...
By the way, what happened to your sniper?
You mean Murata?
Your skin looks really pale. Are you from the north?
l'm from Aomori.
How long have you been doing this?
Since last week.
Really? You're pretty good.
Have you worked in the sex industry before?
l was a secretary working for
a major armed security company.
Really?
We have to protect ourselves in this day and age.
You were working for a good company.
But l shot a hostage and got fired.
You shot a hostage?
That's hilarious.
Why am l here?
l can't remember anything.
Now...
...the victim of yesterday's hostage
crisis, Mayumi Wakabayashi...
She was rushed to the hospital, and...
This is it! This was aired during that time slot.
Most viewers tuned in to our channel.
We had such high ratings.
Really?
Plus the footage we sold to the other channels...
...will be quite profitable.
Nevermind that.
You just enjoy this nice time, it's on me.
l really appreciate what you did for me.
Everyone approves of me because of you...
You don't have to be so formal,
you can just call me by my name.
l know that l'm five years older than you and...
...l'm a middle-aged woman of 28 years, but...
What are you talking about?
You're our big-name newscaster!
You're beautiful and intelligent.
You're the perfect female newscaster.
l want to get to know you more.
Me too.
Here. A present for you.
Present? For me?
This is...
lt's mine.
Soaked with cunt juice.
What are you trying to do?
Sexual harassment.
Just like l thought.
l'll give you my champagne.
Let's change positions.
You're so nice, Etsuko.
Letting me do this kind of thing.
lt feels good!
Yes.
Your cock feels so good!
lt's like a dream.
l can't believe l'm doing it with a woman like you.
Excuse me.
Oh, did you just come in?
Yes.
Hey you.
Do you want to be on TV?