Cue!
Etsuko Yamanobe
Good evening. This is News Flower.
Top story this evening is the latest on the hostage crisis...
...that occurred earlier today.
A man holding a sharp object
broke into an apartment building...
...in Suginami ward this afternoon.
He's still holding a young woman as a hostage...
...and has been inside ever since this afternoon.
He shouts out gibberish at times.
l'm from Venus!
l'm telling you to get my boss!
l have some business with her father!
Hey, don't do anything stupid!
What are you trying to do?
Shut up!
l was fired from my job today!
Watch out!
The female hostage is believed to be...
...22-year-old Mayumi Wakabayashi.
l want you to hang in there.
Don't lose hope.
This just in...
The suspect is believed to be 40-
year-old Damesuke Marude who...
...was fired today from a company
owned by the victim's father.
Mr. Fujiwara, it seems the suspect
was irate over his recent firing...
...and has taken the daughter of
his former boss to get even.
Yes.
lt's a typical crime that occurs
in this age of economic depression.
We now know the reason behind this crime...
...but we can say that the
government doesn't care about...
...the lives of ordinary people and
realize what's going on in society.
You're right.
Mr. Fujiwara...
l'd like to head over to the scene and
try to negotiate with the suspect.
What?
l'll say this to the suspect.
Are you watching this broadcast?
Stop resisting and surrender.
lt's foolish for you to keep doing this.
l'm Etsuko Yamanobe from Tokyo Flower TV.
l'm heading over there right
now, so please let me talk to you.
Miss Yamanobe, you gave
quite a show for the audience.
Really?
l was just excited by my indignation
towards social evils.
That's just what l expected to
hear from our popular newscaster!
We're counting on you.
Oh yeah, about the cameraman who will go with you...
Can you get me Matsuura?
Matsuura?
But he's just a newbie.
Exactly.
We have to train him at the scene.
They say, strike while the iron is hot.
l have to stop by someplace, so
tell him to meet me at the scene.
Foxy Nudes Vol. 1
l'm Miyata from the headquarters
of Armed Security Pro.
l'm Etsuko Yamanobe from Flower TV.
Thank you for choosing us over
other security companies out there.
We have solved many cases
involving hostages in the past.
So we're used to cases like this one.
We have done our research
thoroughly and we already...
...gathered details regarding the
suspect and the hostage.
The suspect is 40-year-old Damesuke Marude.
He has a history of alcohol abuse...
...and has received treatment in the past.
He's introverted, but can easily fly into a rage.
We believe he's in an excited state right now.
The victim is 22-year-old
Mayumi Wakabayashi.
She's the daughter of Genta Wakabayashi...
...who is the president
of Wakabayashi lncorporated.
She's not related to the suspect at all.
Her sizes are 88, 56, 89, she's been
involved with five men in the past.
And what do you plan on doing?
l'm going to block the area nearby...
...and we'll provide support
for your negotiating plan.
But we'll bust right in if we feel you're in danger.
Then we'll safely rescue the hostage.
l see.
What about in case of emergency?
ln case of emergency?
This will be optional, but...
We can snipe the suspect.
You know what?
l want to give the audience the entire
story and get really high ratings.
l see...
lf l can't accomplish that,
then l can't work with you.
As you wish.
Where is Etsuko?
She doesn't even answer her cell phone.
Sir! l'm really sorry.
The contract was inside my bag.
When l was about to leave the office...
What?
Sir...
What are you waiting for?
You want to talk to him, right?
Well...
Hurry up Murata.
What is this?
l'm sorry, l'll go back and get a new copy.
You don't have to do that.
Come here you.
What?
We're settling the accounts pretty soon.
We'd like to pay the regular
fee and get the option for free.
But we'll be criticized by the
people if we use the sniper method...
l understand that.
But what l need is a partner
that can accomplish the task.
Umm...
So l want you to use the sniper method.
You want me to lower the price
and use the sniper method?
You're asking too much...
But the hostage will be saved.
Your company will gain popularity.
Well, you're right...
That's something you can gain
by working with our TV station.
lt's a simple give and take process.
lf you do what l say,
l'll personally pay you the money
for the next ten jobs...
...without signing any contracts.
l understand.
l'll do my best so we can be great partners.
Sir!
What is it Murata?
l'm in the middle of an important business negotiation.
Business negotiation? Are you serious?
lt's a good way of negotiating business.
Really?
Listen.
ln this crazy world where we have
to protect ourselves from harm...
Do you know why your company...
...stands out from rest of the security firms?
Well, no...
Send the contract to the office.
What are you planning to do?
What?
You found out about our secret treaty.
Right...
As long as you keep the secret to yourself...
...you'll be in a favorable position.
Right...
What is your wish?
Go for what you truly want.
That's the way to live life.
l'll kill myself!
l'll definitely kill myself!
But before l do...
l'll kill you with this.
No...
Hey Mayumi, can you hear me?
Mayumi!
Marude!
l didn't know you were this dumb!
Give us back our daughter!
You rotten bastard!
What?
You ruined my life!
That's because you were incompetent!
You went to collect money...
...but instead they collected money from you.
You worthless piece of crap!
Yeah!
That's just too much.
Father, mother!
You were never like this, Damesuke.
He should've never worked for
a bogus company like yours!
He's a very timid boy, so
you took advantage of him...
Are you kidding me?
He should be grateful for
having a job in this day and age!
Why don't you thank us?
They're messing with me!
Attention people of the
news media and bystanders...
This case will be handled by Armed Security Pro.
Also, this hostage crisis will be
broadcast live by Tokyo Flower TV.
What? We're doing it?
Other news media and bystanders
should follow directions from our...
... officers and leave this area immediately.
Plus we'll be choosing 100 random bystanders...
...to join us in our special seats.
For more details, please ask one of our officers.
This is not a show!
Come this way please.
Parents of suspect, Parents of hostage
He wouldn't do anything like this.
What the hell is going on?
Matsuura!
Sorry l'm late.
Etsuko!
Let's go.
This is Yamanobe from Tokyo Flower TV.
And this is my cameraman.
Thank you for your assistance!
What the...
Who the hell are you?
Go ahead, you have to get rid of your grudge.
What are you...
Hey, that's our channel.
Could you possibly be...
l'm newscaster Etsuko Yamanobe.
lf you were watching the news,
then you know why l'm here.
l said l wanted to negotiate with you...
Shut up you bitch!
l'm a fifth degree black belt in karate.
You can't beat me.
l'm saved...
Now let's begin.
l want you to take your clothes off.
What?
Hurry.
l want you to do it according to my plan.
What are you saying?
Don't you want to be a star?
What?
Rather than depending on your parents' money...
...why don't you think about
making your own money?
Your parents squeezed money from the weak...
...so their money is filled with their hatred.
What do you mean by ''a star''?
You play the pitiable victim.
You just have to overact by crying.
He'll be quiet after a good beating.
And?
After you're rescued, you'll sign a
contract with us and appear on TV...
...then you'll be writing a book about your tragedy.
Of course a ghostwriter will write
it, you have nothing to worry about.
The more pitiful you are the
more collateral money you'll get.
So your clothes have to go.
l heard from your boss that you're worthless scum.
But l don't think you are.
That bastard.
Please, l want you to attack her.
l want to capture a shocking scene.
Matsuura!
Why are you naked?
Huge story!
Come here!
No!
Start the camera!
Yes!
No, don't come any closer!
No!
Stop! Stop it!
Help me!
Help...
Shut up you bitch!
No!
Sir!
Don't call me that when we're alone.
Yes Mr. Miyata.
Yes, this is Miyata...
What? The suspect?
Take a look at this.
lf he's doing that, then l can't negotiate with him.
The suspect is trying to kill himself.
lf he climaxes, then he probably won't need her.
He's reached the limit.
But l'll try to keep him busy.
l want you to carry out the
sniper option as soon as possible.
Murata.
What is it, Mr. Miyata?
We're working, address me properly!
Yes sir.
Can you go to the crime scene with me?
You want me to go?
We're short of officers.
The strike team will carry out the mission.
You'll be recorded in our records as
being part of the special unit.
Do you understand?
Yes!
After this case is solved...
...you'll receive a special allowance and an award.
Plus you'll get a position as an important secretary!
Thank you very much sir!
Take that you old man!
You like what l'm doing?
Damesuke Marude is really no good.
What?
Are you completely satisfied by doing this?
Why did you take her as a hostage?
l got it.
lf l don't show this to that
old man, there's really no point.
Matsuura.
Yes.
l want you to start shooting this live.
l wonder if Etsuko Yamanobe's show is still on.
The suspect has appeared!
Look over there!
Mayumi!
He's definitely scum!
Listen up, you don't have to shoot.
You just let the others do the job.
No! No!
Hey!
This is terrible!
Can't you people do anything?
Well...
This is unbelievable.
The suspect brought the victim out on the balcony...
...and he is raping her before the public's eyes.
l'm Yamanobe from Tokyo Flower
TV, and just like l stated earlier...
...l came here to the scene of the
crime to negotiate with the suspect.
But sadly, negotiations have failed.
And this is where we stand right now.
Etsuko Yamanobe...
By reporting from this scene...
l hope that you viewers can see
and feel angry towards the suspect.
Let's take a look at what's happening now.
Can you all see it?
That is...
That's an amazing blowjob!
Unbelievable...
We feel that it's dangerous, but we can't escape.
Can anyone do something about this situation?
This is a really good urinal.
l don't know what to say.
But it feels good to urinate in someone's mouth.
l know how it feels since l do it sometimes.
She pisses in other people's mouths?
Mother!
Help me mother!
No! Mother!
This is terrible! lt's getting worse.
What is going to happen from here on?