Sen... pai?
Be my woman, Futaba.
B-But what about my older sister?
Close your eyes.
Who cares about boundaries? Boyfriends should be this daring.
You need to be more daring too, Senpai.
Your girlfriend is going to get tired of you
if she always has to make the first move.
I want to experience you being more forward with me too, Senpai.
Are you awake yet, Senpai?
What are you doing, Futaba-han?
You're such a bad boy, letting the girl be the one to initiate sex.
I told you this is a bad idea. I can't do
this with you anymore, Futaba-chan.
It's big.
It's so big.
It's just so big.
Geez, I love you.
I have a big cock in my pussy, first thing this morning!
I haven't had your cock in a while, Senpai. My pussy is so happy!
I train my pussy for your use when
your cock isn't inside me, Senpai.
This isn't fair to Mihane, Futaba-chan.
Geez, my pussy can easily handle your big cock.
How dare you say another woman's name at
a time like this? When did you get so cocky?
She's your sister.
She'd think differently if she saw your perverted, dirty, cock, Senpai.
Your morning wood is burrowing deep into my pussy.
Senpai!
I'm going to overflow if your cock keeps filling me up.
My pussy is making lewd sounds as you fuck me.
Your cock is so great, Senpai!
It's hitting me all the way at the back!
I want to cum together with your cock, Senpai!
Cum inside me with your cock, Senpai!
I'm going to cum from your cock, Senpai!
I'm cumming!
You haven't cum yet, Senpai!
I'm the only one who came.
My pussy isn't good enough for your big cock.
Original work:
Blue Gale Original Animation
Fukubiti Triangle.
Futaba head over heels
WALL-PINNED NAUGHTY LITTLE VIXEN"S SONG OF LAMENT
Sex sure is great first thing in the morning, Senpai!
Maybe for you, Futaba-chan.
Are you talking about me satiating my darling pussy?
Don't be so loud!
You're a man, deal with it.
Women like to be honest.
Yeah, with their girlfriends.
I'll make sure to do that with Miharu.
We have co-ed P.E. today, right?
I'll fuck you in my bloomers, Senpai...
Come again?
You make a move the second I take my eyes off of you.
But I haven't done anything!
You were up to something.
Uh...
Now then...
Where is Senpai?
There he is! With my big sister.
Now's my chance!
Senpai!
Huh?
Futaba-chan!
Ouch!
Are you alright, Futaba-chan?
I scraped my leg.
Take me to the nurse's office while
carrying me princess-style, please!
You suck, Senpai.
Geez!
Lick my boo-boo, Senpai.
Geez! Can't you look at me even a little?
Do you hate me that much?
I don't hate you. I did look at you, even
when you were applying eyedrops.
Hmph. Whatever. I'm thirsty!
Okay, okay.
So this is it?
Be careful. I made it for you, but I don't know what it does.
It'll be alright. We became friends thanks to this.
No we didn't!
Besides, my mom got attacked by some men when
using this, so you really should be careful!
Yeah, yeah, it'll be fine!
Senpai, let's do it mouth-to-mouth.
Wh-What are you saying, Futaba-chan? Quit teasing me.
I'm being serious.
This will be the last time. I'm moving on with my life so I'll cherish
the memory of you giving me a drink, mouth-to-mouth.
This will be the last time.
You are such a dork, Senpai! Why so serious?
Yay! This will make Senpai more daring with me!
I don't know how long it'll take until
we see results, so don't blame me!
It'll be alright.
Se-Senpai?
Is it already working? This quickly?
No, something's wrong.
What should I do? What do you want me to do, Senpai?
Se-Senpai?
Huh?
Are we in class?
Oh, I'm alone with you, Futaba-chan.
What, did you skip class again?
Uh, um, Senpai?
Something's... Senpai is, huh? Something's...
No!
Is this what she was talking about? Is it the medicine?
No way! He has me up against the wall in a place like this? But...
Close your eyes.
No way, no way! Good job, Airi-chan!
Futaba.
Here it comes!
What did you just say, Senpai?
Suck my cock.
Th-This isn't right!
What are you doing, Senpai? You're a pervert!
This is so disappointing. Getting my hopes up like that, idiot.
Ouch!
The one who has something to look forward to...
is my cock.
Wh-What are you saying?
H... Hey!
Seriously, cut it out, Senpai!
This isn't what I wanted, Senpai!
This can't be happening! I didn't think
Senpai would turn out like this!
Please, stop!
I don't want this, even though it's Senpai's cock.
Isn't this what you like?
I don't like this!
Then learn to like it, Futaba!
This does nothing for me!
I won't forgive you for this!
I'm done with you once the medicine wears off!
I'm going to cum from your blowjob, Futaba.
No! I don't want you to cum in my mouth at school!
This is just perfect for a little nympho like you, Futaba.
Nympho? Me? Senpai!
Your perverted mouth-pussy is the best, Futaba!
Well continue once you finish swallowing.
No, Senpai! Please, stop!
I won't do this!
This is perfect for an exhibitionist like you, Futaba.
I am not an exhibitionist!
I don't want to do it in a place like this!
Yes, you do.
I don't want to have to hurt you.
I-I'm not afraid of you, Senpai!
You good-for-nothing Senpai!
Ouch!
Stop it, Senpai! Why are you doing this?
Stop!
Move your hand.
See? You're all wet.
Your body sure is honest, nympho Futaba.
I don't want Senpai to act like this...
I can't believe he called me a nympho!
This is the medicine's fault. However... but...
You like this, don't you?
I don't! I hate your good-for-nothing cock!
No! Stop, Senpai!
They can see! They'll see us!
Let's give them a show.
Stop, Senpai! This is embarrassing! Please!
You sure know how to ruin the mood, even though you like it.
I don't like it!
I don't want this! I don't want to do this
but why is my body hotter than usual?
Just accept it! You're a nympho, Futaba.
I am not! That's not true! No way!
My pussy is so happy to have Senpai's cock,
even though he's being so rough.
No! That's my g-spot!
No!
Is this it?
I'm scared. I'm going to cum! I won't be able to take it any more!
I really will lose it if I don't hurry up and make him cum!
Your good-for-nothing cock isn't doing anything for me, Senpai!
Is that so? Well then...
My perverted side will be revealed at this rate!
Stop! This isn't what I want!
This is as far as you go.
No! You've got to be kidding! They really will see us!
Well, let's put on a show for them then.
No! I really am indecent, Senpai!
I am a pervert!
Alright then.
No! Senpai!
No! I was enduring it...
Your cock is amazing, Senpai!
There you go!
You're being so rough with me with
your cock in a place like this, Senpai!
Stop, Senpai! I'll go crazy if I get any more cock!
Cum is coming out of your cock!
I'm cumming too!
Your cock is throbbing in my pussy!
He took her so roughly from behind, and Futaba's
expression... I couldn't stop them.
He was so rough with me and said such mean things...
I never thought Senpai could be like that!
Or is that what he really thinks of me?
Am I a burden to him?
But why did my body respond that way?
I'm not a pervert, and I don't like it when Senpai is rough...
I wonder if it's worn off by now. It'd be nice to have
the usual Senpai by the time he gets home...
Futaba-chan?
Damn, she's not here.
Senpai is still violent.
Did you think you could hide from me?
You're mean, Senpai!
I love getting a blowjob from you with
that expression on your face, Futaba.
This sucks for me.
I won't forgive you for using such a patronizing tone!
In what way? Do you mean that I have to satisfy you?
Quit playing around!
I'll get you back for this!
I'm looking forward to it.
This hurts. He's cumming in my throat.
That cute face is such a waste on you.
Being called cute by you doesn't make me happy at all, Senpai!
You idiot! I don't want this! I hate you, Senpai!
I hate you so much! Pervert! Brute! Scum! Trash!
What, are you mad because I didn't get you a ring? You pervert.
You're so mean! Why? Am I a bad girl?
You always do this to me, Futaba.
So you did think that way about me.
Am I right?
I was just bothering you, wasn't I, Senpai?
It really wasn't much of a bother, but more of a nuisance.
A nuisance? Why do you keep saying such mean things?
Won't anyone do as long as they can satiate
your perverted bitch pussy, Futaba?
What the hell? Do you really mean that?
You think my dick's a joke, don't you, Futaba?
In order to compete with Miharu.
I really do...
I won't let you get away with this!
I hate you! Scum! Pervert! Pervert! Idiot!
Good-for-nothing! Fatass! Scumbag!
Hey! Not there, Senpai!
What are you saying? Sex maniac! Worthless! Rock-head!
This is cruel!
What are you doing? This can't be happening!
It's in my ass!
What are you doing? Stop!
My ass feels strange. Please stop, Senpai!
It'll go in with another push.
This is...
What is this? My insides are so hot!
What the hell does he think he's doing?
Stop!
You'll get used to this right away since
you're a such a pervert, Futaba.
Stop, Senpai! Take it out!
Take it out!
You always say you want my cock, though.
What is that supposed to mean? You can say no if you want to.
I don't want to force you either.
I am saying no.
You're not taking me seriously.
Tell me the truth, you didn't like it.
Amazing.
Stop! It hurts!
Are you feeling horny already?
Stop! I don't want this!
This can't be happening! I'm getting hot
and bothered while being fucked.
Pervert.
This isn't doing anything for me!
I won't moan, no matter what.
You're no fun.
I'll hurry up and cum, and then go have some fun with Miharu.
Just hurry up and cum with your good-for-nothing cock, Senpai!
Senpai is cumming inside me!
What is this? It's so hot!
My ass feels weird.
Don't cry over such a trivial thing.
I told you to stop!
You liked it.
I did not!
Pervert! Scumbag! Idiot!
The medicine needs to hurry up and wear off already!
I don't want Senpai like this!
My ass hurts.
G-Get out, please.
I don't want to be in the same space as a scumbag Senpai!
This is my house, though.
Alright, I'll leave then.
P-Please, stop! I'm going to leave.
I hate you, Senpai!
Futaba...
Please... stop.
Look at me.
You came at me with your cock again,
even though I don't want it, Senpai!
Your scumbag good-for-nothing senpai
cock is brutalizing my pussy.
You know you like it.
I don't like your scumbag cock!
You sure are being quite daring, you good-for-nothing Senpai!
You aren't very convincing with your overflowing perverted juices.
Stop! My tits are going to sag from your lousy touch.
They're not big enough to sag.
Shut your mouth! They'll get bigger!
Then I'll help speed up the process.
I don't need help from a good-for-nothing Senpai!
Being fucked by your scummy dick is just a nuisance to me!
You say that even though you're sticking out your ass.
I am not!
Stop! Don't grab my ass!
Do you like it in the ass now, too?
I don't! Like hell I would!
Then prove it.
I don't want this!
Your good-for-nothing cock is in my ass, Senpai!
Please stop already!
I don't want this!
What are you saying with such a lewd expression?
I don't want this! Senpai!
I need to pee! Let me go to the bathroom!
Just do it right here.
What are you saying!?
There's no way I'd do something so embarrassing!
Look at you being shy while getting fucked in the ass.
No! Senpai, please! Let me go to the bathroom!
No! I'm going to pee!
Don't! Senpai! Don't look!
No!
I don't want you to do this to me, Senpai!
Hurry up and cum!
And leave!
I thought you were leaving.
Shut up! No!
My ass is hot!
No! This feeling...
No way!
This can't be happening!
Even though it's my ass...
I've gone crazy.
I peed myself again.
Huh? Senpai?
Hey, Senpai!
Are you alright, Senpai?
Huh? Why am I here, Futaba-chan?
Huh?
It's you, Senpai.
You good-for-nothing Sempai.
I'm sorry.
I see. I understand.
Don't worry about it, Futaba-chan.
Senpai!
I did such cruel things to you, Futaba-chan.
Yeah, you did do a lot of cruel things to me, Senpai.
I was trying to figure out what to do, too.
Be more careful!
Sorry. I'll be more careful next time.
What do you mean, next time! You never learn, Futaba.
This isn't working, Ushio.
You can be more rough.
I can't be rough with you.
What the hell is that supposed to mean? You
can't do to me what you did to Futaba?
No!
Not like that! Be more rough!
This is the best I can do.
Not like that!
Fuck me harder and rougher!
I wonder when I'll do it again.