Many Women Members・Free Registration・Quick Meet-ups Are OK
There is a particular online message board.
The girls who use it were often the ones who ran away from their homes, or truants from school.
There they arrange for "meet-ups" with strangers in order to have a place for the night and money.
For Kaito, who's not good at developing deep
romantic relationships, it is also a place where he can fulfill his desires in exchange of money.
Beautiful girl with a long black hair
living without a single relative:
Shinozaki Sumire
Sumire, being the an only daughter,
lived together with her single mother.
Her mother's sudden and unfortunate death from
an accident left her alone to fend for herself.
She tried to seek for help from her uncle,
a distant relative, only to be coldly declined.
She's barely making the ends meet that even
having a square meal every day is a burden.
Desperate to earn money to survive,
she registered at "Free Friends",
an online message board a friend told her.
It didn't take long for her to get a response
and started clumsily texting with a man.
Quelling all hesitations, she decided to make
an appointment and go meet up with the man...
Present Day Cool Student Teacher:
Kaito
I am an indifferent student teacher,
aiming to become a certified one.
My personal motto is to keep my
interpersonal relationships at minimum.
I hate nurturing closer relationships,
especially when it comes to women.
What I am yearning for is something way beyond these usual chance encounters.
Ever since I found about "Free Friends",
an online message board fit for finding
such instant relationships, I've been
using it to relieve myself of stress.
Even when I'm in the school under training,
I'm using the message board already as soon as the morning assembly at the staff room is done.
All for the purpose of talking with a girl
I am fond of that I recently get to know.
I've been posting in "Free Friends" to arrange
meet-ups with a girl of various circumstance.
Seeking for girls with no relatives and are
desperate to sell their body for money...
Seeking to get that pleasure at an
agreed time without any strings attached...
Sumire and Kaito met without knowing each other's names.
This fateful encounter ended up at an unlikely place: a love hotel.
He forced himself on Sumire who
was still baffled on her first time.
He payed five times worth for but only ended up
taking her virginity on that brief encounter.
They haven't met again since then,
but it never took long for both of them to cross paths again at the same school...
Reunited, the deeper bonds
between the two begins to unfold itself...
Furifure 2
Original
Animation
I-I'm gonna take a shower first.
It's my first time, you see...
I'm nervous and all sweaty...
The smell of your sweat spices things up.
Kai, your hands are... rubbing my tits...
Huh?!
Uhm... What's the matter?
Nah...
I thought that men who do this are the older ones...
No... That's my...
It's exposed... This is embarrassing!
They're beautiful.
You can let your voice out more.
No... It's embarrassing!
I don't want to, jeez...
No... This is bad!
It feels way better than when I do it myself!
This... I can... take this much!
I'm sure that's the landlord. My uncle
refused to give me any assistance.
I always relied on mom to take care of me,
and I'm all alone now that she's gone.
But even so, I have to keep going on.
I guess don't have any other choice.
Your thing is... incredible!
That thing won't fit in me!
Wait!
No... This position is embarrassing!
Ouch!
It hurts...
It's okay... You can start moving...
I can feel your thing deep inside me!
This is... amazing!
It hurts but... No!
It feels so hot deep inside me... No!
Let me hear you moan.
This is embarrassing!
It hurts, but...
No... It's going in deeper than before!
This can't be... Why... It's supposed to be my first time...
No... Not like this...
Kai... I don't want this, I'm...
Wait for me!
You left me alone, you're so mean, jeez...
It's you fault for dawdling around.
It's my first time doing it with a virgin.
I see...
How should I even reply to that?
Uhm, how should I say this...
What's the matter?
I got to meet with a pervert last time , you see...
A student teacher? He seems
cool but doesn't he feel kinda off?
Y-You think so?
Title
Delete this message draft?
Cancel
Delete
Mail
Inbox
Outbox
Drafts
Trash
He seems kind of gloomy and
he might have some sort of fetish...
He's a teacher so he shouldn't be
someone dangerous, right?
Kobayashi Kenjirou
Komori Kasumi
Shinozaki Sumire
Sudou Haruhiko
Suzuki Teppei
Kaito and Sumire's last...
What's wrong, Kaito?
N-Nothing.
And what's with the "Kaito"?
Well, you already found out about it.
I'll do something different for you today.
I'm talking about the last time.
You look like you're feeling good.
Wow! So it really felt that good.
Y-Yeah... It's because you were touching it.
I'm glad. I've been studying about this, you see.
I wanted to make you feel good.
This thing went inside me...
Saying that he's a weird guy...
It's twitching...
Hey...
It tastes bitter...
Wait, no! Not in this position!
Kaito, you pervert!
No... Stop, that's...
That is...
I don't want this... This is so...
Why am I...
We're siblings, and this is supposed to be wrong...
No... You're thing...
It's filling me up inside!
No... You're being rough!
You're going too deep...
No! I'm gonna...
Well then, I still have a homework so I'll be going.
What's wrong?
Don't be surprised.
The truth is, I am your blood-related brother.
Onii-chan...
Is that what you want me to say?
If you want a little sister incest role play,
then you will have to pay me more.
See ya!
Does he not have a girlfriend
'coz he has that sort of fetish?
Onii-chan...
It's 'coz I said we're siblings out of the blue...
And after we had sex, to be worse.
If you say that we're siblings,
then I can sleep over here, right?
Horndog.
It's your fault for dressing like that.
This is 'coz you peeped on me like that...
And also because the rent was too high for me...
That's why I'll be... with you...
You can stay here.
I couldn't really believe about us being siblings,
but I thought that I will believe in you.
Good night, onii-chan.
Pervert.
I can't help it.
You're already on with it!
I can't believe I have a brother
who'll assault me while asleep.
That's right.
Doing something like this, and talking like that...
I can't believe this!
So it was all true...
But I want our current relationship to last a little more...
No! This is...
No... You're filling me up inside!
It makes me feel safe when
we're connected like this!
Kaito, let's do it together...
Oh no... Kaito!
There's a lot of your semen!
Oh yeah, we went all the way so that's worth 30 000.
But I'll make it free since you're taking me in.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time On Furifure 2
No! We can't do this here!
No one's gonna come here at this hour.
You are a bad teacher!
Your lewd hand is rubbing my breast...
It's feels way better than usual...
No! Don't!
It's coming out!
W-Wait—
I said you can't!
I can't hold back anymore.
You're even making me do this, pervert!
Onii-chan, your thing is...
You're being too rough!
This is—
I look like a peeing dog in this position!
You're so lewd, onii-chan!
You're the lewd one, Sumire.
No, I'm not!
You're the lewd one!