Lots of Girls, Free to Use, OK to meet up immediately
Free Friends.
An internet board for run away girls and truants where you can start a relationship with a stranger. Get lodging for the night and got paid for it... That's what that internet board was about. Katio is a guy who's bad with deep relationships such as romance, so he used the board to exchange money for his desires to be sated.
A long, black hair girl with no living relatives
Shinozaki Sumire.
She was the only daughter of a single mother, and was left alone when her mother died in an accident. With no way to make money, she tried to sell her body to her distant uncle, but was denied. And now, she's in great financial distress.
In order to live, she needed to make money, so she registered on an internt board her friend told her about, "Free Friends". She nervously typed that she was a virgin on the board and got an immediate response...
Though she was a little hesitant, she steeled herself and headed towards the meeting place...
A modern day, "cool" teacher in training
Kaito.
He ended up deciding to be a teacher and is training to be one, but he always has a cold look on his face. His motto when it comes to relationships is to keep them basic. He hates getting too involved with people and even with women, he'd rather a quick fling rather than a full on relationship.
The "Free Friends" internet board was the perfect place for him. He since then, used it to release his stress. After saying goodbye to his fellow teachers for the day, he'd go right onto the board and post. There, he could find girls he liked and hook up immediately...
The two of them started using "Free Friend" for different purposes and ended up meeting each other by coincidence... One was on there because she had no choice and was looking for ways to get money... the other was looking for quick flings for pleasure...
Sumire and Kaito met without even knowing each others' real names. Though a meeting of destiny, it happened in a love hotel. Sumire was confused since it was her first time, so she pushed a little hard on the price. Though abrupt, her first time was worth fifty-thousand. She never thought they'd see each other again, but then she saw him again at school... Little did she know just how confusing their relationship really was. It might've been a reunion, but it was the beginning of something else...
U-Uh, I'm gonna take a shower.
This is my first time and all, so
I'm kinda sweat, from nerves...
I love the smell of sweat.
Kain, your hands...
They're on my boobs!
What? Is there a problem?
Nope.
I just figured you'd be an old guy.
No... That's my...
Being looked at is so embarrassing!
You're very pretty.
Let me hear you moan more.
That's too embarrassing!
I don't want to!
No! This is too...
This is more amazing than when I do it myself!
This...
This is...
Too much!
I bet it's the landlord.
I had to rely on mom to pay the bills,
but now I'm all alone and not
even my uncle will pay me for sex.
But I need to keep living.
I don't have a choice... right?
Kain?
Wow!
I don't think that's gonna fit!
Wait!
Don't! This position is too embarrassing!
Please?
Ow...
It's okay. You can move.
I can feel you deep inside me!
This is amazing!
It hurts a little, but...
No.
My insides are getting so hot.
Let me hear you moan.
That's too embarrassing!
It hurts, but...
Oh god, it's going even deeper inside!
No way... Why?!
This is my first time!
No, don't...
Wait, Kain, stop.
I...
Wait up! Why didn't you slow down for me? Meanie.
It's your fault for taking so long.
It was my first time doing it with a virgin.
Oh, really?
That doesn't matter.
How do I put this...
What's the matter?
The guy I met up with was a total freak.
A trainee?
He looks good, but isn't there something off?
H-How so?
Delete Draft?
Cancel     Delete
Inbox
Sent
Drafts
Trash
He seems shady or just like a total pervert.
But he's a teacher, so it should be okay, right?
Shinozaki Sumire
The last time Kaito and Sumire were...
What's the matter, Kaito?
N-Nothing.
Also, how do you know my name?
Well I guess the cat's out of the bag.
I'll do something different than last time.
So, give me a little more than last time, okay?
You look like you're enjoying this.
Wow, so it really felt that good?
Y-Yeah. It's because you touched me, Sumire.
I'm so happy!
I studied a little.
I wanted to make you feel good.
This was inside me...
He doesn't seem weird to me.
It's so... big.
H-Hey...
It's so bitter!
Wait... Not in this position!
Kaito, you pervert!
No! Stop! Too good!
It's too...
No, stop!
Why is this is so...
I...
It's because we're siblings.
We shouldn't be doing this.
No!
My insides are being filled with you!
No... this is so rough!
You're going so...
So deep!
N-No, stop! I'm gonna...
Well, I have homework, so I'm going home.
What's the matter?
Stay calm when you hear this.
I'm
your real brother.
Onii-chan?
Is that what you want me to call you now?
If you wanna do the sibling role play that's fine,
just make sure you pay me more, okay?
Later.
Is he just into weird stuff because
he doesn't have a girlfriend?
My big brother, huh?
I guess it was too out of the blue.
Not sure why I was expecting her to believe me.
If we're siblings, you'll let me sleep over, right?
Pervert.
It's your fault for dressing like that.
I was being peeped on and the rent was really high.
So that's why I'm here.
You can stay here.
I don't really believe that we're siblings, but...
I trust you, Kaito.
Good night, onii-chan.
Pervert.
Could I help it?
Are you serious?
I can't believe I'm the sister of someone as perverted as you.
Well, I'm not lying about that.
It's hard to believe you when you're doing this!
He was telling the truth!
But,
I want things to stay they are for a little more...
No... this is so...
No! My insides are full with your dick!
I feel so safe when we're connected like this.
Together with you...
No! Kaito!
There's so much of your cum, Kaito!
Oh, right.
That'll be thirty-thousand yen since
you went to completion, okay?
You aren't getting any free rides.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
We can't do this here!
No one's gonna be here now.
You're such a bad teacher!
Sensei, your dirty hand is on my boob!
It's going deeper than...
Oh my god!
No!
Wai...
No, stop!
I can't wait.
You're even making me do this?
You're such a pervert.
Onii-chan is...
Onii-chan's filling me up!
So intense!
It's like I'm a dog trying to pee!
Onii-chan, you pervert!
You're the pervert, Sumire.
No, I'm not!
You're the pervert, onii-chan!