On that day, I had fought with my dad and ran away from home.
I just couldn't go back there again.
I needed a place to stay overnight so I could think.
I had called some of my friends, but none of them were willing to help me.
With nowhere else to go, a friend of mine told me about a certain message board.
Furi... fure?
That day, I had to accept the consequences of my actions.
Presented by Oppaisubs | http://oppaisubs.net
Translator: shiken | Timing: Mr.Mew | Edit: D.R.A.
The Extracurricular Lesson of a Fallen Angel In a School Uniform.
I wonder if meeting someone else going through the same issues as me, would make me feel better?
Not even that, if I could just find someone who would listen to me about my problems, I'd be happy.
Hoping to find someone I could rely on, I signed up for the message board and arranged a meeting with a man.
I'm standing in front of the Central Line water fountain.
I have long, dark hair.
I'm wearing the Midorigaoka Academy uniform.
And I have a beauty mark on my face, so if you look closely, you'll know it's me.
I guess we wouldn't meet that easily after all, huh?
Kurahashi? Are you... Kurahashi?
Eh? Hirosaka-sensei...
It seems like students have been up to no good at night, lately.
Eh? N-No, this is... I just...
What are you doing outside this late?
I can't just leave you out here like this.
Sensei wanted to know what I was doing, so he took me back to his place.
Dry off with that for now.
Um, Sensei? You're married, right?
Where is your wife?
She's back in her hometown. We've been separated for half a year now.
I-I'm sorry to hear that.
If you want to take a shower, there's one over there.
I'm glad, though. If it's Sensei, he might listen to what I have to say.
Now that I think about it, it's probably for the best that Sensei found me instead of some stranger.
Kurahashi, I'm coming in!
Posting on that message board... You were expecting this to happen, weren't you?
Or did you want money?
N-No, that's not what I...
N-No...
Wanting your first time to be with your teacher, as expected of a virgin.
S-Sensei... please... Please stop...
You still don't get it, do you, Kurahashi?
No!
The one who answered your post on the message board was me.
You wanted this to happen, didn't you?
T-That's not...
Stop it! Don't touch that area...
If I kicked you out, It's not like you would have anywhere else to go, would you?
You don't want to go home do you, Kurahashi?
T-That's not fair...
I'll let you stay here for free, so let me take care of you.
N-No, that's not...
It's not a big deal, I have plenty of other students that are sexual deviants.
B-But... No!
Lift your legs up.
What is this... I'm scared...
Sensei, please. I don't want it to hurt...
No...
I'll try my best not to.
I'm putting it in, okay?
I-It hurts!
I've only put the tip in.
No!
N-No...
It's all the way inside me...
I can't breathe...
I'm going to start moving.
N-No, it hurts! It hurts!
Don't move anymore!
Get over it, you'll start feeling good soon enough.
No, p-please stop it!
It hurts, this doesn't feel good at all!
I'm going to break at this rate!
No way, it keeps getting bigger inside of me!
Your body just keeps getting tighter and tighter!
Kurahashi, I'm gonna cum!
N-No, don't. Anything but that!
No... No! Please!
Please, stop!
No!
It's flowing out...
After that day, Sensei continued to violate me several times, and always came inside me.
Don't worry, I'm sterile.
That's also why my wife left me.
Now that I think about it, Sensei didn't seem like he was enjoying himself either.
I think he just became desperate and lonely after his wife left him.
I ran away from home, so I had no choice but to do whatever he told me to.
What's the matter? Your clothes are still on.
Um, I understand. I'll take them off but can you look away?
No. Hurry up and take your clothes off.
I-I understand...
Make sure you put the swimsuit on too, Kurahashi.
Okay.
All right then, let's start. Kiss me.
Excuse me, then.
No...
No more...
Suck it.
Eh? Suck it?
Like I just said, suck it!
Use your tongue to clean it.
And be careful not to bite it.
Don't let your teeth get in the way and make sure you suck it thoroughly.
Good. Just like that...
This is the best, Kurahashi!
Don't try to spit it out. Make sure you drink it all.
Very good. I'd expected nothing less of an honors student.
Hey! Pull yourself together. We're just getting started.
Sensei continued to take his frustrations out on my body.
Don't try to rest, keep going.
Get it wet enough for me to slip it in right away.
Rub your nipples too.
Being watched while I masturbate is already embarrassing as it is, but with him watching so closely...
My body feels so hot. Much hotter than doing it by myself.
Don't...
Moaning like that... What a lewd girl you are.
Stop... Sensei, don't...
Please stop, I'm gonna cum...
Did it feel good, Kurahashi?
I... I...
There's no time for crying. We're going to do something that feels even better.
Sen-
Please stop it, already!
I-I'm gonna c-cum!
Sensei, please... just let me take a quick break!
I just came, so...
Even though you're saying that, your body is wrapping so tightly around my dick!
I can't... my body doesn't have any more strength.
I... I feel strange.
After being violated by Sensei so many times, I can no longer go back to normal.
Sensei, I-I feel...
Being violated so many times like this, I can't help but feel good!
Good, Kurahashi! I'll reward you by cumming inside you again!
He came again...
There's no time for any breaks.
We're staying at this hotel for the entire night, so we're going to enjoy every last moment.
Before I knew it, my body had became so perverted.
I couldn't resist Sensei anymore.
Sensei!
I can't take anymore, at this rate I'm gonna... No!
I won't get you pregnant, so you don't need to worry.
That's not the problem...
He's going to cum inside me again...
Sometimes Sensei does this, and licks my sensitive areas.
Even though it's embarassing, I force myself to do it for him as well.
I can't hold back anymore!
This is all because you were sucking my dick so lewdly.
I'm sorry!
My butt...
Sensei, it feels so good...
Wanting him to hurry up and finish quickly, I tried my best to make him cum as quickly as possible with my body,
and make him feel good.
I'll make you feel even better!
I-It hurts... It hurts... It hurts!
I'm gonna break!
Hurry up and cum, Sensei!
Please... just finish already!
I'm gonna cum!
With this, It's... finally over...
Even after violating me so many times, Sensei still wouldn't let me free.
Incoming Message
Not yet, Kurahashi. I'm still not finished with you.
No... no more!
Please, Sensei!
Please... Please forgive me...