Many Women Members・Free Registration・Quick Meet-ups Are OK
There is a particular online message board.
The girls who use it were often the ones who ran away from their homes, or truants from school.
There they arrange for "meet-ups" with strangers in order to have a place for the night and money.
For Kaito, who's not good at developing deep
romantic relationships, it is also a place where he can fulfill his desires for a price.
Beautiful girl with a long black hair
living without a single relative:
Shinozaki Sumire
Sumire, being an only daughter,
lived together with her single mother.
Her mother's sudden and unfortunate death from
an accident left her alone to fend for herself.
She tried to seek for help from her uncle,
a distant relative, only to be coldly declined.
She's barely making the ends meet that even
having a square meal every day is a burden.
Desperate to earn money to survive,
she registered at "Free Friends",
an online message board a friend told her.
It didn't take long for her to get a response
and started clumsily texting with a man.
Quelling all hesitations, she decided to make
an appointment and go meet up with the man...
Present Day Cool Student Teacher:
Kaito
He is an indifferent student teacher,
aiming to become a certified one.
His personal motto is to keep his
interpersonal relationships at minimum.
He hates nurturing closer relationships,
especially when it comes to women.
What he is yearning for is something way beyond these usual chance encounters.
Ever since he found about "Free Friends",
an online message board fit for finding
such instant relationships, He has been
using it to relieve himself of stress.
Even when he is in the school under training,
he is using the message board already as soon as the morning assembly at the staff room is done.
All for the purpose of talking with a girl
he is fond of that he recently got to know.
It was supposed to just be a carnal relationship,
but he ended up living together with her who's a blood relative...
This became a way for them to start a relationship
of drowning themselves in muddled debauchery...
In such a place as the school, their ever growing
and depraved relationship escalated even further...
Doing her from behind in an empty classroom...
Getting a blowjob in an empty toilet cubicle...
The two are unaware of the fact that there's no going back for them as they continued to fulfill their lust...
Whenever he calls for her, he ends up indulging
in depravity with her without a care of their surroundings...
Her friend who already had suspicions... unexpectedly confronted him...
However, that hindrance just spiced up his lust instead...
It only welled up his burning desire...
Before they knew it, their brother-sister relationship
started to take a turn towards a master-slave one.
Furifure 2
Original
Animation
Last Time On Furifure 2
Huh, you're awake.
Hey, Sumire.
You told me last night to do this.
Was that so?
If possible...
I'd prefer something like this.
You talk like that when you do
things even beyond this to me...
I want your thing inside me already, sensei!
Your insides feel incredible, Sumire.
Sensei, you're way bigger than usual!
The truth is, I also have that very same
family picture in my album.
Why?
I really thought that it was great...
but in the end being my brother
instead of a boyfriend is just too cruel!
Onii-chan, your thing is...
You're being too rough!
Onii-chan...
Come a lot inside me!
Keep on going!
Right there, keep doing that!
Your dick is making me...
I'm coming!
Onii-chan, you're filling me up inside!
Onii-chan...
Oh yeah, there's something that I need to ask you.
Just how many girls have you
met up with using that site?
Sumire, did you just go somewhere?
Huh? I just got assigned some chores...
That student teacher again?
Isn't that getting too often?
Jeez... Calling for me in a place like this...
We don't have much time!
You get horny so much, sensei!
The thing is, even after I've taken care of it...
You still get like this again in no time!
I get it.
We'll keep about us being siblings a secret in school.
I have to get this done and go back...
Your body says otherwise, though.
Jeez!
Hurry up and come already!
If you're planning to come like this,
don't stain my uniform!
Drink it then.
No way, it tastes bitter!
No!
Let go of me!
Jeez!
I already told you that it tastes bitter!
I swallowed a little of it, so that's worth 3000 more!
Then, let's go all the way while we're at it.
No! We can't do it here!
What are you thinking?
Aren't you aroused?
No! This is embarrassing!
Stop! There's not much time left,
and someone might come in here!
No! It went inside me!
No! My pussy is getting penetrated
while I'm inside the men's toilet!
Someone might come in here—
No way, someone really came!
It won't be a laughing matter if they catch us here!
You're kidding me! Stop!
He really is manhandling me!
No! I can feel the way it's moving!
I can feel how it slides in my pussy and even its shape!
No way, we'll be heard!
We can't do this, won't you
also get in trouble from this?
Get your act together!
Jeez, you're always doing things like this!
Pervert! Fuckboy! Scum!
And so are you for getting so aroused.
That's not true at all!
You're dripping down your feet.
There's this much of it?!
This is too embarrassing! No way!
Not in such a place like this...
Pervert!
What happened during lunch break?
Well, I was asked to photocopy some documents...
Right...
You weren't even in the staff room...
I'm being suspected!
By Miki, she's been doing "that" too.
Isn't it just fine?
Of course she can't know about this!
We ended up like this all thanks to her.
Jeez, I give up.
It would have been fine if we're
ordinary lovers, but this is...
What?
If she finds out that we're siblings having sex...
We can't let that happen.
That's what the society defines as deviant.
It would be bad if that gets out.
There's no way I'll tell anyone about this,
especially when I'm sucking my brother's dick!
You're right.
So, what are you gonna do?
About Miki? There's no way
I can tell her about this.
We can only let things be as they are.
Just what were you thinking?!
Wasn't she just cleaning or something?
Stop kidding me!
Laying your hands on a highschool girl, you pervert!
Never go anywhere near Sumire again,
or else the world will know about this!
Are you in there?
Jeez, you called me at the same time again!
Did you do as I told you?
I did it, just as you said.
It's worth nothing if you do it that way.
Come to the P.E. storage room right after your P.E. Class.
I'll be waiting.
Huh! Pervert! We don't have P.E. class today.
We don't have club activities
as well so I can't wear that!
Are you angry?
No, not so hard!
Don't knead them so hard!
With still my bloomers on? Sensei!
Never go anywhere near Sumire again!
No... Wait, sensei!
No way, you're being rough!
Hey, that spot is...
No! Wait!
Sensei, that's my...
No, no way!
Hey... No! You can't lick me there!
Hey!
No way, that place...
Wait, no way! Hey!
No, wait! That's the wrong hole!
Sensei!
No... No, you can't! Not that!
No... You can't!
Hey, wait!
No!
No, this is weird!
This feels disgusting!
You'll get used to it.
No way, I won't get used to this!
Pull it out already!
No... No! Stop! No!
I'm feeling weird!
No! It's pouring in my ass!
You're so mean!
I said no, but you still went on it!
Then, shall we stop this?
You must hate a relationship
you can't tell your friends about.
Wait! Why will you say that?
If I want to do it, I can call other girls.
Y-You can't!
You see, I was just shocked earlier.
I won't say that again.
Sumire is just being deceived!
I won't let that pervert do as he pleases anymore!
I'm the one who told Sumire about that sideline
so I have to pull her back to her senses!
Sorry for keeping you waiting!
She sounded so happy!
But before she gets even crazier, I have to...
No! Jeez, aren't we going to eat?
I'm gonna eat you.
No way, you're a dirty old man!
No, that's my ass!
Not again!
Hey, I said you can't!
Sensei!
Not there!
No, isn't this...
You're hard as rock!
Your dick has an amazing shape!
No... This is kind of amazing!
Something's coming out from the tip!
What is this stuff?
Hey, I can't take it anymore!
Hey, give it to me!
Good!
So intense!
Even though we shouldn't,
we're doing it here again!
It was you who wanted this and came here.
That might also be true!
That's why...
If you rub my tits that hard...
You're getting off from the pain, aren't you?
That's not true!
If you do any more than this...
No!
This feels awful! It's so deep!
It feels good! I can feel it deep inside!
Your dick is jammed inside me!
We don't have much time left!
So it's okay, pour a lot in me!
Good! I'm coming!
Let's come together, sensei!
No, this is... I'm coming! I'm coming!
It's pouring in... a lot inside me!
You're pouring in a lot!
You came a lot again here at school...
You're so robust, onii-chan!
Miki?
Onii-chan?
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time On Furifure 2
Jeez...
I can't hold myself back when I'm with you, Sumire.
I never felt like this before I met you.
Jeez... You're so naughty, idiot!
Just how many girls have you tricked
and left crying with that?
Onii-chan, your finger is rubbing my pussy!
Right there! Your dick is in my deepest parts!
Onii-chan!
My pussy is feeling weird and getting stirred,
it's getting teased by your dick!
S-Sorry, even when we're in this situation...
I-I'm fine with doing it... right here.
It's always me getting treated
like this, that's not fair!
Onii-chan...
I'm doing it with my brother in such a place...
Your dick is jammed deep inside me!
Onii-chan, it feels good!
Your dick is squeezing its way inside me!
No, onii-chan! You're being too sudden!
Stop rolling my nipples on your fingers!
You're so defenseless.
There's a lot oozing out of the tip.
You're almost there, huh?