Lots of Girls, Free to Use, OK to meet up immediately
Free Friends.
An internet board for run away girls and truants where you can start a relationship with a stranger. Get lodging for the night and got paid for it... That's what that internet board was about. Katio is a guy who's bad with deep relationships such as romance, so he used the board to exchange money for his desires to be sated.
A long, black hair girl with no living relatives
Shinozaki Sumire.
She was the only daughter of a single mother, and was left alone when her mother died in an accident. With no way to make money, she tried to sell her body to her distant uncle, but was denied. And now, she's in great financial distress.
In order to live, she needed to make money, so she registered on an internt board her friend told her about, "Free Friends". She nervously typed that she was a virgin on the board and got an immediate response...
Though she was a little hesitant, she steeled herself and headed towards the meeting place...
A modern day, "cool" teacher in training
Kaito.
He ended up deciding to be a teacher and is training to be one, but he always has a cold look on his face. His motto when it comes to relationships is to keep them basic. He hates getting too involved with people and even with women, he'd rather a quick fling rather than a full on relationship.
The "Free Friends" internet board was the perfect place for him. He since then, used it to release his stress. After saying goodbye to his fellow teachers for the day, he'd go right onto the board and post. There, he could find girls he liked and hook up immediately...
What was supposed to be a one right stand ended with Sumire finding out that she might be his long lost sister... Not sure of whether to believe his claim or not, she found herself outside his apartment. And so thus began their sudden life together... The two siblings who were separated from a young age deepened their bonds inch by inch with Kaito's meat stick... he did her as much as he wanted for the price of thirty thousand yen... That clear cut relationship continued between them...
Unable to resist carnal temptations... they turned to looking for chances even at school... Taking off her school uniform in an empty classroom... Having her suck his dick in her gym uniform with bloomers on in a bathroom stall... He gave her his flaming hot male essence in a variety of places... The bond they built through love making... became a seemingly bottomless, murky swamp that they kept falling deeper and deeper into.
Previous on Free Friends 2
U-Uh, I'm gonna take a shower.
This is my first time and all,
so I'm kinda sweaty from the nerves...
I love the smell of sweat.
Being stared at is so embarrassing!
You're very pretty.
Let me hear you moan more.
That's too embarrassing!
I don't want to!
Kain?
Wow!
I don't think that's gonna fit!
Wait!
Don't! This position is too embarrassing!
Please?
No.
My insides are getting so hot.
Let me hear you moan.
It's too embarrassing!
It hurts, but...
Wait up! Meanie.
It's your fault for taking so long.
This was inside me...
He doesn't seem weird to me.
It's so... big.
N-No, stop! I'm gonna...
What's the matter?
Stay calm when you hear this.
I'm
your real brother.
If we're siblings, you'll let me sleep over, right?
Oh, right.
That'll be thirty-thousand yen
since you went to completion, okay?
You aren't getting any free rides.
Awake?
Hey, Sumire...
You told me to wake you up, didn't you?
Yeah, I guess I did.
But if possible...
I'd like it done this way instead.
This is so embarrassing!
Why are you so big, first thing in the morning?
No... don't put your tongue there!
Stop!
How'd you cum this much? It's only morning!
Huh?
Better get going.
Yeah...
What's the matter? Study too hard?
N-No, not at all.
She'd be really surprised if she
knew what I did, wouldn't she?
Ugh, I struck out today...
Your face is kinda red. You sick?
No, no, I just feel a little warm.
Well, it is almost summer, after all.
What, Shinozaki?
Not gonna eat lunch?
Are you horny?
Sumire, you...
My body's on fire.
It's all our fault, Kaito.
Call me sensei here.
It'd be bad if people found out.
This is worse than me calling you by your name.
This... This is so embarrassing.
Y-Your finger...
W-We shouldn't do this!
Nobody's gonna come at this time of day.
You're such a bad teacher!
Sensei, your dirty hand is on my boob!
Oh my god, it feels better than usual!
Well, we are at school.
I want you inside me already, sensei!
It feels so good inside you, Sumire.
You're even bigger than usual, sensei!
It feels good.
You're going so hard inside me!
N-No... I'm gonna...
I'm even more...
No!
W-Wait, sensei...
Stop!
I can't hold back.
Onii-chan's getting off so much from me!
Sensei! No!
Any more and I'll...
You're a pervert, sensei.
S-Sorry.
I didn't get to eat lunch.
Just kidding.
My body's felt so warm since this morning.
It was really strange.
We might need to stop this.
Yeah, you're right.
I told you, that's not right!
Huh? You think so? I think it's fine.
School's out. Change and go home.
Oh, okay, sensei!
Okay.
Oh, actually, Shinozaki, I need to speak with you real quick.
I thought we were stopping this?
You're too perverted for your own good, sensei.
And do you know where we are?
It's your fault for staying here in your gym clothes.
You're really pushing the blame onto me?
It's so hard.
I need to get back soon or else Miki'll suspect something.
Might be easier without clothes.
Not mine.
Really? You're even making me do this? Pervert.
Peace sign?
That'll be twenty thousand yen
for making me do this here...
Onii-chan's too perverted.
It must be because he doesn't have a girlfriend.
I think it might be nice to try being
more romantically involved with him...
But knowing my brother,
I bet he'll open that door right now and...
I knew it. You're such a pervert, onii-chan.
No, don't do that, onii-chan!
You didn't believe that we were siblings, did you?
To be honest, I had a family picture in our photo album.
The same one as yours.
Why?
I thought it'd be nice if that guy in the picture
was my brother, not a boyfriend...
Oh, then why are you prostituting yourself?
I didn't just want to freeload off of you.
I didn't want you to buy things for me either.
Anyway, you want to do this, don't you?
It's twitching so hard. It's so dirty.
No... That's...
No, stop!
Sheesh.
Give me your dick, onii-chan!
Onii-chan's...
You're filling me up! So rough!
My stomac...
This position makes me look like a dog trying to pee...
Onii-chan, you pervert!
You're more perverted than I am, Sumire.
No, I'm not!
You're the perverted one, onii-chan!
I'm just doing this for the money!
No, onii-chan!
I'm...
No... Stop! I'm gonna cum!
Onii-chan came inside me!
No... I'm peeing!
This can't be happening!
You are such a pervert.
I told you, it just kinda happened.
You've been a total pervert
since the moment I met you.
Even after finding out we're siblings, you haven't changed.
That's your fault.
How exactly?
You just pushed all the blame onto your little sister.
How cold-hearted are you, onii-chan?
It's your fault that you're too cute.
It's not fair to say that.
You're hard again. Pervert.
Hey...
I'll stop if you tell me to.
No.
This'll be about five thousand yen.
If I'm gonna have to pay up anyway, then...
Your dick's so big!
Your tongue is so intense, onii-chan!
No... Not there, onii-chan!
Sumire, try doing it like I taught you.
Onii-chan's dick...
It's so amazing! Does your dick
really feel that good, onii-chan?
Yeah, it does.
Your tongue feels so good inside me!
Onii-chan, I'm...
Me too.
Onii-chan, right there...
My pussy feels so good!
Give me your cum!
That was too intense.
Onii-chan, you pervert.
What?! You just came, but you're this hard again already?!
It just doesn't go down when I do it with you, Sumire.
Your dick's pounding inside me!
I want to feel more of you, onii-chan!
Come in me more!
Onii-chan...
You're going to make me go crazy with your dick, onii-chan!
Cum in me lots, onii-chan!
I want you to leave your mark in me!
Just like that! Onii-chan, your dick is...
It's making me cum!
There's so much of your stuff inside me...
Onii-chan...
I just remembered. I needed to ask you something.
How many girls have you met on this site?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч