Many Women Members・Free Registration・Quick Meet-ups Are OK
There is a particular online message board.
The girls who use it were often the ones who ran away from their homes, or truants from school.
There they arrange for "meet-ups" with strangers in order to have a place for the night and money.
For Kaito, who's not good at developing deep
romantic relationships, it is also a place where he can fulfill his desires for a price.
Beautiful girl with a long black hair
living without a single relative:
Shinozaki Sumire
Sumire, being the an only daughter,
lived together with her single mother.
Her mother's sudden and unfortunate death from
an accident left her alone to fend for herself.
She tried to seek for help from her uncle,
a distant relative, only to be coldly declined.
She's barely making the ends meet that even
having a square meal every day is a burden.
Desperate to earn money to survive,
she registered at "Free Friends",
an online message board a friend told her.
It didn't take long for her to get a response
and started clumsily texting with a man.
Quelling all hesitations, she decided to make
an appointment and go meet up with the man...
Present Day Cool Student Teacher:
Kaito
He is an indifferent student teacher,
aiming to become a certified one.
His personal motto is to keep his
interpersonal relationships at minimum.
He hates nurturing closer relationships,
especially when it comes to women.
What he is yearning for is something way beyond these usual chance encounters.
Ever since he found about "Free Friends",
an online message board fit for finding
such instant relationships, He has been
using it to relieve himself of stress.
Even when he is in the school under training,
he is using the message board already as soon as the morning assembly at the staff room is done.
All for the purpose of talking with a girl
he is fond of that he recently got to know.
The girl he supposedly met up with that day...
which turned out to be his long lost sister...
is standing right at the entrance staring at him,
and talks about something far-fetched.
They suddenly ended up living together
under the same roof afterwards.
Deeper than the familial bond both the siblings share
have his rigid shaft shoved in her violently.
He penetrated and poured her full for thrice the price.
Their far-removed relationship went on like that...
Drowning in carnal desires for each other,
his rigid shaft curves upwards even when in school.
Copulating with her still wearing uniform sitting
at a desk in an empty classroom...
Making her suck him in a toilet of a private room
while she's still in her P.E. uniform (bloomers)...
Whatever became of their entangled and twisted bond
just keeps on sinking into a bottomless and murky depth.
Furifure 2
Original
Animation
Last Time On Furifure 2
I-I'm gonna take a shower first.
It's my first time, you see...
I'm nervous and all sweaty...
The smell of your sweat spices things up.
It's exposed... This is embarrassing!
They're beautiful.
Let me hear more of that voice.
No... It's embarrassing!
I don't want to, jeez...
Your thing is... incredible!
That thing won't fit in me!
Wait!
No... This position is embarrassing!
...No!
It feels so hot deep inside me... No!
Let me hear you moan.
This is embarrassing!
It hurts, but...
You're so mean, jeez...
It's you fault for dawdling around.
This thing went inside me...
Saying that he's a weird guy...
It's twitching... like this?
No! I'm gonna...
What's wrong?
Don't be surprised.
The truth is, I am your blood-related brother.
If you say that we're siblings,
then I can sleep over here, right?
Oh yeah, we went all the way
so that's worth 30 000.
But I'll make it free since you're taking me in.
Huh, you're awake.
Hey, Sumire.
You told me last night to do this.
Was that so?
If possible...
I'd prefer something like this.
Not like this... This is really embarrassing!
You're already big in the morning.
Don't put your tongue in there!
It's still early but you came so much!
H-Huh?
We have to go.
Yeah... you're right.
What's the matter, did you study all night?
Th-That's not it...
If anyone finds out what I'm doing,
won't they be shocked?
I got no meet-ups for today.
Hmm? Your face looks flushed.
Did you catch a cold?
No, not at all. It just feels a little hot in here.
Well yeah, it's almost summer...
What's the matter, Shinozaki?
Won't you have your lunch yet?
I'm feeling horny...
Sumire, are you...
My body is burning. It's your fault, Kaito.
You have to call me 'sensei' here.
It will all be over if we get caught.
You talk like that when you do
things even beyond this to me...
No... This is embarrassing!
Y-Your finger...
We can't do this here!
No one's gonna come here at this hour.
You are a bad teacher!
Your lewd hand is rubbing my breast...
Wow! It's feels way better than usual...
That's coz we do it here.
I want your thing inside me already, sensei!
Your insides feel incredible, Sumire.
Sensei, you're way bigger than usual!
Does it feel good?
Sensei, you're thing is ravaging me a lot inside!
No! I'm already...
This is way more than usual...
No! Don't!
It's coming inside!
W-Wait—
I said you can't!
I can't hold back anymore.
Onii-chan is so into me!
Sensei, you can't!
Any more than this...
You're so lewd, sensei.
S-Sorry...
I ended up not eating lunch.
Just kidding!
I've been feeling like my body is burning
since morning. It was so weird.
We'll have to clean this up.
You're right.
Hey, that's not the one!
Eh, you think so? I think it's okay.
It's already past school hours.
Hurry up and get changed.
Okay, sensei!
Okey-dokey!
Oh, I need to talk to you, Shinozaki.
Even making me come here...
You're really so lewd, sensei!
And here, of all places!
It's coz you're still here wearing that.
Now you make it my fault.
You're hard as rock.
Miki will start to get suspicious
if I don't go back soon.
Can you roll the shirt up?
Not my shirt.
You're even making me do this, pervert!
Peace sign?
Making me stroke and suck
you here costs 20 000 yen.
Onii-chan is very lewd.
I think it really is because he have no girlfriend.
I'd love to experience us being
more like lovers though...
It's onii-chan I'm talking about so
he'd open the door for sure and—
I knew it, onii-chan is really lewd!
No... You can't do that, onii-chan!
You didn't believe that
we're siblings, right?
The truth is, I also have that very same
family picture in my album.
Why?
I really thought that it was great...
but in the end being my brother
instead of boyfriend is just too cruel!
Is that so? Then How about
acting like a whore like this?
I feel bad for being a freeloader
so I can only pay by doing this.
Don't you want to do this too, onii-chan?
You're twitching down here,
it's like replying to me instead.
No! That place is...
No, you can't! Any more of that and...
Jeez! Give it to me, onii-chan!
Onii-chan, your thing is...
You're being too rough!
This is—
I look like a peeing dog in this position!
You're so lewd, onii-chan!
You're the lewd one, Sumire.
No, I'm not! You're the lewd one, onii-chan!
I was just doing this for the money!
No! Onii-chan, I'm gonna...
No, I can't! I'm coming!
Onii-chan is coming inside—!
No way, Am I peeing?!
This can't be happening!
Jeez, you really are lewd!
You're the one who asked for it earlier.
You're all about sex since we first met.
Nothing changed even after
finding out that we're sibling.
That is your fault.
What's with that?
Putting all the blame on your little sister,
just how cruel are you, onii-chan?
It's your fault for being so adorable.
It's unfair when you say it like that.
You got big again, pervert.
Hey there!
I'll stop if you don't want this.
Don't.
I think this will be around 5000 yen...
Since I'm gonna be paying for it...
Onii-chan's is so big!
No! Onii-chan, your tongue is being too intense!
No! Not there, onii-chan!
Sumire, say it just as I told you.
Onii-chan's dick...
Amazing, onii-chan! I'm making
your dick feel that good.
Yeah, it is.
Your tongue makes my pussy feel good!
Onii-chan, I'm...
Me too...
Onii-chan, my pussy feels so amazing!
Squirt it from your dick!
No more....
That's too intense! You're so lewd, onii-chan!
No... You just came but you're already...
It just won't settle down when I do it with you.
Your dick is pushing into me!
I want to feel you inside me more!
Give it to me a lot!
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, your dick is messing me up!
Come a lot inside me!
Keep on going!
Right there, keep doing that!
Your dick is making me...
I'm coming!
Onii-chan, you're filling me up inside!
Onii-chan...
Oh yeah, There's something
that I need to ask you.
Just how many girls have you
met up with using that site?
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization