That day,
I had a fight with my father,
and ran out of the house.
I just didn't want to go back.
I wanted a place to spend the long night.
I tried contacting close friends,
but no one replied with what I was looking for.
To me, who had nowhere to go,
a friend introduced a certain Internet bulletin board.
Meet Them right away Find them right away
FreeFriends
Begin with a simple registration
member Log In
Terms of Conditions
Free... Friends?
That day,
the sin that I had brought upon
myself with my carelessness,
I had to...
accept it no matter what.
~Extracurricular Lessons for the Fallen Angel in Her Uniform~
If I met someone who has the same worries as I do,
how encouraging that would be.
No,
even if it's just anyone who wouldn't
listen to me troubles,
it will definitely help me.
I registered on to the site feeling like it was my last hope,
I had a fight with my parents, and ran out of the house.
I was hoping for someone whom I can talk with.
I'm in front of the fountain at Central Street.
I have straight hair up to about my waist, and I'm wearing
the school uniform of Midorioka Academy.
and decided to meet up with a man who contacted me.
I have a mole under my eye,
so if you look closely you'll know it's me.
I'm in front of the fountain at Central Street.
I have straight hair up to about my waist,
and I'm wearing the school uniform
of Midorioka Academy.
I have a mole under my eye, so if you
look closely you'll know it's me.
I guess it's not that easy to meet someone...
Kurahashi?
You're...
Oh, Hirasaka-Sensei...
They talked about it on the Teacher's meeting.
That recently there's been students out late at night,
and doing some improper things.
Huh? Um, um...
This isn't it! I'm...
Either way, you're out here at this time of the day,
I can't just let you go.
Sensei said that he wanted to hear about my situation,
I brought me to his own house.
For now, dry yourself with the towel.
Um, Sensei...
You were married, right?
Your wife...
She went back to live with her family.
It's been half a year since we started living separately.
I... I'm sorry...
If you want to use the shower,
it's over there.
But, I'm glad it happened.
Sensei would be able to listen to my troubles,
and thinking about it, compared
to someone I don't even know,
it might have been better to have met Sensei there.
Kurahashi, I'm coming in, too.
The fact that you wrote on that site,
means that you were planning for this, right?
Did you want money for running away from home?
That's not true!
I wasn't thinking about anything of the sort...
No...
Doing it with a student...
That would be a first, even for me.
Sen-sensei...
Please, please stop.
Kurahashi, could it be that you didn't notice?
No!
The person talking to you on the site,
was me!
This was what you were looking for, right?
That, that's...
Stop!
Don't touch... those places...
You're sure you want to say that?
If I kick you out,
do you have anywhere to go?
You don't want to go back home, do you, Kurahashi?
That's mean...
I'll let you stay over for free,
just let me do you.
That, that's...
I can't...
Don't overthink it,
There are plenty of people at our school doing this.
But, but...
No!
Hey, spread your legs.
That, that's...
What is this?
This is really scary...
Sensei...
I beg you... not this...
No...
Relax as much as you can.
I'm going in.
Okay?
It hurts!
It's only just the tip right now.
No!
No, no!
It's going all the way inside...
I can't breathe!
I'm moving now.
No, stop...
It hurts... it hurts!
Don't move!
Endure it for a bit.
It'll start to feel good right away.
That's... please...
Stop already!
It hurts...
Something like this...
Doesn't feel good at all!
If this goes on I...
I'll get broken!
No way...
It's getting larger inside me...
No... It's twitching!
You insides here...
It's squeezing tighter and tighter!
Kurahashi... I'm about to cum!
Don't!
You can't do that!
No! No!
Please!
I beg you, stop!
No!
No way... it's coming out...
After that,
Sensei violated me again and again,
and came inside me.
Don’t worry,
I'm infertile.
That's also the reason my wife left.
Thinking about it now,
Sensei did not look like he was
enjoying himself the slightest.
I think he was depressed about his wife.
Now that Sensei has a weakness of me...
I had no other way but to listen to what he says.
What's wrong? You still have your underwear on.
Um... I'll undress, so can you turn around?
No.
Hurry and strip.
I... I get it...
Kurahashi. Put on your swimsuit.
Yes...
Good. Now, we kiss.
You initiate.
Yes.
Excuse me.
No...
No more...
Take it in.
Take it in?
I'm telling you to do this!
This is...
Move your tongue up and down,
and clean it up.
Don't bite.
Suck without using your teeth, and move in and out.
Good, just like that.
This is the best, Kurahashi.
Don't spill it. Drink every drop.
Good job, as expected from a top student.
Hey, get a grip of yourself.
We've only just started.
As if it was an expression of his frustration,
and his feelings for his wife,
Sensei attacked my body.
Don't rest your hands, tease the clit more.
Wet it so that I can enter right away.
Don't forget about your nipples, either.
Even though just having him watch me masturbate,
is already so embarrassing that I could die...
On top of that, he's right before me, too...
My body is heating up...
Compared to masturbating alone, I'm...
Feeling it so much more!
That's...
N-No...
No!
You can hear it right?
This erotic sound.
What a slut you are.
Stop...
Don't make such noises, Sensei...
No...
Something's coming...
What, what is it...
Kurahashi, did that feel good?
I... I...
You don't have time to cry.
We'll be doing things that feel even better.
Sensei...
Please stop already...
Cumming, cumming!
Sensei, please...
Let me rest for a while...
I just came... this is...
You say that, but...
You're squeezing tight onto me.
No... my body is losing strength...
I'm... going crazy...
I'm being messed up by Sensei...
I can't go back anymore!
Sensei... I'm feeling it!
Being forced...
Being violated is starting to feel good!
Great, Kurahashi.
As a reward, I’ll cum inside you again.
No, no!
Again...
You don't have time to rest.
We came all the way to a hotel.
I'll make sure to do lots.
My body...
Before I noticed, it had become completely lewd.
I can't leave Sensei anymore.
Sensei...
Too much...
No... No more!
You won't get pregnant Don’t worry.
That's not the problem here...
No!
No more...
He'll cum inside again...
Sometimes, Sensei will lick my embarrassing parts.
Even though I'm too embarrassed about it... I’m forced...
Don't...
I can't hold back anymore.
It’s because Kurahashi is so perverted while licking!
I'm sorry...
Stop... my butt...
Sensei... it feels good!
Wanting it to end quickly,
I moved my body with all I had,
shaking my hips up and down.
Make it feel even better!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
I...
I'll break!
Cum... Sensei...
Please... please end this!
Cumming!
With this...
It'll finally... end...
Even after messing me up so much,
and cumming inside again and again...
Sensei would not let me go.
Incoming Call
Not enough, Kurahashi.
I’ll be sure to pour more inside you.
No... no more!
I beg you! Sensei...
Please, please forgive me already...