Previously on Free Friends 2
Awake?
Hey, Sumire...
You told me to wake you up, didn't you?
Yeah, I guess I did.
But if possible...
I'd like it done this way instead.
This is worse than me calling you by your name.
I want you inside me already, sensei!
It feels so good inside you, Sumire.
You're even bigger than usual, sensei!
To be honest, I had a family picture in our photo album.
The same one as yours.
Why?
I thought it'd be nice if that guy in the picture
was my brother, not a boyfriend...
Onii-chan's...
You're filling me up! You're so rough!
Your dick's pounding inside me, onii-chan!
I want you to mark me!
Just like that! Onii-chan, your dick is...
It's making me cum!
There's so much of your stuff inside me...
Onii-chan...
I just remembered. I needed to ask you something.
How many girls have you met on this site?
Where'd Sumire go?
Huh? I think she was called to do something.
By that teacher in training again?
Isn't he calling her a bit too much?
Geez, you're seriously making me come in here?
I don't have that much time!
You're way too eager, sensei.
You always get like this so fast too.
Fine, I won't say anything
about us being siblings at school.
I need you to finish up quick so I can go back.
That's not what your body is saying though.
Are you serious?
Hurry up and cum!
If you're going to cum,
make sure you don't cum on me, okay?
Okay, then can you swallow it?
I don't want to. It's bitter.
Wai...
No...
Sto...
Seriously?!
I told you, it's bitter!
It's three thousand extra because I swallowed.
Then we might as well go to the end.
No! We can't do that here! What are you thinking?!
You're turned on, aren't you?
No... this is too embarrassing!
Stop! We don't have much time
and somebody might come!
No... It's inside me!
No! I'm having sex in the boy's bathroom!
Someone's definitely going to...
You're kidding! Someone's here!
If we're found out, we're really screwed!
Are you serious?! Stop!
There's something wrong with you!
I can feel him moving around inside me!
I can even feel the exact shape of his dick!
Stop! He'll hear!
Stop! You're a teacher!
This definitely won't be good for you!
Are you kidding me?! You always do crap like this!
You pervert! Sex-craved lowlife!
You're not too different.
Th-That's not true!
It's dripping on the floor.
That much?!
That's so embarrassing! No way!
In the boy's bathroom?!
Pervert.
Where were you at lunch?
Um, I was asked to make some copies of stuff.
Ah...
You weren't anywhere near the staff room though...
People are getting suspicious.
Huh?
I'm talking about Miki.
She's always been really perceptive.
Is that a bad thing?
O-Of course it is!
It's thanks to her that we have this relationship.
I'm done arguing.
If we were a normal couple that'd be fine, but if...
If what?
If people found out that we're siblings
and having this relationship, then...
We'll need to hide that part.
We'll definitely be called perverts.
It'd definitely be bad if we're exposed.
This might not sound convincing
while I'm sucking your dick though...
Yeah, true.
So? What are you going to do?
About Miki?
Well, I'm not telling her the truth.
Just gotta try to keep things the way they are.
What are you thinking?!
I bet she was just doing some cleaning.
Like hell she was! You pervert!
You're going after your students!
Stay away from Sumire!
If you don't, I'm going to expose you!
You here?
Are you serious? At this time again?
Did you not do as you were told?
I did!
That's not enough.
Gym uniform, gym storage room. I'm waiting.
You pervert!
We don't even have gym class,
I can't walk around wearing my gym clothes!
Are you angry?
S-Stop being so rough!
You can't be that rough!
R-Really? Sensei?!
Stay away from Sumire!
Wait, sensei! Y-You're being so rough!
That's too...
No... Wait, sensei! That's...
N-No way!
No, stop!
Not there!
Come on!
Wait, that's... No, don't!
No, not there!
Sensei!
No! No! Stop!
No! Wait! Listen to me!
No!
No! It feels gross!
Just get used to it.
No, I don't want to!
T-Take it out!
No! No!
Stop! This...
Inside...
No! It's coming!
It's in my ass!
You're so mean!
You just kept doing it even though I said to stop!
Then do you want to stop?
You don't want to be in a relationship
you need to hide from your friends, do you?
Wait, why are you...
If it's just for sex, I can find someone else.
Don't! I was just a little bit surprised, that's it.
I won't complain anymore!
He's deceiving Sumire!
I won't let that pervert have his way with her anymore!
It's my fault for introducing her to that site.
Slo-Mo     Video    Photo
I need to show her reality!
Sorry, I made you wait.
She sounds so happy!
But I need to stop her before she gets any crazier!
I thought we were going to have lunch?
You're my lunch.
You sound like an old man.
No... That's my ass!
No! Don't! Stop already!
Sensei!
Not there!
Wait, are yo...
You're so hard!
Your dick's shape is amazing!
Wow, it's so amazing!
Something's coming out from the tip... What's going on?!
I... I can't wait any longer.
Give it to me.
So good!
So rough!
We shouldn't be doing it here, but...
You came here because you wanted this.
You looked like you wanted to.
That's why...
If you grope my boobs that hard...
It feels good when it's a little rough, doesn't it?
That's not true!
If you keep doing that...
No! This is so rough!
It's so deep!
It's so big! I can feel it!
Your dicks filling me up!
We're running out of time. Go ahead, cum.
Cum a lot!
I... I'm cumming!
Let's cum together, sensei!
No, this... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
There's so much coming out inside me!
There's so much!
You came so much again.
You're so depraved, onii-chan.
Miki?!
"Onii-chan?!"
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч