Many Women Members・Free Registration・Quick Meet-ups Are OK
There is a particular online message board, where
the girls who use it are often the ones who ran away
from their homes or are truants from school.
There, they arrange for "meet-ups" with strangers
in order to have a place to stay for the night and money.
For Kaito, who's not good at developing deep
romantic relationships, it is also a place
where he can fulfill his desires for a price.
Beautiful girl with a long black hair
living without a single relative:
Shinozaki Sumire
Sumire, being an only daughter,
lived together with her single mother.
Her mother's sudden and unfortunate death from
an accident left her alone to fend for herself.
She tried to seek for help from her uncle,
a distant relative, only to be coldly declined.
She's barely making the ends meet that even
having a square meal every day is a burden.
Desperate to earn money to survive,
she later signed up at "Free Friends",
an online message board a friend told her about.
It didn't take long for her to get a response
and started clumsily texting with a man.
Quelling all hesitations, she decided to make
an appointment and go meet up with the said man...
Present Day Cool Student Teacher:
Kaito
He is an indifferent student teacher,
aiming to become a certified one.
His personal motto is to keep his
interpersonal relationships at minimum.
He hates nurturing closer relationships,
especially when it comes to women.
What he is yearning for is something way beyond these usual chance encounters.
Ever since he found about "Free Friends",
an online message board fit for finding
such instant relationships, he has been
using it to relieve himself of stress.
Even when he is in the school under training,
he is using the message board already as soon as the morning assembly at the staff room is done.
All for the purpose of talking with a girl
he is fond of that he recently got to know.
It is a relationship they cannot tell anyone about.
They let their arousal rule over both of them
in their escalating relationship, without telling
Sumire's best friend anything about it.
The two continue to fall lower in depravity as they
keep pushing beyond the risky boundaries.
On one of those days, that friend of hers caught them.
Her eyes are filled with horror as she intently stared
on those two who were unaware of her presence...
In the living room, the bathroom, the classroom, the toilet...
Each ordinary day turns into an extraordinary one
due to their depravity, making Sumire's
still inexperienced body throb and then
gently making it overflow and soaked.
And at that particular moment, a single word
breaking the taboo slipped off Sumire's lips.
A word that clearly reached her friend's ears...
"...onii-chan..."
Furifure 2
O
A
Ori
An
Origi
Ani
Origina
Anim
Anima
Animati
Original
Animation
L
La
Last
Jeez... Calling for me in a place like this...
Last Ti
Last Time
Last Time On
Last Time On Fu
Last Time On Furi
Last Time On Furifu
Last Time On Furifure
Last Time On Furifure 2
We don't have much time!
You get horny so much, sensei!
Jeez!
Hurry up and come already!
No! We can't do it here!
What are you thinking?
Stop! There's not much time left,
and someone might come in here!
No! It went inside me!
No! My pussy is getting penetrated
while I'm inside the men's toilet!
Someone might come in here—
No way, we'll be heard!
We can't do this, won't you
also get in trouble from this?
Pull yourself together!
Gosh, you always do stuff like this!
Pervert! Fuckboy! Scum!
And so are you for getting so aroused.
Of course, she can't know about this!
We ended up like this all thanks to her.
Jeez, I give up.
It would have been fine if we're
ordinary lovers, but this is...
What?
If she finds out that we're siblings having sex...
We can't let that happen.
That's what the society defines as deviant.
It would be bad if that gets out.
Just what were you thinking?!
Wasn't she just cleaning or something?
Stop kidding me!
Laying your hands on a high school girl, you pervert!
Never go anywhere near Sumire again,
or else the world will know about this!
Are you angry?
No, not so hard!
Don't knead them so hard!
No! Wait!
Sensei, that's my...
No, no way!
No, wait! That's the wrong hole!
Sensei!
Y-You can't!
You see, I was just shocked earlier.
I won't say that again.
Good!
So intense!
Good! I'm coming!
Let's come together, sensei!
There's a lot inside me!
You're pouring in a lot!
You came a lot again here at school...
You're so vigorous, onii-chan!
Miki?
Onii-chan?
Don't stand right behind me, I'll kill you!
Just what kind of assassin
are you? Cheer up already...
What are you saying, isn't all of this your fault?
What were you doing, Miki?
I was worried for you, so...
But, what's with that "onii-chan"? Are you siblings?
Miki, umm... Siblings, that's... Well...
It's a role-playing.
You see, it feels good whenever
Sumire calls me like that.
Don't give me that crap, pervert!
You're pestering Sumire to do
this, always calling for her!
I'm not forcing her. This is also Sumire's choice.
Stop meeting this pervert, okay?
You'll just end up getting hurt!
You can't tell her about us, huh?
That's right...
You can't even explain it to her, right?
Jeez, what should I do?
Oh, gosh...
I can't hold myself back
when I'm with you, Sumire.
I never felt like this before I met you.
Jeez... You're such a smooth talker, idiot!
Just how many girls have you tricked
and left crying with that talk?
Onii-chan, your finger is rubbing my pussy!
No, that's my clitoris!
Huh?! No!
Onii-chan, your dick...
It's all jammed up in my pussy!
It's reaching deep inside me!
No!
Gosh, getting so frantic like that.
Onii-chan, you're so cute!
You're saying I'm cute...
No, I wasn't making fun of you!
You're being rough!
This position...
It's making your dick rub even harder inside me!
Right there! Your dick is in my deepest parts!
Onii-chan!
My pussy is feeling weird and getting stirred,
and it's getting teased by your dick!
Right there, it's rubbing against me!
I'm coming! I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
You're filling me up inside!
This playboy brother of mine
is swiftly winning over my heart by doing this.
Calling me a playboy...
And you've been meeting with
several high school girls...
I just didn't want to settle with a particular girl.
Uhh... How about now?
Well, it all ended up with meeting you.
You really are such a smooth talker.
That's it! This coming weekend...
Window shopping is fun in itself.
Is that so? I thought that we're gonna buy some stuff.
We don't have to for today.
Let's do it next time, okay?
Roger that.
Do you want that?
It has a date function... It just piqued my interest.
I see.
Hey, where should we go next?
I was thinking about going home after this.
Ehh, no way! This is our first date!
I'll take you out somewhere again.
Alright.
Then, in return...
I'll understand if you're fine with that,
but I can't see this going anywhere good!
I understand that she's against our relationship.
But being able to spend time with onii-chan like this...
Shall we go home?
Our date isn't over yet.
That was surprising... It suddenly rained!
Didn't the saleswoman tell us that earlier?
Come on... That we're, umm...
That we're lovers?
Yeah, I just thought that it is how others see us.
Maybe that's how it is...
You think so as well, then!
Even so, we're siblings so that doesn't matter.
Yes, of course...
O-Onii-chan, I'm scared!
We can't go home with this weather, huh?
Did you feel horny?
S-Sorry, even though we're in this situation.
I-I'm fine with doing it right here.
It's not fair if it's just me!
Jeez...
Onii-chan...
Isn't having your first date with
someone you love the best?
Just stay still like that, onii-chan.
I'll do the moving.
You're inside me!
You're jamming up my pussy!
We're doing this in such a place...
Your dick is a tight fit deep inside me!
Onii-chan, it feels good!
Your dick is squeezing its way inside me!
You're reaching me deeper in this position!
Onii-chan, you're so intense!
To be able to do this with my brother...
Onii-chan, you can come whenever you want!
I'm already...
Onii-chan...
You're filling me up inside!
The downpour stopped.
Do you find it embarrassing when I do this?
My little sister wrapped around my arm is nothing.
I see, then it should be fine.
H-Hey!
Miki!
Here's the one you're talking about, Sumire.
Thank you!
That one's quite soon.
Really? Then I need to contact them.
See you, then.
Yes, I understand. I'll leave it to you.
Ahh, that took me some time.
I need to get some clothes on.
Why?
Onii-chan!
I don't want to get sweaty again!
That's your fault.
No, onii-chan! This is too sudden!
Stop rolling my nipples that
much with your fingers!
You're so defenseless.
No!
You're the only one around here,
so can't I walk around with just a towel?
No... You keep on playing with my clitoris!
No... Onii-chan!
Gosh, you always do stuff like this!
You don't usually get hard this much!
There's so much oozing out of the tip.
You're almost there, huh?
Onii-chan, you got big again!
Your outrageous dick went inside me again!
No!
It's going inside!
Your dick is so intense!
You're being too reckless!
You're so deep, onii-chan!
It feels good! More!
I can feel your dick deeper than before!
It's okay.
Keep doing what you want to me!
Keep lusting for me, onii-chan!
Onii-chan, give it to me!
Shoot lots of your sperm out!
I'm gonna come too!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
I'm coming...
Onii-chan, you came so much again...
So you have a staff meeting.
I'm gonna be late as well. I'm studying with Miki.
I understand. I'll try to get this done and over with.
I'll go now before I get late.
Take care on your way!
I have to earn enough soon.
They call me suddenly, and I
still am just a student teacher.
What a bother.
The number of cases increases at summertime,
so we should intensify our preventive
measure and increase our patrol...
I think it was called "King Castle"...
Thank you very much. I'll call for you again.
Did I find one already? Jeez, you're so obvious.
Yes, same here. Until next time.
Onii-chan?
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization