I wonder...
What are we really to each other?
Hey, I think this is really a bad idea.
This is the faculty restroom!
What are we going to do if someone finds us here?
How about telling them that I seduced you?
That excuse became invalid the moment we started doing this.
But I...
I really want to feel you more, Sensei.
What? You came already?
You really love this, don't you?
Neither of us actually confessed to one another,
so we don't know how the other really feels.
We simply desired each other in the heat of the moment.
But in reality...
Quivering Lips
I already taught you this before.
You're not supposed to mess this part up anymore, you know?
Hey...
You're too focused.
Delving too deeply into something isn't good, you know?
Say, why don't you take a break,
and have a taste of a little maiden sex?
It's quite effective, you know.
You're so annoying!
You come here every day and stay too long.
If you're ditching school, then work!
Contribute something to society!
And go home already!
Not listening!
I'm not contributing to a society that
I don't even know or care about!
Then try to know.
You're living on the same planet as them.
Of course, if it's about you Sensei,
I'm more than willing to contribute.
Using my body.
Idiot.
The spark that started my situation with Katakura Kon today...
...was an incident from when I was
the adviser of her class last year.
Hey, classes are still going on.
I became focused on straightening up this young little delinquent,
and one day our relationship went to an entirely different level.
But, I really don't know what's on her mind.
Hey, why are you here?
Okay, I get it.
The kid's going home now.
No, I mean...
Why are you with someone like me?
How about you Sensei?
Why are you letting me stay here?
Huh?
Is it because I'm a problem student that needs to be taken care of?
Well...
Or maybe,
you're just letting me stay so that you can
have this idiot girl anytime you want?
What are you saying?
I just...
This is so irritating!
I'm going home.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
I'm not telling an idiot.
I said just wait!
No...!
What?
Why did you try to stop me?
You're troubled that your pussy's about to escape?
There are some things that won't be
understood unless said clearly!
You've never said anything either.
I see...
She doesn't know either, just as I don't know what's on her mind.
We're both afraid we'll break apart if one of us opens up...
Listen, I...
Lo...
You’re the worst.
In the end...
What? You're this stiff down here.
That’s...
So you really just wanted to do it after all.
She's really wet down here.
For me to have met someone who's not only
a chicken, but also an anal sex lover...
I'm starting to feel sorry for myself.
What?
You're about to cum already?
Kon!
J-Just how much are you going to pour out Chicken-sensei?!
You came too.
You really do love this huh?
I'm going to put a lid on this once and for all.
You sound like a middle-aged man.
What's this?
Your insides are very wet and soft.
So? Your thing is also very stiff, and it's even bent upwards.
What?
I...
It's wrapping me tight!
Oh no...!
Kon...
You're cumming too much.
You too Sensei.
It looks like you're really trying to impregnate me.
Just don't say anything more.
Hey, Sensei.
Say it to me.
This time, properly.
I love you.
Once more.
I love you, Kon!
Sensei...
More, more...
Both of us were concerned.
Our relationship wasn't really clear.
We were anxious, cautious, even afraid.
That's why,
I wanted to reassure myself,
even with just a few simple words.
I'm about to cum Kon!
Jeez, I'm going to be late!
We did it too much.
Sorry about that.
The next day,
she finally wanted to come to school
after being absent for a few days.
Oh no, my hair's all messed up.
I didn't get to ask you last night, but...
What?
So, what do you think of me?
Of course, I...
L...
Lo...
TL Note: Suudon = Broth noodles
Suudon.
Okay, okay, no need to tell me you're also a chicken.
What?
You're the real deal chicken here!
I don't even know what that meant.
Hey, hey!
We're going out this time!
Going out.
Going out~!
What are we going to do if someone sees us?
That's not really a problem.
We're already dating, right?
But I'm your teacher, and you're my student.
You'll be in trouble too if I get fired from my job.
Fine then.
Hey, what are you...?
Problem? You're already stiff down here anyway.
Were you expecting something else?
Hey, stop that.
Let's make a deal.
If you can last until 10 am without cumming,
then I'll forget about it.
Huh?
In exchange, if you cum,
we're going to the amusement park.
What's with this girl?
She's really persistent.
Well?
I don't know.
You can't act as if you're not getting aroused you know?
I know all of your sensitive spots Sensei.
I see you're still very weak in this spot.
Want me to make the deal two cum counts instead?
You're probably about to cum any moment now.
Don't make a fool of me.
I'm not a kid.
Controlling when I cum is a piece of cake.
Then...
You came.
It's been a long time since I got to hang out like this.
Geez, if we get found out, you won't just get expelled you know?
What? So you're really sore about that after all?
Well, I'm not really bitter about it,
I'm just a bit upset that I wasn't able to turn you down completely.
Here, let's go and hang out!
Hurry!
Hey, wait!
True, it's been a long time since we've been out together like this.
I was too concerned with Kon being a student.
But, as long as I see her happy face like this,
I guess it's not bad to hang out like this.
That was fun.
Did you see my charm again, Sensei?
Those things shouldn't be said consciously, you know?
Hey, Sensei.
What?
Let's have sex.
Okay? Let's do it here?
What are you saying all of sudden?
Can't we? You don't want to?
We can't do it here!
Not in here, no matter how much you want to.
Okay...
Then...
I'll just have to make you want to do it here.
Kon...
Look.
Look at how I do it.
See? It's wet already.
What are you doing?
You see Sensei, I get really aroused simply by being with you.
When we held hands, or crossed arms,
I felt horny then.
So gross, right?
But...
I just can't help myself, because that's
just how much I love you Sensei.
Sensei, I want you to look at me as a woman, not just a student.
Good grief.
You really are an idiot.
You're freaked out with me, right?
I'm not.
Even I, didn't really intended to...
You really are an idiot.
And I am as well...
Oh no...
We just kissed... so it's really sensitive.
Yeah, your clit is already bulging.
You don't need to tell me that.
I should give it what it wants.
That's...
I'm about to...
Sensei, I came.
Let's do it more.
I really want to do it.
You're a woman now.
Really?
I wouldn't be like this if you weren't.
I'm going in now.
Okay, come inside.
Put your thing into my...
Kon!
Sensei...
This is amazing,
Your insides feel hot, I feel like I'm going to melt.
Your thing too Sensei, it's rubbing hard inside.
What are we going to do if we make a mess of the floor?
I don't care.
What?
I don't care what happens, as long as I'm with you.
Kon!
Amazing... oh no, I'm about to...
She's really a hardcore idiot.
And I really want to make a mess of her now.
It's coming.
Oh no, it's flowing inside.
I think I'm going to get pregnant.
It's okay, become pregnant.
Sensei...?
I'm going to take responsibility.
S-Sensei, oh wow...
You just came, and yet...
It feels even deeper than earlier.
We're also exposed in this position.
I can go deeper with this.
I know... but...
You don't like it?
I can't hate it now, can I?
Sensei...
Oh no, that's...
Not there!
I'm sensitive there.
I'm about to cum.
Kon, me too...!
Oh no, if you thrust hard like that...
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm sorry for today.
I'm not going to impose myself on you anymore.
Sorry for what I did.
So...
Hey, idiot.
Next week, I'm free on Saturday, so...
Let's go out somewhere, and find a place to stay for the night.
Okay...