Hey Akagi,
can we put an end to this relationship already?
We were just overwhelmed by the heat of the moment, right?
Do you hate me, Sensei?
Of course not.
But...
I won't let it!
Here, take a look.
I just licked your dick and it's already this wet.
Not only did you take my virginity,
but you're also responsible for making my body like this, Sensei.
You can't just forget everything at this point, can you?
Akagi...
Sensei.
I'm even good at this kind of kiss now.
Akagi...
It got big already just by kissing.
You want to put it in, right?
You want to slide it inside me, right?
Your insides are pulsating...
Yes, they are.
Because I actually came a little.
Y-You're the one who did this.
The one who made me like this.
Akagi!
Sensei, I love you!
You're my everything, Sensei!
A-And I'm ready to do anything for you!
Just this once.
Just one more time, and we'll have to end this.
This position... is making it go even deeper than earlier.
Akagi, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's coming out.
The tip is starting to bulge.
I don't think she's serious about it either.
Yeah, this is merely a physical relationship.
Sensei, we're still not done yet.
But we're out of condoms already.
I'm safe today.
Sensei, don't you want to cum inside me?
Cumming raw, pouring it all out...
Look.
She's just driven by her youthful impulses.
It's hitting me, Sensei.
Your raw dick is hitting me.
You're really into it now, aren't you?
This is amazing.
Your raw...
Your raw dick, feels even better without the condom, Sensei!
Oh yes!
Your insides are also sucking me in more.
It feels great.
I'm going crazy!
Sensei...
More, more...
I should always be wary of dealing with students.
She's still a kid, so I simply have to deal with her lightly.
Oh yes, oh yes!
I'm cumming!
I think... I'm cumming again.
Does it feel good here, Akagi?
Yes, it does.
Your raw dick is rubbing me inside.
Is it here?
Hey, is it here?
S-Sensei, it's too deep!
It's just in the heat of the moment.
It'll all end once I let her graduate.
That's just the extent of our relationship, so...
Sensei, Sensei, Sensei...!
Sensei...
Crap, I can't fap to this.
The situation feels very familiar.
This is a story from before I confessed to Kon.
I feel like I'm totally being dragged into this.
Sensei, your thing is surprisingly big.
What? Surprisingly big, you say?
If you moan that loudly, someone will hear us.
But, you're the one who's fucking me really hard.
Well, can't deny that...
This is...
I can really feel it.
Her nipples feel really stiff.
And her thing is pulsating hard.
She feels the same way.
She's getting more aroused thinking
this might turn out really bad for us.
Oh no...
What is this?
M-My body feels weak.
S-Sensei...
Please...
Hurry up, hurry up and finish this.
At this rate, I'm going to go crazy.
If you suck me inside that hard, I'll...
No, don't push too hard.
I'll start moaning loudly.
What? Did it really feel that good, Kon?
If you'll have sex with me regularly,
then I'll probably come to school more often.
What are you saying? Idiot.
A month has passed, and a lot of things have happened.
I feel like I'm having more problems both inside and outside now.
Maybe it's because I always cling on to troublesome things.
Just throw away all of those troublesome things~
Why are you here?
Huh? I said I might come here today, didn't I?
I never said you could take a bath with me.
Well, no need to be so uptight.
You're the one making me uptight, you know?
Here, a nude high schooler
for someone who's stressed and tired like yourself.
Why are you sighing like that?
The percentage of students who went
on to college last year was 67%,
which is a difference of about 2 points compared
to other prefectural institutions.
So, our focus of discussion today will be guidance
for future successful employment.
Selection for those in need of guidance will
be held by their respective advisors.
Kurosawa-sensei, do you have something to add?
W-Well, I think that's a good idea.
If they want to go to college, then let them do so.
I understand the principal's opinion about it,
but simply recommending things like that is just...
Sensei?
Before, I thought things were a lot simpler.
What is?
The world and everything around it.
I thought that as long as you did fine,
then there wouldn't be problems.
Unlike now, where everything has a cause and effect.
Of course, that's just normal.
I already understood that, way back in grade school.
There were endless nights where tension
and silence filled our home.
As if we were all trapped in quicksand or something.
Kon...
I was careful not to stand out too much at school.
I learned not to poke and how to not be poked by anything.
That's why...
I escaped.
Because I didn't want to stay at a place where I didn't belong.
Though, there was really only one place where I could escape to.
That's how it was.
Kon...
That's why people say that we should not try to escape it.
But...
I'm trying to understand whether that's really true or not.
When we escape, and finally reach that
point, are we going to be alone there?
In this situation, I should be scolding her with a word or two.
But...
Her warmth made me feel like it didn't matter at all.
Sensei, I feel hot.
Your thing is hitting my back.
You say that, but you're also....
It's really heating up in here.
It might be getting hotter than the bath water.
No, don't...
Don't rub it on my back.
Kon.
No, wait...
Sensei!
I said wait!
Jeez, what are you trying cum by yourself for?
Your back just felt good, so I...
Give me your first shot.
The real me, who would have tried to correct her right away,
actually brought this student in,
and right now she's in the middle of giving me a blowjob...
You really do like sex, eh?
I like having sex with you, Sensei.
Oh crap, I think I'm really cumming here.
You've been holding it in for quite a while.
It's really dense and sticky.
Was I really like this?
Hey, are you feeling dizzy here?
Let's continue on the bed, okay?
Kon, don't suck me in too tightly!
Does it really feel that good?
It feels... really good.
S-Sensei...
It feels really good...
Oh crap, I'm...
I'm getting overwhelmed by this situation.
Sensei... oh no...
Not... my clit too...!
This is too intense... no...
Damn, Kon!
H-Hey, Sensei...
No...
You've been fondling it all day, so...
I won't stop...
I don't need to hear that!
Kon, we're going to go all the way!
Sensei!
In the end,
we're exactly the same.
Desperate to break free from our shackles.
And at the end of the road,
I found Kon.
Sensei...
I'm about to...
More...
Sensei...
Something's...
Kon!
...coming!
Hey.
If staying here becomes too tough for you,
are you going to run away again?
Well...
I'm always escaping, always finding my place...
But I think, I'll always end up here in the end.
What's with that expression?
It's nothing.
And that was the story from before I confessed to Kon.