What exactly...
are we?
Hey, Kon... This is really bad!
This is the staff washroom! What if someone finds out!
You can just tell them... that
I was seducing you, Sensei...
Just being seduced is enough to
get me into serious trouble...
But... Sensei... I want to feel you more...
What's this? Did you cum already?
How much do you love this, huh?
Neither of us have had a confession, so
we don't know each other's feelings.
All we did was seek for each other's bodies.
No, no...
But, to be honest...
Trembling Lips
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | httpy/www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ ircjrizon.net
I just taught you this recently!
Don't make these mistakes...
You're pushing yourself too hard!
Too much of one thing is not good for you, you know.
C'mon, to cheer you up, how about
a kiss from a young girl?
It works real well.
Shut up!
You're here day after day as if you live here!
If you're not going to school then get a job!
Contribute something to society!
And go home already.
I don't want any of those!
I don't want to contribute to this
stupid society I don't even know!
Then get to know it.
It's the fish tank you live inside.
Oh, but I'd love to contribute to Sensei!
With my body.
Stupid.
The beginning for my half-ass relationship
with Katakura Kon,
Was when I became her homeroom teacher a year ago.
Hey, you should still be in class!
While I was getting worked up about trying
to correct her poor behavior in school...
The two of us...
Somehow, ended up crossing the line...
However, to be honest I don't
know what this kid is thinking.
Hey...
Why are you here?
I understand, okay?
I'll go home.
No, not that.
Like, why are you with me?
Then why does Sensei... let me be here?
Ha?
Because I'm a troublesome student
that you need to keep an eye on?
No...
Or what? A convenient dumb lady who
will do it with you whenever you want?
What are you talking about? I'm only...
This is unpleasant at its best!
I'm leaving!
Hey! What's wrong?
I'm not telling any idiots!
Just wait!
No!
What? Why are you now chasing after me?
Don’t why the pussy you finally got to run away?
There are some things that I can't
know unless you tell me!
Sensei hasn't said anything, either.
She's right... She doesn't know either...
She's scared that by saying it out
loud, we lose something...
You know, I, I...
Li...
You’re the worst...
And, in the end...
What's with this... you’re getting so hard....
That's...
Maybe... he just wanted to do it, after all...
She's incredibly wet...
He's chicken, plus he gets turned
on by his ass... poor me...
What? Cumming already?
Kon...
How much do you plan to let out, chicken-senseil?
It's not like you didn't cum, sex maniac.
This'll seal it.
That sounds like a creepy old guy...
What? Your insides all wetland squishy!
Huh? Sensei, too...
You just came... but you're hard...
and so rough...
What?
Wait...
I...
No...
It’s tight!
You can't!
Kon... you just came really hard...
Well, Sensei followed up and came, too...
Shut up...
Hey, Sensei...
Say it.
Eh?
Properly, this time...
I love you.
Again...
I love you! Kon!
Sensei...
More... more!
We were both anxious...
Out relationship was ambiguous...
And we were scared... to get hurt...
So... even with flimsy words... we wanted to know...
I'm cumming, Kon!
Geez, we're going to be late, now!
Doing it so many times after that...
My bad...
The next day, after skipping for several
days, Kon decided to go to school.
No... my hair is all messy...
I didn't ask yesterday, but...
Huh?
So, what about your feelings?
I... of course I...
I like...
I like u...
I like u-u...
I like u-u-u...
I like udon...
It's okay, I know...
You're chicken, too...
What? Well Sensei is just fried chicken with sauce!
That makes no sense...
Hey, hey!
We're going to go play today!
Recreation! Having fun! Having fun!
Having fun!
What do we do if someone finds out?
It's fine if they know!
We're dating, after all.
Before that, I'm a teacher and you're my student.
It'd be bad for you if I lost my job, too.
Then fine!
Hey, what now?
Huh? You're hard already...
Were you hoping for something?
Hey, stop!
Let's do this: up until 10 o'clock,
If you can hold back from cumming, I’ll give up.
Huh?
On the other hand, if you cum...
Take me to the amusement park.
What's with Kon today? She’s really forcing it.
How is it?
Who knows?
It's pointless to pretend you're not feeling it.
I know all of sensei's weak spots.
You're weak here as always.
Want me to change the rules to
you cumming the second time?
Looks like you're cumming already.
Don't joke around.
I'm not some kid. I can control
when I ejaculate, no problem.
Oh really?
Then...
Bingo!
It's been so long since I've played outside!
Geez, if anyone finds out, you won't get
away with just a suspension, you know.
Huh? Are you a bit angry, after all?
Well, it's more like I'm upset at myself
for not being able to say no...
C’mon, let's play!
Hurry!
Hey, wait...
But it's true... that we haven't been
out together for a while...
I paid too much attention to the
fact that Kon was a student...
But, if I can see such a happy face on her...
I guess coming out isn't too bad.
That was fun.
Sensei has re-realized my charm
and appeal, too, haven't you?
Say those things after you've fallen asleep.
Hey, Sensei...
Let's have sex.
C'mon, right here...
What's with the sudden...
No? But I want to...
Of course not...
Not here, no matter what!
I get it.
So...
I just have to make you want it, right?
Kon...
Look at me... while I do it...
See, it's already wet...
What are you doing?
You know... just being with Sensei... turns me on...
Holding hands... or linking arms... turns me on...
Hey...
It's gross, right?
But... that’s how much... I love you... I can't help it...
Sensei...
Not as a student... but, treat me like a woman...
Geez...
I'm such an idiot.
You were looking down on me, weren't you?
Not at all.
It's not like, I really wanted to...
And you're stupid, too.
Just as big of an idiot as I am.
No...
We just kissed... so...
I'm really... sensitive...
Yeah... your clit is standing up...
Don't say it out loud...
We have to take care of that...
No... that's...
Don't..
Sensei... I came...
Do me... more...
I want you so much... I can't help it...
You're already... wonderful as a woman...
Really?
If not so, mine wouldn't be like this.
Hey...
Yeah... I'm going in.
Come... Sensei's...
The sensei that I love...
Kon...
Sensei!
Amazing... you're insides are so hot... it's like I'll melt!
Sensei's is... so hard, too...
What if we get so into it...
we stain the floor or something?
It's fine...
Huh?
If it's with Sensei... no matter what happens...
Kon!
Not there... no, I...
This girl is really, stubborn on top of stupid...
You just want to mess her up...
It's coming...
No...
You came inside...
With this, I could get pregnant...
It's fine. Bear my child.
Sensei...
I'll be sure to... take responsibility!
Wait...
Sensei... that's...
I just came... but...
Just now... no...
This position... they can see from outside!
I can go in deeper... like this...
That's... true, but...
You don't like it?
There’s no way... I don't...
Sensei...
No, not there... not there!
It's... sensitive...
I'm almost... cumming... no...
Kon... I'm also...
No, don't thrust... so roughly...
It's coming, it's coming!
It's coming...
Sorry about today...
I won't force stuff anymore...
I'm really reflecting on it...
So...
Hey, stupid!
Next week...
I get Saturday off, too.
So... we can travel somewhere and stay overnight.