Hey, Akagi...
This kind of relationship...
Don't you think it should end?
It was just one wrong step we took back then... right?
Sensei doesn't like me?
That's not true.
But...
I... won't forgive you.
Here, please look.
Just from licking your penis, I'm getting this wet.
Sensei, on top of taking my virginity,
you also made my body so perverted.
Do you think you can just let go
now that we've gone this far?
Akagi...
Sensei...
I've even... gotten this good at kissing.
Akagi...
You've gotten so large just from a kiss.
You want to put it in, don't you?
You want to thrust...
Inside here...
Your insides are... twitching...
Yes... it's true...
I'm cumming... just a little...
Sensei's the one...
who made me... like this...
Akagi...
Sensei... I love you!
Sensei... I...
Sensei is everything to me!
If... if it's for Sensei...
I'd do... anything!
Just this time.
This will be the last time.
This position...
Even deeper... than before...
Even deeper inside!
Akagi, I’m cumming!
Cumming! I'm cumming!
It's coming out...
Your tip is spurting... deep inside...
This girl, too...
She can't be that serious about it.
That's right. It's just a physical relationship.
Sensei... it's not over yet...
But... we're out of condoms.
It's... a safe day for me today.
Sensei... don't you want to try letting it out?
Inside me... raw... spurt it all...
Right there, see? This girl...
She's just letting her emotion and desires run freely.
It's hitting...
Sensei's penis... raw...
Geez... doing whatever she wants...
Amazing... it's amazing!
Sensei's... raw...
You raw... penis...
So much better than with the condom...
Sensei!
Yes!
Your insides, too...
They're sucking on so hard...
It feels good!
I'll go crazy!
Sensei!
More... more!
I have to be careful about... my
relationship with my students.
They’re just children...
I can't take them too seriously...
Yes... Yes...
Cumming...
Again...
I think I'm cumming!
Is it that good, Akagi!?
Yes... it's amazingly good...
Sensei is raw dick... rubbing...
Here... huh? Is it here?
No...
Sensei... so deep...
It was just a moment's temptation of the devil...
Once she graduates it'll be over.
Let it out!
All... let it all out!
The relationship is only that long, so...
Let it out! Cumming!
Sensei!
Sensei, Sensei! Sensei!
Sensei...
Woah...
Unbelievable...
I don't think it's someone else.
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat j http.//www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Trembling Lips
That was a story long before I had confessed to Kon.
I think...
I've gotten myself quite deep into trouble...
Sensei...
Unexpectedly... large...
What you mean, unexpectedly.
If you make so much noise, someone will notice.
If they find us,
Sensei's the one... in real trouble, right?
True...
This...
No... it's too... I...
Her nipples are stiff and erect,
and she's twitching down there...
She's just the same.
Getting even more excited knowing that this is bad.
No... what is this...
My body is... losing strength...
Se... Sensei...
Please...
Hurry... hurry and end...
If this goes on... I think I'll go crazy...
If you squeeze so hard... I'll also...
No...
If you're so rough... my voice will come out...
Hmm? Was it that good, Kon?
If it means I can have sex with you...
Maybe I'll come to school every day from now...
What are you saying, silly.
A month of this relationship with Kon
who had been skipping school.
It feels like in and out I'm getting
into more and more work...
I guess I pushed myself into a troublesome job.
You can just forget about...
All the troublesome things...
Why are you here??
Huh? Didn't I tell you that I might be here today?
I did not agree that we could bathe together.
Don’t be so stubborn about things.
You're the one who's making me stubborn.
See? To relieve your stress,
Take the essence of a high-school girl...
Huh? What's with the weird voice?
The Education Continuation Rate last year was 67%,
Future Plans on the Education Continuation Rate
which is 1% lower than Prefecture West Public School.
To change that, for students who plan to go into work,
we suggest the teachers to help them reconsider.
We will leave the decision on individual
subject to the homeroom teachers...
Kurosawa-Sensei, do you have any suggestions?
Uh... it all sounds good.
Continuing in studying should
just be for those who want to.
It's not that I don't understand the
head teacher's intentions, but...
Why do we have to recommend something
they aren't even thinking of to them?
Sensei?
I used to think it was much simpler.
What?
The world in general.
If you just do good things, everything
will turn out alright, or something.
But now, it feels like everything's fenced
up and I can't do anything.
That's normal.
I got that figured out when I was in elementary school.
It was always like we were at a funeral
at home, with no one talking at all.
Nobody wanted it to be that,
but as if we were possessed it just went on like that...
Kon...
At school I had to be careful not catch attention,
and spend all my time worrying about
what others thought of me.
So...
I ran away.
I just couldn't stand having to be
somewhere I didn't want to be.
But... even if I run away, I'm still alone.
So, you know what I mean...
Kon...
And everyone says that... you shouldn't run away.
But...
I'm really wondering... if that is true.
Are you really doomed to be alone... as you run away?
Being her teacher, I should at least
have been preaching or something.
But...
Kon's body was just so warm, that
none of that mattered anymore.
Sensei, you're so hot...
It's knocking against my back...
If we're talking about that, you're also...
Right here, it’s really hot.
Might be even hotter than the bath.
No... don't rub it... on my back...
Kon!
No, wait, Sensei!
I said wait!
Geez, why are you trying to cum on your own?
But... your back just felt too good... I couldn't help...
I want to have... the first shot...
I should be trying to guide her back on route...
But in here I am taking my student to my house,
And getting fellatio...
You really like sex, don't you?
I like it with Sensei.
This is bad... I'm cumming just
thinking about this situation!
You really saved up...
There's lots...
Was I always... this kind of person?
Let's get out.
We can continue... on the bed...
Thick...
Kon! Don't squeeze so hard...
Is it really that good?
It's really.... good...
Sensei...
It's... wonderful...
Ughh. This is bad, I...
I'm getting addicted... to this situation!
Sensei...
No...
The same time...
Not my clit at the same time... no!
Not so... rough! No...
No...
Dammit, Kon!
Wait... Sensei...
You can't...
We've been... doing too much today...
I won't be able to hold back...
That...
You don't have to!
Kon! We're going as far as we can!
Sensei!
In the end, we were the same.
I ran away from all the fences and barriers I bump into,
and where I ended up,
There was Kon.
Sen... sei...
No...
I can't...
I'm really...
Sensei!
It's coming!
Kon!
Hey...
Hmm?
If one day it gets harder for you to be here...
Will you run away to somewhere else again?
I guess.
Running, and running, trying to find where I belong.
But unexpectedly, I might come back in the end.
What's with that face?
Nothing.
That was a story, long before I had confessed to Kon.