But, this is...
There's nothing to be bashful about, right?
We are mother and son after all.
Here, please sit down.
Didn't we often bath together like this before?
But, I've grown since then...
Oh, gosh! You're right.
Does this mean that you're lusting after Mom?
So you are conscious of me as a woman.
That, that's...
I'll have to punish you for being a lewd, bad boy.
We can't do this, Mom.
We're mother and son...
It's fine.
I'm just rubbing it with my hand.
It's getting hot and itchy down there...
It hurts!
Turn around properly, and show me, okay?
Huh?
Hurry!
You much be really feeling it.
The pink tip twiches whenever I rub up and down.
Is it strange?
No, it's very cute.
Sturdy cocks are great, but I really love this kind as well.
I'm, I'm becoming strange...
It's getting hot... and it's twitching...
Don't worry, let it all out.
Cum as much as you want from my hand job.
Oh, no! It's coming!
It's coming!
Amazing!
There's so much of the sticky stuff.
Mom will squeeze it all out for you, okay?
No...
I just came...
If you squeeze it now...
Mom, it's coming out again!
It's coming out!
At that time, I had never thought that
things would turns out like that...
The Busty Mom Penetrated and Impregnated by Delinquents
~The Game of a Family Falling into Loving Hell~
Translation: Snake | Timing: Anon | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobet | httpj/www.erobeat.net | #erobeat@irc.rizon.net
April - Times of Spring
Hey, didn't you say you'd help with the dishes?
Oh, this is bad.
Don't worry so much about the details, Obasan.
Like I said, stop rubbing my boobs.
If you don't stop already, I'm going to get angry!
Even if you're his friend...
But isn't your son safe from bullying,
because he's become friends with me?
That's... I am thankful for that but...
Where are you touching, bastard!
You're nipples are really hard, aren't they.
Did you get turned on by my technique?
It's just your imagination.
Who would get turned on by a delinquent like you...
This is nothing to me!
Well, if you insist.
Hey! What are you doing?
So you wouldn't get turned on, huh?
O-Of course not! Who would?
This is bad, I haven't done this in a while.
I'm really feeling it.
You, you're not planning to go all the way, are you?
I won't go that far.
But, this hot thing...
I can't calm down unless I cum at least once.
If you play along for a bit more,
I'll continue on being good friends with your son.
Okay, I get it.
But anything beyond this is...
I know, I know.
Wow, this kid's thing just might be amazing.
Huh? Do I smell something?
Coming from that sweaty skin...
A wave of feminine stink!
Shut up!
Just hurry and cum and end this.
Don't be in such a hurry.
I'll make you feel really good.
For some reason, letting him do whatever he wants...
Is starting do feel good..
Woah, what kind of face is that?
Your drool is flowing out.
Amazing it's larger than my son's..
It's so lewd!
What should I do...
If he were to insert it inside me...
What are you going to do?
What do you want?
I...  I...
Wait!
It's all out.
That felt great.
Oh, no... There's so much it...
The stinky stuff is all over the place
If I ever save up a lot, I'll ask for your help, Obasan.
Huh?
Or should I say, Kyouko-chan.
No... Calling me by my name is cheating.
The Busty Mom Penetrated and
Impregnated by Delinquents.
June - Times of Rain
It's rubbing..
A hot and hard one is rubbing against there..
What do you mean, there?
Stop pretending to be a good girl.
I've came so many times from my pussy being rubbed.
It feels good... I can't...
You're soaked, aren't you.
It's because you save up so much of your lust,
that you'd even go after your son, you know.
Having such a stiff one is cheating...
Having such a stiff one is cheating... It feels so good.
I can't think straight.
Oh, no... this is bad...
This... This is...
My clit is being rubbed over and over again by his cock...
That's an amazing face you're making.
Such a slutty messed up face.
Please... have mercy...
If this goes on, I... I...
A dream?
Oh, no... I had such a weird dream.
Like I thought, it's really wet.
What's this?
I've become really sensitive...
It feels so good that I can't stop.
My insides are reacting... It's overflowing...
More... more!
This isn't enough!
I want something hard, hot and thick.
It feels good.
More... More...
I want cock!
Please mess up my insides!
Huh?
No way. Is he watching me masturbate?
Watching me stir myself around there?
I want it.
I want something stiff and hot...
I want cock...
I don't care if you're my child, just fuck me...
M-Mom...
Please... Please...
If you...
If you love Mom then please, give me your virginity!
It inside!
My son is inside me!
It's hitting deep inside...
Thrust it!
Ram my womb hard!
Mom you're squeezing against me...
No...
The head is twitching...
Are you cumming?
Are you about to cum?
You've been holding back, haven't you?
Its all right. You can cum inside me.
It's coming! It's coming out!
Cum as much as you want, all inside Mom, okay?
Mom!!
Hey...
Do you...
Do you want to do it with Mom for real?
You can cum a lot...
Come over here.
You coward.
I will forever regret, not doing it with Mom on that day.
The Busty Mom Penetrated and
Impregnated by Delinquents.
August - Times of Summer
Stop, stop right now.
Let go!
I like how you put up a fight but it's just a bit too much.
Please stop! please!
Why are you doing this?
Aren't you his friend?
That's why I thought I'd do it, instead of that sissy, right?
Hey, don't zone out like that,
Or it's never gonna end.
Is it okay for him to come back and see this?
That... of course not...
This person is serious about raping me.
No, not in my son's room...
Resist all you want.
But whatever you do, I'm not gonna stop.
Hey, what's this?
You're completed drenched.
That's not true!
As if it's saying "I can't wait" to me.
That's...
You'll start feeling really good soon.
There's no way I'll feel good!
Let's give it a try then.
A large one came in...
Amazing!
Even though that place belongs only to him...
You'll become a meat hole.
Not for him, but for me.
Our bond will never lose against, such a dick like yours!
Like I care!
Don't rub there!
My G-spot is weak...
Let's see how long you can hold in for!
I'm being fucked by such a huge dick...
I'm going to break!
Being rubbed there feels so good!
Wow, what another slutty face you're making.
Please, don't rub against there anymore...
Or else I... My son...
I'll make you forget all about him.
With a son of our own.
Stop!
Please, I'll do anything...
It'll all vanish!
All my feelings for him will fade away!
You're at your limit, aren't you?
Why don't you just give up and become my woman?
No... No...
Not that easily...
As if I'd fall for such a cock.
Stop being so stubborn, Obasan.
Or should I say, Kyouko-chan.
I'm cumming! Cummingl!
Morel I want to cum more!
Make me cum more!
That's right.
I love you, Kyouko-chan.
Try moving on your own.
I want to cum more...
want a thick cock thrusting at my womb...
It feels good!
A thick one feels good!
A young man's big cock...
I'm cumming!
Amazing, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's coming! Semen is flowing inside me!
I let it all out inside you.
Did it feel good, Kyouko-chan?
can see it flowing... It's so lewd...
I can see it flowing... It's so lewd...
Hey! Give me morel
Do all you want.
Sorry I'm a bad mother.
But you know, it's all your fault.
What happened, Mom?
Just a little change of image.
How is it?
Good...
Don't I look so much younger?
S-Sure...
Where are you looking? Such a perverted child.
September - The Beginning of Autumn