M-Mom?
My mother has changed.
Completely from whom she was before.
Hey there. I got myself inside first.
What are you staring at?
Such lewd eyes.
Could it be that you're getting turned on by your mother?
No, I'm just thinking... what are
you doing with Shin-kun, Mom?
Isn't that obvious? We're washing our bodies.
Because Mom is really good friends with Shin.
How about you join in as well?
It's fine, I'll pass.
Ah, that's too bad. If you wanted I could service you lots.
Well then, Kyouko-chan, please continue.
What shall I do for you...
The Busty Mom Penetrated and Impregnated by Delinquents
~The Game of a Family Falling into Loving Hell~
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | httpy/www.erobeatnet | #erobeat@ircrizon.net
Oba-san will make Shin's all wet and covered in bubbles...
Hey, does a bubble bath feel good?
Shin's body is very sturdy, and it
looks great down here as well.
Ahh, my womb is twitching...
Mom... is kind of...
I've been waiting all this time...
Soaking myself down there and letting
out so much feminine stink...
Mom... My mom is doing such slutty things.
Oh my,
are you erect?
You're cock is getting larger from looking at your mother.
But... Mom and Shin-kun are... but, but...
You're only good at complaining, aren't you?
Although you never try to do anything yourself.
It's fine.
You can just watch me and Shin do erotic things.
Watch us and fap as much as you want.
Mom... Please, stop it already.
Hey, watch carefully.
A hard, huge penis going into Mom.
Wow, it's amazingly wet.
That's good! It's rubbing inside...
A hard and thick one...
M-Mom!
All the way deep inside my pussy,
rubbing... again... and again...
You're really lewd... actually masturbating...
But... but...
Let's keep going without hesitation as well.
Alright.
Mom... Why? Why are you making such an erotic face?
As if you're happy having lewd things done to you...
I'm...
Amazing... this is great!
I love it, I love it! I love dicks!
I don't care about that child anymore!
I'm going to become a slutty girl who always
waits for cock with a soaked pussy!
How shameful. Is that a face to show your son?
Hurry and give it to me. Shin's semen!
Wash my insides with white and hot and, sticky semen!
Cum! Cum, cum, cum!
Mom!
Oh, did you cum as well from masturbating?
I'm so happy. I'm so happy that I have Shin-kun.
As long as I have this penis, I don't need anything else.
Mom, please!
Don't leave me...
Well then, why don't you serve me?
As a maid, as a servant.
I have raised you up this far. It's
natural that you repay, right?
I'll do it. I'll do anything you say.
I'll always be a good child.
Are you happy with just that?
It's fine. That guy is...
I'm fine. As long as Mom is happy...
Hey Shin, fuck me one more time with your thick one...
Alright.
It's fine... If she's happy...
The Busty Okaasan Fucked and
Impregnated by Delinquents
November - The End of Autumn
You know, Shin's been bored with just sex,
and says he wants something exciting.
Your pink skin is twitching as if it wants something.
Stop! Stop! Don't look there!
My butthole... No! Don't spread it!
It's just your anal virginity, it's fine.
No. No!
Stop!
Even though I'm a man... such... such things...
You're such a slutty child. Even if you
say no, your dick is rock hard.
That's not... I'm... not that...
Well, I'll put it in for you.
If you're not a slut then you should bear it.
Be sure not to lose to your mothers
dick or your own ass-pussy.
I won't lose! Watch me, mom!
You're really a lewd child. Your
dick is even larger than before.
No! Not there! Don't rub my penis!
Mom! Why!?
Hey, do you remember?
When I was raped and forced to do what he wanted.
I thought you would come and save me
and yet you failed to notice my SOS.
That's not it! I was... I was...
It's not that you didn't notice.
You looked elsewhere on purpose, right?
That's not...
You found masturbating better than being
connected with me, didn't you?
You didn't want to get hurt, so you pushed
everything to Shin, and you just watched!
Don't stir up my asshole... No! Don't!
My penis is going to melt!
Your clothes match the masturbating pervert very well!
Your ass-pussy is squeezing really tight as well.
C'mon, hurry up and let out your dick-milk!
It's much better than masturbating yourself,
isn't it? C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
It came out, it came out! Perverted
semen came out! Shin, look!
But, there was no way that...
Shin-kun's boredom could be satisfied
by something like this.
December -Time of winter
And so, me and Mom...
No... No!
See? It's gone all the way inside. Your poorly done
dick has gone back inside Mom's pussy!
Why? Mom... such things!
But... Because Shin told me to...
What's wrong? You actually want to do it, don't you?
Make Kyouko-chan cum with your dick.
That's!
If you can't do that, I'll have to end
the relationship with you guys.
It's an end.
Jeez. How useless can you get!
Ah, Mom!?
I'm telling you to hurry up and do
it! You love me, don't you!?
Are you saying that it's fine even
if Mom is ditched my Shin?
Help me!
Please! I'm begging you! Move!
Violate me in front of Shin! Listen to your mother!
If you go on and finish him, there
would be no one in our way.
Haha, Shin, that's the best idea!
You have to say stuff like that earlier!
Inside of me, something was at the point of breaking out.
What's this? So enthusiastic all of a sudden!
I'll do it for you, lots and lots!
I'll do it just as Mom wants!
There, not there!
You can't keep attacking my G-Spot over and over again!
I know Moms weak spots, all of them!
What's this? Amazing! This is a first...
Even though you can't compare to Shin's
in hardness, length or thickness... Why?
It feels good! What is this...
It's hitting all the good spots...
This is really bad... sex between mother and son...
I'm getting really really excited.
More, do me more!
Lots and lots!
Amazing! I can feel it.
Hey, hey, Kyouko-chan.
Aren't you supposed to be my woman?
I guess as long as they have a dick,
it doesn't matter who the person is.
That's not it! I'm... not that kind of bitch,
not a slut who loses herself to any dick!
What are you talking about. You've soaked
yourself down there with pussy juices!
No! This is not love juice... this is just a
protection instinct... so I don't get hurt...
Because I'm being forced into sex...
Mom, does my penis not feel good?
Then, should I just stop like this?
No! No, don't stop...
You can't just stop in the middle of it!
If you stop now I'll go crazy!
Well then let's test it out.
The loyalty of Kyouko-chan.
Loyalty?
It's simple. You need to not give in to his dick
and resist cumming until the very end.
Resist? My son's dick... I hold back
and not cum. I'll hold back!
Mom will definitely pick me, right?
Hey! No! Wait, it's completely exposed...
No!
Well, let's begin.
It's Kyouko-chan's pussy's judgement time!
Yes! It's feels good!
Yes!
It's reaching! Deep inside... it's trying
to go back into my womb...
It's hitting deep inside... deep inside...
I can make Mom feel this good. So don't leave me.
Please stop! I understand... I understand
your feelings... so no more...
Why? Why? Are you holding back, Mom?
No! I'll cum I If this goes on... If
you do me anymore, I'll cum!
I'm having sex like you want.
Just for you, Mom! So... so please! Please!
I won't cum. I definitely won't lose
to my son. I won't give in!
That position is bad! This is bad! My weakest
spot is being hit... it's hitting!
Mom, please cum! Together with me! C'mon, c'mon!
I won't cum... I won't, cum... like I'd ever... cum...
In front of Shin... not when Shin is watching... never...
So are both of you feeling good!
It's flowing out... My son's semen
is... flowing back to my womb!
Mom!
I didn't! I didn't cum!
I ended up getting creampied by my son's dick,
but I held back from cumming just for Shin.
Well done, Kyouko-chan.
That's... that's....
I loved you... But.. I wished you expressed
your feelings like this earlier...
It's already too late.
Right now, both my body and my heart belong to Shin.
Mom...
I'm...
See you... Bye-bye... Farewell.
February - The End Of Winter
Shortly after that, Mom and Shin-kun disappeared.
I came to the hot spring with Shin and his friends!
I'll be doing fun things with everyone!
Show us your slutty boobs!
That's right, that's right!
Wow! Kyouko-chan is amazing!
Your ass, show us your ass!
Amazing, oh!
There's so many of rock hard dicks!
You're such a horrible mom. He must be crying right now.
That's why I'm sending him a video
letter so he doesn't feel lonely!
More, more! Give me more semen!
Mom's face says that it's really tasty...
Oba-san is so happy having you guys come from me!
It's just gotten started.
We're nowhere near ending yet.
Everyone's so amazing!
Mess me up completely! Cover me in semen!
Kyouko-chan's such a pervert!
Even though he's watching this on video as well...
It's fine. Don't worry about that child.
He'll end up masturbating anyways.
Here, I'm letting it out Be sure
to get pregnant, Kyouko-chan.
As expected Shin's dick is amazing!
Cum! Cum! Spurt it all inside my pussy!
Hey, more, do me more.
Cum more from Oba-san's body!
I'll work hard! I'll do my best to service you...
Oh dear. Looks like she wont be going home for a while.
Hurry up! Hurry and put a dick inside!
Spurt semen all over!
My pussy and my asshole,
my mouth and my boobs as well! Do whatever you want!
What should I have done?