Skipping class to masturbate is awesome.
You'll have to forgive my youthful indiscretions.
What the hell is this?
All Club Members
Come to the club room
"Come to the club room <3r?"
That's it?
What's up? What did you want?
Hi! I'm Elen.
Well then, I'll be going now.
You can't go running off!
Futa-Club!!
Japanese-American Chick Dick-off
My page has been hacked.
I'm the culprit!
Elen-chan says that she's an international
exchange tech student.
So that strange mail just now came from you?
She hacked my FaceBukkake admin
account before I even realized it.
Look at your pages, everyone! I pinned them!
I figured I had to hack everyone who was my type!
We've already been cyber attacked.
When I snuck in and took a look around,
I found tons of your futanari pics!
It was awesome!
Well, it is a porn exchange site for women.
Huh!? She's not surprised by dick girls.
That means...!
That's right! I'm a dick girl just like you guys!
Have a look!
Can I?
I'm no shy about being a dick girl!
There are lots of perks, and it's fun!
So? What do you want to do in our club?
She wants to have a competition with us.
In other words, she wants to fuck!
Speaking of which, you two... What are you doing?
What the hell is that?
Looks to be dick girl play gear.
She forced us to put them on.
So that means you already lost?
That's secret!
What the hell?
That's a pleasure sensor.
It lets me know how much pleasure everyone is feeling.
I can also control the machines with them.
Aya-tan!
You're just my type, Aya-tan.
Let's have fun!
Who are you calling "Aya-tan"?
Y-You have a foreskin!
Yes! Here's my penis!
It's delicious if you lick it like a lollipop!
Hey! No way, Jose! Don't stick it in my face?
Huh? "No way, Jose"?
Ah! "Okay"? Got it.
You're annoying. Take that!
Don't get all excited from a foreskin!
Geez! You have a ton of excess skin!
Prepare yourself!
Ah! Your fingers feel great, Aya-tan!
Nice!
You seem to be enjoying this.
Take that!
Aya-tan, I have a sex play request.
Look here! Lift up your cock!
It's gross that I can make an opening
even though you have a dick.
Geez!
Take that!
Your foreskin sure stretches out well. It must feel good.
Penises sure do have unlimited potential.
Deal with the cock of a stunning Japanese beauty!
This is the first time I've done this sort
of sex play, but it's really nice!
It's like getting a blowjob without the sucking!
This feels incredible!
Who would've thought that this would turn Aya-san on.
I can feel it all the way over here!
This isn't good.
It got me horny too.
I-I'm cumming!
Right back at you!
I'm just getting started. Prepare yourself.
Super Charger! Oh!
My penis is getting all twisted up on the inside!
Aya-tan! Flaccid penises can twirl around like this.
How does it feel?
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum again! I can't stop it!
Yo, yo!
Futa-Club!!
Futabu! Yes!
Geez, it's not like I can make a move
even if I'm called out during class.
All Club Members
Everyone is in
The gym right now
Come to the club room
Condom Ejaculation Convention Announcement
Bound Assplay Weekly Overload
Akane-san's Second Extension
Dick Training Gym
Well, that's how Elen-san, the exchange student
became our guest at Chick-Dick Club for today.
Why is the guest hosting this?
Well, you see...
All three of us of have already lost to her.
Or something like that.
I see. So we just have to play along with Elen-san, right?
Oh yeah, I forgot to mention.
There's a penalty game if you lose.
My cute elephant-kun...
I'm going to take embarrassing pictures of
you that leave nothing to the imagination,
and upload them to the net.
Pretty cocky for someone with an excessive foreskin!
Well, could you at least not upload them to FaceBukkake?
I'm going to upload the pics to both!
You can't escape from elephant-kun!
Oh! Okay, Akane-san!
You're not a dick girl! You wouldn't even have a chance!
Oh, just you wait! I have a dick too!
President, it's time to bring that out!
Are you sure, Akane-san?
If only I had a dick...
Check out this high-spec multifunctional mecha dick, Dave-kun!
The club president made this for me!
I'll make her cum, so just relax and enjoy the show, Prez!
Got it!
You want it from the back right from the get-go?
As you wish. Here we go!
I can see everything!
I'm checking you out in 4K UHD!
Eeny-meeny-miney-moe...
This is incredible!
Nikon camera tech sure feels great!
Well, I am a genius when it comes to pussies
ever since I became a dick girl!
This feels so good! It sure feels tight!
My pussy is filled up with Dick Girl Elen-san's dick!
This feels good, doesn't it?
W-Well, that's a robot, so...
I'm cumming! Something is coming out!
You lose!
Yay!
Little Penis-kun's back rotary engine was a little too sensitive.
Its optimal efficiency is something we need to keep in mind!
Well then!
It's about time for the final battle! Against the club president!
You sure are a cutie, Prez!
I would appreciate it if you'd cut it out.
You sure have a dangerous appeal, Prez!
It's really small and cute!
Let go of it!
Do you like titties, Prez?
I love titties!
Oh baby!
No, don't!
Mao-senpai is sensitive at first!
Elephant-kun is getting more erect!
P-Prez is so fast!
I'm... I'm going to cum again!
I'm sorry! Forgive me, guys!
H-Hurry up and get it over with, please.
Your cute little penis sure feels good, Prez!
How very very cute!
This sensation... this softness...
Big dicks are rather nice too.
Your pussy looks like it's already welcoming me.
Prez, I'm going to shove my super cannon up into you!
Look forward to it, okay? Yes!
Thick... So thick!
You're so tight!
Wow, you sure are taking your time.
Are you in it for the long haul?
This is as far safe driving takes us. Accel on!
Come on! Come on!
Looks like you're raring to go again, Prez!
Wow! Prez, you got a full chub without it touching your body!
What an incredible oxygen uptake!
Ah no! I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum! For real this time!
Oh, so this is miss club president's big bang dick...
I'm going to have a nice long taste of it with my pussy later!
Chika!
Prez!?
No!
Oh! What spirit!
Oh no! I'm losing consciousness.
I don't know how many times I'm going to cum!
What?
What happened? What's going on?
H-Hello!
You sure had our fill of fun!
Enjoy being throat-fucked as your punishment!
Alright, I'm going in deeper!
This is somewhat...
different...
This is payback!
Prepare yourself!
I won't let up even if you cry uncle!
This is different! Foreskins sure are awesome!
You sure give a mean blowjob!
It's about time.
Your hole opens up this far.
Alrighty then!
Please! Anything but that!
This is my next step!
So this blowjob is the real deal.
Cut it out!
People who fight back get punished!
It went in all the way! You've got the depth there, Elen-san!
My asshole... is going to be destroyed!
I haven't ever gone this far either, you know!
Nice milk! I'm going to cum too!
You win!
Futa-Club!!
Futabu!!
Thank you very much for the exciting experience.
I think I became a little more mature from this event.
Well, isn't that nice!
Japanese people sure are very scary even
though they are small... I learned a lot.
I'm thinking of having surgery in order to retrain myself.
S-Surgery?
That's... a pity.
But it is different when covered by a foreskin.
I just might want it afterwards if she cuts it off!
Come again?! What are you going
to do with something like that?!
Dick Club
Oh, I don't know? Bite on it? Wear it?
Like hell you will!