Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Futa Club!
Part 2
No more... I can't hold it anymore!
Huh?
It's locked!
Where is Akane-san??
Let's keep it clean!
I wonder which one the others use...
Standing? Squatting?
I can't disturb her while she's cleaning...
Large Bath
That's true!
It's strangely easy for the soap to bubble
up, and really simple to clean, Aya-chan!
It's because the wax from everyone is mixed inside!
Eh?
Well, you could say that it's an air freshener, too.
A lubricant, too.
And depending on the person, I'd
use it as a cosmetic as well.
As a punishment, I will now start to bully Aya-chan!
What for, all of a sudden!?
For anything!
Take this!
Hey! Wait!
Hey, Ai, stop!
I’m taking the top role today!
Once in a while is fine, right!?
Here I go.
There!
Wai...
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
I get it, okay?
Let's do stuff that feels good already.
For today, Aya-chan's place is for me alone to enjoy!
Why does it have to end like that?
Well I suppose it's fine. Only for today, thought.
Yes! Understood!
You won't get any action today, I’m sorry.
Hey, don't talk with that thing!
Aya-chan's so cute...
Hey, sit down.
Aya-chan, open your legs.
Aya-chan's being shy!
Even though your penis is so hard
and tall? It doesn't suit you!
Shut up!
Just hurry up and do it already!
Alright, alright.
Well then...
Here I go...
Aya-chan's pussy... the entrance is
tight, but that feels really good...
It's starting to feel good...
This small, wonderful pussy... is only for me... right?
Her pussy is so tight... I'm cumming right away...
I'm cumming already!
I'm going to let out lots and lots!
You're cumming?
I'm cumming!
Cumming!
It feels good, Aya-chan!
Creampie is the best! I can't stop ejaculating!
Ai...
Like always, you cum loads!
Hey, it's such a waste for the semen to flow out.
Well I guess it's fine. I can still cum lots.
I'll make sure Aya-chan stomach
will be expanded by my semen!
Expanded??
Just a moment...
Ouch! Hey, what are you doing!?
You're always teasing me during club
activities, so this is payback!
Alright! I'm taking over this mouth this time!
Hey, not there!
I know that Aya-chan loves it in the butt!
I said no...
This side squeezes as hard as your pussy...
Aya-chan's rectum is squeezing really tight!
It's true that... my butt is weak, so...
And... take that... off my penis...
I guess that can't be help.
Aya-chan's butt!
I can cum the rest I have, right?
Idiot! No more... will fit inside...
It's fine!
If it's Aya-chan, you can take all of mine!
Cumming again!
That was great, so satisfying!
It's been a while since I've felt this refreshed.
You worked hard, didn't you?
Let out about a litre or so, right?
Good for you, Ai.
Getting to ejaculate as much as you want.
I guess we have to clean up all over again.
You're getting too full of yourself!
You know what's happening afterwards, right?
Nessi!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Let's not go on anymore!
Nessi!!
No more Nessi!
Shut up!
The inspection will be soon! We
must fight with all honor and...
Huh? Where's the prez...
Well, I've taken care of the first shot for now.
I'm lucky that the prep room was open.
But it's still like this...
Is it okay to go ahead and use the masturbating
tools for new members?
Vice president!?
It's not good to sneak around alone.
But...
It suddenly got wet during class...
It felt like my penis was going to get erect...
I can't let it get erect in front of others,
so I had to head to the club's room,
but then the door was locked...
I'm so sorry President! That's because...
Huh?
It's probably because the drug I gave
you yesterday is finally working.
Huh? The drug? The kind that makes you wet and all?
Yes!
I thought that this type of play is needed once a while.
That's so mean, Sumika-san!
It’s fine, isn't it?
Prez has been all about Akane-san recently.
That's...
It's such a great opportunity, and for once
in a long time it's just the two of us...
Sumika-san...
I have something different prepared for today.
It could be too tight...
Well then, Mao-chan, let's spread your legs more.
Sumika-san, your eyes look scary...
Just thinking about thrusting inside the
prez's pussy makes me super excited...!
With this being its normal size, it's hard to keep it in.
Please be the cute prez for now.
Well then.
Has it always been so large?
To think that you'd be so serious at fellatio...
The prez’s small mouth... feels so good!
No, not this... please wait for a moment.
I had decided that my first ejaculation in
three days would be inside the Prez!
Here, I go, Prez!
If I put it all it, it'll rub against your womb, okay?
But first allow me to enjoy the Prez's vagina!
Don't stir around with your penis!
My insides are being pushed from below!
The prez's vagina feels really good,
I'm going to cum inside!
Is it okay?
I feel good, too, but my penis is in pain!
It wants to get erect!
I'm cumming, Prez!
It's been stored for three days, there's a lot!
I'm filling up the prez's small womb!
Prez, please put it in on your own this time.
It won't all fit.
It's fine.
The female genitals of a futanari girl are the
same size as her male ones, so it'll fit!
Is that even true!?
it's going... it's going in...
It's in!
Deep inside my stomach...
Sumika-san... please untie my penis... already...
But this feels good...
I don't want to faint...
It feels good, but it's painful...
Please endure it, Prez.
I feel good from your tight, cute pussy, too!
It's about time, Prez!
Cumming, cumming!
Asakura Mao is now in full erection!!
Vice... president... Sumika-san!
Let me put it inside, too!
Amazing! So this is the Prez's beastly true form!
I understand, Prez!
I'll be sure to let you cum inside me!
No... if this goes on, I'll faint...
Why... why am I tied up?
Well the prez is quite dangerous
after you get erect, you know.
Here I go, Prez. Is it okay?
Please get messed up by my penis!
Sumika-san's hot pussy!
We've done it, Prez!
Hurry and move, I can't hold back anymore!
It's going in! It's spreading it apart!
Here, with your mouth...
It's tight... but it feels good...
It's like you'll pull out my insides...
Sumika-san's insides feel good!
Hey, Akane-san, you join, too!
Yes!
You’ve gotten even larger inside!
Geez, Prez...
Prez's... thick semen!
Sumika-san!
To be honest, to fit Prez’s penis, I had special
expansion training for my pussy.
So that's why it fit so well.
How is my pussy?
It's hot... and dripping wet... I think it's great.
I'm so glad you like it.
Wow... if only I had a penis, too...
Geez, don't laugh...
Ah, I thought it smelled quite a bit.
What is this!?
Even though we just finished cleaning the bathroom!
Geez, no more!!