Futa-bu!
Mix!
Futanari World.
Now then,
we shall now commence
the 3rd Annual President Selection Physical Check-up!
Though, it looks as if you're all so not into this.
That's because all of us have to restrain ourselves
from cumming for the entire day!
And with it all stiff for the entire day
we can't even go to our classes
Okay, Akane-san,
do you still remember the Futa club's check up procedure and
the minimum stat requirements I taught you yesterday?
The width is measured at the thickest point.
The overall grading also includes the corona width itself,
as well as the amount of cum per ejaculation, right?
Correct, good work.
Since Ai's cum volume is already out of everyone's league,
we've already placed it at the top of this single criteria.
Alright!
I'm going to cum all over you!
I'm sure everyone already knows about this,
but the total score will determine who the next president and
vice president will be, starting with
the highest pointer, of course.
Futa Club Physical Check-Up!
*Zip*
Now, Akane-chan, please do the
check-ups with utmost accuracy.
Leave this to me!
Now, who shall we measure first?
I'm... number one!
Okay.
Here we go then.
Ai-san, your length is...
Well...
Eleven centimeters.
And your corona width is four millimeters.
Alright, I'm steadily growing!
I see.
So your body is still in active development.
How about your width?
Your width is...
Four centimeters.
Oh? It got smaller.
What?
I'm relieved it wasn't too perfect.
W-Well, our measuring devices were
kind of insufficient last time,
so there was probably a miscalculation or two before.
I'm up next.
This guy's really active right now, so
please don't stimulate it too much.
Okay.
Aya-san, your dick looks very intimidating!
Hmm... it's difficult to measure.
Its shape is rather crooked.
The length is twenty centimeters.
And the width is around... ten centimeters.
Nothing's changed, I guess.
What? That's a bummer.
Oh? Wait a second.
The corona width is twenty-two millimeters!
Oh yeah, it feels like it's been hooking
up inside rather more intensely lately.
U-Umm... it's a bit hard to hold onto this,
so I'd like to finish it quickly if possible.
Okay, right away then!
A-Akane-san!
Please do it more gently.
It's going to come out!
I-I'm sorry!
Sumika-senpai's dick usually feels soft and elastic.
But it looks really stiff today, it's hardened up to the tip!
Amazing...
Length is forty centimeters.
Width is six centimeters.
And the corona width is four millimeters.
I seem It's the same as ever.
Oh, so it has stopped growing?
Hey!
What are you still dilly-dallying for?!
Coming, prez!
Sorry for the wait.
Get the measurements over with already so I can cum!
Okay, okay, I got it.
Actually, yours is the one I look forward to measuring the most.
Because lately, it feels your thing is pretty
big whenever you put it inside me.
What are you talking about?
Whoa!
This is...
Forty-three centimeters!
It grew two centimeters in such a short amount of time!
Oh my.
If it continues to grow so fast,
we won't be able to distinguish it from the actual body!
No way...
Just kidding.
Now, it's time to measure the amount of cum!
Okay, mine is... this...
Ai, yours is small so you can't really go wrong here.
What?!
This is stressful.
Don't say that, prez.
I hate condoms!
Alright, about the measurement procedure,
this time, everyone will get their chance
to cum inside Akane-san on their respective turn.
I'll get fucked four times in a row!
We'll then measure its weight using this
Futa Club special weighing scale.
On top of this list is the smallest, going down to the biggest.
Ai-san, me, then Aya-san.
Eh? But yours is bigger, vice-prez!
But, I think I really won't be able to restrain
myself if I still wait after your turn.
Oh, of course, the prez is last.
Oh, oh no...
I think I'm going to cum quickly.
As expected of Akane-san's pussy, it still feels
really good even with a condom on.
Just cum to your heart's content, okay?
I'm gonna get squeezed!
Your ejaculation takes a really long time, so we'll just
measure what you can release in one minute.
It's coming!
She's really cumming a lot, and I can
feel it bulging in the condom!
This is my full power burst cum!
She's cumming an even larger amount!
She came a vast amount like always.
I think that's about enough.
Roger!
Okay! You're done.
Huh? It's over already?
I'm still cumming! How terrible!
The condom got left behind, but this is...
Alright. Just a wait a minute.
Here we go.
Sumika-senpai...!
It's really opening wide!
Umm...
About 1,300cc, | guess.
Ai-san, you sure came a lot.
Hey now, Akane-san, I'm your next partner.
Okay...
I've built it up since our training camp, you know!
I was actually starting to hallucinate
by the third day of my 'fasting'.
Prez?!
Oh?
I can't hold back anymore!
And you better stop messing around!
Yours is really amazing, prez!
Cumming first!
We're going to measure this, right?
I'm still cumming,
but, umm, 1... 1,200cc.
Oh well.
Now, Akane-san,
we're just getting started!
But this condom is still on...!
I finally realized that it still feels great
even when it's on after cumming!
The cum won't spill, so it'll just keep on bulging.
If this continues, I'll be using your womb to weigh my cum!
Ack.
She's all messed up.
Prez.
Prez!
Good grief, you're messing up this
important physical examination.
What a helpless prez.
Looks like you need some punishment.
Sumika-san, you went in deep all at once...
I'm saved.
Prez is already going berserk.
It's Prez's raw hole, it's Prez's raw hole...
And Sumika-senpai has gone berserk as well!
I'm getting filled completely with dicks, and I can't stop!
Just wait, it feels like something's about to burst inside me!
Wait, what have I done?
W-Well...
Th-The results of the physical examination shall
not affect our current positions for now.
No complaints here!
Okay, please clean up afterwards, prez.
I don't think she hears you.
Seems so.
My corona width is now increased to four millimeters!
Prez!
It's this late already?
I have to let it out soon.
It's already this stiff.
Just go.
I'm about to...!
It feels tight!
I have to take it to the toilet.
Love and Penile Skin.
I've finally caught up!
Oh, Haruka.
We went ahead thinking you might not come.
That's terrible!
Things always turn out this way, though.
Let's hurry to the classroom.
O-Okay.
What's wrong? Let's go already, Haruka.
Oh, I see.
It's Sanjou-senpai, eh.
Just give it up.
She's very popular, so you'll probably just
end up in the middle of the competition.
Jeez, just leave me alone.
I already came lots earlier today.
Why is this dick so perverted?
This dick will surely make even senpai...
Se-Senpai?!
I-I'm sorry!
I didn't know someone else was already here.
I'm really sorry.
It wasn't my intention to peek.
So I was seen.
This is so embarrassing...
But, the fact that you aren't in the practice room to jerk off
means that you're also thinking about something.
Eh? So, senpai, you also frequent this place?
Yes.
Since it's not fair you were the only one seen,
I'll show mine, too.
Th-This is... senpai's...
Because of its horse-like resemblance,
I felt reluctant to do it in the practice room.
It's gross, right?
Eh? No...
Mine too, with its very thick sheath,
I can only jerk off from the outside.
Before I realized it,
I was already making it a habit of hiding here.
S-So...
If it's okay with you...
Do you want to jerk off with me?
I kind of feel really refreshed now that
I've revealed everything to you.
Me too.
Haruka-chan, do you want to caress each others' dicks?
Here, this way we both jerk each other off.
Senpai, your thing feels hot.
It's all warm, and it looks beautiful.
I'm envious.
You see,
mine is sensitive due to jerking off lots
of times, so be careful with it, okay?
Okay.
And you can rub mine however you want.
Yours also looks big and cute.
Umm, are you dating someone, senpai?
Oh, no one at the moment.
Lots of people are into me, but I've yet
to do 'that' because of this dick.
Umm...
If it's alright with you, would you take my first time?
B-But, Haruka-chan...
Are you alright with this?
Yes!
Well? Is this okay?
Yes, it's fine.
How about you, senpai?
It's starting to squeeze me in.
It feels so good that I'm about to fall down.
Senpai's thing is deeply penetrating me!
It's coming out.
I want to see your real dick.
How cute!
Senpai, I'll cum again!
Me too, I'm about to cum.
L-Let's cum together...!
I'm cumming lots!
Oh yes!
Good morning!
Whoa.
Seems she stopped fixing it anymore.
No, because I have to meet with senpai
by the practice room later.
Good morning.
Sa-Sanjou-senpai?!
Whoa...
I-Is this really okay?
Yes.
She's now the type to go to school in such a dreadful state!
It's alright.
Haruka-chan, your insides feel great.
Senpai...
Good morning, Miss Yurie.
We have come for the preparations.
Mornin'.
A Certain Lady's Morning
Did you steep well yesterday?
Yes.
Excuse me.
It is quite dirty,
so we shall proceed to clean your lower parts as well.
Hey, Saki.
Please do it more gently.
My apologies.
It is done.
Shino-san, her change of clothing.
Y-Yes.
Wait, Maya, Saki.
You two are done for now.
I'll let Shino do the rest.
Alright, understood.
Umm...
Excuse me.
Whew, they're gone now.
Those two are really formal and rigid.
H-Here is your change of clothes.
Shino!
M-My lady!
You'll be late if you don't change quickly.
Forget about that.
Besides, I'm still like this.
Shino, you already know why I requested
for us two to be left alone, right?
R-Right now?!
Yup.
Even a blowjob is okay.
I-I understand.
Shino, that's not right.
A-Alright.
Yes, that's how you do it!
I like how you lick around the tip inside the sheath.
Shino...
You're really good at this.
No, not that!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
How was that?
It felt good.
I think your blowjobs feel better than the real thing.
Look. Do you know what this is?
You did well earlier,
so I thought of rewarding you after I didn't do it for one week.
Want it?
I want it.
Shino, you're really cute.
Come on, show it to me.
That looks a bit painful.
How did the entire week go?
It's about to burst.
I see. Then I'll release it now, okay?
Oh wow...
My lady...
Now, looks like the maid wants to put it in the lady's hole, right?
She wants to cum after not being
able to for an entire week, right?
It's okay.
Here.
You're already very aroused.
Look, my insides are now like this
because of your horse-like penis!
My lady...
Shino, that's too intense!
It's so big!
My lady, it feels so good.
Does it?
Here, fuck me some more.
Rub it inside me more!
I'm cumming.
It's about to burst out.
Go ahead and cum.
Just cum!
My lady!!
One week's worth of cum is pumping into me!
Hey, Shino.
Shall we rape them tonight?
Those two.
I'll fuck Maya, and you fuck Saki.
I'm looking forward to tonight, Shino.
Y-Yes.
Take care.
Shino...!
My... lady...
Go, just do it.
Just do it!
Do it, Shino! Shino!
For me, the yearly physical checkups are so troublesome.
It sure feels depressing whenever it's
time for the physical checkups.
I know, right?
Not only is it growing now, but it's really
bad timing to have the check-ups now.
...Since I've put on some weight.
Oh, Hikari-chan, I'm over here.
Alright, see you later then.
Decision! Yuuko-sensei.
But, the one who listened to my troubles...
Come in.
Excuse me.
...was Yuuko-sensei.
She was the one who listened.
I've been waiting,
Fudou Nana-san.
How are you feeling?
Alright, we'll start with the examination
right away, so take off those shorts.
O-Okay.
I'm pretty sure that it'll all work out with her, but...
I'm really looking forward to how you grow every year.
Getting that special check-up permit under the
pretense of being sick really was worth it.
It's hard but it can't be helped, right?
As your body is quite special indeed.
As you advised, I've done my best to manage it.
But it's starting to become noticeable.
Oh my.
Looks like simply wrapping it up won't do anymore.
You really do need that kind of P.E. uniform for this.
Let's see...
We're going to examine it now.
I'm taking it off.
Okay.
Sensei, if you pull it that quickly...!
It's still...!
Sorry about that.
Anyway, it sure is very sensitive as always.
It's bulging already.
Alright, we'll start by measuring its length.
Wow, this is some amazing growth.
I can already see just by looking, but it gets
even more shocking as I take the numbers.
It's twenty-eight centimeters!
N-No, no way...
It's width is eight centimeters.
Circumference is twenty-five centimeters!
This looks like too much to jerk off to now.
Yes, very.
You know what's next, right?
Y-Yes.
No need to hold back.
Just go ahead and cum.
I'm cumming!
My dick is about to squirt it out!
Nana-chan, wait...!
Immeasurable, I guess.
She came this much with just one shot.
Looks like she's having real trouble dealing with this.
And it's also very thick.
It doesn't feel satisfying with just masturbating, right?
I have the perfect present to solve just that.
Actually, I'm examining another student.
I'm sure you're going to be surprised.
It's finally my turn now.
Hikari-chan?!
No need to hide it.
I've already disclosed your secret in its entirety to her.
This can't be...
It's Nana-chan's actual dick!
See this? It's a sex toy that was made from
the shape of your penis last year.
Hikari-chan's pussy is opening really erotically.
Does it want to take my dick inside?
She can't just take normal dicks, so she really loved it.
She said she wants the real you.
Is it okay, Hikaru-chan?
I'm putting it in.
It's alright, put your thick thing inside me, Nana-chan.
Put it in!
Hikaru-chan, I'm sorry!
It's so... thick...
So this is how your real dick feels.
Now, I'll let this nuisance of a teacher go away.
It's going inside.
Your thing is really inside me!
I love this kind of huge dick!
My insides are really full!
Hikaru-chan!
It's completely taking me in!
I'm going to cum!
Your dick has completely filled my insides.
It's my first time having someone cum inside me!
Would you let me... fuck you again next time?
Okay, fuck me all you want.
Sensei, thank you.
Oh crap, I completely forgot about the actual chek-up!
Oh well.
I'll just put some numbers here.
It's so thick!
It just keeps on pushing and pumping!