This is the palace of love
for Yura and myself.
We're happily enjoying
our marriage in this room.
The Yabuki couple lives
next door to us.
They've been married
a bit longer than we have.
They seem to get along well.
But we haven't had sex
for more than a year...
But this person has problems...
Kyoko Omiya, the gynecologist.
She's my second cousin, and
she moved next to us on purpose.
She's been talking like a grown-up ever
since she was little and I hated that.
Makoto's mother told me
to take good care of them...
...so that they could have a baby.
But I'm 30 years old
and still a virgin...
Anyway, Yura and I are
enjoying our married life.
STEP UP LOVE STORY
2nd Season: Part 1 - White Lovers
So cute!
Those red foxes are cute, aren't they?
What are you doing?
You're being a bit rough, Makoto.
I always wanted to try this.
It's so tight...
Yura...
You can ask them to come along.
Really? I'm so happy!
I can't believe they do it every night.
This is dumb... what am I doing?
Running out of time...
What? Hokkaido?
We won the neighborhood association
lottery. It's 3 days and 2 nights.
Are you sure we can come along?
We'd be happy if you came.
I really want to go!
We can go, right, Makoto?
Of course!
Wonderful!
We were just talking about
wanting to go to Hokkaido last night.
Last night?
Hokkaido! I'm going too!
What? Umm...
You see, Kyoko, only
2 couples can go on this trip.
I kind of feel sorry for Kyoko...
I don't feel sorry for her at all!
She moved in next door
to us on purpose.
Besides, my older brother and I
don't get along with her at all.
Anyway, we should enjoy
this vacation by ourselves.
I can't believe she paid
for her own ticket...
But when it comes to
vacation, the more the merrier.
You might be right, but...
K-Kyoko?
What are you...
It's getting real hot down here.
My cute little Makoto...
You got so big...
Kyoko...
You're amazing, Makoto!
I wish...
It's wonderful!
We can't waste much time.
We have to go to Niseko by noon,
otherwise we won't be able to go skiing.
Okay, Makoto.
I think we should stay here
instead of skiing.
It's okay, Kyoko, you paid
for your ticket, so you can do...
...whatever you want.
Makoto!
You're being mean to Kyoko.
Sorry...
Is Kyoko really your cousin?
What?
Yes...
I see.
Are you okay, Yura?
Makoto! Where are you going?
I'll spin around and come back...
Oh!
The Yabuki's are
really good at skiing.
You're right...
Where's Kyoko?
She said she'd be
snowboarding with us, but...
She's being selfish again.
Hey Makoto, Kyoko is
the only one who's single.
I don't think we should be...
We shouldn't be flirting like this, huh?
Well, we can continue this
when we get back to the hotel.
Okay.
Here you go.
Please come downstairs to
the first floor for your meals.
Yes.
Please enjoy.
It's kind of small.
I don't think so.
It was a prize for winning the
lottery. We can't complain about it.
You're right.
Okay, let's go!
Already?
Hey! Let's get something to eat!
Coming!
Don't be lazy...
Does this mean she can
hear everything we say?
I think these walls are pretty thin.
I guess it's more comfortable
eating in our own rooms.
Of course, we won
this trip from the lottery.
Oh, I'm sorry. I...
It's okay. It's the truth...
But I paid for this trip.
So you can have those
deluxe meals all by yourself.
What do you mean by that, Makoto?
You really hate traveling with me, huh?
I don't hate it, but...
What?
Onoda.
You're going to take
a bath after this, right?
Yes.
Do you want to go to
the open-air bath?
Let's see...
The open-air bath is
supposed to be unisex.
Unisex?
Wait, I bet this kind of place
has only wrinkly old women, right?
Is that right?
Yes, that's probably it.
Makoto!
What?
Could it be...
Let's take a bath. Come on.
Hurry!
So many breasts...
I mean, so many women... women...
Onoda?
Are you okay?
Are you feeling dizzy?
I think you should
get out of the bath.
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
Let's have sex.
No, they'll hear us.
We'll do it quietly
so they can't hear us.
I don't know about this...
Do you want to do it
for old times' sake?
What's wrong?
Look.
Red fox.
I'm glad we saw the real thing.
It felt good, right?
Take a look, Makoto!
That bear has a funny-Iooking pose.
I think that bear is hungry.
Why don't you give the bear some food?
Here!
It's pretty cold.
I'll get some hot coffee.
I'm sorry, I will...
Don't worry about it.
Oh no!
I'm sorry!
Teahouse Bear
Did it come off?
Yes, I think it's going to be okay.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, but
are you two newlyweds?
Yes, sort of.
I envy you two!
Huh?
We're getting married next month!
Congratulations!
We've been dating ever since we
were in middle school. That's 7 years.
So I thought it might
be best to tie the knot.
Umm...
You have big boobs. I envy you.
What?
It bothers me since
I have small boobs.
They look cute even though
they're small, right Yura?
What?
Right. I agree.
Really?
This is wonderful. I hope we can be
a happily married couple like you two!
Did you have a good time? Huh?
Yes.
Let me introduce you to Kaoru
and Goro. We just met them.
Hello! I didn't know we were
staying at the same hotel.
Well, let's just take
a bath first, okay?
That's right.
You came all the way out here, so you
might as well enjoy the hot springs.
Wow, you have a really nice body, Kyoko.
But Yura is probably the
most feminine out of us all.
I'm not that...
I envy you.
My boobs are so small.
They say that small boobs have
less fat, so they're more sensitive.
I really worry about
my waistline these days.
I worry about my legs.
I have big boobs, so maybe I'm
not as sensitive to the touch?
Let's see...
I'll examine you.
Stop it...
Looks like we can get
some good breastmilk.
Please...
I see, being married
isn't easy after all.
We learned a lot today, right, Goro?
Yes, we did.
You don't need to have lots of sex...
...but I think it's very important.
If there's little or no sex,
then the woman feels very sad.
Hey, don't drink too much.
But we did it last night, right?
I'm sorry, she's drunk.
You do it every night, Yura?
What? No...
They're pretty bold...
Then why don't we all
expose ourselves and do it?
I can join you, right?
It's embarrassing!
What?
I guess I'll join them too...
Yura!
Do you want to change partners?
Sounds good.
Wait a minute!
You can do it with me.
No...
Yura!
Don't do it, Yura!
It's late, so nobody is in here.
Really?
This is romantic...
Yeah.
Someone's here.
Amazing, using both
his mouth and hands...
We shouldn't watch.
Go ahead and climax!
Makoto...
Hurry up and do me.
This is the first time I've heard
you say things like that.
It's just...
Match your partner's
breathing patterns...
I see, then we can
experience greater pleasures...
Makoto!
It was fun, wasn't it?
Let's go by ourselves next time.
Okay.
Why did you do that?
You did it too!
Oh, stop it!
I want a partner too!
You try to make it look
as if nothing is wrong.
The Knife of love won't show any mercy.
You just hold back your feelings
and live each and everyday.
You say you're used to it or
there's nothing you can do.
We should be much
more straightforward...
...and hug each other real tight.
Even if we're feeling
awkward at times...
On the night when I dream
as many times as I shed tears...
I'm sure an angel will smile at me.
Let's dream of all the stars in the sky.
I hope you keep on smiling.
Next episode
Yura and I went out on a date
for the first time in a while.
But when we went shopping, she began
to tell me that she wanted to work.
This work that Yura wanted
was to be a waitress.
A cute costume with a miniskirt...
Many customers are going
to be staring at her.
Plus she's too tired to
do anything at night.
This is really bad!
Next time on
Step Up Love Story 2nd. Part 2.
Yura in Costume.
Yura is all mine.
Yura in Costume