Futabu!!
Futa-Club!!
SubDESU-H
Manra Hot Springs Field Trip Chapter
Wow, the atmosphere here is awesome, Aya-chan!
Coming all the way here really was worth it.
I'm so excited about this hot springs trip.
Welcome.
Good day, we'll be under your care.
Welcome to the Manra Hot Springs.
I'm the newly appointed head hostess, Chie.
The place is already reserved for you.
So please, enjoy the place to your heart's content.
Okay!
Man, I really want to play now!
What are we going to play?
Are we going boating? Fishing?
That's not called boating, that's kayaking.
Now, now, everyone.
Do you still remember why we came on this field trip?
Studying Manra's inherited customs and culture,
as well as researching the Manra Festival.
Many people think that the festival held here,
is nothing more than a prayer for prosperity or good harvest, but...
It seems it also serves as an event for something else.
We know, and we already heard this lecture many times during our meetings.
Same for both of us.
OKay, I got it!
Research is important, but let's first visit the hot springs!
We're really pumped up for this.
All thanks to Akane-san.
I guess it looks alright.
It seems we're completely covered.
Manra Hot Water
Effects
Invigorating
Improves Youthfulness
Increases Potency
We can totally relax with this.
Alright, I'm in first!
I'm second!
Sorry, but I need to pee!
Make sure you clean yourself well afterwards!
This scene...
Where have I seen this before?
You mean this place?
Didn't you just see it in some hot spring magazine?
Well, maybe you're right.
Toilet
I'm about to burst!
Oh, it's Japanese-style.
Ah, that feels good.
The hot water feels just right.
It really does, and it's washing away all my stress.
Umm... Sumika-san?
This wet feeling just feels so good,
my dick simply got aroused.
Well, now that vice-prez has started already,
why don't we start doing it too?
Eh?!
I know that this place is covered, but...
Then, if anything happens...
I shall take responsibility for it!
For I am the Futa club's president!
Yes I am!
Now that you mention it, prez,
you lost in our game of cards on the bus, right?
Oh yes, we did talk about there being a punishment game.
Th-This kind of punishment game...
It probably isn't very appropriate to be...
Hey, not there!
Oops, I grabbed the wrong dick.
I am very sorry.
Ambushing me like that is unfair!
But, I see that your dick is already getting aroused too.
Aya-san, your thing is already on my soft spot.
And Akane too,
she's gotten a lot better at this already.
Aya-san, your soft breasts are pressing against my back.
Getting pleasured by breasts on both sides is just...
Prez, your thing is starting to bulge.
Oh no, I have to hold her before prez goes all out.
Akane-san,
please, point it away.
Th-That stimulation...!
Prez, your thing is...
I'm about to cum.
I'm about to cum already!
Prez, let's...!
Now for the breasts.
You're pushing it against my nipples...
We just dirtied the water.
It's okay, the entire place is reserved for us, right?
Umm, I'm the one who's dirty here though.
We know.
We'll go for your ass to make up for it.
Here.
Will it go in easily?
It's gotten a bit loose because of the hot water, so I think it's okay.
Aya-senpai, your dick really is thick!
Anal injection, complete!
Your ass is really gripping me tightly.
Akane-san, your pussy is opening and closing itself.
Since you're occupied with her rear, I'm going to take the front.
Sorry if gets a bit too tight.
Okay, here I go!
It's really tight with a double penetration.
I not even gotten serious yet,
so please endure it.
Okay...
Your front pussy and back pussy,
which do you prefer?
I love both.
Both of them are going wild inside me!
Too tight, I think I'm going to finish soon.
I can feel your dick hitting me from the other side, Aya-san.
I can't stop all of these pleasurable sensations!
Then, I'll go on ahead.
It's going to let it explode!
No.... stop!
If you lick me that passionately I'll...
Oh no, again?
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum again!
No, not by hand....
I'm going to feel good again.
It hurts, it hurts!
No!
Be more gentle if you want to continue.
Futa-bu!
TL Note - An object of worship housed in a Shinto shrine
and believed to contain the spirit of a deity.
A shintai?
In this place?
Manra Hot Springs Guide Map
I see.
I get it now.
Huh? Where is everybody?
Umm...
Excuse me.
Oh yes, what is it?
I can't seem to find my friends.
Would you happen to know where they are?
If it's them you're looking for, they left a while ago.
They said they were going to search for something.
Miss head hostess.
May I ask you something?
Yes?
Why is it that...
You seem to reek of cum?
Wh-What?
Do you know where my friends are?
Wh-What are you asking about?
I-I don't really know.
I'll take my leave then.
I knew something was up.
The futanari head hostess,
Chie-san.
Now then,
where shall we start our interrogation?
No...!
What a wonderful pair of breasts.
I realized something once I knew what the Manra Festival was all about.
The shintai that I saw on the picture,
I guess it just happened to look like one,
but it's clearly obvious with just the name.
They say that the truth is hidden in legends and folklore.
Well?
Should I stop?
Or should I just keep going?
Please do...
Chie-san, what is the purpose of this festival?
To ejaculate on the shintai itself.
It is said that if one keeps ejaculating on it,
a miracle will happen.
I see.
Letting a futanari do it is indeed interesting.
The hot water here is particularly effective for futanaris.
It has... hypnotic properties.
So that's what happened.
Oh, by the way,
what did you do to them?
I'm sorry.
I told them about something rare in the storehouse, and led them there.
Why would you do that?
I grew fearful,
when I noticed that you were all futanaris.
I thought that I would lose my place here,
if more of you came over here.
Of course that won't happen.
Is that so?
I guarantee it.
Sure, the festival is important,
but our dicks are originally meant to pleasure each other, anyway.
I'll never do anything to harm someone like us.
Thank you.
It feels good....
Where would you like it in,
in the ass, or in the pussy?
In my pussy... please.
Head hostess, your pussy...
It feels quite good.
Is that so? I'm glad.
I'm going to raise our position a bit.
Now, I'm going to slowly push it in and out.
Oh yes... it feels very good.
This... really feels good.
I'm about to cum.
Push it in faster now, please.
Chie-san, isn't it still a bit early?
Cumming is also part of my job.
I don't want to soil the tatami floor.
At least let me cum on that table.
Now that you said we can't, the more reason we'll have to do it.
It's going to be hard to clean.
Now, now, you need to twirl!
Oh no...!
A head hostess of a futanari specialty hot spring.
Your erotic qualities are wonderful.
Chie-san, your dick feels hot.
Sumika-san, your skin is rubbing very nicely on my skin.
Let's kiss, Sumika-san.
My dick is realy happy as it rubs on your pure and supple skin.
I think I can even call it a skin pussy now.
Chie-san, that's erotic.
Your tongue's movements are very erotic.
Your dick, it tastes great, but...
I kind of want to lick your pussy now.
Even your ass looks very cute, Sumika-san.
I suddenly feel embarrassed.
Your reverse tit fuck feels very good.
It's a sensation that can only be experienced by two futanaris.
Your small pussy,
it feels like it's even tighter now.
Old age can make your start a bit slow.
But,
once we get completely aroused,
we really can't stop anymore.
This small pussy,
feels very warm and amazing.
It feels like it's going to take my dick all the way inside.
Oh no, I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum!
Please cum.
Please, let it all out.
An amazing amount is coming out!
It's filling me up inside!
Me too...!
Man, why are we locked inside a storehouse?
About an hour or so has passed already.
I can't believe they'd treat their customers this way.
It opened.
Hey, Ai, wake up!
What in the world is this?
I can still do it...
But, she sure did cum a lot.
My oh my.
Sumika-san!
Well, now I see why you were scared.
Yes.
Futa-bu
I'm in a family that has given birth to futanaris for generations.
So, where's the place you're going to inherit?
That's a secret.
You can't just ask those things out of the blue.
You're right.
Yup, there are indeed secrets that must never be told.
Glory to all futanaris, right?
Then I'll be the father,
and Aya will be the mother.
Hey, it's supposed to be the other way around!