Here you go!
What?
Please support us!
Yes, thanks for...
Makoto!
Yura...
Did I keep you waiting?
No, not at all.
STEP UP LOVE STORY
2nd Season: Part 2 - Yura in costume
I'm sorry for making
you come out like this.
We haven't dated
like this for a long time.
Yeah, it's fun being a
housewife everyday, but...
...when we date like this,
we're like lovers forever.
We're married, but like lovers, huh?
Can you come here for a second?
What?
What's wrong, Yura?
Can you help me with the zipper?
Sure.
You're getting hard, Makoto.
Yeah.
Do you want to do it?
Yeah, I want to do it.
Right here?
Don't make a sound, okay?
Makoto?
Did you say something?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm sorry for buying such
an expensive item, Makoto.
That's okay. My lunch from
now on will have to be 250 yen.
What?
I'm just kidding.
I have enough money to
let you wear pretty clothes.
Following day
I'm home! Huh?
Welcome!
What the...
Am I imagining things?
Makoto?
I feel bad for making
you do all the work, so...
...I decided to work
at a family restaurant.
You don't have to do this!
But I have a lot of free time.
I've always wanted to be a waitress.
I only have experience
working as an office lady, so...
I see...
But a waitress has to deal with lots
of rude customers who say nasty things.
Plus you meet so many men.
I'm sorry, Makoto.
But I just don't love you anymore.
You shouldn't do this. Okay?
Okay, Yura?
If you say no, then I can't do this.
No, it's not that...
...I don't like the idea.
Let's see.
22 and 34...
Here?
YAMADA
Ah, here it is.
I can't believe he invited me over
to his folks' place. Could it be?
I want to introduce you to my
parents as my lifelong partner.
That's not possible...
You're late!
My family went on a
vacation all of a sudden...
...so I have to stay and
take care of the house.
I knew it.
Come on. This is our castle now!
We can do whatever we want!
So let's just do it right now!
You're unbelievable! I'm going home!
You can't go home.
What do you mean?
Look!
Love slave for a day
I gave that to you last Christmas.
I'm going to use this coupon
for you to be my love slave!
Damn! It was a trap!
Oh, I think it's a good idea.
You think so?
That's called double income. Since
you both work, you get more money.
Plus there will be more danger...
I'm also guessing that your wife wants
to wear those waitress costumes, no?
What?
Then it's like that thing...
Cosplay, was it?
It's what all those greasy old men want to
watch...
You really don't
understand girls, do you?
It's fun for girls to do cosplay.
Then you do it too, Makie?
Of course.
Are you okay?
What's wrong, Teacher?
Miyuki?
You like to do cosplay, too?
When I wear this kind of
costume, I get really excited.
Didn't you know, Teacher?
Cosplay is dangerous...
It's my oldest sister's.
Are you sure we can do this?
I always wanted to do it
once in a situation like this.
I'll play the patient who's hospitalized.
You can be the nurse who cares for me.
This is just like an image club!
Don't worry about it.
This is exciting!
The outfit just...
Welcome!
Table for 2, right?
I'll take you to your table.
Come this way, please.
I can't believe that beautiful
woman is working for us.
She looks like a secretary
for a big name company.
Working is fun.
Plus this costume is so cute.
Welco...
Welcome! Smoking or nonsmoking
I'm sorry.
I can tell even if you apologize.
What's wrong?
What brings you here, Makoto?
Well, I just came here as a customer.
Try not to bother me
when I'm working, okay?
Why do guys like it
when a girl dresses like this?
Aprons like that cover up
the boobs and the private area.
You can't see everything,
and that's the good part.
But you can clearly see the hips, so
people who like ass will be excited.
You don't have to explain it!
Your cooking is pretty good.
Can you pass me the ketchup?
Okay, okay.
Let's see...
What are you looking at?
Rika!
Hey!
Second time around?
Is this really fair?
Hey, Waitress!
Can you get me some coffee?
Yes, just a minute, please.
I'm still waiting for my parfait.
I'm sorry. I'll go take a look.
You're beautiful.
Go out with me on a date.
Damn! You talk to my Yura like that?
This place is definitely dangerous...
You look good in any costume!
How much do you need
to do to be satisfied?
Well, you're my love slave
for the day so...
Oh, I got mail!
Makoto Onoda
Huh? It's from my brother.
What? You have a brother?
I recently got one.
Good night, Makoto.
Good night.
I'm sorry. I feel so tired.
This is bad...
This is bad for our marriage.
What should I do?
Yura is full of life after
she began working.
I would be a bad husband
if I tell her to quit.
She's wearing really short skirts.
She never wore those for me!
I can't believe she wears that for those
wolves that come to the restaurant!
You know what? It's all her fault.
Everything she wears looks good on her.
You called for me?
Yeah. Sit right here.
Huh?
But...
But the other passengers...
They're all sleeping.
We shouldn't be doing this.
It feels so good.
Makoto...
I'm sorry, Yura! I'm about to climax.
That was close.
Why do I ejaculate prematurely
in my fantasies?
No way...
What's the matter?
I stopped fantasizing, huh?
Thank you.
You like those kinds of things, huh?
What?
No, this is just...
Welcome...
Yahoo!
Rika, what are you doing...
Nice to see you again. I'm Yamada.
That waitress uniform
looks good on you.
Really?
She looks amazing.
I want to have fun with her
wearing the waitress uniform.
Why are you working a part-time job?
I got it.
You came here because Makoto
told you something, right?
I don't know but...
...you're really good at
figuring out things like this.
Makoto doesn't trust me at all, I guess.
I see.
Yeah, thanks.
Well, I don't think
you should worry that much.
My sister seemed to
be enjoying the job, so...
Yeah.
I'll come and pick up
the money next time.
Ah, my batteries are running out.
Thanks, Rika.
Am I worrying too much?
Can everybody come here for a second?
He asked Rika to check up on me.
He doesn't trust me?
I...
Yamamoto can't make
today's late afternoon shift.
Can somebody fill in for her?
I'm sorry, I can't...
I'm sorry, but my child
gets home early today.
What about you, Onoda? Onoda?
What?
Can you do it?
Yes...
What?
Huh?
She's not home yet?
What's wrong?
Ah, Kyoko. Good evening.
So she started working part-time.
I think it's a good idea.
You think so?
What?
You want to be the one who
wears the pants in your household.
It's not like that!
You just want her to
stay home all the time, right?
I don't really want that, but...
Well, Yura is beautiful. So maybe
she'll be seduced by another guy.
That's it!
That's what I'm talking about!
I see. The problem I see
is that you're really jealous.
What?
For example, if Yura worked
in a place full of women...
...or worked by herself, then you
wouldn't have any problems, right?
I guess...
But you see,
girls find that to be boring.
Girls?
Yura is an adult.
She's still a girl.
Even though she's a housewife.
They all are.
I'm late.
Girls want to put on makeup or dress
nice to catch other people's attention.
That's different from
having fun or cheating.
You have to understand that.
I think I understand it.
Working as a waitress
is really difficult.
Approaching customers
and meeting their demands.
But girls really enjoy
doing things like that.
Do you want to do cosplay too?
Me?
I would try it...
I'm sorry, Makoto.
You're late.
I called your cell phone, but there was
no answer, so I sent you a text message.
What?
Sorry, my phone was turned off.
You didn't read my text message?
I would be lying if I said
I wasn't worried about you.
But...
I was doing some soul-searching.
I didn't trust you at all.
I thought maybe it was because
I didn't love you enough.
Makoto...
Even if we can't contact each other
through phones and text messages...
...we can still reach
each other's hearts.
Am I right, Yura?
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry!
I'll fix your dinner real fast.
About 20...
No, wait about 30 minutes!
Okay.
But if you were going to be late, then
you should've bought some appetizers.
I can't do that!
I'm still new at this, so...
I'll help you out.
Thanks.
Can you peel the onions?
Okay!
Would you like some coffee?
Please...
Thank you for waiting.
Thanks...
Sir! Please don't do that!
Makoto...
I'm a happy man.
There...
We're doing it here?
You're amazing, Yura.
It's really tight...
Makoto!
Yura...
I'm coming!
Okay...
Makoto...
I'm going to quit my job.
What? But...
I want to cook and clean at home.
When you come home,
I want you to feel relaxed.
That's the kind of place
I want this to be.
Okay.
You can go back to work
whenever you feel like.
Thanks.
You try to make it look
as if nothing is wrong.
The Knife of love won't show any mercy.
You just hold back your feelings
and live each and everyday.
You say you're used to it or
there's nothing you can do.
We should be much
more straightforward...
...and hug each other real tight.
Even if we're feeling
awkward at times...
On the night when I dream
as many times as I shed tears...
...l'm sure an angel will smile at me.
Let's dream of all the stars in the sky.
I hope you keep on smiling.