You've got mail
Please watch this animation in a well-lit
room, as far away from the TV as possible.
STEP UP LOVE STORY
Lesson 1 - Masturbation/Sex
First time having sex?
When I was 16.
Well...
It was with my friend's boyfriend.
How many times
do I masturbate in a week?
I don't have a boyfriend now,
so I masturbate once or twice.
Wait, do you mean masturbation or sex?
I love sex.
Date With That Girl
This is no time to be
doing this kind of stuff.
2 days ago
Then I recommend this one.
There will be a tour guide and you'll get
plenty of free time for yourselves.
I hope we can go
on a honeymoon very soon...
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'll take over from here, Kawada.
It doesn't look like they'll decide anytime
soon. Why not go drop him a note?
Thanks.
Oh no!
If you don't mind, I'll be leaving now.
Onoda.
Yes?
You're treating us like total strangers.
Let's have fun before you settle down.
No, I have to...
We're going out for a drink.
You're going, right? Right? You're not
going to say no, right?
I'm sorry!
I can't go with you today! I'm sorry!
Shibuya Station
I'm conducting a survey
of women in the city.
Please reply at your convenience. And
please be honest.
Are we clear?
Excuse me...
How old are you?
25.
Occupation?
I'm an office worker, but...
Married?
Two days from now...
When was your first sexual experience?
What?
What's your favorite sex position?
Excuse me...
Are you interested in adult videos?
Hello?
Do you want to star in an adult video?
No.
Not even a little?
No way.
Thank you very much for your time.
Makoto Onoda!
Right?
No?
That's me, but who are you?
You look much younger than
you do in your picture.
What? Who are you?
Umm...
I guess you're okay.
What are you talking about?
Do you have a weird hobby?
Hobby?
You like to tie people up?
Or do you like to do it outside?
You like to be sucked
instead of doing a girl...
...or you like to do it up the ass?
Now wait a minute.
Don't tell me you like guys.
That's enough!
Who are you supposed to be?
Just answer me!
Why are you asking me this?
I'm normal!
Oh.
Boring!
What the hell?
If you make my older sister
unhappy, I'll kill you!
What? Older sister?
Oh no!
Oh no.
This is bad, this is bad!
Makoto.
Yura...
She shows me such a wonderful smile...
I can't believe I'm marrying her.
You look beautiful.
Thank you...
You're beautiful to begin with, so
it didn't take much time to prepare.
I'll go get the groom.
Thank you very much.
Does it look weird?
I don't know if this looks good on me...
No! It really looks good on you!
I went to say "hi" to your
parents not too long ago.
Oh, okay...
One of my friends is a receptionist.
She's here already.
I'll introduce her to you later.
Okay...
Makoto?
What?
Oh yeah, I'm supposed
to say something, right?
There were lots of things
listed in the manual, but...
...it all got confused inside my head.
But I...
You don't have to say anything.
You!
Rika.
Sis, you look so pretty!
I see, so you really were...
Oh, you already met Rika?
Yeah. Not too long ago.
I can't believe you're
going to stick with one guy.
I don't think I could do it.
I'm going since we're
about to start soon. Bye!
Wedding reception hall
Onoda Family/Kawada Family
No way!
If you're talking about kisses...
...then we kiss lots of times
I guess I got here a bit too early.
I'll head to the bathroom real quick.
Why did we have to come here?
Since you had such a
serious look on your face...
I just couldn't take it anymore.
But why here?
Not there...
It's your fault, Rika.
I was just doing my job.
There's someone in here!
Shh!
You're late.
Sorry.
What happened?
It's nothing...
I wish you great happiness!
Thanks, Rika.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
For the first time...
...the 2 of us are...
...spending the night
I wonder if I can do it right...
Yura.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I don't usually take
a shower that long.
But in a way, it might've
been better if you came...
...to my place instead of
doing it here at the hotel.
It's our first night together.
So...
It was a long day.
Next time...
...it will be for real.
We get to spend...
...our first night together.
Makoto Onoda/Yura Onoda
Date With That Girl
When I was 16...
It was with my friend's boyfriend.
How many times
do I masturbate in a week?
What?
Wait, do you mean masturbation or sex?
Oh yeah. Can you give me this one?
I enjoy masturbating.
What?
I'm home!
Makoto...
I've been waiting for
this moment for so long.
I was hoping you'd be the
one to make me feel good.
I want you to come inside me and mess
me up.
Use your amazing sex techniques.
I... I...
What's wrong, Makoto?
No, I...
Please...
Makoto, can you turn off the lights?
But...
Yura.
Please, be gentle with me...
Okay.
It's really wet.
Yura...
I'm sorry.
It's my first time doing this.
You find it strange, right?
I'm already 25.
It's not that I hate it or anything.
It's just that... I think I was timid.
That's why I was interested in
things like masturbation...
I'm sorry.
What?
It's my first time too.
I'm sorry if I made it sound
like I've done this before.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I'm already 25.
So we're both virgins.
Not after tonight.
Yes!
Not there!
It's inside, right?
Yeah.
We're as one!
What's wrong?
Sorry, but I climaxed already.
Not only was I a virgin,
I'm a premature ejaculator as well!
Yura...
It really hurt, but...
...it felt good for a little bit.
We're just getting started, right?
Yeah, you're right.
We're just getting started.
You try to make it look
as if nothing is wrong.
The knife of love won't show any mercy.
You just hold back your feelings
and live each and everyday.
You say you're used to it or
there's nothing you can do.
We should be much
more straightforward...
...and hug each other real tight.
Even if we're feeling
awkward at times...
On the night when I dream
as many times as I shed tears...
...l'm sure an angel will smile at me
Let's dream of all the stars in the sky.
I hope you keep on smiling.
Next episode
Because they both have no experience...
Makoto and Yura develop
a problem in their sexual life.
Rika tries to give them advice
while teasing them at the same time.
Then Miyuki Kikuchi appears before
them and tries to get in their way.
Makoto is seduced by Miyuki.
What will happen to
Yura and Makoto's love?
Step Up Love Story episode 2,
Kiss, Kiss, Kiss.
If you don't make my sister happy,
I'll beat you up!