Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Akane-san, did you bring a change of clothing?
Yes, right here.
Futa Club
Once we go in, there's no going back, 'kay?
Yes, I understand, Sumika-senpai!
C'mon, Ai, shake your butt morel
Aya-chan's thick thing is rubbing so hard!
You're almost at your limit, aren't you?
You don’t have to take of the ribbon...
I won’t be able to stop myself!
Everyone!
This is our new member you've all been waiting for!
Oh, hi!
This is Itou Aya, second year; and
Aihara Ai, a first year student.
Nice to meet you!
Good day to you!
And this is our new member Niimura Akane-san.
Nice to meet you!
Geez, I already told you guys that we'd
have a new member come today.
Sorry, I completely forgot.
I remembered, though.
What!?
Um, excuse me!
Oh, sorry I forgot.
This is the president of the Futa Club
Asakura Mao in second year.
Prez, you hid your presence too much.
I was just reading.
I know what you want to say.
She might not look like it, but she's
a genius who skipped a grade.
Well then, let’s start our secret activities
in the old school building.
With her first visit to the haven
of futanari girls, Akane-san is...
A normal girl!
Woah, such a pretty pussy!
And the good news is, Akane-san wishes to do service!
Yay! So she's even lower in rank than I am!
I don't think it works like that...
Well, to start off...
For the entrance test,
We'll be your partners!
Everybody really does have one...
Let's get you to start with your mouth.
A real penis... it's twitching...
Your penis is so warm!
Penises are softer than I thought...
Akane-san, feel free to take off
your clothes if you want to.
I will.
Please allow me to take my clothes off!
Good work, Akane-san.
But then, my penis is a bit long...
If you don't take it in deeper, it won't feel good.
Akane-san's throat feels very good...
Akane-san... is pretty good...
Akane-san's hand feels good!
Rub it more!
It's your first time... how are you so...
I'm cumming. I'll cum inside.
I can't... cumming!
Me too, let me ejaculate!
Semen... sperm... so much...
So much all of a sudden... you guys are mean...
Even though it's my first time...
Oh my, sorry. It felt so good I couldn't help it.
But if you're shocked already you
won't make it very far in service.
Well, um, it did feel good.
Huh? Where is Ms. President?
Oh, Ms. President!
C'mon, join us, Ms. President!
No, um...
Hey!
This... What are you...
Please keep it just like this.
Ms. President is...
Do you like it? Well, in fact...
So small! With phimosis, too!
So cute!
Isn't that a little too sudden?
I'll pull it... back for you...
No, you can't!
I guess it can't be helped.
My penis is... exposed to air...
Ms. President's penis is very pretty.
Ms. President?
What now, Akane-san?
What if it becomes completely erect?
What do I do? What will happen?
I can't... If this goes on I'll...
Ms. President!
Hey!
So what are you going to do about my penis!?
See? She's like a different person.
Since our uniforms got dirty, we decided to
take a bath while they're in the laundry.
And it's such a great opportunity, we thought
we might as well wear swimsuits!
To think you have such facilities for club activities...
The Futa Club must be quite rich!
More importantly, even though you fainted
from anemia, you still stayed hard.
Ms. President is amazing!
Even Akane-san is wearing a swimsuit; you took
time to measure her sizes, didn't you!?
Prez is wearing a cute one, too,
so no complaints, alright?
Yes complaints! Let me do it already!
Well then, Akane-san, what do you plan to do?
I'll calm down Ms. President!
Amazing... it's still... getting larger...
Hey, you just learned that you should stick penises
all the way down your throat, right?
More, more; use your tongue, too.
It can't go that deep! I'll die!
Well you're the one that gave me the erection!
You've haven't taken nearly enough
responsibility for that!
No fair...
Oh, I know! Then...
How about... something like this?
So this is how it's going to turn out...
Ms. President's penis is getting very hot!
You're pretty good, but...
It’s such a waste to not go all the way.
All the way?
Of course it's your first time, right?
It's alright... It's been penetrated with toys before...
Well then I won't hold back.
It's so large... will it be okay?
Okay or not, we'll have to find out the hard way.
So thick!
Ms. President! You’re too thick!
We're fine! There's no problem!
Something's... coming deep inside...
I haven't felt a pussy... in so long!
As expected it's great!
Really? Does my pussy feel good?
You can take such a monster dick like mine...
Akane-san's is a monster pussy!
That’s as far as it'll go! It’s a dead end there!
Just a bit more! We'll make it!
It's hitting... it’s hitting inside...
The tip...
Amazing... it's the first time I feel
like cumming inside a pussy!
Hot stuff is... swelling even morel
Just a bit more to go!
Don't lift me with your penis like that!
My pussy... is being stirred up!
I... I might be cumming...
Cumming!
The deepest parts... right at my womb...
Things have just gotten started!
Take it out.. Please take it out once!
My tummy will break!
It's fine! Akane-san's monster pussy can take it!
Sumika-san!
You shouldn't bully the newbies like that.
Are you trying to break Akane-san already?
But it's Akane-san that made me...
Well, Prezis having too fun alone
leaving the rest of us out.
Geez, Prez, did you let out thick stuff again?
I don't want it to end! I still want to cum!
I know, I know.
But before that, let me enjoy, too.
Prez has got a great pussy, too!
Hey, it's at these times that you have work to do, right?
Huh?
The bukkake!
A cum bath!?
Understood!
You don't have to get that excited!
Why!?
I'll do Prez's favourite for you, okay?
Twirly twirly!
Don't!
It feels good...
When you stir my pussy... my penis feels it too!
Coming... it's coming...
A really good one is coming...
Prez... I'm cumming, too.
Together... Let's cum together.
Akane-san, I'm so sorry about earlier.
I got too full of myself.
No, it's really my fault.
It was my first time feeling that good...
Please allow me to do it again someday.
Well, in short, let's welcome Akane-san to join us.
Welcome to the Futa Club, Akane-san!
Let's all get along well.
Nessie!
Woah! The lake monster Nessie!
Toaru asa
One morning
mega sametara
When I opened my eyes
watashi ni mo haete ita
There was one, on me too
yume ni made mita
What I have dreamed of
sono nari no nari ga
those dreams paid off
anoko tachi mo kitto jibun de
The others must also be
mousou shiteru hazu
daydreaming on their own
hitoriyogari wo dekiru hi mo
And the day I can be proud of myself
tooku nai
isn't far
dakedo yappari
But, still
kininaru
I’m really curious
onnanoko no mama mo ii kedo
It's fine if I stay as a girl,
dashi no mesenn de shitai janai
but don’t you want to try it in
the point of view of the guys’?
futanari nari ni
Become futanari,
jibun nari ni jibun no nari wo
become yourself, and let yourself be
tomadoi kakete
Although you still might be lost,
futanari ni jibun nari ni
just be futanari, let yourself be
futanari nari ni
Become futanari
jibun nari ni monmon to
And become yourself, although worrying all the way
watashi no subete ga
All of me,
futanari ni
Will become futanari
futanari ni nari ni
Become futanari