Manahime-sama.
We have received reports that.
Uneme-dono and Setsuran-sama's troops
have taken one of Imai's fortresses.
I see.
The Higo country's military strength is overwhelming.
We won't even be able to defend ourselves
properly once they launch an assault.
What should we do?
What did Imai Yoshinori have to say?
Well, that's...
They said that they would only cease hostilities
if Manahime-sama is handed over to them.
We can't possibly accept that demand!
I'm going to crush Imai's troops!
Uneme.
I am grateful for that, but I am sorry.
If the only way to end this without
bloodshed is to sacrifice myself...
Unacceptable.
I won't allow it!
We can't hand you over to the Imai clan!
But their military's offensive capabilities are tremendous.
How do you plan on taking them on?
I'm going to...
We have a plan.
Fuurin Kazan Chapter One
By a poison, through a poison
A captured woman from the Higo country
is currently in the basement.
Woman?
What do you intend to do with her?
She is to be the puppet that gathers troops for us.
We shall use her as bait for the ruffians,
who are craving for a female.
If we give them a fine woman, it is highly
probable that they will submit to us.
What I want you to do is properly train her for the job.
This is one step in order to defeat Imai Yoshinori.
In order to defeat Imai Yoshinori...
If we're to achieve that goal,
then I have to make do with the choice that I currently have.
Let me go!
So you are Manahime's sister from another woman.
Himemusha Akane, eh?
Your level of beauty is as they say.
Don't touch me!
My brother Uneme-dono will bring swift vengeance unto you!
These breasts are perfectly my type!
Stop, don't touch them!
Oh? Don't you like your breasts being caressed?
Then how about here?
Not there...
No...
Well?
How does my finger feel?
Is it this spot? Or this one?
Stop...!
How about we go for the main course already?
Stop...
Don't...
Don't...!
It hurts...
It's going to rip apart.
Brother, save me.
Oh, so you were still a virgin?
I'm your first partner then.
Brother...
As expected, the tightness of a virgin is just right.
Don't you agree?
However...
I don't want to be the only one who enjoys this.
My body feels weird.
I see, I see...!
It feels great, eh?
No, don't!
Are you about to cum?
I also feel like cumming inside you, Akane.
Oh no...
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming.
Oh, finally cumming?
I'm going to cum inside you as well.
If the elder sister is this great,
then I would expect her younger sister
Manahime, to be even better!
I want to get her soon.
No, Father, please stop this.
You have been raised wonderfully, Shizuku-hime.
I've always wanted to do it with you.
Did you think I would not have known,
that you and your betrothed plan to kill
me to claim the country as your own.
That is not true!
We are not plotting such a thing!
Oh, I wonder...
I'm your daughter!
And that's exactly why I am very eager to do this.
You're not human!
You're just a beast!
You dare call your father a beast?
It seems that I need to teach you a lesson!
Buttholes really are very tight.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me that fucking you in the butt is getting you aroused?
No...
That... cannot be...
Oh, so you really are feeling aroused?
The beast's child is also a beast it seems.
No, that's not true...
Don't...
That's good!
I'm going to cum inside your butt then.
There!
And there!
No resting just yet!
Because you've made me wait too long, I'm
going to violate you to my hearts content!
No...
I think it's about time.
Shizuku-hime.
Here is your beloved, the one that you've been waiting for.
He may have been too aroused at the
sight of your obscene self though.
Yoshinori...
Uneme.
Are you not pushing yourself too hard?
Thank you, but everything is moving forward as planned.
You mean the plan suggested by Setsuran?
I understand that it is for the sake of this country.
But... is this really the only way?
I beg your pardon Princess, but we need to
do this in order to defeat Imai Yoshinori!
No!
Stop it!
In order... in order to defeat all of them...
It's about your younger sister, Sakura-san correct?
Just don't force yourself too much.
Princess...
My apologies.
But I can no longer turn back.
Is this even real?
Wow, her skin and hair look very smooth.
Are they going to let us bang someone like her everyday
if we become soldiers for the Hizen country?
If it's for this fine woman, then I'll accept any order from them!
Hey, hurry up.
Hurry up and give me your cocks already.
I can't get enough of this.
Let me have a taste too.
I'm glad.
There are lots of cocks here.
Hey, rub my cock too!
Okay.
Finish it already!
Use my pussy more!
Give me your cocks.
It feels great there.
It feels good.
I'm happy.
I love the smell of semen.
It's my turn now.
We can use her butt too?
Just how much of a pervert is she?
My insides are...
This is...
This is just too much...
Yes...
Just too much...
I'll use this hole as well.
We're going to cover you in semen, inside and out!
I can still go on.
Give me more cocks!
This is...
...good.
More, more!
Yes! This is really good!
Give me your cocks!
It feels good.
My pussy feels great.
Yes.
It feels good.
More, more!
The results are far better than we had expected.
Yes, if this keeps up, we will eventually have the
assault force required to match Imai's forces.
My Lord!
We have just received news that one of our fortresses
was taken down by the Hizen country's forces.
What?!
Again?
Is that true?
Yes.
The report says that it was overrun by
a very large contingent of troops.
How dare that Manahime...
Damn their shrewd tactics!
I won't allow them to just attack us like this.
I'm definitely going to violate her with my very own hands!