Manahime-sama!
There's a report that says that the troops lead by Uneme-Dono
and Setsuran-sama have lost another fort in Imae.
...I see.
The troops of the Higo are way too overpowering.
We can hardly fight back when they attack us.
What should we do...
What does Imae Yoshinori say?
That's... He says that if we give up Manahime-sama
he will spare others.
There's no way we would answer such requests!
I'll take care of all Imae's troops!
Uneme,
thank you.
Yet, if sacrificing me can end things
without anyone being hurt...
No way!
We can't.
There's no way we could hand Hime-sama to Imae.
However, the difference of power between
us and Imae is too great.
What are you planning to do?
That's...
I do have a plan.
Fuurinkanzan
Episode One: Fight Fire with Fire
In the dungeons we have captured a woman of Higo.
A woman?
What are we going to do with a woman?
We'll use her as a tool to gather troops.
As bait for the failures who lose themselves in women.
If given a good woman, they'll work for us happily.
I'd like to get your help for the training she needs for that.
This is for defeating Imae Yoshinori.
To defeat Imae Yoshinori...
We can't choose by what means it is done.
Let go!
So you are the half-sister of Manahime,
the princess-warrior Akane.
You are indeed beautiful as the rumors say.
Don't touch me!
Someone like you will be taken care of by
my brother, by Uneme-Dona right away!
No!
Oh, tits of the size of my taste!
No! Don't touch me!
You don't like your tits being touched?
Then how about down here?
No, not there...
No!
So how are my fingers?
Is it good here? Or here?
Stop it!
Should be about time I take you...
Stop! No, stop! Stop!
No!
It hurts... It's tearing apart...
Brother... save me...
Oh, so Akane was a virgin. I am Akane's first man.
Brother... brother..
As expected a virgin is very tight. However...
It would be bad if I were the only one enjoying this.
My body is becoming strange...
I see, I see.
Does it feel good?
No! You can't!
Are you about to cum?
I've started to want to cum inside Akane as well!
No!
Cumming... I'm cumming!
So you're cumming! Then I'll cum inside Akane as well!
If the elder sister is this good,
then the younger sister Manehime
can be expected to be amazing!
I want to get her right away.
No...
Father...
Please stop this...
You've grown up beautifully. Princess Shizuku.
I've been looking forward to do this all the time.
Besides, Princess Shizuku, don't you think I don't know.
You've been looking for men to
me and take over this country!
That's not it! We aren't thinking anything of that sort!
Oh really.
No!
We are father and daughter!
Doesn't that make it more exciting?
Someone like you isn't human! You're just a beast!
To call your father a beast!
Seems like you need some punishment!
As expected the ass is tight.
No!
What's wrong?
Could it be that you're feeling it from your butt?
No...
There's no way...
Wow, to feel it from your ass...
Seems like a beast's child is also a beast!
No! That's not!
Don't!
That's right! Go ahead and cum from your butt! There! There!
Dont!
There's no time for you to be taking a break.
I'm going to make up for all the time I've been waiting!
Guess I should stop here.
Princess Shizuku, the lover you've want to see must
have been really excited watching your slutty face.
No...
No!!
Imae...
Yoshinori...
Uneme, aren't you forcing yourself?
Thank you for your kindness.
Everything is going well as planned.
You mean the plan Setsuran made?
I understand that this is for the country.
But is this really the only way?
I might sound offending but Hime!
This is necessary for defeating Imae!
No!
Stop it!
To defeat... to defeat those bastards...
Uneme...
It's for your sister...
For Haguro-san, right?
At least please don't force yourself.
Hime.
I'm very sorry.
But there's no turning back anymore.
Amazing, her hair and her skin is all so smooth!
If we become soldiers for Hizen we can
sleep with here as much as we want?
If I can get such a nice girl,
I'll do anything!
Hey, hurry...
Hurry and give me dicks...
I'm so happy!
There are so many dicks!
Hey, rub me properly as well!
Yes.
Hurry up!
Use my pussy more!
Give me cock!
Yes! There!
It feels good...
I'm happy...
I love the smell of semen...
This time I'm the one shoving it inside!
You can use here ass as well. She's a real pervert!
Something like this...
This is too amazing!
It's good... It's too good!
Use your mouth, too.
Let's get her full of cum inside and outside!
I can still go on.
Give me more dicks!
Yes... Yes...
More... More!
Yes! It feels really good!
Give me more dicks!
Yes!
My pussy feels good!
It's good... It's really good!
More! Deep inside!
This was more productive than expected.
Yeah.
We can catch up to Imae's troops with this.
Sir! There's a report that our troops have
been captured by the troops of Hizen!
What!? Really? Is that true?
Yes. Apparently they were attacked by
unexpected large amounts of soldiers.
Damn you Manahime!
Using such despicable ways!
I won't let it end like this!
I'll destroy you with my own hands!