I, it seems I have come to some amazing place!
Excuse me! Is there any one here?
It is practically a castle!
What? You have got to be kidding...
No, just a moment! You can't, so stop it!
You can't!
Stop it, Dark.
Miss Mizutani! Miss Mizutani!
You called, Lady Kannazuki?
This here is Miss Nana Morimura,
a young lady that we will have
work here with you, starting today.
Nice to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
I am Risa Mizutani.
Please bring her to my room after
she has changed into her uniform.
Uniform...
You will catch a cold dressed like that.
This way, please.
Excuse me...
What is it?
Who was that person just now?
Lady Mai Kannazuki. She works as the
Master's secretary.
Is that so.
This is your room.
I will bring your uniform right away.
What a lovely room!
Yes?
This is your uniform.
Now, take off your clothes.
What?
Please change your underwear too.
Face this way, please.
Oh, you are nipples are erect, aren't they?
No, that's not...
We have to go soon; Lady
Kannazuki will be angry with us.
Yes.
Yes?
It is Risa.
Please enter.
Miss Morimura, your experience with men?
Any?
None?
Not yet... but...
Then...
Are you masturbating?
Masturbating?
Perhaps you do it everynight?
Well, that's fine. Miss Morimura,
please ask Miss Mizutani about your work.
Understood, Miss Mizutani?
Yes, Ma'am.
Miss Nana! Miss Nana?
Oh, yes?
Would you please wipe the entrance's windows?
I understand.
The supply room is further up that way.
Um... About how many rooms are in this mansion?
Let's see, fifty, one hundred, maybe  more than that.
Even I don't know all the rooms,
as there are some places we are not allowed to enter.
What?
There are numerous places with a mask on the door.
The areas past them are off limits.
Wow...
Now, let's get to work.
Miss Risa!
I wonder how did I get so lost?
What is this room?
What are you doing here?
Weren't you taught that you aren't allowed in here?
Uh... Ye... No.
Miss Mizutani! Miss Mizutani!
What could it be?
Didn't you teach this girl about these doors?
What? No, umm...
Miss Mizutani, come here a moment.
Yes, Ma'am.
What is the meaning of this?
I'm sorry.
After I strictly warned you about it!
Whose fault is it that girl opened the door?
That is...
The girl is a novice, she just arrived today!
It wouldn't do to scold that child, now would it?
It's your fault as her senior for not teaching her correctly,
is it not?
Yes.
It is, isn't it?
Yes... it is...
Then this punishment can't be helped, can it?
Miss Morimura, I cannot think that it is a very good hobby.
to secretly listen to other people's conversations.
Right, Miss Mizutani?
No... don't look.
When I think about it, it is unfair to mete out a punishment...
...to just one of you.
I must equally handout punishment...
...to the two who did something they shouldn't have.
Have you repented a little?
How is it?
I... have... repented...
Really?
Yes...
You, perhaps you are feeling it?
No, something like that is...
Is that so?
Now... It's your turn, Miss Morimura.
Now, Miss Morimura, I shall begin.
Miss Morimura, what is wrong? Answer me!
Yes!
Ouch!
Sorry, Risa.
Lady Kannazuki, it hurts.
Oh dear, you say things which aren't in your heart,
don't you, Miss Mizutani?
What does that mean?
You masturbate every night using high heels, don't you?
It's not like that...
It's not like that?
Miss Morimura...
You need not restrain yourself.
Move your heels with all your strength for her.
If I do something like that, Risa's body wil?...
You want it done, don't you, Miss Mizutani?
That's how it is, Miss Morimura.
But...
Please, Nana.
I w?-onder what the master would say
if he saw in this state?
Miss Risa, did you need something?
What...
You don't know, do you?
What?
I'll teach you.
Risa...
You can't. A place like..., all
sweaty from today, it's probably...
You are right, it's a little salty, isn't it?
That's not...
Hmm... Nana, you are hairy, unlike your face.
So very indecent.
That's not...
I haven't taken care of it at all.
Turn around.
Stop!
So deeply!
Nana, coming by yourself; you are so mean!
If you keep doing it so intensely...
I can't... no...
Stop...
I am gonna come!
Just a minute, Dark!
You can't pull my panties!
I get it, I get it. Just wait a bit, okay?
Enough already, Dark. Really, you're hopeless!
Lord Master, how is it?
As you can see,
it maybe that it's about time for both of them.
Is that so? I shall leave it to you, then.
Lord Master, if you do it so intensely...