I want some more.
But if I drink more,
I might not catch up the meeting.
This is going to outdated.
I have to drink it first.
But... I really got to go.
I still want some more...
What... what should I do?
Good morning, Asaka.
Good morning; good morning.
You are still in the room?
You have to hurry up or you will be late.
Yes.
Is she... excepting me again?
Kanae.
Let's work hard today together.
Yes.
What's wrong, Asaka?
Kanae is like my nurse.
Asaka, are you all right?
Are you fine?
I wanna be a nurse just like you.
Good morning, Megumi.
Doctor Usoki.
Good morning.
All right, so...
Let's begin our examination.
We just did it yesterday.
Some people get sick overnight.
Doctor, this is...
It's too suddenly:
Come on, lie down.
Doctor, I...
I got to go.
What's wrong, doctor?
You sound so wet.
It's shaking inside.
Is it...
I hate it.
Please don't say anymore.
I can't stand it.
Is this...
Please...
Please listen to the sound of my breasts.
Please don't stimulate me.
Your breast's sounds are nice.
But now what I wanna hear is...
Doctor, not this pose...
It's too...
How melodious.
You drank milk in the morning?
Please, I wanna go to bathroom.
Its so great,
I can hear that voice.
Yes, I have drank the milk.
I drank one pint.
I like milk.
Asaka
Kanae.
I should get some rest.
Yes.
Well, Kanae.
Please take it if you don't mind.
Really? Thank you.
They are so big.
Why are your breasts so big?
I wanna bury my head in them.
Too bad.
Kanae.
I can't wear this uniform.
It's so wet.
You are right; you should take it to the laundry.
I have a spare one.
Asaka, what's wrong with you?
This is...
This is Kanae's G-cup.
What should I do?
I can't believe it.
I have done that thing to Kanae.
She might think I am a weird.
If she hates me, what should I do?
Megumi, Megumi Asaka...
Yes.
Thank you, Megumi.
Doctor's operation went succesful.
But it was very strange.
Strange?
Patient said he didn't need anesthetization.
He could hypnotize herself.
By the way, Mr. Harada studied in mind treatment.
It seems so.
I used to be in the bathub...
At the time...
That's right.
Open your button; unzip your pants.
Just relax.
Yes.
That's right.
Take off your uniform.
You are set free from your daily restrictions.
No, how can a nurse wear such a sexy underwear?
I am sorry.
You might turn the patients on.
I...
I get wet easily in normal
panty, so I have to wear this.
Open it now.
Yes.
So...
Don't hide your breasts.
Take off your bra.
Yes.
Much easier, right?
Now there is only one piece of cloth left on your body.
Well...
The last one...
Please, please hold on for a second.
Don't...
I will get embarrassed.
No...
Please, I beg you.
Take off your last piece of cloth.
Show the whole body to me.
Well...
But... and your nurse hat.
All right, take off your panty.
Hurry up.
Yes.
That's it.
It's so great.
Don't take it all off.
Just stay right there.
Well...
It's so close...
This is important, Miss Megumi.
Yes, but how is the nurse hat.
I can imagine.
So, doctor...
Does Mr. Harada's operation
also used anestheization?
I want to listen to him, but...
he passed out right away.
Thank you, doctor.
I thought I couldn't.
But I still made it.
What a nice Doctor Usouki.
By the way,
What is it?
Megumi, do you know this?
I don't know.
Hold this, open your mouth.
Put it inside to test your body temperature.
It's nice stuff.
Doctor, can this be used in other parts?
Other parts, well...
Like here.
Doctor, we just examined it this morning.
You seem to get a fever over here.
Let me check it for you.
Thank you, Doctor Usouki.
I almost thought I couldn't make it.
Is it called virginal clonos?
It's the first time I saw it.
Be careful yourself.
Well, I...
But that voice is really nice.
Yes, it feels simple.
Thank you, Megumi.
It's a busy day.
But you are really a great help to me.
No...
To thank you,
I made special milk for you.
Doctor, you must be tired.
It's all right.
Doctor Usouki
Doctor Usouki's special milk.
I drank it.
This is...?
It's not normal milk.
I can feel the warm liquid
flowing down to my throat.
My body was touched all over tenderly.
It feels like flowing into my stomach.
And it goes down.
It's in my bowl.
Going down...
Down... to the deep...
No... I can't.
It's reaching the end.
It's the begging of an adult.
What's going on?
I can't help it anymore.
My body itches...
I am going to pee.
But I am not...
Why... why am I masturbating?
I wanna drink; I wanna drink more.
But... what should I do?
If I drink more, I might get sick.
But... I really want to drink more.
No...
What?
Doctor Usouki.
Megumi, what is wrong?
You don't look good.
My stomach...
Does it ache?
Really?
Doctor, are you...
No, a nurse should take care of her health.
Megumi, it's so great.
I never heard any voice like that.
Doctor.
What a melodious voice.
You must drink a lot.
How can it be possible?
Doctor, not in this place...
It's so melodious.
It's great, even the center of your body can hear it.
Patients might hear us.
Megumi Asaka, a new nurse.
I...
I still like milk best.
I want some more.
Good morning, Asaka.
Good morning.
Kanae.
From today on, we will work together.
Yes.
Nice to meet you, Asaka.
So am I.
Yes, I was transferred to
Kanae's nursing building.
Good morning, everyone.
Today's medicine was taken care of by this one.
Thank you very much...
From today on,
I can seen Kanae's breasts often.
It feels like in a dream.