News Planet
Hello,
And this is News Planet.
Let’s see the world news.
It is today
That the world eroticism show opens.
Lots of males
gather around the world
in the cities
Confronted with this, the authorities
are concerned
and the prolongation...
My name is Yuna Shingyouji.
I am the new ana.
Ah, ana means ''newscaster''
Teshigawara is so beautiful.
Beautiful, stylish
and professional.
I would like to become like her fast.
Ah, ana means ''newscaster''
Let’s start with the weather
Today...
is the first time that I
take care of the weather forecast.
Yuna, put your earpiece.
Sorry, I feel better without it.
It’s going to start in ! 5... 4... 3...
He... Hello I am Shingyouji,
the new newscaster.
From now on I will present
the weather forecast.
Nice to meet you.
G.taste ~Shingyouji Yuna~
He.. Here is.. the forecast
for tomorrow.
In the western part, mild sun
in the indicated places.
The Northern and Eastern parts
of Japan
will be sunny
the Pacific coast.
The weather will be
equally fair
in Hokkaido.
Although above the interior North-Eastern
coast
there will be a drizzle,
the weather
will be fine globally.
Shingyouji.
What do I have to do ?!
I am too stupid !
Accept my apologies
It’s not going well Shingyouji.
I’m sorry.
What did you learn during
the initial training ?
To do this live...
I am really sorry.
When I get the stage fright...
My heart beats fast.
If what you are saying is true.
You will never be
a newscaster.
You...
were taking pleasure.
It’s not true.
No matter what, prepare yourself
well for tomorrow, ok ?
Alright.
If it’s ok, you can come back.
I am going now.
A hunter who can hunt
without his hound
is a good hunter...
A dry sausage...
that can dry
without getting dried...
You were taking pleasure.
Am I really weird ?
When Madoka is nagging me....
I...
Yuna is the best! Yuna!
The weather will be fine globally.
I think she will be famous.
Shinseijun Games & Hobbies
Last waiting line
I’m having the stage fright...
Even if I have done this
many times !
Moreover in places like this,
people come
all of a sudden.
Calm down Yuna, calm down.
We must go and check.
Let’s go...
Yuna!
Your hands, your hands!
I’m sorry, I’m sorry.
I’m sorry.
Toilettes.
Yes, me too.
The kids are wild with joy
in the room
The grown-up are gathering up, too.
The last games and toys are
without a brand.
We don’t know what to chose anymore!
I am going to try them out
and give you a report.
It’s the realm of dreams!
It’s a magic fascinating world !
Apparently my stage fright is disappearing.
Words come out naturally.
You should all love that.
Yes, that’s the way Yuna!
Can you feel my excitement?
Yuna, your hands!
I am so sorry.
Let’s go there and see,
there is something.
Grown-up
The grown-up angle
The surroundings...
have changed.
How...
do we use it?
It’s full of...
explicit objects.
Let’s get inside
this audio-visual booth.
Hello...
May I bother you?
Oh, you’ve been fast!
Well, let’s get started.
What do we start?
Er...
Locking up.
Locking up?
Excuse me, tell me what...
Relax.
It’s coming.
Coming?
What is it?
What’s happening?
Congratulations!
It’s incredible teacher,
you are the best!
This is the outcome
of many years
''The capsule of pleasure
male free''!
Excuse me... I...
Obviously males
can also use it!
It’s equally possible
to combine all the situations
that you have in mind
with the other sex.
And with this button, the options...
Excuse-me...
What’s happened?
Sorry for being late,
I had to present.
Then...
A the for Shimoi Gusa
and coffee for Nakamura Bashi.
And for Saginomiya...
that’s it.
Oh no!
I let them get blocked...
without taking them.
It’s not moving.
That’s it !
Well then, following...
Oh no...
I need those 10 yens
to buy my drink.
How am I going to do?
Come on...
Come...
Thank you so much...
News Planet.
Good evening, it’s time
for News Planet.
Let’s see the world news.
It appears
an alien raised in the United States
escaped
from a certain ''zone-51''.
Here are the first news of...
Shingyouja Yuna.
Is this good for you?
Oh no!
I mispronounced
when I said my name!
Shingyouji, Shingyouji.
Madoka is going to lecture me again.
Madoka...
Is she going to recognize
a bit of talent
in my flash today?
No!
I can’t, I am a newscaster !
I am sorry Madoka.
To do this in this studio...
In those moments, read out
your phrases to calm down Yuna.
A hunter...
who can...
hunt...
without his..
hound...
His hound...
His hound... Without...
his hound... who can...
Without his hound...!
I can’t calm down.
Chief Madoka,
what do I have to do?
You were taking pleasure.
We are going to move on now to
the games section.
It’s on you Shingyouji.
Shingyouji?
Yes! Excuse-me.
The showroom that I presented
included a lot of games
destined to the family
designed as ''Games & Hobbies''.
A lot of people
came.
The first stand that I visited
was the one of the American Xbox
And then...
Oh no!
Why do they see me?
The redaction didn’t cut it?
What are you doing ? Cut this!
Well, thank you Shingyouji.
It was interesting.
Starting tomorrow,
until next transfer,
we will see together...
Sorry... the next piece of news...
Newscaster section.
It’s already been 30 minutes.
How long is it going to be?
But...
Keeping me standing...
I... This...
You failed totally
as an “ANA”.
But not for having ridiculed you
in front of the audience.
You...
You abandoned your post!
We are always delivering the news
in real time.
The accidents are frequent on the air.
But at ease like that...
And not having commented
in detail your experience...
You cannot be a good Ana.
But the event happening was...
This is the proof.
- Don’t do any more mistakes.
- Madoka...
If you don’t start again with the same mistakes
it should be ok.
Yes.
I have high hopes for you.
Very good !
I will double my efforts !
This is the first time
that she congratulates me.
Well, even if it’s quick...
Can you record a special...
show.
Special show?
There is a person
for whom you have to do
- this special show.
- A person?
Great! I’ll be there!
I hope so.
This person has an eye...
for these things.
The audience is going to have fun.
We are going to broadcast soon.
Can you get closer to them?
Yes a bit closer
behind.
Yes.
Kawamura is this good?
Sanjo, we’re on stand-by here,
it’s OK.
News Planet Evening.
This is News Planet Evening.
The special show tonight
focuses on a SM club
Night Spot.
At the site, Shingyouji.
Let’s call her. Shingyouji ?
Yes I...
am in the most famous club...
of Shinjuku, owned by Mr. Mascarade.
Shingyouji,
it’s a serious place,
it seems?
Get dressed accordingly.
What?
Very... Very good.
In fact, the people of the club...
told me if I wasn’t wearing
these clothes, I couldn’t come in
It seems they were not joking.
Yes, it’s true.
I will try right away
a bit the SM to see.
Ouch ! Ouch!
I wanted to try this experience.
By the way, the tariffs
are 5 million yens a year.
Despite...
my lacking of experience, it’s going to work.
The package ''first experience''
is free!
Once more ? Hum, ok.
That suits her well, doesn’t it.
It’s funny!
I want...
to become!
A pro of the same level of Madoka.
A totally professional woman.
Excuse-me.
I am your newscaster.
This seemed funny.
We got to the end of
our show, News Planet Evening.
Yagami, Kodansha,
Planet, Green Bunny.
Put on sale by Green Bunny.
This program is owned
exclusively by its makers.