Elder Sister
Hello, sis?
How unusual of you, calling me like this...
Huh? Getting married?
Today's the ceremony? That's too sudden... Huh?
Congratulations, Saki!
Sis...
Kasumi-san!
Kasumi-san...
If I'll describe
my memories using colors,
it's less like a dull vintage
reddish-brown.
My memories are less like a dull vintage reddish-brown...
Darkness...
It's pitch-black darkness...
I've been bullied by girls...
I never had any good experience
dealing with women ever since.
Despite being like that, I had someone I like.
Thanks for today as well!
Yup, see ya!
She's a friend of my sister who used
to visit home from time to time.
Boku-kun!
Dammit... Kasumi-san!
Everyone else found happiness...
I'm the only one who stayed the same from back then!
Dammit, that girl too!
And that girl who bullied me as well!
Everyone!
I'm the only one who couldn't!
I really want to go back all the way!
Back to the past and start over again!
Back to being a child and relive life with no regrets!
One more time!
Gaki ni Modotte
YArinaoshi!!!
Turn Back To A Child And
START all over again!!!
RAPE
Uhh...
Wait... Seriously, are you alright?
I wonder if he bruised himself...
Are you alright? Does any part of you hurt?
Sis... And Kasumi-san as well...
How's the wedding?
Huh?!
Are you dazed or something, Boku-kun?
Don't you feel bad saying that to Boku-kun?
Kasumi-san...
The girl I looked up to back then...
Looks like you have no bruises.
Okay! Let's go home, then!
I went back in time.
I'm not sure how it happened,
but it seems that I went back to the past
from that moment I wished I could.
Hey, Boku-kun! Hurry up and go to school!
You'll be late!
I'm going to school? H-Huh—?!
Good morning!
Boku-kun!
It's the lady next door... How nostalgic!
That's right, she works as an English tutor.
Now that I look at her again,
she's so young and pretty.
Sera, come out and say hello.
Huh?!
Good morning, Boku-kun!
S-Sera...
Oh, that's right!
Won't your parents be away for tonight, Boku-kun?
You can stay at our house!
I'm sure Sera would be thrilled.
You're right, mama! He'll be lonely alone, right?
You should come over, Boku-kun!
Alright, you two should go to school now.
if
you
Watch out for the cars.
come
I'll
kill
you
If you have nothing to do, then let's play.
A "pro-wrestling" game, perhaps?
"Pro-wrestling" game?
I give up!
Here you go!
I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up!
Here, have this!
That was one hell of an experience!
O-O-Ouch!
Let me go, idiot!
I said that it hurts!
Huh? She's weak.
Umm, after this...
No—!
Whoops!
Ouch...
Don't you get carried away!
You just got lucky today...
Huh?
No—!
No... Wh-Where are you looking at? Idiot!
What are you gonna do?
Stop!
What's with that foot?
No! No way! Don't!
Wait, stop this already...
No... Idiot!
Getting an "electric massage" move feels so inappropriate!
No!
What is this... It doesn't hurt, though...
I never felt like this before.
No—!
No...
Hnngh!
Not there!
My crotch feels hot!
No...
I don't want to lose to someone like him, and yet...
No—!
Ever since that incident,
Sera's queen-like status in the class has changed.
Whoa...
I can see them changing right in front of me...
That's right, we don't have a changing room here
so we all change here together
for our swimming classes.
Huh?
Wait, what's the meaning of this?
Why is my swimsuit so small?
Someone pulled a prank on Sera, huh?
Where are you looking at?
Don't tell that me you're behind this!
Huh—? I'm not.
And considering how you treated me before,
you won't get away easily with just that prank!
Wh-Wh-What... No...
No... What are you doing?
No...
No!
Any more than this and I'll tell about you!
I'll tell the teacher about you!
It's going in...
No—!
Your dick is going deep inside me...
What's so fun about
doing this to me, you idiot!
No... No—!
Am I having sex right now?
Why is my crotch feeling hot?
This is bad, my body will get ruined from this!
No...
He poured something inside me...
You should apologize for now.
This will be over if you say that you're
sorry for everything you did up to now.
Are you stupid?!
I'd rather die than apologize to you!
You should prostrate yourself
instead for doing this to me!
I see.
Then...
You...
No! No—!
Not to someone like you...
It's going inside me again.
No, it's going inside!
I can't do this over and over!
I will die! I'm gonna die!
My mind is getting all messed up!
No way...
No...
Not to someone like you... I won't apologize...
I won't ever forgive you for this...
No...
No!
No—!
My crotch is already full—!
More people are to blame for my traumatic childhood,
like her who always treated me like a baby...
Welcome home, Sera. Boku-kun came over.
Wh-Why is he...
Why is he here?!
His parents are away starting today
so he's staying over, remember?
I-I don't care! Don't go anywhere near my room!
Gosh, what's wrong with Sera?
The truth is she's happy about it.
I wonder about that.
Of course, she is!
You always got along, saying that
you'll get married someday.
Oh, Boku-kun.
Should we go to sleep now?
Don't worry, I'll be sleeping together
with you while you stay over here.
I'll go with you if you need
to go to the toilet, alright?
Make yourself feel home and have a good rest, okay?
Alright then, good night.
Darling...
Boku-kun?! What's the matter?
Boku-kun is mistaking me for his mother...
No...
Boku-kun is still half-asleep...
I'll just have to spoil him a little.
I'm sure he'll fall asleep soon.
He's been going on for too long... This is bad!
Don't! Not so rough!
No... Stop it already!
I'm throbbing down there and
it's starting to mess with my head!
I never felt anything like this before!
This will immediately make me...
No... Boku-kun, auntie is...
Coming—!
I did such a thing with Boku-kun...
Auntie... auntie!
Huh? O-Oh my...
Good morning, Boku-kun! You're up early.
What should I do, auntie?
When I tried touching myself down there
like you did last night, my dick grew big...
This is Boku-kun's dick? It can't be...
It hurts when touched by hand...
I'm sorry, then...
It got this big...
I-It's alright, this won't hurt...
Even though I haven't done this yet to my husband...
Snuggling a dick into my mouth...
His dick is in my mouth... It's huge!
It's filling up my mouth!
This is how a dick tastes...
When I lick it with my tongue...
When It rubs against the tip of my tongue, it twitches...
Boku-kun's dick...
He's a child I've known since he was a baby...
And now I'm here trying to make him ejaculate...
So this is what a blowjob is...
We won't get anything done
unless I get more stimulation!
A-Am I being violated?!
Boku-kun is using me like I'm just an object...
It feels good!
I'm coming!
Don't spill any of it...
Put all of it inside my mouth...
Don't play with your dick anymore...
Okay... But what if it grows big again?
I'll do this again for you when that time comes, alright?
Come on, let's get you changed.
I will too since my clothes got stained.
Good morning, Sera!
I'll be going now.
Boku-kun, you hurry up and go to school too...
Sera already went out.
Mom, I forgot something!
Can you bring my recess bag here at the entrance?
S-Sera... I'm sorry!
I'm busy at the moment, so could you get it yourself?
Okay!
Stop messing around!
Stop that!
Not now... Wait until Sera goes out...
Boku-kun, what are you...
No, don't!
No! It's inside...
No way, it's going inside me...
Boku-kun's dick...
His dick is inside me!
No, don't! Pull it out!
No way... It's hitting me deep inside!
His whole dick is going inside me!
No, it's pressing against my womb!
I should be running away...
I should be making him stop, and yet...
No—!
If his huge dick inside me keeps going on...
His cock is gonna get deformed from this!
No, I'm gonna get ruined down there!
I'm gonna come inside...
You can't! No way!
No, he's coming! Don't come inside!
No...
No... There's a lot coming out...
If he comes this much inside me, I'm gonna have a baby...
Boku-kun?! Stop it already...
He just came, and yet...
No... I can't keep my voice down anymore...
This is bad...
I'm feeling so good that my mind is going blank...
It's so intense, huge and long...
It feels so good that It's driving me nuts!
No, It feels incredible! I'm coming!
I can't! There's no going back for me now!
Darling... Sera... Forgive me!
Good...
It feels good!
Having my pussy creampied feels great!
My pussy is filled with semen deep up to my womb!
I love it...
I love Boku-kun's dick...
Boku-kun, you're amazing!
Compared to uncle's...
whose dick would you rather get fucked with?
Whose dick feels better?
Your dick! It feels way better than my husband's!
Both the length and stiffness...
Mom, I can't find it. Where was it...
I love everything about it—!
Wh-What are you doing...
Boku-kun, I want it inside! Give me your semen!
My pussy is filled to the brim...
You... What are you doing?
No!
You're the worst!
Shut up... It's your fault that I had a miserable life...
Let go of me, idiot!
No—!
I'll keep on raping you until you apologize.
Never!
Haven't I told you that I won't apologize even if I die?!
Then, you'll be raped as long as you live!
No—! You can't!
Don't! No—!
I managed to start my life all over again.
A life where I managed to exact
my revenge on these two...
I'll never apologize...
But I haven't had enough yet.
Not to someone like you...
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization