Due to the bullying I went through from childhood,
my life is in such a huge mess right now.
Here, here you go!
How is it?
I give up!
I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up!
I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up! I give up!
However...
By some strange incident,
I came back to the past...
I got myself a chance to take revenge
on women who oppressed me.
Huh?
Whoa!
S-Sis!
Hmm?
Why are you dawdling around looking like that?
Oh, what's that?
Boku-kun, did you say something
about my voluptuous body?
I-I never said anything like that!
C-Cut that out!
Look, don't you want to see them?
If you'll say that you want to no matter what,
then maybe a little...
...touch will be fine with me.
Hey... Come on...
Come on. Say that you want
to see them, Boku-kun.
Shit! You're always...
Sis... No, Saki!
Oops...
I should go to school now.
You should hurry up and go as well.
Saki... For having fun from making a fool out of me,
you deserve my revenge!
Gaki ni Modotte
YArinaoshi!!!
Turn Back To A Child And
START all over again!!!
RAPE
I'm home!
Uh? What's the matter?
U-Uhm... You see, umm...
Sis, aren't you always telling me
that you'll show me your boobs...
Th-That's why...
I want you to show them to me...
Oh, maybe you're embarrassed
to show your boobs.
Even though you always say that...
Huh!?
Oh, I see...
You're so cute, Boku-kun!
Did you think that I'll get
embarrassed when you say that?
That's too bad for you, Boku-kun!
Will you get embarrassed when a baby sees your dick?
It works that way!
Th-Then, show me your boobs! Show them to me!
Are you still saying that? Okay, okay...
I'll be changing so stay right there.
But in return,
you're not allowed to run away
when you feel embarrassed.
Here you go.
Hmm?
I'm feeling a bit conscious.
No, no... Just the fact that
I'm feeling conscious is stupid...
So, where are your boobs?
Huh?
I can't see your boobs though.
You just pulled and rolled up
your shirt. That's just cheating.
I know!
How about this?
Here, how's this?
You're witnessing me changing live!
You might never get any other chance to see this!
So, where are your boobs?
You're still wearing a bra.
What the hell... How did this happen?
I shouldn't have said that I'll show
my boobs on the spur of the moment.
I want to get this over with already,
but my hands are shaking...
Oh, why don't your boobs have tips?
Huh?
Th-They're right there...
My nipples are just hidden beneath...
It's no big deal... They can come out...
Huh, so my snobby older sister has inverted nipples!
Wh-What?
Boku-kun...
Whoops...
H-Hey, what are you doing?
No!
H-Hey, Boku-kun!
Why are you touching me without permission?
N-No! You can't! Wait!
I said you can't!
Don't touch me there! No!
H-Hey, what are you doing?
We're done now!
N-No... Stop!
No... This is bad...
He'll make me come if this goes on...
But what should I do to make him stop?
No, I can't...
Sis, did you come from your boobs?
What a rotten bitch, despite being my sister.
Boku-kun...
N-No!
No!
S-Stop!
N-No...
Don't... Don't!
D-Don't look!
N-No...
Hey, sis... What's this round and stiff thing?
No... I don't... I don't know!
Tell me properly.
Or else, we won't get done!
No, stop...
I'm gonna come again...
I'm coming... Stop...
Wow, even your panties are soaked!
Sis, what is this fluid?
I don't know! I don't know!
Sis...
I told you that we won't get done
if you won't answer me properly.
Huh?
What is it, Boku-kun?
Huh? Here's your hymen!
Oh, so you're a virgin.
You even acted like an adult woman so much.
Y-You... Do you have any idea
of what you're talking about?
That's because you've always been seducing me.
Boku-kun...
Huh? What's the matter?
Is having your hymen seen embarrassing?
Then...
If it's embarrassing, I'll tear it for you.
No... No!
Stop!
It's going inside me!
No!
Boku-kun's thing is really going inside me!
Hey, hey... I just shoved it in.
Coming instantly as your little brother
rapes you. Are you a pervert?
No! Pull it out! It's so deep!
Huh? Why? You were totally leading me on.
Ahh! Don't!
I'm kidding! I was obviously kidding at those times!
Was that so? I'll have to stop here
if you were really just kidding.
But sis, you've always been
giving me trouble. That's why...
I want you to apologize with all your heart.
No... Don't...
I feel hot down there...
Boku-kun's dick feels amazing!
I feel electricity running up to my head
every time he thrusts it into my belly.
My mind goes blank!
No...
No!
Not there! No! Don't!
No—!
Don't go on a coming spree while saying no!
Perverted older sister, want to get knocked up
with your little brother's sperm?
No, not your sperm!
Sorry... I'm Sorry!
I won't make fun of you anymore!
Like I'll stop from that kind of apology!
Stop!
Apologize for everything you did to me!
I'm telling you to stop, and yet...
No!
No way!
Don't!
It's coming out.
Don't shoot it inside me!
I'll shoot it inside!
Make it stop!
How's that, sis?
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
I don't want it anymore!
I-I'm coming!
No, I'm coming...
I'm still coming!
It's gonna come out!
W-Wow... It feels amazing!
My pussy is already full...
I'm sorry... I can't take it anymore... Let me go...
My little brother kept raping me for the whole time.
I really am...
Boku-kun, I-I'm coming!
I might actually be a pervert.
That's because...
Alright then, I need to go to school.
You too, sis... Hurry up and go.
It really is incredible!
P.E. is our next class. Should we go now?
My shoes are not here.
Shit, this is pissing me off! It's that brat again!
Huh?
S-Sera, you're messing with me again...
Huh? Are you stupid?
Let me tell you this...
I'm not one to sneak around behind
your back. That's too much hassle.
Then, who are you saying that did this?
Who knows? I'm not telling it to an idiot.
How about going through the trouble to find the culprit?
It might be impossible for an idiot, though.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
That's because you promised...
Promise?
...that we'll get married when we grow up.
And yet, you fawn over other girls,
and then fall for them...
Isn't that the reason?
Doesn't it mean that you're a liar?! Dummy!
Does that mean that you love me?
Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?
Who would...
With a pervert like you...
Huh?
I love you...
I love such a boy like you!
What do you want to talk about?
Could it be that the one who hides my shoes
and does mean things to me is you?
I did those.
You're the culprit!?
It's my business.
Huh!? By business, you mean...
Are you getting paid to bully me?
Are you a bully for hire?
Will you do anything for money?
It depends on the job specifics and cost.
Oh... That's good to hear.
Hey, how about making a deal with me?
Hmm?
For how much? You'll have to pay upfront.
No—!
No, I never did anything!
It seems that you were the one
who messed with Sera's swimsuit.
That was because Sera is acting full
of herself and she annoyed me.
I never did anything on you!
Shut up!
Sera is already my woman!
When you lay a hand on my woman,
shouldn't you obviously have to pay the price?
U-Uhh...
No—!
Alright, then...
Hey, Suzuhara. Will you do
one more business with me?
It's gonna be a lucrative deal on your end...
So, what are we doing next?
squish
What are these?
It's pretty simple. You'll have to
wear them for a whole week.
However...
Wh-What's this? My nipples...
I'm also getting sucked out down there!
There, I turned them off for now.
Do you think you can do this? Give my
down payment back if you can't.
I'm fine... I'll do this.
Alright, we have a deal.
Keep them on you whether you're home or at school.
Well, you'll only have to bear with it
for a bit and get yourself some cash.
Oh, that's right.
They'll vibrate stronger the closer I am within range.
They might stop when I'm far away though...
What's happening?
They only felt painful at first...
It's getting sucked out...
I'm throbbing down there and my belly feels hot...
They won't stop even when I went home!
Is he still nearby?
This will go on for a few more days...
Suzuhara, this is my sexual development plan for you.
Well, I'm looking forward to this whole week.
And then, the week went on.
Just a little longer...
I'll have to endure this during our P.E. today...
Oh!
Good morning, Suzuhara.
I-If it sucks me this hard down there...
I-It's gonna get torn off!
You promised, so hurry up and take them off me!
This brat Kiri's nipples got this bigger.
Then down there should've also...
Hurry, my groin is tingling!
I know.
Your clitoris got erect and is bending backward.
See it for yourself, Suzuhara.
My thing... It grew this big...
This is your bonus for doing such a great job.
Huh? What is that thing?
This is a pocket pussy for your clit cock!
I'll stroke your vulgar clit using this.
Here, come from your vulgar clit cock!
N-No... No!
Huh? No... Don't put that in...
No!
No, not that!
No, don't do that!
I'm coming... Help me...
Hey, hey... Don't black out yet.
I still have something to ask.
Hey, why...
Why did you stop? I want to come...
I want to come from my clit cock!
Hurry... I want to come...
So you want to come?
Then, you'll tell me which client asked you to bully me.
I'll tell you... I'll tell you everything...
So keep pounding it in!
Make me come from my clit cock!
Alright, come!
Keep coming from your clit cock!
You're pounding my pussy!
No way, I'm coming! I'm coming!
Suzuhara, I'm coming!
Come like you're dying in the end!
Hey, Suzuhara... Spit it out.
Who was your client?
Yes... That would be...
Sera...
Did you find the culprit?
Shut up.
Right...
Dummy...
No, that can't be!
I don't believe it! I'm not buying that!
Oh, Boku-kun.
Good afternoon!
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji