This is the man who cast aside my mother and I.
In order to get revenge on him, the headmaster
of Excellent All Girls' Academy,
I got my hands on a device that allowed me to stop time at will
and infiltrated the academy.
The first thing I did to thank him...
was to meet up with the daughters he had with his current wife.
Kanako...
Hina...
I raped them both.
Well then, who's going to be my next target?
I can freeze time as much as I wish.
My revenge is nowhere near being finished.
Enough jizz to fill a swimming pool, and school swimsuits don't float in it edition
The locker room, huh?
Locker Room
Is anybody in here?
Well, hello there.
Bodies that are still developing sure are sexy.
This girl has average tits, but has a nice, tight body.
Her determined expression is also rather arousing.
Wow! Her tits are ridiculously huge.
Wouldn't big tits such as these just
get m the way when swimming?
She has a nice face too.
I've seen her face somewhere before.
Just as I thought, it's no wonder I've seen her face before.
Gojima Academy's beautiful Olympic athlete,
Kamisura Risa-chan, huh?
Not bad... It'd mean that the academy's star would get raped...
The others must be her close friends.
It's settled then. She's my next target.
first off...
It's a bit cramped in here, but...
...if I hide in here...
...then they won't know it's me.
Come on, everyone went on ahead already.
Ah! That was fast!
But...
...aren't our swimsuits rather difficult to take off?
Now that you mention it, changing out of them is a bit of a hassle.
It's rather depressing whenever we have this class.
B-But it's fun when we're swimming.
Yeah, for you, Risa-chan.
You are training for the Olympics.
Ah, I would love to be popular like you, Risa.
Really... you sure can swim well with such large tits.
Risa... have you grown another cup size?
Cut it out, Yuka.
They really have gotten bigger. They're rather impressive.
Don't just stand there staring, Akari! Help me!
So her friends' names are Yuka and Akari, huh?
They sure do seem to get along well.
It's about time I got in on the action.
Well then, who should I start with?
I would like to start having fun with Risa's tits
right about now, but not in this position...
Nice!
I can't decide which ass to sample first.
She has a nice ass. Both her tits and ass are huge.
Not only that, but it's also really soft.
I'm horny now.
Well then... I'll squeeze your ass nice and good, alright?
She has a huge ass, as well as huge tits.
You have such a pathetic look on your face, you know.
Well then, maybe I'll play around with your friends' asses now.
Oh! What a nice sound!
Let's give this one a smack, too.
Nice!
All three of them have nice asses.
Akari has a small, muscular ass...
...And Yuka also has a tight , muscular ass, too.
All of you have great asses. Mmhm.
Well then, next up is... the much-awaited pussy check.
What's up with this pussy?
She has lots of folds, her pussy lips are
huge, and it puckers up quite nicely.
The shape of this pussy is rather sexy.
Let's see how it tastes.
She has a sexy pool-like taste.
She's like a remodeled character.
I'll suck on it some more.
Geez, you're quite wet.
You want me to stick my cock in you
so badly that you can't stand it, huh?
But just hang on for a moment, please.
I have to check out your friends as well.
Oh, so this is Akari-chan's pussy?
It looks a bit childish just like her.
But this one also has its charms.
Oh! It's really tight!
This means that she's a virgin.
She has a rather childish pussy, but
it looks like it'll feel rather good.
Who would have thought that she'd get
so wet just by fingering her a little.
I see, I see.
It looks like she's untouched, but her parts aren't half bad.
Wow! My fingers are already soaking wet!
She tastes pretty good too.
I'm looking forward to thrusting my cock into her later.
Well then, last but not least... sorry
to keep you waiting, Yuka-chan.
Oh, nice response, just as expected.
She's gotten gradually wetter.
Alrighty then, I'll just move right along to playing with your pussy.
What do we have here? Aren't you rather slutty, Yuka-chan?
Wow, girls nowadays... they're all a bunch
of lewd bitches who love sex.
They all just want me to stick my cock in them.
Well, alright then...
I'll make good on your requests...
I'll be starting with you after all, Risa.
I'll give your cramped tits some breathing room.
Whoa! Your tits are nicer than I thought.
I'll rape you while your slutty tits flop about.
Okay, I'm going in.
I'm sticking it in, Risa-chan!
She's still rather tight. Her pussy is really
squeezing down on my cock.
This is totally a virgin pussy!
It looks like it hurts. But we're just getting started.
I'll be sticking it in all the way to the hilt.
That's the spirit, Risa!
Let's start with your first rutting.
This is the day you became an adult woman, after all.
Wow! You're really tight!
It's so tight, it almost hurts. This is great!
What the hell is going on?
You don't have to resist. I'm already inside you, though.
Ow, it hurts.
I stuck it all the way in to the hilt, as you can see.
Wh-Who are you?
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Hmm... of course you still don't understand the situation you're in.
Risa-chan, your pussy is currently getting raped by a cock.
A cock that belongs to a complete stranger.
Ah, you're totally confused.
It can't be helped, so should I help you
understand through your body?
Here we go!
Ah, it hurts!
Oh, it's tightening up!
It feels great when it tightens up like that!
It hurts! It hurts!
It really hurts!
This is your first time. You should enjoy it too!
No! It hurts! It hurts!
Does it really hurt that much?
Then I'll make it feel good right away.
Your body will remember it even if your mind doesn't.
Ah! You suddenly started behaving
honestly as soon as I stopped time.
Is it because you can't feel the pain?
Your body sure responds quite honestly.
You're letting out a voice that sounds like you're enjoying it.
It'll probably feel really good as soon as I start time back up again.
Your body will respond truthfully even if I stop time.
I'll make those huge tits of yours feel good as well.
Well? Doesn't it feel good to have your tits squeezed
while your pussy is being pounded?
There we go! I'll make you feel even better. Just you wait!
Alright now! I'm going to unfreeze time again soon.
I wonder what sort of reactions you'll
have for me this time around.
What is this? Ah!!
Hey, Risa! What's the matter?
Has the sensation of my cock inside
of you started to feel good yet?
What is this?
No! Stop! Don't cum in my pussy! I...
Oh, you came? Did getting raped by a man
you don't know get you all worked up?
An Olympic athlete in training enjoyed getting
raped... what an unimaginable scandal!
No... this can't be happening... no!
Why?! It hurt up until just a moment ago.
I don't understand it at all.
It feels so good that you can't stand it, huh?
No!
It's because you're a perverted girl who
does nothing but masturbate.
That's why you have such a slutty pussy.
No I don't! I wouldn't do something like that!
What's the matter? Are you gonna cum again?
Then I'll make sure it feels even better for you this time around.
I'm going to drain myself dry in your pussy!
No! Drain yourself? Of what? Drain yourself?
What, you ask? You should know.
Semen, of course! Semen!
Semen? What about it?
You don't understand what semen is?
Bodily fluids, you see. Bodily fluids!
I'm going to fertilize your egg with my seed!
Your seed? P-Please don't!
I'll get pregnant!
Of course. It'd be great if you got pregnant.
I'm looking forward to it. Ah, this is great.
Please don't do it. I'm begging you.
No can do! Get fertilized like a good little bitch!
No! I don't want to be fertilized! I'll get pregnant!
You have no choice but to give up and get fertilized.
Let's make a fruit from our union!
Pull out!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to fill up your virgin pussy with my cum!
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes!
Going that fast...
I'm cumming!
It's all over the place. Why is this happening?
Ah, it felt really good. This will be a fond memory for me.
This makes you my woman. You should be happy.
Well then...
Maybe I'll get on with deflowering your friends like I did with you.
Huh? My friends?
The two over there.
Akari?! Yuka?! Why!? What's going on?!
Run away! Run!
Geez...
She finally realized amidst her confusion, huh?
But it's too late. They can't hear you.
Who should I fuck next?
Maybe I'll fuck Yuka first.
Akari looks rather spineless, so I want to show her the
other two getting raped to give her a good scare.
I'm going in now. I wonder if you're a virgin too.
There we go!
She looked like the sluttiest out of all
of them, but she's actually a virgin!
As to be expected from a lady of Meimon Academy! I'm so glad!
I'll loosen up your virgin pussy with my cock!
Well then, maybe I'll get on with the introductions.
It hurts! What is this? It hurts!
Hey, are you awake?
How does my cock feel?
Wh-Who are you?
What is this? Blood?
Ah! Why? How did this happen to me?
Stop! Stop it! Who are you?!
Does it really matter who I am?
The only thing that matters is that you're being raped
in your virgin pussy by a complete stranger.
Being raped...? That can't be! No! No!
Pull it out! Pull it out right now!
No can do!
What's going on? I was just talking with Risa and...
Yeah, you thought you were getting changed along
with Risa and your friend, but you're being raped.
Funny, isn't it?
What did you do? Get off of me!
That stubborn face sure is nice!
It gets me all worked up, and my cock is throbbing!
There's something big and gross inside of me!
No! No!
Hey, Yuka, I'm going to show you what the ultimate climax is.
What are you talking about?
Alright, time to make this slutty pussy feel good.
The sensations built up when time is stopped seem to come
rushing to the surface when time starts back up again.
There we go! Your pussy is nice and
wet, and it's easier to move now!
I'll play with you down here so it feels even better for you.
Your pussy got all tight all of a sudden! Nice! It's tightening up!
Yuka! You're about to cum, right?
I can feel it with my cock. Go on and cum already!
Why am I cumming? Why?
Nice! What a tight pussy!
I'll cum inside you now, okay?
No, stop it!
No! What is this? This isn't right!
I'm going crazy!
There you go! Getting raped in your sensitive
pussy right after cumming feels great, right?
I'm begging you, just let me go already!
No! Stop! Don't cum inside me!
If you want me to leave you alone, then you're going to
have to apologize to me from the bottom of your heart.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Seems that apologizing will do you no
good. I'm about to cum, you see.
But you promised!
Promised? Did I?
You're terrible! You're the worst! No! Stop!
Here we go! Here we go! I'm cumming
cumming, cumming, cumming!
I'm going to cum into your climaxed pussy!
Ah, that was great!
I came a bunch.
How cruel... That was cruel...
You're the last one, Akari-chan.
Well then, let's get you good and scared
by showing you your two raped friends.
Huh? Wh-What the...?
Hey, Akari-chan! Can you see the two in front of you?
Ah! Wh-Who are you? A boy?
Why?
Now now, don't worry about me. Why don't you
try worrying about your two friends instead?
What the...? Risa-chan?! Yuka-chan?!
Wh-What's the matter?
You don't get it? Then let me break it down for you.
These two, you see, were raped by me.
I stuck my cock in their pussies.
And now I'm going to do you the favor of raping you as well.
Huh? This can't be! Why?! Help me! Help me!
Yuka-chan! Risa-chan!
How cute! Do you really think they can save you?
Help me! Save me!
That won't do you any good!
Stop! Let go of me!
There we go!
It hurts! It hurts!
You tore, you tore!
I tore your virgin pussy in one go!
It hurts!
My pussy hurts!
What's wrong with you two? Say something!
Yuka-chan! Risa-chan! S... Save me!
Ah, it can't be helped. Maybe I'll show you how
I made the other two climax, Akari-chan.
What? Stop! Don't do mean things to me!
This pussy is great!
I'm going to fuck this tight pussy until it's nice and loose!
She's all wet! She's feeling it now!
She has smaller tits compared to the other
two, but her nipples are rock hard.
Well? Does this feel good?
She's about good to go.
Akari-chan looks like she's about to cum too.
What?! Wh-Wh-What...?
Well? It doesn't hurt anymore, does it?
Having sex with a guy has started to feel good, hasn't it?
That's not true! I could die! I could just die!
You say that, but you sound like you're enjoying it.
What is this?! What's going on?! Tell me!
Even if you ask me to tell you what's going on...
The only thing to be said is that you're a perverted
girl who gets off on being raped.
That's not true! Lies! All lies!
Geez, she doesn't get it even when I spell it out for her!
I'll fill you up with cum to make you understand!
Inside? you mean...?
I'm saying I'm going to pour my cum into your womb!
You should be thankful!
No! No! Not inside! I'll become a mommy!
I don't want to be a mommy!
I'm cumming! You should cum together with my cock!
No! No~!
No! What is this?
I don't get it! I don't get it...
Ah! I'm still cumming!
This c... can't be happening...
Good for you.
Now you're in the same boat as your friends.
No! Someone help...
Well then...
What should I do next?
I did the beloved student body president...
and her sister.
Along with the Olympic candidate in training...
That alone would be enough of a big incident
to turn the school upside down, but...
I'm just getting started.
As long as I have this time-stopping device...
...then I can continue to rape every single girl in this school.
Doing that would be an unprecedented, huge scandal!
The students who realized what happened
to them at that moment...
I'll destroy all of them without leaving a single one out!
No~!
An unheard-of, unprecedented incident has occurred.
At the school known worldwide as Meimon All Girls' Academy...
And known locally and statewide as Excellent Academy...
...The students and teachers have reported incidents
of being assaulted and then losing consciousness
without getting a clear look at the assailant
The assailant still remains at large, and the chief of security has
reported that there have been no sightings of the perpetrator.
The parents of the students have raised concerns
that security had been too lax...
This school is done for.
I wonder... who were those two?
But none of that matters now.
I don't know where they're from or who they are,
but I was able to get my revenge thanks to them!