For exacting revenge on the Headmaster
of Excellent Girls Academy,
the man who cast my mother and me aside,
I infiltrated his school and raped every one of its students.
The memory of it is still fresh in my mind.
However,
after finding out that
there were some lucky students who weren't
in school when I went on my raping spree,
I infiltrated the place once again.
Today, I will place the final nail in the coffin
and destroy the school he holds so dear.
Even if the school already announced
its closure at the end of the year,
I won't allow any student feel it's safe
to stay until their graduation.
Finally, this school will be done for.
Only two left.
At the school, stop by time.
The time stopping nighmare. The tragic finale cannot be stopped arc.
What a great view.
You two just can't wait for me to rape you, huh?
Sorry to keep you two waiting.
Manaka, your ass isn't that big, but it sure is toned.
What a nice, tight one you've got.
You have quite the ass, Honoka.
You're young, so your ass is still so pliable.
While I'm at it, I'll check whether you two are virgins.
You might look like a delinquent,
but let's see if this is still pure.
What do we have here?
Oh, it's pink!
Let's have a taste.
Your pussy tastes great. It's perfect!
I can feel the pool water off your swimsuit
mixing with your pussy juice. It's amazing!
This is real tasty!
After tasting so much of it, I've gotten so aroused.
Well that's no good. I almost forgot about you, Honoka.
It's time for your virginity inspection.
What a great smell.
It's a bit sweeter than Manaka's.
But are you still a virgin? Well...
Let's have a look.
This is a great shade of pink.
Let's see if the hymen's still intact.
Oh, it is. It's still in one piece.
Damn, what an erotic pussy you have.
So you're really sensitive here? How nice.
At this rate, the pain from losing your viginity
might be replaced by pleasure.
I almost forgot to say hello to your tits.
Well then, it's time to have a feel for both
of your school-swimsuit pussies.
Sticking it in between two school
swimsuits is a damn honor.
My dick rubbing against your school
swimsuits feels so good!
This feels great!
Don't worry. I'll make it feel even better.
Both of you have gotten so wet already.
The sound of your love juices soaking
onto these swimsuits is so loud.
I can feel both of your pussies getting so hot from my dick.
I guess it s about time to see some reactions.
Honoka?
Huh, Manaka-chan?
Why are we on top of each other?
Wh-What's happening?
Why?!
What's wrong, Manaka-chan?
Manaka, behind you! Who the hell are you?
What the hell are you doing?
What? It's just how it looks.
You're just as bad-mouthed as you look.
Don't look at me like that.
You piece of...
Stop! Don't do something so disgusting!
Shit!
I think I was asleep or something,
so I don't really know what's going on,
but why are you doing this?
I came out of my way to meet you guys.
All because I wanted to tell you that you should
stop coming to this school immediately.
Huh? Are you a staff member?
Not exactly.
You guys know about the recent rape
incidents in this school, don't you?
Wait, you mean...
So, you really are...
Yep, that's right.
Shit! Honoka, move!
I'm gonna beat the shit out of him!
Okay!
Huh? I can't move. I'm being held down!
Wh-What should I do, Manaka-chan?
Seriously. Who the hell are you?
Why the fuck are you doing this?
I told you, I merely came here as a good Samaritan
to tell you to leave this school immediately.
What the hell do you mean by that?
I'll teach your bodies what I mean.
It might break your minds though.
But then, you'll all turn out to be splendid women.
Honoka, we have to get away! This bastard...
What do you mean by that?
You'll understand soon.
Now that you've all settled down, let's get to it.
You've gotten this wet even though
I was only rubbing your ass.
I'm not one to betray expectations, so here I go!
Did it feel good when I put my dick right in, all at once?
You should be thankful. As a result of time being
stopped, you don't even feel the pain.
You should thank me for letting you
experience this without any pain.
I don't know how you'll feel when I start time again though.
After all, you just lost your virginity.
Your pussy's as hot as an oven and it's so tight!
Your pussy's starting to tense up
from being fucked so hard, huh?
If I started time again, I can't imagine
you not having a great time.
Manaka-chan!
N-No! Stop! What are you doing to me?
What is this?
W-When did you...
Take it out! Take it out, you bastard!
Was it really that much of a shock for you?
You're softer than I thought.
You piece of shit! I'm gonna get you!
I'm gonna get you, you hear?!
Manaka-chan, what's wrong?
Look, you're scaring your friend by
making such a face again.
Shit! It's your fault! This feels horrible, so stop it already!
Sorry, this feels too good to stop.
Stop! This feels disgusting! Get away! Take it out!
You're so loud. Be quiet for a bit, okay?
Huh? Manaka-chan, what's wrong?
Phew, she has become quiet.
So then, Honoka-chan?
You seem like you don't really understand what's
going on, so I'll better explain the situation.
H-Huh?
Now, look closely.
So, how do you think Manaka is feeling?
U-Um, she looks like she's in pain?
She does, doesn't she?
All girls feel pain when they take
a man's dick for the first time.
Take a man's dick?
But if we keep going like this...
Pay close attention to her face now.
Her expression changed?
She's feeling good from having sex with me.
Sex? Feeling good?
Don't you know? Sex is something that feels really good.
She hated it just a few seconds ago,
but look at how much she loves it now.
Watch closely, okay? During sex, girls
feel so good and then they cum!
Cum?
Yeah, that's right. Just watch.
Wh-What is this?
What?
Did that feel good, Manaka-chan?
I-It...
You're really dirty, Manaka-chan.
N-No, I'm not!
Don't say stupid shit like that!
Alright I'll drill the meaning of pleasure into your body.
S-Stop! What do you think you're doing?!
What? You want me to stop?
O-Of course!
Maybe I'll have some fun with Honoka instead.
What? What are you talking about?
What do you mean by that?
I mean that I'll have sex with you instead.
I-If Manaka-chan is in pain, then I'll...
Oh, you make me wanna cry.
This is such a beautiful friendship.
You fucking bastard!
Take this!
I'll never forgive you! I'll never fucking forgive you!
Manaka-chan, does it hurt? Why?
You were feeling good just then.
Manaka-chan!
No! Something's rubbing against me...
Don't feel good from tha...
Shit! Why am I...
You're doing great. I'm gonna cum!
Like hell you will!
Stop! Stop!
Why is there so much inside me?!
Getting cum inside your womb felt good, didn't it?
Like hell it did! It felt like shit!
You're a tough one.
Most girls would be breaking down
and crying right about now.
Thanks for the creampie!
Are you okay, Manaka-chan?!
Y-You're satisfied now, right?
Even if it's just Honoka, please spare...
Like hell I will.
You're up next, Honoka.
You look like you're feeling pretty
good despite being a virgin.
You're feeling it already?
I have high expectations for your nympho pussy.
It feels so good. It's like you were born for this.
You're feeling too good for a virgin.
I'm almost jealous. You really were meant for this.
All the other girls would be green
with envy if they knew about this!
I wonder what you'll think of your first sexual experience.
Let's take a peek.
What? What's going on?
My body feels all warm and fuzzy.
You fucker! You're doing the same thing to Honoka?
Yep. Honoka's gobbling me up too.
Knock it off now!
Don't you think Honoka-chan is surprisingly cool with this?
I don't really know what's going on,
but I feel strangely good.
Honoka?
It feels all tingly deep inside me!
H-Honoka? What are you saying?
Don't you get it?
There's a big, hot thing inside me and
even though it hurts a little, it...
That's not right, Honoka!
Alright. I think it's time I let you get a good taste
of my juices deep inside you, Honoka-chan.
J-Juices?
Wait, stop! What the hell are you thinking?!
Geez, you're so thick-headed, Manaka.
Okay, I'll show you something good.
Wh-What? Honoka?
Honoka!
Sorry, but she won't be responding anytime soon!
Hey, what the hell did you do?
I turned her into a doll.
A-A doll?
Wh-What do you mean by that?
What did you do to her? Answer me!
You haven't figured it out yet? Look around you.
What?!
Everyone's frozen... What happened?
What the hell did you do?
Hm, what indeed.
You're slow and clumsy but your
pussy responds much faster.
You were just a virgin a few seconds
ago and now you're dripping wet.
You got used to this way too quick!
Let gо of Honoka! Let gо of her! Cut this out!
Should you really be using such
a tone when asking for a favor?
I could make you a doll too and end your life as you know it.
Wh-What do you mean?
What are you going to do to us?
If you don't want to know, then shut up and
watch your friend's face fill with ecstasy!
Can you see the face of that laid-back girl you
knew changing into one of pure ecstasy?
Sheesh, she's letting out such a sweet voice.
Is having sex with me that good?
You're doing great.
Your dripping wet pussy is wrapping around me
more than Manaka's failure-of-a-pussy ever did.
This pussy is so much better!
You really are great at sex, Manaka-chan!
I'm gonna cum!
C-Cum?
I mean I'm going to cum straight into her deepest reaches.
We're having sex in order to make a child, after all.
N-No! Stop it! You can't!
If you want, I can cum in your pussy instead.
In mine?
Yeah. Just like with the others,
I'll make sure to cum in one of your pussies.
Come on. Make up your mind.
Who should I cum inside?
If I cum inside you again, you're sure to get pregnant.
Getting pregnant when you're a student
sure would suck, wouldn't it?
Ho... no... ка...
What did you say? Couldn't really hear you.
Inside H-Honoka...
Alright! Let Honoka hear what you have to say, too!
Honoka-chan, Manaka-chan just said
you should be my cum dumpster.
C-Cum dumpster?
Yер. Isn't that right, Manaka-chan?
No! Stop! Don't say that!
That's a lovely face you're making.
After all that resistance, I was beginning to
think you couldn't make a face like that.
Manaka-chan... I don't know what's going on,
but it's okay. I'm fine, okay?
How beautiful.
Now I'm gonna cum in you!
Take it all in and get pregnant!
No! No!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum inside!
Something weird's coming!
It's going into my stomach...
Hot stuff is going inside me, so deep inside me!
Yeah, this is how babies are made.
I'm going to have a baby? So I'm going to be a mother?
Exactly. So you can't come to school anymore.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Alright then, let's put the finishing touches on this.
No more! My mind's going blank. I'm gonna go crazy!
No! Take it out! Take it out!
No not inside!
No... No...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Whew. I sure came a lot.
What's wrong, everyone?!
How did this happen?
Everyone, get it together!
What happened? Answer me!
How did this happen?
No! No!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent