I'll go tell your brother, then.
Just stay there and rest up.
Okay.
I'm being a burden to him again.
Your sister is currently resting at the infirmary.
Be sure to drop by and visit her, okay?
Got it.
I'll be heading over to the faculty room. If you
need anything, you can find me there.
Guess I'll see how the club's doing first.
Hey, Sumire-chan,
can you check this out for a bit?
What's this, some movie?
No, but I just found it uploaded a while ago.
Do you think it's real?
Shitsuji-senpai.
I see. So Touka-chan's out sick again.
Well, she's really just anemic.
She'll get better with plenty of rest.
I'll be making dinner for you today, then.
Thanks, and sorry as usual, senpai.
It's okay.
I kinda like doing it, anyway,
so don't mind it.
Senpai, did you hear that just now?
What is it?
No... what is this?
What the hell is that?
Houichi, head on over to Touka.
And what about you, senpai?
I'll catch up later.
So hurry!
Alright.
Be careful.
Touka.
Touka, please be safe.
Damn.
This place's no good, either.
Houichi!
Daisuke?
What's going on?
What in the world are those things?
How would I know?
In any case, I need to hurry and find Touka right now!
Touka!
Ni-Nii-san!
What the heck is that?
Looks kind of disturbing.
Touka...
Hey!
Nii-san!
Damn!
Let go of her!
Why you!
Daisuke!
So slimy... and gross.
Please don't move.
Don't rub it in there!
I don't want this.
Please save me.
Nii-san.
It hurts.
T-Touka.
Stop... moving!
So gross.
The slimy sensation is seeping through my body.
No, please don't stir it like that.
If you keep pushing hard like that,
I'm going to lose my mind.
Any more and I'll...!
It feels hot.
Something's coming.
D-Don't look, nii-san.
Nii-san!
It swallowed her whole!
Can you get up?
Senpai, where's Touka?
It devoured her, and then immediately left.
I have to save her.
How are you even going to do that?
We should just focus on getting away for now!
I agree. We need to get out as soon as possible.
I'm still alive.
I'm scared, nii-san.
Am I going to die soon?
I wonder what this scent is.
My head feels so fuzzy,
and my body feels sluggish.
It's trying to wrap around me again!
Its shape.
My body feels hot, and tingly.
Why am I feeling pleasure with this?
It should feel painful to be constricted like this, and yet.
I'm scared. What's going to happen to my womb?
My pussy's feeling good.
My breasts are feeling good.
Have I gone mad?
For me to feel horny with this.
It's going wild inside me,
hitting all of my soft spots.
This slimy feeling is good.
It's like my body's about to melt.
I'm cumming.
I'm being forced to cum!
I'm cumming!
In the end, I was never able to confess my feelings to nii-chan.
We'll soon join them if this continues.
Let's just head somewhere where they're not around for now.
Rokugo-kun?
Thanks for saving us, Rokugo-senpai.
I'm not sure if we're in the clear yet, though.
Can you tell me what the situation's like in other places?
They've completely infiltrated the school building,
so I think it's just a matter of time before
we run out of places to hide.
I see.
It's possible that it's exactly the same outside.
We're lucky that classes are already over.
Had this happened at noon, we would
have been cornered already.
How many have already gathered here?
Ten, including myself.
They've retreated to the second floor.
You guys should head there and get some rest.
How about you?
There might still be a few survivors out there,
so please wait for me in the meantime.
I see. Be careful then.
Hey, Dai-chan!
Thank goodness all of you are safe.
Still your usual self even in this situation, huh?
Being cheerful is my only specialty, after all.
Don't mention it yourself.
Oh, I was actually on my way to the toilet.
This feeling of relief also made me want to go.
Anyway, we'll head over to the restrooms.
You two go and meet up with the others.
We're still unsure if this floor is safe,
so stay on your guard.
It'll be fine.
I'll have Dai-chan protect me if something happens.
I'm scared.
Now nobody's going to come and rescue us.
Calm down, Kaori.
Houichi!
Thank goodness you're safe.
Well, somehow.
What's wrong?
It's... nothing.
Huh? You're not with Touka-chan?
Hey, Natsumi-chan,
where are the people that are usually here?
Well...
Inagi-sensei and Jinmuji-sensei are in the faculty room.
It seems they're attempting to contact people outside.
Also, Muttsura-sensei went to the
northern school gate to close it.
Thank you, senpai.
That was close.
Things really spiraled out of control.
I wonder what's going to happen now?
What's this?
To-Touka-chan?!
How did...? You were eaten by that thing!
Touka-chan?
Saori!
No!
Where are you touching me?
What is this thing?
No, not there!
If you keep touching me there I'll!
I peed.
Is it...
Is it trying to eat me?
No, get it off. It feels gross.
Please don't rub me there.
I'm being violated inside!
Is it painful... or pleasurable?
The feeling's starting to become more and more muddled.
This long thing is caressing all of my soft spots.
I can't take it anymore!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
It's going to make me cum!
It feels so good, that I'm starting to
no longer care about anything.
Okay. I'll be sure to inform the rest who are not present.
For everyone who's here, this is the current situation:
as everyone is well aware, an unknown
life form assaulted this school.
This unprecedented situation is not restricted to campus.
It's been confirmed that many locations
around the world are also in dire straits.
The general report is that there is still no confirmed
explanation for this phenomenon.
So you mean, it's not just this school,
but the entire outside world?
This can't be.
Does that mean we can't leave?
It's fortunate enough that there are no signs of these
things breaking in from the east school gate.
We'll collect information as we continue
inspecting the situation.
We need to come up with a plan of
action for the foreseeable future.
Just wait a second.
I think it would be better if we evacuate as soon as possible,
and then immediately find adequate refuge.
If the entire world is in such turmoil,
then we can basically forget about being rescued.
We don't even have enough rations to keep
everyone here alive for several days.
Hiro-kun.
I understand your opinion.
More people will die if we attempt
an escape without a proper plan.
We need to be more cautious, and plan out
our escape by first gathering information.
I'm saying that it'd already be too late by then.
It's been an hour.
What are those two doing?
It's not picking up.
Sensei, it's been a while since they left.
I'm going to check and find out what's wrong.
Wait.
It's dangerous to go alone.
You won't be able to do anything if something happens.
I'll go with him, then.
I have a weapon in hand as well.
You mustn't.
I cannot let students put themselves at risk.
I'll be the one to go.
Then,
it wouldn't be a problem if Jinmuji-sensei
accompanies me, right?
While we're out,
the rest will go to the computer lab to collect info.
I don't think we need four people to go out.
Alright then.
Can I ask you to patrol the surrounding area as well?
But you absolutely mustn't leave this building.
There's nobody here.
All empty here, too.
But, something definitely happened here.
Perhaps like at the infirmary.
It came out from the ground, though.
Natsumi!
Why are you here?
I was worried.
That doesn't mean!
Well, she's here already.
I want you two to investigate all the other areas here, alright?
I'll meet up with Rokugo-kun on the first floor.
Is this really okay?
Trying to escape without telling the others.
This is the only option available to us.
My suggestion was never accepted.
They would have definitely stopped us if we told them.
You may be right, but.
Damn.
Hiro-kun!
Don't mind me and...
No!
Hurry!
Get away.
Release Rokugo-kun!
Hey, Houichi,
could Daisuke and Saori have.
But those things haven't reached this area yet.
Even if that's the case,
not seeing a single trace of them still doesn't seem right.
What's that sound?
It's the floor. Something's moving underneath!
It can't be...
Hiro-kun.
Ka... Ka... nako...
Hiro-kun, do you still recognize me?
No matter what you are, you're still.
His thing is inside me.
It's going wild inside me.
Hiro-kun, that feels good.
It's filling me up.
I don't care what you do as long as it's you.
Let me go.
Save me, Hiro-kun.
It's ripping me apart!
It's making a mess of me deep inside.
No... if you keep pushing that hard, I'll.
It's coming... it's coming!
Wait, Hiro-kun.
I just came.
If you do that, I'll cum again.
Ka... na... ko...
Hiro-kun.
I'm quite scared.
He's eating me.
Now we'll be together forever.
It hurts.
I can't breathe.
I'm completely drenched in Hiro-kun's drool.
My body... is being soiled by someone
else other than Htro-kun.
If you keep that intensity up, I'll cum in no time!
Hiro-kun's going to make me cum!
Hey, have you seen Natsumi-san?
She was with us when we came here.
Goodness. I said it was dangerous to wander around alone.
Why don't you just leave her?
Just leave those who try to do things by themselves.
And you call yourself a teacher?
Well, try looking over there.
Wait... this can't be real.
Kanako!
Ai-chan, Chiaki-chan, I'm sorry.
I guess, he really likes Shitsuji-senpai.
Houichi?
No, Natsumi-chan. It's me.
Daisuke!
Where have you been?
Everyone's been looking for you two!
You're not with Saori?
Hey, what's wrong?
You seem kinda strange.
It's nothing.