Are you Kagetora-sama?
I was told you are a clown who came from Japan?
Yes I am. Princess Ridim.
Your highness...
There's no need for you to talk with the likes of this clown.
Why?
I've loved clowns since I was a child.
Say, Kagetora-sama
What sort of act do you perform?
Act?
I acted stupid and set myself as a clown to hide my identity.
But I don't have any acts.
My princess,
apparently this clown can drink wine through his nose.
Really!
I want to see it Kagetora-sama!
I understand.
Wow, that's amazing, Kagetora-sama...
Thanks, Kagetora-sama
You are the only one who will speak to me
with such familiarity.
Not at all!
I'm the one who's humbled for having the Princess'
accompany a clown such as myself.
Well, Kagetora-sama.
If it's not too much to ask of you.
Would you like to befriend me?
Why gladly.
The tea Kagetora-sama prepared tastes so refined.
I'm honored it is to your highness's liking.
Then, what's the continuation of that fairytale?
What will happen to the princess and the young man?
Indeed.
The young man felt love at first sight for the princess
and both fell in love each other.
However, their status was far too different.
So, the young man
decided to use a certain spell.
A...spell?
Yes, a spell.
The young man cast such evil spell on the princess.
He wanted to have a lasting love.
Yes.
Just like this.
As for the requested investigation of Ridim-sama's trend.
Ridim-sama seems to swim alone in the pool to cool down her body after her dance practice.
Really,
she's already been through all that, and is still the careless princess.
Well, it works to my advantage.
Why is my body this hot?
It won't cool down even if I swim in the pool.
And why does this feel so good if it's not even sex?
I'm just rubbing that part.
There's a sticky liquid coming out from down there.
It's so good I'm...
I'm going to pee.
It'll be a while until she's at her limit and craves for me.
I'm wearing a swimsuit today too.
So I'll take good care of her here where no one comes.
Meylin? What's the matter?
It seems Ridim-sama collapsed in the middle of her practice.
She's currently resting at the infirmary.
What?!
Why?
Why won't this throbbing inside me stop?
Didn't I tell you?
Kagetora-sama?
You're already affected by this clown's charm.
A little.
Why do you run away?
You can't hold your craving for my sperm since that day right?
Yes.
Yes...yes.
I'm losing my strength.
What a big clitoris.
I can tell even with your bloomers on.
My clit.
It wasn't this weird before.
This is your fault!
Is this because of my sperm?
I think it happened before.
I had sex with many girls before but this is my first time to see one this big.
Touch it, please.
If you touch me there.
You'll feel good right?
You should know.
Since you're touching it by yourself.
How did you know?
Oh, so you really touched it?
You fooled me!
Yes...you must.
Please touch me there.
I'll pee...I'm going to pee.
Please spare me.
What a shameless princess.
This comes next.
You must have sex with me.
But, I'm a princess.
I need to protect my purity until I get married, for my country.
But you wanted this right?
I know you want this, right?
Your throbbing won't stop unless you
enjoy yourself with this thing.
If you ignore it, you'll wet yourself just by being touched.
But...
the sex is....
If you keep quiet no one will know.
A man can't tell the difference between a virgin
or someone who experienced it only once.
Is that true?
Yes.
Now, say "please stick your dick in my pussy".
Say it and you'll be rewarded.
Please stick your dick in my pussy.
Inside my pussy!
Well, I can't help it if you keep pestering me.
This is the greatest ever!
How?
It's nice!
It tickles?
Your clitoris is getting bigger.
You're enjoying yourself, aren't you?
Well then, I'm going to cum inside that princess' pussy with that giant clitoris!
Yes inside.
I'll get fertilized if you come inside!
Exactly. I'll have you bear my child!
Ok but they'll find out.
They'll find out I had sex!
I shouldn't.
I mustn't get pregnant!
Wow!
I know it's wrong.
But it feels so good coming inside.
I'm cumming!
What?
It won't stop.
He won't stop coming inside.
If he comes that much, it'll feel too good.
I'll break.
The princess not only has big clit, but squirts as well?
Maybe.
Might as well take this occasion and drop a
second load to make sure you get pregnant.
Yes.
Don't stop too soon.
I can't.
I'm going crazy.
It's so good I'm going crazy.
I'm coming.
It's still coming.
It's coming out. He's really coming again.
Why? It feels good dripping from my pussy.
Yes.
I want this as a first kiss.
My head.
I'm going insane.
It's so good I'm going insane.
He just released it a while ago and he's releasing it again inside!
It's coming out.
It's so good. I'm going to die.
How was it, your Highness?
The throbbing in your body is gone right?
Ah...she can't hear.
Well then, I'll leave the cleanup to Meylin.
I'll let you enjoy it again, your Highness.
Why?
I was pleasured just yesterday.
He even came inside me.
Why is my body throbbing again?
Why do I want more sex?
I apologize for the delay, your Highness.
Here.
I'll stop that throbbing of yours.
You're going to fuck me again right?
Possibly.
If you prefer, you can do it with your mouth alone.
Eh?
So...what's wrong?
You want the sperm right?
Squeeze it out already.
Yes.
If you want to ingest it.
I'll just use this on Yukino again.
Please, wait...
Oh.
Would Princess Ridim prefer to have sex?
I love having sex...
Even if it's just to protect that girl.
Besides a man can't tell the difference between a virgin
or someone one who only got fucked once.
Yeah.
Then, I really do want it.
I prefer hot and dirty sex.
Doing it with the mouth is awesome.
Do it already.
Yes.
What? Did you cum with just one thrust?
You were really holding it right? You perverted princess...
I didn't cum.
I haven't cum yet.
Wow.
If you do it that hard...I'll...
As a clown, I must make you enjoy yourself!
Yes.
Please...faster.
I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum.
Well then.
I'm going to thrust hard until you cum!
Yes...I'm in ecstasy...I'm already gone.
Thrust more.
I'm cumming now.
It's coming out.
The cum.
The sperm.
He's ejaculating so much. I'm breaking.
It feels so good...I'm breaking.