No! Stop!
Not inside!
No!
I had that dream again.
It's because of that threatening text.
I can't believe someone peeked and took pictures of me.
Dear Miss Student Council President,
I have something to discuss with you in secret, so come to the Anime Club's clubroom alone.
If you don't show up, I'll publish this picture on the internet, so please don't keep me waiting.
President of the Anime Club, Satou Futushi.
What's that scumbag's scheme?
No way!
Is he planning to rape me like in my dreams?
I don't want that! I don't want to be raped by that scumbag.
Still, I can't do it in a place like this.
If that scumbag found me,
what would he do to me?
But when I imagine that someone's
watching me, I can't hold back.
Y-Yuna-chan...
You were staring at Himeno-san just now, right?
Like I said, it's a misunderstanding, Yuna-chan.
You're awful! You're Yuna's boyfriend now!
Don't look at other women!
We're lovers after all!
Futoshi-kun, you know... I love you.
It's been a week since we became lovers.
Yuna doesn't look at other men anymore!
Yuna-chan's unexpectedly jealous, huh?
That was thoughtless of me.
As an apology, I'll invite you to my home this Sunday.
I want to take your picture, Yuna-chan.
But... photos, you say... That's so embarrassing.
But, if it's a memento that Futoshi-kun won't part with...
I can't?
N-No, it's okay.
I'll come to your home this Sunday, Futoshi-kun.
Um, Futoshi-kun...
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Kiss me.
Th-Then, I'm going now.
Looks like the order to get horny after kissing me works well.
Thanks to that, I got horny as well.
I can't go to class like this.
Maybe I'll call my cum-dump and enjoy myself a little.
Gakuen Saimin Reido
~ I can't take it anymore. I'm cumming while you're cumming in my womb ~
Remember this, Fatass. When I repay Akira-kun's debt to you,
I'm gonna make you disappear from the campus!
Oh, are you sure you can talk to me like that?
I'm gonna tell Aihara that I'm the father of your child.
No! Don't tell Akira-kun!
Then, if you don't have sex with me to repay
his debt, and erase the stench down there,
you can't do it with Aihara.
If not, you won't deceive Aihara with your child.
You really are the worst kind of trash!
That's what Nagisa-chan believes,
but I've been cumming inside her for three weeks now.
She really might get pregnant.
Not that!
I'm gonna go crazy!
Oh my, are you enjoying this?
I thought you said that you wouldn't
enjoy being fucked by a scumbag.
I'm not feeling good at all! Who would!?
You're right.
You couldn't enjoy getting fucked by someone
you hate so much you want to kill them.
No! Not that!
If you do that, I'm gonna cum!
Even though it's just this scumbag's
dick, I'm getting addicted to it!
I'm cumming!
You came so hard.
Well, you can't do anything about that
after enjoying my dick every day.
I didn't cum because of you, scumbag.
Nagisa-chan never betrays my expectations.
If she did, I couldn't enjoy this order I prepared earlier.
Oh my, your cellphone's ringing.
Aren't you going to pick it up?
I can't answer it at a time like this, you trash!
It may be something important. Answer it. That's an order.
No!
Too slow! Pick it up sooner, Nagisa!
Akira-kun? I-I'm sorry, I'm a little busy.
I'll call you back later.
Don't screw with me!
I even took my time and called you!
I'm sorry, Akira-kun. Don't be mad.
Thanks to the order, she thinks that calls
from me are calls from Aihara.
Why do you have such a weird voice?
It's nothing.
Let's go on a date this Sunday.
Huh?
What, aren't you happy?
I'm happy. Of course I am.
And you know, it's about time you
gave me your virginity, Nagisa.
If you love me, you'd want to have sex with me, wouldn't you?
Th-That's...
Ah, no!
Nagisa, you don't want to?
N-No, that's not what I mean.
You didn't even let me kiss you last time.
Don't you love me?
I love you! I really love you!
Then, on the next date, we're gonna go all the way.
Bye.
Akira-kun!?
How did you like being pleasured by a scumbag's
dick while talking to your lover, Nagisa-chan?
Fatass, I'm gonna kill you!
I'm cumming!
I'll kill you for sure, Fatass.
I don't like this attitude.
What now?
What's this?
My pussy's hot inside.
Piss!?
No!
Stop that!
No, no!
I even came inside you, but in the end,
I washed it out with my piss, huh?
Please!
No, no, no!
I'm... not a toilet.
Don't piss inside me.
No other girl smells as much like
a toilet as you do, Nagisa-chan.
You gotta be kidding me!
I'm to become your slave!?
Anime Club
I'm surprised that you can even say those
indecent and inappropriate things!
But you have no right to choose, Himeno-san.
Let me go, you filth!
Doing this... Don't tell me you're gonna...
...rape me?
Stop!
You can't cum inside me!
No!
Oh, it seems like Miss Student Council
President fantasizes about rape.
Don't put rape fantasies and I in the same sentence!
You can't hide it from me.
No matter what you say, you re a pervert whose pussy
gets drenched when she masturbates in the bathroom.
Stop this at once!
If you insult me any further, you won't get away with-
Then, remember everything now.
Of course, everything from your hypnosis training.
Now, please dedicate your precious
first kiss to me, Lady Himeno.
No!
Don't!
My body's moving on its own!
Stop this!
My first kiss is with a stinking penis.
Not only is it violating my lips, but it's also deep in my throat.
Why do I feel good, even though he's
doing something this awful to me!?
I-I can't breathe...
Why!? Even though I feel like I'm gonna die...
It feels too good. I'm cumming!
No! Stop that!
I can't believe something so filthy is inside me!
My asshole is still too tight, even though
a big enema was used to widen it.
What a thick penis you have!
No!
It's gonna turn inside out! My butthole's gonna turn inside out!
I'm gonna break!
And now a man is spanking me.
It's so shameful that I feel like I'm gonna die!
It's strange!
I'm feeling good from getting spanked? I'm a pervert!
No! I'm gonna cum from having my asshole violated!
I'm cumming!
Do you remember now?
Where am I?
This is a hidden room in the Anime Club.
D-Don't tell me...
I experienced all of that for real?
I was thinking about fulfilling your dreams.
No! S-Stop that!
Restricting your freedom and taking your virginity by force.
How do you like it? It's a situation from
your dreams, right, Himeno-san?
That's a lie!
There's no way I'd wish to be... violated like that!
A high-class girl who wishes to be treated
like a bitch by someone of humble birth...
It's lovely.
No! Stop!
Don't look at me.
I'm really going to be raped... like that girl in the book.
I'm being tortured...
and enjoying it.
Here, I'm gonna stuff this inside you.
Y-You can't! Anything but that!
My chastity is a very important asset of the
Ryuuguup family, so don't break my hymen!
I'll do anything!
In the end, it's useless.
I won't get my wish, and he'll take my virginity.
For my first time, I m being roped by o commoner.
This is the worst possible experience for a woman.
Here, I m gonna take your virginity with my scumbag penis.
No! Stop that!
I'll do anything. I'll give you anything besides that!
So please, leave me my virginity intact!
You'll do anything?
Yes, of course.
Then, I'll take your offer and make
you bear my children, Himeno-san!
What!? W-Wait a second!
Ow! It hurts!
It hurts so much!
It's gonna tear!
This is the pain of accepting a man inside, isn't it?
The pain of my polished body being violently pierced.
Pull out at once!
Don't violate me with your dirty penis anymore!
This scumbag s penis is penetrating inside my
body, as if it wants to stick to my insides!
It hurts!
They're pinching my nipples!
You wanted me to do it like this
You enjoy things like this.
Don't screw around with me!
There's no way I would enjoy being humiliated like this!
What an incredibly pleasant feeling,
As the pain radiates from my genitals and nipples,
a pleasant feeling, like I've been struck by a
thunderbolt of humiliation, is rushing to my head.
I can't resist this pleasure!
I understand the feelings of that girl in the
book, who's o slave to being humiliated.
Stop this already! Don't insult me anymore!
Or I won't be able to turn back!
This piece of trash has even taken my first kiss!
And I thought that I'd give my first kiss to someone I loved!
Don t worry. You gave away your first
kiss to my dick a long time ago.
No!
And now, as I promised, I'm gonna make
you pregnant with my child, Princess!
No, are you thinking about cumming inside me!?
You can't! You can't do that!
When I think about this scumbag's sperm entering my womb,
about this commoner impregnating me,
about the unmatched misery that will ensue...
it makes me shiver!
Here I come!
He's cumming inside!
Inside me, inside my pussy, deep inside my womb!
He finally came inside me.
Not only did he take my virginity, but he also came inside me!
I've descended to the lowest level a human can reach!
Now you've lost your status as a princess.
Start acting like my slave, just like you want.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Why would I do that for an ugly commoner like you!?
You're still saying that, huh?
You trash! You're still thinking about cumming!?
You can't! No more...
I'm telling you that you can't!
What an incredible quantity.
With this, I'm really going to get pregnant.
No!
I'm really gonna get pregnant!
You spurted again!
I came when you came inside me.
Sperm, sperm, shoots like cream...
With an asshole shot, I'm gonna become a slave.
With this, I've changed into your anal slave.
Please, cum already, Master.
You're such a demanding princess.
It's in there!
Master's dick is in my ass-pussy!
The game is over. Now it's your turn, Yuna-chan.
I'm not sure about this.
It's a little embarrassing to wear my
leotard in front of you, Futoshi-kun.
Aren't we lovers?
But...
As lovers, we should be naked together, without the leotard.
So that means, you and I...
When he invited me to his home, I was
thinking that maybe it was about that.
As I thought, I'm going to experience my first time.
Futoshi-kun...
Well then, it's adults' time.
Now, remember everything from your hypnosis training.
What is... this?
Why is Yuna doing these things?
What's more, it's not like I love Satou-kun, but I'm kissing him.
Oh my, are you all right, Yuna-chan?
You did all this...
Yes, with hypnosis.
You're awful! Why would you do such cruel things to me!?
You're the worst kind of trash!
Pervert!
I'll never forgive you!
I don't mind that.
After all, I'm gonna make you love me, Yuna-chan.
Me, love you!?
That's impossible!
No! Stop it!
Wasn't it you who lured me by dressing erotically
and getting wet between your legs?
You made me like that with your hypnosis!
Please, forgive me!
I don't want to give my virginity to someone like you!
Please be sure to engrave your first
time in your heart, Yuna-chan.
This is the feeling of Yuna-chan's pussy? It's simply the best!
Ow! It hurts! Pull out!
You're gonna feel good soon.
After all, I've given you a hypnotic suggestion
to feel good while you're getting fucked.
And the better you feel, the more you'll grow to love me!
No! I don't want to! Stop it!
Don't thrust it against my womb!
Don't make me feel any better!
It hurts! My special place hurts so much, like its going to tear.
Why am I feeling good?
Why am I beginning to think fondly of Satou-kun?
Looks like you're feeling pretty good already.
Which means that...
Of course not!
Nobody would feel good while being forcibly violated!
Then, I'll thrust it in more so you'll feel better!
No! Your dick is going all the way inside me!
Don't thrust it against my womb!
Don't make me feel any better!
Why are my hips moving?
It's just like when I feel good from masturbating and can't stop!
How is it? I bet hitting your womb
feels so good that you can't resist.
Don't hold yourself back. Cum!
Cum? I don t want to cum in front of Satou-kun!
But... But, but...
It feels too good. I can't take it anymore.
That's right. You'll climax when I cum inside you.
Soon your body will want sex with me all the time, Yuna-chan.
Love or hate won't matter. Your body
will just keep demanding me.
That's... No.... Don't cum inside me!
It's a dangerous day! I'm gonna get pregnant!
Your voice is saying that, but your
body wants me to cum inside.
I don't want that!
I don't want to, but... but...
Looks like your body has already been captured by pleasure.
No! I'm gonna have a baby! I don't want to get pregnant!
Here, welcome to the world of depravity!
No!
His sperm's coming in. No... It's pouring into my womb.
How do you feel?
More...
I want you to fuck my special place more.
In that case, should I take another of your virginities?
Yes, I'll give it to you.
I'll give them all to you whenever you like.
Even though it's your first time, I've trained
you for this, so it went in so smoothly.
So this is anal sex. I dreamed about it so many times.
The real Futoshi-kun's dick feels so good!
My butthole feels so good!
A hard and thick one's going in and out of there!
I'm gonna cum inside you again.
Cum! Cum inside my butt!
This time your sperm came into my butt!
I'm cumming!
My womb's gonna break!
Even the inside of my womb is filled with your dick!
I'm cumming!
With this, Yuna-chcm's heart and body are mine.
10 Months Later
Even though I have a fiancée, I'm having sex!
It's still before the wedding!
I want to get pregnant with Futoshi-kun's child!
It seems like I can complete Kaoruko-sensei's training.
Cum already!
I'll always dress any way you like, Futoshi-kun!
So spurt your thick sperm inside me already!
You're too violent, Master!
If you use my butt like this every day...
my ass-pussy will become too loose!
Don't do that, Fatass.
Don't cum inside me! It's a dangerous day!
You really shouldn't!
I don't want to get pregnant with your child, Fatass!
Just don't impregnate me!
My child's going to be born soon
so be satisfied with just my mouth.
In exchange, I'll drink as much cum as you want, Futoshi-kun.
Futoshi-kun, hurry up! Cum! Make me pregnant!
Here it comes.
Futoshi-kun's sperm is coming in, trying to make me pregnant.
I'm cumming!
It's coming in. My student's going to impregnate me.
Futoshi-kun's sperm is swimming towards my oviduct.
Good luck, Futoshi-kun's sperm.
I believe that you can do it.
I'll never forgive you.
Hey...
Instead of a stupid game, let's practice sex with cute little me.
Sensei, you have your own character. This one is mine.
You think so? But a long, silky haired character fits me better.
Like I said, I'm the real one!
Oh my, if we speak about blonde, noble
characters, nobody's more suitable that me.
You're from a different game!
She's right. That's why you should play with me, Master.
Who's that?
EROGE GOES
INTO THE OTHER STOMACH
After all, I'm just...