Two weeks have already passed since the revelation
of the horrifying incident at Excellent Academy.
The culprit remains at large and his motives
and methods are still shrouded in mystery.
The investigation has come to a standstill.
In the midst of this, Excellent Academy has
confirmed it will be closing down, and will be...
At the school, stop by time.
The unenoing play of vengeance. The unctoppable deflowering arc.
That's the end of this school.
It's strange to see that they're still operating,
even after everything that's happened.
I hear that all the affected students have either
already transferred or are at the hospital.
The only students still here are the ones that were
lucky enough to have avoided the incident.
I win!
Darn, I was so close.
You two are so fast!
You're amazing!
Not at all.
Yeah, we're still only novices at best.
Still, it's pretty lonely now
that it's just us in this huge school.
I guess it's cool that we can
have the pool to ourselves, but...
You're right.
Every day is just self-study anyway,
is there really any reason for us to come at all?
There's nothing we can do about it.
We were lucky enough to not be around when
it all happened, but the rest of the students...
Yeah, especially considering what happened...
If we hadn't all gone out on
an errand that day, we would've also...
The girls who were attacked either transferred out
or were so traumatized that
they had to be taken into hospital.
Yeah, it's really annoying. I've been getting
pressured to either transfer or study abroad, too.
I want us all to graduate from here together,
but that didn't sit too well with my parents.
Naturally.
Sure, I'd love to graduate
with my best friends too, but...
In light of what happened,
we just look crazy for wanting to stay here.
I want to graduate with all of you.
I couldn't stand to transfer
to another school at this point!
Uh, let's stop talking about this for now.
We're safe now, so let's just focus
on making more fun memories at school!
Don't worry, we'll all be able to graduate together!
Yeah, let's drop this topic for now. We're all safe anyway.
The culprit will surely be caught soo...
I didn't think there were still leftovers
from the last time I was here.
I heard the news and came
rushing over to see you guys.
I checked your names from these
things I found in the locker room.
Katy Majima.
Seto Manaka.
Takahama Shizoru.
Shinjou Honoka.
Rejoice.
Today, you'll be getting a special
private lesson from me.
You don't have to wait until graduation.
I'll help you guys leave school now.
If the only students left
in this school are raped too,
this school will be finished for good!
First up is...
Katy. I guess I'll go with you.
I'm kinda curious what
a half-japanese girls body is like.
What a tight ass you've got.
Your G-cups feel so good. I could do this all day.
Damn, I can't get enough!
Sucking tits through a swimsuit feels great!
The combination of the pool water with her
deliciously sweet odor is absolutely awesome!
I'm going to get a taste of this next.
The taste of a half-japanese pussy mixed
with chlorine is so good! Amazing, in fact!
I'll suck it all out for you!
Sweet. Your swimsuit has started
to soak in your pussy juices.
Now, I'll lick it directly.
Hm? Is your pussy saying something?
It's saying it's really wet and
hungry for a dick, isn't it?
That's fine. I'll lick you until I'm hard.
What a dirty smell.
Smells like a bitch in heat.
Wow, we've got a good flow
coming out now, don't we?
Your asshole is getting wet,
should I play with it as well?
Well she is a hottie, so maybe this
has already seen some action?
Oh? It sucked me in with no trouble at all.
Is this not your first time doing anal?
You really are getting off
from your asshole, aren't you?
Looks like I'll have to ask her directly.
What?! What's going on?
I can't move my body!
Oh, Katy. Are you still not used to
using Japanese? Your pronunciation is off.
Who are you?!
Let go of me! Let me go!
Tell me, do you usually speak
like you're some kind of foreigner?
I'm going to keep playing
with your asshole until you answer.
No, knock it off! Stop!
Calm down. It feels good, doesn't it?
No! Stop!
You have anal sex all the time, don't you?
See, your asshole is spread so wide.
What... are you saying?
Why am I... I don't get any of this!
You should calm down a little.
Look, your asshole is accepting me so easily.
No, it's not! No way!
It feels good though, right?
Well, we'll confirm this soon enough.
With one thrust of my dick,
everything will be clear.
You pervert! I can't believe this is happening!
I would never feel good from...
Well, now that you've calmed down,
let's go a round.
I wonder what a half-japanese girl's asshole is like.
I'm putting it in.
I'll make sure it goes all the way in.
You're so tight! This is amazing!
Just how I imagined the asshole
of an anal freak would feel like.
It's so tight! It's like it doesn't
want me to take my dick out!
What's with that face?
Does having a big fat dick shoved
in your asshole really feel that good?
All right then. I'll take your veteran
asshole and rip it a new one.
You're already feeling it from your asshole.
Does having foreigner blood mixed in you
make your asshole loose from birth?
Doing anal with a halfie is new for me.
The sensation is completely different from a pussy.
How about we ask Ms. Halfie here
for her impressions on this dick in her ass.
What's going on? My butt...
Oh? Did you just cum with your ass?
Ongasming with your ass? What a bad girl.
How? When did you...
put it in my ass?!
How about it? Anal sex feels good, doesn't it?
No, it doesn't!
Take it out!
What did you do? What did you do to me?!
Anal sex, my dear. Anal sex.
This... This sensation...
What is it?
Did you feel some kind of amazing
sensation that you've never felt before?
It feels so good that you can't even answer?
Well, your pussy is totally drenched after all!
No! S-Stop it!
Look, It's getting soaked.
It's making your asshole wet too.
Your lust is different as a halfie, isn't it?
Wh-Who are you?
How did you do this?
How indeed.
Everyone in this school asked the same thing.
You pervert! You dirty, horrid pervert!
Don't move my hips! Stop it!
Anal sex feels good, doesn't it?
I'll let you experience something
even more amazing!
What? No, you can't do tha...
As soon as I stop time,
your mouth and asshole become honest.
With your body being more relaxed,
it's far easier to move my piston!
Fucking a half-japanese
beauty is totally awesome!
Every time I thrust,
I can feel her swimsuit rub against me!
It really turns me on!
Oh, that's good! That's really good!
Your rack is amazing too, but your huge ass
just makes me want to thrust harder!
Okay, here we go.
I'm going to blow everything I have into your ass!
Here goes!
It's hot! My butthole is... No!
What is this? It feels so good!
I'm not done yet. There's still more coming out.
I'll shoot everything I have inside you.
I just got raped by a man I don't know,
but my mind can't stop
thinking about how good it feels.
My butt is so hot!
This is new.
Steady never did this to me.
I came inside as promised.
Was it better than expected?
No, it wasn't...
There's no way it was!
No! Why did I cum with my butt? Why?
Did having my dick shoved
in your ass feel that good?
You really are quite the slut, aren't you?
No, I'm not!
Don't lie. Just look at yourself.
You got off, didn't you?
So which of us is really the pervert,
you anal-fiend halfie!
I-I'm not! That's not true!
So why are you so wet, then?
Your pussy juices are dripping to the floor.
No! It's not what you think!
You might say that,
but your ass looks like it's thrilled.
Oh, what a wonderful sound.
No! It's really not what you think!
Do you want another taste?
Don't say such stupid things!
Of course I don't! I won't let you!
How about it? Our bodies are really compatible.
Compatible?
What I just did was something
you've never felt before, right?
That's...
I'll let your pussy have a taste next.
My pussy?
No, you can't!
No way! I'm saving that for my future husband!
Oh my, that's a rare sentiment in this day and age.
Y-You really can't!
I'll make you orgasm with your pussy this time.
It might feel even better than your asshole did.
No! I don't want to!
I really don't want to!
I won't forgive you if you do that!
You say that, but your tone
of voice isn't very convincing.
No...
All right, I'll let you taste my dick all you want!
No! Stop!
Dear friends, can you hear this dirty sound?
She's this wet even though she's a virgin.
She's what you would call a pervert, right?
Okay, time to start time again. Here we go!
It's in me! It's inside me!
I've been saving myself for my
future husband all this time...
But this feels so good!
I feel like I'm going to melt!
Sex with me is the best, isn't it?
With a stranger, I...
No! My virginity wasn't something
I wanted to give to a stranger!
I know that, but my body won't listen!
It's happy! It's rejoicing!
My pussy is glad it's having sex!
Looks like you like it a lot, Katy, you slut.
That's not true!
It hurts, it's just because it hurts.
That's the truth...
It's too late to be trying to make up truths.
Here!
I'll cum a shit-load in here, too.
I'll never... forgive you.
My body feels so weird
and my head's a mess...
Did me cumming in both your asshole
and pussy really feel that good?
No, it didn't!
There's no way it could have!
It didn't feel good at all!
You're not very convincing with your
face in ecstasy, Ms. Sexually-starved Halfie.
No, this pervert...
I didn't want to have sex
with this pervert at all...
Excellent.
I'm glad that you seem to
be satisfied with your care.
Okay, so who's next?
She seems like the type who's strong willed
and has a strong sense of responsibility.
I'll use my power to make her submit to me.
That seems like it'd be one hell of a good time.
She's not exactly flat-chested,
but she's definitely lacking compared to the others.
Instead, she's slim and has amazing legs.
Her skin's so smooth, I just want to rub my face against it.
Her ass is on the smaller side,
but it's still nice and tight!
Oh, God, I can't get enough of the smell of their assholes
through their swimsuits mixed witch chlorine.
It really turns me on!
Okay, I've decided, I'll rub my dick against your ass.
Oh wow, the feeling of your ass through
this swimsuit... Swimsuits are just great!
I wonder what kind of reaction
you'll have when I unfreeze time.
Yo.
No!
Whoa there. I'm not letting you get away.
Wh-What are you doing? Who are you?
Don't make that face.
Who am I? You know already, don't you?
You... Are you that rapist?
That's correct. Now, rejoice.
I've come to rape you all.
Just like your friend over there. See?
Katy? Katy?!
I'll rape you just like I did her.
No! Stop! Let me go! Let me...
It's good that you're feisty,
but in the end, you're just gonna get raped anyway.
Bad girls need to be punished.
You seem like the type of smart girl
who hasn't masturbated in her life.
Can you handle a dick right off the bat?
I'll go all the way in!
Yeah, now I'm getting excited!
Can you feel my hard rod pushing inside of you?
I'll make you feel even more pain!
Here, take this!
Can you tell?
Like this, the pleasure you experience
will just keep accumulating.
Both the pain and pleasure will build up!
What a great sound. Let me hear it more!
Louder! Louder!
Alright, I'll unfreeze time now.
Look, it's inside you.
You can clearly see all the blood from your hymen.
No!
It hurts! I'm in agony!
Let me go!
You don't mean that.
Your pussy is so happy right now.
Ow! It hurts! It really, really hurts!
Looks like it really does.
Well, since you don't have any experience,
I guess that's not too surprising.
Ow! Ouch!
It really looks like you're in pain. How about this?
Wow, this is fun!
How about I teach you the pleasure of climaxing?
What are you going to do? What are you...
More! More!
I'll give you the greatest orgasm ever!
One that'll make your head spin!
Come on, cum!
It's hot...
No! Something's coming!
I'm going to pee myself!
Oh, you peed yourself?
It felt good, didn't it?
Don't worry, I'll make sure that your other
two friends get the same treatment.
S-Stop! Don't touch the...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: fyurie | punk4real
quality control: fyurie