R-Rokugo-kun...
Why...
Who's there?!
Koujiya-kun?
Good evening, Tsutsuji-senpai.
Is that you... Touka-chan?
Tentacle Academy XX of the DEAD
D-Daisuke...
This can't be real.
I see. So nii-san's okay then?
That's a relief.
I'm gonna go check on Saori. You should
go meet up with the others in the library.
Saori-senpai? Oh, there's nothing to worry about.
Your body... It's the same as those things!
Don't look at me like that.
If you get the same body as me, you can
do anything you want with its power.
Why are you...
I want you to attack Natsumi-senpai, Daisuke-san.
Wh-Why?!
Why Natsumi...
I'd like anyone who tries to steal my
nii-san away from me to disappear.
Your nii-san?
You really see him like that...
No way... Touka-chan did?
Yeah, so there you have it.
Sorry.
Stop!
Let go of me! What are you trying to do to me?!
Just stay still.
If you don't it won't go in easily.
Stop!
I'm still a...
Holy crap, it's tight.
That's the magic of being an athlete, huh?
Please, Daisuke...
Please stop this.
That's not happening.
I've always wanted to do this after all.
I guess there's no way you'd know that, huh?
You were always so tunneled onto Hoichi-kun after all.
But I guess it's thanks to his denseness
that I get to take your first time.
So how's my dick feel?
It's completely different from a human's.
I can even make it bigger than humanly possible!
Even if you do that, it won't feel good...
What? You like Hoichi that much?
Come on, I'll make you feel good in his stead.
Stop running off your mouth.
Just take it out already!
This is so good! You're the best, Natsumi-chan!
Why is a guy like this...
Don't leer at me like that.
Your lower half doesn't seem to hate this.
Just thinking about having sex
with you gets me so tunned on!
Yeah and I couldn't feel worse!
It feels disgusting!
I'm about to cum inside. That's okay, right?!
No! Stop it!
Don't be so loud.
Everyone's gonna hear us.
What's there to hate about this?
I'm just cumming a little inside you, that's it.
I'm gonna fill your insides with my seed, okay?
Save me, Hoichi!
At this rate, I'm gonna...
Come on, if you don't get away quick,
you're gonna get cummed inside.
Or what? Do you feel good from me now?
No!!
What's the matter?
Not going to draw your bow?
Whose side are you on?
This boy over here says he wants to get
back at you for before, Citsuji-senpai.
Eat her up.
Tsutsuji-senpai!
Wait!
How unfortunate.
I'm glad you're safe.
R-Right. I thought I saw someone, but
it looks like it was just my imagination.
What's the matter? Done fighting back?
Or what? Does it feel good now?
There's no way this'd feel good for me.
It's this smell...
It's making my mind go crazy.
It's because of this weird mist I'm being forced
to breathe that my body's reacting like this.
Natsumi-chan, you have such a nicely shaped ass.
Maybe I should take your first time here too?
And there we go.
Now then, please relax your ass for me.
So fucking tight!
I feel like I'm gonna be crushed!
What's this? Are you turned on, right now?
I found your weakness, Natsumi-senpai!
Why is this... I don't want to feel pleasure from this!
This is great. I love being able to fuck both holes at once.
This body was worth getting.
No! I don't want to cum from this!
Let's cum together this time, Natsumi!
Why did you think I was being attacked, Hoichi?
I could sense its presence when I was on the second floor.
"It?"
The thing that attacked Touka.
I see...
I should tell Hoichi about what Touka-chan said...
Hoichi?
Natsumi?
I've had a lot of fun when you were gone.
What?
Poor Natsumi-chan.
She loves you so much, Hoichi.
You can't protect anyone!
Next up might be that girl right there.
Daisuke!
Don't stare at me like that.
Later, Hoichi.
I'm taking Natsumi-chan with me.
So they got Natsumi-chan too?
Um, so about Rokugo-senpai and the others...
Yes, we could see it happening from here.
Sensei, it seems they've infiltrated
this side of the school as well.
I think we'd be better off evacuating as quickly as possible.
No, I think leaping into the unknown is
much more dangerous than staying here.
But if they've already made it into this building,
then we can't stay here anymore, can we?
If we're going to run away, we need to find a safe place.
Let's take turns taking watch outside the room.
Let's make sure that we can at least escape
through the emergency stairs if need be.
Geez, I'm unlucky.
I just want a way out so I can say goodbye to these idiots.
And now you're one of us, Natsumi-chan.
One of you? What do you...
My body's...
Oh, looks like your transformation's starting already.
My body...
It's so hot!
And now you're a monster just like me!
Mon... ster...
That can't...
I can't be...
It's all Hoichi's fault.
If he didn't leave you by yourself,
this never would've happened.
No...
Why don't you just forget about
him and start cozying up with me?
Shut... up...
The girl that Hoichi always liked
was Tsutsuji-senpai anyway, right...
Welcome to this side.
Who's there?!
T-Touka-chan?!
Why are you with those things?!
They won't attack their own kind, so don't worry.
My body... won't move...
Are you surprised?
I can manipulate any of them as I like.
It's Tsutsuji-senpai's turn next.
I need to make everyone who's
made a pass at nii-san, disappear.
Hoichi...
Hoichi? It's time to switch.
Don't blame yourself too much.
Not just Touka-chan, but even Natsumi...
If the same thing happens to you, I...
S-Senpai?
When I saw Natsumi-chan being attacked,
I thought "thank god that's not me".
That's horrible, isn't it?
Anyone would think the same thing in that situation.
I know that, but...
I need to do something about
these feelings or I'm going to...
Hoichi, you're getting big from me, right?
Yes. Senpai, you too...
Hoichi, it's okay now.
Hurry and come inside me.
This is my first time...
Me too.
Are you okay?
Should I stay like this for a little?
No, don't worry about it.
Just move however you'd like, Hoichi.
Hoichi?
It feels good!
It's so warm inside of you, senpai.
And it's so wet.
I've become one with you, Hoichi.
I'm so happy!
I feel like I'm about to lose my mind. I'm so happy!
Your dick's getting even bigger than before!
I might be reaching my limit!
Let it out inside...
Please!
Here I go, senpai!
Please, flood my insides with your semen!
I'm cumming!
There's so much hot stuff deep inside me.
You're really going at it, huh, Kaori-chan?
Why don't we run away together?
We can take Sumire-chan with us too.
U-Uh...
I can look after the two of you.
P-Please stop.
Don't lay a finger on my sister.
You wanna run? Do it by yourself.
Oh, you're so scary.
What's the matter, Chiaki?
Nothing.
All clear.
I'm finally free.
A teacher trying to run away by himself? What a bad man.
Shit!
First, let's go to the faculty office to get the car keys.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, do you mind if we turned on the lights?
We can't. We have no idea what those things react to.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe there's still someone holed up in here?
You...
It feels so gross!
Don't touch me there!
I can't let myself get attacked by this piece of crap!
Every time I breathe in this mist, my lower half starts to...
It's so hot...
I'm starting to feel really hot down there.
No... Don't come inside!
What are you trying to do now?!
Do it more!
Mess me up more!
More! Move that slimy thing more!
Make me feel good!
Don't focus on that spot so much!
It's starting to feel tingly!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
The things roaming around outside are gone.
We might be able to make it to the
parking lot without any trouble.
Hoichi?
If Touka-chan were somewhere nearby...
T-Touka?
Natsumi!
Hey, Chiaki? Are you actually looking in there?
Ch-Chiaki!
A weapon! Is there anything here I can use as a weapon?
Nii-san? Are you gonna leave me behind?
You're both alive?!
Don't go!
Eh?
Sensei?
O-Onee-chan?
Matsubara-san... Natsumi-san too?
We don't need anyone but nii-san.
Everyone, run!
Natsumi...
You're wasting your time nii-san.
She won't listen to anyone but me.
Ho... ichi...
That guy didn't finish the job?!
You're not completely transformed!
Run! Now's your chance!
Don't be stupid! I can't leave you guys behind!
You have to... We're not humans anymore.
Hurry, Hoichi!
Move! I'm not letting anyone have him!
Go! Hoichi!
Please!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч