It's been a week since the sisters started
living in the Kurokawa household.
Ever since that night, I haven't been
able to look Arisa-chan in the eye.
And as far as Mika-san is concerned...
Sosuke, gimme more.
Why me?
I'm sorry.
I'll bring it right away.
Ever since the incident with the pictures,
I haven't been able to get the
upper hand with Mika-san.
This is Arisa?
And what's more, every night
she comes into my room...
and treats me like a toy.
You're so hard.
Well? Does it feel good?
Sosuke, you gonna cum?
Will this kind of life go on forever?
Hurry up!
Gimme more!
S-Sorry.
Honestly...
I need to do something about this.
Something in there?
Uh, no... Well...
Mika-san...
Gakuen Shimai 2
I'm headed that way.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna stay late at my club today,
so you should go on home without me.
Really?
Well then, I'll have a delicious
dinner waiting for you.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
I guess if things keep up the
way they are, it'll be bad.
Arisa-chan...
Sosuke-kun, are you alone?
Arisa-chan, what's wrong?
I thought we could walk home together.
Arisa-chan...
Super-cute.
Is that your camera?
Uh, yeah.
That's right.
I remember, your lather is a photographer.
Um, while we're on the subject, I have a favor...
Sosuke-kun?
I was just wondering if you wouldn't
mind being my model right here?
A model? Me?
You don't want to?
No, I'd love to! Snap away!
I've never done modeling before,
but I wouldn't mind if you took my picture.
Really?
Well, as long as we're going this far...
Please wear this!
What's that doing in your desk?
It's a photo accessory.
Arisa-chan, look this way.
This might be the first time I've
seen Sosuke-kun look so serious.
He's kind of handsome too.
That's good enough, Arisa-chan.
Thanks.
Sosuke-kun, let me see them!
Wow! You take good pictures.
I've got a good model.
Um, Arisa-chan! This is just...
Sosuke-kun! Let me see that!
But, I mean, it's just...
Sorry! Arisa-chan...
Arisa-chan?
I must admit, when you were taking
my picture, I got a little nervous.
Seeing you up close like this, you're actually...
Um, well...
May I kiss you?
That was my first kiss. I gave it to you.
S-So cute!
My virginity, too...
I could give it to you.
Arisa-chan!
Arisa-chan, I've always liked you too!
Don't do that, Sosuke-kun.
You mustn't squeeze me that hard.
It hurts a bit.
Having them squeezed so
hard makes my body tremble.
Arisa-chan, you're already wet down there.
Please don't say that.
Hearing those words makes me get even wetter!
Arisa-chan, you're kind of a pervert, aren't you?
Yes, there! Clit...
Oh, no!
My boobs and my clit...
I feel it! My clit feels it!
Arisa-chan, which feels better to you?
Gentle or rough?
Rough. I like it rough.
More! Be rougher with me.
Oh, no. Don't! If you go further than that...
I'll... Not so rough! I'll cum right away!
I think I'm losing my mind!
Oh, no. I...
You came already,
Arisa-chan.
I'm sorry.
So, this time, I'll make you feel good, okay?
So this is the real thing.
It looks bigger than when I
saw it in the laundry room.
That's because I'm so excited to be with you.
Oh dear, Sosuke-kun, you sweetie.
Well, it's my first time,
so I'm not sure it I'll be any good at it.
You're good, Arisa-chan! It feels great!
I want you to feel really good, okay, Sosuke-kun?
Oh, no. Not so rough.
Arisa-chan!
No... I'll...
I'm cumming!
I'm sorry. Arisa-chan, I just...
So this is semen.
There's so much.
It's all squishy.
Mika, nice work!
Nice work.
Well, I'm going home.
Be careful!
Bye-bye!
Damn, it's late.
Oh well, time to go home.
Arisa-chan, are you sure?
Yes, Sosuke-kun. This time
I want you inside of me.
Arisa-chan...
I-It hurts!
Arisa-chan, are you okay?
Please, don't stop.
I want to give my virginity to you.
I understand. Then...
It's inside!
Amazing! So this is a man.
So big!
Does it hurt? Are you okay?
I'm okay.
More! Push further inside me, Sosuke-kun!
Arisa-chan, you're so soft.
It feels great!
Me too. It's throbbing deep inside of me!
It feels good! It feels so good!
So this is sex. I can't stand it!
Oh no!
You've gotten bigger, Sosuke-kun!
Arisa-chan...
My pussy is making weird noises.
No, Sosuke-kun,
– I'm about to...
– I'll pull out!
Don't do that. Inside of me.
Cum inside of me, please!
I can't... Arisa-chan... I'm... I'm gonna cum!
Cum! Fill me full of your white seed!
It's cumming! Your cum...
I feel it inside of me!
I'm cumming!
I'm sorry, Arisa-chan. I released inside of you.
That's line.
I felt like I became one with you.
And I'm... so happy!
Hey, Sosuke-kun.
Don't tell Mika about this, okay?
Of course I won't!
Now that you mention it, she's not home yet.
She said she'd be out late at her club.
But even so...
Yeah.
It's sure annoying to pee in this uniform.
Hey! This is the girls bathroom!
Whoa, what's your problem?
What the hell are you doing?
Let me go!
Shut up, bitch!
Hey, that hurt!
Don't put up a fight if you
know what's good for you,
Nanase Mika-chan.
That's right. You don't wanna see this guy angry.
Suck it.
Huh?
I said, suck it.
No! No fucking way!
Just behave yourself already.
What a dream come true!
I never thought I'd be doing the campus idol!
Hey, use your tongue more!
I can't get off with that kind of technique.
She's really tight on this end too.
Oh shit, I'm gonna cum already!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna put it all inside of you!
Me too now!
Yuck! Why did you do that?
Because it's fun, why else?
Now it's my turn.
No!
N-Not in there!
I-It hurts!
Not my ass! No!
Please, stop it! I'm begging you!
Her hand isn't being used yet.
Neither is her mouth.
I knew it. The real thing feels amazing.
Suck it harder!
Don't wimp out on me!
Move your hips more!
I can't last much longer.
It's so tight, I'm gonna cum.
This bitch fucks three guys at once!
No!
How about we try her big sister next?
I approve of that 100%!
What are you guys doing here!?
You're Kurokawa?
Oh shit, he just took our picture!
Mika-san?
You assholes!
I'm taking you and my camera to the police!
Let's get gotta here.
Yeah!
Mika-san!
Mika-san, are you okay?
Sosuke!
There's nothing to worry about anymore.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Why?
I mean, I've been such a bitch to you.
And I...
I don't really mind.
It's who you are.
Idiot! Nerd!
You're just Sosuke. Don't be so cocky!
What's wrong with you, Mika-san?
Hey, will you help me forget it?
I can't go home like this.
I want you to help me forget
everything that just happened.
Please.
Mika-san...
That Mika, I wonder where she is?
Put it in, Sosuke.
So hard!
What's with you, Sosuke?
How can you be this hard already?
I'm sorry, Mika-san!
Oh, well, whatever
I'll let it slide just for today.
Mika-san! That feels great!
Dumbass! You're not the one
who's supposed to be feeling good.
I can't help it.
Then how about this?
Your dick and my pussy sliding together.
Are you feeling it too?
Oh, shut up! Why do you
have to inform me of that?
No!
Idiot! Not my nipples.
Sosuke, not there.
Oh yeah, Mika-san.
Your boobs are very sensitive, aren't they?
Sosuke, in that case... in that case,
will you make me feel even better?
Yes. I'll make you forget everything else!
This feels great.
The tip of your dick is scratching against me.
I'm flattered. This is the first time
you've told me it feels good.
Of course it does. You're so big.
You fit perfectly inside of me.
What is it, Sosuke?
When you're having sex, you look really cute.
Idiot! Don't talk all sweet like that!
Mika-san, I'm gonna...
Y-You're gonna cum?
Then cum with me. Le's cum together.
I'm cumming, Mika-san!
Okay, me too.
Keep it in! Shoot it deep inside of me!
It's flowing inside of me.
Your semen's inside of me.
Mika!
Arisa-chan!
Arisa...
Where were you? I was so worried!
If something had happened to you...
I really was worried about you!
I'm sorry, Arisa.
Several days have passed since then.
After our bodies merged.
Arisa-chan and I became closer and closer.
And I guess this one's the same as usual.
Don't touch me down there!
If you touch me there, I'll...
I can't hold out any longer. I want it!
I want your dick right now!
Then, should I put it in?
Hey, Arisa, about dinner tonight...
M-Mika-san!?
You guys!
Oh, my, Mika-san!
You're certainly home early today!
Mika-san!
I can explain.
There's a perfectly innocent explanation for this!
Arisa, you're stealing all the fun!
It was my job to do that to Sosuke.
Um, Mika-san, what are you talking about?
Perhaps,
you also want to have sex with Sosuke-kun?
S-Something wrong with that?
I see.
Well, since we're all here, why don't you join in?
Arisa-chan, that's not like you.
I'm cool with it. As long as Arisa is.
Why does this have to happen?
What is it, Sosuke? You got a problem with it?
No, not at all.
What a hard dick.
Sosuke-kun, you're throbbing.
Because I'm getting a double job!
Wow, it's all wet.
My pussy too.
Mika-san, you're already really wet.
D-Don't talk. I don't wanna hear it.
You're embarrassing me.
Aw, Mika, you sound so cute right now.
It's getting me excited too!
Arisa, you're putting it in already?
I'm sorry. My pussy is all wet.
I can't hold back anymore.
Does it feel good?
Arisa, does his dick feel good
coining from the bottom?
Yes. I like it best that way.
It's shivering and dancing inside of me.
Yes. Yes!
It feels good.
Sosuke, stick your tongue out more.
Twirl it around inside of me like your dick!
It's gotten bigger inside of me.
This is...
Oh, no. Sosuke-kun...
This is bad. I'm gonna cum.
Not yet, Sosuke!
If you're gonna cum, cum with us.
Come on. Suck harder!
Yes! Yes! I love it! Sosuke,
I love it! I'm almost there!
You too, Mika? Me too. It's hitting my womb.
Arisa-chan! I'm gonna cum...
inside of you, Arisa...
Wh-What are you doing, Mika-san?
Why are you taking pictures?
If you leave me out of the fun again,
I'll show this picture to all of Arisa's fans.
What the hell for?
You're my toy, Sosuke.
You're not allowed to mess around with
other girls without my permission.
Even Arisa.
Got it?
You're impossible!
Aw, Mika, you were always a jealous one.
– That's bad. Give it back!
– No way!
But it looks like things will be a lot of fun here.