If you are to condemn your friend and swear loyalty,
then surely you shall be saved.
What's the matter? Is that all you got?!
There has never been anyone who has seen God as of yet.
But if we love each other, then God is in our house.
What are you afraid of?
God? Divine punishment?
They don't exist.
Those who hurt others keep on going,
and those hurting suffer their whole lives.
There is no such thing as retributive justice in this world.
Bring it on!
I don't need God to watch over me!
Choose the path you walk on your own.
Don't look. Got it?
Don't look at me while I'm insatiable.
This too is a tribulation.
We shall not give in to our deep affections, but
should rather finish reciting the scriptures.
Yes, but Mr. Priest, if you keep playing
with my breasts and pussy like that...
My my, giving up with just this is just plain
embarrassing as the Virgin Saint.
Don't touch me there!
Don't finger me, stop rubbing it onto my clit!
We're just getting started!
My clit is totally getting played with by some thick fingers.
Shoko-chan, I won't give up no matter what happens
to me, until you come to my rescue!
Alright, our Virgin Saint, it is time to atone
for your act of immoral behavior.
You shall atone for your sins by having
them watch you masturbate.
But, doing that... in front of everyone...
...masturbating...
If you can't step up and decide to do it,
then shall I have my students help you out?
G-Got it...
I will...masturbate.
Wow, Virgin Saint, that is so sexy!
I'm being watched.
Everyone can see me.
All kinds of people can totally see my pussy and asshole!
They are making me show them!
Hey, check it out! She's being watched by all of us,
yet she's so into it.
Don't say that! I can't stop!
Even though it's so embarrassing!
Alright, let's give the shameful Virgin Saint a present.
That actually looks good on you, Virgin Saint.
By this, it couldn't possibly be...
This is a mask.
It's perfect for hiding the face, for the shameful and
carnal things that you're about to to do, is it not?
Please look.
Check out the Virgin Saint who's playing with herself
while wearing her own panties on her head!
These have probably caught everyone's attention.
These hidden nipples, that is.
I'll dig them out!
Doing this will get my areolas all worked up.
Working them up and popping out my
hardened nipples with all my might.
There they are!
My huge nipples!
There my nipples go!
My nips are so sensitive once pulled out!
It feels so good to squeeze them!
That's so sexy, Virgin Saint. This is totally perverted.
Sorry. I'm losing my mind.
It feels like I'm going to go crazy if I don't get
a cock in me, even though I'm a Virgin Saint!
Go! Go to where God is!
Transcend to where the paths lead beyond!
Sh-Shoko-chan! I beg you, save me!
I'm going to lose my mind at this rate!
Having already reached such a state,
you still seek that woman's help?
Whatever shall I do with you?
Well...
I... I...
The unwilling Virgin Saint,
shall be taught a lesson in pain.
I'm not a Virgin Saint!
This is... divine punishment!
Give it back! Give me my eye!
Please!
What is this? Why you...
Alright, Virgin Saint Mari, there's
no need to be afraid any longer.
Go and fulfill a greater purpose as a servant of the Lord.
Yes, priest. Thy God's will be done.
Mari! What's gotten into you?
If only you had not resisted the priest, Shoko-chan...
Then this would never have happened.
Since I was your friend, Shoko-chan, I...
...had this happen to me.
Mari...
If you had only stayed by my side, Shoko-chan...
I... I would...
It's okay. Shoot if you want to.
You can shoot me as much as you like
if it will make you feel any better.
It's no use.
I can't shoot someone with such cool resolve.
Sh-Shoko-chan, be more dirty! Just like I had to...
Being made to do something perverted by everyone.
Get all wet and dirty from it!
If you don't, then I will completely lose my way!
Okay. I understand, so...
...cut it out... Mari!
You can do what you want if you hate me that much.
I'll do anything you want me to.
I was waiting for you to say that!
You will give your whole self up.
Your mind, body, and soul.
I'm not to blame!
Damn it! Damn it! You bastard!
I won't forgive you, you son of a bitch!
I so won't lose to a cock!
Well then, let's knock that pride of yours down a peg or two!
It's hard, huh? It hurts, huh?
You can't breathe, and you're getting raped in the mouth!
How does it feel, huh?
That is so hot, Shoko-chan!
Alright now, your spirit should be broken a little.
Damn it! Fuck!
I will not lose to a cock!
Alright, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to squirt out all the sperm
that has been pent up in my balls!
We're just getting started!
We're going to fuck you silly until our balls are drained dry!
You bastard... doing whatever you
like with other people's bodies...
Give me a break!
You damned delinquent virgin, trying
to deceive our Virgin Saint...
We will punish you!
I'm being pounded and fucked silly
on the inside by a thick, fat cock.
Hey now, what happened to your spirit?
Does it feel that good? Huh?!
Stop! Stop!
I will... so not... lose to your pencil dicks...
Come on now, be honest with yourself.
You just love the cock, and just can't get enough of it, can you?!
I won't get hooked on cock to where I can't get enough!
It doesn't feel good at all!
Well, does it feel good? I bet it feels good.
Don't play coy!
The cock is thrusting deep inside of me,
and throbbing.
I'm really starting to lose it!
Damn it! I will so make you pay for this!
Prepare yourselves, you bastards!
Bring it on!
I look forward to seeing how long
you can keep up the tough act.
Big-breasted Delinquent Virgin
And the Lord said.
If someone slaps you on one cheek with a dick,
offer the other cheek to the dick as well.
Shoko-chan, I beg you, help me take care of this.
Come to the cock, my wayward lambs!
Blood and guts, search and destroy!
Give everything you have to God; mind, body, and soul!
I have to punish you for going against God, Shoko-chan!
Ma-Mari?!
I'm going to stick this up your ass, Shoko-chan!
It's your fault, Shoko-chan. All of it.
You're getting ass-raped because you dare to defy God!
That's right! There will be no breaks for you!
What's gotten into you?! Cut it out!
Oh wow.
The cock going in at a different angle
each time it goes in and out.
The cock is pounding and throbbing inside my ass.
And it's messing my internal organs all up!
Your asshole is latching firmly onto my cock,
Shoko-chan! It doesn't want to let go!
S-Stop it, you bastards!
Cut it out! I really am going to be ruined!
Let's wrap things up already, shall we?
Shoko-chan, my cock can release sperm!
I'm going to cum buckets of thick, hot jizz into you!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Wow, check out your asshole, Shoko-chan!
Don't tell me we broke you to the point
where you can't use it anymore?
Don't look! Don't look at me!
D-Damn it!
This is a test of faith handed down to me by God.
I have to do my best to take it on!
If that's the case, then you need to
prepare for it this time around.
I will be putting you to the test!
Exactly... what is it that I should...?
This is another test.
If your faith is true, then surely God will...
grant you salvation.
We're going to fill you up with your
long-awaited hand-jerked semen!
Giving your all to someone else...
is the way to save your soul.
Wait! Why?!
I did exactly what the priest told me to do!
I did it, so why?!
I want to stick my cock into your inverted nipple, Virgin Saint!
Not in my nipple! It will get stretched
out and won't return to normal!
Once I'm done raping your right nipple, I'll do the left as well!
I can't take it! My nipples...
Are going to get deformed!
My inverted nipples are getting fucked like some sex toy!
Hey, which cock feels better, the right or the left?
Both.
Both feel good. My boobs getting fucked silly feels so good!
Bear it, Virgin Saint Mari!
All is for the sake of God!
Priest, please!
I beg of you! Fuck my unmanned pussy!
Fuck me hard!
Your virgin pussy is an important sacrifice unto God!
Let me fuck you here instead.
I'm going to be wrecked with this rod of steel!
My ass is going to be ruined!
You sure have a huge ass. How does your first time feel?
It sure is nice and tight!
It feels like it's reaching my very depths inside
me as it tries to rub deeper and deeper.
My ass will get all stretched out and won't go back to normal!
This lotion has a powerful aphrodisiac in it!
I'm going to have my fill of fun today!
Cut it out! If you keep that up, I'll...
Oh, it's kicking in!
Your blown out pussy is tightening right up!
Damn it! I don't want this...
I don't want it to feel good, but my mind is all hazy!
I'm hot! I'm so horny!
Hey, I'm going to cum inside of you!
Gratefully accept my precious sperm!
Ah, that was refreshing! It felt great, Delinquent Shoko-chan!
D-Damn it!
Th-These bastards have...
Well then, shall I wreck this pussy without hesitation?
Stop it! I just came, and I'm not-
You sure look happy! Did it feel that good when you came?!
Please!
Everyone show me the love of God all together now!
Very good. I have seen your resolve.
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming with a fat juicy cock inside of me!
Cum, my child!
Give your body and soul to God!
This is the love of God.
Everyone's desires are inside of me. This is the greatest.
This is the best!
How do you like that?! Does it feel
good?! Gonna cum already, right?
I'm dying! I'm going to die!
My mind is getting all fucked up, along
with my pussy! My juices are-
If you want more, then become our slave from here on out!
You shall be our cum dumpster!
How do you like my cock?!
Your cock is great!
I'm going to die from having sex!
Y-You... bastard!
I will never forgive you, you hear?!
You're all bark and no bite!
You have already been exposed to all of them a this point.
Do you still believe that you can still
do something in this situation?
I won't forget this!
You dirty son of a bitch! I will win, you bastard!
I so won't lose to some cock!
I can't see you as a woman who would rise
against us after having gone this far.
From then on, we...
were fucked by everyone's cocks. Over and over again...
until we we no longer able to stand.
And our bodies were perpetually covered in semen.
Hey, Shoko-chan...
It seems you couldn't win against the cock after all, huh?
Damn it! Those bastards!
Shoko-chan!
I will never...
give up, you hear?!