The static scenery, the same streets,
with a gloomy mood similar to resignation.
I planned to keep climbing this horrible hill for four years.
That's right.
Until yesterday.
From the old man? That's rare.
He just sends money every month without ever writing a letter.
A cellphone?
This gift from my genius inventor
of a father changed everything.
You otaku scum!
How filthy!
Itou.
Ma'am?
My uniform is dirty. Prepare a change of clothes at once.
Understood, Himeno-sama.
You're to burn this uniform afterward.
Even our dog is cleaner...
C'mon.
Nagisa-chan?
Grab my hand, Satou-kun.
What are you planning, right after tripping me?
What are you talking about?
Never mind. Just hurry up.
I fell for bait like that.
Satou-kun, you pervert!
How could you look under my skirt!?
Fatass did that again? I hope he dies!
Fatass, I told you not to come to school anymore.
You stink, and you're filthy and disgusting.
Just die already,
you worthless piece of trash!
S-Satou-kun?
Kaoruko-sensei?
You know, I think you shouldn't do these indecent things.
Sensei!
Please don't scold Satou-kun.
I think that he just gave in to his urges a little.
Oh, Izushiro-san's so kind.
In that case, respecting Izushiro-san's wishes, I'll forgive you,
but don't do it again.
Yes.
Let's go, Izushiro-san.
Nagisa-chan is great only on the outside.
Yuna-chan.
She's beautiful and gentle. She's just like a goddess.
Are you okay, Satou-kun?
I-I'm all right.
Why are you falling over, Fatass?
Aihara Akira...
Good morning, Sakurasawa-san.
U-Um, good morning, Aihara-kun.
He's Nagisa-chan's lover, and as they
say, birds of a feather flock together.
You should be more careful.
Thank you.
To be honest, I also trip often.
But you're in the rhythmic gymnastics club, right?
I think that I'm good at exercises...
Please keep it a secret from the others.
Yeah.
By the way, Fatass...
You brought the money, right?
I've given him over a million already
It's still not enough, you scum?
You two are really close.
Of course, Satou's as important to me as a wallet.
It hurts!
I see.
I envy him.
Well, I'm going ahead of you.
Yuna-chan?
Fatass, come with me.
I told you not to get close to Yuna!
You're hopeless!
You and Nagisa have the same lecture in the afternoon, right?
I'm gonna go home with Yuna, so
tell Nagisa not to wait for me.
Today I'm finally gonna make Yuna mine.
Aihara, I'm a different man today.
Satou
Serizono
Futoshi-kun's dick!
It's incredible!
My old man's really a genius.
This is exactly what I suggested to her with the hypno-phone.
No! Don't!
Even though I can't... Even though it's unforgivable...
My pussy demands sperm!
It wants to become pregnant with Futoshi-kun's children!
I'm gonna cum!
His sperm is flowing inside me.
I'm definitely gonna get pregnant this way.
I'm gonna get pregnant and have a child without my husband...
With the power of this hypno-phone,
I'm going to teach you all a lesson.
Gakuen Saimin Reido
You Really Are the Worst Kind of Trash
Well then, who should I hypnotize?
Yuna-chan?
Do you want to eat lunch with me?
Yes.
He's really going to do it with Yuna-chan.
That won't do. I have to protect Yuna-chan from Aihara.
So, what did you want with me?
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
I know, I'll be done soon.
Please follow my orders from now on.
Yes,
Satou-kun's a good friend.
But he doesn't have romantic feelings for me.
Yes,
Yuna loves Satou Futoshi-kun.
I really hate Aihara-kun.
I love Futoshi-kun.
I want to give my first kiss and my virginity to Futoshi-kun.
Yes,
I want Futoshi-kun's bodily fluids.
I can't hold myself back and want to
drink Futoshi-kun's drool and juices.
You know, Futoshi-kun...
I'm thirsty.
I want to drink Futoshi-kun's...
Can I?
Of course, I know it's precious,
but I can't bear it anymore.
Please.
Yuna-chan's taking my dick into her mouth.
It's the first time I'm drinking sperm.
This cheese-like stuff is delicious.
I feel like I'm going to be addicted.
Come on, cum.
Hurry up.
Let me drink your sperm.
It's throbbing. You're about to cum, right?
Hurry up.
I can't take it anymore.
Don't be mean. Let me drink it already.
Cum a lot inside my mouth.
It was so delicious.
Your sperm is the best.
I'm glad you like it.
Now I'm gonna teach you what you
should do at home every day.
As long as I have this, I'll be able to fulfill all my desires.
Now, it's time for that woman.
Hm?
That's right. Before the maim dish,
I should prepare for tomorrow.
Akira-kun, you're late!
Fatass?
Are you alone, Mizushiro-san?
If so, what about it, Fatass?
Nothing, I just thought that was convenient.
What?
From now on you can only recognize
me as Akira, Nagisa-chan.
Before me, there is no Fatass, but rather Akira-kun.
I'm "Fatass" for you even under hypnosis, huh?
So this is how you recognize me from the depths of your heart.
No, I haven't kissed or had sex yet.
I decided to do that with the person I'm going to marry.
Yes, when you give me a signal, I'll return to my true self,
but I won't be able to move my body freely.
My body will obey Fatass's orders.
My sexual sensitivity will be doubled,
and when I'm being touched by Fatass, I'll get really horny.
Well then, wake up now.
Akira-kun!
Jeez, Akira-kun...
Don't look yet.
If I'm going to screw her, this way will be more enjoyable.
Okay, I'm dressed.
But you said that you prefer swimsuits.
No!
Aren't we lovers?
Yes, we are.
I'm your lover.
Then, a kiss isn't too much.
Th-That's...
Do you hate me?
Of course not. I love you!
Then...
You stole my first kiss by force. You're awful.
I'm happy to give my first kiss to you.
That was your first kiss as well, Akira-kun? I'm glad.
Since we're past the first ones, come on.
But...
Nagisa-chan...
I love you.
Fatass!?
Thanks for your first kiss, Nagisa-chan.
What are you doing!?
Die, you disgusting piece of trash!
Open your mouth.
Wh-What!? My mouth opened by itself!
What are you doing!?
Stop it, stop!
Before swallowing it, taste it thoroughly with your tongue.
All right, swallow it.
How was it?
Fatass! I'll kill you!
Wh-What!?
My body won't... You, what did you do to me!?
Just a little hypnotism.
What was that just now!?
Let me go!
You're filthy! Someone...
Be quiet.
Even though your heart's filthy,
your body is beautiful.
I can smell something.
You don't have any perfume on, do you?
This is the smell of your sweat, isn't it?
You're sniffing a woman's smell. You pervert!
You're really the worst kind of trash!
This stinks!
Just now, that was the smell of your crotch?
So that's why you usually use strong perfume.
N-No.
My crotch doesn't stink!
You can speak now.
Was that odor your real smell, Nagisa-chan?
Yes, it's my real smell.
I stink down there.
Lately, it's started smelling stronger,
so I've tried to cover it with perfume.
Why did I say that!?
No! My special spot doesn't stink!
I thought of something nice.
Yes,
in response to Fatass's questions, I'm going
to say the opposite of what I think.
But those are my real feelings, my real self.
Oh? Are you feeling this?
Your nipples are erect.
You got horny because someone
ugly touched you, Nagisa-chan.
Maybe you're just a masochist?
Yes, I'm a masochist.
I feel like I'm gonna cum just from your touch.
W-Why!? No, it's not like that!
You're just Fatass.
In that case, if I touch it...
You came just from being touched through your swimsuit.
You're really a perverted masochist.
Yes, I'm a pervert.
I-It's not like that.
In that case, I wonder what'll happen
when I touch you directly?
N-No! Don't touch me! I don't want to feel any better!
Why does it feel this good?
He's just Fatass!
Not there!
If you touch it now, I'm gonna break!
I'm gonna go crazy!
I took it, Futoshi-kun's flute.
Yuna's such a bad girl.
Even though I knew that it was wrong,
when I think about Futoshi-kun, I just can't help myself.
I wish this was Futoshi-kun's dick.
No, Yuna, you silly girl. You're not even Futoshi-kun's lover yet.
If I think about Futoshi-kun while masturbating,
my asshole becomes so sensitive that I
feel like I'll cum from taking a dump!
Yuna is just a pervert like this.
Futoshi-kun's going to hate me.
What are you doing, Yuna? But...  I can't take it anymore!
Futoshi-kun's dick is entering Yuna's ass!
Futoshi-kun's dick feels too good!
It's too thick. My asshole's going to tear!
If you do it so roughly, I'm going to break!
But it feels good...
Yuna's a pervert having her ass-pussy
fucked by her beloved's dick!
Having it shoved in so hard really hurts, but it feels good too!
I'm cumming with my ass-pussy!
No!
I don't care if you scorn me, just don't hate me.
Yuna will do anything!
I don't care if you do it by force, since it's you.
There are so many of Futoshi-kun's dicks.
It feels so good.
Futoshi-kun, Futoshi-kun!
My pussy, my ass,
breasts and mouth...
my whole body belongs to Futoshi-kun.
Futoshi-kun, what now?
You can't get any more of them in there!
Futoshi-kun's dicks are rampaging inside me.
Too good, it feels too good.
I'm going to cum!
It's too violent.
I'm going to break!
I'm so happy. It's good. I'm gonna break!
It's coming in!
There is so much flowing inside Yuna.
It's Futoshi-kun's sperm...
So much of Futoshi-kun's cum...
I'm going to break from happiness.
I'm cumming!
You came again.
You've cum over and over again at the hands of
a disgusting man like me. You really are a slut.
Because I'm a perverted masochist.
N-No,
I'm not a pervert!
Should I take your virginity soon?
Anything but that!
I can't, Nagisa-chan?
All right, I'll give my precious virginity to Fatass.
I-It's not that!
Which is it then?
Women are really complicated.
In that case, show me what you want.
My body's doing it again...
Please take Nagisa's virginity with your thick dick.
No!
You're saying that you want me to take
your virginity of your own free will?
Don't make a woman say a thing like that.
I-It's not that, Fatass!
Fine.
Don't tease me. Stick it in already.
No!
It hurts!
It feels good, Nagisa-chan!
No! It hurts!
Take it out!
You're gonna feel good soon. I ordered you to.
To put it simply, a masochist like you
turns all the pain into pleasure.
Impossible!
Fatass, you liar!
It hurts!
Wh-What is this!?
It hurts! Even though it hurts, it feels good!
But...
I made a suggestion so that pain increases your
pleasure, but it's not like the pain is gone, right?
You're cruel!
Then when it hurts, I'm gonna...
It hurts, but it feels good!
What's that!?
I'm gonna make you feel even better.
Your dick's deep in my vagina.
My dick is big, so it reaches all the way into your womb.
My womb's gonna tear!
It feels good when Fatass screws my womb!
It hurts!
This is the first time I've felt so good!
It hurts! It hurts!
I'll die! I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die from having
my womb screwed during my first time!
I'm gonna cum, Nagisa-chan.
No! Don't cum inside me!
I'll get pregnant!
I don't want to get impregnated by Fatass!
No!
He's filled my womb directly with his sperm!
Even thought it's a safe day, I'm going
to get pregnant if his cums this much!
I'm gonna get pregnant with fatass's child!
There's more.
If you do that anymore, my womb will break.
I'll get pregnant!
If your womb breaks, you wouldn't have
to worry about pregnancy, would you?
No!
I can't take it anymore!
If he keeps doing this to me, I'll fall
in love with him! I don't want that!
Don't! Stop it!
I can't think of anything anymore!
My womb hurts!
I'm gonna die from the pain and pleasure!
I come! My pussy come!
I'm gonna cum because of the pain!
My pussy's cummmg!
My pussy is being screwed all the
way to the womb! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
It's coming inside! Fatass's stinking sperm is flowing in!
I gave a new suggestion to Nagisa-chan.
I have been impregnated by fatass,
but an abortion woul be impossible.
Even if I menstruate during the pregnancy, it's nothing unusual.
If I don't drink Fatass's sperm every day,
and if I don't have sex, the stench won't go away.
If I don't do that, Akira-kun will hate me.
With this, Nagisa-chan and Yuna-chan are done for.
I hope Himeno's training is going well, too.
This is a pack I picked up from in front of the Anime Club.
I masturbate with this every evening.
For some reason, I'm entranced by the
smell of Satou-san's handkerchief,
so I've made it my own.
Well then, I wonder how long until this woman is ready.
No! Stop it!
You ugly plebeian, you won't get away with this!
What? That thing roaming inside me just got even thicker!
Don't tell me... You can't do that!
You can't do that!
No!
No...
To think that I'd cum because that brute came inside me.
You're going to cum more? No, I don't want it!
If you cum any more, I'll really become pregnant!
Not good! I can't calm down with just that.
If that lowly Sotou brutally raped me, like in this book,
and if I became pregnant because he
came inside me against my will...
No, it's so filthy!
But just from imagining it, I can't hold myself back.