No!
Stop it!
lt hurts!
No... Stop it!
l'm going to climax!
What? Shiori?
Don't raise your voice.
But...
Hey, is that really true?
They said she got a serious fever and had to be hospitalized.
Yeah...
But don't you find that strange?
l mean she didn't even have a cold to begin with.
You're right, but that's not...
Then why won't they tell us where she's hospitalized?
They told us we don't need to go see her.
Even the teachers are acting strange.
...telling us to study by ourselves and they're holding staff meetings all the time.
l'm certain that something happened.
But you just assume...
...that Shiori got raped.
l don't want to believe it either.
But they say there's no smoke without fire, so...
lt would be terrible if it were true...
l will never accept this!
But that's just a rumor, right?
That's why we have to investigate!
lnvestigate?
You mean us?
That's up to the school and the police.
This isn't like you, Mia.
lf there really is a rapist on the loose...
...then we should find him and punish him.
Punish him?
That's right.
By using your powers.
We have to get back at him.
lt's just not fair to Shiori.
Don't be stupid!
Listen up.
People's thoughts are much stronger than you can imagine.
What's scarier than a spirit that wanders around after death in regret...
...is the heart of a living human being.
So you shouldn't be thoughtless and talk about getting revenge.
l'm sorry.
Sorry about that.
Forget about what l said.
lt's just that l remembered what happened at my previous school...
At your previous school?
Well, l'll tell you about it someday...
But keep this in mind.
Even if it's nice and pretty, it can become cold and ugly.
That's what a human heart is.
lnterview with the Teachers (3)
This time around, we'll interview Assistant Principal Yasaka.
''Students are my treasure''
What do you mean your students are your treasure?
He's all talk.
You're still not satisfied?
Over the rape, that is.
We discussed this.
Even if it were true, it's just wrong to print the article.
lt's not nice to Shiori.
l know that.
l know, but... it just feels weird.
l heard rumors that it might be one of our students.
They're just saying that for fun.
But what if it were true?
This guy would be coming to school pretending to be innocent!
lf we don't do anything right now, then he just might do it again!
But do you want to be exposed to public ridicule?
We're the ones on the losing end all the time.
Ayaka!
Bathroom.
Who's there?
ls anybody there?
Ayaka...
You're doing this, right, Ayaka?
Stop playing these games...
Ayaka?
No!
Help me!
What the hell are you doing?
Come back here!
Hey, come back here!
Where did he go?
Maybe he's hiding somewhere.
Where would he hide?
Then how come we don't see him?
He disappeared?
l heard that the girls for the school newspaper were attacked.
l know. l know.
Ayaka and Midori, right?
l heard Shiori from class A was raped by the same guy.
ls the rapist from one of our classes?
He's good.
Who is he?
Study Time
Huh?
The rapist just disappeared?
No way!
l heard it's true.
There's an eyewitness too.
l heard it from a guy on the baseball team.
l'm sure it's true.
Follow-up report on the rapist who disappeared.
l heard something really interesting.
Earthbound spirit?
There was a male student who hung himself...
...in the student council room several years ago.
So you think this earthbound spirit is the rapist who disappeared?
Right.
Chief...
Yeah.
lt's worth checking out.
Student Council Room
Well, Mia?
l don't feel any spiritual energy...
No spirit?
lf this earthbound spirit is possessing the school...
...then maybe he's wandering around the school grounds.
Well, we don't have to get the results in a hurry.
These spirits love the dark.
Let's just wait till it gets dark.
Were there any incidents like this before?
Like people witnessing ghosts.
l've never heard of any...
l haven't heard of any rumors like that at all either.
This sounds kind of fishy.
l mean if you think about it, it's kind of odd...
...that a spirit of a student who committed suicide several years ago...
...would start acting up now.
We can't find any spiritual energy in the area...
Well, l'm kind of happy about that...
Chief.
l guess it was just a rumor after all.
Are you cold?
lt's starting to get a bit chilly in here...
You're right...
This must be...
What's wrong?
lf there's a strange phenomenon, they say that the temperature drops.
Foxy...
He's coming!
Rin, hyo, tou, sha, kai, jin, retsu, zai, zen!
Mia...
Chief...
Mia!
Chief!
l'm okay...
Thanks a lot.
l owe you one.
That was one powerful spirit.
No...
lt was more than that.
l see...
Even with Reina's contacts, we can't find out where Shiori's hospitalized...
Shiori is a classmate of ours.
So l thought we could get more details about the attack...
l guess we'll just have to keep taking risks.
We'll have to ask the two girls of the school newspaper that were attacked.
Huh?
l thought you were going to the club...
Yeah, well, the chief is in the student council room.
Why does he like this place so much?
This undulation...
What's wrong, Mia?
Who's the guy in the middle?
That's Kitagawa. The student council head...
l mean the former head.
Former?
Kitagawa stopped coming to school all of a sudden.
Then he stayed home all the time.
And as a result, he was no longer the head of the student council.
Why did he stop coming to school?
l really don't know why...
lt's not like he was being bullied...
He was always getting good grades.
We don't want any more people to suffer.
So please tell us the details.
l'm telling you l don't have anything to say!
Leave!
Midori!
Please leave!
Maybe he reminded you of someone.
Am l right?
Midori!
l'm scared...
l'm really scared!
l'll protect you.
Don't worry, Midori.
Mia will protect you.
l want you to trust her.
Kitagawa is responsible?
But that wasn't Kitagawa.
lt didn't look human at all.
Yeah, you're right.
That was definitely a spirit.
Kitagawa's doppelganger.
Doppelganger?
ls there anyone that knew Kitagawa very well?
Shimizu might know something.
Shimizu?
Miyu Shimizu.
She was the vice-chair of the student council.
Plus, l think she was going out with Kitagawa at the time...
l don't know if we were going out...
You weren't?
l met Kitagawa three years ago...
l confessed to him three years ago on Christmas eve.
Right where we stand...
Kitagawa said he liked me too...
So...
But you know, we never even kissed...
Even though you were going out for three years?
You two went out on dates, right?
l even went over to his place one time.
Even then...
He wouldn't even hold my hand.
Are you serious?
l guess he was a late bloomer.
That's just too much.
With a girl like Shimizu in front of him...
What a waste...
Yoshikawa!
lt's ok.
l was starting to feel uneasy as well...
Then on the last day of the second semester...
l told him l wanted to break up.
l didn't really want to break up with him...
l guess l wanted to know how he felt...
lf he was a late bloomer, then l wanted him to be more outgoing...
But...
You broke up with him in the student council room?
Yes...
l see.
So that's why the spirit likes that place...
Kitagawa thought he was really dumped by you.
He stopped coming to school, so l stopped by his house.
But he wouldn't come out of his room...
l guess he was really suffering from a broken heart.
No!
lt's not that easy!
l'm guessing Kitagawa had sexual desires.
More than the average person.
But he couldn't even touch the girl he loved.
So he felt hopeless.
Then she wanted to break up with him...
lt would've been good if he just withdrew into his own shell...
He was hopeless and full of regret.
And those feelings came out in a distorted shape.
He couldn't satisfy his sexual desires...
...and that became his doppelganger.
What's scary is the heart of a living human being...
You heard about the rapist who disappeared, right?
Yeah...
Kitagawa's doppelganger is responsible for all that.
What?
Miyu, l'll get right to the point.
How do you feel now?
Do you still like Kitagawa?
l do.
Then we can make the doppelganger disappear.
How?
We just have to let Kitagawa satisfy his desires.
l was expecting you.
Please take good care of him.
You can count on me.
l'll get Kitagawa out of his room.
l promise.
Open this door, Kitagawa!
lt's me, Kitagawa.
Please open the door.
Let's talk.
Hey, Kitagawa!
Kitagawa!
Where's his mother?
She said she'll stay at some busines hotel with her husband tonight...
How is he?
Anyway, we have to make him open the door...
Open this door, Kitagawa!
Kitagawa!
l wasn't going to break up with you.
So please open the door.
Will you listen to what l have to say?
What's wrong?
l thought l heard Mia's scream...
Chief...
Kumi, Shimizu.
Step aside!
Stop it...
Ready...
Kitagawa!
l'm sorry for saying we should break up.
l really didn't mean it.
l still like you.
lt's true...
So please wake up! Please Kitagawa!
Rin, hyo, tou, sha, kai, jin, retsu, zai, zen!
You won't get away this time.
Hey, Kitagawa!
Kitagawa!
Snap out of it, Kitagawa!
Kitagawa...
Miyu...
You're back, Kitagawa!
You know who l am, right?
Yeah...
Kitagawa!
Now we'll just leave the rest to Shimizu.
Let's go back to school.
Okay.
Evil spirit, disperse!
Kaman!
Looks like Kitagawa was able to satisfy his desires...
You look beautiful.
Really?
Yeah...
No...
Kitagawa...
Ready?
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Yeah... Keep going...
Miyu!
Sorry...
lt felt good.
Really?
Really.
Hey, look.
Kitagawa and Shimizu.
Looks like they're madly in love.
l'm jealous...
l want a boyfriend too!