Walking along with those bright and cheerful faces...
Damn.
Excellent Academy.
An international school for girls.
A school attended by the upper class elite,
and the big head of the school, are these two.
Or should I say, the father of Kanako and Hina.
That same man,
is also my biological father,
and is the man that I've sworn my
entire life to take revenge against.
I don't want to look at what happened to my life.
But, I simply must.
It was a time when I was still young.
A time when my mother was still alive.
The memory conjures the image of my mother's
thin and sickly figure, and our impoverished life.
My father's nowhere to be seen.
We can't meet him due to his important work,
but he'll someday come for us.
The school which my father managed soon became famous,
and was advertised as a world class
prestigious academic institution.
That's the only memory I have of him.
One day,
mother took me, and together we
went to the place my father was.
He cannot meet with you.
I just need to see him once; please, I beg of you!
At that time, my younger self finally understood.
That my father had already taken off with another woman.
That we were forsaken and thrown away long ago.
My mother eventually died from over exhaustion.
I then lived off a very frugal life without proper education.
I lived my life on the lowest rung of the social ladder.
But even from down here,
I can see my old man being hailed as the idealistic educator.
I eventually swore to myself this.
That I will destroy every single thing,
that he took in exchange for throwing us away.
However, I don't have the power to do that.
The school's security is very tight,
and I can't even get close to one of his daughters.
If only I had the power...
I need something absolute.
Something that I can use to finally fulfill my
revenge without anyone getting m my way.
So, do you need that kind of power?
Oh, forgive me if I startled you.
That doesn't matter, right?
Here.
This is a device that can stop time.
Just by pressing this switch,
You can stop the flow of time around you.
Stop time?
What a load of bull.
That just can't be tru-
What in the world is this?
See? It stopped, right?
Time, I mean.
Original Animation Disc
A device that can stop time...
I can't possibly believe it.
But, I've seen it with my own eyes.
No way.
It's up to you on how you use its power.
I'm looking forward to seeing something very entertaining.
A time freezing device.
I shall confirm my hypothesis first,
by testing if it really works or not.
I tested it on various objects and things
to see if time really stops around them.
I also tried to see if there are any risks involved in using it.
And then I finally understood.
That this power is very real.
I don't care how, or why it was given
to me, or even where it came from.
If I have this power,
I can finally exact my revenge!
Just you wait, my shitty dad.
I'm going to crush all that is dear to you.
So, getting used to the school already?
Jeez, how many times have you asked
me that already, Nee-chan?
I'm not a kid anymore.
Oh, but you're still Hina no matter what happens.
My cute little sister.
Even Excellent Academy's top security seems
to be powerless against this time freeze.
I'll destroy everything,
All things that are precious to that dirtbag.
I'll start with this Academy.
I've been wanting to meet you, Kanako, Hina.
Now, who shall I deal with first?
How about the younger one?
What a nice smell.
Something bad will surely happen if they
were to be toyed with by someone.
... or not.
But you just can't help but want to touch them.
And I don't really care if I get into trouble for this.
That is, if I really get into trouble.
They're quite soft.
They're a bit smaller compared to her older sister,
but they still have a lot of room to grow.
This time freeze thing sure is the best.
Now then, why don't we get a bit more daring here.
Now, this looks like a cute bra.
But I guess it suits the childish Hina.
I wonder if some guy already fondled them.
Probably not.
Wh-Who are you?
No!
Don't try to struggle, Hina.
How do you know my name?
No need to be so repulsed by me.
I came all the way here just to rape you, you know.
No, no, no...
Let me go...
Onee-chan...!
It's no use, Hina,
Your Onee-chan won't be able to save you.
What? No way... Onee-chan!
Stop...
Don't fondle my breasts... no...
No...
P-Please...
I don't want this...
Getting your nipples hard like this...
What are you saying?
Seems you're getting quite in the mood.
What are you trying to say?
Let me go!
It feels gross!
Not the nipples, please don't lick my nipples!
Despite that, your expression is quite amazing.
Why don't we adjust things a little bit here?
This is great, just the best.
This is our remembrance photo.
Your dad will surely be surprised,
once he sees you like this.
Your pussy still reeks of piss.
But, that's what makes it attractive, I guess.
I probably won't be able to savor this well if she's not frozen.
Whoa, you're really drenched there already.
I'm getting quite aroused already.
Here, Hina, have some of your favorite dick.
"Oh no, it looks so big and scary!"
How about saying something along those lines, eh?
Wow, this is good.
I wonder how her first blowjob felt.
Hina-chan, I'll be sure to...
... violate your mouth completely with my dick!
Looks like we still lack some stimulation.
It'd be better if I could secrete a bit
more, but I guess this will do.
Oh yeah, this is great!
Suck it in properly, I'm the only one moving here.
Alright.
Why don't we take another remembrance
photo of your blowjob this time.
But, she'd probably burst into tears
once I turn time back to normal.
Oh well.
Hey, surprised, eh?
Whoopsie, don't let it spill now.
Okay, keep at it like that.
I'm snapping this moment when you're sucking my dick.
Just keep on sucking it firmly.
I'm about to release lots of my delicious
cum milk inside your mouth.
Wow, actually swallowing it already,
that's really welcoming of you.
Your reaction after drinking cum for the first time,
how marvelous.
Such a nice expression.
Now, stay that way for a bit.
I'll be freezing time again.
Thank you, Hina-chan.
That felt really good.
You're next, Kanako.
Though, I never though you'd mature so well.
A real beauty, and on top of that,
a student council president that is admired by everybody.
More than enough reason to rape you.
It's really soft.
Very soft and tender.
I'm now looking forward to how she moans.
I wonder how she'll react once she suddenly finds out
that she was being treated like a toy all this time?
Let's see and find out.
Wh-What?
Who are you?!
It looks like we haven't heard you shout
or let out your voice for a quite a while.
Now Hina's in a complete mess because of that.
Wh-What are you...?
You don't know what happened to her?
Oh, it seems you really don't.
Just what are you...?
Then I shall make you understand.
Now then,
she's back to being vulnerable,
there!
As expected, her breasts are a lot bigger than Hina's.
It's clear that her breasts are quite sensitive.
Let's see how you're doing down here.
Wow, what a sight.
You look really elegant today, Miss President.
This smell of a young girl is great.
Alright, let's now see how it tastes.
This indeed is a virgin's taste.
Oh, I have a good idea.
Here it goes.
Oh crap.
I'm about to cum already just by moving a bit.
But, I'm still going to move, though.
Good for you, Kanako.
Now you've finally become an adult.
I want everyone to witness,
this magnificent form of yours.
Wh-What is this?
It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts!
Congratulations on losing your virginity.
This is where you'll finally become a woman.
I've uploaded it on my blog already.
It hurts... stop, let go of me!
Please stop!
No can do, lady,
I can't just stop doing something this good.
No, what are you trying to do?
Stop this at once!
Oh, please don't say that.
This an important day to remember.
Here, put a smile on your face.
Why... why did this happen?
What did I just do?
That's great.
Be more afraid.
Let the terror seep in more!
Yes, that's the expression I want.
My dick's really lively now!
Why am I being violated by this guy...?
Why, why?
You're asking why you're getting so horny now?
That's because your body has now become
a sex-loving erotic maniac!
No, that's not true.
That's not true!
I don't want it like this.
No, no...
Wow, it's really gripping me tightly.
All my careful planning was totally worth it.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
It's your first time being impregnated.
It's overflowing.
What a shameful sister you are, doing this in front of Hina.
Well, I'm about to cum inside her too, though.
W-Wait, don't you...!
Just stay where you are.
The next thing that you'll see is the
moment Hina loses her virginity.
Hina's insides feel a bit more tight.
Ouch, I think that hurt.
But now you're finally a woman just like your Onee-chan.
Alright, let's see how Hina reacts.
What is this?
So, how does it feel to lose your virginity, Hina-chan?
It hurts, it hurts!
No, no!
It's okay, it'll feel good soon enough.
Why do I have to...?
I'm not surprised that you're confused.
Still, it's quite sad, because this is very real.
As for me, I'm enjoying every second of this.
Pull it, pull it out.
No...!
Looks like your pussy and my dick are quite compatible.
Your insides are getting sloppily wet as I fuck you.
No way...
Let's go for the final stretch!
I'm cumming, Hina-chan!
No, no, no...!
Onee-chan, Onee-chan!
Congratulations, Hina.
Now let's have your Onee-chan see your big debut.
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan!
Hina... why?
Onee-chan...
Hina...
My oh my, what a nice day for you to
show your precious sisterly love.
I'll have you two raped together for one last time.
But...
Having time freeze like this feels like you've become a sex doll.
I'm going to drown you in ecstasy to the point that you
can no longer have time to worry about your sister!
Alright then,
let's now see how she'll react when she realizes once
again that she's being raped in front of her sister.
Just when did, something start welling up...
Many things already happened, you see.
We're currently in the middle of enjoying this.
Feels good, right?
Stop... Hina is...
Are you worried about her?
Look.
Hina!
Run, run!
Why isn't she responding?
Just what did you do to her?
Who knows, I have no idea.
Maybe she's too shocked from seeing her Own Onee-chan
become horny while being raped by some unknown guy.
Why..?
My sister is...
I don't care what happens to me, just...
Violate me however you want, but please,
just don't do this to my sister!
My, how valiant.
But... I cannot grant your request.
Wait!
Not to Hina, please, not to her...!
That's too bad.
I really want to see you suffer.
Now that you've begged me not to,
I just can't resist myself from raping her anymore.
Looks like you're really getting horny from this, Hina-chan!
And you were just a virgin earlier!
You're actually quite the pervert.
This is interesting.
This time freezing thing is fun!
I can imagine all the fun things I'm
going to have with it from now on!
Hello there, Hina-chan.
Now I've raped you in front of your Onee-chan.
Again... why...?
Why...?
Please let me be already.
Oh, and why should I?
You were loving it earlier, right?
N-No, I'm not...
I'm not...
That's not true.
My oh my.
I don't really like lies.
Your pussy doesn't look like it's not getting horny!
No, please don't...
Please...
Any more and...
Here, let your Onee-chan hear your cute moans more!
No, no... stop...
Onee-chan, save me, save me...
Onee-chan!
Why aren't you responding?
Why do we have to suffer like this?
I really wonder why.
How about thinking about it for a good while?
Here, I'm going to take you straight to heaven shortly!
Your body sure is honest.
Even if you say you don't like it,
your pussy just craves for my dick
as it tries to squeeze it in tighter.
See? My dick feels great, right?
Oh? Are you about to cum already?
L-Let me be already...
It's going to...
I-I don't want to...
Please, let me be...!
Then...
I'm going to completely make you cum!
Oh wow, oh wow...
It's coming... I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Whoa, she's really cumming!
The way you came was just amazing, Hina.
Now then.
You're next, Kanako.
I'll be sure to make you cum as well!
You seem to be getting horny as well.
I'm going to mold your body to my liking!
I think now is a good time.
Huh... what just happened to me...?
Nothing really.
But did you actually cum?
Jeez, you two sisters sure are a pair of bitches.
Hi-Hina! Hina!
I'm going to make you cum just like her right now!
No, no...
Pull It out!
Even if you say that, your body seems to really feel it right now.
No way... I'm not getting horny.
That can't be...
No, no!
The way it wraps around my dick...
The sensation of it squeezing me is the best I've ever felt!
Your slutty pussy is really top notch!
Don't say that!
It's making really sloppy sounds.
Your pussy is really going ecstatic.
It's not... no...
I'm going to cum inside you now.
Cum hard!
If you keep on pushing hard like that...
It's really squeezing me.
The hot thing is really pumping inside me.
That was really fun... you two.
Excuse me.
Prez, are you...
Sensei, sensei!