If you promise to let go of your friends
and be faithful to our God,
you can probably be saved.
What's wrong? Can't fight anymore?
No one has seen God yet.
However, if we love each other, God shall live within us.
What are you afraid of?
God? Punishment?
They don't exist.
Those who hurt will continue living happily.
And those who were hurt, will suffer forever.
There is no such thing as karma in this world.
Repent your sinful actions.
I don't need God's meddling.
I'll decide how I will live.
School
The big tit rebel girl reduced to a playmate
Scapegoat
Brown devil invaded by while & sinful activities
Don't look at me.
Everyone, please don't look when I'm moaning.
This is another test for you.
You must read the scriptures out loud while
being fondled, without giving into us.
Yes, but bishop...
If you touch my tits and pussy like that...
My goodness.
What a shame that a supposedly holy
woman like yourself gives in so fast.
Please don't rub my clit like how you stroke your cock.
Please stop.
How's that? Huh?
This is just the beginning.
My clit-cock's being touched by your thick fingers.
Shoko-chan, I will never give in until you come and help me...
I will do my best not to cum, whatever they do to me.
Now, holy woman, you must perform
a sinful activity. Masturbate.
By letting others see you do so...
Show them the gravity of your sins.
I can't masturbate...
In front of everyone.
If you cannot make up your mind...
Shall I let the students help you then?
I und...
I understand.
I'll masturbate.
Wow, you're such a dirty holy woman.
Everyone is looking at me.
My pussy, asshole and everything else is exposed.
Everyone is staring.
Hey look, we're watching her touch
herself but she doesn't even care.
Don't say that.
I can't stop myself.
Even though I'm so embarrassed.
No.
Well then, let me give a present to this sinful holy woman.
It looks really good on you.
Holy woman.
This can't be...
That's a mask to hide your embarrassed face.
It is perfect for pleasing those men, isn't it?
Look at me please.
While wearing my panties on my face...
Look at a holy woman masturbate.
Maybe everyone is curious.
I'm going to dig into my hard nipples,
buried in my areola.
I'm touching my areola-pussy like this.
I'm touching them up real well,
until my nipples get hard.
When I pull very hard...
Now they're exposed...
My long nipples.
They're coming out...
They've just come out and they're very sensitive.
It feels so good every time they get hard.
You're nasty, holy woman.
You're completely perverted.
Mari...
I can't help but touch my tits,
even though I'm a holy woman.
I think I'm going to go crazy.
Cum.
Reach the world where there is overwhelming light.
Shoko-chan, please help me.
I'm going to go crazy if I keep doing this.
I can't believe you're still seeking help from that woman.
It's outrageous.
But...
I-I am...
For a dumb holy woman like yourself...
I need to teach you a lesson by hurting you.
I'm not holy... I'm not a holy woman.
This is divine punishment.
Give it back. My eye.
– Please.
– Mari...
You...
Now, Saint Mari...
There's nothing to be afraid of.
You must complete this great task as God's apostle.
Yes, bishop.
I will do as God wishes.
Mari...
What happened to you?
If you hadn't disobeyed God...
This would never have happened.
We were friends, Shoko-chan.
I had to go through all this.
Mari...
If you had stayed by my side...
I... I wouldn't have become like this.
Go on, shoot me.
If that makes you feel better, I'll take it.
My eye.
Don't act so cool.
Shoko-chan.
You should also become dirty, just like I did...
Everyone molested me.
You should get wet and squirt too.
Otherwise, my soul will wander forever.
Alright.
I get it.
Please stop.
Mari...
if you hate me that much, I'll do as you say.
I'll do anything.
I was waiting for you to say that.
You must sacrifice everything.
Sacrifice your body and soul.
I'm not to blame.
Shit. Damn it!
You bastard.
I won't forgive you.
I'll never be defeated by a penis.
Even so...
I'll destroy your pride for you.
Isn't it hard, not being able to breathe?
You're helpless while being fucked in the mouth.
I can only imagine what that feels like!
Shoko-chan, you're so cute.
Now, I suppose it's time.
Shit...
Damn it!
I won't be defeated by this cock.
I'm going to cum.
I'm gonna shoot my load of spunk in one go.
I'm not done yet.
We won't stop until all of our balls have been drained.
You're using my body however you want...
Give me a fucking break.
You rebel girl, you drove our holy woman into madness.
We'll punish you.
You keep pounding my pussy with your hard cock!
Hey, what happened to your war cry from earlier?
Does it feel that good now?
Stop, stop!
I won't be defeated by your pathetic cocks.
Hey, be honest. You like this, don't you?
I've been fucked so many times...
I don't feel anything any more.
Do you like it? You like it, don't you?
Don't be stubborn!
Your cock is pounding me so deep.
I'm gonna cum.
Goddammit.
You'll pay for this.
Mark my words.
Fine.
I'm curious as to how long you can keep up that attitude.
God says this.
If you're slapped on your right cheek with a cock...
you must be slapped on your left cheek with a cock too.
Shoko-chan, please, let's serve him together.
Wander, you little sheep.
Kneel before my cock.
Holy soldiers, search and destroy.
You must sacrifice everything.
Your body and your soul, to God.
You disobeyed God, Shoko-chan.
I must punish you.
Mari...
Let me stick this cock in your ass-pussy.
It's all your fault, Shoko-chan.
If you hadn't been stubborn...
your ass-pussy wouldn't have been fucked.
Yes, there is no time to rest.
What's happening? Stop.
Wow, every time the cock goes in, my insides get peeled out.
My asshole is all stretched out from your cock.
I feel my insides getting fucked real hard.
Shoko-chan's asshole feels so tight around my cock.
It just isn't letting my cock go.
You guys, stop. I'm going to break!
It's time for the final attack.
Shoko-chan, my cock can produce cum too.
I'll cum my hot juices deep inside your ass.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Wow, Shoko-chan, your asshole is completely filled.
I bet your insides are all fucked up.
Don't look...
Don't look at me.
Damn it.
This is a test that God has given us.
We must do our very best.
Then...
I'll put your ambition to the test.
What...
What are we supposed to do?
This is yet another test.
If your faith is real...
God will help you.
Wait for us, we'll give you lots of cum.
To give to others...
That is what will save your soul.
Wait...
Why is this happening?
I did as you told me, bishop.
Why? I did everything right.
I've always wanted to fuck your nipple.
Please, not my nipple.
It'll stretch and won't go back.
If I fuck your right nipple-pussy, I must fuck the left one too.
I can't! I just can't!
I'll... obey you.
You're fucking my nipple as if it's my pussy.
You're fucking it just like you would a sex toy.
Which cock do you like, right or left?
Both...
I like both.
I love my nipples getting fucked.
You must endure, Saint Mari.
This is all for God.
Bishop...
Please.
Please touch and fuck my pussy too.
Please fuck me hard.
Your virgin pussy shall remain for God.
I'll just fuck your ass instead.
My ass.
My ass is going to break.
My ass will break open!
Your ass is so tight and big.
I can't believe it's your first time!
It feels like you're digging into my asshole.
My ass is being stretched out and
I don't know if it'll ever go back.
This lotion has a lot of beauty-enhancing effects.
I'm going to have so much fun today.
Stop!
If you keep going, I will...
Oh, it's working so well!
Your stretched out pussy is still tight around my cock.
Fuck, I don't want to feel this...
I don't want to feel this but yet, your
cock feels so hot and good right now!
I'm gonna cum inside you!
Take all of my cum and be grateful for it!
That was real good, Rebel Shoko-chan.
God dammit...
These bastards...
I'll fuck you next then.
Stop! I just came, I'm not ready yet!
You're still moaning pretty loud. You like it that much, huh?
Please...
Please give me God's love, all at once.
Okay, I understand you're ready for this.
I'm gonna cum!
Your big, thick cock is fucking me so hard. I'm going to cum!
Go on, give your body and soul to God.
I can feel God and everyone's love inside me.
This is amazing...
So good!
How's this? How's my cock inside you?
I'm gonna die!
My brain is getting messed up together with my pussy.
If you want more of this, become our servant forever!
You're the whore for our lust!
How's this cock that you want so much?
I love your penis. I love having sex with you!
You... Bastard...
I'll never forgive you.
Stop talking.
You're flaunting such a sinful body.
Things will not get better for you.
Remember this...
You bastard.
I will win, bastard.
I'll never be defeated by a cock.
If this was too much, don't disobey us next time.
After that...
We were fucked by everyone's cocks...
So many times...
Until we couldn't get up.
Our bodies were all stick with cum.
Hey, Shoko-chan. We couldn't win
with those peruses, could we?
Those bastards.
Tranlator: Vaughan
Translator Check: Jimaku-Danshaku
Timing: v1toush
Typesetting: Ephemere
Editor: Punk4real