Really. How did you find out about it?
On the lnternet.
They had instructions as well as the spells.
Really?
Now, Reina and Kumi.
Place your fingers...
Ready?
We'll begin.
Do it, do it!
Spirit, spirit...
lf you can hear me, please come...
Don't do it!
lf you try to summon the spirit for fun...
...you're going to be possessed.
Possessed?
Who the hell are you supposed to be?
You mean by a fox?
No way.
l'm not kidding!
lt's true.
l'm scared.
Mind your own business!
Fine.
Then do whatever you want!
Who is that?
l don't know what she's talking about.
Maybe she wanted to join us.
She seemed like a paranormal otaku.
Do you know her?
Remember?
She's the one in class C who transferred here last month.
l believe her name was Mia Tsunoda.
She's a third year student who created this paranormal club or something.
Very odd girl.
Now let's start over.
What? We're doing it again? She said we'll be possessed...
Stop messing around!
ls it that funny to make fun of me?
You shouldn't take it seriously.
lt's just a love fortune.
This isn't good, you two. We shouldn't just quit when we're in the middle of this.
After we summon the spirit, we should say thank you and make it go away.
Thank you?
After being told that l'm hated... how could l even thank this spirit?
Mari...
The coin...
What?
l...
...won't...
...for...
...give.
l won't forgive?
What does this mean?
The coin is moving on its own!
What's going on?
Are you serious?
You're okay with 10,000 yen?
Yeah.
l'll be waiting on the pedestrian overpass in front of the station.
You'll know it's me...
...with the red umbrella.
Excuse me...
Are you Mari?
Yes...
l'm coming...
l'm coming too...
Yes!
lt's getting hard again.
Mari...
Yes...
Mari didn't come today either.
She won't even answer her cell. l wonder what she's doing...
ls it because of that spirit?
What?
l mean Mari stopped coming to school after that day...
...and she was acting weird on the way home.
l'm guessing she's doing well with the college student from her workplace.
They're probably having lots of fun right now.
l hope you're right...
You shouldn't worry too much.
Hey, Reina.
Do you want to stop by Mari's place later just in case?
Ma'am!
Kumi!
ls something wrong?
Mari...
l heard Mari is severely injured!
What?
Prostitution?
Yes...
No...
Not my Mari...
lt looks like a man cut her on the face at the hotel.
But why?
We're going to investigate this in more detail, but...
According to the man's testimony, Mari was being persistent.
So he got scared and cut her on sudden impulse...
Yes...
More...
What are you doing?
Stop!
Stop...
Mari, stop it!
Mari!
Mari, Mari, Mari!
Mari! Mari!
Hello?
Don't ''hello'' me.
Where are you right now?
Where...
You disappeared from the hospital all of a sudden.
l was worried about you!
l tried calling your cell, but you wouldn't pick up.
l was looking all over for you!
What?
Hello?
Are you listening to me, Kumi?
l'll call you back later!
Thanks for waiting...
No!
Kumi?
You're late.
What was l doing there?
l can't remember...
Kumi?
lf you try to summon the spirit for fun...
...you're going to be possessed.
Chief!
Huh?
She says she wants to talk to you.
l'm positive.
Possessed by a fox.
Possessed by a fox?
l'm guessing that the fox spirit first entered Mari's body...
...but decided to leave her since she was deeply hurt...
...and transferred to your body.
That's why l warned you people.
What should l do?
Don't worry.
The chief can get rid of the spirit for you.
What?
Right, Chief?
Oh, great...
She's a medium.
Medium...
But she's a busybody.
Right?
That's not necessary.
Mia!
Don't worry.
l'll get rid of the spirit.
Hurry up!
l'm all ready to go!
Yes...
No...
Mia...
What?
You're breaking my concentration.
Umm...
Can you really get rid of it by doing this...
l told you.
Demons and spirits feed off human energy.
For men, it's the semen.
For women, it's the love juice when they climax.
That means we have to make you climax in order to lure the spirit.
Yes, but...
Yoshikawa...
No...
Stop...
l'm coming!
l'm begging you, spirit. Leave Kumi's body and disappear.
l... won't...
l won't?
Why?
That's the...
Rin, hyo, tou, sha, kai, jin, retsu, zai, zen!
Tenchigen Myokoujinpentsuuriki!
lt got away...
Kumi!
Looks like you people summoned something terrible.
Something terrible?
l thought it was the fox spirit.
That was not a weak spirit.
What exactly was it?
Three of you were involved in this, right?
Who's the third person?
What's wrong, Tachibana?
- Tachibana!
- Reina!
Oh, Kumi.
What happened?
Nurse's Office
Please...
l don't care what you do. Just stick it inside!
Reina!
Stop this, Reina!
Kumi!
No...
Stop it...
Reina...
Stop...
No...
What happened to Reina?
The spirit that's in her body...
...is a darkini!
Mia!
Chief!
Hold on.
l'll save you in a bit.
You're pathetic, darkini.
You're doing well after becoming a yaksa.
But you want more power. You're despicable!
Oh, l see you're pissed off.
Then why don't you try taking my power?
l'll feed off your power!
Rin, hyo, tou, sha, kai, jin, retsu, zai, zen!
Yoshikawa! Close the door!
Now you can't escape.
l set up a barrier here in advance.
Using this technique, l'll defeat the spirit that's possessing her body.
Your name is Reina, right?
l'll make you feel comfortable...
Mia, what are you doing?
Don't worry.
lt's holy water made from a divine tree.
Now, you people need to help me out from here on.
Holy water from the top...
Fudo's sword from the bottom...
Then we coerce her from the sides...
...and lure the spirit to one spot.
Evil spirit, disperse!
Kaman!
Reina!
Kumi? l...
Why?
Why am l naked?
Mia!
Yeah, she's all right now.
Thank God.
Reina!
Kumi?
A baby fox?
This fox is the one that probably caused all the trouble this time...
The reason why you weren't possessed as much as Mari or Reina...
...is because you showed respect for the spirit.
Then that means this baby fox doesn't hate me right?
Maybe l'll pet this little one.
Pet the little one?
That thing is a demon.
Don't do it!
What should l call you?
Foxy.
Yeah, l'm going to call you Foxy!
Sorry l'm late!
Now, let's get started.
Start?
But what about the other members?
Huh? l didn't tell you?
Our members include myself and the assistant manager, Yoshikawa.
Right.
So you're the third member of our club now.
Then Foxy is the fourth member of this club.
Right, Foxy?
Fine...