Good morning.
Good morning!
No way! You're kidding right?
Look at those happy faces.
Damn it!
Excellent Girl's Academy.
An academy, targeted towards rich nobles around the world,
a place where their precious daughters come to study.
Kanako and Hina, their father's the one who owns this place.
That man is my biological father. I've sworn
upon my life I'll make him pay.
Upon the life I can no longer get back...
Though it's not like it's worth getting back...
I was just a child back then,
when my mother was alive.
What I remember is her firm resolve and her bright spirit.
I never had a father figure.
Your father is a great man.
He's doing an important job right now
so you can't meet him but,
some day, he will come back and take us with him.
The school my father founded was praised
all over the world and considered grand.
It was picked up by all the media outlets.
For me though, it just helped channel the hate I had for him.
I remember my mother took me to
my dad's place one day.
The master can't meet you right now.
Why?!
Just once would be enough!
Please! Please! I beg of you!
That was when I understood what was
going on, despite being a child.
My father had already started a family with another woman.
Our lives were about as important as the trash they threw away.
My mother passed away shortly after, overworking herself.
I couldn't go to university. So I started handing
out flyers as a part time job, just to get by.
I was destined to be a loser the
moment I came into existence.
My father however, being the founder of a prestigious academy,
stood out in society as a brilliant scholar.
At some point, I made a vow in my heart...
I'd crush whatever was important to the
man who tossed us out like trash.
But I didn't have the power.
The security in this academy is tight.
I can't get anywhere close to that man or his daughters.
If only I had the power, I'd definitely do it.
I'd take my revenge without letting
anyone get in the way.
If only I had a way!
Well then, should I give you that power?
Oh, I'm sorry I caught you by surprise.
What are you?
That doesn't really matter, does it?
This is a time-stop watch you see here.
By pressing this switch, you can freeze time around you.
Freeze time? Bullshit.
There's no way something like that ca...
Wha...
What is this?!
See? It stopped, didn't it?
The time, that is.
At the school, stop by time.
Original Animation Disk
Resting Hina, moving Kanako.
A hardened resolve, the blood of deflowering. The compilation.
To be able to stop time at will...
That is something unbelievable.
However, I actually saw it with my own eyes.
That's ridiculous!
How you decide to use this power, is up to you.
I'm looking forward to seeing something interesting.
A time-stop watch.
To see if this mysterious power was actually real,
I tested it again and again.
I have to see if it can stop time for
objects and living organisms.
I have to see if there's any risk involved.
And then I concluded,
that this power was, without a doubt, the real deal.
I could care less why, who or from where
someone could get this and give it to me.
If I have this power, I can get all the
revenge I could possibly want.
Sit back and enjoy it, father.
I'm going to crush everything you treasure, starting right here!
Student Council Room
How is it? Did you get used to this school yet?
Onee-chan, just how many times
have you asked me that?
I'm not that much of a kid anymore, you know.
Is that so? No matter how old you are, Hina will always be Hina for me.
My cute little sister.
Even the advanced security of Excellent Girl's Academy
is useless when faced with time-stop...
I'll destroy everything that piece of shit holds dear!
First comes this academy.
I wanted to meet you, Kanako, Hina.
Well then, where should I start?
From the little sister?
That sure is a nice smell.
I'm sure I'd be punished for pulling a prank on a girl this cute.
As if...
But I really wanna feel her.
Doesn't matter what the punishment is.
If they can even touch me that is...
Oh! These are quite soft.
They seem a little small compared to the big
sister but, I guess they're still developing.
This time-stop watch is the best!
Well then, should I get a little more adventurous?
This is a very cute bra.
I guess it suits childish little Hina.
I wonder if they've been groped by a man before?
Of course not, night?
Wh-Who is this?!
Noo!!
Don't move so much Hina.
Why do you know my name?
You don't have to be so scared.
I came all the way here to rape you after all.
Huh?!
N-N-No! No! No!
Let go of me! Onee-chan!
Its useless Hina, Onee-chan won't help you.
Eh? Why!? No way!
Onee-chan!
Stop it!
Don't do this! No!
I beg of you, I don't want this!
Just what are you saying when your nipples are this hard?
You're actually feeling good, aren't you?
What are you saying?!
Let go of me!
It's disgusting!
Not my nipples! Don't lick them!
Keep going, that's a nice reaction you've got there.
More? Should I stop here?
It's great, isn't it? Feels amazing.
Time for a commemoration picture.
I'm sure your dad will be surprised.
Seeing his daughter in such a compromising position...
It's a pussy that still reeks of piss.
Or did it get excited by me?
Even if I do this, you can't really move can you...
Oh! It's already drenched huh!
My dick is completely erect!
Look, it's that dick you love so much.
"Ahh it's so big! I'm scared" –
it's alright to say that, you know!
Oh, this is nice!
How's the feeling of eating your first dick?
Hina-chan, allow me to rape that cute little mouth of yours!
Hmm, this lacks a little excitement, doesn't it?
I would've liked a little more movement...
Can't help it I guess...
Oops!
Damn! That feels nice!
I'll thrust it in myself, so suck it properly okay?
Alright! Now it's time for a commemoration
photo of you taking a dick in your mouth.
But if I unfreeze time, she'll be crying for sure.
Oh well, whatever.
Yo! Did I surprise you?
Oops, you can't take it out you know...
Come on... Just like that...
It's a memorial photo of you eating a dick.
Keep eating it like that!
I'll pour a lot of delicious milk into your mouth real soon!
Damn, to just start gulping it down... that sure is impressive!
I must say, the reaction of Hina-chan getting
her first taste of semen is rather splendid.
That's a nice expression...
Well then, I should probably have you frozen again.
Thank you, Hina-chan.
It felt really good, you know.
You're next, Kanako.
Damn, you sure seem like a grown up woman.
Beautiful, and the academy's
student-body president.
That's something worth raping.
Kanako-chan's lips are so soft.
About as soft as pudding.
I feel like listening to the voice that
comes out of this cute mouth.
I wonder what sort of face you'll make
if I did the same thing to your sister.
Let's check it out!
Huh?! Wha-What?!
Who are you?!
Yo, Kanako. You sure sleep pretty carefree.
Thanks to you, something terrible happened
to your precious little sister.
Just what are yo...
Even though Hina-chan was calling out to you for help,
You don't know anything do you...
You! What is this?! What are you saying?!
Well then, let me make you understand!
Now that you're all quiet... here!
Oh! As expected, Kanako's boobs are
definitely bigger than Hina's.
Your boobs are shining!
I wonder if it's looking good down here as well?
Oh! Amazing!
That's a wonderful pose, Ms. President.
It's nice, the smell of a maiden.
Well well, how about the taste?
This is, without a doubt, the taste of a virgin.
Good, I just thought of something nice.
Not yet...
Shit, I'm screwed! I'll cum right away if I try to move!
But... I'll have to move right?!
That's good isn't it, Kanako?
With this, you've become an adult woman!
Now let's show this glorious appearance to everyone.
Huh?! Wh-What's this?!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!!
Congratulations on graduating from being a virgin,
it's the moment you're no longer one.
I just posted an update on the blog.
Lies! Something like this...
It hurts!
Stop it! Let me go! Make it stop!
No can do!
Like I'd stop something that feels this good!
No! W-Why are you moving?!
Stop! Please stop!!
Don't say that.
This is a memorable moment after all.
Come on! Smile, smile!
Why... Why do something like this!
Just what do you get by doing this to me?!
That's nice! Whine more! Get scared!
This is the best reaction!
My dick is rock hard with excitement!
Why? By a man like this...
Just what happened to me?!
Why are you feeling so good, you say?
Well, that's because you've got a sex obsessed perverted body!
No! That's wrong! That's wrong!!
This...! I don't want this!
No! No! No!
Oh! It became really tight!
So you're starting to like my meat stick huh?
Cumming, cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Have your first load of semen!
You let it come out.
Doing this in front of Hina-chan...
You're a disgraceful big sister, aren't you?
Well, I'll be giving a shot to Hina-chan as well...
Huh?! Pl-Please don't! Don't do anything to Hina!
Just sit quiet for now,
you'll be able to see the deflowering
of Hina-chan real soon.
I guess Hina-chan's insides are a little too tight...
Oh, that must have hurt!
But now you're a grown up woman, just like your sister.
Well now, I wonder what sort of
reaction Hina-chan will give me...
Huh?!
No! What! Just what is going on?!
How is it, Hina-chan?
The feeling of graduating from being a virgin!
It hurts! It hurts!
Sto... No!!
It's alright, I'll make you feel good in a minute!
No way...
Why... Why are you doing something like this to me?
You can't help but ask that right?
But even though it's a little sad, this is reality.
Well, I'm enjoying it of course!
Mov... Please don't move...
No!
Hina-chan is a good match for my dick you know!
Your pussy is making all kinds of noises!
No way...
Well then, let's go out with a bang!
Oh! I'm gonna cum Hina-chan!
No! No! No!!
Onee-chan! Onee-chan!!
Congratulations Hina.
Now let's show your new self to your big sister...
Onee-chan? Onee-chan!!
Hina...? Why?!
Onee-chan!
Hina, Hina!
What a good day for sisters to comfort each other.
For the finale, let me pin you both down
and rape you properly, okay?
Though, when you lie there with a stoic face,
it makes you seem like a dutch wife.
I'll make you feel so good, you won't even
have time to worry about your sister!
Now then, I wonder what sort of reaction you'll give me
when you find out you're being raped in front of her sister again.
Just when did this?!
What just happened?!
A lot of stuff happened... you see,
right now, you're in the middle
of having some fun with me.
It feels good right?
I beg of you, Hina...
Curious about your little sister?
Here...
Hi-Hina! Run! Run away!!
Hina!!
Why won't you answer me??
You! Just what did you do to Hina?!
Yeah I wonder what happened...
Maybe seeing her sister getting raped by a random stranger,
has traumatized her to the point she can't speak?
Please... Not my sister...
If it's just me, I'll listen to everything you say!
You can do whatever you want to me...
Just let my sister...
That's so admirable!
But that's a request I cannot accept...
Wait! Not Hina! Not Hina!!
It's a pity isn't it...
All I want to see is the both of you suffering.
So if you give me a request like that...
Then there's no way I won't lay my hands on Hina!
You look like you're really enjoying it huh, Hina-chan!
Even though you were a virgin just a minute ago.
You're one hell of a pervert!
It's interesting, isn't it?
The time-stop watch, that is.
Its just one amusing thing after another when I'm using it!
Okay Hina-chan, it's time I rape you in front of your sister.
Ag... Again... Why?
Why?!
Please, forgive me already!
Why?
Hina-chan is feeling good as well, right?
Th-That's wrong...!
That's... That's not true...
Tsk tsk, it's not good to lie you know!
This doesn't feel like a pussy that's not feeling good!
Stop...! S-Stop!
Onee-chan, Onee-chan!
Here! I'll let your big sister listen to your cute voice!
No... No! Please stop!
Onee-chan!
Help me, help me!
Onee-chan!!
Why won't you answer me? Onee-chan!
Why... Why does Onee-chan have those eyes?
Yeah I wonder why...
Think about that a little harder!
Here!!
I'll give you another load to mull it over!
No! No!!
Your body is quite honest huh...
Even if your mouth says no,
your pussy is gripping my dick tighter than ever!
How is it?
My cock feels good, doesn't it?!
What? Are you about to cum already?!
Please forgive me!!
No! No!
It's amazing!
I'm about to cum!
That's why, that's why... please forgive me!!
In that case, I'll let you have everything I've got!
Amazing, amazing!
It's cumming! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!!
Woohoo! It's coming in, it's coming!
That was quite a feast, Hina.
Well then, you're up next Kanako!
I'll rape you hard as well, don't worry.
It seems like you're really enjoying it.
I'll explore every inch of you with my cock!
I guess it's about time...
W-What did you do to me?
Nothing much, don't tell me you came already?
Really... both of you sisters are such perverts.
Hina!! Hina!!!
I'm going to leave you in that state as well!
N-No! Stop! Stop it!!
Even if you say that, you're feeling quite good huh!
No-No way! I'm not!
That's a lie!
No! N-no, no!!
You know how you're making me move my dick right?
It's best when you shake it like that!
Kanako's perverted pussy, that is.
Please don't say that!
It's dripping wet you know!
Kanako's pussy is overjoyed isn't it!
Th-That's not it! That's not true!
I'm going to let it out just like this!
Let yourself get loose!
No! Please don't be so rough!!
Stop! Stop! Stop!!
Oh! It's getting so damn tight!
Your semen's coming in...
That was fun, both of you.
Excuse me.
President, are you ther...
Sensei!! Sensei!!
Tranlator: Maq-kun
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Punk4real