This is the man who tossed my mother and me aside.
In order to get my revenge on the director
of Excellent Girls Academy,
I got my hands on a device that
lets me control time at will,
and infiltrated the school.
To start off,
I took the daughters of his new wife,
Kanako and Hina,
and raped them.
Hey, did you hear?
What happened?
Well then, who's my next target?
I've got all the time in the world.
My revenge is far from over.
At the school, stop by time.
The muddy body fluids that fill the pool. The school swimsuits that don't float.
Original Animation Disk
Gakuen de Jikan yo Tomare
The muddy body fluids that fill the pool.
Srory arc: The school swimsuits that don't float.
This is locker room, huh?
Changing
Room
Is anyone in here?
There they are.
Her body looks like it's still developing,
but that's what makes it irresistible.
This girl has passable breasts, but the
rest of her looks nice and toned.
That pampered face is pretty arousing as well.
Holy! They're humongous!
Won't those melons get in the way as she swims?
She has quite the face.
Have I seen her somewhere?
I see. No wonder her face felt familiar...
That's the Girl's Olympics representative,
Kamisuura Risa.
Splendid. When they find out that the academy's
treasured celebrity was raped...
I guess those are her friends?
That settles it. These girls are my next targets.
First...
It's a little narrow,
but I won't be found if I hide in here.
Come on, everyone has already left.
Whoa! When did they...
But...
These swimsuits are hard to take off, huh?
Yeah, it's such a pain for us to change, right?
It's especially annoying when we
have to go to class afterwards.
B-But it's fun when we're swimming.
Well of course, Risa would say that.
You're our Olympics representative, after all.
Man, I want to be popular like Risa too!
G-Geez!
Seriously, how can you swim with that rack?
Risa, they've gotten bigger, right? Here, here!
Stop it, Yuuka!
It's true. They're amazing!
You too, Akari! Stop watching and help me!
So her friends are Yuuka and Akari, huh.
They seem quite chummy with each other.
I guess it's about time I join them.
Well then, who's first?
I'm dying to feel Risa's breasts,
but this is...
This is good!
Whose ass should I grab first? Oh, decisions, decisions!
This one's nice!
Her boobs are massive, but her ass is huge as well!
Damn, this feels incredible!
It's getting me excited!
Don't worry, I'll rub them all over for you.
Looks like your chest isn't the only big thing you've got.
Really, you've got a sexy body.
Well then, guess I should check up on your friends too.
Oh? That's a nice sound.
And, here too!
How nice. All three of you have amazing asses.
Akari's ass is small and plump, while
Yuuka's is tight and toned.
You girls are the best!
Well then, next up...
The long-awaited pussy check.
Oh? What do we have here?
Her labial folds look nice and perky! The way her
smooth skin curves around it is amazing...
This pussy's shape is incredibly erotic.
Shall I taste it as well?
It has the same nasty taste of a pool.
Your reactions are just right.
I'll let you really feel this!
Well now, getting this wet...
You want me to thrust my cock in you
so bad, you just can't help it, huh?
Wait a little bit more, okay?
I have to properly taste your friends as well.
So this is Allan's pussy, huh?
It looks a little small for my taste.
But it's good in its own right!
Oh damn, it's so tight!
She's definitely a virgin alright.
It's like a little girl's pussy. Bet it's pretty sensitive.
Making such lewd sounds just by being teased by a finger?
I see, I see. She probably hasn't fully developed yet,
but I'm definitely working with some good material here.
Whoa, my finger is already drenched?
This taste is quite something. I can't wait
to shove my dick inside her later.
Well then, the last one?
Sorry to have made you wait, Yuuka.
Oh! A great reaction from the get-go!
How can she be so wet?
Alright! How about I tease your pussy some more?
Well, well! Could it be that Yuuka
is actually ready for this?
Just kidding.
These all-girl schools are full of sex-loving sluts these days.
Everyone wants my dick so much, they just can't help it.
Well then, let me take you up on your requests.
Risa, I'll start with you.
Time to loosen up those stiff-looking tits of yours.
Oh! They look like cow tits, don't they?
I'm gonna rape you right here to see those boobs jiggle.
Well then, I'm putting it in.
Risa, here I come!
It's so damn tight!
Your pussy is squeezing me hard!
This is, without a doubt, the mark of a virgin!
Looks like it hurts, but I'm not done yet!
I'm pushing it all the way to your womb!
Alright Risa, let's have our first meet.
Today's the day you finally become a woman.
There!
Damn, it's tight! It's so tight that it kinda hurts!
I can't get enough!
No... what is this?!
It's alright, you don't have to resist.
I'm just inside of you.
As you can probably tell, it's reaching into your womb.
W-Who are you!?
Ow! It hurts!
I guess you don't understand the situation you're in.
Your pussy's being violated by a dick at the moment.
By the dick of a stranger, that is.
Oh my, you seem confused.
I guess I've got no choice but to let your body understand.
Here!
Ow! It hurts!
Wow! So tight!
If you grip me that hard, you just might feel good too!
It hurts, it hurts!
It hurts so much!
Come on, this is your first time.
Learn to enjoy the moment!
No. It hurts. It hurts!
Does it really hurt that much?
Well, this will feel better soon.
If you can't remember this with your head, I'll make
sure you remember this with your body!
You become so straightforward when I stop time...
Maybe you can't feel the pain anymore?
Your body is always honest though.
Look at you moan from all the pleasure.
Once I resume time, you'll definitely feel good.
Even when I freeze time, her body reacts to instinct.
I'll make you feel good with my hands as well.
How's that? It feels good when I grope your boobs
while slamming your pussy, doesn't it?
This is great. I'll make you feel even better!
I'll really make you feel this!
Alright. Let's unfreeze time again.
What sort of reaction will you show me next?
Hi Risa, what happened?
Did getting raped with this dick make you feel good?
No! Stop it! Don't mess up my pussy!
Did you cum?
Did you feel good from being raped?
Everyone's beloved Olympic candidate
just got raped. What a scandal!
No way, this can't be... No!
Why? It hurt so much before!
I don't understand this!
You feel so good that you can't hold back anymore!
No!
The reason your pussy is so erotic is because you're
a perverted girl who loves to masturbate!
Here!
You're wrong! I haven't done anything of the sort!
What's going on? Are you going to cum again?
Well then, this time I'll make sure
you feel good when you do!
I'll unload all of it inside your pussy!
Unload? W-What are you...
What, you say? Isn't it obvious!?
Cum! My cum!
C-Cum? W-What?
You still don't get what I'm saying?
It's semen! Semen! I'm going to deliver my genes from
the depths of my balls, right down to your womb!
G-Genes!? Please forgive me!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Yes, that's right!
It'll be good if you get a baby, huh?
I look forward to it.
Oh! How nice!
Please don't! I beg of you!
No can do! Now, get pregnant!
No! I don't want to be pregnant! I'm gonna cum!
You're gonna give up and accept it, right?
Let's savor the fruit of your love!
Let go of me!
I'm cumming! I'm going to impregnate your virgin pussy!
C-C-Cumming!
This can't be happening.
I'm almost there! I'm letting it all out!
Why me? S-Something like this...
It felt good, right?
You made me release so much.
With this, you've become my woman.
You should be happy y'know.
Now then, guess I'll take the virginity
of your friends, just as I took yours.
Friends?
I'm talking about those two over there.
Akari? Yuuka!?
Why? For what reason!?
Run away! Run...
Geez. She finally gets it after being confused for so long.
How tragic. Your screams will never reach them.
Well then, who's next?
Yuuka, I guess?
Akari seems like the timid type.
I'll really scare her when I reveal what I did to her friends.
Okay, I'm coming in. Are you a virgin as well?
Here!
She seems the most playful of the lot,
but she really is a virgin, huh?
As expected of a lady from Excellent Girls Academy.
I'm so happy!
I'll loosen up your virgin pussy with my dick, okay?
Well then, guess I should introduce myself.
It hurts! What is this!?
Oh, you're awake? How do you like this dick?
W-Who are you!?
Is that blood?
Why!?
What's happening to me!?
No, stop! Stop it! Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am, does it?
What matters is that you're getting your
virgin pussy raped by a total stranger.
Raped? It can't...
No, no, no!
Take it out! Hurry up, and take it out!
No, no!
How did this even...
I was with Risa and the others a minute ago.
Yeah, you're supposed to be with your friends
but here you are, getting raped instead.
It's a strange world, isn't it?
What did you do? Let go of me!
I like that defiant face.
That really turns me on. My dick is getting rock hard!
His big and disgusting thing is inside of me...
No! No!
I'll make you experience the best climax ever.
What are you talk...
Now then, shall I make this erotic pussy feel good?
All these sensations will merge together
the instant I unfreeze time!
Just like that!
Your moist pussy helps make for
some smooth pistoning action!
Let me tease you a little more to make you feel better!
Whoa, your pussy's twitching all of a sudden!
Holy! It's squeezing me tight!
You're going to cum, aren't you?
I can feel it with my dick!
Go on! Cum on my dick! Cum on it!
Why am I cumming? Why?
This tight pussy of yours is just amazing!
I'm gonna cum inside you right now!
No! Stop it!
No, what is this!?
Crazy, my mind's going crazy!
Come on, your pussy should feel better now.
It's pretty sensitive after cumming, right?
I'm begging you. Please, forgive me!
No! Don't! Not inside!
If you want forgiveness, you'll have to apologize
from the bottom of your heart.
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
I guess it's no use even if you apologize, 'cause
I'm going to cum inside you regardless!
No way! You promised!
Promised? Did I do something like that?
Horrible! You're the worst!
No! Stop it!
Here I come! I'm cumming!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
I'm gonna shoot my load into you while you're squirting!
Ahh, that was the best...
You made me cum so much.
Horrible. This is awful...
You're the last one, Akari.
Well, I should probably scare her first by
showing her the bodies of her friends.
Huh? E-Eh?
W-What?
Hey, Akari! Can you see those two in front of you?
W-Who!?
A-A man? Why!?
Now, now, don't worry about me.
What about those two friends of yours?
It hurts! Eh!? What?
Risa... Yuuka?
W-What happened?
You don't get it?
Well, let me explain it to you.
You see, I just raped those two.
I shoved my dick inside their pussies.
Now I'm going to do the same to you, Akari.
Just like them, understand?
Huh? No way! Why!?
Help me, help me!
Yuuka! Risa!
Aren't you cute. Do you think they
can do anything to help you?
H-Help me! Help me!
It's no use.
No!
Stop it! Let go of me!
There!
– Ow! It hurts!
– I tore! I tore it!
I just ripped your virgin pussy apart in a single thrust!
It hurts! It hurts!
My stomach hurts!
What happened to you two!?
Say something!
Yuuka, Risa, it hurts. Help me!
Ah, I guess I have no choice.
I'll have to show Akari how to climax.
What? Stop! Don't do these horrible things to me!
This pussy feels incredible.
I gotta fuck you till this tight pussy becomes a little loose!
Oh it's getting wet, it's getting wet!
You're really feeling it, huh?
She has smaller breasts compared to the other two,
but her nipples are rock hard.
Come on! It feels good when I do this, right?
I guess it's better now.
Akari is going to cum too.
What? What is this!?
How's that? It doesn't hurt anymore, right?
You're feeling good from having
sex with a stranger, aren't you!
That's not true. It's ripping me apart!
I'm dying! I'm going to die!
Judging from your voice, you're feeling
way too good to want that.
That's not true! What's going on!?
Tell me!
Even if you ask me that...
Akari is a perverted girl who loves getting raped.
Lies! That's a lie!
A complete lie!
You really don't listen to others, do you.
I'll make you understand by cumming inside you!
Inside? You can't mean...
In other words, I'm going to spray
my load inside your womb!
Be grateful!
No, no! Not inside! I'll become a mother!
I don't want to be a mother!
Here I come!
Make sure you cum with me, okay?
No! No!
Don't! What is this!?
I don't understand! I don't know!
I'm still cumming!
T-This can't be! It's not real!
It's good, isn't it? Now you've been properly
initiated, along with your friends.
No. No! Someone, help...
Well then, what should I do next?
The Student Council's president, admired by
her sister and the entire student body,
and now the Olympics candidate who
carries everyone's expectations...
These incidents alone are scandalous enough
to ruin this academy's reputation. However...
This is only the beginning.
As long as I have this time-stop device,
I will rape every single girl in this academy,
without leaving anyone out.
Once I do that, this incident will be heard worldwide!
That man's beloved academy and students...
I'll destroy every last one of them!
Eh? No!
No!!
Today, a strange incident took place.
Breaking
News
Developing Srory on Scandal of
Excellent Girls Academy!!
At the world famous Excellent Girls Academy,
students and teachers were mysteriously
attacked and left unconscious.
It's a horrendous incident like no other.
The culprit has yet to be found,
and the police have no leads.
Breaking
News
Developing Srory on Scandal of
Excellent Girls Academy!!
The students' parents are questioning the
security standards of the academy.
This academy is done for. And so is that man.
Just who was that woman?
That doesn't even matter anymore...
I don't know who she was or where she came from,
but thanks to her, my quest for vengeance is over.
Translator: Maq-kun | Hikarucon
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Punk4real | Sill