So that's the younger of the Nanase sisters?
She's so hot!
Yo, Sosuke.
Taking tons of pics of the
Nanase sisters as usual, I see.
Taking them in secret like that. It's kinda sick.
You should just ask her out and get it over with.
That's impossible, because
she's one of the Idol Sisters.
I'm not taking pictures of
them for perverted reasons.
I just think they make great models.
Then why don't you ask her to model for you?
Great idea!
If I could ask her, I would've done it already.
But Arisa-chan would never
cooperate with someone like me.
That was just... my imagination, right?
Gakuen Shimai 1
What's wrong? Are you not gonna do it?
Don't tell me you don't want to do it?
Please stop. Why are you making me do this?
How can you talk like that?
You came in here because of that letter we sent.
I think you knew what it meant.
Weren't you looking forward to it?
That's not true at all.
Your mouth might say that, but your pussy
has been doing a great job squeezing me.
Then I guess it's about time I join in.
Come on. Turn your ass this way.
You've got a great ass.
You don't mean you're going to... Not in there!
You're pretty when you're scared.
Usually she's so smug as a teacher,
and now she's in tears.
I love seeing that expression.
He really likes doing it in the ass.
He's sick.
Shut the fuck up. You guys are no better.
Don't...
I can't have two thick things
thrashing inside of me!
Deep inside... I feel it!
Oh, I thought you didn't like
it, but you're feeling good.
In that case, we'll thrash even harder.
Oh, no. I can't feel anything anymore.
You're a strong-willed woman, Sensei.
I think I'm gonna cum!
Stop it. Come to your senses.
I'm gonna cum!
Me too. I'm gonna cum!
Don't! Not inside of me! Take it out!
Don't say that. We're gonna fill you up.
No!
Well then, Sensei,
if you tell anyone about what happened,
we'll share this picture with the whole school.
What's up?
Just checking out our next target.
I guess I just imagined it.
Hey, Kurokawa!
You've got a visitor.
You're Nanase Mika?
You're Kurokawa Sosuke?
Y-Yeah, I am. Did you want something?
Why the hell does it have to be this loser?
Um...
I've got something to tell you,
so wait by the front gate after school.
Got it? It's a promise.
Hey, Sosuke!
Since when are you and
Mika-chan on speaking terms?
Asshole! Was this happening behind our backs?
I didn't do anything.
She didn't find out I was taking pictures, did she?
You're late, Kurokawa Sosuke!
Sorry! Homeroom ended late.
Arisa-chan?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Nanase Arisa.
I'm Kurokawa Sosuke.
This place is a little awkward,
so let's go somewhere else.
Follow me.
Uh, okay.
What was that?
What...
did you just say?
I'll repeat myself. The three
of us are all siblings now.
Y-You've gotta be kidding!
I wish I were kidding!
Mika, this isn't for us to decide.
It's something Sosuke's father
and our mother decided.
Yeah, well, you always go along
with what people want anyway.
I hate the idea of living under the
same roof as this fucking nerd!
I'm a nerd?
Well, I can't argue with that.
Mika, please control yourself.
Otherwise, we'll no longer have a place to live.
So, the story goes like this.
Their mother is an anthropology student who
went to South America to study some ruins.
There she met my dad, who's a photographer.
Since they're both rather impulsive,
they fell in love and got married
in a South American church.
That means their children from
former marriages become siblings.
Her mother sold the condo
where they'd been living,
and she moved in with my dad at our house.
So this means I'll be living under the
same roof as the famous Nanase sisters.
But why do I feel so uneasy about it?
How peculiar.
I never would've dreamed that Arisa-chan
would be in my house cooking me dinner.
But it feels like we're newlyweds,
so I guess that's a good thing.
Dinner will be ready soon, so please
stay comfortable while you wait.
Okay, I'll go wait in my room then.
I wonder if Arisa-chan would become my model.
There aren't many girls with faces as nice as hers.
Arisa-chan...
I...
Arisa-chan, I'm sorry.
I know you're my sister now,
but I still think of you this way, Arisa-chan!
Wow, looks yummy!
Arisa, you've always been such a great cook.
Dinner will be ready soon,
so call Sosuke-kun down for me.
Why does it have to be me?
Because we're living together now.
Okay, fine, whatever.
Sosuke, Arisa has dinner ready.
S-Sosuke! What?
No! This isn't what it looks like!
This is Arisa?
And all of these are candids?
But those are just...
So you've got the hots for Arisa, right?
And what's worse, you get off on pictures of her.
You're really sick, ya know?
Give those back!
Hey, Sosuke, instead of being a
loser and jacking off to pictures,
wouldn't you feel a lot better
letting a real girl do it for you?
What are you implying?
I'm implying that I'll be a real girl for you.
I'll do this, you see.
Mika-san, please stop this! I'm losing my mind!
How cute.
You know Sosuke, seeing a pitiful little nerd
like you makes me want to tease you.
Mika-san...
We shouldn't be doing this.
Your mouth may say that, but your
dick is getting harder by the second.
Oh, now it's throbbing.
Think it'll get wet soon?
I can't help it.
Your hands are so warm and soft!
Sosuke, your balls are so soft.
Mika-san, you're grabbing too tight!
Oh, stop it. Don't be such a wimp.
Mika-san, don't be so violent.
I'm not gonna be able to hold back!
Don't release yet.
If you do, I'll tell Arisa about those pictures.
Oh, no!
We've just barely started anyway.
Well? Aren't my boobs pretty?
Now I'll let you feel them.
Your nipples are touching the head of my dick!
It's all wet.
You say you don't like it, but you're enjoying it.
You really are a pervert.
Well, yeah, any guy would feel
this way if you did that to him.
Well, Sosuke?
My boobs feel great, don't they?
Yes, they're wonderful!
I can feel how soft and squishy they are.
It feels great!
Sosuke, that's such a lewd expression.
Gives me the creeps.
This is bad, Mika-san! This time for sure...
This time for sure, I'll cum.
The head of your dick is throbbing.
But, Mika-san, if you do that,
I'll cum in your mouth!
But I don't want you to cum yet.
Bad boy.
I can't hold back anymore.
Mika-san! I'm gonna cum in your mouth!
Mika-san!
I'm sorry, Mika-san.
I hadn't done it in a while, so there was a lot.
Mika-san, you didn't just...
What was that for?
I told you not to cum until I said it was okay!
But I can't exactly control my...
Jeez...
They're sure taking their time.
I wonder what they're doing?
Sorry about that, Arisa.
Sosuke suddenly made me drink something gross.
Mika-san?
She's...
Those two certainly became friends really fast.
I wonder if Mika-san has done anything
like that in front of Arisa-chan?
Just remembering it makes me...
Arisa-chan?
I-I'm sorry!
Arisa?
Oh crap, I'm completely...
Mika-san!?
Oh, I didn't know you were in here.
Cut it out. You knew I was.
Well, let's not dwell on specifics.
Anyway, Sosuke, I came here to wash up,
so will you wash my back?
Why me?
My back. You'll wash it, won't you?
Okay, fine, I'll do it!
If I don't, you'll tell Arisa
about the pictures, right?
Oh, so you do understand after all.
I wonder what Mika-san's trying to do,
asking me me to wash her like this.
Hey, can you wash my front side now?
Yeah, fine.
Wow. For a nerd, you're sure good at this.
I wonder if your boobs are extra-sensitive.
That's good. Now do it harder.
You're pretty good.
Then, come on. Clean them with your tongue.
Mika-san, your nipples...
They're getting harder.
I'll help you out.
You're not going to play the aggressor with me!
What's this? You're already hard.
I thought so earlier, but you're surprisingly big.
Mika-san, not that!
It feels great, doesn't it?
Can you see? The spot where your
dick and my pussy are rubbing...
Oh, no! I'm gonna cum again!
Oh, no, I'm cumming!
Why?
Wanna cum?
Yes!
I want to cum.
Not yet. I'm not even close myself.
Mika-san, what are you...
It's your first time, isn't it?
Uh, yeah.
Wanna put it in?
Mika-san, don't tease me!
Oh, what a lewd expression.
You want it bad, don't you?
Yes, I want it.
Good. You're being honest now.
Feels great, doesn't it?
Yeah, you're so slippery!
You too. You've got a pretty nice tool.
It's hitting my womb!
Did that surprise you?
Of course it didn't surprise me!
You're getting a bit cocky, Sosuke.
Sosuke, you're staying too still.
I wonder if you like being dominated like this?
For the last time,
any guy would put up with this if a
pretty girl like you was doing it to him!
Then, how about this?
From the tip to your balls, in one thrust!
Mika-san...
Your insides are squeezing me. It feels great!
Doesn't it?
Come on, you'd better move your pelvis too!
You're actually pretty good at this, Sosuke.
It's hitting me... inside. It feels so good!
I'm cumming!
H-Hey, not yet!
I need just a little bit longer.
But... I...
Me too!
I'm cumming!
Sosuke, you're pretty good at this.
Mika-san!
What's wrong with me?
From seeing that earlier, my body's throbbing.
I'm losing my mind.
I had no idea that a man's dick was that big.
If that came inside of me, how would that feel?
If Sosuke-kun were inside of me...
Down there. Sosuke-kun feels it down there.
Oh, no, I'm gushing so much fluid.
Sosuke-kun, what should I do?
What should I do from now on?
I guess I'd better apologize about earlier...
But if I apologize now, I might be
able to ask her to be my model.
Arisa-chan?
Sosuke-kun... I...
Put it in! Your big thing... Put it inside of me!
It's in! Sosuke-kun, you're inside of me!
It's so hot! My pussy's getting so hot!
There! Sosuke-kun, not so rough!
It's my first time!
It feels great.
It feels really great!
Your dick feels so great.
My boobs...
Rub them harder!
Oh, no, I can't hold back anymore!
Sosuke-kun, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from your dick!
I... I can't...
I'm cumming!
I came, Sosuke-kun. I came!
I wonder if it would feel even
better if it were the real thing.
Sosuke-kun... I...