Okay, I'm going to let your brother know you're here,
so you get some rest in the meantime, okay?
Okay.
I'm causing problems for him again.
I'm letting your sister sleep in the infirmary,
so check up on her when you can, okay?
Will do.
If you need me, I'll be in the staff room.
I guess I'll check up on her after practice.
You free?
Yep.
Wanna go to the arcade then?
Hey, Sumire-chan?
Could you take a look at this?
What's this? A movie?
No, it's something that I found on the internet.
Do you think this is real?
Chitsuji-senpai?
So Touka-chan collapsed again?
Yeah, but it's just anemia. With a little rest,
she'll be as right as rain.
Alright then, I'll make dinner for you guys again.
Sorry for making you do this, senpai.
It's fine, I don't mind.
I'm doing it because I like doing it, so don't worry.
Archery Range
Senpai, did you hear that?
W-What?
No... what is this?
What is that?
Hoichi, you need to get to Touka-chan, now!
What about you?!
I'll be right behind you.
Get moving!
R-Right, I'll go.
Be careful.
Touka!
Touka, please be safe!
Shit! I can't go this way either?!
Hoichi!
Daisuke?
What the hell's going on here?!
What's up with them?!
How the hell should I know?
Either way I need to go to Touka, right now!
Touka!
N-Nii-san...
The hell's that? Gives me the creeps.
Touka...
H-Hey!
Nii-san!
Shit... Let go of Touka!
You piece of...
Daisuke!
Ugh, it's so slimy. It feels so disgusting.
Stop fondling me.
No!
Don't touch me there!
I don't want this!
Save me, nii-san.
I-It hurts!
T-Touka...
Stop moving!
So disgusting.
The sliminess is seeping into my body.
Ow, don't move so much around there.
Stop!
Th-This is so rough. My mind's starting to go blank!
N-No, stop!
It's starting to feel hot... Something's coming!
P-Please don't look at me, nii-san.
I-It's swallowing her?
Can you move?
Senpai, where's Touka?
It swallowed her and ran away with her.
I need to go and save her!
And how are you gonna do that?!
We need to get away from here and fast!
I agree. I think it's best if we
find a safe place to hide for now.
I'm still alive?
I'm so scared, nii-san.
Am I going to die like this?
What's this smell?
It's making my head spin.
I can't move a finger.
The tentacles... they're wrapping around me again!
The shape's different than before.
My body's starting to feel so aroused.
Why does it feel so good?
Being this squished shouldn't feel good.
So good! My pussy feels so good!
My boobs feel so good!
What's happening to me?
Why does this feel good?
It's rubbing around inside me... right where it feels best!
The slimy stuff feels good.
I feel like I'm melting.
I-It's gonna make me... It's gonna make me cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Oh darn, I guess I couldn't tell nii-san how I felt about him.
At this rate, we're gonna become one of them.
For now, let's just stick to safe areas.
Rokugo-kun?
You saved us, Rokugo-senpai.
I'm not too sure about the "saved" part yet.
Can you tell me about what the
rest of the school's like right now?
They keep flooding into the school from the gate.
I think it's just a matter of time until they're everywhere.
I see...
I have a feeling that the school's not
the only place like this right now.
We're lucky that they came after school.
If they came during the day time, we'd be dead by now.
How many people are taking shelter here?
About ten, myself included.
I'm having everyone take refuge on the
second floor, so you guys head over there too.
Rest a little.
What about you?
There could be more survivors, so I'm gonna wait here.
Okay. Be careful.
Oh hey, it's Dai-chan! Thank god, you're all safe.
You're as chipper as always even in this situation, huh?
Being chipper is my only selling point.
You shouldn't be the one to say that...
Oh, right, I was on my way to the bathroom.
Yeah, I suddenly have to go now that I feel safe.
So I'll go with Saori to the bathroom.
You two go meet up with the rest, okay?
We don't really know if this place is
safe yet, so don't let your guard down.
We'll be fine. If anything happens, Dai-chan will protect me.
Library
I'm so scared! There's no way we're getting saved!
Kaori, calm down.
Hoichi! What a relief, you're okay!
Yeah, somehow anyway.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Huh? Touka-chan's not with you?
S-So, Natsumi-chan, what happened to the
rest of the people here? Where are they?
U-Uh, Inagi-sensei and Jinmuji-sensei
went to the staff room
and were apparently able to get
through to someone on the phone.
And Mutsuura-sensei is trying to
board up the doors on the north side.
Thanks, senpai.
That was close.
Everything's so messed up right now.
What's gonna happen to us?
Huh? What's this?
Wh-Wha...
T-Touka-chan? I thought that thing swallowed you...
How'd you get free?
Touka-chan?
Saori!
No! Stop!
Where do you think you're touching?!
What's with this thing?
No! Not there! If you touch me there right now, I'm gonna...
I peed!
Is it trying to eat me?
No! Let me out!
This feels gross!
Stop rubbing me there!
These weird tentacles are wrapping all around my body!
Is this pain? Or is this pleasure? I can't tell anymore!
The tentacle keeps hitting me where it feels good!
No... I can't...
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
This thing is gonna make me cum!
It feels so good that I'm starting
to not care what happens to me.
I'll fill everyone who's not here in later.
For now, I'll tell everyone here the current situation.
I'm sure you already know that there have been many
casualties due to the appearance of these monsters.
But this isn't happening at school,
there are similar reports across the world.
I've received reports that no one has been
able to figure out what started all this either.
So does that mean that they're
crawling all over outside too?
Th-That can't be. Does that mean we're stuck here?
Fortunately for us, there haven't been any signs of them
making there way into the east building where we are.
We need to slowly gather information and decide
what we should do going forward as a group.
Wait a second.
I think we should get out of here and get to a safer spot.
If the whole world's in the same boat
as up, there won't be any help conning.
We definitely don't even have
enough food for the entire group.
Hiro-kun...
I get what you're saying, but I think that going
out there blind will only put us at a greater risk.
If we're going to leave, we need to take
it slow and get more information first.
And by then, it's gonna be too late.
It's already been an hour.
What are those two doing?
It's not connecting, huh?
Sensei, those two haven't come back
yet so I'm gonna go take a look.
Wait. Going by yourself is dangerous.
You can't do anything by yourself
if something happens, can you?
Then I'll go with him.
I have a weapon too.
No, we can't put students into danger.
If anyone's going, it should be me...
Then how about I go? I'll go with Jinmuji-sensei.
In the meantime, everyone else should go to the computer
lab on the third floor and search for information.
Do we really need four people?
Okay then. I'll leave it to you.
However, be sure to not leave the
school premises for any reason.
No one was there.
Same here.
But something definitely happened.
Do you think that the same thing that
happened in the infirmary happened here?
But that time it came out of the ground...
Natsumi!
Why are you here?!
I... I was really worried.
Sure, but...
Well she's here and we can't change that now.
The two of you should look elsewhere.
I'll meet up with Goroku-kun
and the others on the first floor.
Is it really okay for the two of us to just run
away by ourselves without saying anything?
What choice did we have?
They didn't listen to my plan at all.
If we said anything, they'd just stop us anyway.
Yeah, that's true, but...
Sh-Shit...
Hiro-kun?!
Leave me...
No!
Hurry!
Run!
I won't let you go!
Hey, Hoichi, you don't think that Daisuke and Saori were...
They haven't broken into the east side of the school right?
Even if they did, then why haven't
we seen any of them at all?
What's that sound?
There's something moving under the floor!
It can't be...
Hiro-kun...
Ka... na... ko...
Hiro-kun, do you recognize me?
Hiro-kun, no matter what you turn into, I'll always...
Hiro-kun's inside me!
Hiro-kun's thing is rampaging around inside me!
That's good! That feels really good, Hiro-kun!
There's so much of you inside me!
I don't care what you do to me at all, Hiro-kun!
Let go of me... Hiro-kun...
Save me!
You're being too rough...
I'm being messed up so deep inside!
No wait... Too strong!
I'm gonna cum!
Wait, Hiro-kun...
I just came.
If you keep doing that, I'm gonna...
Ka... na... ko...
Hey, Hiro-kun, you're scaring me...
I'm being eaten by Hiro-kun! Now we'll be together forever.
It hurts! I can't breathe!
My body's becoming so slimy with Hiro-kun's drool.
My body's... it's being defiled by
something other than Hiro-kun!
If you're that rough, I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum again!
Hiro-kun's gonna make me cum again!
Hey, have you seen Natsumi-san?
She was with us when we got here.
Geez, I told her to not do anything on her own!
What's the problem? Just let the people
who don't want to group do their thing.
Huh? And you call yourself a teacher?!
Well, take a look at that.
Wha... You're kidding me!
Kanako!
Ai-chan... Chiaki-chan...
I'm sorry!
She really did like Chitsuji-senpai.
Hoichi?
Nope, it's me, Natsumi-chan.
Daisuke?!
Where have you been all this time?!
We've been looking all over for you two!
Saori's not with you?
Hey, what happened?
There's something off about you.
There's nothing wrong with me.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: oblivionshadow
encoder: nino
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч