Using the hypnophone I received from my inventor father,
I've carved pleasure into the bodies and souls of these
women, and turned them into my sex slaves:
Yuna-chan,
Nagisa-chan,
Himeno-ojousama,
and Sayuri-san too.
I made a promise with all of them.
Gakuen Saimin Reido
No, I'm Definitely Not Pregnant Yet!
When their pregnancy is confirmed,
I'll leave the memories of the intense
pleasures carved into them during training,
and the sensitivity of their bodies that can
no longer be satisfied by anyone but me,
and return just their minds back to the
way they were before hypnosis.
Then, I'll make them choose.
Will their self-respect overcome their craving for pleasure,
allowing them to return to their
boring, free lives from before?
Or will they leave it all behind,
become my sex dolls again,
I want your dick so much I can't help myself.
Make me cum as you cum inside.
I can't live without you.
Rape me and impregnate me.
and give birth to my children?
It hurts, but it won't stop throbbing.
My body is burning up. I'm gonna go crazy!
I can live without your dick anymore, Futoshi-kun!
I'll do anything you want, Futoshi-kun.
Just make me your sex doll!
Only your huge cock can fill my pussy up!
I'll deceive my husband and raise your
children properly, so fuck me more!
I can't swear something like that in front of my fiancé!
No! If you keep thrusting it in like that, I'll go crazy!
Even though I was raped and impregnated...
Even though I'm being forced to have
sex with such a disgusting otaku...
Neither my body nor my heart can
resist this disgusting otaku's dick!
I swear, I'll have your child, so fuck me silly!
Sakurazakawa Yuna
Nobody left me after all.
Serizono Sayuri
Mizushiro Nagisa
Ryuuguuji Himeno
Sadly, Himeno miscarried.
Serizono Sayuri
Sakurazakawa Yuna
However, Nagisa-chan sure got me good.
I didn't imagine that she'd lie to me about
giving birth and abort it instead.
But still, it's cute how she still can't
live without my cock after all that.
That's exactly what they mean by a "tsundere", right?
Well then, let's finish off Kaoruko-sensei next.
Since I mode her breasts feel like genitals
she's come to like titty-fucking quite a lot.
I'm cummmg!
My milk is spraying all over.
Now, let's have Sensei make her final decision.
Sensei, let's kiss.
I love kissing.
Wh-What?
Why am I doing this?
Why?
The suggestion I gave her causes time to rewind
and makes her remember all of her training when she kisses.
What kind of reaction will you show me, Sensei?
S-Satou-kun, why would you do something so terrible?
How could you hypnotize girls, rape them
and make them do those improper things?
It's unpardonable for a human.
You aren't very convincing saying
that while looking like this,
Kaoruko-sensei.
N-No.
Don't.
What's the matter, Sensei?
Can't you say it?
In that case...
I'll continue having sex with you.
No.
I have Shinya-san, my fiancé.
Stop this!
Oh my, and this is what Kaoruko-sensei has to say
as she has sex with her student... Minazuki-sensei.
Shinya-san.
This... i-isn't what it looks like.
You're the only one I love, Shinya-san.
Shut up, you dirty bitch.
Shinya-san, that's so mean.
What are you saying is mean?
You said you wanted to stay pure until our
wedding day and wouldn't let me, your fiancé,
do anything more than kiss you.
But you're letting Satou cum inside you all he
wants without even using contraceptives.
You're wrong.
You think I'm letting him have sex
with me because I want to?
Didn't you even let me use your asshole
under the pretext of sex practice?
You gave me your virginity while dressed in a wedding
dress and even swore to become my sex friend.
Stop!
Teachers are supposed to lead their students
yet you're even cosplaying like this?
You're really terrible.
You're wrong. Satou-kun made me wear it.
Oh my, did you hide your cosplaying
hobby from your fiancé?
That's terrible, Sensei.
No! This isn't the real Kaoruko!
Sensei, if you'll give birth to my child,
I will hypnotize Mmazuki-sensei too and
let you lead a happy married life.
Don't be ridiculous. Who'd give birth to your child!?
But don't you think it's too late for that now, Sensei?
Have you had your period this month?
Impossible.
This can't be.
I have sex with you every day and
cum inside you a few times a day.
No, you're lying. I can't be pregnant.
Sensei, I'm about to cum.
No!
Do it outside!
I'm definitely not pregnant yet!
If that's the case, all the more reason.
I'm going to make sure to impregnate you.
No! I'm begging you. Do it outside!
Don't cum inside me!
No!
You climaxed from a cumshot in front of your fiancé, huh?
You act all innocent, but you're a total slut.
I'm breaking off the engagement.
Have a nice life living with your student.
Wait! Shinya-san, it's not what you think.
I'm begging you. Don't leave me.
Oh dear, Minazuki-sensei left you, huh?
You can't blame him.
Someone else came inside you, and you came from that.
No, it's not like that.
What do you say?
If you do what I want, Minazuki-sensei will
love you even though you're such a slut.
Shinya-san will...
If you give birth to my child, you
can marry Minazuki-sensei
and not have to feel embarrassed
about this lewd body of yours,
because I'll make you feel good as your
sex friend, like I've done up to this point.
That's... Ah, not there!
Don't you want to get married, Sensei?
As long as you don't say anything
nobody will know whose child it is.
If you insist, I can hypnotize everyone and
make them think it's Minazuki-sensei's kid.
Now, swear.
Not in that spot!
So big!
If you swear, you'll be able to live
a happy life with Minazuki-sensei.
Happy with Shmya-san...
I swear. I'll give birth to your child, Futoshi-kun.
No, I'm gonna cum!
Negotiations complete.
With this, Kaoruko-sensei will be my sex doll as well.
I'll train you so hard you won't be able
to think about anyone except me.
Please stop this already.
You do those things to me day after day.
This is it. If you continue to do those
terrible things, I'll tell the teacher.
You're wearing it like I told you to again, right?
No, if you do that, it will stand up.
It's gonna stand up.
You don't seem to understand your position yet.
If that happens you'll be the one in trouble.
If I expose your secret on the schools unofficial
website, everyone will be shocked.
The beautiful transfer student beauty
is actually a slutty futanari
who can't even hold back the urge to
masturbate until she's back home.
Stop that.
What's more, she's having sex every day with
the most hated man at school as his sex friend.
That's not true!
You're the one who...
Either way, the result will be the same.
If your secret is exposed, no doubt
delinquents will catch and gangbang you.
They'll all cum inside you to their
hearts' content every day.
I'm sure you'll get pregnant.
No!
Oh, did you get horny after you imagined
yourself being gangbanged?
You're wrong!
Oh, so it was impregnation that got you aroused.
Then, do you want me to cum inside
you without contraception?
No, don't. I won't fight you anymore, so use contraception.
If I were to have a baby with you because
of the things you're doing to me,
I wouldn't be able to continue living.
I suggested that cumming inside her
asshole could cause pregnancy.
It's more effective than I expected.
No more.
If only I were a normal girl, this
would never have happened.
Haven't I been telling you, ever since
we had sex for the first time,
that you shouldn't criticize your body like that?
No, don't look! I'm begging you. Forgive me!
That I love your gorgeous body?
Well then, be sure to come to our usual place today.
If you're late, I'm gonna turn the vibrator on.
Oh, one more thing. Hold on to
this for me until after school.
Your embarrassing photo is inside, so don't lose it.
Aihara-san.
Yes?
There's something I need to talk to you about.
Do you have a minute?
You've got some nerve, putting your hands
on another person's belongings
as soon as you get transferred.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb. You know I'm talking about Fatso!
"Fatso"?
I'm talking about that disgusting otaku Satou.
I-It's a misunderstanding.
I have nothing to do with Satou.
Th-That hurts. You're going to tear my breasts off.
Spill it! You seduced him with these
indecent boobs, didn't you?
Here I was, wondering why he didn't
called me much last month.
So he's found himself a new bitch, huh?
Are you Satou-kun's girlfriend, Mizushira-san?
His girlfriend!?
Don't fuck with me. Who'd want that piece of garbage?
He's my... slave. Yeah, my slave!
Then make him stop.
I can't stand having him as a sex friend,
or relieving him of his sexual urges anymore!
You don’t want to be sex friends?
You're saying that you want to be his lover or something?
That's not what I meant.
And this is coming from someone who left
me out and is fucking Fatso all she wants?
You piss me off.
Very well, I'll make you unable to
speak like that to me ever again.
No!
Wh-What is this sensation?
No, please stop.
I'm sensitive around there. Don't!
You... You're a transvestite!?
N-No, I'm a woman.
Oh really? I've got a nice idea.
No! Stop! Don't take pictures of
me in this embarrassing state.
You even had a vibrator in your ass.
After I spread these photos around the school,
the guys will get together and rape you.
Fatso will then leave you, just like you wanted.
Ah, but maybe they'll get grossed out by
this filthy dick and refuse to touch you.
You're wrong. It's a clitoris.
I'm a girl. I don't have a dick.
Then what splattered all over my face earlier?
You touched my sensitive clitoris, so it spouted juice!
Are you dumb? No matter how you
look at it, that was ejaculation.
Well, whatever.
I'll use this thing you had with you and capture lots
of scenes of you spewing those so-called juices.
Wh-What are you going to do?
Stop it. Let me go.
No!
Stop that. Don't move it!
It's filling up this onahole so perfectly.
What do you mean, "clitoris"?
No more. I'm gonna spew my juices again!
I'm cumming!
Oh my? You came already?
You can't do that.
You're a woman, so you should
say you're cumming properly.
All right, let's try again.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I've apologized, so stop already.
I'll make you feel even better, so be sure to say it.
No, no more.
I don't want to release any more of my juices. No!
It's the appointed time.
Sotou-kun's gonna be mad at me!
I don't want to be punished!
You didn't want to let anybody know about your clit,
yet you still masturbated at school.
That was careless of you.
If you don't want your secret to be exposed...
No!
Well then, I'm gonna cum inside your
virgin asshole, Shouko-chan.
Don't! If you do that, I'll get pregnant!
No! You can't!
No...
I'll cum. I'm gonna cum again.
You're a girl, yet you're cumming over
and over again with an onahole.
You're such a pervert, Aihara-san.
Yes, I'm a pervert. So let me go already.
Oh? If you're a pervert, there's no way
you'd be satisfied with this much.
I wonder what would make a perverted dick-girl happy?
No, no more.
You're right. Shouko-chan wouldn't
be satisfied with this much.
Ugh, Fatso?
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
What were you doing, Nagisa-chan?
You're slow and a blockhead, so I was
training this transvestite in your place.
Oh, how thoughtful of you, Nagisa-chan.
But Shouko-chan is not a transvestite.
She's a full-fledged woman.
I-I apologize.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry!
My womb's going numb! It's..
Stop. No, don't. Make it stop.
If you cum before I cum inside Nagisa-chan,
I'm gonna do it inside you too, Shouko-chan.
No. If you cum inside my asshole anymore...
I'm gonna have a baby.
I'm gonna cum with the onahole!
I'm gonna spout juices again!
You came before me, didn't you?
Well then, I'm gonna do it inside Nagisa-chan now.
D-Don't! It's not a safe day!
I don't wanna get pregnant!
Don't cum inside me anymore!
You're saying that, but your womb
can't wait for me to do it.
Don't!
If you do it inside, you're dead!
I'm gonna kill you, Fatso!
It's going directly into my womb.
I'm gonna have a baby.
I don't wanna get pregnant!
Well then, I'll fuck you too, Shouko-chan.
No, just don't cum inside.
I'll do anything.
No!
Your asshole feels really good.
Your body is unmatched, Shouko-chan.
No!
Since we've already come this far
let's have Nagisa-chan give us a hand too.
I-It hurts! It hurts! Stop that!
Don't. My clit and ass are gonna break!
No...
No!
I wonder how I should make Shouko-chan mine.
Looks like I'm gonna have much, much more fun.
Preview
The second season's finally begun.
Futoshi-kun indulges himself even deeper in his lust.
Next time, I, Serizono Sayuri
the carrier woman next door,
will have Futoshi-kun do this and that to me.
Oh, and if you'd just say something,
I'd do anything for you.
Futoshi-kun, you meanie.
Next on Gakuen Saimin Reido:
Huh? There's no next episode?
Oh, stop with the jokes.
Huh? This really is the end?
W-Wait. That's not what I was told.
Staff! Staff!
Hey, Shouko-chan,
look at the picture the staff made me
to commemorate the anime's release.
Another sudden pairing. It's so cute.
Huh? Is it okay to say that?
That's what's bugging you!?
You're so naive!
With your mere power of twenty thousand IGU
I could even make a beat-em-up game.
Stop right there, Mizushiro-san.
You shouldn't be talking like that.
What's your problem, Sensei!?
It's out of scale.
Could she be the legendary Warring Goddess!?
Can you say it without the meter!?
I've heard something about it
There are twelve pillars supporting the eroge realm.
If you look at the IGU of the twelve
divine generals protecting them,
the Warring Goddess is said to be the strongest in Japan.
She said things like, "It's for the nation. It's for the nation."
She led five or even ten thousand eroge believers
to Valhalla in one night during the last war.
What's more, they say that the persona left behind
after her human form reached its limit
can still play some simulation RPGs.
Could it be that Kaoruko-sensei is the same?
Wh-What's the matter, girl?
We apologize, Mistress.
H-Huh? More importantly, is this everyone?
I have a feeling we're forgetting someone.
Huh? Was there anybody besides us?
Everyone is here. Were you working elsewhere?
I just transferred, so I wouldn't know.
Sensei, the purple person is absent.
Purple?
They're all so mean!