What if...
... somewhere in the city,
there is a sanctuary where each and every form of love is accepted?
Just how many people would find happiness in it?
which is why...
Planting these seeds of love...
Is where we will start our story from.
Subdesu Translation
hentai-ni-juu.blogspot.com
H Ni Juu
Sex Friend
The first time I met her
was during a meeting between Internet game players.
That uniform...
Isn't it the dress code of my school?
Suiren-san, could it be we're in the same grade?
This is actually a cosplay.
Uh, is that so?
It really feels awkward with just the two of us here.
Anyway, where are the others?
It seems they won't be able to make it.
They called me earlier and informed me.
Hey, hey.
A karaoke booth isn't a place
where boys and girls meet for the first time.
You especially,
don't find yourself here alone with a cute girl either.
That's...
Wanna take a look?
All sorts of delusions start going into my mind.
Woah, you sure know how to pull off a joke.
I'll pass then.
I wouldn't be satisfied with just looking anyway.
So you want to have sex then?
Wanna do it?
If she...
... really was a classmate of mine, this would not have normally happened.
But since it's my first time meeting her...
Even if I have my way with her now, all that will change will be our relationship as online gamers
There's no need to hold back or debate on the consequences.
Your pants are starting to bulge.
It looks painful so allow me to let it out.
So you're already this aroused?
Does it feel good?
Hey, mind using your mouth instead?
I see...
Well then...
It's okay to move my head anyway you like.
Please do whatever you want in order to feel good.
Just who is this girl?
She's enthusiastically sucking the cock of a man
She's just met
But it feels good...
Her tongue that delectably twirls around...
Crap, I'm about to cum.
Your cock,
is still lively, isn't it?
Here,
my pussy will be even more pleasurable compared to my mouth.
I-It feels like...
It's extremely wet and it's sucking me in.
It quickly went all the way in.
Please enjoy my pussy to your heart's content.
Of course.
I-I'm...
... having sex with a girl that I've just met.
It's really wet,
totally soft, and perfectly warm.
I would have definitely cum immediately,
If she hadn't given me a blow job earlier.
I can't get enough of this!
How is it?
Does it feel good,
inside my pussy?
your cock is rubbing my insides. It's totally...
your insides feel really good,
but your expressionless face is killing the mood.
I am sorry.
Wow
I never thought that a female body could feel this great.
All the fleshy insides surround and stimulate my cock.
The sensation totally envelopes me.
This is the best sex toy I could ever have!
It's okay.
Do anything that you want.
Make a total mess of me.
I'll do exactly that.
Let's take it up a notch.
Raise your butt.
I just realized that I am back to using my coarse tone.
I'm loosing logical traction on the situation.
The only thing on my mind is the sensation of this flesh rubbing against me.
Are you about to cum?
What do you want me to do?
You can cum inside.
I'm safe today.
that's great then.
I didn't have any plans on pulling out until the very end anyway!
I'm going to release it all inside!
I'm cumming.
When I came back to my senses,
I realized I was on top of her with my teeth dug into her nape,
all the while releasing my semen inside her.
Even though she claimed it was a safe day for her,
the feeling of shooting my load deep inside her womb was something else.
My mind was completely engulfed with the fantasy that I just knocked this girl up,
and did so while dominating her completely.
After that...
Until the very end of the karaoke session, we stayed connected together.
Then we parted ways, without exchanging any contact details or even our real names
Sacchan...
Sacchan!
It's morning already.
Wake up!
Sacchan!
If you don't wake up, I'm going to bite you!
There's nothing better than,
a soft munch the very first thing in the morning.
So it's already morning, huh?
That's my cousin
Yep! I did my best!
Good girl, good girl!
Here, take my revenge!
Oh, no!
Sacchan?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I may be only able to listen,
but it'd feel better if you talk about it.
Then,
I'll attack here this time!
Hey, no fair Sacchan! No...!
Uncle...
What's wrong?
Kotarou-kun...
What are you doing to Ninjin?
No, this is...!
Good morning, Fujieda.
Good mor- Wait, what happened to your face?
My uncle apparently can't take jokes.
What?
Well, they're letting me stay there for free, so I can't really complain.
There are a lot of things going around in your household too, huh?
Hey, Sugawara. Have you hears of the love seminar?
Love seminar?
It's the hottest gossip of the town lately.
Within the log house deep in the mountains,
you can seek consultation regarding any problems involving love and relationships apparently.
What's with that?
Are you trying to hint on something here?
Well, I was just kinda interested, that's all...
So, bad idea?
Text on Paper: I don't need to go to a such place just to tell you that I love you.
You're at it again!
Sugawara?
Azami, please take care of my attendance call.
Azami?
It's the first time that he called me by my first name.
Maybe I should give it a try?
That seminar...
That was her.
It's definitely her.
I had planned on ignoring her if she really turned out to be a student of my school...
One fine day...
I mindlessly fucked someone randomly at the spur of the moment.
Yet...
Here I am, instinctively chasing her down.
There is only one answer to that.
and that sensation...
Oh, yes.
We haven't introduced ourselves, right?
I'm working as a concierge representative of this academy.
My name is Minagami Hitsuji.
Normally, I stay here overnight and hold the keys to the school as well.
If you feel like it, you can always drop by and visit here.
I'm sorry, Azami.
I'm not really sure how,
but I seem to have found a sex friend.
Sacchan!
It's morning already. Wake up!
So he stayed somewhere else again last night?
I'll bite him!
Sacchan is a problem child, isn't he?
Did you see him?
Isn't he doing this practically every day?
Yeah, that's right.
He's slowly becoming a delinquent day by day.
That's not right, is it?
Maybe I should be a bit more strict with Sacchan.
But that's because I think that I'm now his parent.
Understand, Ninjin?
Yeah, I understand.
Oh, yes.
Why don't you go fetch Sacchan from school?
If you go for him like that, I'm sure he's going to come back home.
Okay!
I'm going to fetch Sacchan!
That's right.
Thank you,
Ninjin.
Sugawara-san? The club room's not that way,
Senpai?
Geez, I texted you a lot already. Didn't you read them?
I'm sorry, I seem to have forgotten my phone.
Do we have club activities today?
Not really,
but I just wanted to consult you about something.
Is it okay to ask for a few minutes with you?
Today is a bit, well...
My schedule's really slammed, so...
Next time I'll help you for sure!
Hey, wai-!
Geez, acting all sneaky like that.
Is he hiding something?
Ninjin,
I want you to find out why Sacchan isn't coming home lately.
It's possible that he might be influenced by bad friends.
Then I'm going to take a bit out of him and make him open his eyes.
In here?
S-Sacchan?!
What's going on?
You're getting extremely wet.
This isn't just my semen, right?
Your secretions are also mix in it!
Feels great, right?
Say it.
It feels good.
I'm getting horny.
No way...
Sacchan is... Sacchan is...
What's wrong?
You were supposed to fetch Sacchan, right?
Umm, you see...
Sacchan is...
This is enough!
That's enough already.
Seems like you witnessed something painful.
There, there.
It's okay. Uncle's here.
It seems he was at the right place at the right time.
Now everything will go according to my plan.
Now, I'm going to carry you there,
Ninjin-chan.
To the sanctuary...
Where am I?
It tickles...!
I'm being licked...!
Sacchan!
After about 30 minutes,
Ninjin started showing signs of arousal.
She gazes at me, her eyes filled with lustful anticipation like a mate.
Now it's time.
Now it's time to take away her virginity.
Is this a... cock?
This is the thing my friend used to talk about...
The thing that is inserted in a girl's...
And with that, both boy and girl can start feeling good.
At that time,
Sacchan and... that girl also...
What's this?
It feels tingly and hot down there!
It's Ninjin-chan's...
Ah, amazing.
Her face has lust written all over it.
Her pussy is now starting to get wet and everything around it is really getting twitchy.
You're aroused.
I'm going to put it in now.
This thing that would amplify your pleasure...
It's entering me.
Wow. This is incredible.
It's narrow and feels really tight,
but the soft and tender sensation is all around me.
It feels great.
My head's about to go crazy.
Now my dream is fulfilled!
My insides... feel full.
That's right, that's fine.
Because your pussy is now this hot, drippy and wet.
It's okay, it's okay...
Nipple...
Ohh... Ninjin is aggressively enjoying this as well.
What a pervert...
Making a face like that while having sex with a masked man, you're really helpless.
Please don't rub it in too much.
Sacchan...
What should I do?
It feels great...
If you keep on doing that...
I'm going to lose it...!
That's right...
Ninjin-chan, you're really getting into the mood, right?
It feels so good, I'm about to cum.
Something's coming out!
Something is bursting inside of me!
It...
It felt great...
That felt really great, so...
Mr. Alien,
you can put your cock if you want to.
Ni-Ninjin! you...
Yes...
Yes!
Am- Amazing...
If you keep doing it intensely like that...
It feels hot...
Ninjin-chan, you reallr are something!
Falling in love with the stranger who's fucking you...
You are such a little slut!
Something... Something's coming...!
Ninjin-chan,
here's your reward!
No, stop...!
I'm going to cum
I'm going to cum!
Ninjin-chan!
Amazing.
It's an amazing feeling!
It's the best.
Oh, no!
Something's coming out...
Please, do me more...
I planned on creating a love utopia,
using this seminar.
In this place, any kind of love taboo is warmly accepted.
Even we ourselves can fully make love to each other here.
It's like a dream come true, isn't it?
And then,
we'll slowly increase the numbers of our brethren.
Are you willing to assist me from now on,
Hitsuji?
Yes.
That's why you need something called "Change",
Azami.