Doesn't it feel good?
Huh?
You seem to be thinking about something else.
Nah, it's nothing.
I don't know what Hitsuji thinks of me,
but I don't have any romantic feelings for her.
As I try to sink myself in the sensation of her body,
something in me changed.
I now I find myself thinking about Azami from time to time.
I guess having long hair does make one look a lot more feminine.
I'm about to cum.
Yes.
Sugawara often says that I'm cute, but I know he just enjoys saying it to me.
He usually pets my head, and I feel happy whenever he does it.
I really feel happy when that happens.
I think you've finally made the first step .
You've done well, Azami.
Azami, it's already late.
There is an available room upstairs.
You can spend the night there.
O-okay.
H Ni Juu
Memory
I can change.
Even I can change myself.
Sugawara, I'm going to become more straightforward.
If I do so...
Hello Azami.
Stop.
Let go of me.
No!
No, no, no.
Don't lick me down there.
Don't Touch me down there.
No!
What's this?
Oh no...
It tickles.
I'm bound like this...
Being touched wherever they want...
I'm supposed to be scared, but...
No way...
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, not so fast there.
Stop.
Oh yeah.
You want this, right?
Itadakimasu.
It hurts!
Help me...
Huh? I can't speak...
It hurts, and I'm afraid.
What are they talking about?
I can't understand what they're saying.
I'm getting violated by all of them.
Come on.
It hurts, it hurts.
Why they're all moaning like that?
Help me!
Somebody notice me!
Ouch!
I'm being devoured.
I'm being devoured by these men.
I fearfully know that my holes are being stretched wide.
I can feel that their penises are going to release something anytime soon.
And this is my first time.
Even though it hurts...
Why? Why wont these people stop?
I don't want this!
I don't want any of this!
Oh baby!.
This is great!
Oh yeah!
Eat it!
No!!!
Such big hands...
Azami.
It's big, and warm.
I wonder why.
They've already done such cruel things
but the warmth from touching each other feels very endearing.
I still feel numb from being "devoured" down there
but if they are gentle with me
I think that I could endure it all.
Do it gently, okay?
Please.
It's entering me again.
But it isn't so painful.
Is it because my pussy opened up?
Oh, he hugs me tighter the more I relax myself.
He's trying to support my body.
It makes me feel safe.
It's warm.
I really shouldn't have felt good,
but somehow I feel happy about it.
Umm, huh?
Why is it bad to do this kind of thing again?
It's just fine to do it, right?
Everyone's will be happy.
Because my body tells me that it's okay.
I just feel it in me.
He's getting a little faster again.
I'm scared.
I feel a tingling sensation, and it's a wonderful feeling.
I see.
So feeling another person's warmth inside your body makes a person happy.
It's coming out.
I can feel it pouring out inside me.
so warm.
I'm not alone anymore...
After that, I've started having sex with them many times over.
It hurts and yet it feels little bit good at the same time.
But more than that,
the fact that another person can touch you like this feels like a good thing.
before I knew it, I found myself unconsciously drawn to them, to their bodies.
The thing that I was looking for...
The thing that I craved for, I finally found it.
A person's warmth.
These people are the same as you.
They came here to fill the void in their hearts.
Though it seems that they already like you.
This place is a sanctuary.
Nothing in the outside world matters to what happens here.
Think of it this way and you will feel much better.
It's okay.
I believe that you're capable of finding the answer yourself.
Soon you'll come back here again to visit.
Azami.
That's right.
The only thing that can fill the void in my heart
is this love seminar.
Azami.
You look down.
Azami lately doesn't come to school.
And I can't even face Hirugawa-senpai.
Isn't that good?
Want to have sex?
Is that the first thing you suggest to someone who's depressed?
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
It'll only make me feel more depressed.
In that case...
So, why are we at a karaoke again?
Revenge.
This time, I'm going to sing properly.
Wait, so she's actually into it?
She still has the same straight face
but she is trying to be considerate in her own way.
I thought that it was okay even if one had few friends.
But when you can't even talk to even one single friend,
it gets really tough.
You see, I know we're just sex friends, and this might seem a bit imposing to you,
but it seems I'm not at fault for what happened before, but...
What are you talking about?
Like I said...
Can we stop having sex for a while and just be normal friends?
So, can't we?
It's okay, let's be friends then.
So you really wont smile even for a bit, would you?
Well, you always have that straight face.
I just thought it would be nice if you smiled once in a while.
L-like this?
That's a really strange way to smile.
It's been a long time since I enjoyed myself this much.
Maybe I should try visiting home and play with Ninjin sometimes.
Huh..?
You can't move your body, can you?
Hirugawa.
Hanagi-sensei.
Some strange girl spoke to me recently.
She asked me to buy one of hers.
I know that it was wrong to do it,
but she said that I was free to do it.
That it would feel really good.
No!
H-Ni Juu
Stop.
They are so soft.
My body feels very fuzzy.
It's as if the surface of my skin is being shaken by something.
Hey hey...
Try licking the tip.
Come on do it .
No!
It felt so good that I came immediately.
Hirugawa.
It feels awful.
Now, now. It's a waste to spill it.
You learned about sex education during health class, right?
You can't conceive a child without it.
You're actually supposed to insert it here.
No stop!
No!!!
This is great!
Hirugawa and I are having sex!
Stop!
Pull that dirty thing out right now!
Hirugawa, Hirugawa! I love you, I love you!
Stop that.
I don't want to hear those foul words.
I don't want to hear it!
No! don't cum inside!
I can still go on.
It's still very energetic.
That's good for you, ain't it?
I can cum as many times as I want to!
Please don't!
No...
Contrary to my cries
my body feels warm and tingly.
The sensation of his cock rubbing in me,
makes my insides shiver.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to make you happy.
Forgive me.
Please forgive me.
Yeah, I forgive you,
so pour lots of it into my pussy, please!
Even when I'm ashamed like this,
the pleasure and excitement becomes etched into my mind.
I can no longer resist.
It seems that resisting is only a waste of time.
Yes...
Sensei, it feels great.
I feel really horny.
And my heart is pounding.
Sensei, having sex with you feels great!
Seems that you have finally giving into it, eh?
Your attitude now looks much better than what it used to be!
Now you and I can have sex every day.
This is great.
This is the best!
Make me cum more!
Hirugawa let's go to the love seminar.
Let's leave this reality, and let's indulge in it at another place.
I'm cumming.
Fill me with lots of it sensei!
I'm cumming again!
Here, from now on I'm going to give you a lot of my semen.
Please do!
Pour it all inside me!
You only need to cause a spark.
A four-person love orgy.
Sex between teacher and student.
Humans hold many kinds of taboos.
And we have our own Utopia.
And the only way to it, is through our love seminar.
Hey
can we stop having sex for a while and just be normal friends?
Koutarou-san...
Sorry. It was me.
I'm the one who invited Azami-san to the love seminar.
I was also the one who trapped  Hirugawa-senpai using that teacher.
You should've just kept giving me the cold shoulder, as you always had.
Are you crying?
I sneaked in to try and surprise you.
But I'm surprised because you're crying Hitsuji.
That's not good.
I'm happy that you were able to fulfill all my requests
but you don't have to force yourself.
Why are you here?
I came to pick you up.
Thanks to you, the number of members attending the love seminar have increased.
You don't need to be here.
There is already a sufficient amount of donations.
The house is almost complete.
Then, I...
Here now...
I've really made you work a lot, haven't I?
But it's okay now.
The day for us to be together has finally come.
Now, speak the name of the one you want to be your husband.
Tsubaki.
senpai?
Everyone...
Disappeared right infront of me.
Azami...
Senpai..
Ninjin...
And now, even Hitsuji has...
What in the world is happening ?
Are there still disappearing incidents?
Is there something I can find?
What's wrong with this computer?
There's nothing in here.
Huh?!
What are these image files?
She's smiling...
I've never seen her smile like.
Now Hitsuji.
Take this as a token of our sexual indulgence.
Yes, master.
Kissing with Tsubaki feels normal to me, and it's been that way for a very long time.
Is it because of my relations with Tsubaki that person is now gone?
But, because I love Tsubaki I try not to think too much about it .
And I had sex with him.
Hitsuji.
This is her
Did you know that females remember the taste of the first semen that their wombs have taken?
Hitsuji.
I want to...
I want to feel that tingling ecstasy more, Tsubaki.
What the hell is this?
Hey Tsubaki
my pussy already wants to do it.
It's throbbing.
It feels tingly.
From now on, you don't need to take a pill.
You will give birth to my child, Hitsuji.
Tsubaki.
My beloved...
Hey Tsubaki...
Do you like me?
Of course.
If so then... then I want to be your wife.
Your pussy feels great Hitsuji?
I love it, I love this.
Are you okay with having sex with me, and have a good time like this?
Yes, yes I am.
Every woman actually wants to have a dick in her pussy.
Even before you're born,your body already knows what it tastes like.
So don't leave me for someone else.
Let's stick more closely together.
Let's have some real sex, Tsubaki.
My pussy feels delighted!!!
Thrust it... Thrust it in more deeply.
You really enjoy it deep, eh Hitsuji?
You always caress me there.
And you always know where to hit my soft spots.
Your cock is really great!
Hitsuji, you're my sex pet.
Make sure to drink it all up like an animal!
All your semen will go all the way inside the womb this way.
I want it to open more with your dick!
I'm cumming, Hitsuji.
It feels good.
Your cock is great.
Your cock is great...!
It's coming out.
This hot thing, your semen...
It's all coming out.
It's been years since I had sex with you, so it just wont stop.
It's flowing endlessly.
Then, will I bear children now?
Hey Tsubaki.
Do you love me?
Yes I love.
And we are going to  have sex every day?
Of course.
Then... then I want to be your wife.
Okay, I understand.
Now I'm going to create a paradise
where we can openly make love with each other.
A love paradise.
So everyone is there now?
What the hell...
What the heck is that paradise?
Hitsuji?
Hitsuji!
Hitsuji I want to create a love paradise.
Do you want to help me?
Yes.
H-Ni Juu
hentai-ni-juu.blogspot.com