This is coercion you know.
I'm well aware.
That's why if we can't defeat you in ten days,
then we'll leave this academy.
I'm the one being threatened here, so I have no
choice but to agree to this condition, do I?
Well then, time is precious so, shall we start right away?
Do as you wish.
Ten days... I just have to endure this for ten days.
It's big.
As I thought, it's way too big!
Rin-nee, you like it from behind, don't you?
If I'm being forced into this, there's no way I'd feel that good!
But your pussy is way tighter than it was a second ago.
Shut up! Don't lie!
It's almost as if I want Souma to do me.
Why does it feel so good?
Even though I'm being raped by a student... by Souma.
Why?!
Why?
That's because your body and soul wants Kimishima-kun.
I'd never wish for anything like that.
There's no way I want to do it with Souma.
I'm cummmg Rin-nee. I'm going to cum inside you!
N-No! S-Stop it right now!
Don't cum inside me!
Rin-nee!
I told you to stop...!
I'm cumming again!
I guess we don't need ten days after all.
The last volume
10 soaking wet days
Day 2
Good morning, Rin-nee. Did you finally wake up?
Stop it... No more...
I'll serve you some special milk.
Enough. I don't want it!
Day 3
If you don't make me cum quickly, then someone
might come in here, you know.
What class do we have this afternoon again?
Modern Japanese
Ah, with Kazama-sensei.
Kazama-sensei.
I'm actually looking forward to it.
Let's continue.
Day 4
Not in a place like this.
If some student sees us...
If we don't do it in a place like this, we can't
show anyone the moment you cum.
There's no way I can do something like that!
No good, I can't hold it any longer!
Did you really want my semen that much?
I guess it's about time.
Nurse's office
3 days remaining
It feels good.
It's been a while since I've felt Kimishima-kun's dick.
I've wanted it all this time!
Hazuki-sensei!
Why with Mizushiro-sensei?
Kazama-sensei, I'm sorry but...
I'll be borrowing Kimishima-kun's dick for a little while longer.
I'm only here to get on with the challenge. It's
not like I actually want to do it with Souma.
While we're doing it, I'll let you borrow this, Kazama-sensei.
Use this while watching the two of you have sex, you mean.
I'll switch with you when I feel satisfied.
T-This is big.
It's like Souma's dick coming inside me.
Both the stiffness and the thickness are the same.
My pussy is gripping Kimishima-kun's cock all by itself!
Getting myself wet with something like this...
It's almost as if I want Souma's thing inside me.
If you cum inside me now, I'll definitely get pregnant!
Mizushiro-sensei's pussy is getting all foamy.
I want it too.
It's leaking out!
My pussy is filling up with semen!
I'm also camming. I'm going to cum with something like this!
Why can't I cum? It's supposed to be the same
shape as Souma's so it should feel good.
What's with that dick-craving face?
I'm not making any such face.
More importantly are you guys fine with this? You'll
be leaving this place in three days you know.
Well, when that time comes...
I'm willing to take responsibility
and look after Kimishima-kun.
It's my fault that something like this happened.
After we leave this academy, I was thinking of continuing
my sex life with Kimishima-kun in my apartment instead.
Did we ever make a promise like that?
No.
Isn't that good? Now you no longer
need to have sex with him.
That's so unfair.
I... too...
I too want Souma's dick! I want to make love to Souma!
Rin-nee?
Forgive me, Souma.
I was really happy to know you had feelings for me.
But...
I am your teacher and you are my student. Having a
relationship with you would be unforgivable, wouldn't it?
I think that's why I also became a lot stricter than
necessary, to put some distance between us.
That's so like you, the strict Kazama-sensei.
Th-Then, that means...
I admit it.
I admit it!
I love you!
I love you, Souma!
Now I know it's selfish to ask this of you, but...
I don't want something like this. Please love me
like you love Mizushiro-sensei!
Really? Then would you also bear my children?
Y-Yes! Please let me bear your children as well!
Rin-nee!
It feels great! I came just by sticking it in!
Amazing! Is this what real sex is like?
It's pounding me deep inside.
Your dick is kissing my womb!
Rin-nee... Rin-nee!
It's good. Souma's raw dick feels so good!
It's reaching all the way to the back!
I'm cumming!
Bear my child, Rin-nee!
Y-Yes!
I'll bear your child!
Let me bear my beloved Souma's child!
It's coming! It's flowing into me!
After that, if you're wondering what
happened to the three of us...
Souma's dick juice is so tasty!
Let it out. Let me drink it too!
I want to drink Souma's semen so bad!
I'm cumming. Both of you!
It's like I'm having sex with my stomach.
The pressure I'm feeling from both of your bellies is amazing.
When I feel Souma's dick rubbing
against me with the baby inside...
It almost makes me cum from that alone.
The same counts for me. Souma.
Hurry up, cover us up with a load of your hot stuff!
Pour all of your thick semen on
these expanded bellies of ours!
Please take care of these holes next.
Please make us feel good with your dick.
There's a big thing coming inside of me!
So rough!
It's hitting me deep inside!
Souma, stick it in this hole as well. Hurry!
This dick is amazing!
It feels so good!
I'm cumming! I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming as well!
We're going to cum together!
It's so...!
I'm cumming!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
Both of you, turn this way and say peace.
Peace!
Pea... Peace...
Someday, with Souma, and his kid...
With the three of us...
translator: maq-kun
translation check: jimaku-danshaku
timing: v1toush
typesetting: haidaraaaaa
editor: punk4real