Souma, I'll always protect you, okay?
Don't you have that backwards?
I'm the man, so I should be protecting you.
Yeah, I guess you're right. I look forward to it.
Her name is Rinne Kazama.
She lives next door. I love her like a big sister.
She's been looking after me ever since I was a kid.
However, for some reason, she's become
rather indifferent as of late.
It's gotten to the point where she won't
give me a straight answer anymore.
Even though we're finally in the same school,
it's become so awkward that I can't even look
her in the eye, let alone try to confess to her
– Yesterday, you see...
– Oh, really?
I decided to express my feelings for
her through another method.
Alright, before we start today's class,
I have something to show you guys.
I wonder if Rin-nee read the letter.
You see, this is a love letter addressed to me.
Why? Why is she
taking it out in front of everyone?
I'm showing this to all of you for one simple reason.
Let me make this clear. This is my answer.
Nurse's Office
...and that's what happened.
Don't you think she was a bit harsh?
And because of that, you hate Kazama-sensei now?
Is that it?
No, well, it's not like I hate her...
So, you still love her?
Well that's, um, y-yeah...
I see.
Here, take this.
What is it?
It's a supplement that increases your popularity.
What? Seriously?
I'm serious.
Does it really work?
If you take it, you might be able to
finally go out with Kazama-sensei.
How is it?
Hmm, even if you're asking me that...
W-What?
My body... what's happening?
Oh? This is quite something.
Wai... P-Please don't look!
I can't perform a medical examination if I don't look, right?
Mmm, I see.
W-What do you mean "I see?".
I'm saying that this erection is a
side effect of the supplement.
S-Side effect?
I'm sure of it.
What should I do about it?
In this case, ejaculation is your best option.
W-What are you doing!?
Well, it's my fault that it's gotten like this.
T-that's true, but...
You don't want me to?
My heart already belongs to Rin-nee.
But, of course, if you ask me if I like
Hazuki-sensei or not, then...
Doing it with your mouth all of a sudden?
Whoa! She's licking it.
Hazuki-sensei is licking it!
Amazing. Sensei, it feels great!
Not yet. I'm going in deeper!
This is bad, Sensei...
Something incredible is coming out!
You can let it out any time, okay?
Uh, Sensei, I'm sorry. Please, spit it out.
Eh?
Just what is this? To think that his semen would be so tasty...
Ahh... it feels so good!
My pussy is restless from drinking semen. I can't hold back!
Eh? No way!
I'm cummmg. I'm going to cum!
I'm c-cummmg!
Sensei, are you alright?
Y-Yeah.
Just ejaculating once doesn't seem
to have alleviated the effect...
This is, uh... I'm sorry.
Don't let it bother you. I'll take care
of it until it reverts back to normal.
I want it. I want to be stirred up by this penis deep inside!
Just by sucking on your cock, I've already become like this.
I'm sorry that I'm not Kazama-sensei, but
is it okay if I become your first woman?
P-Please do!
Well then, here I come.
I put it in. Kimishima-kuns cock is inside my pussy!
How is it, the body of your first lady?
It's awesome! I feel like I'm gonna cum immediately!
It's fine. Cum inside whenever you feel like it.
Come on!
I have to take it slow, I'm going to cum first if go any faster.
Today's a safe day, so it's fine to let out as much as you want.
Sensei! Hazuki-sensei!
N-no! D-Don't be so rough!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum from this virgin dick!
Please cum! Hazuki-sensei, please cum together with me!
Cum inside! Inside my pussy!
C-C-Cumming! I'm camming!
It's coming! There's so much of it inside my pussy...
How was it, having sex with me?
To have sex with such a gorgeous lady...
It was the best.
But...
What is it?
You went so far as to do it with me just
to test the effects of the supplement.
I was wondering if that was okay with you.
Oh, just that?
"Just that?"
If that's the case, then it's no problem.
In fact, even if it was like that, I'm happy
to have done it with the one I love.
Huh? Love?
You love me?
It's the truth.
I've been in love with you for a while now. I may be a
little eccentric, but you've always kept me company.
S-Sensei!
W-Wait!
I still have to tell you about the other side effects!
It's become really late, hasn't it.
What is he doing at this time?
How that I think about it, Souma joined a suspicious
club that Mizushiro-sensei started, didn't he...
Amazing!
I'm cumming again!
My pussy's being messed up by Kimishima-kun's penis!
Huh?
R-Rin-nee...
You liar.
Mizushiro-sensei, I am reporting this to the school board.
You've got it all wrong, Rin-nee!
T-This is part of the treatment!
Are you messing with me?
No, I'm not!
Hazuki-sensei and I got like this due to the effects of a supplement I took.
It was to help Sensei with her research!
I don't have any intention of believing a story like that.
And no matter the reason, having
a relationship with your student...
You're a failure as a teacher, Mizushiro-sensei.
Indeed, it's just as you said.
S-Sensei...
Forgive me, Kimishima-kun, but the effects
of the supplement were still unknown.
No way!
Why won't you believe us, Rin-nee!?
I can't believe a single word coming from the mouth of a liar.
W-What do you mean "liar"?
Shut up. Of course, I'll have you
accept fair punishment as well.
Why!? Why won't you believe me!?
Don't make me repeat myself, liar.
Dammit! All of this is making me mad!
Aside from what she did to my love letter,
why am I being treated so poorly!?
Are you done talking?
I'll make you believe me.
If you don't get my explanation, then I'll
make you understand with my body.
W-What is it?
H-Hey!
If what Hazuki-sensei said was true, then
this should make Rin-nee fall for me.
W-Wait!
I still have to tell you about the other side effects.
Huh? There's more?
It appears that your penis and other body fluids can
cause people to climax if there's any contact.
S-Stop.
Anymore will...
Stop it!
What is this? My body is...
You understand now, don't you?
You came just from a kiss, after all.
There's no way that's true, right?
I explained it before, didn't I? My body isn't normal right now.
There's no proof that I came. None!
Oh, is that so?
S-Stop!
You... Don't think about doing anything stupid!
I won't stop until Rin-nee believes me.
My body feels so weak.
I-I told you to wait, didn't I?
I-It went in!
This cock... inside me...
I'm Rin-nee's first man.
Something so big... Impossible...
Hurry up! Take...
It's alright, Rin-nee.
I'll make you feel good right away.
As if something like this could ever feel good...
It only hurts!
My body is becoming hot.
My pussy throbs whenever he pushes it in.
Stop it! I'll start going crazy!
Lose yourself more.
You can't! Don't stir it up!
It's reaching into the very end!
Ugh, it's impossible!
There's no way I can endure this!
It's coming again!
An amazing one is coming!
Show me how you cum. I'm going to cum as well!
Cumming!
I'm cumming!
Souma's semen is making me cum!
I admit that your body is pretty abnormal at the moment.
If that wasn't the case, I would have
never done something like that.
T-Then that means...
No, the fact that Mizushiro-sensei
must resign hasn't changed.
Wha...
Also, you will withdraw from this school.
P-Please wait!
Isn't it obvious?
Did you think I'd forgive you after
you did something like that?
Are you okay with that, Kazama-sensei?
You'll regret it if you expel him, you know.
What do you mean by that?
It's simple: Kazama-sensei is in love with Kimishima.
Huh?
O-On what basis are you making that joke?
There's no mistaking it.
I'm confident.
You hold feelings of love for him.
Even if you deny it with your brain, your heart says it all.
So? I shouldn't expel Souma?
That's right.
That's just dumb.
Well then, how about something like this?
If I make you realize your true feelings within ten days,
you'll accept we're right and revoke the punishment.
Do you think I would accept a nonsensical challenge like that?
You have no right to refuse, you know.
An amazing one is coming!
Y-You were recording it!?
Show me how you cum. I'm going to cum as well!
Just in case something like this happened.
This is blackmail!
I understand that.
That's why, if I don't succeed within ten days,
we will bid farewell to this school.
I'm being threatened here
I have no other choice but to accept that condition, right?
Alright then. Since there's little time,
shall we begin now?
Hmph. Do as you like.
Ten days. I just have to hold it together for ten days...
Translator: Maq-kun | Hikarukon
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Sill | Punk4Real