That's right.
I'm going to always protect you.
No you're not.
I'm the guy, so I'm going to protect you, Rin nee-chan.
I guess that's true.
I'm looking forward to it then.
Her name is Kazama Rinne.
She's our neighbor and the Onee-san that I really adore.
She's been taking care of me ever since I was little.
However, lately she's been keeping her distance from me,
and she doesn't really talk to me that much anymore.
We attend the same school now.
And yet, because of this I'm unable to properly confess to her.
So I decided to convey my feelings in another way.
Now then,
I have something to show to the class before we begin.
Rin-nee, I wonder if you read the letter I sent to you.
This is a love letter that was addressed to me.
Why?
Why is she pulling that out in front of everyone?
There's only one reason why I showed this to you all.
I'll just come out and say it.
This... is my answer.
Infirmary
And that's how it happened.
Don't you think that was too cruel?
And so, that's what made you hate Kazama-sensei.
Is that it?
No, well...
It didn't really make me hate her...
Then you still love her?
Well, I...
Yeah, I guess.
I see.
Here.
What are these?
Supplements that will boost your appeal.
Huh? Is that for real?
I'm serious.
Do these even work?
If you take those, then you might have
a chance to be with Kazama-sensei.
Well?
Even if you ask that...
Whoa, what is this?
What's happening to my body?
Oh, this is quite something.
Wait! Please don't look!
We can't examine that if I can't see it well.
Hmm... I see.
I see? What do you mean?
This arousal was a side effect of the drug I gave you.
S-Side effect?
I can definitely say this with certainty.
So... what should I do with it?
I suppose the best thing to do here is to simply let it ejaculate.
Wh-What are you trying to do?!
Well, I am responsible for this after all.
Y-You're right, but...
You're not satisfied with me doing it?
But the one for me is...
Though, if I were to ask if I love or
hate Hazuki-senset, of course I...
Using the mouth so suddenly?!
She's licking it.
Hazuki-sensei is licking my dick!
Wow...
Sensei, that really feels good.
We're just... getting started.
This isn't good, sensei!
Something really big is about to burst out!
Just cum whenever you want, okay?
Sensei, I’m sorry.
Just go ahead and spit it out.
What is this?
I never imagined cum could taste this good.
That's really good!
The taste of cum is enough to arouse my pussy.
Huh? No way...
I'm cumming,
I'm going to cum!
Se-Sensei...
Are you alright?
Y-Yeah.
Seems the side effect didn't go away with just one ejaculation.
This is, well...
I-I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I'm going to take care of it till it's not aroused.
I want it.
I want to be stirred by this dick.
It's already become like this after just sucking your dick.
Sorry if I'm not Kazama-sensei,
but would it be alright for me to be your first woman?
Please do.
Alright, here I go then.
It's in.
Kimishima-kun's dick is inside me.
How is it?
How does it feel to fuck your first girl?
It's amazing.
It feels like I'm about to cum at any moment.
It's alright.
Just cum whenever you want to.
Cum inside me anytime.
Here.
As I gently move my hips, I feel like I'm
the one who's going to cum first.
It's safe today,
so you don't have to hold back.
Sensei!
Hazuki-sensei!
Don't...
If you...
keep on... pushing hard like that...
It's going to make me cum.
I'm going to cum with this virgin dick!
Please... cum.
Hazuki-sensei, let's cum together!
Cum inside me.
Cum in my pussy.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
You're cumming inside me.
It's going to fill my pussy...
So, how did it feel to have sex with me?
I never thought my first time would
be with such a beautiful woman.
It was the best.
But...
What's wrong?
You had to have sex with me just to alleviate the side effects.
I was wondering if this was really okay with you.
Oh, so that's what you meant.
You're calling it just 'that'?
I have no problems with it.
In fact, I was even happy to be one with the
person I like, even under the circumstances.
Huh? Like?
Sensei, you're...?!
I'm telling the truth.
I've love you for a long time.
For all of the days that you've been with a deviant such as I.
Sensei!
Wait!
I still have something to tell you about the drug's side effects...!
It's quite late already.
What are people still doing at this is hour?
Oh yeah, that Souma's into that weird
club that Mizushiro-sensei formed.
Oh wow...
I'm going to cum again.
My pussy is being tiled by your dick!
Ri-Rin-nee...
Liar.
Mizushiro-sensei, I'll have to report this to school principal.
Th-This isn't what you think, Rin-nee!
Th-This is...
This is part of my treatment!
Are you fooling around with me?
I'm not!
The reason why we're now doing this,
is because I required her treatment in order to alleviate
the side effects of the supplements I took.
I don't have the slightest intention of believing such a story.
And for a student and teacher to have such a relationship,
you're a failure as a teacher, Mizushiro-sensei.
True, it's as you said, Kazama-sensei!
Se-Sensei...
I'm sorry, Kimishima-kun.
Even though we're still in the middle of your treatment.
No way...
Why won't you believe us, Rin-nee?!
I won't believe the words of a liar.
Liar? What are you talking about?
Shut up.
Of course, you'll also receive ample punishment for this.
Why?!
Why won't you believe us?!
Don't make me repeat myself, liar.
Damn...
I'm starting to get really pissed off.
Not only during the love letter incident,
but why do I have to be constantly treated like this?
Anything more to say?
I'll make you believe then.
If I can't get through to you with words,
then I'll use my body instead.
What?
Hey...
If Hazuki-sensei is right about this,
then I can take her with this!
Wait!
I still have something to tell you about the drug's side effects...!
Huh? There's still other problems?
Aside from your penis,
any partner that gets in contact with your fluids, or your semen,
will be able to reach orgasm.
Stop... this...
Anything more and...
Stop!
Something's welling up...!
Now you know.
You came just with me kissing you.
That... just can't be true...
I've explained it to you already.
That my body right now isn't normal at all.
And what's your evidence that I actually came?
Oh, really now.
Stop...
You're...
Stop this ridiculous foolishness!
I'm not stopping until you believe me.
My body feels weak...
I said wait!
It's, in me...
And this is my first time...
Rin-nee's first man is me!
That big thing is...
Pull it out!
It's alright, Rin-nee.
It'll feel really good soon enough.
How will this feel any better?
It just hurts!
My body feels hot.
My insides feel all tingly as he continues fucking me.
Stop this already.
I'm about to go crazy.
Then get crazier.
You can't...!
Stop stirring me inside!
Stop hitting me deep inside.
I can't take this anymore.
I just can't resist any longer...!
I'm going to cum again.
Show it to me, and I'm going to cum as well.
It's hot!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming while you cum inside me!
Fine, I accept that this indeed is not normal as you say.
If it wasn't, then I wouldn't have...
Th-Then...!
But this does not change my stance on Mizushiro-sensei.
Wha-
You're also going to have to leave this school.
J-Just wait!
Of course you need to.
Do you really think I'll forgive you for doing this to me?
Are you really okay with that, Kazama-sensei?
You're going to regret it if you expel him from this school.
What are you trying to say?
It's simple.
You're in love with Kimishima-kun.
Wh-What proof do you have of such a ridiculous claim?
I'm sure of it.
And I'm confident that I'm not wrong.
You hold feelings of affection for him.
Even if you deny it in your head, your heart openly admits it.
You're telling me not to expel Souma because of that?
Correct.
This is going nowhere.
Then, how about this?
If Kimishima-kuh is able to make you realize
your feelings for him in the next ten days,
then we win, and you shall forget
all about kicking us out of here.
Do you think that I'll accept such a stupid challenge?
You have no right to say no to this.
You recorded it?!
I thought this might be useful for these situations.
This is blackmail.
I know.
Which is why if we're unable to win
you over during those ten days,
we're going to leave the school of our own accord.
I'm the one being blackmailed here.
I have no choice but to agree to your terms.
So, time is of the essence.
Why don't we start right away?
Hmph. Do what you want then.
Ten days.
I just have to restrain myself for ten days...