No. No.
You're so intense,
I don't know what I'll do.
Make sure the wedding dress I'm
going to wear to the wedding...
...won't get stained.
It's already too late.
Your pussy juices are all over it.
But it's on the inside,
so don't worry.
No!
You're terrible.
No?
What are you talking about?
You're all wet down here.
A helpless nymphomaniac you are.
Ow!
Nothing compared to giving birth.
I'll make you feel much better.
Do it more, Yusuke.
Y-Yes. Oh, yes.
It feels so good!
Feels good, huh?
Stop! Please forgive me!
I don't think so.
I want you to feel with your body...
...how much I resent my mother.
Poor woman. Looks at those welts.
You're horrible, Yusuke.
Don't think that this is the last of it.
Are you sure Shiina doesn't
have a boyfriend?
Yeah.
But she's so hot.
You think she's maybe a virgin?
Yeah.
Fantastic!
I'm definitely going to be
the one to pop her cherry.
D-Don't be stupid.
You're not going to be the one.
I'm going to be her man. Me.
How dare they have a fantasy
about a woman.
What fools they are.
Hey.
Yusuke!
Wow! How cute!
It's yours.
I've always wanted one of these.
I'll take good care of it.
Is that all it takes
to make you happy?
It's my first present
from you, after all.
I'm so happy!
I'll give you another first next time.
Yusuke! Shiina! Dinner time!
- Okay!
- Coming!
Come on, Mom. Stand up straight.
B-But...
Shall I give you more pleasure?
No.
We're going out shopping together.
We've got to have lots of fun.
R-Right.
Yusuke, wait a minute.
You don't mean for me
to go in there?
You may protest...
...but look at how wet
you already are.
You actually want it
to stay in there, right?
No, don't take it out.
If you make too much noise,
the old guys outside will hear.
Hey, come over here.
I heard a woman's voice!
- Are you serious?!
- Hey, what're you doing in there?!
Open in! Open it!
Use your hips a little more, Missus.
Suck on it good.
Look at how wet you are.
You sure are getting off on this.
To think I'd get my mom to suck
me off in a place like this.
And this elevator's an express;
straight to the top.
That's good, Mom.
Please, stop.
They'll notice us.
There's no point in worrying now.
Besides, are you sure you
really want me to stop?
Look at you move those hips.
But, that's because you're...
It's amazing. I can't take it.
I think I'm going to cum, too, Mom.
Don't pull it out.
Cum inside of me.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, Mom!
Are you all right, miss? Miss?
Uh, yes.
Well, Mom? What do you
think of shopping with me?
Isn't it fun? Doesn't it feel good?
Isn't it fantastic?
Slam that ass into me, Mom.
It seems like such a waste
not to share all this pleasure.
Next time, let's bring Shiina.
Wait, Yusuke.
It's okay for you to vent your anger
towards your mother on me.
I'll do everything you want me to.
But, please. Please...
...treat Shiina like you
would to a real sister.
Okay. I understand.
It's only my mother
that I can't forgive.
I'm so happy.
More! Fuck me harder!
Fuck me all over!
My brother, huh?
Yusuke.
Please, Yusuke.
Please fuck me!
I'm cumming! I going to cum!
Yusuke!
I'm home!
What did I pick up shopping today?
Who is it? Yusuke?
I have an interesting show
I'm putting on tonight.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, let's go to the room upstairs.
You're tying me up again.
Now, go on in.
H-Hey, wait a minute, Yusuke.
Isn't this Shiina's room?
Okay, Mom. I'm taking
the blindfold off.
Shiina!
All right. Let's begin the show, Mom!
You said... You said that you
wouldn't touch Shiina!
Because you asked me not to,
I had to do it.
My goal after all is to make...
...this nymphomaniac
of a mother suffer!
H-How could you?!
But look at how much
Shiina's enjoying herself.
Will you stay calm?
If you promise me,
I'll let you down.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
It must be nice and tight down here.
And I have a big cock...
...so that'll make it really tight.
Well? Is it getting any better?
I hate liars.
You promised me before
that you'd stay calm.
Now, that's very good.
Your favorite brother is
going to give it to you.
Are you excited?
Mother.
Yusuke.
Please. Please. I want it, too.
I want your nice,
hard cock in me, too.
No. No!
Hurry, Yusuke.
Stick it in my pussy
and fuck me all over!
Mother...
More... More...
I want it more intense!
Y-Yes!
That feels so good! Yusuke!
So? Are things going well
with your new family?
Yeah.
Your sister's name is Shiina, right?
Are you treating her nice?
Yeah, totally.
Oh? So it's going well, then.
Of course! There're no problems!
We're all getting along!
Wh-What are you getting
all upset for?
I'm not getting upset.
You start to act strange when
you talk about your mother.
You're always talking about...
...how much you hate your real
mother, or your stepmother.
But maybe you're actually
starving for motherly love.
Of course not.
Then, why don't you leave
that house and live freely?
I bet you're actually quite
comfortable in that house.
O-Ow! That hurts! Yusuke!
Hold on! Wait a second!
Can't you... Can't you be
a little more gentle?!
Don't be so rough!
Shut up! Keep your mouth shut!
What is this?! I've never
felt like this before!
It's amazing, Yusuke!
How strange.
I didn't realize it until
Mio mentioned it.
When Dad was around,
I wanted to run away so badly.
But now I look forward
to going home.
I always thought of women as
the enemy, and I've hated them.
But yet I'm comfortable living
with such women.
Did I really hate my mother so much?
No. I really did hate her.
I didn't even want to breathe
the same air as her.
In which case, that woman
living in my house...
...who is that mother?
Don't tell me I actually feel for her!
That's crazy!
Yusuke! Yusuke!
What's the matter?
Stopping so suddenly like that.
I was so close.
Shut up!
That feels good!
More! More! Fuck me deeper
and deeper!
Oh, no!
My pussy tingles all over!
No. Yusuke, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
Please, Yusuke. Cum inside of me.
I want to feel you cum inside
of me. Please, I want to feel it!
Y-You're back.
You must be hungry. I'll have
dinner ready in a moment.
I don't care about that.
Where's Shiina?
She left for her grandfather's
place early this morning.
I see.
I guess she just couldn't take it.
The relationship I'm having
with her mother.
Hey, nice lady.
Hey, there. Where are you going?
How about going for a ride with us?
Come on. Hurry up, Mom.
There's no sense in being
embarrassed at this stage.
Let's see it. Let's see you piss.
Please, Mom.
Okay? Will you?
No. I just can't.
Please don't make me do this.
Are you sure you can't?
If you can't, I'll have
to give you an enema...
...and make you embarrass
yourself even more.
Is that okay with you?
That's a lot of piss.
You didn't have to hold it
in for so long.
But it sure has an awfully
strong smell, Mom.
My ass. M-My ass feels so good!
Yusuke, go deeper! Go deeper!
I'm going to burst! I feel like
my pussy's going to burst!
Oh, no!
No?
Look at how wet you are?
It looks like you're getting off
on this, Mom.
Of course you're getting off!
How much of a pervert
are you, Mom?
Oh, Yusuke. That's amazing!
It's amazing.
I've never felt it so good before.
Yusuke!
Yes.
Yes, Yusuke.
Better?
Is it that good?
Then, I'll give you much,
much more!
This woman is enjoying
this sex with me.
This isn't revenge.
Then, what exactly is it
that I'm doing?
You're always talking about...
...how much you hate your real
mother, or your stepmother.
But maybe you're actually
starving for motherly love.
That feels so good!
More! More, Yusuke!
Fuck me hard! Please,
fuck my brains out!
I... I... Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
Mom.
What?
I want you to forgive me
for what I've done to you.
What do you mean?
I'm thinking that I was wrong
about hating my mother.
I realized that I look forward...
...to coming home to
a house with you in it.
It's hard for me to say this...
...but I want you to stay
in this house forever.
So, I beg you.
I'll be nicer to you, so please...
What are you talking about now?
You forced yourself onto us.
And I feel bad about that.
L...
It's already too late.
Then, what should I do?
I want you to be rough with me
and fuck me all over. That's all.
But you hated it when
I did those things.
But I can't stop now.
I can't stand it if I'm not
having sex even for a minute!
Wh-What the...?
Now, come and be rough with me.
I want you to fuck me
until I pass out!
Wait! Yusuke, wait!
How could this...!
How could this have
happened to Mom?!
Is it... Is it all my fault?!
Hey. What're you looking at?
No! Stay away from me!
No!
Officer! This is the man! This man!
Yes. It's this man!
This man forced himself on me!
Sir? Would you mind coming
to the station with me?
First it's stone! Stone,
scissors, paper!
And one more time!
Well, I guess I get to go first.
Hey, don't take too long.
You always take forever.
Yeah. There're others waiting
after you, you know.
Yeah, yeah. I'm going to give her
all the milk I can give her.
Mom.
More.
No... No... You mustn't cum yet.
I-I'm cumming!
M-Me, too!
S-Same here!
You forced yourself onto us.
I want you to be rough with me.
But I can't stop now.
I can't stand it when
I'm not having sex!
I want you to fuck me
until I pass out!
More! I want more!
Hey, you still want more?
Oh, boy. I don't know
if I can handle it.
If you want it that bad,
I'll give it to you in the ass.
Oh, that's so good. More.
More intensely. Please.
How's that?
It's so good!
Just keep fucking both my pussy
and ass until I burst!
More! More! Fuck me harder!
Fuck me to death!
Yusuke.
Hey, will you come here?
I want you, Yusuke!
H-Hey! What're you doing?!
S-Stop it! Stop it!