lt feels good.
No, don't stick it in there...
lt's making me excited...
Stick it inside, Chikara-san...
lt's going inside...
You're too loud, Sayo.
What?
Kai-kun?
Please don't...
l'm sorry, Mother, but l love you.
l couldn't take it anymore.
l can't believe you like me this much...
We shouldn't be doing this...
No, l'll climax...
Me too, Mother...
No...
l'm coming, Mother.
No, not inside!
No!
l placed these hands on my mother...
What are you doing, Kaito? You'll be late for school.
Yeah, l'm leaving now.
l'll be going away on a business trip starting today.
Listen to your mother and stay out of trouble.
Good morning, Mother.
Good morning, Kai-kun.
l'll have your breakfast in just a bit, so you'll just have to wait.
Mother, it's about last night...
Mother?
Stop.
Kai-kun...
When l cut my finger as a kid, you used to do this, remember?
But...
Mother, about last night...
Stop, we shouldn't talk about that.
Why?
l really like you Mother...
No! Don't say that!
No, no! l don't want to hear it!
Mother.
Mother! Calm down!
Mother...
l'm sorry for shouting...
l'm okay now.
Let's just end this conversation.
l want you to do me a favor.
A favor?
You know the documents for the PTA l told you yesterday?
l want you to deliver them to Tamae-san.
Takumi's mother?
You'll do it for me, right?
lt's hard for me to deal with her...
Your house is huge, Takumi!
You think so?
Anyway, l have to give this to his mother.
Since l'm with Takumi, l'm sure she won't get all nasty like last time.
Well, l have to go to a cram school.
What?
Wait a minute.
Since l came all the way out here, let's just go say hi to your mother.
l can't do that...
Because last night, my mother and l...
Last night?
Sorry Kaito!
Takumi!
What was that all about?
That's strange.
She's supposed to be home today.
Excuse me.
Could it be her?
lnside...
lt's going deep inside...
Why is my body getting so hot...
Takumi-chan's hands are touching my boobs...
Touch my boobs, Takumi-chan...
l want you to do me harder...
Yes...
You're so big Takumi-chan...
Your cock is bigger than your father's...
We shouldn't be doing this...
Your father should make love to me more...
Then l won't have to do it with you, Takumi-chan...
l want it...
Not a toy like this, but your cock Takumi-chan...
l want your sizzling, hard cock...
Who's there?
Oh no!
Takumi-chan?
What?
Takumi-chan...
Takumi-chan, right?
What's going on?
Takumi-chan, you should say something when you get home.
You were peeping into my room, you naughty boy.
l'm sorry about last night.
You were masturbating while looking at porno magazines so...
But don't worry.
lf you feel like you have to unload, l'll help you out from here on.
Tamae-san isn't wearing her glasses, she thinks that l'm Takumi.
lf we keep going like this...
Damn it, Takumi.
So this is what he was doing, no wonder he seemed odd...
lt's so hard...
Plus it's getting much bigger.
She's really good...
Does it feel good, Takumi-chan?
Of course it feels good.
My cunt is really wet now.
l want you to stick your huge cock inside, please.
Yes...
l can feel your cock going inside me.
lt's really getting tight inside.
lt feels so good...
Yes, it's inside...
l feel it deep inside!
Yes, that's it Takumi-chan!
Harder... l want to feel you more inside.
You're amazing, Takumi-chan...
l can feel your cock deep inside.
l can't believe l'm doing it with my best friend's mother...
But this is the same thing l did with my mother...
Mother.
lf my boobs and pussy move that hard...
l'll break...
l'll break into pieces...
Now do it from the front...
Yes...
More...
Give me more, Takumi-chan...
lt feels good...
You get to look at my slutty face...
lt's not fair...
l want to see you enjoying this.
What? You are...
What are you doing?
No, get away from me!
You said you wanted my cock, right?
l didn't say that...
You think you can get away with this?
Don't suck on them too hard...
No, it feels good...
Stop moving...
Don't do it so hard...
You're going to climax, right?
Go ahead.
No, this is just...
l'm coming too.
l'm coming!
You released it inside...
Kai-kun.
Your bath is ready, you can go in first.
l'll take it before l sleep, you can go first.
l'll take it later.
You're always taking a bath after us, you should go in first for once.
Kai-kun.
Are you trying to be nice?
Not really.
But you go in first.
All right then, l guess l'll go in first.
Okay.
My father went on a business trip today, now my mother and l can...
l'm all alone with Kai-kun...
Chikara-san, l...
Kai-kun?
What?
Mother...
l'll join you.
l'll help you wash up, Mother.
Stop...
Your boobs are big...
Even if my father finds out, l'll just say l forced you to do this...
l can't let you take the blame...
l want to take all the blame.
You were forced into doing this, it's all my fault.
Kai-kun...
Your nipples are getting hard...
Down here too...
Not there...
No, don't touch it...
Your fingers are going inside!
Kai-kun, you can't touch there.
Stop moving your fingers...
l'm about to...
No! Stop it.
No, it feels good...
No, don't touch there.
l want my cock inside you.
You don't mind, do you?
l want to stick it inside you...
Here l come...
No!
Not in this position.
Don't worry, l'll support you...
Your thing is going inside me...
What thing?
l can't say it...
Why?
l want you to say it, Mother.
Don't say such mean things...
lf you're not going to say it...
Deep...
Your thing is going deep inside...
l'm in such an embarrassing position, but...
lt feels really good, right?
Don't say that, Kai-kun.
lf you say things like that l'll be addicted...
ls it bad to get addicted?
Let's both get addicted.
l want to get addicted with you.
No...
Kai-kun, you're...
You're the only woman for me, Mother!
l only love you!
What...
l'm going to climax!
l'll release it inside.
No, not inside...
You might get me pregnant...
Please...
Fine...
Lots of your white stuff...
Mother...
Kai-kun...
Chikara-san...
Mother, are you asleep?
Kai-kun?
No! Don't come in!
We can't do that kind of thing anymore!
Don't worry, Mother.
l'm not here to do it with you.
l just want to talk to you...
What l said to you before was the truth.
l love you, Mother.
Why Kai-kun?
Why does it have to be me?
You have the chance to meet many more attractive women.
That's true, but l'm the only one for you!
What?
l'm the only man for you now!
What are you talking about?
l still have Chikara-san.
My father might never come back...
He's cheating on you.
l saw him going into a hotel with a younger woman!
Chikara-san is cheating?
Kai-kun!
l'm glad it turned out this way.
Thanks for worrying about me, Kai-kun.
But l already knew.
l knew that Chikara-san didn't have any feelings for me.
l'm sorry for being a bad mother.
l can only do this to respond to your feelings.
l love you, Kai-kun...
l can't believe l'm getting excited by doing this...
Mother!
Kai-kun, l...
l'm happy, you chose me instead of my father.
Are you sure you want to be with a mother like me?
l can be happy with you...
Fine...
l'll get addicted with you...
Yes...
l feel it there too...
l feel it in my ass.
No!
lf you play with it too much...
...l'll pee...
No! You're going to make me pee!
lf you play around that much, l'm really gonna pee!
No!
l'm peeing...
l'm peeing in front of you...
Mother, you're so sexy...
l feel really embarrassed when you watch me.
l can't take it anymore!
Slowly...
lt's my first time taking it up the ass...
l know.
l can feel your thing in my stomach.
So big! Your thing is so big...
Maybe l shouldn't have put it in there.
l'm okay...
l want you to start moving...
Make me feel good in my ass...
Mother! Mother!
Yes, it feels really good...
l think l'll climax soon!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
Go ahead, you can climax as many as you like.
Kai-kun, l'm coming again!
l'm coming, Mother!
No!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
My ass feels hot...
Lots of juice came out.
Kai-kun, l want you to...
Kai-kun, l want you to love me forever.
Mother...
Kai-kun, don't ever let me go...
Some time has gone by since, and my mother and l are still together.
l'm going now.
l don't know if my father is still having an affair or not.
But l didn't care about that anymore...
Kai-kun.
Mother, that child is mine, right?
l don't know about that.
Chikara-san did a good job too.
That's not fair, you shouldn't talk about him in front of me.
Not here...
She will always be my mother even from here on.
l won't let my father have her again.