Kai-kun...
lt's time to get up, Kai-kun...
Mother?
You're a real sleepyhead.
You can't get up without my help.
Now wake up before your breakfast gets cold.
Okay...
Hurry up.
My mother died due to an illness when l was just a little boy.
You can't be lazy just because you don't have school today.
l know...
My father remarried this woman named Sayo-san. She's my new mother.
She's much more important to me than my real mother...
...since l don't remember much about my real mother.
l went to the hospital yesterday.
l'm showing progress with my sterility treatment...
You still go to the hospital?
Yes, l wanted to have your children...
You even said so yourself...
When did we talk about this?
That was many years ago.
You're right but...
l don't need any breakfast, l have to get to work early today.
l know the truth.
My father doesn't want any children...
Feels good...
You're wet, Sayo.
l touched you gently and now you're all wet...
l'm sorry, Chikara-san...
Not there, Chikara-san.
No, stop...
You're such a slut.
lt feels good...
Yes, it feels good...
Yes, yes!
Suck me harder Chikara-san!
More, more! Suck me more!
More! Suck me more!
lt feels good!
No, it feels good...
No, not there!
l can clearly see your pussy.
What do you want me to do?
l want you to make me feel real good.
Chikara-san, please do the inside as well.
No! Don't do it that hard!
More, more!
Yes, it feels good!
Chikara-san!
lf you keep going, l'll climax!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
l'm coming Chikara-san!
Chikara-san, why?
Shut up...
Here, suck on it real good!
Chikara-san...
Come on! Face your ass towards me.
Yes, it feels good!
Chikara-san, if you keep moving that hard, you're going to mess me up.
lf you make that loud of a noise, you're going to wake up Kaito!
l'm sorry, but your cock is running wild inside me and it feels so good!
lt's inside... lt's going deep inside!
Your cock is going deep inside me!
This is amazing...
Your hard cock is rubbing inside me.
Do it hard so that l'll break into pieces.
Chikara-san!
l can't hold it.
l'm coming, Sayo.
No...
Chikara-san, l still haven't...
l'm coming.
Chikara-san, release it inside me...
No.
Why did you release it outside?
Shut up.
Mother?
These are...
Mother's panties.
Mother, l'm sorry for doing this...
Kai-kun?
Kai-kun...
What's wrong, Kaito-kun?
Did something happen? You're out of breath.
Nao-san...
Here, hot cocoa.
Thank you very much.
l guess you're a man after all...
...getting caught with Sayo-san's panties, huh?
Well, l too...
What is it?
Nao-san!
What?
l'm begging you, please let me stay here for the night.
My mother caught me masturbating like that.
l'm too embarrassed to see her eye to eye.
Just for the night.
lf you don't mind me staying, that is.
l don't mind since l'm all alone.
Really?
Thank you very much.
But you'll have to keep me company.
You're a real man now.
Nao-san, what about the store?
lt's okay, l'm done for the day.
By the way, you can drink a little, can't you?
l can't drink wine...
Don't say that, you're supposed to keep me company, remember?
Fine, l'll help you drink.
Well? Was it good?
Nao-san, what are you trying to do?
You wouldn't drink so...
But...
lf you won't drink, then l'll have to give it to you mouth to mouth.
l'll drink it, l'll be happy to drink it.
N-Nao-san?
Your cock is getting so hard.
l'm dreaming...
You must be half asleep.
All right then, l'll take away your virginity.
Stop this Nao-san...
No, l can't take it anymore.
Here l come.
Can you see it, Kaito-kun? lt's going inside.
No, don't do this...
Yes...
Your cock is nice and hard...
Nao-san...
That's it...
That feels good...
Yes...
Do it gently...
Kaito-kun, don't just keep on touching them.
Touch them and try to make a shape.
Can you tell that it's getting hard?
Yes, l can.
That's too hard.
This is a very sensitive area, do it more gently...
Nao-san, Nao-san...
Are you going to climax?
Just hang in there a little longer, l still haven't...
l can't, Nao-san...
l'm coming, l'm coming!
Are you coming, Kaito-kun?
l can't hold it...
You climaxed...
After all, it was your first time...
Looks like you still have some energy left.
You have to do a better job this time...
l want you to make me feel good.
Look, your cock is going inside me...
lt's making me feel good...
l can feel your huge thing rubbing inside...
Feels good doesn't it?
Well? Does it feel good?
l...
lt feels good, right? Does it feel good, Kaito-kun?
Nao-san...
No, don't suck on them that hard!
You're cute Kaito-kun...
l want you to get wilder inside me.
Kaito-kun, l want you to keep going deeper...
That's it.
Nao-san, l'm about to climax...
More, more!
l'll climax soon...
l'm going to climax.
l'm coming...
Fine! Go ahead and climax!
l'm coming too!
l'm coming!
Nao-san...
Amazing...
Look at all the white stuff from your cock...
Tastes just like you.
This isn't a dream, right?
No, this is not a dream, Kaito-kun.
How am l going to apologize to my mother?
Oh stop it...
Father?
Father...
l'm home.
Did Takumi's mother come by to make some snide remarks?
Kai-kun, don't be so mean to Tamae-san.
She's the head of the PTA and she always looks down on others.
She doesn't do anything, she always makes you do all the work...
Anyway, about this morning...
Let's go inside and talk about it...
Okay...
l went into your room without knocking...
...l must've made you feel real bad.
l'm sorry.
No, it's all my fault.
l took your panties and...
You shouldn't blame yourself.
You're at an age where you have an interest in things like that.
l should've been more careful.
l'm really a bad mother...
Mother...
End of conversation.
You must be hungry, l'll fix you some dinner.
Mother...
My father is having an affair with a younger woman.
He's taking advantage of my mother since she doesn't know.
And he tries to play the role of a good father at home.
Then what's going to happen to my mother?
Who's going to protect my mother...
...who doesn't even have children on her own?
No Chikara-san...
Chikara-san, it feels good...
lt feels good.
No...
Don't stick it in there...
Stick it inside, Chikara-san...
lt's going inside...
You're too loud, Sayo.
Kai-kun?
Please don't...
l'm sorry mother, l love you.
l couldn't take it anymore.
l can't believe you like me this much...
We shouldn't be doing this...
No, no...
l'll climax...
Me too mother...
No...