It's not like you're a virgin.
How about relaxing a little more
and enjoying this?
Y-Yes...
Please... Please let me come.
My husband's going
to be home soon.
I suppose...
But with Yusuke here...
Don't worry. He's probably out
collecting insects or something.
How about this?
You must be feeling quite a bit
aroused now.
Y-Yes...
I want you to be
a little more intense.
If you don't want your husband
to cheat on you...
...you'll need to improve
your technique.
You have a nice pussy.
It's hard to believe that
you've given birth.
That's embarrassing.
Please don't say such a thing.
Well?
How does it feel to be
fucked after so long?
I don't know.
You don't know?
How can you say that
when you're so wet?
Does that feel good?
It feels so good.
My dad is remarried to
a widow with a child.
He didn't marry out of love.
It's a marriage of convenience.
That's nothing but a cover.
When he was posted abroad
for a long term...
...the wedding was postponed.
But he did the paperwork,
giving her power over the house.
He planned it all out.
He only thinks about work.
An appropriate married life
for my father.
How dare she move in and claim
to be my mother.
I'm not going to be sucked into it.
She's not fooling me.
Go deeper.
Like this?
Yes. Right there.
That feels so good.
You're such a demanding lady.
It's been a week since uncle left.
Well, how is it going?
Pretty good, I suppose.
Mio. This is it. I'm going to cum!
Where do you want to cum?
In my mouth?
Or on my face?
Th-The face.
That felt so good.
Oh, I hope I find a wonderful
boyfriend soon.
I'd do all kinds of things for him.
You're always saying stuff like that.
You'd better find a boyfriend, quick.
That's easier said than done,
you know.
Oh, well. I'll play with you
until you find one.
Seems kind of pathetic. Cousins
helping each other out like this.
It's fine for you, because you
don't believe in romance.
Rather than not believing in romance,
it's more that I detest women.
Since that time.
I'm home.
Mom?
More.
Mom.
I don't know if it's because
of my mother's adultery...
...but my parents divorced
shortly after that.
After I saw her commit adultery...
...my mother, the one person
that I ought to love the most...
...became a woman that
I hated and detested.
And that sentiment extended
to all women thereafter.
Yusuke.
She seemed well.
Can't you forgive her?
Of course not.
But don't you think it was
also your father's fault...
...for not paying enough
attention to his family?
It's not fair to make it
completely her fault.
I don't just blame
my mother for this.
I hate my father by about
the same amount.
Then, why don't you leave?
I want to leave.
I've thought about it
for a long time.
I've got no where to go...
...and besides, I've got to keep
an eye on his new family.
So, in the end, you don't have
the courage to fight it.
Maybe you shouldn't be
acting so harshly.
It's pathetic.
That new little sister
you have there...
...is, like, totally hot!
Looks delicious.
Wonder if she has a boyfriend.
If not, maybe I'll...
No way. I've got dibs on her.
I've gone longer without
a girlfriend.
That shouldn't have anything
to do with it.
It's your fault for not being popular.
Here's your lunch.
Here're your clean clothes.
Damn. What, mother?
Yusuke.
I've finished practicing.
We should go home together.
See you later.
To be living under the same
roof as that woman!
That's a crime!
I envy you, you bastard!
Don't get too close to me.
What'll people think?
Oh, come on.
I know I'm only your stepsister,
but we shouldn't act like strangers.
I suppose.
I've always wanted a brother,
you know.
So, let's get along.
Under the surface, she's also
nothing but a nympho.
You don't fool me.
You're home.
You must be hungry.
Dinner's ready.
I'm taking a shower first.
You mustn't run inside the house.
It looks like she's fitting
right in at her new school.
Good.
Yusuke, I'm counting on you
to watch over Shiina.
Of course.
We've become brother
and sister, after all.
Well, let's have dinner.
She pretends to be such a good mother,
but she's nothing more than a sow.
You don't fool me.
Not for one minute.
Damn.
Why is she in my house?
Yusuke!
I'll wash your back, Mom.
I-It's okay. I'll do it myself.
Oh, come on.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mom?
Y-Yes?
I only have bad memories
of my real mother.
So, I want us to have a great
relationship together.
Yes...
I'll work hard to make that happen.
Your skin is so smooth.
It's so beautiful.
You mustn't, Yusuke!
Why?!
Why can't I?
I just wanted to...
I'm sorry.
You're starving for affection
from your mother.
Yes. That's right.
All right. Come on, then.
Then, you can do
what  ou want to.
Mom!
I'll wash it for you.
I've got to go all the way in.
You look beautiful, Mom.
You're so beautiful that look
what's happened to me.
Mom, will you wash me, too?
Oh, yes.
Mom...
Can you use your mouth?
But, I can't.
I suppose.
I suppose that's going too far.
All right, then.
Mom...
Mom, that feels great.
I want to become one with you.
No. No.
That's one thing we mustn't do.
Why not?
What am I supposed
to do with this?
We're supposed to
be mother and son.
That's just something we can't do.
But...
You'll have to do with this.
That feels good.
Your tits are so soft.
I'm...!
I'm cumming!
That felt real good.
Thanks, Mom. Let's do it again.
No! Never!
That's the end of it.
I want you to get out of here.
I'm off!
Okay! Have good day!
Yusuke?
Yusuke, are you all...?!
Mom, I'm sorry about last night.
But when I think about it,
I get all hard.
I can't even think about
going to my lectures.
Stop this.
Yusuke, I said that that
was going to be it.
I don't know very much
about sex yet.
That's why I want you
to teach me about it.
No. No.
I can't do that!
Please, Mom!
I want to have sex with you so
much I think I'm going to die!
A little more...
A little bit more...
...and that woman will
reveal her true self.
Yusuke!
Mom... I just... I just can't
take this anymore!
I think I'm going to go crazy.
Please help me, Mom!
No... I can't.
We're supposed to be mother
and son, you know.
That's one thing we just can't...
Mom!
Your pussy tastes so good.
It's a bitter, sweet taste.
It makes me feel so at ease.
No... No, you mustn't. Yusuke.
You must be lonely
without Dad around.
You're very precious to me, Mom.
When I see you all sad and lonely...
...I just feel like I have to help you.
No, Yusuke.
No.
Look at me now.
And you're not going to
do anything about it?
That's horrible!
You don't care if I go crazy?!
All right.
I'm so happy, Mom.
Well, Mom? Have you tried
anything like this before?
No...
I really can't be doing this.
I've got to stop all this now.
But you look pretty
aroused by all this.
Would you still like me to stop?
No!
See? It feels good, doesn't it?
But isn't there something else
that you'd rather have, Mom?
We'll always be mother and son,
no matter what.
You want it, don't you?
I want it.
Here I come, Mom.
It's so good, Mom.
You feel fantastic inside!
Yes, that's amazing, Yusuke.
Fuck me harder from below!
The sow.
After all that proper talk, she's
nothing but a hussy underneath!
I can't take anymore, Yusuke...
I'm going to cum!
Okay...
Mom, I'm going to cum!
Yusuke! What are you
trying to do?!
Don't worry, Mom.
Just leave it to me.
All right.
Give me pleasure, Yusuke.
Yes. Pleasure is everything.
Mother!
Ow!
Yusuke, you can do anything you
want to me, but please be gentle.
Gentle, huh?
Why?! Why are you
doing this to me?!
That hurts! I don't like that!
That doesn't sound quite right...
...coming from a nymphomaniac
like you.
Yusuke!
I'll give you lots of pleasure, Mom.
Stop this. I'll scream, all right?
Fine.
The first one who'll come
running will be Shiina.
I wonder what she'd
think of the sight...
...of her mother getting fucked
in the ass by her stepbrother.
This is nothing.
This is just the start.
This isn't going to ease the resentment
I have against my mother.
I've got to be rougher
and cause more pain...
...and fuck her up!