Translator
Chii ^ ^
I woke up one morning, and fell in love
aru asa ni mezamete koi wo shita
Editor
Torgan
We couldn't tell what's going on
bokura wa tomadotta
The scenery has repainted everything
slide wo shite iku
Timer
babbit
As if it's just sliding by
fuukei ga subete wo nurikaeta
It feels like my precious treasures have been reduced to dust
daiji na takaramono ga gomi ni nacchau kanji
Typesetter
Eise
I can go anywhere with you
dokodemo issho ni ikeruyo
Where do the answers to love and kisses lie?
koi to kisu no kotae wa dokoni aru no
Karaoke
Turles
Sneaking away from a closed yesterday
tozasareteru kinou wo nukedashite
Where am I heading with you in my arms?
kimi wo dakishime doko ni ikuno
Encoder
Kamui ^ ^
I'll be dreaming
yume wo miteru
Even if "goodbye" and sadness is what awaits us
kanashimi ya sayonara ga futari wo mattetemo
Quality Check
W2k
Green Green
Hananoka Foundation Festival
Hey, hey, they're coming tomorrow, right?
Oh, you mean those experimental transfer
students from Kanenone Gakuen?
I wonder whet kind of guys they are...
I wonder if they're cool...
Well since they're from the mountains,
they're probably just monkeys...
She has a point...
What's going on... Where did everyone go?
Huh?
Are you feeling sick or something?
I-It's all right... I was just a little... surprised.
If I just take my medication...
Surprised?
Oh, it's a ghost house.
Sanae-chan!
I'm going to spill it, I'm going to spill it!
Ahh, sorry!
Sanae-chan just wait a little longer, okay?
Wait!
It'll be much faster if I carry her there
instead of you bringing the water here.
Where are the drinking fountains?
A-ah, over here.
I see crows live in cities like this, too.
Crows have a tendency to collect shiny
things. Be sure to get a good look!
– W-what are you doing?
Who am I?
Armbadge - public morals committee
So Haruno-san liked these kinds of things...
Don't say that, Futaba-chan.
There's no way that's true, right? How disappointing.
I guess you're right.
Wakaba?
Ah, yes, Onee-sama...
Like I said, there's always one each year.
One of those bastards who use the darkness
to try and hug one of our student girls...
I'll eat you up!
No use in doing that, I'm not seared at all.
There's no such thing as a real ghost, after all!
Dumbass! What are you touching?!
Ghost House
Umm...
Thank you very much.
Oh, it's nothing...
Thanks a lot, it must have been hard on you.
You're thirsty, right? After sweating like that and all...
Eh? No, this is...
Oh, umm... I'm Chitose Midori.
I'm Takasaki Yuusuke.
I'll leave these here.
Wait! Stop right there!
Forgive me!!!
Eh? Bacchigu and Ichibanboshi?
Well I have to go...
Umm...
I said wait!
Stop!
Stop right there, you bastard!
I'm telling you to stop!
Socho! Itsuki!
Dokugasu's name, which is presumably
a nick name of some kind, means "Poison Gas"
Tenjin! Dokugasu!
H-help us!!
Catch those guys!
They're perverts!
He touched my breasts!
What did you say?
AFFEC-TION!
Bacchigu... Ichibanboshi...
And for those reasons, during the upcoming week,
we'll be studying side-by-side with the
male students from Kanenone Gakuen.
This is also a test for us to see if we'll
become a co-ed school in the future.
We'll be anticipating everyone to be the neat and
dignified Hananoka Gakuen students that we are.
Heh! What part of this is "neat and dignified"?
W-what is it?
You guys haven't been forgiven yet, you know.
We're just staying quiet because a regent
senpai punished you instead!
The next time you pull off one of your
dirty pranks, I'll notify the teacher,
and get you guys kicked out right away!
No guys allowed past this point.
Ah, a bunk bed, eh?
We slept on the floor at Kanenone.
This is heaven compared to that place.
The blanket's not wet, either.
I don't know how many years it's been
since I've slept in a bed like this!
Ah, I'm so happy!
Tenjin... aren't those Bacchigu and Ichibanboshi's bags?
Those two left their bags to me and went out for a bit.
They went out?
They said they were going to go exploring or something.
Exploring?
I think I get the picture.
Is Takasaki Yuusuke-kun here?
Ass! Ass! Ass! Ass! Ass! Ass!
Guys are the worst!
Thank you for yesterday.
No entry
Oh, no, it's nothing to be thanked for...
She's my type of girl...
And so, we came thinking that we'd show
you around the school in return.
Thanks.
It seems like we've got off on a bad start
because of yesterday's "incident", so...
Then let's get going.
Yuusuke! Don't tell me you're leaving me behind!
I won't let you know when the same commercials appear???
on different TV channels at the same time anymore!
Come on, my bestest friend in the world!
– Geez, you're noisy...
Is it all right if he tags along, too?
Sure!
What about you, Itsuki?
I'll pass.
Then, let's get going.
Hey, Tenjin, let's go.
Hey, wait up!
I can just smell the youth in the air...
There are so many women in the field!
Socho...
Don't you have any special talents, Yuusuke-kun?
Eh?
Me?
Like judo, or...
Oh, we have that as a class back at our school.
Okay, then let's go!
What in the world is she thinking?
Chitose-senpai, will this really be okay?
Well...
Yuusuke! Be sure to teach her a lesson
that'll make her fear us men!
We even cheered him on...
You're not supposed to lose!
If you won, everyone would have a better impression
of you like Hotta-senpai outside...
Oh, I see...
So were you distracted by your opponent's
breasts by any chance?
T-that's not...
Pervert.
Sanae-chan!
Are you talking about that girl who's as tall as a junior
high student, but looks like she's in elementary school?
You're really, really genuine, you know that?
Damn straight!
The moment you set your eyes on my girl, I'll kill you.
When will we be able to decorate the
first page of the morning paper...
I want to wait every morning in excitement!
That's pretty dangerous, you know.
This is the fragrance of a woman...
Did Itsuki catch a cold or something?
– Well...
Come to think of it, we've never taken
a bath together with Itsuki.
Until just a while ago, girls were in this very place!
It's pretty delicious...
What are you doing?
Do you have a girlfriend at the
school you were attending?
What kind of girls do you like, Kobayashi-kun?
A girl who doesn't talk a lot.
It's true that Itsuki is quite handsome...
Socho would be in karate...
Tenjin would be with that freshman chick...
I see you're pretty knowledgeable
about those things, Kuyasu-kun!
Then do you know about White Magic?
Yup...
Even Dokugasu is...
But what about us?! I won't allow that kind of thing!
But you know... You're just reaping what you sowed.
Are you saying that it's my fault? Aren't we friends?!
What happened to our friendship? Huh? Huh?!
Well don't get so mad about
it... Yuusuke's right and all.
Bacchigu, did you apologize to that Haruno girl?
I said, stop it...
A-all right.
My fellow female comrades!
Let's wash away what happened back then...
So let's all be friendly... Are you happy now?
I'll wash you away!
You need to reflect over what you've done more!
Reflect over it?
Idiot!
Retard!
Just die!
You old pervert!
Useless bastard!
Yuusuke-kun!
Chi... Chitose.
Hello, Ijuin-kun... Ichibanboshi-kun.
Who does she mean by "Ijuin"?
Was there a guy like that?
There wasn't...
She's talking about me! Why did you forget?!
You idiot! A pervert like you doesn't deserve that name!
You want to take this on?
What did you say?
Now, now, Futaba-chan, Ijuin-kun,
let's get along, okay?
Midori-chan, there's no way we can
get along with these kind of guys!
What do you mean "these kind of guys"...?
They seem pretty nice to me.
What's "pretty nice" about guys
who do perverted things?!
Futaba-chan, back then we were just...
We were joking around a little too much...
And we are really... sorry for it, and...
Pervert! Don't come...
closer to me!
Futaba-chan!
Are you all right?
I-It... swelled up!
He's an adult.
Socho's not here?
You guys... What are you...
What do you think of Chitose Midori?
What do you mean by that?
Well...
Huh?
That girl came from a different
class just to talk to us, right?
Y-yeah.
If I explain up to here, even you
would understand, right?
She has a crush...
Ah! You really think so?
On me...
Eh?
A man can't just stand and watch as he's being tempted!
Heh?
Although this kind of thing isn't
really my hobby at all...
Ichibanboshi?
We only have one day left anyway.
I'll make that headstrong girl fall for
me and call me "Ichibanboshi-sama"!
H-hey! I don't get what you guys are talking about...
– I'm going to become a man!
In conclusion...
Eh?
They're nightcrawling.
Nightcrawling?
Chitose... Chitose's in trouble!
Leave them alone. There's nothing to worry about.
B-but...!
There's no way they wouldn't have any kind of
security around a girl's dormitory, right?
Security?
It's a pervert!
Hi, mom, how are you? We're in the city right now.
The city is really a scary place. They looked
down on us again thanks to Ichibanboshi.
It's all your fault.
No, it's your fault.
No, no, it's your fault.
It's definitely your fault.
W-w-what did you say?!
I said we're being framed!
Hey, hey, Yuusuke, we were at the dorm, right?
Y-yeah...
He's lying!
You're all saying that we're the criminals
in yesterday's incident,
but do you have any evidence... Futaba-chan?
How did you get those cuts?
T-these are... from that time when we
fell while being chased by wild dogs...
Don't play innocent!
R-right, Yuusuke? They were really big, right?
Y-yeah...
Hurry up and confess.
You're full of lies!
I can't believe you.
You're the worst!
I'll right, all right, that'll be enough.
Just by what I've heard, there seems to be no evidence
that the guys are indeed the criminals.
But...
Ah, we were framed... I'm hurt.
There's blood coming out from my wounds, mama.
I've lived without telling a single lie...
Mama, what part of me is wrong?
Mama, am I a bad boy?
Tell me, Mama...!
What a disaster! They said Chitose Midori-san
got her underwear stolen!
W-wait, we never did such a thing!
Y-yeah... We never had time to do such a thing...
So it was you guys!
So it's been decided!
You guys will just have to get out right now!
Get out!
Go back to the countryside!
Geez, come on... Hold on, you guys.
If you're going to talk like that,
I guess we have no choice.
So you're going to get out?
We can't just simply get out after getting
accused of being underwear thieves!
We'll just have to catch the thief by
ourselves and prove our innocence!
Yeah, he's right!
Catch him? But how?
Right, Yuusuke?
Eh? Why do I have to do it, too?
Geez... Why do we have to it, too...
Hey, are you standing guard properly?
Yeah, I am.
This is my special talent and all...
But the city sure is hot at night!
Really... I should really be sleeping in
a nice air-conditioned room by now...
Whose fault do you think this is?!
That's why we're standing guard, right?
Yeah, yeah, be thankful.
You got us into this!
But it's so hot, I can't stop sweating.
Yuusuke, handkerchief...
I don't have one.
What about you?
Ah, handkerchief...
Ah, here's one.
Here.
Thank you...
But do you really intend on catching the criminal?
We're going back tomorrow, you know.
It doesn't matter if we don't catch him.
The real culprit will be caught before then, and...
"Oh, we've done something bad to Ijuin-kun."
"That's right, let's write a letter!"
Something like that will happen.
Ooh! What a brilliant plan!
After all, a criminal that actually did
this kind of thing is usually sick...
He can't even suppress his own desires, geez...
It might just be...!
Don't say things that even demons would laugh at!
There's a trap right there.
Say that earlier!
In addition to that, there's also a pit full of
tacks just a little bit further to the side...
Are you trying to kill someone?!
Here, eat up.
Sorry... Just because my panties...
N-no, I'm just trying to clear my name, that's all.
Yuusuke-kun...
Hmm?
Just confess. I'll keep it a secret.
The nightcrawler in my room... was actually you, right?
Eh?
It was also you who stole my panties, right?
Y-you're mistaken! It really wasn't me!
What...? So it really is like that...
I'm disappointed.
Why are you being so kind to us?
I'm not exactly being kind to you guys...
Really?
Geez, you're really dull, aren't you?
Eh?
More importantly... Question Number
One, would it be all right?
Y-yeah.
Why did you cover up for me?
I did? When?
Well when we first met, at the nurse's office...
I spilled the water on your shirt,
but you didn't tell sensei...
O-Oh, that?
Yeah!
Well, I didn't really have a particular reason...
So you don't have one?
Hmm, if I say that I do...
And if you do?
I wonder what it'd be.
Question Number Two. Why are you asking about that?
Eh? W-well, that's...
What can I say... No particular reason...
I see.
This origami's good!
Huh? What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
I've never seen this many stars before.
Eh?
Well, I never really had the chance to watch
the star-filled sky like this, after all.
There are many more stars than that, you know.
Huh?
More?
Yeah. My school's in the countryside, you know.
The air is clean, so even the same stars shine brighter,
and the sky has many more stars than this...
And even on a moonless night, you can tell the
shape of the mountain just by the starlight.
I want to see a starry sky like that, too.
Yuusuke-kun...
Hmm?
Question Number Three... Can I come
over to your house next time?
Of course, you're always welcome.
Then, let's promise.
Was that a dream?
Sorry, I must have dozed off.
No, it's okay.
Well then, good luck.
Ah, yeah.
What are you doing?!
You did it, right? You definitely did it, right?
W-what are you talking about?
Watch the stars!
And repeat!
Become relaxed!
And finally, sex!
You did it, right?!
Just as I thought!
Hey, what are you doing?
This guy slacked off from his guard duty
and was making out with a girl!
Making out with a girl?
W-what are you saying? H-he's
wrong! He's wrong, I said!
Ah n-no, wasn't that...
Ah, but I wasn't making ou...
AFFEC-TION!
That hurts...
Are you all right?
Yuusuke, are you all right?
This is the real culprit!
At this time, the baby birds are all
grown up and leave their nests.
So they gather different things to make their nest.
You're so knowledgeable, Tenjin-senpai.
No, it's nothing...
Can I talk to you for a second?
Huh?
Actually it's from a story on the back of a chip bag.
Geez, and to think you were accusing
people of being underwear thieves...
U-um...
Ah! That's...!
Those are the panties I lost last night!
T-this is...
So it was you!
Wait.
That's right. He liked me that much.
I couldn't forgive you for touching
my breasts at the ghost house...
Or the fact that you came to see my
panties during tennis practice...
But this was all Ijuin-kun's...
No, Darling's...
I've finally come to realize... That those were
all just your expressions of love for me!
Darling...
So, what were you going to say?
Ah, I was saying, why don't you come over
to my house to watch the stars next...
Yuusuke-kun...
– Chi-Chitose! What are you...
– Hurry up and go back already!
Darling, touch my breasts... Why
are you being so bashful?
H-help!
Darling, you're so...
I got you!
Ah! Stop it!
Don't touch me! Don't lick me! Don't bite me!
– Darling...!
– Stop it...!
Why me?
I woke up one morning, and fell in love
aru asa ni mezatete koi wo shita
We couldn't tell what's going on
bokura wa tomadotta
The scenery has repainted everything
slide wo shite iku
As if it's just sliding by
fuukiei ga subete wo nurikaete
It feels like my precious treasures have been reduced to dust
daiji na takaramono ga gomi ni nacchau kanji
I can go anywhere with you
dokodemo issho ni ikeruyo
Where do the answers to love and kisses lie?
koi to kisu no kotae wa dokoni aru no
Sneaking away from a closed yesterday
tozasareteru kinou wo nukedashite
Where am I heading with you in my arms?
kimi wo dakishime doko ni ikuno
I'll be dreaming
yume wo miteru
Even if "goodbye" and sadness is what awaits us
kanashimi ya sayonara ga futari wo mattetemo