See you later.
My sister, Makabe Aizawa...
She's always been standing out ever since she was little.
She's beautiful too.
She was always so dignified. No matter what
she did, she was always number one at.
And also, everyone knows that she's
really easy to get along with.
She's a person without flaws.
Her brightly dyed hair and her green
eyes match her perfectly.
Haruto, could you return a DVD for me?
U-Uh, well I was thinking about sleeping soon.
But in front of me, she's...
What? Can't you listen to my orders?
She acts like she's some kind of monarch.
And for the time being, I'm her servant.
I-I'll go now then.
Good, have a safe trip.
Big Sister Heart throb! More
Thanks for returning this.
Adult Corner Back Here
Truth be told, I don't actually mind
the way she acts at home at all.
Thank you very much.
I'm home.
Haruto.
Come here for a second.
Wai... Nee-san?! You're just wearing a towel again?!
It's fine, just come in already.
Hey, Haruto.
Kiss me...
Recently, she's... started ordering me to kiss her.
Hurry up.
I can't help it. Your reactions are just so cute.
It's so much fun.
Wai...
That's my...
Come on, cum with your sister's hand.
I... I...
It's okay.
Looks like you came with your clothes on.
You're gonna get your underwear pregnant.
After I came, she stood there watching me wash my boxers.
Somehow...
She looked like she was enjoying herself.
Does this mean that I've essentially become her plaything?
Huh?!
Oh, are you awake?
It looks like this guy is more of
an early riser than you though.
What are you doing?!
Come on, if you don't cum soon...
Are your balls going to be okay if you don't cum soon?
Th-They might not be.
So, what're you gonna do?
I-I'm cumming!
Time after time...
I'll give you a helping hand.
Nee-san?!
It's already so hard.
It's only midday though.
I'll help you release something thicker.
We can't do this. It's not right.
Come on, shoot it out.
To tell the truth, I wanted to cross
that line with her so badly.
For so long now.
She was acting a little different than usual today.
Do you want to touch it?
Touch it.
Slowly. If you make it hurt, you're in trouble.
Wait, is this...
It's so soft.
You're shaking.
W-Well...
You're being too nervous.
You put your finger inside me without me telling you to?
S-Sorry. It's just so wet, it slid in.
It's fine.
Keep going.
It feels really good!
Keep doing that until I cum.
It has such an erotic smell.
Would she get mad if I licked it?
Wait! Your finger and tongue at the same time?!
I'm gonna cum!
I can't...
Nee-san...
Haruto.
After that, I knew I had to be the one to take the initiative.
I thought all this time she was just playing around with me.
But I got the feeling that she was telling
me that I could put it inside her.
Nee-san, I...
Are you going to put it inside me?
You pervert.
Yeah, I'm sorry!
It's coming inside!
Wait, is this your first time?
Of course it is.
I just gave you my first time right now!
Oh, I see... Does it hurt?
That doesn't matter. Just keep going!
At first, I was just messing around with you, but...
Ever since we first kissed, I started
falling in love with you, Haruto.
If I said that, would you believe me?
I would.
Even if it was a lie!
You're being so rough!
I'd still believe anything you say!
Because I love you, nee-san!
Whatever you tell me, I take to heart!
This isn't the time to be spouting embarrassing lines!
S-So just cum inside me.
Fill me up with your cum!
Okay!
I'm gonna cum inside you, so get ready!
Cum! Cum!!
Lots! Lots! Cum lots!
Nee-san, I-I...
Haruto! Haruto!!
Me too! I'm going to cum with you!
There's so much cum flowing inside me!
I never told you to cum this much.
Sorry.
I forgive you.
You're going to damage the fabric if you're that rough.
Right.
Don't stretch it out so much.
Wash it right.
The monarch peered over me as
I washed our dirty underwear.
I'm sure they're just going to get dirty again, though.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: lord tachanka
softsub: торрент иваниваныч