I'm going!
My sister, Aisawa Makabe.
Since we were young,
she always stood out.
Pretty,
always graceful,
she always aces
whatever she does.
That's why I know how
much she's loved by others.
A perfect person.
Even when she dyed her hair,
it still looks great with her green eyes.
Haruto,
won't you return the DVD?
Oh! Uhm...
But,
I'm going to sleep now.
But when it's just the
two of us...
You're not going to listen
to me?
Hmm?
She behaves like a king.
After all,
I'm her servant.
Then I'll be going.
Okay! Take care.
Thank you for returning the DVD.
Adult Corner
<-Right This Way
Entry restricted to persons
less than 18 years of age
I don't really hate
her domineering attitude.
Thank you very much!
I'm back!
Haruto.
Come here.
What! Sis!
Again wearing only that!
Don't worry about it,
just get in!
Haruto,
kiss me.
Recently,
sis has been ordering
me to kiss her.
Hurry up.
It's because all your
reactions are so cute.
This is so fun.
Wait!
That's my...
Here, cum on my hands.
Wait...
I'm...
It's all right.
You came while wearing pants.
Your underwear will get
pregnant you know.
After being partly pushed,
sis,
she seemed to be having fun while
watching me wash my underwear.
Am I only being played
with like a toy?
Huh? Wha!
Oh! You're awake?
This woke up first though.
What are you doing?!
Come on. You have to
cum quickly.
Or, are you okay to leave
it like this?
Well, no.
What should we do?
I'm comi...!
Over and over...
I'll help you.
Sis!
It's already gotten big.
It's still noon you know.
I'll make you moan more.
Doing this!
Come on.
Let it out.
Actually,
I thought about going over the
line with sis,
even from before.
Today, sis seems a little
different.
Do you want to touch it?
Touch it.
Softly. If it hurts, I
won't forgive you.
Could this possibly be...
It... It's soft...
Your hand is shaking.
Be... Because...
You're too nervous!
You just inserted a finger!
Sorry! It just slipped in...
It's all right.
Go on.
It feels good!
Just continue like this
until I come.
It smells erotic.
I wonder if she'll get
angry if I lick it.
That... If you do that!
I'll come!
No! I'll!
Sis...
Haruto.
She knows that I won't
do anything.
I thought she's just teasing
and playing with me.
But her eyes seems to say it's
all right to put it in.
Sis! I...!
Do you plan on putting
it in? Pervert.
I'm sorry!
It hurts!
Is it tight?
Of course it is.
It's my first time after all.
Oh, I see.
Does it hurt?
It's fine. Just continue!
At first, I was just playing
with you,
but ever since we started kissing,
I began to like Haruto.
Do you believe me?
I do.
Even if it is a lie,
It's too intense!
I'll believe in what you say,
because I really like you sis!
What you said while looking
at me was definitely not a lie!
Why are you suddenly saying
such embarrassing things!
Then,
inside,
let it all out inside!
I understand! I'll cum like
this inside...!
Come!
Let it all out!
Sis! I'm almost!
Haruto! Haruto!
I'm also... I'm also coming!
So much came out.
I didn't tell you to
cum like this.
Sorry.
I forgive you.
The way you wash is not good
for the cloth.
Okay.
Don't pull too much.
Yes.
Properly wash it.
The king watched as the
servant washed the
underwears.
It'll get dirty again I'm sure.