We, who "Fell in love" on a morning, were puzzled.
aru asa ni mezamete "koi wo shita" bokura wa tomadotta
The sliding scenery repainted everything.
slide wo shite yuku fuukei ga subete wo nuri kaeta
Is this a feeling that a precious treasure turning into trash?
daiji na takaramono ga gomi ni nacchau kanji?
We can go anywhere together.
doko demo issho ni ikeru yo
Where is the answer to the love and kiss?
koi to kiss no kotae wa doko ni aruno?
Going out from the isolated yesterday.
tozasareteru kinou wo nukedashite
Where is it going embracing you?
kimi wo dakishime doko ni ikuno?
Even the sadness, which is dreaming,
yume wo miteru kanashimi ya sayonara ga
and the goodbye is waiting for the two.
futari wo mattetemo
Green Green
Hey hey, they're coming tomorrow right?
Oh, those umm... trial transfer students
from the Kanenone Gakuen, right?
I wonder what kind of guys they are?
Will any of them be cool guys?
They'll probably be like monkeys if they
come from deep in the mountains.
I guess you're right.
What the hell, where is everyone?
Are you feeling sick?
I-I'm alright. I was just a little surprised.
If I drink some medicine...
"Surprised?"
Oh, a haunted house.
Sanae-chan!
It's gonna spill!
I'm sorry!
Sanae-chan, please wait a second.
Wait!
Instead of you scooping up the water,
it's faster to carry her there.
Where's the drinking fountain?
This way.
Oh, there are crows even in the city.
Crows have the habit of collecting things that sparkle.
– Keep that in your eye!
– What the hell are you doing?
Who is it?
I didn't know you liked these
kind of things, Haruno-san.
Now wait a minute, Futaba-chan.
There's no way I would enjoy stupid things like this.
Yeah, you're right.
Wakaba!
Y-yes Onee-sama!
Nooo!
...then I heard about some bastards who are
trying to grope female students in the dark.
NOOOOOOO!
I'll eat ya!
Sorry, you're not scary.
Who...?
Because things like you don't exist.
They're huge!
No! Idiot! Watch where you're grabbing!
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
Umm, thank you very much.
No problem.
Thanks for your help. It must have been tough.
You must be thirsty, since you're all sweaty.
Eh? Umm, this is...
M-my name is Chitose Midori.
Oh. I'm Takasaki Yuusuke.
I'll leave it here.
NOOOOOO!
– Wait a second!
– You guys!
What?
– Forgive me!
– Damn you!
– Huh? Bacchigu and Ichibanboshi?
I have to go now.
Ah...
Wait a sec!
WAIT!
STAY THERE!
I told you to wait!
Socho! Itsuki!
Tenjin! Dokugasu!
SAVE US!
Get those two!
They're perverts!
He groped my breasts!
WHATCHASAY?!
Aijou!
Note: Aijou - Expression of Love
Bacchigu, Ichibanboshi.
...that's how it is. For the next week,
the boys from Kanenone Gakuen
will be studying amongst us.
This will also test our school to see if
it is ready to go co-ed in the future.
I expect you girls to behave as the serene and
nice Hananoka Gakuen students that you are.
Hah! What does she mean by "serene and nice"?
Wh-what is it?
This doesn't mean that we have forgiven you.
We haven't said anything because Regent Senpai
told us to keep this under wraps.
If you cause any more mischief, we'll tell the teacher
and get you guys kicked out immediately!
No entry for boys beyond this point.
So we have bunk beds, huh?
No entry for boys beyond this points.
At Kanenone, we slept in the closet.
This is heaven compared to that!
The futon is dry!
It's been years since my last time! This is great!
Hey Tenjin, aren't those Bacchigu
and Ichibanboshi's bags?
Those two gave me their bags
and went off somewhere.
Went off somewhere?
They said they wanted to go exploring or something...
"Exploring...?"
I think I know where they went.
Is Takasaki Yuusuke-kun here?
Men are the worst!
About yesterday: Thank you very much.
No, I didn't do it to be thanked.
She's beautiful...
And to return the favor, we're here
to show you around the school.
Thanks.
Because of yesterday's incident, things
are not going well with the girls.
Shall we go now?
Yuusuke-don, are you trying to abandon me?
I won't help you, even if we're
in the same TV commercial!
Shut up...
Can he come along?
Of course!
How about you Itsuki?
I'll pass.
Then let's go!
Come on Tenjin, we're going.
Hey! Don't leave me behind!
The smell of youth!
I'm in a field with girls... lots of girls!
Socho...
Do you have any talents, Yuusuke-kun?
Me?
How about Judo?
Oh! We do that in class.
Really? I want to see!
What is she thinking...?
Chitose-Senpai, is this really okay?
I don't know.
Yuusuke-don! Show her how terrible
men can be until she is traumatized!
I prepared all this for you...
You shouldn't lose!
If you win, everyone will change their
attitude, especially Hotta-senpai.
I see.
Were you distracted by your opponent's breasts?
T-that's not true!
Pervert.
Sanae-chan!
Are you talking about the girl who looks like she
belongs in elementary school instead of middle school?
Dude are you... for real?
Of course! If you underestimate my
Lolita complex (roricon), I'll kill you!
It'll make me wake up excited every morning!
That's not good, you know.
So this is the smell of a female!
Is Itsuki sick?
– I don't know.
– Oh yeah, we never took a bath with Itsuki before.
Just a while ago, girls were in this bath...
I think of it as good juice!
What are you doing?
Wha?
Do you have a girlfriend in your school?
Kobayashi-kun, what kind of girl do you like?
A girl who is quiet.
COOL!
Well, let's put aside the fact that Itsuki's a player.
Socho is in karate.
Tenjin is with a girl in ninth grade.
Kuyasu-kun, I didn't know you liked things like that.
Then, do you know White Magic?
– Yeah, I know some.
– Even that Dokugasu is...
And how about us?
This can't be forgiven!
But you know, you did make that first impression...
You're blaming me? Aren't we friends? What
are you gonna do to our friendship?
Calm down, dude. What Yuusuke's saying is true.
Bacchigu, have you tried apologizing in person?
Hey, Futaba-chan.
All right...
To all girls!
Let's forget about the thing that happened before!
Let's be friendly and LOVE each other! Is this okay?
Why don't YOU forget it?!
You haven't apologized enough!
Apologized?
Idiot!
Yuck!
Die!
Dirty old man!
Damn you!
Yuusuke-kun!
Chitose.
Ijuuin-kun and Ichibanboshi-kun, hello.
Who is Ijuuin?
Is there someone with that name?
There isn't.
It's me, ME! Why would you forget me?
You idiot! That name is wasted on a pervert like you!
Note: In Japan, the name Ijuun sounds
like a name of a rich boy.
Shut up, bitch!
WHAT?
Futaba-chan and Ijuuin-kun, let's not fight.
Midori-chan, there's no way that we
could be friends with guys like them!
"Guys like them?"
I don't think they're bad people.
How can you think a guy who does
perverted acts isn't a bad person?!
Futaba-chan, about that incident...
I think our mischief went too far.
So we're very sorry!
Don't come...
Near me!
Futaba-chan!
Can you breathe?
I'm in love!
She's an adult.
Socho's gone, right?
Guys, what are you...
Dude, what do you think about Chitose Midori?
What do you mean by that? Well... huh?
She comes to talk with us even
though she's in a different class!
Y... yeah.
Maybe if I put it this way, even someone as
thick as you can understand. She's in love.
She is?
With me.
Eh?
She gave me tons of emotion! It wouldn't
be manly to do nothing about it!
Wha?
I'm not into this sort of thing...
Ichibanboshi?
But we only have one day left.
I'll make that aggressive girl fall in love with
me and make her say "Ichibanboshi-sama!".
Hey!
– I'll be a man!
– What are you guys talking about?
In short.
Sneaky night-love.
Sneaky night-love?
Chitose... Chitose is in danger!
Calm down. There's no need to worry.
B... but!
It's a girl's dormitory, they're bound to be prepared...
Prepared?
Aah! A pervert!
– What? Where?!
– Mother, how are you?
We are in the city right now.
The city is a very scary place.
Today, thanks to Ichibanboshi, I've
met yet another tragic situation!
It's your fault.
No, it's your fault.
No no, It's your fault.
Definitely your fault.
Wha-wha-wha-WHAT?
It's a false accusation!
Right? Right? Yuusuke, I was in the dorm, right?!
Huh? Yeah...
Liar!
First of all, you're saying that we
caused last night's commotion,
but do you have any evidence? Futaba-chan?
How did you get those scars?
Th... these?
I tripped when we were chasing a female beetle...
Sounds cheesy!
H-hey! Yuusuke, it was a female beetle this big, right?
Ye... yeah...
Tell the truth right now!
– Liar!
– I can't believe you!
You're the worst.
Alright! That's enough.
From what I've heard, there isn't any evidence
that would prove that they're the culprits.
But...
Man! We were falsely accused
and my feelings are hurt.
I'm bleeding from my scar, Mama!
I lived without lying...
Mama! What's so bad about me?
Mama! Am I a bad kid?
Tell me, Mama!
But still! Chitose Midori-san's underwear got stolen!
W... wait! We didn't do that!
Y... yeah! We didn't have enough time to do that...
So it WAS you guys!
Then it's decided!
We will have you guys leave immediately!
Yeah! Get out!
Get out!
Go back to the country!
Geez, everyone, wait!
If you people say so, then I can't help it!
Are you going to leave?
How can we go home when we've been
accused of being underwear thieves!
We will prove our innocence by catching the real thief!
Yeah, that's right!
"Catching?" But how?
Hey, Yuusuke?
Wh-Why am I involved?!
Geez, why are we involved...?
Hey, are you keeping watch?
Yeah I am, since I'm good at looking at things...
Damn, even at night the city is very hot.
By now we should be sleeping
in our air-conditioned room.
– Whose fault do you think this is?
– That's why we're also patrolling!
Yeah. Don't be so harsh, dude.
It only natural!
But it's so hot that my sweat won't stop dripping.
Yuusuke, handkerchief!
I don't have one.
How about you, Ichibanboshi?
Handkerchief?
Kerchief!
Here!
Thank you.
But can we really catch the thief?
We're leaving tomorrow, you know.
I think it's alright if we don't catch him.
Someday, the real thief will be
caught and maybe they'll say:
"Oh! We've done something bad to Ijuuin-kun!"
"Oh yeah! I'll write him a letter!"
Oh! What a well-thought plan!
Also, these type of guys are addicted, so they
can't control their desire, and may come again.
It could happen, you know!
Don't start saying stupid things like that.
That's a trap.
Say so earlier!
By the way, there should be a bunch of
pitfalls with spike traps around here!
Are they out to kill us?
Hmm?
Here, it's a present.
I'm sorry, all because of my underwear...
Don't worry about it. We're
doing this to clear ourselves.
Yuusuke-kun.
Hmm?
Please confess. I won't tell anyone.
Eh?
Yuusuke-kun, the one who tried to make "sneaky
night-love" with me was you, wasn't it?
Eh?
You're the one who stole my underwear, right?
N-no I didn't! Seriously, I didn't!
I see... Just as I thought.
How disappointing.
Eh...?
Why are you so kind to us guys?
I'm not being kind to "you guys".
You're not?
Gosh, you're dull aren't you?
Eh?
Apart from that... can I ask you Question #1?
Y... yeah.
Why did you protect me?
Protect you? When?
Remember the first time we met at the nurse's office.
I poured water on you and you
didn't say anything to the nurse.
Oh... that.
Yeah!
Umm, there's no deep meaning to it.
Are you sure?
If I had to pick one...
Had to pick one...?
...I don't know?
Question #2! Why are you asking me that?
Eh? Umm... Well...
How should I say this... There's no deep meaning to it.
I see.
This rice ball is delicious!
What's wrong?
Nothing!
So there are this many stars...
Eh?
I don't look up at the night sky very often.
There are more stars than this.
More?
Yeah. Since my school is in the countryside...
The air is clearer, and even though they're
the same stars, they look brighter.
There's way more than this.
And even when there isn't a moon,
the stars can light up the mountains.
I would like to see a starlit sky like that. Yuusuke-kun.
Hmm?
Question #3. Could I visit you sometime?
Of course! Anytime!
Then, it's a promise.
Was it a dream?
I'm sorry. I fell asleep.
No, it's alright.
Well then, good luck.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
You did it, huh! I know you did it!
Did what?
"Look at the stars!"
Ok, repeat!
Again! Release!
Relax and Sex!
You did it right?
– You did it right?
– What?
Hey. What are you doing?
He ditched rounds and flirted with a girl!
Flirted with a girl?!
What are you talking about? No! That's not it!
No, well, it's not wrong... I guess...
But I wasn't flirting!
LOVE!
– That hurts...
– Are you okay?
– Yuusuke-don, are you okay?
This is the true culprit!
Well, in this season, the grown-up chicks
leave the nest and become independent.
And they take practically anything to make their nest.
Tenjin-sempai, you have a wide range
of knowledge... you're well informed.
Thanks.
Could I talk with you a bit?
Hmm?
Actually...! saw it in the rice cracker
bag... It said, "A cute good story".
Man, and you called us underwear thieves.
Umm...
Ah! That!
Those are the panties that I lost last night!
Th-this...
As I thought, you're a...!
Wait!
I see... So you love me that much?
The fact that you touched my
breasts at the haunted house...
The fact that you were watching
my slip during tennis practice...
I couldn't forgive it.
So this was... all Ijuuin-kun... No, Darling!
They were expressions of love... for me...
Darling!
So, what is it?
Umm, if you want to, you could come to
our school for the supplementary class!
Yuusuke-kun?
Chitose!
Wh... what?
– We're going home right now!
– Why?
Darling! Touch my breasts!
Oh, why are you so embarrassed!
H... help!
Darling! I got you!
Stop it! Don't touch me! Don't
lick me! Don't bite me!
– You're noisy, Darling!
– Stop!
Why me?
We, who "Fell in love" on a morning, were puzzled.
aru asa ni mezamete "koi wo shita" bokura wa tomadotta
The scenery that was sliding repainted everything.
slide wo shite yuku fuukei ga subete wo nuri kaeta
Is this a feeling that a precious
treasure turning into a trash?
daiji na takaramono ga gomi ni nacchau kanji?
We can go anywhere together.
doko demo issho ni ikeru yo
Where is the answer to the love and kiss?
koi to kiss no kotae wa doko ni aruno?
Going out from the isolated yesterday.
tozasareteru kinou wo nukedashite
Where is if going embracing you?
kimi wo dakishime doko ni ikuno?
Even the sadness, which is dreaming,
yume wo miteru kanashimi ya sayonara ga
and the goodbye is waiting for the two.
futari wo mattetemo