Rekka...
Episode 2
Darkness
This is terrible.
Take a look at that.
Was it caused by those barbaric demons?
Could be.
The one who did this
was a pretty tough one.
How are you able to tell?
You can tell by the wounds.
The mark of a demon hunter.
A demon fighter who hunted
demons in the foreign lands.
Our new mission is to
meet up with her...
...and recruit her into
the Crimson Lotus.
Building up our force, huh?
I see. That doesn't
surprise me at all, seeing this.
This is where we were supposed to meet.
I hope she doesn't come
around all late and ditsy.
Akane!
You don't have to be so mean.
Haruka!
Damn!
No!
No! Stop!
Why, you!
Are you injured?
I'm okay. All thanks to you.
That's quite the skill.
Are you Kureha, the demon hunter?
I've heard all about you guys.
You must be the Crimson Lotus.
Thank goodness.
Does this mean you'll
be traveling with us?
I don't think so.
Huh?
I've managed well on
my own all this time.
I'm not about to join
together with strangers.
But that's not what...
And I don't like the fact
that your leader is a man.
What? Me?
I don't want to be told what to do
by a stupid creature like a man.
Uh, but wait...!
How amazing!
A mummy woman?
Yeah. Her whole body was bandaged up.
If your eyes meet hers, that it for you.
I heard that she'll strangle you
to death with her bandages.
Pretty frightening.
What's the matter, Ayano?
You don't seem your self.
A failed mission.
This is the responsibility of all of us!
If only we were able to meet
up with Kureha earlier.
It's all because you took us on
a wild goose chase.
What'd you say?
Now, now...
It's because Rekka's a man!
So, you're going to make it my fault?
I guess we'll just have to
succeed with the next order.
Do we have another mission order?
Looking into that mummy woman?
That's not it.
I'm talking demons. Demons.
At the main castle of Azuchi...
...there's apparently a major demon
called Burai there.
He's seriously into women...
...and the townspeople are really
having a problem with it.
Burai.
I've heard rumors about him.
Sounds like a tough one.
Seems that way.
The order says even I have to go.
Now that that's set.
We'll leave first thing tomorrow!
Yeah!
"Temporarily Closed
- Away on mission"
- Misaki, Proprietor -
Boy, I'm exhausted.
Well, let's rest here for a bit.
But we really have to be careful.
All those who have sought to fight
Burai...
...were killed in this area.
Rumor has it that this is where we
start to fight amongst ourselves.
Really?
Dear god. I pray that we members of the
Crimson Lotus are able to...
...get along forever.
Well.
That Haruka sure knows
the proper thing to do.
You both can learn a
thing or two from her.
How about we check things out?
There doesn't seem to be
anything unusual here.
Oh, right.
I should take the opportunity to
pray for good business at my inn.
I'll pray with you.
Thanks, Haruka.
We pray that we can expand into a
national chain of outlets.
Thank you!
Akane?
What's the matter?
Do you have a stomachache?
Akane! What're you doing?!
Ayano!
H-Hey...!
My name is Sai.
I am going to take this woman's body!
What?!
Stop it, Akane!
W-Wait a minute, Akane!
Akane! That's enough!
Get a hold of yourself!
Please, Akane.
Please go back to yourself!
Damn!
We have no choice!
Let's just get out of here!
Hey! What's the matter?!
There's some kind of monster
called Sai at the shrine!
Is that so? You're off to fight Burai.
Sai is one of Burai's henchmen.
As long as you don't have the mirror
that seals the demons away...
...you will not be able to even get
close to the town of Azuchi.
What is this mirror that
seals the demons away?
You mean, you don't even
know about the mirror?
We weren't given that information.
It would be impossible to defeat
Sai without that mirror.
But, in order to get that mirror,
you will have to fight...
...the multitude of demons
that protect it.
That won't be very easy.
Well, I'd like to hear more about it.
But we had to abandon
one from our group.
Good grief...
Well, this is your lucky day.
Kureha!
Here.
That's it! The mirror that
seals away demons!
I'm amazed you were able to get it.
Thanks, Kureha.
I felt a bit guilty about
taking off on my own.
I've decided to join you
for at least the next while.
Really, Kureha?!
I couldn't sit by and watch you fall
flat on your face, after all.
What is this place?
What is this?! What's going on here?!
Akane, you sure made a mess of things
before!
Now, get me out of this!
Wh-What do you plan on doing?
Look! What's all this about?!
No! Stop this!
Akane! I can't take anymore of this!
Please!
Y-Yes...! More...!
Y-Yes! Right there!
This is it! This is
what I was waiting for!
I feel like I'm going to melt!
Akane! Ayano!
Are you safe?!
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
The two of you!
Stay out of this!
Get out of here, kid!
Damn! You'll pay for this, Sai!
Just take a look at this!
Don't tell me that's...!
...the mirror that seals away demons!
You goddamn Lotus! You'll pay for that!
All right! I'll finish
you off right now!
Hold on!
As for him!
We're the ones...
...who will beat him to death!
Piercing wind storm!
I've got you!
You did it!
You two were so amazing!
How could we lose against
a stupid demon like that?
Nothing is amazing about us winning.
Thank goodness. It looks like
you two might get along, after all.
It's hopeless.
And I even prayed for them.
Strange bunch you are.
Hey. There's a light.
Great! A place to spend the night!
And I'm starving!
This inn sure seems suspicious.
Good taste in design, though.
What? That?
Welcome.
I am the proprietor of this inn.
I've been waiting for you
with bell a-ringin'.
Now, now. Go right in.
The roads are very confusing
around here.
You could spend all night
walking in circles.
I've got six customers coming in!
Wow! It looks delicious!
You folks are awfully lucky, you know.
As this is our opening night, food and
lodging are completely free!
Then why are we the only guests here?
The others have been so taken by the
comfort here that they've retired.
But, in any case, Lord Burai is finally
going to be defeated tomorrow.
So, I want you to have yourself a feast!
Lord Burai?
Thanks for the meal!
Enjoy your stay.
Something just doesn't seem right.
Now, how could you be
eating away like that...
...without any fear of anything?
But this is really good. Right?
That's right! It's even
better than it looks!
You think?
I wouldn't put out anything that smells
or tastes like that at my place.
What's going on?!
Quit playing games, you pervert!
Didn't the sleeping potion work on you?!
I'm impressed, Lotus. You saw right
through my secret plan!
Anybody would think
you're obviously suspicious!
But these two are fast asleep.
That's because...
I get it!
They sacrificed themselves
to lure me in.
Th-That's right.
Crimson Lotus sure are to be feared!
Fine, then.
In congratulations, I'll reveal
to you who I really am.
I am Nuu, a loyal retainer
of Lord Burai.
Right, then. How about
you tell us about Burai?
Burai is a man to be feared,
especially by the likes of you Lotus.
I suggest it would be wise
for you to submit to me now.
Enough messing around!
Good-bye, then!
Stinky!
They say that Burai captures
6 women from the village...
...every month on a particular day.
If anybody were to try to resist him,
as retribution...
...he will sacrifice 5 times or even 10
times that number.
As such, we have no choice but to offer
our women to him every month.
Let's see. Remove those hats
and let's see your faces.
I'm only after your flesh,
but pretty faces...
...sure can get my appetite going.
I can smell it.
I can smell the charade
you women are putting on.
I wanted to introduce myself.
So, it's the Crimson Lotus.
You are an enemy of women!
You will not be forgiven.
Look at you now, you fools!
Down you go!
Take this!
You all right, Kureha?
Somehow.
It seems we've been
separated from the others.
Men sure are stupid and simple-minded.
Look at where your plan has got us.
We'll get out of here.
Huh?
Burai spared our lives.
Which means he's going
to deal with us later.
Until then...
...I'll put my money on us
rotting to death in this place.
Really. I'm surprised you're
willing to give up so easily.
There!
We've been waiting, old man!
Take this!
It's useless.
I will become the ruler of the world!
This one looks tasty!
After I deal with him...
I will have a taste of your blood!
No way!
What crazy power.
You are nothing more than human.
Can't expect more than that.
Lotus man. It's almost time
that you die!
The ultimate, great sorcerer!
Rekka!
He's finished.
Th-The shadow technique...!
How could this be?!
And before I am able to realize
my dream of ruling the world!
That was close.
You're just too much...
You're injured!
Oh, this is nothing.
More importantly,
are you injured at all?
I'm fine...
Rekka, I...
Kureha...!
I'm going to cum.
Cum inside of me!
Oh, there they are.
Rekka! Kureha!
Is everyone all right?
They already got Burai.
That's Rekka for you.
We found the exit! Let's get going!
That Burai was apparently defeated
by those crazy Crimson Lotus.
I suppose that's a proper end
for one who had spurned us.
Now, setting that aside, I hope that
everything else is in place.
Yes. The plan is underway.
What them?
Chiyomaru. Out for a nighttime walk?
Hey. Where did you find this?
I'm just going to borrow it.
Rekka, dinner's all ready.
Huh? Chiyomaru, where did Rekka go?
Tsukikage...
Rekka, this is for you.
This is a symbol that you and I
will always be together.
So, don't you lose it.
Tsukikage, are you still alive?
That's...!