All right. You'll be fine.
Good night.
Rekka...
Retreat! Retreat!
You screwed up.
Did you let him get away?
He's losing it. It won't be much longer.
Finish him off?
No need for that.
I see.
This is as it should be.
Episode 3
Laughter
We failed again on our mission.
I don't think you should be saying that.
Huh?
Boy, you're slow.
You're not supposed to say
things like "failed mission"...
...or "missed opportunity"...
...or that it was a "complete screw up."
Never say that in front of you-know-who.
Oh, is that right?
You're talking about Ayano.
It didn't occur to me. I'm sorry.
Not occur to you...?!
You don't have to apologize to me!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, at least we were able to confirm
there's a major demon here.
We can't call it a complete failure
even though a demon didn't come out.
That's right, Ayano.
It's actually better that a
major demon doesn't appear.
You don't have to keep telling me that!
You're...!
Rekka!
Hey! What's the matter?!
Come on! Get up!
Poor thing. What a terrible injury.
He probably escaped
from the Black Steel.
Based on the injury, anyway.
But look at this as well.
It's a scar from an operation.
What do those Black Steel think
they're doing, anyway?
They call themselves assassins,
but they always keep their demons.
Don't you think that's strange?
You guys... We meet again.
I have a favor to ask you.
I want you to take this opportunity...
...to cut me down right now.
Mr. Gremlin...
What them?!
Let her go!
Everybody, out front! Get out front!
I-It's huge!
Don't tell me the giant
demon Ayano saw...
...was actually you?!
Mr. Gremlin! But, why?!
We've got to stop him here!
But how?
I don't know what the
Black Steel did to him...
...but all I can say now is that...
...that gremlin doesn't exist anymore!
I'm sorry, Mr. Gremlin!
Mr. Gremlin...
Thank you.
Huh?
Now I won't be able to...
...cause you all any more trouble.
Did the Black Steel do this to you?
I completely forgot...
That after I became a great demon...
...I could've kept on smiling.
If I did that...
...I wouldn't have been
hated by everyone.
I really screwed up...
Mr. Gremlin...
What?
So, the number of sex murders
caused by demons has gone up, huh?
Yes.
Even though we're working
so hard to get rid of them.
It could only mean that the
number of demons has been rising.
Where could they all be coming from?
Come to think of it...
What is it?
About a year ago, there were
a number of incidents...
...where some members
of the Kagemai died...
...leaving messages
about becoming demons.
What was that all about?
We still don't know the cause.
What's the matter?
I have to talk to you.
It's said that my step brother
was in the Kagemai...
...and that he died fighting a demon.
Right.
That's not exactly true.
What?!
That was a lie.
A lie?!
My brother was a bright,
strong and dependable Kagemai.
Dear brother...?
Stay away!
A demon... A demon's possessed me!
Brother...
A demon has possessed me!
What's the matter, Brother?
The demon...! The demon...!
How are you feeling, Brother?
Misaki, I'm finished...
What are you talking about?
You're just tired.
I'll leave your dinner here,
so make sure you eat. Okay?
I just know it. I'm going
to turn into a demon soon.
I've been possessed by a demon.
How could something like
that happen to you?
But it's actually happening!
B-Brother...!
Those sure look tasty.
No! Stop it!
You want me to stop?
By wanting me to stop...
...you mean this?
No, no... No!
I'm not your brother anymore.
So, let's not get all hung up with
things. Let's enjoy ourselves.
Stop! Please, stop! Brother!
Brother...!
What have I... What have I done?
I learned later...
...that my brother had
investigated the Black Steel.
Maybe he was also...
Just like what happened to that gremlin.
Misaki, thanks for telling me.
You're going to destroy the Black Steel?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I just don't like them!
You've got to calm down, Rekka.
I understand how you feel, but that's
still no excuse.
Like the Crimson Lotus, the Black
Steel's aim is to fight demons.
It's not right for one to be so hateful
of the other.
Yeah, but...
Besides...
They're not required to state publicly
what their activities are...
...so even if you asked the Elder,
you wouldn't find out what they do.
However...
You're going to go, anyway. Right?
You're going to Kigan Castle,
where they're based, right?
You're not one to give up, no matter
how much I try to stop you, after all.
Tsukikage...
Please, come back alive.
I'm impressed, Rekka.
But it's pointless heading
off into the darkness.
How about I lead you in from here?
Well?
Why would you Black Steel
give us a hand?
I am Akagane.
I have sworn my allegiance...
...to Lord Yasha,
the leader of the Black Steel.
But I've been having some second
thoughts about this recently.
What do you mean?
There are moments when I succumb to
emotion like you guys.
That may actually be a good thing.
I question whether I should continue as
a Black Steel...
Then again...
...after my hesitation, I thought I'd
leave it to you to decide for me.
That's why I let the gremlin go.
What is the Black Steel up to?
I want you to see with your own eyes.
Th-This is...!
A secret factory run by the Black Steel.
Akagane!
Those people are of the Crimson Lotus!
What are you trying to do?
Are you thinking of
betraying Lord Yasha?
Gennai...
This isn't a question of
loyalty and betrayal.
This is so that I can clear the
confusion in my heart.
Don't you feel it as well?
Confusion?
What kind of confusion could there be
in this superhuman research?
Take a good look.
The beautiful children
that I have created.
The result of my
long years of research.
By fusing humans and demons into one...
...one can create a superhuman
race that combines the...
...intelligence of humans with the
violent instincts of the demons.
Superhuman race?
The Black Steel is a
superhuman organization.
Our goals are to develop
a true superhuman race...
...that goes well beyond the
capabilities of humans.
Is this why you always kept
the demons you defeated?!
If that's the case, then why don't
you take the form of a demon?
The research is not yet complete.
If you fuse humans and
demons together...
...in the worst case, one's spirit gets
taken away by the demon...
...and one simply turns
into a pure demon.
What?!
Of course, we dispose of
all of the defective ones.
In other words, we release
them into the wild.
So, there're more demons out there
because they're made here?!
What do you think you're doing?!
What do you think I'm doing?
Don't play stupid with me!
How dare you play with human lives!
You will pay!
I...
...will never forgive you!
The same goes for us!
Akagane! Stop this! Make them stop this!
You really did betray me this time,
didn't you?!
What?!
Yama!
What the hell is this?!
This is Yama, my greatest achievement!
It will become the new superhuman race!
Now, Yama! Eliminate them!
Rekka!
No!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Woman!
What is this monster?
Woman...!
Woman...
What are you doing, Yama?!
Gennai, give me back my woman's body!
Don't tell me that after seeing a
woman's body after all this time...
...human memories are coming back!
S-Stop it!
Stop it!
Stop! Stop this now!
Woman... Gennai...
Give me back my woman's body!
Give it back!
Pathetic!
It's coming! It's rising!
The fire's coming!
Lord Yasha is in the main keep.
Akagane! What's going on?!
Shirogane...
My confusion has cleared.
I cannot allow the Black Steel
to continue existing.
I hope you're ready to
bear the consequences.
Not at all.
Are you Yasha?
Indeed.
I am Yasha, the leader
of the Black Steel.
Are you the Crimson Lotus
who have come to destroy us?
I am Rekka, leader of the anti-demon
brigade Crimson Lotus!
I was in favor of the plan to capture...
...and gather demons and
fuse them with humans.
However...
Without the mental power
needed to beat the demons...
...one becomes simply possessed...
...and then turns into the demon.
I wanted the power.
A great power that can protect
this land from the demons.
Learning of what my desires were,
the Great Elder invited me.
To go "beyond mere human."
What great power?
It's because of sentiments like that...
...that I have an opportunity to emerge.
So, that's what it was about.
So it was the demons that had
led the Black Steel astray!
And what will you do about it?
That's obvious.
I'll kill you!
Akagane, tell me.
Has the Black Steel been
wrong all along?
I'm sure there were times
when we were right.
But we had strayed from
our course without realizing it.
Don't you think?
You may be right...
But since we have sworn allegiance to
Lord Yasha, there was no turning back.
Akagane...
You must follow the path
that you believe is right!
I suppose this is the limit
of your human strength.
Then, how about myself,
who has the blood of demons.
Akagane!
Die!
There is nothing you can do.
Y-You're the great sorcerer
from back then!
Do you know him?!
He's the one who killed my father
the demon fighter 4 years ago.
But that's not all.
All those innocent
people of the village...
Oh, I remember that.
I invited him to join me
and go beyond being human.
The foolish man refused me.
I can't forgive you.
What are you going to do about it?
Hm? This woman...
I shall avenge the deaths...
...of my father and the villagers!
What?!
Haruka!
Rekka!
You came home, Rekka!
Tsukikage...
Tsukikage, we're together again.
Always from now on.
We'll always be together, Rekka.
Rekka!
What is this all about?!
I'm so terribly sorry.
Damn!
I want to rule the entire world
as soon as possible!
Yes, sir!
I wonder how she was able to
draw out the demon within her.
Who knows. Let's just pray that...
...that people like that
don't appear again.
I think a lot of people
would be saved...
...now that the Black Steel is gone.
If something like that appears again...
...we just have to go and destroy them!
That's right.
That's right. That's right.
Yeah, that's exactly right.