Tsukikage!
Are you all right, Tsukikage?!
Yeah.
Rekka, are you okay?
Yeah, somehow.
Shit! There's more of them!
You get out of here, Rekka.
Leave this one to me.
What are you talking about? We're...
There's no way I'll live through this.
I can't have you die here along with me.
Now, you get going!
Tsukikage!
Hurry up and get away!
If you were to die here,
who will then be able to stop them?!
Tsukikage!
Rekka!
Rekka... Rekka...
As the young leader
of the Crimson Lotus...
...your mission is to defeat the demons.
Crimson Lotus...?
Rekka! Get away from here!
Tsukikage...?
We, the Crimson Lotus, are an
anti-demon brigade formed under...
...the direct command of the
Shogun to destroy the demons.
If you were to die here, who will
then be able to stop them?!
Rekka!
Tsukikage!
Well, so you're finally awoken.
How are you feeling?
Uh, um... Where am I...?
I found you lying by the riverbank.
It sure was tough
carrying you back here.
Here. You must be hungry.
There's no poison in it.
Now, eat.
I'll help myself to it then.
Thanks very much.
Old lady... Old lady...?
Where did she go?
Is she in here?
What them?!
Who are you?!
What?
Uh, well, I was just...
No, I was just...!
Pervert!
No!
Please help me!
Let go of her, you demon!
Damn!
This village is the one that
Tsukikage and I were going to.
Sex murders thought to
be perpetrated by demons...
...have been taking place
in various parts recently.
In order to pin down what
this mayhem was about...
...we were supposed to gather here with
the other Crimson Lotus warriors.
Tsukikage would've checked
out the place...
...and would've been waiting for me
and the rest of our group.
Those were my naive expectations.
How dare you come
crawling over here like that!
Not only did you abandon
Tsukikage to her death...
...but you even let a demon
take the woman that saved you!
Unbelievable!
Akane!
I don't think you're being fair.
I'm sure Rekka feels just as badly
about Tsukikage as we do.
I know that much!
I know that. But still...
There was nothing I could say.
When we were brought to the
Crimson Lotus while we were kids...
...we were only taught how to fight,
without being told of our purpose.
During those endless days of brutal
training we had to endure...
...it was Tsukikage who supported us
and kept our morale up.
The words of Akane and Ayano
who suddenly appeared...
...were biting into me along
with my recent experience.
I-It appeared!
Another demon?!
Yeah! When I was
walking in the forest...
...it just suddenly appeared!
I ran away as fast as I could,
'cause I thought I'd get eaten!
I bet that's the one!
I bet that's the one that
kidnapped my daughter!
Damn!
Now, let's go!
How much longer are you going to sulk?!
That might be the same woman
as the one that saved you!
That's right. We might
still make it in time.
Let's hurry!
Right.
This is the area that those
villagers were talking about.
That cabin looks pretty
suspicious to me.
Let's go check it out.
What should we do?
Someone must be out back.
Let's just charge him
at once and be done with it.
That would be way too reckless!
What if he wasn't the one we're after?
We'll deal with that then.
Huh?
So, you live here?
Yes.
I used to have friends
and such around, but...
...they were attacked
by the Black Steel one day.
The Black Steel?
So, I'm all alone now.
But if I don't keep at it, no one will
be there to protect the forest.
I have to make up for
the friends who were taken.
I'd say that we were
thinking the same thing.
Even if he may be harmless to people...
...he's still a demon.
Can we allow a demon
to live free like this out here?
We can't be sure he'll never reveal
his true nature and attack people.
If only I didn't look like this.
Huh?
The people of the village are terrified
when they see me.
Why do I have horns like these?
Huh?
You think it would be better
if I always smiled like this?
I'm not like the demons who
kidnap women from the village.
What? Do you know where
those other demons are?
Yeah. There's a bamboo
forest just a little further away.
They hang out in the
cave at the far end.
Take care.
Come and see me sometime.
Next time, I'll serve up some tasty
delights found in this forest.
All right. I'm sure we'll be by again.
Akane, why didn't you kill that demon?
That's because he was...
I mean, he didn't do anything wrong.
What about you?
I suppose you're right.
Even if he is a demon...
...he's not an enemy of ours
unless he's out to harm people.
Yes.
We do want to avoid fighting any
unnecessary battles, after all.
And there are other demons that
we should be going after anyway.
Yeah.
Stop it!
No! Please stop!
How detestable!
Rekka, that woman's...!
No.
It's from that cave!
Rekka, you have to go!
You can leave this to us!
All right!
No...!
I feel like... I feel like
I'm going to burst...!
Please stop...!
Stop it!
I'm going to burst...!
Who is this woman who lies
collapsed at my feet?
If she weren't here
in this wretched scene...
...that would be the face of any
ordinary woman gently sleeping.
I pondered her predicament.
Burdened by such a power
that transforms her...
...she lay secretly in waiting.
Beneath the innocence of
this expression of hers.
...what amount of darkness lies?
So, you're name is Haruka.
It must've been pretty rough.
If you've got nowhere to go,
why don't you join us?
What?
Are you sure about that?
Of course.
Right, Rekka?
Sure.
Now, what's the matter with this dog?!
Akane! You picked him up, right?!
Do something about him!
Well, isn't she scary.
Why are you attracted
to such a stinky place?
What did you say?!
Oh, Ayano, could this dog be a male...
...or a female?
Can't you tell by the way
that stupid dog is behaving?!
How dare you call him "stupid."
Oh, now, have you already
given him a name?
It's Chiyomaru.
Chiyomaru?
What a boring name that is.
Th-That's not it at all!
I just tried it out on him before.
That's all.
Of course.
Chiyomaru would be in
such bad taste, after all.
Then, can you think of a better name?
How about "Whitey"?
But he's not white!
How about something like "Bean"?
Huh? "Bean"?
No. Not Mr. Bean.
I mean, "bean" as in bean bread.
Bean bread?
I love bean bread.
D-Doesn't seem quite right, does it?
Uh, yeah...
How about we all call out
a name at the same time...
...and we'll make it the
name he responds to.
Oh, that sounds like such fun.
All right, then. Let's try it.
One, two...
- Whitey.
- Bean.
- Chiyo.
Don't you understand the
trouble we're going through!
You stupid!
I think Chiyomaru's about right.
I just can't fall asleep.
Can I come in?
Sure.
Why didn't you tell
them about me before?
That I'm not exactly normal.
But I don't actually
understand it myself.
What that power was,
or why I became like that.
It must be the ugly demon blood
that courses through my body.
We were organized as a
brigade to fight the demons.
But I learned today...
...that not all demons are evil.
But you fought against the demons...
...who captured all those innocent
women from the village.
There's no need to get
everyone all upset.
Besides, I do kind of
owe my life to you.
Thank you, Rekka.
I was really happy.
When I was asked if I
wanted to join you guys...
...I started feeling guilty
about my true nature.
I've been alone all this time.
I was so happy until that day
when those demons showed up.
They took everything away from me.
My family, my friends...
...and everything else.
I lost my parents as well.
Or, perhaps I should say I
don't even remember them.
Before you saved me...
...there was one other
woman who saved me.
When I was younger...
...I had lost my memory, and was
apparently wandering the forests.
The leader of the Crimson Lotus then
found me and adopted me.
I had sword wounds all over my body.
I was close to my last breath.
But Tsukikage was there to nurse me
back to health every day.
After that, we did everything together.
Bathing together, eating together.
She treated me as though
I were truly her little brother.
At times, even like her child.
It made my training with
Crimson Lotus much easier.
All because she was there for me.
Having lost my memory...
...she was the only one
who made me feel at ease.
You feel so strongly about Tsukikage.
From now on, I will be
the one to protect you, Rekka.
I won't let the demons get to you.
Haruka...
I'm sorry. Maybe I've said too much.
No, you mustn't. You have Tsukikage!
I'm just a...
You mustn't.
Haruka...
You mustn't be doing this.
Rekka, you mustn't! I'm...
No, you really mustn't! I'm filthy!
There's demon blood in me...
It's all right.
No!
It's dirty down there.
It's embarrassing!
No! It's dirty!
No!
I...
Ow!
You really mustn't be doing this!
Ow! That hurts!
I have a filthy body...
Rekka...
...I'm not worthy...
It's all right. You are just yourself.
No!
I can't take anymore!
I feel like I'm going to go crazy!
Somethings not right.
Haruka?
I'm...
Rekka!
What's the matter?
I'm hot.
I'm hot all over.
I'm going crazy! I'm going crazy!
I'm going to cum!
I can't take it anymore!
Haruka...
Oh, my. What have I done.
How embarrassing.
Hey, he's gone that way!
Kill him, quick!
You bastard!
What's all the ruckus?
What are you doing?!
Can't you tell? We just
arrested one of them demons!
What do you mean, "arrested"?
You're just a lynch mob
attacking a defenseless creature.
It's okay. It's all my fault.
I thought I'd bring some of
these to you guys, but...
...I suppose I'm not supposed
to come to where humans live.
Sorry for causing all the trouble.
Now.
You're going soft, Lotus.
Letting a demon off like that.
What do you want?
Please stop.
The Kagemai.
Just like the Crimson Lotus,
those men also belong to a brigade...
...whose mission it is to hunt down
and capture demons.
They are the Black Steel.
What?
I can't blame you for
not knowing about us.
Unlike you...
...we are under the direct
command of the Great Elder.
Although the Kagemai and
the Crimson Lotus are charged with...
...with investigation and solving
incidents related to demons...
...the Black Steel are strictly
an assassin brigade.
I would say their fighting ability is
beyond that of the Crimson Lotus.
What?!
We will take this one with us.
What are you going to do with him?
This is prey that we hunted down.
What we do to it has
nothing to do with you.
Let's go!
Damn!