I'm only rubbing you gently.
Are you that sensitive?
Why am I being tied up... and treated this way?
Look at you, all tied up and hard as a rock.
No wonder you're such a perverted priest!
Priest!? I don't know what she's talking about.
Isn't she ashamed of being in such an outfit?
What do you think you're looking at?
Do you even realize your position as the defendant?
Defendant!? And who are YOU!?
My, how rude.
E-Enma-senpai!?
Enma Kaoru-senpai, the most popular girl who's
said to be the Madonna of our school.
Senpai... What is this?
Defendant Aiba Sakae, we will now
start the Reverse Witch Trial.
Reverse... Witch Trial!?
Yes, for you are the priest who has
come to hunt me, the witch.
What the hell are you talking about!?
Don't pretend you don't know what I'm talking about,
you perverted priest!
I'm not a pervert or a priest!
No, you are definitely a pervert.
You've been hard non-stop since you've
been watching me from the sidewalk.
And even now...
How could I not be hard, being forced
to look at something like this!
Well, the trial is unnecessary since
you are obviously guilty.
But I will give you a chance.
What? What does that mean!?
If you say you're not a pervert,
try stopping yourself from staying hard right now.
That's impossible!
Then will you admit it?
That you are a perverted priest, hunting me down?
There's no way I can keep this down
under these circumstances.
Look! It's even more excited than it
was before. This perverted cock!
You like it, don't you? Then just
cum and admit it all now!
You pervert!
I admit! I will admit it!
Good! Cum! You perverted dick!
I'm cumming!
Until a little while ago, I was just an ordinary
school boy you'd find anywhere.
Just how did this happen?
Reverse Witch Trial
Judged by the Slutty Witch
Translation: Nagisa Rikuma | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
I had just changed schools and I had no friends.
Days went by without much activity.
Sakae-kun.
Class rep.
She is Himeno Yuki.
She is the representative of our class and
takes care of new students like me.
What an angel!
Hey, I told you not to call me that anymore!
It would make me happy if you just called me Yuki-chan.
Sure, I'll be careful.
Anyhow, she's looking cute as usual.
Sakae-kun, what's wrong? You're staring at me.
Oh! No! It's nothing!
What's up?
It seemed like you weren't blending
in too well with the class...
I thought I'd just tell you, I'm always
here for you if you need me.
That day on my way home I saw Enma
Kaoru-senpai, the class idol.
I got rock hard just looking at her ample chest and butt.
E-Enma-senpai...
What's that sweet smell?
And I passed out.
I'll be keeping you company until
there's a decision on your ruling.
You said I was guilty... It was such
a humiliating punishment...
What are you talking about? That
was punishment for stalking me.
It wasn't for whether you're a perverted priest or not.
N-No way!
I wonder what results the various trials will bring about.
Y-You're kidding...
The Reverse Witch Trial huh...
How could this have happened!?
If there's anything I can do, I will do it for you!
No matter what, there's no way I can
ask her to help me with this...
Huh? Did I just fall asleep?
Th-This isn't what I think it is... What should I do?
Sa-Sakae-kun?
Wh-Why is she here!?
It's not what it looks like! There's an explanation for this!
Just listen to what I have to say!
Sure.
Senpai, how did you get here!?
It seems like defendant Aiba Sakae has something to say.
Let's let him have his lawyer.
What? A lawyer? Who could it be?
Her.
What!?
I can't have the class rep be my
lawyer! It's too embarrassing.
I'll cheer you on all the way, Sakae-kun.
So, how did you get a hold of those panties?
I'm sure you just stole them anyway.
I didn't do anything like that! At the time I...
It doesn't look like you have an alibi.
It doesn't matter what your think
of me, because I am... A virgin!
Sakae-kun... I had no idea...
I didn't expect to have to make
such an awkward confession!
If you're so insistent, let's just have you explain it.
Explain... whether I'm a virgin or not?
Yes, with magic!
What is this?
This potion makes someone taste sweet if
they're not a virgin, but bitter if they are.
So bitter they have to stop licking you.
Sakae-kun, I'll give it my all!
Okay... I'll trust you.
Whoa! The class rep is sucking my...
No. It's embarrassing when you say that.
Sorry. If it's bitter, stop right away.
It's okay... It's very...
What did you just say?
Sweet... Sakae-kun, your cock is so sweet...
It makes me want to... Lick some more...
Look who's caught red-handed.
This is absolutely ludicrous! I am a virgin!
Sorry, but this is the result of the potion is absolute.
It's a lie!
This is amazing,
I want to suck more.
I can't believe the goddess-like class rep
is sucking on my cock like a slut.
Damn it.
There's no way she could be enjoying
my dick like it's some kind of fantasy.
I'll make you feel good.
I'll make your dick feel really good.
I want your sweet, sweet cock.
I want more of your love juice.
I want to drink all your sweet juices!
I want it!
I want to swallow it all!
There's so much... cock milk.
Delicious!
Looks like we've come to a conclusion.
Wait! This is all wrong!
Oh? But, you lied that you were a virgin.
I am definitely a V.I.R.G.I.N.
My, you really are persistent.
Well, then I'll do you a favour.
I'll find the owner of those panties for you.
I suppose if we do find out how
I got ahold of the underwear,
my accusations would be lifted.
If you drink this potion, we can see
your past sexual experiences.
Give it to me.
This is there I was...
Who's talking? I know this voice.
Someone's straddling me!
Class rep!
This must be cum from earlier...
Sorry Sakae-kun, I had sex with the physics teacher.
He came so much inside me... but it wasn't enough.
Then I saw you sleeping here, as though
you wanted to be fooled around with.
I can't take it anymore! Your cock is just like a virgin's...
Amazing!
Are you going to cum, Sakae-kun?
Cum! I want you to feed my wet
pussy with your cock juice.
I'm cumming, too! I'm cumming!
My pussy will drink it up for you.
Oh no, I can't leave his cock lying
out like this. Better clean it up!
Oh, I know!
There we go.
It's all clean now, I guess I'll be on my way.
Later, Sakae-kun! Next time you can fool around with me!
See you.
No way!
I will now announce the ruling for this case:
I hereby find defendant, Aiba Sakae, guilty of falsely
testifying that he is a virgin under oath.
And so, I was then forced to do many things...
I sentence defendant Aiba Sakae to be my dog!
I was taken out for a walk in the park at midnight,
and my asshole was exploited.
I was even forced to have sex all night.
Sakae-kun, how are you holding up?
I was invited out by the class rep, who
acted like she worried about me.
Damn you! You slut, I can't believe you tricked me!
OK
You're right, I'm just a whore.
I'm just a girl with a perverted pussy
that wants to do it with everyone!
I was dragged into the bathroom so I
could help that slut Yuki-chan cum...
And sometimes...
I needed this!
So you want a mature man's penis
more than your boyfriend's huh?
Yes!
It's so great!
My classmate's virgin cock isn't enough!
I don't want that tiny dick, I want all your fat cocks!
She shattered my pride as a man
by making me watch her cum with homeless men.
Seems like you've taken a liking to my slut lately.
What slut?
Yuki of course. Who else?
It's true, I am attracted to Yuki.
But if I stay a slave...
In that case, I'm going to do things the way I want to!
I'm going to devour her sexy body!
That's all I want!
I'm gonna cum all over that perverted slut!
So you've made plans to see her tonight?
How did you know that?
I told you, she's my slut.
Alright then, today I sentence you to hold it in!
What are you going to do?
I just said you're forbidden from cumming. See ya later!
No way! I'm going to have sex with Yuki-chan!
I don't even know how many days it's been, but
my dick's been blocked from being able to cum.
Senpai!.. Senpai... Is that you?
You've been a good boy.
Hurry up and take this off!
How many time must I repeat myself?
You're banned from cumming.
You must be having such a terrible time.
Do you want to cum that badly?
Isn't it obvious?
I have no idea, can you tell me in your own words?
I want to cum...
Be loud and clear!
I want to cum! I want to cum a lot!
Oh really?
Very well, very well.
This is what I've been waiting for.
Alright then, I'll give you this.
Now announce it before you cum.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I'm gonna explode!
Very well.
It's coming, it's coming!
It's like milk machine!
Where is all of this semen coming from?
It's so smelly...
I can't stop. Senpai, help me!
Here, I stopped it for you.
Senpai your boobs feel too good, I'm gonna...
It's shaking so violently between my boobs!
Don't tell me you're cumming again.
They're too... soft.
Then I'll suck it all up for you.
How can you cum so much, I only put it in my mouth.
Just what kind of fetish do you have?
But it's your magic...
No excuses!
What a cute weiner...
There's cum all the way up your shaft.
Please stop!
It's so tight! I'm being sucked in...
You want to cum right?
Go ahead.
Cum. Cum all you want!
I'm... cumming...
Help...
But it looks like you haven't had enough yet.
Now time for some real fun!
I'll let you... come inside my pussy.
You came so many times, but you're still so hard.
Senpai, your pussy feels too good!
What are you talking about?
You don't care who it is, so long
as you can cum in their pussy.
You're right. My slut cock will take any pussy. But...
But what? Just say it.
Your pussy feels different from Yuki-san's.
Your pussy feels too good!
It's coming... Your hot stuff is...
Is it really that different?
It's totally different. It's incomparable!
Does it really feel that good?
Oh my god, I'm feeling it too.
I'm being fucked by a slave, and
feeling it all the way inside.
Are you cumming again? Are you still cumming?
Are you feeding me your smelly cock juice?
Sure, just let it... out.
My womb is being filled with your cum!
I'm miserable. But this feels so amazing!
I'm cumming again!
It's your reward.
This...
Your dick is getting hard again!
That's right. If you're a pervert, you'll understand.
This is a more powerful aphrodisiac.
I'm tired already! My dick hurts... It feels so good.
More, more!
That's right, more... You must pour your juices into me.
You have to get closer to my belly!
Pump harder and cum inside me!
I will make you feel good!
Yes, yes, very good. I knew you could do it.
Very good, I'm cummingl I'm cumming!
More, pump more!
Keep thrusting that dirty, pathetic cock into my womb!
Keep thrust harder into my womb!
Senpai, I'm cumming!
It can't be helped. I'll cum with you.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
You didn't think you were getting
away with this, were you?
You mean... it's not over?
Why of course! This is only the beginning.
It feel so good! So delicious! I'm gonna drink it all up!
You want more of my semen?
You're such a troublesome slut.
I want more of your cock. Please mess up my insides.
Yuki-chan...
Alright, this is your punishment tonight.
You like Yuki right?
Sa-Sakae-kun likes me?
I know Yukkhan's a slut... but even so I...
Even though Sakae-kun is watching me...
I'm loving this cock so much that my pussy gets so tight!
What will you do now?
Can you just stand there, watching silently while
your crush is being pounded by some man? Or...
Well? Be honest with yourself.
I'm... I'm...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Yes, that's very good.