I'm being really gentle right now.
Does it honestly feel that good?
How the hell did I wind up here all tied up?
Why is this happening to me?
You sure got hard after being tied up.
Expected nothing less from a perverted clergyman.
What does she mean by that?
What's up with her anyway?
Isn't she embarrassed wearing that outfit?
What do you think you're staring at?
Should the accused
really be acting like this?
Huh? Accused?
Who are you, anyway?
My, how rude of me.
Enma-senpai?
Enma Kaoru-senpai.
She's the most popular girl in school,
the model of perfection.
Senpai. Wh-Why are you wearing...
The accused, Aiba Sakae.
Let us begin your Turnabout Witch Trial.
Turnabout... Witch Trial?
Correct. You, a clergyman, have been put on trial
for attempting to hunt witches such as myself.
What are you going on about?!
Playing dumb, are you?
You perverted clergyman!
I-I'm not a clergyman or a pervert!
Nice try, but you're definitely a pervert.
You got hard the moment you laid eyes on me.
You're still twitching, in fact.
As if anyone could keep it down
in a situation like this!
Even without a trial, I can tell that you're guilty.
I'll give you a second chance though.
What? How?
If you're not the pervert you say you are,
then ridding yourself of this boner should be simple.
Like hell I could!
Then admit it.
Admit that you're a perverted
clergyman trying to hunt me down.
How could I possibly not
have a boner at a time like this?!
Oh, my. This perverted dick of yours
seems to be getting even livelier!
This makes you feel good, doesn't it?
Admit it already, you pervert!
Fine! I admit it! I admit it!
Very good. Now let that perverted dick of yours cum!
Until now I was definitely a normal student.
How did this happen?
Turnabout Witch Trial
I'm Going te be Judged by a Perverted Witch
I was just a transfer student who
had no friends and lived a very dull life...
Sakae-kun?
Class rep?
This is Himeno Yuki.
She's our class rep, and she's the only person
who has been nice to me since I transferred here.
She's my angel!
Please, I told you. You don't have to call me that!
I'd be a lot happier if
you'd call me "Yuki-chan" instead.
I'll be sure to!
Seriously though, she's as cute as ever!
What's wrong, Sakae-kun?
You've been staring at me for a while now...
Oh, no, it's nothing!
So, did you need something?
It seems like you're still having trouble
fitting in, so I wanted to let you know
that you can talk to me if you have any problems, okay?
Then on the way home,
I saw our schools idol, Kaoru Enma-senpai.
I ended up getting hard from looking
at her titanic tits
and her bursting butt.
E-Enma-senpa...
a sweet smell?
And that's when I lost consciousness.
We'll be together until
a verdict is reached, understood?
You just said I was guilty though!
And I got an embarrassing
punishment because of it...
What are you talking about?
That trial was to convict you for stalking me,
not for determining
whether or not you're a clergyman.
What the hell?
I wonder what will happen to you
after we finish this trial.
Oh god...
A Turnabout Witch Trial, huh?
How did things end up like this?!
If it's something I can do, I'd be glad to help.
But I can't keep relying on her, can I?
Huh? Did I fall asleep?
W-Wait, is this what I think it is?!
Wh-What should I do?
S-Sakae-kun?
Why are you here?
Th-This isn't what it looks like!
Th-Theres a explanation for this!
Please listen to what I have to say!
Sure.
S-Senpai, why are you here?
Well then, Sakae-kun, the accused,
seems to have something he wants to say,
so I'll appoint him a lawyer.
A lawyer? Who exactly?
That girl!
I'd die of embarrassment
if she served as my lawyer!
I'll support you with everything I've got.
So, how did you obtain those panties?
You stole them from someone, didn't you?
I'm telling you, I didn't do that!
What happened was...
I don't see any plausible excuse
that you could make though.
I don't care what you say! I'm innocent!
Wanna know why?!
Because I'm a virgin!
Sakae-kun...
You're a virgin?
I can't believe I was forced to say that.
If you're insisting that you are,
then how about you show me some proof?
Proof? Of whether or not I'm a virgin?
What else? We'll use magic to find out.
Wh-What is this?
When applied on people
who are not virgins, it'll taste sweet.
And if you're a virgin, it'll taste bitter.
So much so that you
wouldn't even want to lick it.
I'll do my best, Sakae-kun!
Yeah... Please...
She's licking my dick!
Don't say that.
Don't say that, it's embarrassing.
Sorry. If it's really bitter, just stop, okay?
It's so sw...
Wait, what did you just say?
Sweet... It's so sweet.
Your dick is so sweet,
I can't stop... licking it!
Looks like your lie's been uncovered.
This can't be right! I'm definitely a virgin!
Unfortunately, this liquid is never wrong.
You're lying!
It tastes so good!
I need to lick it more.
I can't believe that this angel of a class rep
is sucking on my dick like a total slut.
Shit!
There's no way that she's happily
sucking on my dick like some whore!
I'll make it feel better.
I'll make your dick feel even better!
It's so sweet.
I want more!
I want more of your dick's sweetness!
I want this liquid and your sperm.
I want all of it!
I want to chug all of it down my throat!
Your dick milk is so sweet!
There's so much!
It's so good!
Looks like a verdict has been reached.
Wait! I'm telling you, there's something wrong!
But you were lying about being a virgin.
I am definitely a virgin!
So you're still sticking to your story, huh?
Okay then, I'll do you a favor
and search for the owner of those panties.
It's true that if we find out how I got
these panties, we can dear this up, but...
If you drink this potion,
you'll be able to see your recent past.
Give it here!
So this is where I was...
This voice...
It sounds so familiar...
W-Wait, is someone mounting me?
C-Class rep?!
He came inside me.
Hey, Sakae-kun,
I've had sex with the Physics teacher,
and he came inside me a lot,
but it just wasn't enough.
I saw you lying here, sleeping, and I just...
Oh no!
Your dick reeks of being virgin...
but its so amazing!
Sakae-kun, are you going to cum?
Cum!
I want you to mix your juices
with my wet, sloppy pussy!
I'm going to cum too! I'm cumming!
It's so warm. Don't worry though,
I'll be sure that my pussy drinks every last drop.
Oh, wait.
If I leave his dick like this,
he'll see that something happened.
I need to clean it.
Oh, yeah!
It's all clean now,
so this should be good enough.
Okay, Sakae-kun.
Next time, you should come onto me, okay?
See you later.
Are you kidding me?!
I will now hand down the verdict.
The accused, Aiba Sakae.
For committing perjury in this holy court
regarding his virginity, I declare you...
Guilty!
The sentence for that was...
I sentence the accused, Aiba Sakae,
to be my dog.
I was taken around the park like a dog,
and even had my ass probed!
She also made me have sex
with a homunculus all night.
Are you okay, Sakae-kun?
After being lured in by kind words from the class rep...
Damn you! How dare you fool me into thinking
you were anything but a cum dumpster!
You're right!
I'm nothing but a human toilet!
I'm just a loose girl who will have sex with anyone!
I was also forced to satisfy the sexual desires
of the school slut, Yuki-chan, in the bathroom.
And then finally...
This is what I wanted!
So is an adult's cock better than your boyfriend's?
Yes!
This is great.
A student's dick isn't nearly as good.
I don't want his dick!
I want more of these big, hard cocks!
She made me watch as she was fucked
by other men, to hurt my pride.
Looks like you've taken
a liking to my human toilet.
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about Yuki. Isn't that obvious?
Well, it's true that I'm interested in her.
But at this rate...
I need to live my life the way I want to!
I'll use all of her body as I like!
I'm fine with doing that!
I'll cum all over that fucking slut!
I hear you have a meeting with her after this.
How do you know that?
Weren't you listening?
She's my human toilet.
Okay then, how about today, we...
Make it so that you can't cum!
What are you doing?!
I told you that I'd make you unable to cum, didn't I?
I'll see you later.
No! I want to have sex with Yuki!
I don't know how many days have passed.
In spite of that, my meat stick keeps writhing,
wanting to release everything held inside it.
Senpai?
Is that you?!
Looks like you've been a good boy.
Hurry! Please, take this off!
I told you that you can't cum, didn't I?
Looks quite painful.
Do you wanna cum that badly?
You know the answer to that...
No, I don't.
You have to tell me with your own mouth.
I want to...
Louder!
I want to cum!
I want to cum a lot!
Oh, really?
How wonderful! This is what I wanted!
All right then.
I'll give you this.
Go ahead!
Cum after you say what you're going to do.
I'm going to cum!
I'm gonna blow my entire load!
Well done.
I-I'm cumming!
You're like a milk tank.
Where in the world did you store all this cum?
It smells so bad.
I can't stop cumming.
Senpai, help me!
Look, I stopped it.
S-Senpai, your boobs feel so good.
I'm gonna...
Your dick is pulsing like crazy between these,
are you going to cum again?
They're just so soft, I can't...
Okay, I'll suck it all out for you.
I only sucked on it a little bit
and yet there's so much.
Is something wrong?
You used magic...
No excuses.
What a cute dick.
I can feel the cum welling up inside.
No, stop!
You're sucking too hard!
You want to cum, don't you?
Go ahead.
Go ahead and cum.
Let out as much as you want!
I'm... cummmg!
No... more...
But it doesn't seem like
you're satisfied yet.
Well then, this is where the fun starts.
Go ahead and stick your dick in my pussy.
I can't believe you're still
so hard after cumming so much!
Senpai, your pussy feels so good!
What are you saying?
You'd be okay with anyone's pussy
as long as it helped you cum.
That's right!
My promiscuous dick would be
okay with anyone's pussy.
But! But...
But what? Come on, spit it out!
Your pussy is completely different than Yuki-chan's!
Your pussy feels so much better!
I'm cumming!
Hot stuff is filling me up!
Are they really that different?
Completely different! They're worlds apart!
So it really feels that good, huh?
Oh, no. I'm getting
turned on from being fucked.
I'm really feeling it by
being fucked by this slave.
Are you still going to cum?
Are you going to blow your load?
Are you going to fill my pussy with your cum?
All right then. Cum!
Your sperm is filling up my womb to the brim!
I'm pathetic but I just can't help it!
This feels too good!
I'm cumming again!
Here's your reward.
Wh-What...
Your dick is getting hard again!
That's right!
A fellow pervert like yourself should understand
what I gave you. It's an aphrodisiac!
I'm so tired and I'm in pain,
but my dick feels so good!
More! More!
That's it!
More! Pour more of your cum inside me!
Fuck me harder,
as if you're trying to impregnate me!
I'll make you feel good!
Good! Good! See?
You can do it if you try!
Harder! Do me harder!
Pour all of your dirty dick milk into my pussy!
Thrust harder into my womb!
Senpai, I'm gonna...
Fine, I'll cum with you then.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
You don't think we're done yet, do you?
Wait, we're still going?
Of course.
We've only just begun.
These dicks feel amazing!
They taste so good!
I want them deeper in me!
You want my cum?
Wow, you're such a hopeless slut.
I want more of your dick!
Stir my pussy up some more!
Yuki-chan...
Okay, this is today's trial.
You like Yuki, don't you?
S-Sakae-kun likes me?
I know she's a slut.
But still, I...
Though I'm being watched by Sakae-kun,
I love these cocks so much that
my pussy just won't stop throbbing!
So, what will you do?
Are you just going to watch while
the girl you like gets gangbanged?
Or...
Yes. Be true to yourself.
I... I...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
So that's it? That's good.
translation: hikarucon
timing: period
typesetting: haidaraaaaa
editor: punk4real
quality control: fyure