You're... very good.
It's... almost like you're a baby.
That's my bellybutton!
Don't.
That's not where you're supposed to put your dick.
The hole you put your dick into is...
Right here.
Wow... Amazing!
My dick's melting!
My dick is getting tighter... something's coming!
Hachishaku-sama! Hachishaku-sama! Hachishaku-sama!
Hachishaku-sama!!
Ghost Story: Eight Stories of Hachishaku
Pleasure Ahound
Heteromorphic Oddity
"Hachishaku-sama. The Tale of Dreams"
Hachishaku-sama?
Now, let us go.
Where?
To the amusement park.
Here.
Taste good?
Yep.
Let me get that for you.
I...
I wish it could just be the two of us like this forever.
Hachishaku-sama...
You're such a naughty child.
It just keeps getting harder.
Just a little more...
I'll have to get you back for that.
Yeah...
Hachishaku-sama...
Why...
Why are you only licking the tip?
All of it... Eat all of it!
You're driving me crazy!
My dick is going insane!
Don't fret.
I'll do it properly.
I'll gobble it all up for you.
Good boy.
I'll eat every last bit of it.
I'll swallow all of you.
You can cum as many times as you want.
I want you to fill both my heart and my insides up.
Hachishaku-sama!
Hachishaku-sama, I... I love you!
Please...
Please be with me forever!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Hachishaku-sama...
Hachishaku-sama, I... love... you...
Please stay with me forever...
That was but a brief...
dream from a hot summer day.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч