Excuse me.
Could you take me to Inuboe?
Ghost Story: Eight Stories of Hachishaku
Pleasure Ahound
Heteromorphic Oddity
Episode 1 "Hachishaku-sama"
Please use this if you'd like.
Thank you.
You could catch your death out there
in this weather. What were you doing?
My bike broke down, and then I lost reception,
and then on top of that, it started raining really badly
so I couldn't really move at all.
You've really had it rough then, huh?
I'm glad I came across you though.
It's raining a lot harder now than it was before.
Just driving through this might take longer than usual.
Yen
Off Duty
That should do it.
The meter's not running, so don't worry too much.
Thank you.
You must be a very tall woman.
Oh my, that's very embarrassing.
But you're not wrong. I was pretty famous
in my village because of my height.
How about I tell you a little horror story to pass the time.
There once was a boy.
Let's call him A-kun.
Because both his parents were at work, he'd often return
by himself to his grandfather's residence in a remote village.
Being in the village was nostalgic for A-kun
and he'd catch all kinds of insects and bugs.
But that was when...
Ho
Ho...
Ho... Ho... Ho...
Ho... Ho...
Ho...
That woman was taller than any man.
She was more than a head taller than an adult male.
For some reason he felt fear at the sight of her,
so A-kun ran back into his house.
Though he wasn't sure of it at the time,
he had a feeling that at that moment, their eyes met.
Thanks for the food!
Your fried chicken is so delicious, Grandma!
Oh, you.
Food ain't going anywhere. Take your time.
Yep!
Oh yeah, Grandpa?
What?
Is there a foreign women living in this neighborhood?
Can't say I've heard of anyone like that.
What's the matter? Something happen?
Well, you see, I saw a really tall lady today.
You could see her head peeking out from over the wall.
She was muttering something like "Ho... Ho... Ho...".
She was also wearing a straw hat.
I was so startled, I just ran back
into the house without thinking.
When?!
When did you see it?!
In the afternoon...
I need to make a call.
Yeah, there's no doubt.
My grandson. Yeah, please.
You... You met with the Hachishaku-sama.
Hachishaku-sama was something of a ghost
story that was passed down in that village.
She was as tall as bamboo, around 240cm.
She seemed to always target younger children
and changed her clothes, shape,
and age, to make it easier, but she would
always leave that straw hat on her head.
After several days, the only fate
left to those who saw her was death.
It'll be fine! Everything will be fine!
Got it? You're not to leave that
room until tomorrow morning!
We will not talk to you at all.
When the clock strikes seven, you come out by yourself.
Until that time, do not open
that door no matter what happens.
That's what he said, but...
But what happens if I'm caught by Hachishaku-sama?
By that monster...
Ho...
Ho... Ho... Ho... Ho...
This... This voice...
Hey, are you okay?! It's over! You've got to run away now!
Hurry!
What happened? Grandpa?!
Grandpa!
Huh?
Good evening.
Crap!
They even told me not to open the door!
I'm gonna be killed!
No... Don't...
I can't look at its face no matter what!
Hey, let me see your face.
Is this Hachishaku-sama?
P-Please, hurry...
You're so cute.
You have a very beautiful penis.
What are you gonna do with me?
Did you come here to kill me?
I won't kill you or anything like that.
But I might have a taste of you.
Wai... Don't...
My dick... it feels weird!
Sto...
My dick looks all weird now and it's so big.
It's fine.
After we're done, it'll go back to normal.
Hachishaku-sama smells really good.
Hachishaku-sama is so pretty and kind.
So, please...
Do you think you could make me feel good too?
I will!
I'll make you feel good!
You're very good.
You're almost like a baby.
That's my belly button!
Stop.
That's not where you put your penis.
This is where it goes.
Wow! So good!
My dick is melting!
My dick is kind of tensing up!
Hachishaku-sama! Hachishaku-sama!
Hachishaku-sama!
The next day...
No matter how long they waited,
A-kun didn't seem like he was coming out of the room.
His grandfather removed the seals
and went inside to check on him.
There lying in the room,
he found A-kun passed out on the ground.
In order to avoid Hachishaku-sama's detection,
his grandfather put him in his car
and drove him away from the village.
He drove him away to stop him from being killed.
Slowly, he drove away leaving the house behind him.
As long as he leaves the village, he'll probably survive.
We're almost out of the village. Hang in there.
Hachishaku-sama...
A-kun?
Don't look!
Don't do it!
Please, don't go.
Please.
I'm begging you.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
But they told me that I can't be with you!
I'm so sorry!
Ho.
And with the help of his relatives, A-kun was able
to flee the village, but was never able to return again.
That sure was scary.
But...
Thinking about it from a woman's perspective,
it's also kind of saddening.
Oh, I know. The rain hasn't stopped yet, so how about this?
Let me tell you a horror story.
This is about someone who got lost in these mountains.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: akin
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч