Ghost Story: Eight Stories of Hachishaku
Pleasure Ahound
Heteromorphic Oddity
"Hathishaku-sama. The Final Story Arc"
We're almost at your destination.
Oh, I know. Since were almost there, how about...
we talk about something that you might fear the most.
When it comes to nightmares, people
always think "I'm so glad I woke up.
I'm so glad that wasn't real."
But to actually think that, they need to
have seen something, or so I've heard.
Once upon a time, there was a girl who was dreaming.
In the dream, there was a train with a monkey that was
similar to something she'd seen at an
amusement park when she was little.
Riding the train were several pale-faced people.
However, at some point, she was able
to figure out that it was all a dream.
She rode the train thinking, "I'll be fine
as long as I wake up from the dream."
However the train kept moving forward,
not even taking a moment to stop.
She wondered where exactly the train was
heading towards and thought that
it was a very strange dream.
But right when she started getting
relaxed, an announcement played.
The next stop is the gutting station. The gutting station.
And then out of nowhere four figures appeared.
They went to the person furthest in the back and...
Slice.
And they cut her as if they were
preparing some kind of meat.
One after another, the woman's organs
spewed out from within her.
The screams of being carved up accompanied with the
sordid smell of blood and flesh had her paralyzed with fear.
Disturbed by the grotesque sight before
her, she began to become distraught.
Doubts of whether or not this was really
a dream or not flooded her head.
She began fearing what might happen next.
However despite her fear, she couldn't
will herself to get off the train.
Clang. Clank.
Clatter. Cling.
The train continued on its track, unperturbed.
And then came the next announcement.
Next is the carving station. Carving station.
And then the things went to the person second
from the back and carved out her eyes.
Squish. Slurch.
Gurgle.
Splish splash.
Dabble dabble.
The woman trembled and her hairs stood up on end.
The simple reason being that the person next in line was...
her.
"I need to wake up. I need to wake up!"
"This is a dream! This is just a bad dream!"
But the next announcement came and
it was even worse than the others.
Next up is the mincemeat stop. Mincemeat.
"Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!! Wake up!!"
"Hurry! Hurry up and wake up!"
"Wake up from this nightmare!"
And when she did wake up, she was in her usual room.
She was lying on her bed, covered in sweat and tears.
"Oh, I'm so glad I woke up."
"I'm so glad that wasn't real."
Running away?
The next stop is the end of the line.
And that's the last of my stories.
That one was called "the monkey dream".
No one knows where that girl is or how she's doing.
But here's what I think.
Dreams can only be called dreams
by people who can wake up.
If you can't wake up, then dreams are nothing
more than reality at that point.
Are you alright?
You don't look so good.
It's okay, I'm fine.
Your story just made me remember.
It made me remember the continuation to
the Hachishaku-sama story from earlier.
That kid began to be able to see dreams too.
A-kun, might have been attacked by Hachishaku-sama
and almost lost his life to her, but...
He was able to escape her grips with the help
of his grandfather and others from the village.
And then he lived a peaceful life
as if nothing had happened.
With his usual friends.
Everything was supposed to have gone back to normal.
But from that day on, she'd always appear in his dreams.
That soft and comforting get frightening touch...
Please... don't leave me by myself.
When he'd wake up, for some reason, there'd
only be her sweet scent left around him.
And a new day that made it seem as if the
last night had never happened began.
Those days continued day after day for years.
The boy grew older and slowly became an adult.
Hachishaku-sama!
Your boobs are so soft and so warm!
Your dick is so cute.
Let me eat you up down here too.
You're such a good boy.
You're really such a good boy.
I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting for you forever.
I'll be waiting for you to come back.
"Why did I meet her that day?"
"Why did she choose me?"
He couldn't think of a single reason why, but...
There was one thing that he wondered about.
Why did he run away from her in the first place?
It's possible that he was no longer able
to tell his dreams apart from reality.
He'd see her everywhere he went, not
sure if she was real or an illusion.
He began seeing every woman with
long hair and a hat as her.
He began being unable to go out with friends.
"I want to go back."
His head began to be filled with that and that alone.
And amidst all of that, he received
a call from his grandfather.
The statue that sealed Hachishaku-sama
was destroyed by someone.
And so he rushed to the village knowing
that he'd probably be killed either way.
He was at his wits' ends.
She was calling for him this entire time!
But I... I...
Am I still dreaming?
Hachishaku-sama?
Po.
I'm back.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч