STEP MILF
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Right there.
Not right there.
No.
You like it right here right?
No stop.
So good, I'm going to melt.
Seiichi, it feels so good.
Oh I forgot about the clitoris
Sorry about that.
No, I'm going to cum!
You have to be a little more quiet
when you cum.
If you're loud they will hear you
in the kids room.
I'm sorry, it's been awhile since
you've made love to me.
Now it's your turn to make me
feel good.
Yes.
You've become good at teasing.
I'm not teasing you, I'm licking
you because it tastes delicious.
Hanae...
What, you want it inside you
already?
Yes, your dick is so hard I
couldn't hold myself back.
It's been awhile, can I put it in
and move now?
I guess you can.
You move and make me feel
good.
Your dick, I can feel it pulsing
inside me.
So good.
So good, I haven't had this in so
long.
Seiichi's dick, it feels so good.
So good.
Oh no!
My clit, it's rubbing against it and
feels so good.
I'm about to cum.
So good, Seiichi, it feels so good.
Hanae, you're shaking your hips
that much
It's hitting my uterus.
I'm gonna cum!
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
What is this, you came before me
alone.
Crap !
Don't be done alone, it's time for
me to cum.
Yes, please pound me a lot.
So good ! Deeper!
So good, Seiichi, you're amazing !
Feels so good!
More, please pound me stronger
Seiichi!
Oh gosh, that spot feels so good!
Yes Yes!
More, pound me harder and
deeper inside!
There! It feels good.
No I'm going to cum, I'm going to
cum Seiichi!
Feels so good!
I love you, I love you Seiichi,
more!
Crap, he may have seen me...
So good!
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum again!
No !
Come on, don't just lay there, lick
and clean me up.
Yes.
Episode 1
Mom, you seem like you're in a
good mood.
You think so?
Did something good happen to
you yesterday?
Not really, there's nothing.
Hurry and get ready, you'll be late
to school.
Good morning Tomonori.
Good morning brother.
Ah, yeah.
Can't you greet your mother and
sister properly?
I'm sure brother is tired from
staying up late last night studying.
Yeah, hey Hanae I don't feel too well
so I don't need breakfast.
Are you okay?
Yeah I'm fine so please don't
worry about me.
I'm off.
Hey brother!
Do you have time tonight?
Should be fine if it's at night.
There's a part in my homework I
want you to help me with.
As long as it's something I can
handle.
You'll be fine, unlike me, you're
smart.
Then I'll see you tonight.
Marie, you should hurry and get
ready too.
Okay.
Brother, is it okay?
Come in.
What's the matter, if you're
coming in, just come in.
Do I look good?
How is it? Were you surprised?
Don't you think I look great in it?
Isn't it adorable?
What do you think brother?
Is it sexy? Or cute?
Which one?
What, you came to show me your
cosplay?
What about your homework?
This isn't cosplay!
I was chosen as one of the
regulars.
T-That's not what I'm saying.
Oh forget it, I just wanted to
show you first.
I'm sorry.
It looks good on you...
and it's amazing you've been
chosen as a regular.
I saw you going to practice from
early in the morning.
I saw you working hard so I'm
happy for you too.
Really? Thanks!
Brother praised me!
What's wrong?
Well, your skirt is too short and I
can see your underwear.
It's fine, during club practice I
wear shorts under them.
It's not that, you can see your
underwear right now.
It's not you can see it, I'm
purposely showing it just to you.
What?
Come over here.
Did seeing my underwear turn
you on?
I shouldn't have desires to my
sister.. .
That's true but we're not blood
related so we can have a baby.
Well by law.
Brother, your heart is beating so
fast.
My heart is beating fast too right?
Her breasts are so soft.
I like you and I can't hide it
anymore.
But.
Brother, how do you feel towards
me?
I think you're cute as a little
sister but...
Your think but...?
What's what, I think.
Brother, you like mom so you
can't love me huh?
What, why Hanae?
I've been watching you everyday
for the past couple of years.
The way you look at mom is
different.
I like Hanae?
She's the one that stole my
mother away from this home.
Oh gosh, that feels so good !
More, more!
I can't stop, my hip just moves
on it's own.
It's hitting my uterus!
Pound me harder!
It feels so good Seiichi, I'm
cumming, I'm cumming!
That's not true!
I can,
I can become a girl just for you.
I'm not like mom.
Brother, I love you.
Marie's lips are so soft, it feels so
good.
It's okay, if it's to you I can give
you my virginity.
Not... right there...
Wow, you're soaked.
Right there.
So good brother.
That spot feels good.
Hey, can I lick you?
Yeah, lick me gently.
That spot!
Brother, there!
Don't suck on it!
I'm gonna cum!
Your dick is so hard.
It's all ready.
Was getting head this good?
No, I'm about to cum.
That's enough.
You swallowed but are you okay?
Yeah, it was a little bitter but it's
yours.
It was delicious.
Are you sure we can do this?
Yeah, 'cause I've always wanted
to do this with you.
I wanted to be one.
You can put it in me.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Yeah it hurts a little but I'm fine.
I can bare it.
Brother, how is it inside me?
It's warm and feels so good.
I'm so glad you like it.
I'm fine so please move, please
pleasure yourself.
It's starting to feel.. .
Brother's dick is so good.
Brother! Brother!
It feels so good, please pound me
more!
Brother!
No, no I'm going to cum!
I'm about to cum!
You would have been fine even if
you came inside me.
Brother, let's do this again.
Oh hey Tomonori .
I wanted to look something up on
the internet.
Dad's computer is faster than my
Laptop.
Just make sure to clean up after
yourself...
because Seiichi is sensitive.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
Speaking of, dad's on a business
trip from today right?
Yes, for about a week.
Why?
Cause I haven't really spoken to
dad recently.
You should we are all family.
Close relationship is something
important.
Yes, I'm sorry.
What is it?
It's been awhile since I saw you
smile.
Y-You think so?
Did something good happen?
Well I guess you can say
something did happen but...
You've looked a little depressed
recently so I was worried.
Please tell me what happened
later okay?
Oh okay.
Eventually.
Ill be looking forward to it.
Seems like she doesn't know
about the relationship between Marie and I.
Plus about dad's affair.
Hanae is pretty and she has good
style, I feel bad for her.
This is the first time seeing this folder.
Hanae-letter
Is it the shots of him and his
affair partner's sex photo's
Please stop Tomonori!
No !
Please stop, how could a kind
person like you do such a thing?
You're not going to scream?
Marie and dad aren't home but if
you scream enough...
our neighbors should hear you.
If we do such a thing, then our
home, this family will be over.
This house?
How could you act like you're
family?
You're a pest who kicked my
mom out and started...
living in this house.
That's not... we're family.
Please calm down, okay?
If family is so important then
calm down this son of yours.
If I do it with my mouth...
would everything go back to
normal from tomorrow?
Could we stop this idiotic thing?
Could you promise that with me?
Hey, you said with your mouth.
I-I'm sorry.
Stop.
It's over.
So we won't continue this idiotic
thing anymore right?
This isn't enough.
No !
Stop doing this!
Please, we're family!
No! No!
No, not that deep!
No stop, please forgive me!
No don't cum inside me!
Take it out!
To be continued