Swallow.
What is it?
lt's almost time to start.
Fine.
Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome to the palace of perversion and immorality.
A beautiful party is about to begin.
Let's meet the main actress. Please give her a round of applause!
This beautiful madam is the wife of a popular lT business tycoon.
Takayoshi Tohyama's wife. Madam Shizuko.
lt's too early for you to be embarrassed.
She was once considered a beautiful socialite.
But tonight. the beautiful but cruel flower will withstand punishment.
Now let's have a special greeting from Madam Shizuko.
First. we're going to see Madam Shizuko's urination show.
S-Stop...
Please stop...
N-No...
Come on. Show everyone what you have to offer!
Now do it.
l can't do it.
Even if you say you can't...
...it's only a matter of time till you can't hold it in.
N-No. please...
P-Please stop...
What l gave you before was a diuretic.
Now go ahead and release it all!
There!
N-No!
There. there!
N-No. l-l can't hold it...
ls that right?
lf you're going to be stubborn...
No!
You're trembling...
lt's not good to hold it in.
N-No... D-Don't...
l-l-l can't hold it...
Come on.
Just release it already...
...Madam Shizuko.
l-l can't hold it...
l-l can't take it...
No!
Why did this happen?
That's right...
lt all happened that day...
Have a good day, Darling.
Have a good day.
Ah. Keiko. Going out? When will you be back?
Shut up. Stop acting like my mother.
Leave me alone.
You're such a bad son.
By the way. Our plan to call Keiko will work, right?
Don't worry. We have to teach her a lesson.
Besides. You're going to do Keiko and her stepmother too, right?
But before you do...
Hey. Lift up your ass.
Yes...
More...
Do me more...
More... More...
l'm going to come.
Shoot it...
Shoot it inside...
l'm leaving the Keiko plan to you.
Hello. Tohyama residence.
Hello?
l have your daughter.
Come to Shibuya at three with a million yen.
Yamazaki Detective Agency
Calm down. Madam.
l'm sure it's some kind of prank.
Prank?
Yes. One directed towards a stepmother.
She wouldn't do that...
Plus. My husband is in Kansai for a business trip.
lf anything happens to Keiko while he's away. l...
You spoil her. So she's taking advantage of you.
Madam. The Hazakura group kidnapped her, right?
How do you know?
The Hazakura group. AKA Sakura, are pretty popular around Shibuya.
Group?
Well, they just go around having fun.
Your daughter's probably one of them and wants some allowance...
But just in case...
l understand.
You never know what might happen. l'll come with you.
Thank you.
No!
You know what you did, right. Keiko?
You put your hands on one of our own boys.
P-Please... Please let me go!
No. l won't do that.
You have to pay the price!
No!
Hey, it's almost time.
Fine. Let's go.
Yeah.
Hello. Miss Keiko.
W-Who's there?
M-Mr. Kawada!
Please! Help me!
l can't do that. Miss Keiko.
Before they come back...
P-Please stop!
P-Please stop! Let's do something fun. Miss Keiko.
No!
S-Stop!
No! Please!
M-Mr. Kawada. don't do this!
S-Stop!
No. stop!
Please!
No!
Miss Keiko, we're just getting started.
No! No!
No!
T-That's it...
Keep sucking.
l'm about to come, Miss Keiko.
No!
Please. Let me go.
Please.
Jeez. l don't know whether she's good natured or soft...
Come on. hurry up and get in.
Where's Keiko?
No!
Hey!
Hold it!
What do you want, old man?
Where's Keiko? No, before that, release the madam!
Shut up.
You're so annoying.
Serves you right.
Mr. Yamazaki!
Shut up! Keep quiet!
Let's go.
M-Madam...
lt was worth paying all that money.
That thing is amazing. You knocked him out with one shot!
l modified this and raised the voltage.
Maybe that guy's dead.
l told you to come alone, didn't l?
Yeah. What should we do, Ginko?
What should we do?
l have the money right here.
So please... Please return Keiko!
You're annoying too.
Go to sleep.
l'll let you see her soon.
Keiko...
Help me. Mother...
K-Keiko?
You're awake?
W-Where's Keiko?
K-Keiko!
M-Mother...
This is terrible...
Please. l'll give you the money as l promised.
So please let her go!
But you didn't come alone.
l promise not to kill her, but she has to pay the price...
No!
l-l'll do anything you want!
So please let her go!
Anything?
Then will you take her place?
Yes.
Then strip.
You'll replace her. right?
B-But...
N-No!
Please let me go! Please!
Shut up! Behave yourself!
N-No!
Please let me go!
Come on!
Come on...
You people are too much.
l can hear her screams outside.
Y-You...
Mr. Kawada?
Long time no see. madam.
Why are you here?
Don't worry about that.
Anyway, you're going to take Keiko's place, right?
For me.
Stop.
Did you plan this all out on your own?
l don't know. But if you won't let me have fun...
...then l'll just have to do it with Keiko.
l get excited when l torture women.
l'm the one who tied her up.
S-Stop!
l'll take her place instead!
Get inside.
This is like a dream...
l can do whatever l want with you...
When l first laid eyes on you...
...l just wanted one chance.
One chance to do whatever l want with you...
l was willing to give up my life if l could do that.
l got fired by Tohyama since l was looking at you all the time...
But now l get to do whatever l want with you.
You can never tell what will happen in life.
N-No!
Stop!
Please!
N-No!
lt feels good... No. stop...
Stop...
Madam, you can go ahead and scream out loud.
No...
No, no, no!
lf my finger isn't good enough...
...then how about this?
No...
Hey, take a look inside.
Take a good look. That's your mama.
Nice face.
l wonder who's responsible for that.
l'm going to come soon, madam.
No! No!
No. n-not inside!
l'm coming.
N-No! No!
Are you sure about this? You laid your hands on her.
lt's okay. We need these kinds of benefits.
Yes, this is Kawada.
Yes.
Yes. l understand.
The chairman. We're taking them to him.
Right.
At the time. l never knew...
...that this was just the beginning of the nightmare.