That's right. sir.
But l'm surprised.
At what?
l've never seen that kind of woman before.
l'm sure she'll be cutting bananas with her cunt in no time.
Looks like she's worth torturing then.
How is she doing?
lt was shocking to climax in front of others.
l'll just leave her alone till she calms down.
Will she be ready for the show?
Yeah. They both will.
lt's up to you. More will come from the worlds of politics and finance.
Onimura.
Listen up.
Shizuko's show ends after tonight.
After the show. Shizuko will become my personal pet...
...and spend the rest of her life with me. l'll teach her a great lesson.
Honey. l...
Yeah!
Show it to us!
Etsuko, give me a hand.
Sure.
You know, there's something l really want to see.
l want to see you pee. You can't say no, can you?
Do it in that washbowl, okay?
l don't want you to make a mess.
No!
lt's not good to hold it in.
Come on.
lf you don't put out the light, you'll burn your private area.
Hey. Stop holding it in.
Just let go.
Come on. So stubborn.
Aim well. The deal's off if you miss.
Nice shooting!
But if we keep doing things like this, her spirit is going to fall to pieces.
That's the aim.
l'm leaving the rest to you guys. Do exactly what it says here.
Let me see that.
What shall we do next?
This seems like fun.
This looks good too...
This one for sure.
Yeah, this might be good too.
They're all evil.
Good. Now we'll try this.
Make sure you can lay this egg.
lt's finished.
l don't know how much time has passed since then.
My husband betrayed me, and l lost hope for any escape...
l stay to protect Keiko.
S-Stop... Please stop.
Come on. Show everyone what you have to offer!
N-No, no, no, no...
Tohyama isn't here yet?
He'll be here soon. And one more thing.
We took care of two scum.
No... Stop...
Please stop.
No... No...
Yamazaki Detective Agency
Now go ahead and release it all.
Come on. Come on.
N-No!
There, there, there!
N-No. l-l can't hold it...
No... No...
ls that right?
lf you're going to be stubborn...
You're trembling...
lt's not good to hold it in.
l-l can't hold it... l-l can't take it...
Next, a lesbian show you can only see here!
l created the greatest device just for the madam.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
Yes.
K-Keiko?
Mother...
l-lt can't be...
Believe it or not, though unrelated by blood, they are mother and daughter.
K-Keiko...
Mother.
This can't be...
Well? A wonderful idea, right?
l-l can't believe this... You're not human...
Brutes...
Demons!
You're the demon who sold your wife and daughter.
Humans can become demons, but demons can't become humans.
l-lt can't be...
Shizuko... Keiko...
lt's all your fault.
Just relax and watch what happens to your wife and daughter.
You must live carrying the burden of your karma.
Mother...
P-Please stop this, Keiko!
N-No!
Don't do this, Keiko!
Mother?
Mother, why?
No...
No. Keiko!
K-Keiko...
No... Don't do this, Keiko.
No... No. no...
Stop it! Don't do this, Keiko!
No... No...
No, stop it. Keiko!
No...
P-Please...
Stop this. Keiko...
Ouch! lt hurts! N-No!
lt hurts. Keiko!
Stop it...
lt hurts. Keiko...
Please stop.
No, it hurts!
Please, Keiko!
Stop it!
The show isn't over yet.
Mother...
lf you care about your daughter, then do what she tells you to.
Mother, let's come together.
Keiko...
l'll untie you, Mother.
You're amazing, Mother.
You're so wet...
No, t-that feels good...
No...
No! No!
l-lt feels good...
You're amazing, Mother.
You're so wet...
Plus, your cunt is so tight...
Yes...
Keiko.
Mother, let's come together.
Keiko...
l'm sticking it in, Mother...
Yes! lt feels good!
More... More...
Keiko! Keiko!
More!
Yes... Yes... Yes...
Keiko!
More. More.
Mother...
Yes...
More...
Mother...
More!
Keiko!
Yes!
More! More!
Keiko!
Yes... Yes... Yes...
Keiko! Keiko!
Yes...