Did you call for me. sir?
ls she here yet?
You'll have to wait a little longer. l'm sure she'll be here soon.
How do you want me to torture her?
lt's up to you.
So you don't mind if l treat her rough?
No.
Jeez, is she that good?
When we get there. l won't be able to do anything.
So l have to enjoy it while l can.
Must be hard for you. Taking the fall when she's not your real daughter.
But it's because of Tohyama...
My husband is involved in this?
Nope.
You're going to forget everything and have a good time.
Your cunt is of the highest quality.
No... No...
No...
lt gets tight and sucks it in. lt's the best.
What on earth is going on?
No!
Yamazaki Detective Agency
What's that? Don't get involved?
This is a kidnapping.
lf we don't notify the police, your wife and daughter...
l can't do that...
What exactly happened?
Now, madam.
This will be your room starting today.
Keiko!
Mother!
M-Mother...
K-Keiko!
This was supposed to be a tearful scene. You people are cruel...
Y-You...
You know him, right, madam?
He's the chairman of the Morita Company. Mikizou Morita.
Why are you doing this?
Yes?
Quite right.
Kawada. Onimura.
The chairman wants to speak to the madam in private.
Take her daughter to another room. Be gentle with her.
Understood. Let's go.
Right.
No! Mother!
Mother! Mother!
Keiko! Keiko!
l'm begging you! Please let her go!
We have every intention of doing that. But that all depends on you. madam.
l'll make it clear to you. You're going to have to be our slave.
Slave?
That's right. A sex slave.
As you know. madam...
...the Morita Company made a fortune through finance and real estate.
On top of that, we have connections in politics and the financial world.
ln order to strengthen those connections...
...we're also getting involved in show business as well.
We're especially putting more effort...
...for celebrities who are tired of the same things...
...and need more stimulation.
The show must have a star.
You're telling me that l have to...
You can go find someone else.
Why do Keiko and l have to be tortured?
lt's your husband's fault.
He did too much.
He should've just worked for me.
He didn't just refuse. He went against me.
He doesn't know his place. Rich lT businessmen are all like that.
We won't let anyone rebel against us and harm us in any way.
T-That's...
A large bribe to a politician. What would happen if this gets out?
You know. right. madam?
Then those people tried to...
lt would be cruel to tell this to your daughter.
Now, madam, you'll do as we say, right?
No! Such embarrassing acts in public...
You people are evil!
lndeed. But so is our master.
lf you refuse, we'll use your daughter.
That's what our master told us.
Keiko? How cruel...
We're not mad for money. We're just like demons.
Now, what will you do?
You promise not to do anything to Keiko and let her go in peace?
l promise.
l'll do it...
l'm counting on you.
Right.
Do you want to feel comfortable?
Then l want you to pleasure me.
lf you do. l might let you go.
l got so wet when l was watching your mother get tortured.
You knew that l like women too, right?
Make me come. Then l'll let you go.
Now do it.
Come on.
You're pretty good, Keiko.
Come on. Deeper...
Yes...
Feels good...
P-Please. l want you to untie me.
l can pleasure you more if l'm free...
Fine.
Come on.
Do it.
Yes...
Feels good...
More...
More... More...
What's wrong, Keiko? Keep going...
K-Keiko. you...
W-Who's there?
Mother!
K-K-Keiko!
l'm sorry.
This is all my fault...
lt's all right. As long as you're safe...
Mother...
Oh. right. Let's get out of here.
Hurry!
Don't worry. There are no guards now.
l see. They're trying to escape before the torture begins.
You need a little hope to create the necessary despair, right?
l see...
Hold it right there!
Stop right there.
Keiko, thanks for stunning me.
Hey, let me borrow your gun. l'll kill her...
That won't happen.
This is what the chairman said.
We'll punish them severely to show the weight of the sin of trying to flee.
Grab them!
Yes, sir
Come on.
No, let go!
Mother! Mother!
Mother! Mother! Be quiet!
Things should get interesting.
Yes. that's right.
This is too much...
There'll be more people at the show. This is nothing in comparison.
This hand is free not just to cover your face.
Madam! Let us see more!
Madam, don't be a cheapskate!
That's it! That's it!
Y-You mean...
Open up your cunt and show it to us.
l-l can't do such a thing!
Kawada.
Yes sir.
Go to her daughter.
That's not fair, Mr. Onimura. lt's just getting good...
Just go.
lf the madam refuses to cooperate. l'll contact you.
Then...
...do what you want with her daughter.
l see. That sounds like fun.
l understand.
W-Wait. Mr. Kawada!
l'll say it again. Show it to us yourself.
Then ask the people here to look at it.
P-Please look at it...
What the hell?
l can't see it that well!
Whose what?
Say it clearly!
What's the matter? You want me to whip you again?
P-Please wait!
P-Please look at my cunt.
Hey, it's really wet.
Man. this is great.
That's it, madam.
Looks nice.
lt's nice, madam. Let us see more. madam.
l think it's time for the next torture.
No!
Don't make such a fuss by screaming like that.
The wooden horse used for torture is usually much sharper.
This is nothing compared to that.
Looks interesting.
This is where it really gets interesting.
Hey, hurry up and walk.
Who's this?
My ex-boyfriend. Keiko flirted with him.
M-Mr. Murase.
What'll you do with him?
Just watch.
Right. Keiko?
This guy and your mother are going through lots of pain because of you.
Well, whether they go through more pain or not is entirely up to you.
lf you do whatever we tell you to...
...then l'll free them both.
H-Hey.
You can't do that...
Well?
l'll do anything you say! So please let those two go free!
Okay.
Then l want you to start by sucking his cock in front of your boyfriend.
l-l can't...
You said anything.
This is great. Great benefits.
l'll have so much fun.
Ready. Miss Keiko?
Hurry up and do it. lf you don't...
Amazing.
Even if you're not blood related, you eventually turn out like your parents.
You're getting excited watching your girlfriend give a blow job?
All right then.
Akemi, since you're friends with the ex, why don't you?
Sure.
Well? l'm better than Keiko, right?
What's with that look? Pisses me off.
Then l'll show you how it's done.
Move!
Can l do her?
Go ahead. This way, they can see each other.
Let's go. Miss Keiko.
No!
No...
Seems like that guy can't control his sexual desires.
By the way, chairman, we decided the date for the next show.
Shall we invite him too?
He'll be very surprised to see his wife and daughter transformed...
Look at that.
She's really wet.
Amazing.
Touch yourself some more.
Spread your legs out more.
lt's dripping to the floor.
Keep touching yourself.
Show us more!
Good. Now use this next.
N-No!
You're still going to resist?
No... No...
N-No...
No!
No...
Stop...
l-lt feels good...
No...
lt feels good...
No! S-Stop it...
No... lt feels so good...
No...
No!
l-l'm coming...
l'm coming! l'm coming!
No!
l'm coming!
That's it, madam! This is great!
That was great!
That's right.
This was just the beginning.
Nightmarish days for Keiko and me began just like this...