This is feet's paradise!
Coming now!
Shoot!
Hamaji! Are you okay?
Himaji-kun, resist!
These voices are... Shinozaki and Hagiwara-senpai?
I was training with Senpai...
Hagiwara-senpai...
I won't let them do that to Hamaji.
Shinozaki.
I did not.
What is this? What's happening?!
Stop, please stop.
Unfaithful.
Shinozaki, forgive me.
I will not,
you seem to have a weakness.
Not there.
What a pervert...
However
I want to do this!
Hey, boy... you shouldn't be so violent...
Hamaji-kun?
Senpai?
Don't worry, let's go, Senpai!
Eh... are you okay?
I have seen him...somewhere...
Ah, he's the guy from the swimming club!
It's so big.
It can't be, what do I do...?
I have to go back!
I am sorry.
Oww...
Eh...
Your underwear...
Sorry about earlier.
Although you have not touched her breasts,
I would not be doing this.
Instead, I...
You can do whatever you want with my breasts!
Really?
Try.
Well, itadakimasu.
It's very hard...
So soft...
No...
Here, how is it?
Hey, boy.
Grope harder.
Again, this dream...
Huh?
Who is there...?
Miyoshi-sensei!
Hello, Hamji-kun.
It's been a long time.
What are you doing?
I was watching the swimming club's training.
But I found something nicer.
Hey, Hamaji-kun, you had sex with Hagi-chan?
That's not...!
I see... So you're still a virgin.
It's just a dream...
Sensei!?
I will make you feel like in a dream.
This is the most real dream I ever had...
It's so nice...
Have you ever felt that way?
In the end, I will do this with Nakajima-senpai.
You have no technique.
But I like that you're aggressive.
Hamaji-kun...!
You could do worse...
Najakima-san has not returned?
Then, following this, please.
This is not a dream?
Excuse me!
Oh, apparently he is no longer lively...
Too bad.
I think your virginity can be ”consumed”.
Hamaji-kun!
Great, at least, you woke up.
Senpai.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt you somewhere?
Uh-huh...
Hamaji-kun...
I am sorry!
You're a man, after all...
I understand this.
Senpai...
I will...take it down.
Hamaji-kun...
I won't do anything.
Okay.
I am doing this for you.
Hey, boy!
I forgot this...
It's my turn now
to make you cry.
Hamaji Kun, you okay?
Senpai...
I was worried about you. So I got back here, and you were talking in your sleep
Sorry.
I couldn't imagine perverted things about Hagiwara-san...
I apologize. Everything is just because of me.
Does it hurt?
Not at all.
Hey, Hamaji-kun.
You had fun in the pool?
Yes. I had fun.
I see.
What a relief!
Thank you for today.
Thank you for participing in the training.
Ah, don't worry.
I regret that I didn't do more.
That's not true.
I like...
people who are blunt.
I understand.
I have seen you trying hard.
Senpai.