There is something very important at stake for this match.
Put your lives into winning this.
Yeah!
We won't say this again. Give it your all!
Finish it, boy!
This is your chance, Hamaji-kun!
Hamaji-kun.
Shoot!
W-We win!
It's our first victory!
Those boys...
I can't believe they actually won.
Noooo!
Miyoshi-sensei!
Hold on.
You boys,
what's with your appearance?
You've promised us haven't you, sensei.
If we win the match, you'll let us fondle your breasts.
I get it.
Anyway, just wear something on.
Breasts Water Polo
I'm keeping my promise.
If you want to fondle them, just do it.
Bare breasts.
Bare b-
Just for this time.
I guess it has started.
I would prefer to share our first victory with Hagiwara-senpai.
Hamaji-kun.
Today's match is a huge win for you guys.
Especially that winning shot.
It was awesome.
Thanks.
Breasts! Breasts! Breasts!
What's that?
W-wait.
Breasts! Breasts! Breasts!
Ouch!
Hamaji-kun.
It's just stretching. Just relax your body.
I can't.
Because, you are...
Hey, Hamaji-kun.
Do you mind to get off?
My bad.
I-I'll go now.
Just like you, I will also work hard in water polo.
Alright.
Breasts! Breasts! Breasts!
One person only get 3 seconds. Got it?
So short.
That's to be expected or it'll cost you.
It can't be helped.
Here we go.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Hell, yeah!
Here I go.
You're good.
More.
More, please.
Alright, that's 3 seconds.
Soft...
Next. Hurry up.
Yes.
Club member, Horiguchi.
Here I come.
There.
Right there.
I'm feeling it.
You are the best.
Who says you're allowed to suck them?!
I managed to suck her nipples.
I'll stop if anyone else does anything weird.
A celebratory party?
Despite it being just a practice match it's still the first victory for you guys.
It's a celebration but we're just taking you guys to karaoke.
Is that fine?
It's definitely fine.
Just so you know, I'm against this.
I don't even want to breathe in the same air as them.
You've improved a lot, Hamaji-kun.
That last shot, you got the passed ball like this and hit without any doubts.
That's all because you were the one who help me with practice all the time.
Not really.
The effort put in depends on the individual.
I've definitely seen the effort you put in.
Senpai.
What? What is with this?
Just because they won a small match.
Senpai.
What are you doing, Shinozaki?
Since you're done here, let's leave.
Stop it, Shinozaki.
What's gotten into you?
What are you talking about?
Stop messing around.
Only a girl will understand where to touch and what to do to another girl.
I won't lose to the likes of Shinozaki.
I like how much force you put into this, Hamaji-kun.
Wait, why me too?
I'm holding a girl in each of my hands.
I'm holding breasts in each of my hands.
You're too good at this.
Hamaji-kun.
Hamaji-kun?
What's wrong?
You suddenly went silent.
I'm sure he's thinking about something perverse.
Let's go, senpai.
Tell the rest to meet up in front of the club room.
Sure.
Breasts.
Nipples.
So soft.
Finally, the last person.
Here I come.
Fine. Come at me.
Just finish quickly.
Three.
Two.
This boy has potential.
What kind of person is he?
He knows how to make a woman feels good.
This is working well. If this continues on...
We'll go all the way until we reach heaven.
Stop getting carried away!
That was a close call.
What am I going to do now? I'm already aroused.
Is it over?
What?
S-sensei, it's not like I...
Hamaji-kun is the only person
I'm giving the special privilege
to feel me inside here.
I will humbly partake your virginity.
My virginity.
I've already vowed to give my virginity to senpai.
I missed the opportunity again.
Hagi-chan, if you keep dilly-dallying, Hamaji-kun will ended up getting taken by someone else.
Hamaji-kun.
Sorry to keep you waiting, senpai.
Where's everyone else?
It seems like they're all tired from the match.
I see.
The rest of the girls already left for karaoke.
I guess we'll do the celebration next time.
Sure.
Damn it. It was such a good chance.
Shall we go?
A celebration just for you.
I'll treat you as my reward to you for working hard in today's match.
Senpai.
I'll also work hard as well so that I won't lose to you.