Dear, we can finally have sex, just the two of us.
Your cock is really big as always.
More...
Dear...
I love you...
More and more...
Could we make Alice-chan the legal wife already?
Once I make the final decision
then it's irrevocable after that.
HAREM TIME
「I want a baby」
Happy Family Sleep
╔
╝
Misuzu-san,
you sure about this?
Just stop worring
and hurry up.
This is out chance!
I'm goint to sleep with you as well!
My wife, Misuzu-san,
has a daughter from the previous
marriage called Misaki-chan.
I understand their situation,
but the problem started during out first wedding night.
Let's sleep together!
She ended up following us on our honeymoon.
And if we secretly try to go to a love hotel,
she always ends up finding us.
It's always the three of us
sleeping together everyday.
Because of that, even though we're newlyweds,
we can't have sex at all.
Seems I am not getting any tonight eighter...
Misaki, how about you try
sleeping separately from now on?
Why? Mama and I have always slept together.
That's why I'm also going to sleep with Papa as well!
Hey... Seiji-san, say something too!
Papa agrees with me, right?
If he doesn't I'll hate him!
I'm originally an outsider between these two,
so I can't really say much.
L-Let's sleep already then!
Yes!
Seiji-san, we can finally make love to each other.
I-It feels good, but this is just a dream, right?
Does this mean I will really have
to go on without any real sex?
No! Wake up, self!
Delicious.
Oh, did I wake you up, Papa?
Oh well.
I'll be squeezing Papa's milk out again, okay?
Wh-What are you doing, Misaki-chan?
Did you say "again"?
Yes.
I've been licking you everyday.
Misaki-chan, you can't do that!
Why?
Why are you...?
When I lick here, it always twitches like this.
You seem to like it here, too.
I have loved you for a long time now, Papa.
Since that time when we first met...
Misaki-chan...
Even so, Mama had to be the one to take you first.
I couldn't accept that!
That's why I won't let you have sex with Mama!
I'll be the one to make Papa's cock feel good!
So that's how it was, huh?
Misuzu-san, were you awake?
I already noticed it before,
but for you to go this far...
In any case, get away from him!
I don't want to!
Misaki!
Even Papa wants someone who's  younger, right?
Mama already gave birth to me,
so her pussy's already very loose.
Mine's still a virgin,
so it's sure to feel better than Mama's.
Very well then, Misaki.
I'll show you that techniques
that you can't even imagine!
It's a challange then.
I-I can't see my cock anymore.
You are amazing Misuzu-san!
She swallows my whole cock...
I-If this continues, I'll be climaxing... soon...
Misaki won't be able
to take it down all the way, right?
That's not true!
Misaki-chan, if you try and force it down your...
There you go.
I can also do this.
Oh man, those boobs are amazingly warm!
This is too much!
Well?
It can't be done with Misaki's breasts, right?
E-Even I can do that!
B-Both breasts at the same time?
It can wrap it in even though my breasts are bigger?
My breasts are better.
Victory for me!
You choose, Seiji-san.
Which of us feels better?
Wh-Which? I don't know...
I'm cumming. I can't hold it in anymore!
Finally.
Papa's milk!
There's a lot of it...
This cum is amazing, Papa.
I can't hold it anymore.
Misuzu-san, you're amazing!
Not fair, Mama!
And I even planned on giving
my virginity to Papa today...
No! You can't have sex with him.
What are you going to do if you get pregnant?
I don't care if I get pregnant!
Because Papa is my destined one.
There's no one that I can like more than Papa!
Misaki...?
I understand. You can have sex with him then.
Wha...?
Wh-What are you saying, Misuzu-san?
But I am Misaki's mother!
Isn't it normal for me
to wish for my child's happiness?
H-Happiness...?
Mama...
Because we're both women...
No, it's because we're family
that's why I understand.
Misaki truly loves Seiji-san.
Thank you for understanding me.
H-Hey, are you serious about this?
Misaki, try to relax.
M-Mama...
Try to lower your hips a bit.
Seiji-san, try to move.
B-But... Umm...
I-I'm okay.
It hurts a bit, but my pussy wants to do it.
Please, Papa. Do it to me!
I-It's tight...!
My insides are getting stirred up...
This is...
Yes! This is amazing!
It feels good, Papa!
Misaki! Misaki!
I can't hold it in anymore...
Papa, Papa...
Seiji-san, give me your cock, too.
Don't, Misaki!
What is this?
The cock's rubbing inside me...
M-Mama, Papa's cock is amazing!
Of course,
becouse it's the cock
that we both love.
Papa, I love you!
I like you!
I came again!
I love you, Papa!
Wow, cumming this much...
I love you, Seiji-san!
Let's sleep together everyday, okay?
Two partners everyday, huh? Gulp.
It has been a long time since, so I feel weak...
Hey, Papa.
Let's do this everyday from now on, okay?
Harem Time.
Harem Time
I like it.
I like Satou-kun's cock.
I love... Satou-kun!
So please, make me your wife!
W-Wow, his cock is getting bigger again...
It's hot!
Hanazawa-san, if you
squeeze me tightly like that...
I...!
It's okay, I want to gve birth...
I want to give birth to your child.
Please, please cum inside me!
Release it inside me!
Hey, what are you doing, Junko-san?
I just thought of cleaning it up for you,
but do you not like it?
W-Well, it's not that I don't like it, but...
Do not worry.
I may be a doctor, but I am also
quite experienced being an attendant.
Th-That's not what I mean...
That's...!
Is it okay for me to stay like this?
Umm... Reiji-sama, I would like to have a word with you.
Hey, wait.
Is this what we were supposed to talk about?
I don't think I have a chance
to be chosen as a legal wife anymore.
That's why I want to at least
service you properly as a women.
Alice-chan, I've been thinking of rejecting
the inheritance of this household.
Eh, why?
I will help in providing a successor.
I want to help Hanazawa anyway, too.
But in the end, I really don't think
I'm fit to be master of a household.
I've been a free part-time
worker this whole time.
Reiji-sama...
You and the others have done so much,
yet this decision will end up hurting you all.
I'm really sorry.
You haven't changed
since when we were kids.
Don't you remember?
Before you and your mother
left this mansion, we met.
Reiji-kun, umm... When we grow up,
be sure to make me your wife, okay?
I see! You were that girl from...
From that time, I've always wanted
to tell to the kind and gentle you
Alice-chan...
Can I also say one thing?
We're the only ones
who can manage the conglomerate,
but it's the master
who pulls and attracts people.
Junko-san...
For that criterion, I believe
you are more than qualified.
Reiji-sama, please do not
say that you want to stop.
We are able to serve
because it is you.
Everyone...
Umm...
Can I say something?
Hanazawa-san...
About Satou-kun's legal wife...
If it's okay, can we settle it
by who get pregnant first?
It's because Alice-chan has loved
Satou-kun for a very long time,
but were separated, right?
I don't feel like it's fair for
me to cut in-between them.
I see. Then Reiji-sama's firstborn...
The mother of the eldest
will be the legal wife, correct?
So that means...
The first person who gives birth to
Reiji-sama's child will be the legal wife.
Reiji-sama!
Get me pregnant as soon as possible, Reiji-sama.
Everyone, wait!
Oh, it has already become this big!
Hey, deciding on the legal wife
based on who gives birth...
Are you really okay with that?
That's okay.
All of us here just can't help
but love you so much.
But that doesn't mean all of you
need to do it simultaneously!
Even if you say that there's already
something dripping from your cock.
Wow, it's really getting wet.
E-Even we would start to feel good with this.
My nipples are getting swept away and it's getting stiffer.
Everyone's breasts and your cock's getting rubbed.
It's at its limit already!
Wow, that's great!
I've been thinking for quite a while
that it's a bit sad that Junko-san is
always left out as a mere spectator only.
You're really cute!
I don't really...
Your breasts and butt are beautiful.
Even my heart's starting to throb.
W-We can't...
We're all girls...
Junko-san's getting aroused.
Gotta do it more over here!
I am Reiji-sama's secretary!
Don't...
... tease that part!
It's already dripping wet here,
so I guess preparation's over.
J-Junko-san?
I'm sorry, Reiji-sama.
I can no longer stop myself!
Junko-san's a virgin?
That's totally unexpected.
No...
Don't just move your hips...
It's my first time, but I feel... I feel good!
It feels so good!
It's wrapping me tight.
Yes, Reiji-sama!
Please feel the pleasure more!
I'll make up for it.
I'll make up for it with my virgin pussy!
Oh no, it's really getting erotic.
We might have turned
something on inside her.
I'm happy.
For someone like me
to have my first with Reiji-sama...
Junko-san, I'm going to cum!
P-Please, just cum whenever you want.
Oh, no. I'm going to cum, too!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
I'm cummming!
I'm going to cum quickly with this cock!
It's hard, stiff and hot...
More... Please make a mess of me some more!
Please, release it.
Release it inside me!
I want to carry your child!
Me, too. I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Reiji-sama, let's cum together!
I'm already about to come just by looking at it.
Please release it and make me pregnant quickly!
Reiji-sama, I give you mine.
Release lots of your semen inside me.
No...
I'm losing it...
I really can't live without this cock!
I'm also itching to have it in me...
Give it to me.
Give all your semen to me!
Reiji-sama...
Are you feeling it, too?
Does my dripping and wet pussy feel good?
It's okay.
Do whatever you please.
Release it.
Release it!
Cum inside me and impregnate me!
It's already there. I'm cumming!
Yes!
I'm also about to cum already.
Let's all cum together!
It's hot!
There's lots of it...
Semen is flowing inside me.
My womb is getting filled with semen.
It can't enter anymore!
Reiji-sama!
We love you!
After that...
So you've all given birth?
Yes.
We all have
perfectly and safely
given birth to 7 children.
I-I never intended to...
Junko-nee, its clearly obvious.
So we didn't seem to have settled it this time...
Seems so.
Make me
pregnant
again, okay?
Make me pregnant again, okay?