Reiji.
Promise to make me your wife when we grow up.
Good morning.
Yes! I've got it!
Reiji.
I'm next!
From today onwards, Reiji will be in charge of our conglomerate, the Kamiyama Group.
Essentially, he'll be the master of the Kamiyama house.
Harem Time!
Feast 1: Sorry to have made you wait, Master!
Sorry to have made you wait, Master.
Satou Reiji,
from today onwards, you'll be the master of the Kamiyama house.
W-wait a minute!
Why me?
Your mother was a concubine of the late master.
There are no other heirs except you at present to carry on the family lineage.
T-that can't be...
There's no way that I can be the successor to any conglomerate.
Please create the next heir to carry on the lineage as soon as possible.
Please decide on your legal wife,
and then formally inherit the Kamiyama lineage.
For now, I've gathered a few girls according to your tastes.
How do you know my tastes?
From the results of the investigation we did on you.
Well then, go on everyone.
Reiji, please come this way.
W-well, nobody seems keen on answering any of my questions.
Geez.
Please don't embarrass us by making us wait!
Hey!
Please relax, Reiji.
Eh?! This can't be happening!
How wonderful!
So big!
Relax and leave it to us.
We'll make you feel good.
Reiji, use my breasts.
Oh, awesome!
Your cock keeps getting larger.
I'm so happy I can make you feel good.
Oh, awesome!
Your precum's leaking from the tip.
Your nipples... are getting hard.
Reiji, so cute!
I'm already...
It seems so delicious.
H-hey, this is bad!
I'm digging in!
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm gonna cum!
Oh crap!
I can't...
Amazing, you came so much!
It's wonderful!
Don't... suck like that!
It's so thick.
The taste and smell are awesome as well.
Please let us taste more!
I just came a bit ago...
This is just the start, Reiji.
Well then, I'll be taking your penis in, Reiji.
Eh?!
You're seriously gonna go that far?
So big!
It's keeps kissing my womb!
So this is the dick of the master of the Kamiyama house.
A-amazing!
S-so deep!
Awesome!
It's so slippery and is coiling around my cock!
Feels great.
I-I can't anymore!
Coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming, I'm gonna cuuuum!
I'm coming!
Reiji, put it inside mine next.
If it's come to this, I'll just have to do it!
Look at it go in and come out!
A-amazing...
Your dick is amazing.
I want that too!
Do it to me too!
Reiji's cock is churning up my pussy!
I'm begging you, please give me your cum too!
Inside, inside my pussy!
Give me lots of it!
I'm coming!
It's coming out, your cum is pouring into me!
There's a lot of it... inside.
I'm gonna cum!
Reiji, I'll do any perverted thing you want as much as you want.
So please make me sticky with your cum!
No, not my nipples!
If you suck them like that now, I'm gonna...
Her pussy's tightening up so much!
With this much, I'm definitely gonna get pregnant.
So Reiji can last this long, eh?
A-amazing!
Reiji, I love you.
I love you so much.
Please cum a lot, and make my pussy pregnant!
Ah, no!
A lot of it is dripping out!
To think you made them all cum.
You're amazing, Reiji.
You're on a different league of your own, eh?
Sorry for the late introduction,
My name is Kisaragi Arisu.
I'm first in the list of the candidates to be your wife.
Wife? Even if you say that...
Indeed, Reiji.
We all yearn for you.
Please let me bear your babies, Reiji!
More, more! Do me as you desire!
Please mess me up more!
You're amazing!
My head is already completely blank!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Me too, I'm cumming too!
Together, let's do it together please!
Reiji!
Reiji, after becoming your wife,
I'll be sure to bear excellent offspring.
Uh, well, you see..
After coming this far, all of it for that, I need to tell you something.
Yes?
There's someone I like.
So, well...
I'm sorry.
Hey Junko, that's not what you told us!
Since it's come to this, we're gonna do it till you forget about that person!
Reiji's got someone he likes?
I need to investigate this.
Reiji, prepare yourself!
W-wait!
I really can't do it anymore!
Hiraizumi, the senior who was elected Miss Campus this year.
She's rejected lots of people
There have never been a shadow of any boyfriends,
leading to the belief that her ideals are extremely high.
Hiraizumi,
the streets here are dangerous at night,
let me take you.
Then, lend me your shoulder.
So Hiraizumi, you ended up drinking a lot today?
Sorry, but it seemed so fun and it seems I ended up drinking too much.
Though, you seem really drunk too.
Well, I suppose.
Well then, I'll be leaving now.
You're going back?
It'd be terrible if I missed the last train.
You went through the trouble of coming all the way...
H-Hiraizumi?
Did you think I invited you just by chance?
You're a freshman, right?
Interested in our traveling circle?
I am!
I indeed am!
You piqued my interest.
I'm not letting you get away anymore.
That was because I loved you, Hiraizumi.
Don't tell me, you're a playboy?
I need to punish you for being naughty!
I-It's true!
Your tongue is...
Oh crap!
S-Sorry for that.
Seems you've built up a lot, eh?
Hey...
Do it to me next.
H-Hiraizumi...
This is like a dream.
To think I can do it with you like this...
You wanted to do this to me all along?
At first, I wanted to touch your tits.
Then, touch them lots!
Pierce my pussy a lot too!
Until today, I've masturbated to you lots everyday.
You just keep on lying.
It's hitting me deep inside!
I'm coming!
Hiraizumi, I...
You still want more?
Yeah.
Do the things you've always wanted to, it's okay.
I've always wanted to try out more perverted things too.
It's so hot!
Just like my pussy, your dick is raping my tits too.
I'm coming!
More, do me lots more!
Like this?
My ass is tinging.
Keep going, it feels good being hit.
When I hit you here,
your pussy tightens up so much.
It hurts, but I'm feeling it!
I'm begging you, please do me harder!
So good!
It's so good!
It feels great!
T-That place is dirty.
Then, I'm gonna make it all clean.
I wanted to lick your embarrassing parts.
N-no, don't!
If you do it that rough, I'm gonna...
That's fine, let it out!
Put out a lot of it in my face!
Give me a facial!
Facial! I'll give you a facial!
Your thick stuff is on my face!
No, I'm gonna cum again!
This can't be, I'm getting more perverted by the minute!
Me too!
You feel... good too, right?
It's okay, do it as you want!
Your pussy feels so good, I can't stop!
S-Sorry!
Thank you for coming so much for me.
It's fine.
Ever since I met you, I wanted to be covered in your cum.
Let me taste it till the last drop!
Hey, wake up already.
Hiraizumi?
You're heading to university already?
Return me the key later once you head out, okay?
Let's forget about last night.
Since we both seemed to be drunk,
things like these happen.
And that's what happened.
You mean that's what happened in your dreams, right?
It's true!
I say that since there's no way she'd get drunk!
She can hold her liquor just fine.
Hey, where are you going?!
Hiraizumi!
You came to return the key?
Shall we... go drinking together tonight?
Again?
I'm not responsible if we get drunk again, okay?
It's been several days since I've came to the Kamiyama mansion.
Junko brought along a new candidate to be my wife.
However, that was....
Hanazawa?!
Satou, so it was you.
Why are you here?
I too was chosen as a candidate to be your wife.
So, you get the rest, right?
This can't be happening.
It can't be anything but a dream.
However, the feelings are all there.
Hanazawa, what are you?!
This is the first time I've done anything like this,
it probably won't be any good, but...
Hanazawa!
I want to do it!
I want to have sex with you!
I can't do this after all...
What do you mean?
I made a promise with someone from the Kamiyama Group,
since Dad's business is about to collapse.
If I, well, did it with you,
they'd help us out financially.
But, I...
Since it's come to this,
I guess it means the contract is void, huh?
I now understand why my mother left the Kamiyama house.
You do things by manipulating people who have no powers into puppets,
just like you did here, no?!
I've made up my mind, I'm not gonna return here!
Wait!
That's not it.
It's something I myself proposed.
Since it's true that my Dad's company is having issues.
And besides, earlier was just way too sudden, and that scared me.
Umm...
I was happy when I learned that I'd be doing it with you.
Eh?
So, if we can get to know each other a bit more...
Can we start off as friends?
How lenient!
Too lenient!
Reiji's got to decide on a wife as soon as possible.
And as such, we can't consent to that!
And so!
Just do it already!
Well, here we go.
No!
It's so tight!
It's coming inside, Satou's thing is penetrating me!
No, I can't believe my first time ended up like this...
Now, Reiji!
Taste her to your heart's content!
Hanazawa, I've been in love with you for a long, long time.
That can't be.
T-Then, why are you saying this now?
No...
What's this?
It feels so good.
This can't be, so good!
Hanazawa?
I've decided!
I actually do want to be your wife!
I love you.
I love your cock.
Since if I become your wife,
I can do this with you everyday, right?
I love you.
I love you so much, so please make me your bride!
I'm coming!
All in all, this ended up going alright, I guess.
I'm never gonna approve of this!
And like that, this story will continue on!
Please look forward to the next episode too!