Hasande
Ageru
Oof!
Keika, are you alright?!
Ouch...
It's getting dark already, so let's call it a day.
I'm fine, really.
The summer competition is only a few days away.
I have to do at least this much to beat my own record.
...or so I say, but that's just an excuse.
The truth is, I just want spend time together
with Makiyama-kun until I retire
and as long as I possibly can!
Makiyama-kun!
I'll be having a good long masturbation at home later!
Hey, Keika...
Hmm, what is it?
You are sincerely working hard every day.
You truly are amazing!
Come on, you'll be able to do it this time!
I'm sure of it!
Yeah!
I'm gonna "come"!
I'm "coming" too!
Let's jump together!
We'll soar together!
I am being indecent.
You can jump now!
You did it, Keika!
That's incredible, you actually
have beaten your own record!
Keika?
Hoah?!
H-Hey!
Don't follow me!
I'm aroused... I have to rub one out somewhere!
What happened to you?
I can't take this anymore...
Makiyama-kun, I'm already at my wit's end!
K-Keika...
Makiyama-kun... Makiyama-kun!
It's no use, I can't stop myself!
Keika, you...
Sorry... I'm sorry!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
This is your...
So, it's this big...
It's the real thing...
It's an actual dick!
Makiyama-kun, your dick...
It smells sweaty with a hint of pee...
It tastes sour and it's hard yet squishy!
It's delicious!
Keika... Keika!
Hey...
Makiyama-kun, aren't you
getting bored right there?
I think it smells all sweaty right now
but won't you try eating me down here as well?
Keika...
I can't believe it.
I'm having my pussy licked!
And frantically, on top of that!
I am so happy!
I'll do my best as well!
Woah! A titjob...
It feels warm!
I can feel how much your dick is throbbing!
D-Doing this with the real thing sure is hard, huh?
Now it won't be popping out all over with this!
Wow, it's being tucked in and it feels good!
This feels good, huh?
Then, how about this?
The tip is twitching!
I-It's gonna come out!
It's alright! Show me how your dick ejaculates!
Let me see!
W-Wow...
You came a lot...
...but you're still full of energy!
Hey, can we put it inside me?
I got soaking wet since you licked me down here.
I'm sure that it will easily slide in.
Huh? This is weird...
It went it easily,
but my hips won't go up...
I'll be at the top.
I'll be moving slowly.
Oh...
No! I'm sorry, I...
I got carried away.
Why are you apologizing?
I forced my self on you. I acted selfishly...
Do you think that I never wanted this?
I have my own ulterior motives!
Huh?
I won't get as hard as this down
there unless it's you, Keika!
You're not just doing this out of pity?
I'm thinking about you every day
as I drown myself with masturbation!
I try to recall you doing your jumps.
I get horny every night thinking how
great it can be if we end up like this!
Really?
Yeah!
You're a closet pervert, Makiyama-kun.
Huh?
But, you see...
In my case, I've always been thinking about you
and my pussy has been getting
sloppy at all of those times!
I'm a much bigger closet pervert.
K-Keika!
Keika...
Makiyama-kun—
Didn't that kiss taste like both my tits
and your dick blended together?
That's because we've been licking each other earlier.
It's alright, I want to know
how sex actually feels like!
Do it hard, thrust it deep inside me!
Shoot it inside me just like this!
I want to "jump" to ecstasy together with you!
I'm coming, Keika!
I'm gonna come too!
Can we do it together?
Together...
Coming... Let's come together!
Let's soar up together!
That is such an incredible amount!
We did an actual creampie!
You only get a bit of training until the competition.
Nuh-uh, I'll still go on after the competition.
I'll start training myself down here next time.
Right?
Looks like the underwear thief at the
male locker room struck again!
Well, the locker room being run-down doesn't help.
Tanabe-san, do the "walking" properly!
Warm-up exercises are a matter of life or death!
F-Forgive me, Mikako-san...
Why am I the only one...?
Right, as long as you understand what I'm saying.
Mikako-san of
the Sports Club
I'm a salaryman for two and a half years.
To address my lack of exercise,
I enrolled in a swimming school.
I fell in love with Makino Mikako-san, a lecturer.
There's one thing that bothers me.
This is a poorly-managed and worn-out establishment.
Mikako-san doesn't seem like
someone fit to be in such a place.
Oh no, I was so absorbed in
swimming and stayed for too long!
Hmm?
Is that Mikako-san?!
Isn't that my underwear?
Wh-What an amazing voice she makes.
Crap!
Who's there?!
Tanabe-san... How long have you been there?
Ah... well... see...
Looks like you've been watching me, huh?
You got big down here.
Hey... Will you keep quiet about what you saw?
I'll do anything!
Anything?
Will this really be alright?
It's me who said that I'll do anything!
It somehow is throbbing and very stiff...
I'm fine with gobbling it down though...
Mikako-san... No way!
R-Right up to the base...
It's twitching...
Sh-She's doing a very good!
Is she used to doing this?
However, I'll end up coming immediately!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity! While we're at it...
U-Umm, Mikako-san. I have a request...
Hmm?
Wow...
It got totally buried even without
her hands pushing them together!
It feels good being squeezed!
Is this the one called titjob?
How about moving just like that?
The swimsuit's fabric is rubbing against me!
Does this feel good?
Yeah, but since we're already at it...
Let me do you as well!
I can't hold myself back!
Not so hard... You're hurting me, Tanabe-san!
Mikako-san, stick your tongue out!
It's gonna come out already!
Wow... There's so much sperm...
I'm sorry, Mikako-san...
Nah... I'm the one who suggested doing this...
It's the scent of a man's seed!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
Huh?
Will you mind having sex with me?
Huh—?!
Do you hate the idea of having sex with me?
Th-That's...
Then, it should be alright!
It's slipping out...
Hmm?
Mikako-san, don't tell me...
Yes, this will be my first time.
No way! If you're just forcing yourself—
I'm fine with doing something like this!
It feels painful...
So this is how sex feels...
Why would you go this far?
You see, I hate getting my chest
stared at for a long time now.
That's the reason why I chose to work
in this place where men rarely come.
But distancing myself away from
men made my sex drive stronger!
Then my habit of stealing underwear started...
What I want to say is that I noticed
your stares at me, Tanabe-san!
I was masturbating while thinking about
how it'll be alright if it's you who will catch me!
I am such a big pervert in heat
who wants to get raped!
I'm sorry! Of course, you're taken aback by me!
Mikako-san...
You don't have to apologize for anything!
Me too... Don't you know
how much I used you as a fap material?!
Huh?!
If you say that you want to be raped that much,
then it's the same as what I wanted to do all along!
Tanabe-san—!
More... More!
Mikako-san!
Rape me!
Keep thrusting your cock even more!
Use my pussy without any reserve!
Make this virgin pussy of mine
unable to forget the taste of a man's seed!
Please turn me into a full-fledged woman!
Getting a creampie feels good!
Did you know? That underwear
thief isn't showing up anymore!
Perhaps her sexual frustration has
been satisfied somewhere out there.
Tanabe-san! How many times do I
have to tell you before you get it?!
Forgive me, Mikako-san...
You'll have to stay behind today.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization