Muratomi-san, where are Miu-san and Oga-san today?
They said they'd drop by after work.
What, you interested in Oga or something, Yurika-chan?
N-No, that's not...
Oh?
So that's how it is.
I-It's not!
Oh, right, this is your first time coming here at night, Asuka.
Yeah, it is.
I came here a lot during the cafe hours, but
it seems more fun to be here at night.
It has that adult taste.
And this is your first taste of it, right?
Don't phrase it like that.
I'm not even drinking alcohol.
Oh, it's Oga.
What? He's still stuck at work?
How's that even possible when we work at the same place?
What's he even doing?
What? Itsuki-san and Miu-san aren't coming?
Seems like it.
Hm hm hm.
Just the two of them in the office
working through the night.
This just screams suspicious.
Ew, you're so gross.
Huh? Wait does that mean...
No way in hell.
Circumstances of Love for Working Adults
Hataraku OTONA no RenAi Jijo
Circumstances of love for working adults the animation.
Your dick is already rock hard.
M-Miyu-san, we can't do this.
It'll be fine.
No one should be coming into the office now.
Doing something like this in our work place
really makes your heart race, doesn't it?
You're in the mood, aren't you, Itsuki-kun?
In the mood for something naughty.
W-Well...
Come on, there's so much naughty
fluids coming out of your tip.
Do my boobs really feel that good?
M-Miyu-san, if you're that rough, I...
It's fine. Don't hold yourself back. I want a closeup
of seeing you when you cum, Itsuki-kun.
I'm gonna cum...
Cum. Do it!
Do it. Cover me with your hot, dirty load!
You came.
I think it's your turn to take the lead now.
Miyu-san, I have a favor to ask of you.
Yeah, I think I basically get the gist.
I've actually wanted to try this for a really long time.
Huh?
Turn around, if you will.
Wh-Why?
Miyu-san, could you shut your eyes?
Wait, Itsuki-kun?
Come on, take a look at your huge tits.
Geez what are you planning to do
by making copies of my boobs?
I never knew you were this big of a pervert, Itsuki-kun.
Don't!
It's gonna copy your dirty face if you're not careful.
Th-That's easier said than done.
I think this is connected to the server.
We need to delete the data.
It won't be a problem as long as you don't show your face.
No!
You're getting really hot down here, Miyu-san.
See? Can you hear the sounds it's making?
No, don't say it like that.
Your dick is so hot, Itsuki-kun.
You're quite the pervert yourself, Miyu-san.
B-But how can't I be in this situation?
How long have you been this wet for?
Ever since you started rubbing my boobs.
My body just started heating up...
I can't stop it anymore!
I want your dick so badly, Itsuki-kun.
I want it in my pussy!
I'll do it in a place that'll make you feel the most pleasure.
Hey, are we really going to do it out here?
Th-There are people in the building over there.
There sure are.
What do you mean "there sure are?" They're going to see us.
But you like this kind of thing, don't you?
Huh? That's not...
But you're already a wet mess down here.
Don't...
Your hot thing is hitting me...
You want it don't you? Be honest and tell me.
Y-Yeah, I want it. I really do want
you to put it into me right here.
You really are a pervert.
Well then.
It's here! Your dick is here!
Your pussy is so hot, wet, and so incredibly tight!
My coworker just complimented me on my pussy at work!
If you keep screaming out like that,
they're really going to notice us.
B-But you're just moving so intensely!
It feels so good! I can't hold my voice back!
Don't! You can't play with my boobs
while moving your dick inside me!
It's going so deep!
No, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
You can cum.
Come on. Cum in front of all these people, Miyu-san.
No!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I never knew that you were this perverted, Miyu-san!
Don't say that!
I can't stop!
Your dick is hammering deep inside of me!
It-It feels so good!
I feel like I'm going to melt!
If you keep squeezing me like that I might
not last as long as I thought I would.
Me too... Just keep going and cum inside me!
My pussy will drink every last drop!
Huh? But...
I want it inside! It feels so good!
M-Miyu-san!
Your cum is coming out!
Your hot stuff is here!
So good... It feels so good!
Your dick is pulsing inside me, Itsuki-kun.
Sorry.
Huh?
I really did mean it when I'd take every last drop, but...
It overflowed.
Itsuki-kun?
Yes?
Let's work some overtime tomorrow too.
Sure.
Circumstances of love for working adults.
Yurika-san, give me another.
Um, Naruto, shouldn't you stop?
Stop?!
Are you saying I should stop because
Yurika-san's alcohol is bad?
I'm gonna kick you out of this bar!
I don't even get what you're trying to say.
She must be drunk.
This is unforgivable. I'm gonna sue you!
Oga-kun, prostrate yourself in repentance on your stool!
You gotta do it...
What? It's almost closing time and
you're acting like this. What now?
You'll just have to take her home now, won't you?
Huh?
You two have been friends since you
were in school together, right?
With Tomoe-chan.
Well, yeah, I guess.
Something really bad must've happened at work.
I'm sure of it.
You think so?
I do!
Tomoe-san doesn't even usually drink this much.
Naruto? Feeling better?
Yeah, a little bit.
I'm really sorry about today.
Don't worry about it. We all have our bad days.
You really are a softie, Oga-kun.
You make me want to let you spoil
me when you act like this.
Will you spend the night with me?
Naruto?
I'll forget about everything after I sober up.
So just think about this as a one-time thing.
Wait, that really tickles.
Are you already getting turned on?
I'm not!
You're barely even touching my boobs, but I'm...
That's not fair! You can't lick there...
You're playing dirty! This isn't...
How's it feel?
You're so mean!
You're really so mean!
You already know how it feels!
Yeah, but I want to hear you say
it with your own words, Naruto.
No! My nipples feel so good.
When you twirl them around like that with
your tongue, my body gets so excited!
Your fingers are...
Why does it feel so good?
Hey, can you hear this? I just teased you a little
and now it's like a water park down here.
You're such a pervert! Lecher!
Jerk...
Why do you have to say these things out loud?
What, so you can handle it if it's about
your boobs but not your pussy?
It feels good! It feels so good!
I feel so good!
Naruto? I can't hold back anymore.
Face this way.
L-Like this?
Relax your legs.
This is really embarrassing.
You shouldn't be. Come on, open your legs.
You need to move your hand too.
But this is, you know...
Okay...
Naruto, you're so cute.
Don't say that to me.
I feel like I'm about to explode.
Oh wow, your dick is amazing. It's so big and it's moving.
Is something that big really going to fit inside me?
I can tell. I can feel how hot and big your dick is.
I'm putting it in.
It's coming in! It's coming!
It's coming inside!
Naruto, are you okay?
I'm okay. So please, please keep going.
Are you really okay?
Your dick's screaming out that it wants to move.
I can feel your dick pulsing inside me.
If it ever gets too tough for you, I II stop immediately.
You're moving!
Your thing is moving inside of me!
This is amazing! I've never felt anything like this before!
My mind's going blank. I think I'm going crazy!
I think your dick is making my pussy go crazy!
So good! It feels so good!
I can't focus. I'm losing it!
What do you want to do, Naruto?
Want me to stop?
No, don't stop!
More! Do me more!
I can keep going.
You're pushing my insides so hard!
I can feel every thrust echoing in my head!
My pussy can handle this, so...
My mind's going blank!
My body feels like it's on fire!
It's so hot!
Naruto, even your asshole is twitching.
I guess that means my dick feels good then?
Do I really have to tell you?
I can't... Even though we're doing it out here in this position
and if anybody saw us, I'd die of embarrassment,
I can't stop!
Your dick is getting bigger and pulsing inside of me!
Yeah, that means that I'm just about ready to cum.
Are you going to cum inside me?
Are you going to feel good from me?
Naruto!
It's going so deep!
This is so embarrassing!
Naruto, you're so tight!
If you keep squeezing me like that, I'm gonna...
I can tell. I can tell that your dick's about
to erupt and let out your hot cum!
It's coming! Your cum is coming!
It's pumping out inside of me.
So this is what sex is like?
Naruto, are you okay?
It hurt a little in the beginning, but
in the end it didn't hurt at all.
Your insides were so tight. It was the best!
P-Please put me down already.
Sure.
This is the only time we'll do this.
Today's special after all.
But please do it one more time.
Huh?
Circumstances of love for working adults.
But seriously, color me surprised.
It's not every day I see you helping
out with the store, Itsuki-san.
I heard that the manager's out with a cold today.
So I volunteered.
My division manager gave me the okay too.
Well I also get to look at Toba-san's maid uniform since I've been
working since the afternoon. Not too bad of a deal in my opinion.
Wh-What are you saying? You're being stupid.
You look good in a maid uniform Yurika-san.
You should work in that when you bartend at night too.
Geez, not you too Asuka-chan.
What's the matter?
No, it's nothing.
You... I told you so many times not to turn
it on when there are people at the counter!
Yurika-san?
Oh no, I'm shaking so hard! Stop! Stop!
Asuka-chan's gonna find out!
Good evening! I know I'm a little early, but can I come in?
O-Oh, welcome.
The recording at the studio ended early.
I heard that Itsuki-kun was helping out today so I was
wondering if there was anything I could do too.
Thanks. That will be great.
He made it even stronger!
Yurika-san?
S-Sorry. M-My stomach's just not feeling too well.
Are you sure you're okay?
We still have some time before the bar
opens. Why not rest a bit in the back?
O-Okay. Sayoko-san, sorry to ask you, but
could you watch the shop for a bit?
Sure. That's no problem.
Thanks. I'm going to lay down for a little bit.
No!
That's ba...
Toba-san, you're getting really wet.
It's not my fault! It's been inside me for so long, I...
You're already about to cum?
My pussy's out of control.
N-No!
This is really, really bad!
I'm gonna cum! No!
Show me how you cum, Toba-san.
No! No! No!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Wow, look at those dirty juices go. You're
making a mess on the floor, Toba-san.
Th-That's...
I came, but it's still so hot. It's not stopping!
I can't! I'm at my limit! I can't hold on anymore!
Look. This is what you wanted, isn't it?
That's it! I want your hot dick!
Well, I'll give it to you since you're
being so dirty today, Toba-san.
Don't be mean.
P-Put it in me already.
It's coming! Your dick is coming inside!
It's so hot! It feels so good!
Toba-san, which feels better? Me or the vibrator?
Your dick! I love your dick!
Please move! Mess me up with your dick!
Toba-san!
So good! You're messing me up so good!
Good! So good! I feel like I'm going to lose it already!
My pussy's going numb, I'm going crazy!
If you're too loud, they're going to notice.
But, I've been waiting for your dick for so long!
I want more! More! More! This time I want to cum with you!
I'm going to break! I'm going to break!
This is bad! My mind's already falling apart!
Toba-san, can you tell that I'm about to cum?
Yeah, I can! Your dick's so hot and it's swelling up!
Do it! Pump your huge load inside me just like this!
Yeah, here I come.
I'm going to give you all of it inside you!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Something big is coming!
It's coming!
Toba-san?
Clean me with your mouth.
O-Okay.
You look so dirty right now.
Don't say that. You're embarrassing me.
I-If you keep looking that sexy, I'm gonna...
It's getting hard and twitchy again.
If you feel like cumming again. Just give me all of it again!
Your tongue... I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!
Yurika-san?
The bar's opening now, so I came to get you...
Y-Yeah, I'll be right there.
Yurika-san, you're drenched in sweat!
Are you okay?
Huh? Sweat?
Do you need any help?
Huh? No, I'm fine. I'll be right out.
Okay. I got it.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Later.
Thank you.
What if she found out?!
You say that, but you're grabbing
me pretty tightly down here.
Let's go one more time.
Y-You pervert!
Sorry for the wait.
Oh, Uratomi-san and Miyu-san, nice to see you.
Sorry, I'll get the usual right out.
Oh, it's the division manager and Miyu-san.
Welcome.
Hey, we're here.
What were you two flirting about back there?
Huh?! You two were flirting?!
Huh? We weren't...
Right, Toba-san?
Asuka-chan, it's getting late, so maybe you should go home.
Don't treat me like I'm a child!
You really do look the part of a bartender, though.
Is it time for a job change?
No, don't joke about that.
I'll be back in the office tomorrow.
Huh? I thought bar-tending made you happier, Oga-kun.
Huh?
It looks like you have lots of different entertainment here.
Right?
Miyu-san, come on. What are you even talking about?
Well, whatever. I'll just write it off as an adult friendship.
But in return, we're going to have some overtime tomorrow.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality check: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч