It's finally finished.
After a whole year...
That's odd.
This time...
Fukaya...
Whenever I was with you, I'd tease you.
But this time...
This time, I'll...
Fukaya!
More! I want more!
Maybe I should still test this one.
Shion Fujino
Fukaya
Mita
Strange ♥ Kind of Woman #2
Now that I know all about Fujino's habits I've had to give it to her a lot.
Fujino! Wait!
I can't! It's been ten times already.
Let's stop for today.
We still have school too.
Come on, let's start on breakfast.
Oh, I have duties today, so I have to leave early.
I'll leave the key for you.
See you later.
Fujino-san?
You're Shion Fujino, right?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Mita, an acquaintance of Fukaya.
You're a little unsatisfied with him, correct?
I have a little something to take care of that.
Have him drink this.
Don't worry, it's nothing weird.
This will make him more agreeable with your desires.
If you give it to him, he'll perk up right away.
But, make sure that you don't drink any.
See ya.
Fujino! Look out!
Fujino!
Fujino! Are you alright?
Augh...
"Augh"?
I have to take her to nurse's office!
Nurse's Office
That gave me a heart attack...
Whoa...
Are you alright?
H-Hey now!
Don't do that, Fujino...
We can't do it here.
Besides, your body's kind of...
Weak from...
That...
Now what did you do?
W-Well, Fujino got hit during P.E. and fell.
Is she alright?
Uh, yeah.
She just came to, so I think she's fine.
I see. Then I'll just take a look at her.
You go back to class.
Huh? Oh, sure.
Bye, Fujino.
Are you alright?
Where is she today?
I haven't seen her all morning.
Have him drink this.
What did you give me?
This will make him more agreeable to your desires.
If you give it to him, he'll perk up right away.
Fujino! Where have you been all this -
Are you all right? You look horrible.
Fujino!
Are you all right? You're not even walking straight.
Where are you... Wait a minute!
Hey! What's going on?
Fujino...
Hey...
What's wrong?
Hey! Fujino!
What's wrong with you, Fujino?
Fujino, what the hell's gotten into you?
F-Fujino!
It...
Put it in! Hurry!!
Fujino spoke!
Put it in!
Now! Now!
Fujino...
What the...?
Fujino's convulsing inside.
Is she out of control?
No choice then...
She needs some release. That's all I can do.
Go ahead Fujino, go for it.
Come on.
Go.
Fujino, did I make it in time?
Fujino.
Well, I'm not exactly sure what happened, but she should be all right with some rest.
I see. That's good to hear.
It's not all right! You go back to class.
Honestly...
I won't tell you not to do whatever, but at least be more careful.
Excuse me then.
Looks like she drank it after all.
That voice...
Mi-Mita!
I told her not to drink any.
What did you do this time?
I finished it.
What did you make me drink?
An aphrodisiac.
The same that she drank.
What do you want from all this?
You'll be getting hot very quickly.
What are you planning on...?
Didn't you think there was a point to all my teasing?
M-Mita.
Oh well.
Let's go to your place. It'll be a problem if we started out here in the open.
I remember this place.
It hasn't changed that much since then.
Oh, you still have this?
I remember it...
You got a bigger bed.
You probably do it with Fujino-san everyday here.
My body...
You want it, right?
You can't take it, right?
You're losing control even as I speak.
I'm sure it's telling you, "Do it, do it."
Even this.
You...
Look, it's already hard.
All right, I'll give it to you...
But you have to say that you want it.
Hey, wait...
If you try to hold it in, you'll go insane...
Let me have a taste.
Going to come?
It's some strong stuff, don't you think?
All right, I'll put it in my mouth for you.
Mita! You're...
I can't hold it.
You have a lot to share.
I can't. I'm trying to stop myself, but I just can't resist this.
I can't!
You don't have to resist.
You want to be inside this, don't you?
You want to be inside me?
It's all right. Let yourself go.
But I'm with Fujino.
I can't.
It's all right.
Just say it's the drug's fault.
You aren't doing anything bad.
T-The drug?
Yes, it's all the drug's fault.
Ow...
Mita.
Y-You're a...
Don't worry about it.
But...
It's all right.
T-That feels so good...
I think I drank some of the drug too.
Fukaya.
I can't take this.
Fujino...
Don't think about anything else.
Just look at me.
Mita.
Oh, you're up.
You're in the nurse office.
If you're looking for Fukaya, he went somewhere with Mita.
That guy's pretty inconsiderate.
Hey, Fujino. You shouldn't be up -
And another one that doesn't listen to me.
Wow, Fukaya.
Yes...
Just... keep...
It's so intensive!
You're in really deep, Fukaya!
I'm losing control of myself!
Good, Fukaya!
Fukaya...
Stronger... Upright.
Please!
Thank you...
Fukaya... I'm... I'm...
I'm...
Fukaya!
Fukaya...
F-Fujino!
Wait, this...
Fujino!
Wait!
Mita!
Let go of me!
I won't!
Mita...
Are you really going to just leave me like this?
Today isn't the first time I've said I liked you.
M-Mita... I can't...
I was lying. Get a move on.
Mita!
I'm an easygoing girl.
I'm sorry...
Well, I understand, but...
Fujino...
I'm better than the vibrator, aren't I?
Fujino!
Damn it! Where are you, Fujino?
Watch it!
You dumbass!
What are you so dazed about!?
If you died, what the hell do you think I'd do!?
You're just lucky I got here in time!
Nevermind that!
You know...
I really do...
...love you the most!
Damn...
Hey, that was the first time I said that I love you...
Fujino...
Sorry if I made you feel alone.
Fujino.
- kaya...
Fujino...
I love you, Fukaya...
The doors will now close. Please prepare for departure.
The usual time...
At the bottom of the stairs...
She'd be at the same place.
Made it.
Morning, Fujino -
Mita!
Morning, Fukaya!
What are you doing here?
I told you that I'm an easygoing woman.
Thanks to you.
But I'm not letting this go!
It goes on from here!