My name is Oshio Tsubohachi.
I am a genius acupressurist.
I have an ability for pushing pressure
points. To explain things further...
There is a certain point in every women's bodies
that puts them in heat when pressed,
and I can spot them in no time.
When I push them using my acupressure finger skills,
any woman will instantly turn
into a crazy cock-craving sow!
I call that particular pressure point as the "estrus switch".
This girl's switch is...
...right here!
I'll say it once again. This woman
who had her switch pressed...
...will turn to a sow instantly
drowning in waves of lust!
Y-Your cock feels good!
This isn't some kind of hypnosis.
The innate desire for a cock in that woman
is just being unleashed and nothing more.
In short, even this seemingly diligent girl in glasses
has been thinking of nothing else but lewd stuff.
She's a filthy slut!
For these women harboring such desires inside them,
this cock of mine is a messiah
that will fulfill their needs!
Pour it inside me!
That's right, my name says
"pushing the points" literally!
Estrus Switch
Women Dragged Down To Depravity
Hatsujou Switch The Animation
Well, then...
What kind of woman
should I get a taste of for today?
Hmm?
Oh...
Mmm...
This girl is a top-notch one!
However, her estrus switch is beneath her nipple!
That is quite a difficult spot...
Huh?
Wh-What?
She's coming this way.
Hey there, mister.
Weren't you just ogling at my body?
Huh?
Don't you know? That's called "sexual harassment".
H-harassment? I just happened
to look a little towards you.
So, you're playing dumb... Then, how about we do this?
Between a suspicious man like you
and a delicate schoolgirl like me,
which one do you think the police will believe?
This fucking brat!
W-Wait!
What should I do so that you'll let me off this?
Shit! I could shut her mouth up
if only I can push her switch right now!
It's gonna be fairly difficult to do it upfront!
What should I do?
Huh, you want me to forgive you?
Huh?
Then, give me your wallet.
Do that and I'll forget about
your sexual harassment.
I-I understand...
This brat is used to this scheme...
Thank you!
This might be my chance!
You're unexpectedly loaded!
While she's busy digging in my wallet...
I don't hate rich middle-aged men like you.
Here I go!
It's right here!
I did it!
Wh-What did you just do to me?
She hasn't been subjugated yet after that?
Interesting!
W-Wait...
Let go of me!
I said let go, you pervert!
Stop...
No... Why am I like this?
I can't muster up any strength!
What's the matter? Aren't you
making such cute reactions?
You can call for help if you want.
S-Stop...
That is if you can.
Y-You're a pervert!
I swear that the police will get you!
I don't hate it when girls try to resist,
but it breaks my heart when
it looks like I'm raping them.
I'll use acupressure on you one more time.
You got quiet now just as expected.
I want it...
Cock...
Hmm? What did you say?
Y-Your cock!
Give it to me!
Please, your cock...
She totally fell down this time.
Acupressure becomes more effective
in succession just as they say.
C-Cock... Cock!
This is what I want!
And this should settle the
issue about your consent.
I don't care about that!
Hurry up...
I want your cock in my pussy!
I see... if you want it that much...
I'll give it to you! Here you go!
Y-Your cock went in!
You acted like you hate this,
but the truth is you couldn't help
wanting me to shove it in, right?
Y-Yeah! Yes... This is incredible... More!
You slutty brat...
You're making such a stupid-looking face!
I'll give you my first shot for now!
I'm gonna have a baby...
Don't expect me to give you a break with just this.
I'll press your switch one more time!
I-I'm begging you, I haven't had enough...
I want more...
S-Squirt your semen inside my pussy!
Please make me pregnant!
I'll lend this to you if you want.
Shove it in your pussy by yourself.
Yay...
P-Please excuse me...
Y-Your cock went inside me again!
Wow...
It's going in deeper than before!
This brat who acts conceited earlier
is now shaking her hips on her own!
This is why I can't stop using my acupressure!
More!
Wow... I'm coming again!
Sh-Shoot it inside me!
Impregnate my womb with your cock juice!
That brat is such a nymphomaniac though...
She keeps on wanting me so much to my
annoyance, so I have to abandon her.
I probably knocked her up.
I came raw ten times inside her, after all...
Well, she's kept bugging me to impregnate her,
so she should be grateful now!
Oh...
Isn't this girl a top-notch one!
Nice! Nice!
Well then, maybe I should get a taste of this girl...
Hey, miss... May I have a moment?
Huh?
You see, I got lost...
I'm sorry, but would you mind
showing me the way to the station?
I'll show you the way.
Huh?
The way to hell, that is! Come on!
You've got some balls to try hitting on my girl!
Th-This is bad! I have to pretend being unconscious!
Alright there, don't think that you'll easily—
Huh?
Looks like he's out cold.
Tsk! Can't help it then... Fucking geezer!
Let's go, Ayaka!
Okay.
That brat actually hit me, shit!
What do you want to eat at home?
Ow... That brat!
I'll make him pay back thoroughly!
Oh no, he tumbled over!
His butt is out! That's hilarious!
Shinya...
What, you wanna have sex already?
How adorable!
You ruined the mood! Shinya, you idiot.
Alright, I get it.
I'll take a nap, so you can use
my cock as much as you want.
Alright then, good night.
He's the worst...
Yes?
Evening! It's a delivery.
May I have your stamp or sign here, please?
Honjou Ayaka...
My revenge will be thorough.
The location of this girl's switch...
I already figured it out last time!
Wh-What happened?
What did this man just do to me?
No... Wh-Why?
Good girl!
Look, don't you want this thing?
You're already game for it?
Go to the nearby park's toilet naked.
If you do, I'll give you lots of love that you want.
You're here.
Aren't you earlier than expected?
Looks like the estrus switch is taking effect.
Wh-Wh-What am I even doing?
But I have to do it with him...
What an obedient girl.
Forgive me, Shinya...
It looks like my body turned strange...
I-I promise that I'll go straight home after this...
I-It's huge... very huge...
And it has such a strong stench...
I-I'll only do this today...
It will be a one-time thing!
You've been craving for this, right?
It grew bigger... I-It's incredible!
It's huge and thick!
I-I'm coming!
His semen is sticking to my throat!
You're used to blowjobs just as I expected.
I'm begging you...
Huh?
Please let me have your dick down here...
That...
That's not the right hole...
I-It hurts...
It hurts, it hurts!
Don't think that I'll simply be making you feel good!
I-It hurts! It hurts...
Please... N-No!
Looks like it's her first time having it in her ass.
Oh, they're getting it on!
Hiya, Tsubo-chan!
You're finally here.
So, is she the one you're talking about?
Huh... Isn't she quite a beauty?
Who are they?
We can do her as much as we want...
I don't want them!
Ouch!
What are you doing?!
Oops, your prank went a little too far...
I-It's the same sensation as earlier!
Sorry about that! I gave her another
acupressure so it's alright now.
Damn! I hope that does it, Tsubo-chan... Ow...
My head is going blank...
No... Stop squeezing my tits!
I'll be having the first bite!
Ouch!
N-Not there!
No!
I'm throbbing deep in my belly from being
touched by these middle-aged men...
I don't care, anyone will do...
I want a cock in me!
We'll be using your lewd body a lot, okay?
Your pussy is soaking wet as well.
I'm putting it in, okay?
Did you already come just from putting it in?
We've only just begun though.
You're so sexy, Ayaka-chan!
Do you want our cocks that much?
Yeah... Your cock feels good!
Your pussy keeps on squeezing me hard!
You look good when being toyed by middle-aged men!
Women who fell so low from grace really are the best!
Huh?
It's about time for him to come out.
It's a call from your reliable boyfriend.
Huh?
Ayaka, are you in the convenience store?
How long are you gonna be there?
Shinya...
Huh?
I-I'm doing lewd things with old men...
Huh, what did you say?
Good... It feels good!
Good!
Th-This feels incredible!
No! I can't! I'm gonna come!
A-Ayaka!
Wh-Where are you right now?
That's right! Get more distressed! Feel more anguish!
You should suffer!
It feels good! So good!
Do you want our cocks that much?
I'll be filling your womb up soon!
Please let her be safe!
Oh, it's a message from Ayaka...
What is this, a video?
Do you want our cocks that much?
It feels good! I'm coming!
More, more...
I'll be filling your womb up soon!
Ayaka-chan, you really love sex!
Yes... It feels so incredible!
This is gonna be our secret...
Which would you prefer between
your boyfriend's or our cocks?
I love your cocks more!
You heard her.
Seems like your modest cock can't satisfy her!
Y-You're tightening up! You're
doing great, Ayaka-chan!
This is so intense!
I-I never had it like this before! Wow, incredible!
We'll mold your pussy to the
shape of our cocks in no time!
I'm gonna come! This is too much!
Hey, hey! Don't be so rough on her!
We finally got a toy but you
might end up breaking her.
Wow, it's incredible!
She's squeezing me so tightly!
Keep them up! I'm gonna go crazy already!
We're already about to come!
Ayaka-chan! I can come inside you, right?
Yes! I want both of your thick baby seeds
to fill my pussy now on my risky day!
Ayaka-chan, from now on
you're gonna be our toilet!
Come on, face the camera and make a peace sign.
Give your peewee boyfriend a parting message.
Shinya, forgive me... Bye-bye...
My revenge is complete.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization