Fujino...
Fujino?
Fujino!
Johnson
F-Fujino...
Me or the vibrator...?
Which do you like better!?
Shion Fujino
Fukaya
Nurse
Strange ♥ Kind of Woman #1
Morning!
Just what is Fujino thinking?
Her name is Shion Fujino.
She has a reputation here of being rather cute...
But she doesn't talk or associate with anyone.
Despite that, we are kind of dating, but...
Dating?
Are we really dating?
Well, if you count...
That stuff...
And that stuff too.
But still...
What does Fujino think about it?
All right, someone come up to solve these problems.
First problem: Fujino
Second: Takano
Come up to the front.
You want me to use this?
During class?
Wouldn't that be weird?
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Are you all right?
Your face is red.
Hey...
Fujino?
Are you happy now, Fujino?
I guess this puts me on the same level as her.
Shit.
Sorry, I have some things I need to do.
So I'll be going myself.
See ya.
A vibrator?
A vibrator.
Nice weather, huh?
Sensei, be serious about this!
I'm really troubled here!
Sorry.
Well, won't it be better to leave it alone?
Sensei, you can't be serious about what you just said.
Well, think about it.
It's not like it's hurting anyone.
Oh boy...
She's not "sweet playing" you, so don't worry.
You should have fun together.
But, just do it in moderation.
But...
But, if she obsesses over that vibrator like she has...
I don't think there'll be room for me.
Nothing I say will work on you.
Does Fujino even like me?
If she's just using me to work that thing...
Then is this just a one-sided relationship?
The doors will now close. Please prepare for departure.
The usual time...
At the bottom of the stairs...
Made it.
And then, she'd be standing at the same place.
Morning, Fujino.
Though she never really greets me.
Can't she at least say something to me?
H-Hey, did you do the internet homework last night?
Somehow, Fujino looks a lot more amorous today.
Are you all right? Your face is red.
Her chest.
S-Sorry, I'll move away from you.
Are you all right?
Her breasts feels so... so good.
Both of them feel so soft.
What's this, hard thing?
This is...
No way...
But...
No, it has to be.
This is...
A... vibrator?
Fujino... No.
Why does she have a vibrator?
And, on the train too?
Crap, I'm getting hard.
Now what?
Fujino
Not here!
She's doing this all by herself.
To think Fujino was this... lustful.
I came.
In place like this.
Fujino...
So that means you're accepting me?
You want more?
Fujino!
You're not serious!
For real?
No, wait.
No matter how you look at it, this is just weird.
But I may not have another chance like this.
Well, maybe not, but...
This may be my only chance that Fujino's giving me...
But then it isn't right to do this in in this kind of place.
But Fujino looks so damn good.
Agh! But at this point I won't be able to turn back.
But then Fujino seems to want it.
But then that may not be a good enough reason.
To hell with it, I can't take this!
It's inside.
N-Now what do I do?
I can't hold out like this.
Good...
More.
More! I want it in further!
I want it all the way inside!
Maybe it'll go in like this.
It's pushing it out.
I should... put it back in.
I-It's tightening...
Coming!
Thank you for riding.
We are ariving at Kina Station. Kina Station.
The exit is to the right.
I just can't believe that you treasure that thing so much.
Even with that roaring sound it makes.
What?
Is this... the vibrator's remote control?
At the time, I thought she gave it as a sign we were dating...
So does that mean that she gave me the remote only because she puts me on the same level as that vibrator?
No wonder you think it's a bad sign.
That's right. It's definitely that.
Fujino thinks of me and the vibrator as the same kind of things.
Hey!
I'm a toy...
Fujino only thinks of me as a toy.
I'm sure of it!
Don't babble so much.
Release it some other way.
Sensei, I don't really feel like that right now...
That's not what this is saying.
I can't, now that I'm with Fujino...
Show me how you pleasure that girl of yours.
Isn't that just an excuse for you to do this?
Shut up...
Sensei...
You're pretty virile.
But I'm not done with you yet.
What's wrong?
Am I as good as her?
You can't be satisfying her like this.
Fujino!
Damn it!
Looks like I hit a nerve.
Good!
Yes!
Just like that! Go in deeper!
Sensei!
Inside!
Now I've done it...
Hey, don't worry about it.
It was consentual.
But I guess you do have your share of strange women.
Fujino's a fine choice though.
Mita!
mita means choice, but of course also sounds like Mita's name.
Please don't mention her!
She almost killed me with all those weird drugs she made me drink!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I didn't do anything bad!
This guy may be the weirdest of all...
Hey, cheer up.
Take these.
These are... pool admission tickets?
Tomorrow's your day off.
Both of you should go.
Fujino...
Were you waiting here for me?
Fujino!
Awkward...
Hey, I have tickets for the pool.
Would you like to go with me?
See you tomorrow then. I'll meet you in front of the station.
I get it. She can't use a vibrator here.
Both of you should go.
The nurse thought it all out, I guess.
She's here --
Why are you in a school swimsuit?
Ah, no, it looks fine on you.
It really does!
Come on, let's go swim.
Ah, right...
We have to stretch first, right?
Hey, shouldn't we go now?
On that?
That was rough...
Huh? You want go again?
Hey, I'll leave you behind!
Hey, you'll fall if you run.
See? I told you...
Thank you.
So Fujino likes shaved ice...
This feels great...
Right?
What's wrong? You're face is flushed...
No way!
Amphibious
Vibrator
Adams
Fujino!
Fujino?
Now what are you doing?
F-Fujino!
R-Right here?!
Here of all places...
Damn.
Wha - ! What's wrong, Fujino!?
Are you feeling ill? Snap out of it! Hey!
Excuse us!
Damn I'm sweating!
Why did you have to go and do that?
I'm still turned on from back there. Coming!
Am I really on the same level as the vibrator?
Are you saying...
I'm not good enough!?
Fujino!
Hey...
You like vibrators, right?
Then...
Between me and the vibrator...
Which do you prefer?
Vibrator
Me
You can't decide?
Ah! I'm finished! I'm finished!
That's it for me!
That's right...
It's fine, don't worry about it...
I'm worth just as much as that vibrator anyway...
Fujino!
Then you mean...!
You like me better?
Fujino...?
I'll give you a good time, even without the vibrator.
How's that?
You're already drenched.
I'll have you feeling even better.
You came...
How about together this time?
I'm much better than the vibrator, right?
You feel the best, Fukaya.
F-Fujino?
I swear I heard her say that!
Fujino!
Fujino's feeling this, just from me!
I'm coming!
Fujino!
What!?
Y -
You bought a new one?
Are you messing with me!?
I'm taking this!
End of discussion!
Shion Fujino...
It looks fun, Fukaya...