R-Remarriage?!
I won't let you be lonely anymore.
From now on, the three of us
shall live as a happy family.
Well, I'm glad to know that you're alright.
And so, I searched around, all just for you.
Ahh!
Here.
She's is my wife,
and someone who can become
a mother for you that I found.
Was that the reason you're gone for four years?
I'm sorry for selfishly making all these decisions. But...
It's alright.
If you chose her yourself,
I won't have any objections.
Jeez... I'm lucky to have a very understanding son!
Cut it out, dad!
His name is Mao-kun, right?
Pleased to meet you. I am Arima Shiori.
From now on, I'll live together
with you as your new mother.
Please take care of me, Mao-kun?
Wait, Shiori-san!
Why are you stepping back?
Err... It's...
I've been looking forward to meet you.
Shiori, Wai—
N-No, it's just that I'm...
Come here. I'm just as nervous as you are.
Nooo!
Mao-kun!
Oh! Good morning, Mao-kun!
G-Good morning.
Hajime-san already went to work.
Yeah... Thanks for the meal.
Is it not up to your liking?
No, quite the opposite!
Hmm, delicious!
I'm glad! From today onwards,
Mama will cook lots for you, okay?
Wah... wait...
He's gynophobic?
Yeah...
Especially when meeting an opposite
gender face-to-face like now.
Since he lost his mother, he's been holding back his own emotions.
His love for his mother and longing for maternal love,
he tried to restrain both of those in him.
What a pity.
He needs someone who can
provide that affection to him.
Can you let me take care of him?
But we can't know for sure, he might suddenly
freak out with all those repressed emotions.
I think it's a little risky.
I decided to give Mao-kun, your son,
all the love he needs from now on.
I have as much resolve as that.
As expected of my wife!
Shiori-san?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ah, oh yeah. Are you free today?
I'd like you to show me around the town.
Hmm, okay.
I'm glad. I'm gonna do some preparations now.
Hello, Kinosaki-san!
Ah... hello, Kurokawa-san.
Jeez...
You can call me like you used to
when it's just the two of us.
But you are already someone's wife.
Of course I am.
Thanks for waiting, Mao-kun.
Oh, who is she?
S-She was my younger schoolmate
back from high school.
She's currently living next door
together with his husband.
May I ask about your relationship with senpai... Kinosaki-san.
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself. I'm his mother.
What a surprise!
I thought he got an older girlfriend!
Wait, Shiori-san! You're way too close!
Eh, what if mama gets lost?
Oh yeah, I still haven't told you about
the apartment's common bath.
Bath?
How splendid! We can all take a bath together here!
Nah, you should take one together with dad.
Oh, what are you saying...
We're already family!
Yes... Yes, okay. I understand.
Mao-kun, your dad said he's gonna be home late.
Dad sure is having a hard time.
So it's only the two of us together in the bath!
Hmm... okay...
Wah... Ehh?!
I was thinking of washing your back.
I-I can do it myself!
Are you still not used to having me as a mother?
I want to do anything I can for you.
Y-yeah, but it's my predisposition.
Okay, next is the front.
Face me over here.
F-Front?!
Anything but that!
C-Coming!
Forgive me, Shiori-san!
It's okay, Mao-kun.
I'll make you get used to it little by little.
Okay?
I'll give you all the affection that you
should have gotten from your real mother.
Hey, Mao-kun.
Sleep together with mama tonight.
No way! That's absolutely too much!
Hajime-san won't be home tonight so I feel lonely. Please.
You were so against it,
but you're sleeping with me in the end.
Mao-kun, you're so kind! I love you!
I knew it...
I'm lactating again.
Maybe it's because my ovulating day is close.
I'm home!
Shiori-san... Eh?!
Oh! Welcome home, Mao-kun!
I-I'm sorry!
A-Are you by any chance pregnant?
Oh, that's not it.
This is just my body's predisposition.
Predisposition?
Want to see them closer? Come here.
But, that would be...
No buts! Jeez!
I'm not letting you go.
Here, take a look.
I want you to burn everything about
your new mother into your memory.
Can you clean mama's tits using your mouth?
Isn't it natural for a mother to breastfeed her son?
Damn... Don't blame me if anything happens!
Tastes good...
Mao-kun, you're doing good.
He's drinking my milk.
M-Mom!
I'm happy. You finally called me mom.
My... Oh my...
Let mama take care of your dick, okay?
Don't hold back.
Whenever you're suffering, mama will comfort you.
How cute!
Your dick is so energetic, it's sliding in my hands.
Sorry!
It's alright. Just keep on gently licking it to make the pain go away.
Just go on like that.
Just keep on drinking a lot.
Mao-kun, you're coming soon, aren't you?
I-I'm coming, mom!
It's alright. Show mama how you come.
Come while your dick is twitching.
Shoot out your white pee!
Shoot your white milk out as much as you can.
Whenever your dick feels suffering,
mama will help you relieve the pain.
Thanks... mom...
Mao-kun, how's this?
F-Feels very good...
Mom...
Coming!
Mao-kun... Do you love mama?
I love you. More than anyone else.
I'm coming, mom!
I'm... coming!
If you come this much, mama
won't be able to drink it all.
I'm sorry, mom. Are you okay?
You had an amazing ejaculation that it startled me.
Mom...
Damn it, man up and don't cry on me!
It will be fine if I go, right?
Did something happen?
There's some trouble in the company.
I'll need to go on a business trip.
Oh my...
I most likely would be away for around a month.
A whole month?
I'm sorry but I'll have to leave
Mao in your care, Shiori.
Okay.
N-no, Mao-kun. Not in the middle of the day. Stop!
No... not there. You can't down there!
It's hitting me!
Don't rub your raw dick on mama's pussy!
Mama is gonna start feeling weird.
What kind of feeling is that?
No! If I say it...
You're gonna get angry at mama!
Tell me, mom!
I won't be able to hold back.
I'm gonna end up telling everything!
No! You're a bad child!
Your dick is amazing!
I can't take anymore!
My affection for Mao-kun
keeps growing day by day.
Mao-kun see me not as a mother,
but as a woman instead.
Which of the two does he need for me to be?
Whether as a mother or as a woman,
I just need to accept his feelings for me.
Good... You're doing great.
It's getting more and more drenched.
It's because you're very good on it.
Mom... Is my tongue making you feel good?
Yes, it fees so good that I'm having spasms!
Ah, oh no!
You're already this hard.
Forgive me, my dear.
I ended up loving this child
as much as I love you.
You'll be inside me for today.
I finally became one with mama.
I'm happy to become one with you as well.
You're so hard! Your dick is so hard!
I love you. Mama loves Mao-kun so much!
Me too, mom!
I never knew that sex feels this good!
I'll end up loving you more!
You can't! Someday you'll have to get over me.
N-No way!
I want to do this with you all the time.
Oh, don't be a spoiled kid.
I just hit something deep inside.
That's where a child is conceived
when semen is deposited inside.
Me, with mom...
It's a place where dicks shouldn't normally poke on.
But today is a special exception.
Mom, I'm already!
It's okay, come whenever you feel so!
Amazing! Your dick is trembling inside!
More! I want to do this more with mama!
Okay!
That's good! Good!
After that, I kept making love
with Mao-kun for the whole night.
Hey, Mao-kun. Want to try making one with mama?
W-What?
Making a child.
That means...
What I mean is, having raw sex.
Mama will show you how much
good it feels when she gives her all.
How is it? Does it feel good inside mama?
It's amazing.
I never knew raw sex feels this good!
Mama feels so good too!
Having your dick directly touch my pussy feels good.
Good! Doing it raw feels so good!
It feels so good that it's messing me up!
It's the first time I had sex like this!
I'm hitting mom's deepest parts inside!
If you come in there, I'll get pregnant.
It would be Mao-kun and mama's baby!
Mama is becoming a woman!
I'm becoming Mao-kun's woman!
Okay, mom! Be mine!
I'm sorry, my dear.
I ended up loving your son too much!
I'll bear Mao-kun's baby!
Mama's gonna come as well.
Coming... I'm coming!
No, this isn't good!
If I feel this good, I'll fall in love with you even more!
Coming... Coming... I'm coming!
I'm coming from Mao-kun's raw dick!
Mama...
I'm gonna come!
Mao-kun...
Mom...
Shiori!
Sorry, I just...
It's alright, darling.
I'll be your wife just for today.
Okay?
Pour your white milk inside mama... inside Shiori, okay?
I'm putting it in, Shiori.
I love you, dear!
Hit me more deep inside!
There!
I'm making a child with you!
I always waited for this moment.
Shiori... Shiori!
Darling... Darling... Darling!
Do it more! Deeper!
I love you!
I love you, dear!
That's why I want to have your baby!
I want to have our own child!
Mom!
I love you... I love you...
I love you so much!
It's going... deep inside!
Amazing! Your dick feels great, dear!
Do it more!
Please plant your baby seeds in my womb!
Mom, is it really okay?
Call me Shiori!
Hurry up and do it!
I want us to come together, so...
I'm coming, Shiori!
I'll pour everything inside your womb!
Shiori, you're gonna conceive my child!
Our own child!
Oh no!
This is amazing!
I can't take anymore!
Coming... I'm coming!
Yes! I will... I'll get pregnant!
I'll have your child!
I think I'll get pregnant.
You look beautiful, mom.
Listen, Mao-kun.
There is something I need to tell you.
To me?
Mama has a baby in her belly.
Eh?! Is that mine?
Well, I wonder if it is.
Congratulations, mom.
Words alone aren't enough.
Praise me by your actions.
Kissing me before papa on our
wedding. What a troublesome son.
It's because I love you as much as dad does.
Mama loves you so much.
I love you...
More than anyone else.
I'll be going now.
Have a safe trip, Hajime-san.
You're such a spoiled child.
I can't hold myself back anymore.
It's fine, right? Shiori...
Okay, okay.
From now on, Mao-kun is mama's husband, okay?
I love you.
Darling...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization