Professor, why do I have to come to school
on a sunday?
Ms. Nakamura, your grades are the worst out of
all my students.
Today is a Sunday, but it's a one day special lesson.
Please...
If not, you won't graduate. Is that okay?
Umm...
We have a high percentage of passing students,
but you are hurting our school reputation.
If you say so.
Okay, anyways, hang in there for today
and finish this.
What? This much?
You don't have time to delay.
So stop whining and work.
I'll come back by the time you're finished,
so don't be lazy.
No, I can't possibly do this.
But if I don't I won't graduate.
Oh well. Umm...
Math. My worst subject.
Umm, square plus two, times five... Umm...
I don't know!
I don't understand at all. I'm not good at this.
Man, I flew right over here
since Mr. Sorimachi called me in.
This sure brought my hopes down.
Instead of this special lesson, I want something
more... ...exciting...
Nakamura...
Nakamura!
Huh?
Mr. Sorimachi.
No, I've been sleeping without realizing.
Nakamura, what are you doing?
I'm sorry, professor.
I'll stay awake and do my work.
Work? What are you saying, Nakamura?
That is not what you're supposed to do.
Huh?
The 1st hour - Masturbation.
Nakamura, don't you get why you're in here
alone on a Sunday?
Professor Sorimachi.
Nakamura, show me your stuff.
But, professor.
I can't do such...
Nakamura, it's just like what you do.
You think I don't know your dirty thoughts?
Professor, oh my...
You like me, don't you?
Professor. Professor Sorimachi...
Now spread your legs.
Nakamura spread your legs.
Professor Sorimachi.
Yes, yes. Good, Nakamura.
I'm excited to see it.
N-No, please, professor.
Pink panties...
Please don't look, professor.
What are you saying?
If I don't look, who's going to look?
Now, touch the inside of your panties with your
fingers.
I, I can't...
If you don't hurry, you're going to fail your first
lesson.
Good, masturbate like you always do.
I... I don't do that.
Don't lie.
See, your fingers are reaching for the g-spot.
Good, good! Before first period is over, cum as
hard as you ever have, okay?
Oh my, professor. I don't know what to do.
What are you saying, Nakamura?
Just think of me and stroke you sensitive parts.
Think of you?
Yea, like you always do.
How you want me to see your private parts.
I don't...
Now stick your hand in your panties.
No, please...
No, it's so messy.
Good, in your cute hole, there, stick your finger in.
Good. Faster, do it faster.
No, please...
The chime will ring if you're slow.
Nakamura, if you act so lethargic,
I can't give you the units.
Now, masturbate in a way I would like it.
Nice butt, Nakamura.
Even if you change the angle, that won't get
your units.
Professor, forgive me! Please forgive me!
Nakamura, what are you saying?
It's for your own good.
Even if I forgive, the units won't spare you.
Professor, it's already... Professor.
Nakamura, you have ten minutes left.
If you don't cum in ten minutes, you won't graduate.
So take off the panties.
Good, yea, the other one too.
Good. Splendid, Nakamura. It's twitching.
It's so wet, you dirty girl.
N-No...
Look, it's itching for something to be inserted.
What does it want, Nakamura?
No, please...
Say it clearly, what does it want?
Professor's...
What?
Nakamura, what are you saying?
The first period is masturbation, isn't it?
How mean.
But instead, I'll let you borrow something good.
Huh? What's this?
The secret machine which ten out of ten girls
have used to cum before.
No, it's moving.
M-Moving so nasty.
Don't you want that in?
This will wiggle in your pussy. Huh?
Don't you want it? Say that you want it.
Good, that's the way, Nakamura.
There, feel your horniness.
Concentrate harder on spreading your legs in
front of me and masturbating with the fat vibrator.
Professor, don't say that.
It's moving more!
There, it's wetter and nastier than before.
Thrust it faster Nakamura, you only have two
minutes left.
Come on, you won't get your units if you don't
cum, Nakamura.
Faster, Nakamura. Thrust it like you're killing it.
Professor.
One more minute.
Put more effort, or else you won't make it.
No, professor, no...
Come on, thrust more! Thrust, thrust, and keep
on thrusting.
There, thrust! Thrust until you lose yourself,
Nakamura.
You pervert.
This is a classroom.
Nakamura, what do you think will happen when
everyone finds out about you masturbating in
the classroom?
You pervert!
Say that you're a horny girl masturbating in the
classroom.
There, say it, Nakamura!
I am a horny girl masturbating in the classroom.
You broke the vibe.
Very well, good job, Nakamura,
you passed the first lesson.
Yes.
Okay Ms. Nakamura, the second period is
"lesbianism".
My lessons won't be as easy as Professor
Nakamura's.
I think you get it, but I won't forgive.
Looks like you already warmed up
from the last lesson.
On the remote rotor is a special adhesive that
will move all over your body.
Thanks to Professor Sorimachi, it should be
very sensitive, so I'm very excited.
See, it's moving around.
How do you like it?
Your tits are sensitive?
I guess it's okay.
I guess down there is better.
Understand Ms. Nakamura, the second period
is not about you cumming.
You have to make me cum too.
Understood?
Yes.
Oh, do you really get it?
I have to bully cut girls, or else I won't feel it.
N-Not there...
This rotor has a turbo button. When I push this,
the micro motor spins at 6,000 rpm.
N-No!
You're cumming with tremendous force.
I will vibrate your deep part.
Now it's a little interesting.
Next is the bigger one.
Can you handle 8,000 rpm?
Of course if you can't, you won't get your units.
Switch on!
It feels so good, Ms. Nakamura.
Like you're losing yourself.
No, no, I'm, I'm going crazy!
I only stuck in the front end.
You'll feel the rotor from before.
The vibrators with 6,000 rpm and 8,000 rpm.
There, it's going in. Going, going...
Look at this monster going in and out of this
cute girl.
No, pull it out, please, pull it out!
Wow, wow!
This girl's really feeling it.
She feels it.
She's feeling the vibrators.
Wow, wow, feel it, yes, more!
Wow, Ms. Nakamura, I, I can't...
I can't anymore.
Lick it.
Stick your tongue in.
Yes!
Ms. Nakamura, you passed.
Second period is over.
Thank you very much.
Third period is this.
Look Nakamura, if you pass this, you'll graduate
at a high grade point average.
Hang in there.
How is it, Nakamura, this is my thing.
It's not fake. It's real cock.
The cock that you've been always thinking of.
I haven't...
Really?
I can see clearly
that you're pussy's been hungry.
Oh my...
Now, say that you want to suck it.
Look! It'll become bigger.
It's already big, but now it's growing even more.
Now, don't you want this?
W-Wow...
This is the theme of third period.
You can stroke or lick, but if I cum, you fail.
How is it Nakamura?
It's what you've always wanted,
but you won't pass if you're overenthusiastic.
No, give me!
Good, good.
It tastes good!
Hey, don't do it too fast, Nakamura...
Wow! Wow, professor!
Man, can't you do it right? I'm really going to cum.
How's this?
You're so drenching wet.
Hmm, I can feel more...
Mmm, professor. Tastes so good.
Good, good...
I don't think so...
Take it easy...
Good...
No...
I can't bare it anymore.
I'm cumming.
Saved by the bell.
Now it's fourth period.
During third period, you did quite well,
but this is the final test.
This!
Bondage? Professor, I can't do that.
I can't deal with pain.
No?
Nakamura, what do you mean "no",
it's your lesson?
I need to challenge your progress.
First, we'll start with the hot stuff.
No!
It's hot, hot!
Whine, whine!
Is it so hot that you can't stand it?
Hot... Stop it...
Look at you.
Whining and crying.
There, you want this?
I'll stick this fat and hot thing in.
Nakamura, you're cumming enough to put out
the candle.
N-No... No...
You have to clean your body of the candle wax.
Professor, not that...
Take this!
How is it, Nakamura? Good? Is this good?
Huh? How is it?
Professor, hurry, I want the real thing, professor!
I want professor's shaft in me.
Please! Hurry!
I guess my training was successful.
Then I shall stick in my fat dick?
This time you'll pass if you can finish me by the
time the bell rings. Okay?
There, this is the fucking by your teacher which
you've been dreaming of.
Professor...
Say that you want, Professor Sorimachi's fat prick!
Professor's fat...
Please put your fat prick in my pussy!
You want it so bad.
You seem not to care about anything else.
Then I shall stick it in!
Damn, she's been played with all this time,
but this tightness.
That's being young.
Professor Sorimachi's prick is in me... Big...
Wow, I never felt this tightness
and wetness before.
This girl can't study for shit,
but damn, this pussy!
Professor's pumping in and out of me!
He's pumping in and out of me...
Oh wow, it's getting tighter.
Professor, more, more, fuck me harder!
More, more fuck! More!
Damn, there's the doggy...
More, more!
Shit, there's twenty minutes left.
I can't handle this.
More! Fuck harder! More, more!
So I'll lose myself!
Really, Nakamura?
You won't mind losing yourself?
You'll lose it.
Professor?
What? What? No!
It's going to rip, it's ripping, no-!
I'm dying, dying!
Nakamura! Hey Nakamura, Nakamura!
Uhh, Professor Sorimachi.
Nakamura, what the hell are you doing?
Uhh, yes. It was all a dream.
I'll be good now. I'll do the worksheet.
Worksheet?
What are you saying Nakamura?
That is not what you're supposed to do.
This is your first lesson... "Masturbation."