It was the final week of a blazing hot August.
My fashion designer mother, Sayoko Kagami...
...received a job offering from a television director, Mantoku-san.
That job was an invitation for our semi-celebrity family,
to participate in a television show which explores hidden hot springs.
We headed off to a local village in some mountainous recess to get filmed.
It had been a long time since we've all had a family vacation.
We were all looking forward to relaxing ourselves at a hot spring with beautiful rivers.
Wow!
Guys, come on!
Haruka, slow down!
Jeez, she's always so hyperactive.
Be careful and don't trip over.
It was supposed to be a joyous, enjoyable family vacation...
We could never have expected what was to come...
The obscene trap that lay before us.
Translation: EROBEAT
Encode: SimpleX
Murky Village
Part 1
I'll be looking forward to working with you, Kasukabe-kun.
No, the pleasure is mine.
But I feel kind of bad.
You're taking care of us even though it's not mentioned in the contract.
Don't say that.
It's my pleasure to have your family, which is filled with beauties, participate in our show.
So, don't worry about it.
You've got such a sweet mouth.
But, are you sure we're suited for this?
Shouldn't you find someone who's more famous to increase the ratings?
No, no.
From my point of view, you're all more than enough.
Really?
There's you, the winner of a world famous fashion exhibition.
You're probably the leading fashion designer in Japan right now.
There's Fubuki-chan, who's not only a model,
but also a fashion designer trained under you with her own brand.
Then there's Haruka-chan, a gravure idol who still participates in her studies.
Her popularity has been rising quickly and she's been on the cover shot of multiple magazines.
Finally, there's Miyu-chan, the Miss Campus winner.
She's been invited to join the acting world because of her beauty.
Mom and I told her to become a model.
But...
Onee-chan, don't talk about that!
I really don't like being the center of attention.
To be honest, I'm the one feeling sorry,
for bringing a celebrity family like yours to a rural village.
So don't hesitate to speak out if you have any requests.
Thank you in advance.
We'll definitely do so if we need anything.
There isn't much here,
but there's a beautiful view and a lot of time to kill.
The camera crew is nearly ready,
so I'd say we should start filming soon.
All right, let's go.
Good work.
I guess this concludes all the filming for today.
Please feel free to use the time left however you wish.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
All right, please excuse me then.
There's still some time left until dinner,
so what do you girls want to do?
I want to go check out the shrine.
Again?
Yeah, I didn't have time to fully take a look when we were filming.
But, aren't we going there anyway when that festival thing is supposed to take place?
Oh, you mean the Hunting Festival.
But I'm sure there will be a lot of people then.
So I think I should go now.
You really do love legends and what not, don't you?
All right, go on ahead.
I wonder what sort of festival the Hunting Festival is?
I've never heard about it in detail before.
The Kagami family are, all beyond top quality.
Someone's talking about us?
Thanks a lot.
But I wonder if the villagers can wait that long?
They're all dying from waiting.
That's only natural when such beautiful prey is sprawling in front of you.
We need to do something about this...
Why don't we just throw one of them in to feed the masses first?
What's going on?
What does he mean, feed?
You're right.
I'll leave that to you.
Do whatever you need to.
All right.
What's going on?
What's going to happen?
I need to let everyone know...
Kasukabe-san?
Something's not right... Something fishy is going on.
Miyu-chan, you just lucked out.
Mr. Headman! Mr. Priest!
Oh. Kasukabe-kun.
And look who we have here.
Kasukabe-san, why!?
Great timing.
Let's use this girl to feed the villagers.
Nice to meet you, Miyu-san.
I'm the head of this village, Hatake Senzou.
Head of this village?
I have a request for you.
What is it?
I want you to become the Shishigami.
Shishigami?
Correct.
The Hunting Festival is where the villagers chase down the person who's the Shishigami...
...and then devour her until the very end.
I want to you become that person.
Me?
By the way, are you a virgin?
I don't know...
Wait, why are you asking me?
She's as pure as one could get.
What are you scheming?
What do you plan to do to my family?
My, my, she's quite slow in the head.
What I'm saying, is that your family has become live sacrifices for the Hunting Festival.
Well, we're not really going to "eat" you up.
But I guess, you could say we're "preying" in a sense.
Don't tell me, that this entire filming thing is a trap?
Yeah, it took us quite some time to plan this out.
No way...
So? If you promise to become the Shishigami, we won't go after your family.
If you refuse, everyone in your family will become live sacrifices.
A good trade-off, isn't it?
In other words, you're saying I don't have a choice either way, right?
Good understanding.
Correct.
If you agree, you will be the only one.
But if you refuse, you and your entire family will get involved.
Fine... I'll do it, but let everyone else go.
You're a smart girl.
Let's begin the test right away.
Test?
Didn't we say already?
The Shishigami must get "eaten" by everyone else.
Well, I guess actually trying her out would be the quickest.
Let go! No! Stop!
Please let go of me!
No! Don't!
What are you doing?
S-Stop!
Stop this!
Let's check out what's under here...
Please stop!
Stop! Let go of me!
Stop!
Don't! Let go!
Oh, so you were lying?
All right, then.
We'll have your family take your place then.
Don't touch my family...
You know what to do then?
Don't look there...
Please...
No!!
I'm so embarrassed that I feel like I'm going to die...
No one's going to die from embarrassment.
No!
Anyway, that's a beautiful vagina.
Don't... Don't look!
What do you say? Shall we do it now?
Right, right.
Let's see then... Why don't I just jam it in?
It hurts! It hurts!
It's too early for you to lose consciousness.
The real thing begins now.
My butt.
It hurts!
It hurts...
It hurts... No...
It's my first time and they took away my anal virginity as well...
How cruel...
What do you think about your first experience with a penis?
No... No...
What feels better,
the back side or the front side?
I don't know...
At this rate, I'm going to go crazy...
Please... Take it out...
Sure, but first I've gotta cum inside.
No, not that!
I'm going to cum soon.
No, please! Take it out!
Please!
No!
Not inside!
I don't want to get pregnant!
This is disgusting...
I'm going to get pregnant.
Feeling so good that you can't even talk?
Now then...
You're going to keep going?
What are you talking about?
That wasn't all, you know.
I'm going to... I'm going to...
I'm going to break...
I hope you understand that if you don't do it, other people will.
Not that... Not that!
I can't let that happen, no matter what!
Let's go a little harder then, shall we?
Mr. Priest, your anal fetish is still as great as ever.
That's nothing compared to your virgin fetish.
Take it out...
My butt... My butt is going to break!
The human body is quite sturdy, you know.
So don't worry.
See?
I'm getting penetrated from front to back...
I'm going to break!
Hurry up and let this end!
I'm going to cum inside your asshole now
And I will fill you up from the front.
No! I'm going to break.
I'm going to break...
Stop...
Cum outside of me please...
That's no good.
It's a Shishigami's duty to receive sperm inside of her.
Stop...
It's so hot!
Damn, that felt good.
I think you should be able to handle the job.
That's right.
That means, the test...
Yeah, that means, you've passed the first test.
First test!?
Everyone in the village participates in the Hunting Festival.
Do you think it'd end after two people?
Don't tell me...
Correct.
Come here for the second round of testing tonight.
If you run away, you know what happens then, right?
Yes...
Let me have another shot before you leave.
Stop please...
I'm already... Please...
Stop! Stop!
Miyu-chan, what happened to you?
Miyu-nee, you're slow!
What's the matter? Did something happen?
Sorry... I kinda lost track of time.
You don't look well
Are you really all right?
I'm fine, I'm fine, just a little tired.
anyway, let's eat.
Jeez, Miyu-nee...
She seemed to be forcing her smile.
Where's she going this late at night?
Come on, take this in your mouth!
Now, your butt's next...
It's going to rip! Stop!
It hurts! It hurts!
Your mouth's too annoying.
Come on, drink it all up.
I'm cumming as well.
No!
It's so hot...
My butt's going to break open!
Miyu-chan!
Let go of her!
Miyu-chan! Miyu-chan!
Mother, what are you doing!?
Cut this out at once!
She asked for it herself.
Stop lying!
Look at her yourself, she's moving her own hips.
Stop... Don't look at me, mother!
Stop! Cut it out!
Let go of Miyu-chan at once!
I'm afraid we can't.
This is a sacred ceremony.
We can't just stop midway.
You bastards.
Well, if you want this to stop do you want to take her place?
Mother, no!
Miyu-chan...
It's fine if you can't.
All right, continue the ceremony.
No, not inside...
Stop...
I'll take her place.
Mother, no!
I'll take you on first, Sayoko-san.
Where have I seen you before?
Have you forgotten me?
I'm Terou.
Sakuma Terou, that is.
Sakuma... Terou? Don't tell me...
You were the one who worked for my husband...
He raped me and was then chased away by my husband...
Why is he here?
Are you surprised?
By the way, Mantoku is my son.
That's right.
Thanks to your husband, we suffered a lot.
Well, I don't like talking about the past.
Take off your clothes.
Mother, stop!
Don't mind me!
I'm coming to save you now.
Just wait a little longer.
Is this all right?
Well, come over and insert it yourself to show your sincerity.
Mother, no!
Don't do that...
Miyu-chan...
I'm just going to shut her up for a little while so that you won't get distracted.
At least take her elsewhere...
I can't do that.
We still don't know if you're a suitable enough replacement.
I have no choice.
Honey please forgive me.
Miyu-chan, don't look...
Once again I'm... This is disgusting.
Having sex in front of your daughter feels kind of different, right?
No... Don't say that...
No... Please...
Miyu-chan, don't look!
Look at yourself.
You're moving your hips as if you were fucking your husband.
That's cruel...
Great, just like that.
I'll tell you something nice since you've become so obedient.
Do you know how your husband died?
Don't talk about him... Don't talk about that accident...
Do you really think it was an accident?
A real incident?
Thanks to that bastard, my wife left me and I lost everything I had.
That was my revenge.
You still don't get it?
I killed him and disguised it as an "accident."
No! No!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Mistress...
Stop! No!
No! Let go of me! Stop!
Stop! No! Stop now!
Let go of me!
Didn't you want to take Miyu-chan's place?
Miyu-chan... Miyu-chan...
All right, I guess I should join in as well
W-What?
You're still a virgin here, aren't you?
I feel honored to take away a widow's anal virginity.
Ow! It's going to rip apart!
It's going to rip into two!
This isn't going to work... Take it out!
This is amazing...
I can feel Mantoku's movement through your walls.
I totally believe that you're a virgin.
It's so darn tight.
Stop... It hurts...
Stop moving...
Honey... I'm being raped by the person who killed you...
No! Stop!
Takayaki-san! Takayaki-san!
Stop!
You've got such a weird fetish, calling out your dead husband's name despite all of this.
I'm going to cum...
I'll cum inside your ass.
No! Don't!
No!!
It's finally over.
Miyu?
Miyu-chan! Miyu-chan!
Why? I thought we promised!
Let go of Miyu-chan!
Oh, I'm sorry.
It seems like the villagers love Miyu-chan so much that they don't want to let her go.
How about you both become Shishigami?
You've got our consent.
Stop it!
Let go of Miyu-chan!
S-Stop it!
Stop it!
Did you really think you could sub in for her?
W-What do you mean?
From the very beginning, I planned to have your entire family become Shishigami.
From the moment you entered this village, your destinies were sealed.
Noway... Then Miyu...
You don't mean...
Fubuki, and Haruka as well?
Right, we'll enjoy them later as well.
No! No! Stop it!
Let go! Let go!
No! Stop!
No! No!!