Under the request of show director, Kasukahe-san,
my entire family has agreed to cooperate
with the holding of a certain remote village's traditional event.
It's been a while since we got together.
It seemed as if we were on a trip, and I was excited about it.
But the malicious hands of the village soon revealed themselves.
What seemed like a simple promotional video for the village,
cost me my virginity,
and its hands even reached my sister, Fubuki.
Right now, all I can do is pray,
for my Mom and Haruka's safety.
The thought that they might expose the video
that they took when they raped us,
gave me no choice but to comply with
all the villagers' dirty requests.
As you can see,
this is how they assisted us in the promotion video.
What is this?
No, I don't want this!
This... what is the meaning this?
Let me see them right now!
I'm fine with that,
but it's not like we can stop filming at this point.
The village event needs this.
Give me a break!
This, this is...
This is no village event!
We can stop if you insist,
but would you be willing to listen to our conditions?
The white-stained village
The dolls shall dance - Chapter
Over here, please.
Mom...
Haruka...
Hurry...
And end this...
Are you worried about them?
No need to worry then.
They're probably on their way here.
Are Mom and Haruka all right?
What in the world do you mean?
You'll know soon enough.
Soon enough.
What are you going to do with Mom and Haruka?
Stop messing with...
Well then, I want you to wear these.
W-What are you going to make us do?
As I explained the other day,
the village is about to hold the Shishioi festival.
Every year, they appoint someone as the "wild boar" god,
and then the villagers chase the "wild
boar” god around the village,
"eating" it in the end.
So what about it?
We're actually thinking of holding the festival right now.
Festival?
Miu and Fubuki were part of the preliminary video shoot.
So now that we're about get to the real thing...
You're saying that we become the "wild boar" gods, right?
Correct. I'm glad you understand things quickly.
As expected of the mother's celebrity status.
I get it then.
I shall become the "Wild boar".
But exempt Haruka from this!
Mom, wait!
I want to meet Miu-nee and Yuki-nee.
So, I'll become a "wild boar" as well.
Haruka-chan...
So it will be you two then?
Okay, now please change,
since we're in the middle of another video shoot.
Miu...
Yuki-nee...
Now then,
let the Shishioi festival... begin!
Do your best!
What?
What was that?
Haruka-chan!
Run!
Let's run towards those two!
Mom!
Haruka, head to the temple.
What about you?
Listen.
No matter what happens, just keep moving
toward Miu and Fubuki, okay?
No, I don't want to!
I want to be with you, Mom!
I'll be fine.
So don't worry.
Mom...
Now, hurry to them!
Mom, you hurry on too, okay?
I'll protect everyone.
Where's the wild boar?
Let me go in your pussy already!
Hey, she's here!
The mother is here!
Run, run!
If you don't hurry,
you're fucked!
I wanna do it already.
Come on, mommy.
No!
Stop, let me go!
No...
It feels gross.
This is really great.
P-Please stop, it's dirty.
Stay still.
No, stop, please...!
Can't be helped.
We'll just have to let Hakudaku-san go first.
No way...
Another man's dick is inside me...
No!
I'll be using these huge tits too.
Please stop this lewd act...
At the very least...
What? Didn't your hubby ever do a tit fuck with you?
Stop talking about that man...
Then I'll just experience it for him!
Please let me go.
I beg of you...
Finish that already.
I want to get a taste of a widow's tits!
This can't be...
I'll have to take on all of them?
Don't make me hurry,
I'll give them to you later, anyway.
After I rub them till they rip off!
Don't be too rough.
We'll make sure to make you cum on both ends.
Please stop saying lewd things.
I see, you already did it countless times with your hubby,
with this very loose hole of yours.
No, that person is...
Save me, save me!
I'm about to cum.
Make sure you get all wet, inside and outside.
Here, here!
This is too rough...
Y-Your thing is starting to...
No, don't cum!
Don't cum inside!
No...
My dear... forgive me...
Now it's finally our turn.
We'll check for ourselves if it's really loose.
Stop, already...
L-Let me be...
This pussy,
it's wrapping around my dick quite nicely.
Your deceased husband sure was all over this.
All over...?
If you have the time to talk, then just suck on this.
Inside my mouth, too?
No, I don't want this...
Damn, can't get enough of this.
Oh well,
I'll just have to take your husband's place and..!
I can't breathe.
Finish this already.
It's getting even tighter.
Oh crap, I'm about to cum!
I'm going to cum inside your pussy, so get pregnant, okay?
For them to cum inside me like this...
Haruka, Miu, Fubuki...
Helter Skelter
The White-Stained Village
Why did this have to happen?
Miu-nee,
Yuki-nee,
Mom!
Just a little more.
Alright...
Found you.
Just give up.
No, don't touch me!
No can do.
You can't resist now, there's still a lot more in store for you.
No!
First, service us.
We're willing to end this, if you do it quickly.
What? What should I do?
Satisfy our dicks using your hands and mouth.
Anything but that!
If you don't do it now,
then we'll just have to fuck you.
T-That's...
Just do it already!
Use your tongue too,
make sure it rubs the underside well.
Don't let your hands rest now,
you still need to service us.
Are gravure idols nowadays this bad with their blowjobs?
Her body sure is beautiful, though.
No good.
Let's just fuck her already.
Okay then, I'll go first.
Hey you...!
It hurts!
So she really was a virgin.
I just took a gravure idol's virginity!
Please, please don't be so rough...
I beg of you, stop!
Stop this already!
No talking, just suck it!
You're an idol, right?
You should be grateful,
because we're about to make your pussy a lot more useful.
I think we can even use it earlier if we do it faster.
Here, I'm about to cum inside an idol's pussy!
No, no!
This idol's handjob is just...!
They poured their cum inside...
Miu, Fubuki, Haruka!
Oh, so you're still in this place.
I sure am lucky.
No, please leave me alone.
Stop this, please!
Okay... but only after the festival.
Somebody save me!
It seems they didn't use you well enough.
This is really something.
I have to hurry to Miu-chan and the others.
Finish it already.
Just hurry...
I want to meet up with everyone.
It hurts...
Miu-nee, Yuki-nee.
Good for you to come.
I really wanted to have your virginity,
but I guess I'll just have my way with you in order to make up for it.
No!
Let's have a taste of the idol's recently fucked pussy.
No, pushing it in deep like that...
I guess it's still pretty tight.
Damn, I really should have been the first one to take your virginity!
I'll start to feel weird if you keep on doing that.
This idol,
hey, play with us more.
No, I can t do this any further...
You're already this wet, what are you saying?
That's not it...
I don't want this anymore.
Don't, please, any more and I'll...
Why don't you move your hips too?
That is, if you don't want your mind to break.
Please don't push it too hard inside me.
Oh, feeling horny while being fucked in your ass?
My asshole is getting opened up.
I'm going to break...
Here, I'm going to pour it all inside you.
No, I don't want it, I don't want it!
Don't...
The festival is about to end soon,
so just hold on until then.
Haruka, Mom...
Haruka, Mom!
Miu-nee,
Haruka,
Fubuki-chan,
Mom...
Thanks to you four, we were able to take some great videos today.
Asking Sayoko-san was really a good call.
Let's wrap things up for tonight.
No!
Well, our Shishioi festival sure was lively this year.
Indeed, we filmed every juicy detail.
Now, let's see who was "eaten" the most?
Don't look...
Okay, the festival is now over.
Everybody, let's eat.
Let me go already...
It's too intense...
You were all a big help.
Now, I think our village is about to get more popular.
I want you all to serve the village from now on.
Oh, seems your job has already started.
Now look at that.
Your celebrity status sure worked very well...
On men, of course.
Since this is such a great opportunity,
we want you to serve them well.
Our beloved "wild boar" gods.
I mean, our divine "wild boar" family.
No!