Under the invitation of the director Kasukabe-san,
The four of us in the family decided to go and
help a mountain village with its revitalization.
It was a family reunion after a long time apart.
It felt like we were on vacation together, and I was happy.
But then before us,
the lewd hands of this village took hold of me.
With the excuse of filming a promotion video for the festival,
not only did they rob me of my virginity,
even my elder sister Fubuki... became their victim.
Right now, all I can do is wish for the safety
of my mother and younger sister.
Onee-chan was also violated by the villagers...
To think that those scenes would be seen by the
people I don't even know all over the country...
All I could do was cooperate with the
lusty act of the village's event.
Yes. As you can see, they are helping
with the promotion event like that.
What is this?
No! Not this!
This is...
What is this!?
Let me meet the two of them this instant!
I can, but...
It would be trouble if we had to stop the filming.
It is necessary for the revitalization festival, after all.
Don't joke with me!
This is... such as thing is...
It's not a revitalization festival or anything at all!
I can stop it if you really want to.
But in exchange will you accept our conditions?
Presented by Erobeat | http://www erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
The Village of Turbid Withe
The Laughing Puppet Arc
Helter Skelter
The Village of Turbid White
The Dancing Puppet Arc
Please, this way.
Mom...
Haruka...
Hurry... and end...
Are you worried about them?
If so, there is no need to.
They should be heading this way about now.
Are Mom and Haruka okay??
What exactly is happening?
You'll know right away.
Right away...
What did you do to Mom and Haruka?
Don't joke with-!
Well then,
Please change into these respectively.
What are you trying to make us do?
As I explained yesterday,
the Boar Chase festival is held in this village.
Every year, we determine someone
to dress up as the Shishigami,
then we chase them around and 'eat' them.
And what about that?
Actually, we were thinking about starting the festival now.
...Festival?
Miu-chan and Fubuki-chan were helping
with something like the rehearsal.
If we can film the festival today...
You're telling us to be the Shishigami, right?
Yes.
It's great you understand right away.
As expected from the mother of a family of celebrities.
I get it.
I'll become the Shishigami.
But, only Haruka-chan, I can't...
Mom, wait, Mom.
I...
I want to see Miu-Nee and Yuki-Nee!
So... I'll become a Shishigami, too!
Haruka-chan...
Well, then it'll be both of you.
Now, please hurry and change.
Even as we talk, other filmings are going on.
Miu...
Yuki-Nee...
Well then, the Boar Chase Festival...
Let us begin.
Try hard!
What?
What is this?
Haruka-chan!
Run! Towards Miu-chan!
Mom!
Haruka-chan, you go to the temple.
What about Mom?
Listen. No matter what happens, run to
where Miu-chan and Fubuki-chan are.
No. I don't want to!
I want Mom to come, too!
I'll be fine.
So don't worry.
Mom...
C'mon. Hurry and run towards them.
You, too. Hurry and come!
I will protect everyone!
Where's the Shishigami!
Hurry and let me in your pussy!
Hey, She's over here! The mother!
Run, run!
If you don't hurry, you'll have a dick in you!
How sexy, oba-san!
No!
Stop!
Let go of me!
No!
So gross...
This is great!
Stop it... how filthy...
You'd better stay still.
No! Stop!
No!
Guess it can't be helped.
I'll give the first to Hakudaku-san.
No way...
No...
Another man's is... inside... no!
I'll go ahead and use those huge boobs!
No!
Such lewd things... stop them already...
At least...
What? You never gave your husband a titty fuck?
Don't talk... about him...
No!
Then I'll taste these instead of your husband!
Let me go... please...
Please!
Hurry up! I want to try the widow's pussy, too!
That's...
Do I have to be the partner for everyone here!?
Don't rush me! I'm going to speed up now.
Here we go, so much that your boobs rip!
Don't be so rough...
Be sure to make us cum with your boobs and pussy.
Please don't say such... lewd things...
You've already done it countless time with your husband, right?
Your pussy is all loose and dripping!
That's not true... he was...
No... no more!
Save me... save me!
It's about time I cum.
Be sure to take it all with your boobs and pussy!
There! There! There!
To rough...
No, no... don't...
My body... is weird...
No... you can't, don't cum!
Not inside!
No!
Darling... I'm sorry...
It's finally our turn!
I'll find out for myself if it's loose or not!
Stop...
No more... let me go...
This pussy... it's really tight!
Was your husband obsessed with it as well?
There's no way he was...
If you have the time to talk then use your mouth!
Inside my mouth, too?
No, not this...
Geez, your fellatio is horrible.
Oh well, I guess instead of your dead husband I'll train you!
It's painful...
Please hurry and end...
Woah... it's getting even tighter!
I think I'm gonna cum!
I'll cum in your pussy!
Be sure to get knocked up!
They're cumming inside again...
Haruka...
Miu...
Fubuki...
Why did it turn out like this...
Miu-Nee! Yuki-Nee! Mom!
Just a bit more. Alright.
Found you!
You should give up.
No! Don't touch me!
I can't do that.
If you're resisting to even this,
You have a long way to go ahead.
No!
First off, service us!
If you get it over quickly, we'll let you go.
What?
What do you want me to do?
Use those pretty hands and mouth to satisfy our dicks.
No!
If you don't hurry, we'll stick it up Haruka-chan’s pussy!
Th-That's...
Just hurry and service us!
Use your tongue, too. Be sure to lick it along the veins.
Stop it.
Don't rest your hands. Help us, too!
A gravure idol nowadays doesn't even
know how to use her mouth?
Although your body is indeed pretty.
Nope, no good.
Guess I'll just put it in.
Then, I'll take the first.
Damn, you...
It hurts!
It's painful!
Oh, as expected she's a virgin.
I just took the virginity of an idol!
No... Stop... something like this...no!
Hurry... and stop! Let go!
If you have time to talk, do your service!
Aren't you an idol?
You'd better be thankful, we're making your pussy usable now!
If you speed up, it still works.
Here, I'm cumming inside the pussy of an idol!
I'm cumming from an idol's handjob!
They... they came inside...
Miu... Fubuki... Haruka...
Oh, to think you'd still be here! I'm so lucky!
No...
Forgive me already...
Please stop...
We will when the festival ends...
Someone... help...
No!
Looks like it hasn't been too overused. How great!
I have to hurry towards... Miu-chan and the others...
Hurry and end... hurry!
I want... to see everyone...
It hurts...
Miu-Nee...
Yuki-Nee...
Welcome! Congrats on finally making it.
To be honest I wanted to take your virginity,
but I guess I'll have to use you lots instead.
No!
I'll take the pussy of the idol whom has
lost her virginity not long before.
Not at once...
As expected, it's still tight!
Damn, I really should have taken it before!
If you do it so much... I'll become weird!
You're an idol, right? Show some more appeal!
No... I can't do that...
Even though you're so wet, you say something like that?
That's not true!
I don't want to...
No, if this goes on...
Use your own hips as well, If you don't want to break.
You Just came inside... don't thrust so hard!
Are you evening feel it from anal?
My butt... it's being spread...
I'll break... I'm going to break...
Here, I'll pour lots inside you!
No... no, no!
Don't...
The festival will be over soon.
Hold on until the very end.
Haruka... Mom...
Haruka!
Mom!
Miu-Nee...
Haruka...
Fubuki-chan...
Mom...
Thanks to everyone, great stuff was filmed.
I'm glad I asked Sayoko-san for the favor.
It's about time for the finale.
No!
Well then, it's the last of this year's Boar Chase Festival.
Yes. I'll be sure to film until the very end.
I wonder who was eaten the most?
No!
Please don't look...
Now, it's the end of the festival!
Let's all eat together!
No!
Let me go already!
It's so rough...
That was great help. Thanks to you guys, it
feels that this village will gain popularity.
From now, please help our village, too.
Oh. Can we ask for your help right away?
Look at this, the celebrity family has quite the effect.
Especially to the men.
It'd be a waste if I don't, so I'll ask you to take
care of them as well, Shihigami-sama.
No, I should instead call you the Shishigami family...
No!!