Our supposedly fun and enjoyable family vacation...
...was actually a sneaky trap.
It was a perverted and obscene scheme aimed to place our family in shame.
My mother and I were the first to fall into their trap.
Translation: EROBEAT
Encode: SimpleX
Part 2
Murky Village
Yuki-nee!
So, did you find them?
No... They weren't at the bath...
I checked the lobby as well.
I see...
They didn't take their cell phones either.
Just where are they?
Yuki-nee...
Is something the matter?
Kasukabe-san?
Good morning, both of you.
Morning.
Please excuse me for my rudeness...
I only entered because the door was open.
Is something the matter?
My mother and sister are gone.
Do you happen to know where they've gone?
Oh, you mean Sayoko-san and Miyu-chan?
You haven't heard about them?
No, I haven't.
What happened to them?
It's a bit hard to explain it all...
Both of them were invited to participate in the village's festival.
A picture is worth a thousand words, after all.
How about you come along and I'll show you?
Festival?
You mean the one Miyu-nee mentioned?
Well, that's what's going on.
They're probably preparing for the festival.
However, this festival officially begins tomorrow.
Very well, take me there.
Haruka, wait for me here.
Why?
I want to come with you...
I have a bad feeling about this.
But staying alone...
Jeez, you're scared so easily.
Yuki-nee...
All right, let's go together.
Follow me then.
Right now, they're in the midst of practicing Boutaoshi.
There they are.
Can you see them?
What's going on? Why are the men in a line?
They're right in front of that line.
What are they doing?
Come on...
Haruka!
My, my... Was it too much of a shock for her?
Kasukabe-san, explain this at once!
Stop them right now!
That's a bit hard to do...
What the hell do you mean!?
Explain yourself!
I told you, they're preparing for the festival.
Yes, and I'm asking you, what exactly is this festival!?
The Hunting Festival.
A festival where everyone chase down the people who've been selected to become Shishigami
and then devour them until the very end.
And as you see, both of them have been chosen to become it.
Wait, what do you mean by devour?
You can take that literally.
Get it?
Why have they been chosen!?
We arrived here only yesterday!
Don't tell me...
You're smart.
Correct, you were selected as tributes to come to this town from the very beginning.
Well, it took quite a lot of effort to fix up your schedules...
But it was well worth it.
Us two as well?
No, no...
Seems like two is enough for now.
Not to mention, Sayoko-san begged us to let the both of you go.
But...
But what?
Well, regardless of it being Boutaoshi...
By Boutaoshi, we mean to bring down our penises, not poles.
I think it'll be a bit difficult since it's going to be an entire village of penises.
Oh, and the both of them are going to be fucked by the entire village during the festival.
But that's nothing you should worry about.
Let's go back and have breakfast.
Oh, right. Haruka-chan fainted.
What do you want me to do?
What do you mean?
I mean, it's not going to be of any help calling the police.
If I become a Shishigami as well, that'd take some of the load off both of them, wouldn't it?
Oh? You're willing to become one?
Well, I'm certainly fine with that.
Stop trying to act like you're dumb.
I have no idea how you forced them into submission,
but I'm sure that you've planned for me as well.
No, no... I promised Sayoko-san, so I wouldn't dare.
But it's a different story if that's what you wish for.
Haruka...
Leave Haruka out of this.
If something happens to her, I will kill you.
That's scary...
Don't worry.
As long as you become a Shishigami...
Then it's a promise.
Also, can't you stop the ceremony...
I've joined after all.
Yes, I'll go make arrangements.
Well, the number of people participating now will drop.
But those who leave will...
Be taken care of by me, correct?
I'm sorry, Haruka.
Shall we go then?
To where?
The shrine.
I'll carry Haruka-chan.
No thanks. I'll carry her.
So, what am I supposed to do?
First, change into this.
Right here, obviously.
Wait... Isn't this my school's uniform?
Where did you get this?
Hurry up and change.
Sly bastard.
Looks great on you.
Now, go and sit on the kagura.
Wait, this is the portable shrine?
Come on, go ride on it.
It's impossible... It won't fit in one go.
You've become a Shishigami already.
Do you not care about what'll happen to Haruka-chan?
You scum...
No, don't touch me!
You're such a spoiled bitch.
If you can't put it in in one go...
No, what are you doing!?
Let go... Let go of me...
You won't be able to put it in in one go, right?
I'll make it easier for you,
using my sperm as lubricant.
No... Stop...
No, stop!
No! No!
It's tight!
You won't be able to become a good Shishigami like this.
I guess I'll have Miyu-chan and Sayoko-san work even harder.
You're a cheap bastard!
Do whatever you want!
I won't admit my defeat!
Very well then.
I won't lose...
Miyu and Mom will have a lighter load to deal with once I join them...
And Haruka won't...
But getting fucked by this guy...
I'm about to cum...
He's filling me up...
It's hot and gross...
Now you should be fine.
Stop!
No! It's going in...
It hurts...
It's so big...
No! No!
It's in.
Now...
Not there!
Oh, I forgot to tell you that I like anal penetration more.
No... Don't tell me... No, don't!
Oh? Are you still a virgin here?
W-Wait...
Stop...
It hurts!
Ow! Stop!
I'm going to jam it in.
How does it feel to give your anal virginity to me?
Take it out! Please! It hurts!
Hey, it's not nice to hog all the fun for yourself.
Take care of theirs as well.
No... With my mouth?
You're kidding, right?
I've never sucked anyone off before...
Come on, you've lost your anal virginity already.
You shouldn't be embarrassed.
I'll never do it!
My mouth and butt are being penetrated...
What's this taste? It's spreading in my mouth...
Something's forcing its way up my butt...
My insides feel like they're going to come spewing out.
No... I don't want this.
Your ass is so goddamn tight.
You'd make a great Shishigami.
No... I can't lose...
But I'll break.
Why did things turn out this way?
I'm going to cum soon.
This is... This is too rough...
It hurts...
Make this end quickly!
N-No...
My butt and mouth are getting filled up...
No... This is disgusting.
Come on, drink it up.
Or do you want to die of suffocation?
Drink it?
That's disgusting.
I can't do it... This is terrible.
But I can't breath...
This is it, isn't it?
Your ass is the best.
Now we're done, right?
You're satisfied, right?
This is enough, right?
I'm satisfied, but...
Wait, no...
W-What's going on?
Is it still going to continue?
I've had enough...
It hurts...
My butt hurts...
Did you think you'd get a break?
If you can't take this much as a Shishigami,
Miyu-chan and Sayoko-san will have to burden all of us.
Yuki-nee...
N-No!
Who are you guys?
We're your biggest fans.
What's with that attitude?
Are you not happy to see your fans?
Um... Where's Yuki-nee?
And...
What? Are you ignoring us?
You act way too cocky for your popularity.
That's not true...
It's because I was just a little shocked...
What's going on?
Why are they all naked?
I have a bad feeling about this...
Now, come and serve us.
Serve?
What?
You do know that you're here to serve us fans with your body today, right?
Today's a thank you day for fans, isn't it?
I've never heard of this...
What's going on?
Yuki-nee, save me...
Whatever, who cares.
You're a gravure idol, so this should be nothing to you.
Let's have some fun.
No, don't...
Don't touch me!
No! No!
Ow...
Let go! Let go of me!
What a hot body.
Do you always fuck your camera men?
Stop...
N-No! Don't touch me!
I can't hold back.
Isn't it big?
The thought of being able to fuck a gravure idol made it two times as long.
Please stop...
Please!
Wait, am I going to be raped?
Like Mom and Miyu?
No, I don't want to...
Someone save me!
Yuki-nee!
Yuki-nee, save me!
Haruka... Haruka...
Yuki-nee, where are you!?
This isn't what we promised!
I thought you said you wouldn't touch Haruka if I became a Shishigami!
That's right.
Then what's going on?
Oh, that's just an activity by the fans.
Fans of the gravure idol, Kagami Haruka.
Though, I don't know the exact details of the activity.
Yuki-nee!
Is your emotional reunion over now?
It's about time to start.
Start what?
Stop!
It hurts! It hurts!
Take it out! It hurts!
Hey, you're a Shishigami now. There's no time for breaks.
It hurts!
Oh, so you're a virgin.
I lucked out.
Hey, let's do it from behind as well.
From behind?
No. not there!
So cruel...
It hurts!
Take it out!
Stop it!
Stop moving!
No!
It hurts...
It hurts, please...
Stop moving!
What's going on?
I don't get it anymore!
Yuki-nee, Mom and Miyu-nee as well... What's going on?
We were such a happy family until yesterday!
It hurts! It hurts!
I'm going to cum.
Take it all in.
No!
Something hot is coming into my butt and pussy...
There's so much...
It ended.
It ended...
Again? Stop...
So you like it up your ass.
We'll help you.
That's not true!
My butt is already...
No! It hurts...
Not there!
Take it out!
I'm getting raped in my mouth as well.
Am I going to keep getting raped from now on?
This isn't going to work...
Who's there?
Three of them...
Haruka!
Miyu-nee...
Haruka...
What did they do to you?
Yuki-nee and Mom are here too...
My god, why is everyone crying?
We're back together, after all.
You're the same...
What?
Haruka, what did you say?
You're all the same...
I'm happy.
Haruka...
Haruka-chan...
We're going to be together forever, right?
Haruka...
Haruka-chan...
Huh? Everyone is really crying...
They must be tears of joy, I guess.
That means we can finally be together.
I like this emotional reunion thing.
But you know, the ceremony is still going on.
Haruka!
No!
Miyu-nee!
Haruka! Miyu! Fubuki!
Thank goodness...
We won't be separated ever again.
I can be together...
with everyone...