Miu-nee! Yuki-nee!
Hurry, hurry!
H-Haruka!
W-Wait a moment!
Are you getting a bit too scared?
You're getting too excited about this!
Want me to shake it more?
Geez, what are you guys doing?
Wow!
Presented by Erobeat | http://www erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode ShocWave
Helter Skelter
The Village of Turbid Withe
The Laughing Puppet Arc
Oh, Kasukabe-kun!
Did you come out just to pick us up?
Yes, of course I have to.
The mother being the world-wide famous
designer, Kagami Sayoko;
Her eldest daughter Fubuki-san, a top model;
The third daughter Haruka-chan, the
gravure idol rising in popularity,
How can I dare not to come out and
welcome such a beautiful family!
Geez, flattery won't get you anywhere, you know.
Same here...
Since you're a designer just like Mom now, right?
Hmm...It's as expected, I don't know if I should have come...
To be honest, I had been worried with
this village revitalization thing.
But thanks to Sayoko-san, looks like we'll be able to do it.
It a favor for the Director-san who
has helped my husband so much.
Please let me help.
Besides...
Thanks to this, the family has a long-awaited
chance to be together again.
It's such a nice place!
It's like we're on vacation together,
which makes me really happy.
Thank you so much for coming.
I work as the village head here,
my name is Hatake Senzo.
I would like all of you to participate in Boar Chase
Festival that is about to take place in out village.
If members from the famous, beautiful family are
willing to help with our village revitalization,
and have the footage of that broadcasted to the
world, borrowing the popularity from everyone,
this village will become famous overnight.
That's not all.
What?
What is this creepy puppet?
It's the mascot of our village, Hakudaku-san.
Great name, right?
By the way, the festival of this village,
the Boar Chase Festival,
was because once when the village had no food,
so they dressed one person up as a boar and chased him,
and in the end had to eat him, right?
Yes, for the festival a person from the
village is chosen to act as the boar,
and people all chase them around.
That sounds somewhat disturbing.
So, do we get to chase them, too?
Geez, I'm so jealous of that careless personality of yours.
Feel free to run around all you want.
I wonder how long it's been since I’ve ran around.
True.
I’ll try hard!
Be careful not to fall.
Don't worry!
I'm confident in my legs.
You say that all the time!
Yeah, Haruka is playful all the time.
Well then, it's about time we go back, everyone.
That's true.
Looks like the sun will set soon, let's go.
I'm sweating.
Oh I know.
Let’s take a bath together! We can wash each other's back.
Yeah, it's been so long since we've done that together.
How has Miu-nee grown...
I'd love to see!
H-Hey! Geez, Haruka!
There, there!
Stop it!
It's fine!
Um, excuse me?
What is it, Kasukabe-kun?
Well, actually
I have a favour to ask.
From Miu-chan.
Huh, me?
Yes, we actually have another test we wanted to do.
Wait, why is it just Miu?
Someone from above insisted that we should
give some of the spotlight to Miu-chan.
Miss Campus at school, your less famous
beauty is essential for us, too.
So you won't gather enough people with just fame?
It's a problem on our side, I'm very sorry.
If Miu-chan's going, then we would go together.
It's a top-secret event, so sorry,
but I will have to ask you to return first.
Why can't we be together?
You guys can go back first,
I'm okay with being alone.
I had been thinking whether I should have come here
with you guys, because I was different, so...
I get it. Well, good luck!
Thank you very much.
Um... is this necessary... for the filming, too?
You see, we want a bit of sexual appeal,
too, so please endure for now.
Sexual appeal?
Please wait!
This kind of filming... not this!
Help!
No, no!
You'd help us, right?
You never talked about this!
Let me go!
I guess that can't be helped.
Since it is orders from above,
I'll have to ask someone else.
No way...
I have to work it out somehow.
These kinds of things... I won’t let you do it to the others.
So you are saying that it is okay to continue the filming?
Well then, let us continue.
What are you...
Wait! What are you planning to do!?
S-Stop!
No! Stop!
No, no!
Stop, no!
No... no...
Please stop... already...
No, wait! Please wait!
No!
Please, wait, not there!
Please... I beg you!
It hurts, no!
Oh, it was your first time? Great.
Stop...
Don't film... those places...
It hurts...
It hurts, it's so painful... I could go crazy...
It'll turn out as a good promotion video.
No! Don't film!
I can't let other see this...
You'd help us with our village revitalization, right?
Then of course this video...
No! I can’t show something like this to anyone...
Is everyone going to see me having sex?
To people who don't know who I am, too?
With this, Miu-chan will be famous, too.
Along with this village.
No! I don't want this!!
Don't say that. You have to work with our promotion properly.
No!
I don't want this, anything more is...
See? Seems like Hakudaku-san wants to cum inside Miu-chan.
No, take it out, take it out!
No, stop!
Stop!
No, no!
Please, just that...
Please spare me from just that...
He came...
Inside me...
This is so... gross...
Wonderful.
With this, I think we'll be able to continue with no problem.
No way... is it not the end?
Congratulations. With this, you'll become the Shishigami-sama.
What more do you want?
Huh?
I can't hold back anymore!
The Shishigami-sama this year is so beautiful!
Can we eat her already?
No...
No, no, no!
Stop!
No!
No...
Shishigami-sama is to be eaten by the villagers.
C'mon, take it in properly, Shishigami-sama!
I'll be using your hand.
And I'll be eating Shishigami-sama!
This is great; such a wonderful promotion video can be taken.
Awesome! The mouth-pussy of Shishigami-sama is the best!
Please stop this...
I'll...go crazy...
There's no way I'd stop until I'm done!
Don't rest your hands, either.
Rub harder.
Hurry and end this, hurry!
No!
Then you've got to use your tongue better!
That's...
I'm almost... cumming...
Stop it! Don't cum!
Use that body to receive it from everyone!
C'mon!
Drink it all!
Cumming!
Me, too!
They came inside... again...
Someone I don't even know...
Then next it's us, right?
Oh, it was such a long wait.
No... no more...
Help...
No, no...
Stop already...
No!
No, no!
No, stop, no, no!
It's useless to run.
You know that the Shishigami-sama is chased by the villagers.
Help...
Cumming, cumming!
Hey are you cumming again?
Shishigami-sama is such a pervert!
No, no!
Hey, your mouth is free.
Suck it for me.
Hurry up! We're tired of waiting.
Shut up, just a bit more.
Huh? I...
Where was this place?
Cumming!
Be sure to drink it all.
Hey, that's such a waste!
This side is in best conditions, too!
No, no!
Then again, she's a beautiful Shishigami-sama.
It's such a shame to stain her like this.
So are you going home?
Don’t be stupid, of course I'm doing her!
Please end this...
She's telling you go faster!
Then I will gladly obey.
No, that's not...
Cumming!
I'm... going to...
Break...
Helter Skelter.
The Village of Turbid White.
Where's Miu?
The filming is running a little late.
Whatever you say, it's just too late!
I'm picking her up.
Don't worry about it.
Just a village revitalization festival.
That place, right?
No...
Mi-Miu!
Onee-chan...
Let go of Miu!
You guys...
Doing something like this...
Did you think you could get away with it!?
We’re just filming the promotion video
for our village revitalization festival.
What do you mean, promotion!?
You're raping my sister, don’t you joke with me!!
I am not joking.
This is the side show for the Boar Chase Festival.
Miu-chan was willing to be our Shishigami-sama.
While testing, we are also filming part of the festival event.
There's no way that's true...
Hand me that tape this instant!
No! Let go!
No, no...
No... don't come...
No, let go!
Onee-chan...
No, let go of me!
Oh, it's a new Shishigami-sama!
No!
Stop!
No, stop it! Stop!!
This Shishigami-sama is so pretty, too!
Hey, hurry up already.
Stop, stop...
It hurts! Stop it!
No, stop... no... it hurts!
No, stop... it hurts...
C-Cumming!
Take it out... such a filthy...
Oh, how wonderful.
What are you doing? Stop! Don't film it!
I want a good product, too, so I can't do that.
You...
Do you think you can get away with this?
That is my line.
I could upload this right now and you'd never be able to erase it.
Who's the one who won’t get away with it?
Raise her up.
Is that really okay?
Of course.
Miu...
Onee-chan...
Wipe the data.
We'd be in trouble, too. If we don't get the promotion done.
I'll do everything, so don't do anything to Miu.
Onee-chan, no! If you do that...!
Okay then.
With the top model, we'll have a better scene.
I get it.
In exchange, you have to erase the data.
Then, let's start the filming.
Filthy... stinking...
What a slutty face!
Her skin is so smooth, too!
Let me do her already!
C'mon, stick your ass this way.
No!
As expected from a model,
such sexy positions.
No, Onee-chan...
Stop...
Hey, this place where it's going in...
Show it to everyone.
No!
Woah...
Cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming, too!
Me, too!
Cumming, too!
You don't have time to rest.
I get it...
Heh, it's my turn now.
C'mon, stick your ass up.
I get it. This is enough, right?
What a great ass.
Stop... don't do such cruel things to Onee-chan...
Please..
Why, why is this happening!?
It's about time we raise up our goddess.
Let's do it, let's do it!
What are you...
On one, two...
What is this, stop!!
What, you ask? We carry our god on our shoulders!
We'll be sure to hold tight, don't worry!
Oh, well done!
Don't joke with me... put me down. Put me down!
Well here we go!
One, two...
Stop, it hurts!
Hey, I said stop!
No!
Stop...
Don’t talk as the Mikoshi!
Stop this at once!
A previous top model being our Mikoshi,
this will make the best promotion video.
No!
Stop, don't film me in this position!
Al least let me down...
Hey, shut her up!
I’m breaking...
They’ll break me...
No, I'm cumming!
Stop it, stop it!
I'm cumming!
No, don't cum inside...
C'mon, this side, too!
Cumming, cumming!
Take it all, Shishigami-san!
Hey, be more gentle!
Don't worry. We treasure the festival a whole lot.
It won't break that easily!
By that you mean we’re eventually going to break it?
That was a very good film, thank you very much.
This is enough, right?
Hurry and hand me the tape.
Actually, we don't have enough footage yet.
What else are you planning to do?
So this is your first time with anal? Great.
No...
That's none of your business!
C'mon, the festival isn't over yet.
I know that!
Please walk forward like this.
Please-stop already!
Stop doing cruel things to Onee-chan!
Miu...
I be there... right away...
What a beautiful sister love.
A wonder footage this makes.
No... don't move!
Unforgivable...
I will never forgive you guys...
I get it. Just hurry and move forward.
Your precious, precious sister is being violated.
Stop...
Don't touch Miu...
I didn't think that the villagers would disobey
me and rape your sister again...
Don't joke with me!
That was your plan all along!
I don't know what you're talking about.
No!
Stay away from Miu!
Please, just stop!
I'm cumming, cumming!
No... don't look, don't look!
She’s cumming!
This Shishigami-sama is cumming!
Please...
Please, just top it...
I beg you...
Please, enough...
You say that, but look at your face already,
it's a face of a female totally in heat.
No, don't...
Onee-chan... I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Don't look...
Don't look at such a face of mine...
Will you hurry and move forward already?
Good, just like that.
Onee... chan...
C'mon, hurry up!
Go!
Onee-chan!
Good!
I'm sorry, it's all my fault that it's like this...
That's not true.
I shouldn't have left you alone...
I'm about to cum. Be sure to take it all with anal.
Inside my butt...
It's coming... inside!
My insides are so full...
O-Onee-chan...
I'm sorry... I... can’t take it anymore...
We still have lots of filming to do.
Everyone...
Stop already...
No...
Hurry...
Hurry and let it out...
Cumming!
So much is coming out...
I'm cumming, cumming!
It's coming out... inside me...
It's coming out... so much...
No... I'll get pregnant...
No, I can’t... I can't...
It's coming, coming...
Onee-chan!
Cumming, I'm cumming...
I can't take it anymore either, I'm cumming!
Cumming!
Woah, what a show again.
We lasted so long.
That's good! The more footage, the better.
So, what are you planning for the other two?
The actual festival has yet to start,
so we can enjoy them lots then.
Miu-nee hasn't come back yet...
This is definitely strange. Fubuki-chan is gone, too.
I'll go look for them!
Wait, Haruka-chan!
Good morning.
Did you sleep well last night?
Kasukabe-kun...
We’ll be doing the finishing touches on the festival preparations,
and we’d like you two to help as well.