No...
Hehehe...
No, no...
No~!
Huh? What? A girl screaming?
Shit...
Stop!
Ouch! No, no...
Hehehe...
Hehehe, I just love schoolgirls.
No, stop it...
There, it's going in. Hehehe, there we go.
Hehe, you're not a virgin?
No, no~!
Then I'm gonna give all I got. Hehehe...
Stop it, stop it...
It's warm... You're already soaking wet.
Stop, stop... No!
Shut up bitch!
Scream even more and
your cute face will be tired.
To avoid that, I'll help you
shut your mouth. Hehehe...
See, you're already horny, hehehe...
Hey keep on licking.
Huh? Open wider!
No, no... No!
You're so fucking stubborn.
Here, you've always sucked dick right?
Just do your normal stuff.
End it quickly and you'll be relieved too.
Here, here, here...
Hehehe... Huh?
Hey fucking pervert.
Go away if you don't want to be killed.
Fucking shit...
Uh, um, thank you very much.
Are you a schoolgirl?
Yes, from Saint Helena Institute.
I see. Stand up.
Excuse me.
Schoolgirls aren't bad at all.
Your breasts looks so soft.
I guess I'll be served.
I can't miss this opportunity,
especially with a girl like you.
Umm... ls there something wrong?
Huh?
Nothing.
You looked like you were pondering.
Yea, I was thinking of
how I should fuck you.
Huh?
My company went bankrupt.
Now I don't give a fuck about anything.
Right, my company went bankrupt.
Hahaha, hey, hey,
don't you dare run away.
Excuse me?
Isn't it sad? I was called
Mr. President up to yesterday.
Now I have no job
with tons of loans.
I don't know anything...
You don't know?
It's my company!
No, no~!
No!
Hahaha, you have a nice body.
Your skin's different from older girls.
Stop it, please...
Don't think of retaliating.
I lost hope in my life.
A person who lost hope don't give
a fuck about robbery or rape.
Understand? Haha...
Yes...
Smells good.
No, please, forgive me!
Yes, your skin's so smooth.
I only could believe in young bodies
in this world. Don't you think so?
No, that can't be, I don't know.
Now I wonder how a schoolgirl pussy
tastes.
Smells good.
No, please forgive me!
This is it.
No, no...
Stop, stop it...
What? You're so wet you bitch. When did
a schoolgirl learn to be this wet?
Your body is matured.
Don't you want to feel me stick it in?
Oh please...
Come on, you're getting laid so
you lick my hot cock with your cute lips.
Yea, that's the way. I'm cumming, good.
Schoolgirl blowjobs are not bad.
Oh yea...
I love this, your tongue sucks nicely.
Oh, dangerous. I almost let it go.
Shit, feels good. You're pretty good.
You have more technique than the sluts.
Don't rest bitch, handle it.
Yes, hehehe... I don't cum that easily.
So suck with all your heart.
Yea, love that expression.
Yea, more, more, more!
Good, good...
Feels good...
There, there, there, right there.
It feels good.
You're so good.
I feel like flying somewhere.
Yea... Slowly, slowly.
Handle my dick with care.
Oh crap, I almost came again.
Nice and slowly...
All in your mouth.
Don't use your teeth.
Hehehe, it feels good.
Yea, slowly, up and down
up and down...
Feels good.
Man, you're the best...
More, more, more,
Yea, that's the way!
Faster, faster!
Right there, yes, yes, yes...
Yea...
You're getting better.
Hehehe, you're better than
the prostitutes...
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
Yea, excellent, good, good...
Good! Good, you're excellent.
Yea, deeper, suck deeper.
Yes, deeper, deeper, stick it deeper.
More, more, grab it firmly.
Yes, yes, yes...
You have a cute face.
There, there...
Hahaha... huh?
What's this on the ground?
No...
Hehehe, good stuff.
You're swallowing it.
Curse the guy who forgot this bat.
It hurts!
But it sure goes in deep. You're sucking
this fat thing and making it sing.
Ouch... stop it!
Hey, hey, how is it? Huh?
Hehehe, suck this!
It hurts, it hurts...
Mister, please stop...
See, it's making a wet sound.
Hahaha...
Don't put that in...
This thing's going in deep...
Ouch, it hurts, it hurts...
Sir, please stop.
See, it's pumping your cum!
Stop putting it in!
Wow, it's going in deep.
Here, here, hehe...
Doesn't it feel good?
No it doesn't...
I know you better!
Please stop...
It's embarassing.
What a nice view, haha...
I can't go to my wedding.
Don't worry, it only hurts the first time.
There, hehehe. Nice reaction, hehehe...
Please, pull it out, pull it out...
No, I won't pull it out.
No, no. Hehe, I can see it clearly.
No, don't look!
Beautiful, beautiful. It's a nice pink.
Mom...
I'm not your mom, hehe.
I'll do anything that you want so say it!
Come on, spread wider!
No, don't look...
This is so exciting, isn't it?
Hahaha...
It hurts.
It shouldn't hurt anymore.
It should feel better.
It doesn't feel good.
Not quite ready...
There, there, hehe...
No, it's embarassing.
What a nice view, good!
Please, get it out...
No!
How is it?
It seems like you're feeling it.
Look, your nipple's rock hard.
Hehe, don't tell me you don't feel this.
I don't feel such thing.
Really?
Then I'll make you feel better.
Stop it!
You have nice tits.
Young skin is the best.
Doesn't this feel like I'm fucking?
Hey hey, doesn't this feel good?
No, no...
Shit!
Stop it!
Doing this makes me want to fuck. Hey,
don't you want to feel the real thing?
Hey, I'll stick my hot dick in your pussy.
Yes, smells wonderful.
I can't bear it.
Ok, I'm going to fuck your
pussy and your ass, hehehe...
No~!
I was off guard before,
but now it's my turn.
It's a waste for an old faggot to be
fucking a schoolgirl. Don't you think so?
I'm gonna fuck before anyone
bothers us. Hehehe...
No~!
Now, this is good.
Please, honesty,
let me go home! I...
Hey hey, enough talking.
No, please... please...
Hey, liottle girl,
I said enough with talking.
Please, if you let me go I'll give you all
my savings and an autograph of Smapo.
I don't need that junk. Listen girl,
I flunked my entrance exam.
Four, four times. Understand? Everyone
graduated but I'm still trying to apply.
Hang in there.
What bitch? Don't be so saucy.
You wouldn't understand my feelings.
Man, what a gorgeous pink. I'm happy
since I'll get to enter your pussy. Hehehe.
No, no~!
There, hehehe. I'm sticking it in.
This way I'll use up everything. Hehehe...
No~!
Good, it's warm. I can't stand it.
Feels good, feels good.
It's like a dream.
Your tits are really soft.
Yes, I've been jacking off all this time,
but now I'll get to cum inside a cute girl.
No! Not inside! No~!
Stop, please! No, no...
Kamakura police makes good country.
Square root of 2 is 1.4142135
It feels good.
Sine, cosine, tangent!
Please stop, please...
I'll forget everything.
I wonder if I'll fail this year.
Whatever. As long as I get to
feel good by fucking. I'm happy!
No, no~!
The noise of the gong of the Gion.
Yea, it's vibrating!
I can still go on!
Don't go on!
I'm going, going!
I've been saving for four years.
This is a piece of cake!
Hey, how is it? Here!
You're starting to feel something.
No I don't. No, please stop!
It's stinging! It hurts!
Not yet!
You're so tight. It feels good.
Let me change the angle a bit.
It hurts, ouch, ouch, stop it!
Pretty... good, it's tighter!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming...
No~!
Hahaha, sucker!
Trying to leave me out mother fucker?
Sir you came to help!
But why are you naked?
Don't you get it, to do this sucker! I only
used the bat and didn't get to use this!
Hehehe, you'll be sucking until
it's rock hard. Hehehe...
There we go. Good, good.
Suck more.
The pervert before made you wet
so now it's my treat!
Sir, no~!
Man I love young pussies.
The tightness is different.
Forgive me, please, Sir...
Hehehe, don't be silly.
You're tightening your pussy too.
No, I'm going home.
What are you saying? I can't go home
because of the debt collectors.
I don't know...
When my company went bankrupt,
you didn't know?
I don't know!
It feels good...
Ouch!
I'm cumming, cumming! Hehehe...
No~!
The rope's loose. Now!
Now I can go home.
I went this far...
My head feels dizzy but don't worry.
Let's continue!
No!
Don't you like young cock is better?
Shit, he came here.
Wait, wait! Oh no, I'm cumming!
Stop bastard, she's my bitch!
I'm cumming!
No, I'm cumming!