Megumi, introduce yourself.
Meet Shinichi. He's going to
be your brother.
Hello.
I'm Megumi.
I'm Shinichi.
Our parents got married three years ago.
That was the first time I met him.
At first, it was very awkward.
Shinichi was always nice to me.
I eventually accepted him.
We became very close,
and I started to see him as my older brother.
You see, with this equation,
you multiply ''c'' into this number.
However...
a horrific event
soon shattered both our lives.
Hika Ryojoku
Where's my favorite underwear?
Megumi, I'm taking off.
Hey, wait for me!
What's up?
Shinichi.
Good morning.
So, you did bring what we asked, right?
Right?
Yes.
This jerk really did bring
his sister's panties!
Teru, we're going to sell that.
Don't fuck it up, all right?
I know that!
This will make us quite a lot of money!
Hey, Shinichi!
Here you go!
Your younger sister's looking
for you, asshole!
Say hi to her for me!
Shinichi!
You could have waited for me
a bit longer, you know!
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm fine.
Let's get going.
Sure.
That's his sister?
She's pretty hot!
Yeah.
I had no idea that Shinichi was...
getting bullied by two of his classmates
at this time.
Your sister's underwear
made us a lot of money.
But, a used one will sell for twice the price,
if you know what I mean, Shinichi.
You know what we want from you, right?
Don't make me do this.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You've already stolen her panties
once, right?
You know what'll happen to you...
if you don't do exactly what we ask?
Yuck!
I'm all sweaty and gross.
This smells like Megumi.
Megumi.
Your next job.
What is?
What do you think?
Take nude photographs of your sister.
I won't!
From what I remember...
your old man's a doctor, right?
Then it should be easy.
You can slip her some sleeping pills.
Right?
Yeah?
I brought you coffee and snacks.
Sure, let me open the door for you.
Come in.
Thanks.
Are you ready for the test?
I think I'll do all right.
Thanks!
I think I'll go to sleep now.
Megumi.
Megumi....
You know what'll happen to you,
if you don't do exactly what we ask?
I'm sorry.
Megumi.
Megumi, I'm....
Sorry!
Shinichi.
Megumi, Megumi.
I wonder why Shinichi...
wants to meet me here.
How are you doing, Megumi?
Who are you?
We're your brother's friends.
His friends?
We want you to come with us
to go meet your older brother.
Meet my brother?
Tell me, where is he?
You want to see him?
Fine, you can see him.
My god!
It's just a minor punishment.
You see, he stopped following
his orders lately.
So, we decided that you can make up
for his fuck-ups, being his sister.
No!
Whoa, you're staying here, honey.
Shinichi, please help me!
You don't get it, do you, darling.
Your brother's involved in this.
He was going to take pictures
and bring back the film...
but he fucked it up,
so we took this picture of him.
But this picture isn't what we wanted
in the first place.
So we asked your brother
to pay for his fuck-up...
by letting us meet you in person.
He said...
that we could meet you.
That can't....
Be true!
You see now,
your own brother sold you out!
Let's have some fun.
No!
White panties?
No, Shinichi!
They're nice and big!
Stop!
And they're sensitive, too!
Let me sample these!
You like that, sweetheart?
Let me see what you have down here, sugar.
No, please don't do this, please!
No!
Stop!
Shut the fuck up, damn it!
No!
Here, talk to this.
Now, I can get a good look at your pussy.
Let's see how your pussy tastes.
You seem to like it!
You have a big clit, little girl.
Play with yourself often?
I think she's really getting into it.
Hey, are you watching?
Your sister's getting all wet, asshole!
Blow me.
Goddamn, this feels good!
Suck on it hard, bitch.
Fuck yeah!
I'm going to come now!
This wet, little pussy should make
my hard cock happy.
No, stop!
So, how does it feel
to be a woman?
It hurts!
You'll get used to it soon enough.
Jesus Christ!
This is one, tight pussy!
Shinichi!
I'm fucking the back door!
That's right, you were into ass-fucking,
you sick fucker.
No! Don't, please!
Shit, it's fucking tight!
Fuck yeah!
Yeah, this is making her pussy even tighter.
Shinichi!
Fuck!
Yeah!
Shinichi!
Megumi!
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
It's not your fault.
But, will you make me
clean again, Shinichi?
They made me dirty down here.
Megumi!
Promise!
Megumi.
Shinichi.
After this...
our relationship was never going to be
the same again.
Are you sure it's okay?
Megumi!
Shinichi!
Megumi, I....
Can't....
Shinichi!
I'm....
I'm coming!
God!
Yes, come for me!
I want you to come for me!
Yes!
Since then...
whenever he gets picked on at school...
he will always make love
to me afterwards.
If that's what I can do for Shinichi
to make him feel better...
I won't let him down.