Knight Princess
Discipline 02
You insolent man. I don't Love you!
I will endure every humiliation!
It's alright now, Princess Teresa.
I have already gotten rid of your kidnappers.
I was so scared!
You have endured it splendidly.
I expected nothing less from our proud princess of the dark elves.
Let us return home now.
Ok.
Cecil!
Do not act so immodest, princess.
I told you to call me Teresa when we are alone.
Ok, I get it,
Teresa.
But why?!
I told you I was ok with it.
We are in Kertoura and I am a human.
I cannot become a palace guard, Teresa.
But it's strange.
You've been my guard as long I can remember,
so you should also protect me from now on.
These are the military rules.
I get it.
If you won't become my guardian then I will join the military!
Then I will make you my subordinate
and keep you by my side forever.
You've been promoted again, Cecil?
At this rate I won't be able to become your superior.
Slow down a bit, will you!
Don't be absurd.
This promotion is a rare opportunity for a human.
Listen, Cecil. I've decided to make you my subordinate and
to have you for the rest of my life, so don't go anywhere!
Don't you dare to leave Kertoura!
Cecil!
Oh, if it isn't Princess Teresa.
No... vice commander of the Second Division.
What brings you to such a remote place?
Spare me the insincere greetings, Cecil.
In that case, what are you doing here, Teresa?
Isn't it obvious?
I have come to check up on you since you have aroused suspicion.
There are rumors that you are doing n-nasty
things to your female prisoners.
So what about it?
It's a common thing among commanders.
It's the best payment you can get.
Y-you can't do that!
I don't care about the others but I won't let you do that!
I don't understand what you're talking about.
At any rate...!
I'll report it to my father... I mean to His Majesty!
You'll be summoned back to our home country!
You'd better start packing.
Tsk!
Is it because she's a woman herself?
She's always made a fuss about other women.
Or maybe she was sent by someone who
doesn't approve of my "benefits".
But I can't let you interfere now.
Should I do it?
Teresa!
W-What is it?
Are you trying to make excuses, Cecil?
No, I just want to ask you something, Teresa.
Let me help myself to hearing the answer from your body.
You've grown up from a little crybaby into a fine woman, Teresa.
Nobody will come to help you.
I've sent your subordinates back to our home country.
You've been manipulated by this Puppet Ring.
Don't frown so much.
It ruins your cute face.
Just wait.
Let's carry on with your inspection.
Let me hear your answer to all of my questions,
directly with that body of yours.
This is the key to the interrogation of a woman.
From now on, if you don't want anything
to happen to you, answer my questions.
Who sent you to such a remote region?
What's his goal?
You bastard!
Don't think that you will get away with this!
I see.
Seems like you won't talk unless I pleasure you, Teresa.
In that case...
In fact, I already know everything after
questioning her with the Puppet Ring.
Who would have thought that she's in love with me?
It's probably a girlish sentiment for me from protecting her.
In that case, she can probably be ensnared
and made into a docile pawn.
This is a potion that makes your breasts as sensitive as your clitoris.
There's a side effect of breast milk leaking during an orgasm.
It should be working already.
How is it?
Feels good, doesn't it?
So, are you saying that you aren't getting excited while I do this?
If you don't become more obedient you won't
get any attention from the man you like.
Looks like your breast milk has started to leak.
It gives you away if you try to hide the fact that you came.
Seems like it's an intense experience to let
out your breast milk for the first time.
But from now on I will make it even more intense.
Do you know, Teresa?
Do you know why intercourse between an elven
woman and a human man is such a taboo?
It's because once she tries doing it with a human man
she can't get satisfied by a mere elf anymore.
How is it?
How does it feel to have your noble elven
virginity stolen by a human of low birth?
You don't know unless you try it, right?
Does it hurt?
It will get better soon.
Every elven woman that tastes this pleasure becomes its slave.
Teresa Kertoura,
the proud princess of the dark elven nation.
How about you?
You're making such a rebellious face.
I guess we need a more violent interrogation.
So you're finally starting to enjoy being pleasured by a human?
You've lost your dark elf elegance and dignity.
Do you like human dick this much?
Such an indecent princess.
I'll let the subjects of Kertoura know that Teresa is a
lewd princess who likes to be violated by humans!
If it doesn't excite you then why are you so wet?
I now what you're hiding.
Go on, admit it...
Sex with a human is great, isn't it?
In that case I have no choice...
I'll try cumming inside.
What?
You wanted me to finish inside you that badly?
You've suddenly become very tight.
Then get filled with human semen, elven princess!
I see that you came.
So you did enjoy it.
My first time with Cecil that I've dreamt
about all this time... so forcefully...
That's so cruel!
How was it?
How did it feel to have your first time with a
human and even be filled with his semen.
You monster!
Don't think you'll get away with this, Cecil!
Stubborn, aren't we?
How about I change your attitude and
we continue with the interrogation?
Don't think you can control me... with... this...
How nasty!
You're turning Teresa into such a perverted princess.
It was you who told me to fuck you in this position, Teresa.
That you wanted to feel like a princess being
screwed by a lower class human.
How perverted are you?
It's because Cecil's human penis feels so good.
An elven dick isn't enough for my loose, wet royal pussy.
No! I didn't think that!
I am a proud princess knight!
I am not a pervert!
Cecil's dick! Human dick!
Teresa's pussy wants more!
Even though I'm a princess I'm being
fucked from behind like a dog!
I've become a bitch!
Copulating like animals doesn't make me happy at all!
If my subjects saw me in this pitiful state...
Do you like being fucked in a position that reveals your asshole?
It's good!
It's so exciting when you're fucking me
from behind looking at my asshole!
Cecil! Cecil!
Oh no! I kissed him!
I'm happy that I had my first kiss with Cecil
but I didn't want it to be like this!
It's coming, I'm going to burst!
I love you! I love you so much, Cecil!
N-No!
I like Cecil but doing something like that
no master how pleasurable, is...
No, Teresa can't go on without Cecil's dick!
I'll do what you want!
I'll bear your child!
No! I can't let this happen!
As a princess I can't let this happen!
I'll be your sperm toilet so please, reward
me with your dick from now on!
No! That's not how I am!
It's coming!
Cecil's semen is coming!
I'll get pregnant!
I'll have Cecil's child!
No!!
Even if it's Cecil, this can't happen...!
I love you, Cecil.
No...
It's not like that...
I hate the Cecil who does such things...!
Even though I hate him...
It's been a week since then.
Teresa's training is going well.
All that remains is Olivia...
You don't understand anything!
L-Lord Karubart!
P-Please excuse me!
Sophia?!
No, it can't be!
She died 15 years ago.
Besides, she's too young to be her.
And wasn't she an elf?
Nevertheless, she's her spitting image.
I...I have arrived.
You're late, Olivia.
You've gotten quite good at it.
You learn fast.
Princess Olivia is excellent!
Even if you say that, it doesn't make me happy.
Finish quickly, please.
In that case, instead of looking around you'd
better hurry up and make me cum.
It's coming.
Drink it gratefully.
I've ejaculated specially for you.
Good.
Looks like you swallowed it all.
Where are you going?
I serviced you properly with my mouth, didn't I?
You wanted to satisfy me with this?
If you want to save the prisoners' lives
then do some more service for me.
Looks like you've learned how to use those huge tits properly.
Using my breasts for something like this...
Then do another service for me.
Put this bracelet on.
This swimsuit is too small, it hurts.
What?
What is this?!
It's a life bracelet.
An item that brings the body back to the
state when it was overflowing with life.
It contains such magic?
No!!
Stop it, you...!
So you've had such a lewd bust ever
since you were born, Princess Olivia?
Of course not, you pervert!
You want to violate me in this form?!
I need a little change sometimes.
Let's try many different princesses.
So her body has gotten younger but
her mind has remained the same?
It's going to be fun!
No! Not there!
Don't lick that place!
Such a strong smell for such a young girl.
No!
You pervert! I'll kill you one day!
When your life force reaches its maximum and you
obtain my semen, you'll definitely get pregnant.
No! Stop it!
I don't want to have your brat!
Let's try this drug then.
No!!
What's that?
Something cold is deep inside me!
What is it?!
What have you put inside me?!
A contraception drug with 100% guarantee.
Stop! It's impossible!
Something that big won't fit inside me!
You're gonna tear my pussy apart!
If I do I'll fix it with healing magic.
Stop it! It won't fit!
It was already tight to begin with but if you put it in now...
Oh, the hymen regenerated?
It's the second time I have taken your virginity.
You're a faithful whore.
I-It hurts!
You're tearing me apart!
Take your penis out!
A whore doesn't get a choice.
It hurts!
If I don't thrust hard my dick won't go in
all the way and through your cervix.
By the way, about this drug,
in exchange for not getting pregnant it multiplies
the amount of semen by a few hundred times.
I's tight and squeezes me nicely.
It feels good.
I'm going to cum now.
You won't get pregnant so don't worry.
No!!
Even though you're not going to get
pregnant your belly swelled up.
Let's make your breasts feel good too.
M-My breasts, they... feel so hot!
Why is my milk flowing out?
That's impossible!
Don't worry.
It's a side effect of the aphrodisiac.
It almost looks like you are really pregnant.
No!!
Oh, it's gone all the way in.
It feels great!
It's like fucking a container of meat.
You won't get pregnant so I don't need
to hold back with cumming inside you.
No... No more...
I want to... stop...
I'm dying...
I'll die...
No!
My belly's gotten so big yet he's pouring even more inside me.
My uterus will burst!
I'm going to deliver!
The bracelet's magic has disappeared?
It still needs improvements.
Oh, so that's how it condenses semen?
It's just like laying eggs.
Sooner or later I will impregnate you.
Fucking a princess with a potbelly could be nice.
Come in!
Excuse me.
Uhm... Erm...
My name is Laura Elfinline.
A-As a sign of friendship between our
countries I have been promised,
to be married to Lord Cecil Karubart.
Please, take good care of me from now on.