A Selfish and Obstinate Princess: Ou Maika
Maika is a stubborn princess who's a year younger than Yahiro,
and is good at hiding her true nature.
She has been sent over for lessons about proper etiquette
because of her extremely selfish behavior.
Despite her usually bad attitude, she manages to perfectly act in a way befitting a princess when she appears in public.
Aware that the brother of another girl is staying there as well,
Maika starts living in the same place as where Yahiro is.
The two of them fall love with each other, spending each day with happiness.
But despite that, Yahiro feels an impending crisis that is upon himself nonetheless...
A Maid Who's Also In Charge of Maika's Studies: Sakuno
Sakuno is in charge of Maika's studies.
She is the only person who Maika won't dare talk down to.
She teaches Maika all things about manners of speech and actions.
Sakuno has an overall good attitude regardless of who she interacts with,
but Maika says that even she is scared whenever Sakuno gets angry for real.
Sakuno gave her approval on the relationship of the two, but Maika sees how Yahiro and Sakuno go along together a little too well as something unnecessary...
A Student Who Sits Away From The Spotlight
and Acts When The Need Arises: Kujou Yahiro
Yahiro might be seen as a man with a passive personality,
but he acts when the situation demands him to.
His hobby is fiddling with his self-built PC,
and there's no end to it when he starts talking about it.
By the orders of Yahiro's father, he had to suddenly move over while still in the middle of the school term.
He currently lives together with his younger sister and other girls.
Yahiro goes on to spends some peaceful time with Maika.
Their platonic and sibling-like relationship then became a romantic one.
Suddenly getting close to each other,
and with him lusting for her body like he wants to devour her as well,
the two enjoyed each passing day filled with indulgence.
Yahiro wallowed in his lust for Maika,
not knowing how to stop his youthful desire.
And so, he delves even deeper as he brings up a certain proposal to her...
While they're occupied on reading magazines,
Yahiro brought up a certain thing that especially caught his fascination.
He nonchalantly asked her about it like it's no big deal:
"Hey, Maika. They said that it feels good even in the ass."
Hime-sama Love Life!
Original Animation
Hey, Maika...
Hmm?
Are you not curious in the ass?
What's that? I don't get it.
They said that it feels good even in the ass.
Huh...
Are you stupid? What are you
saying out of the blue, pervert!?
You're looking too much!
If I'll stay any longer with a pervert like you...
No, no, no way! L-Let me go!
I want to know everything about you, Maika.
Y-You don't have to know about that!
I'll let you know about other stuff instead!
Aren't you paying me back for the last time?
Wh-What... Panties!
You perv!
Shut up!
Isn't it because you buried your face in my panties?
It's not my fault!
You're the one who sat over my face.
I was just a victim.
But didn't I already make it up to you for that?
Th-This should make us even, okay?
Maika, you're wet.
Not there...
If you do that to me,
I won't be able to do this properly!
G-Gosh...
Your dick is oozing at the tip,
and it smells so lewd.
Wow... So this is how you taste like, Yahiro!
You're touching me...
You're playing with my pussy!
Maika, I'm about to come!
It's alright, Yahiro. Shoot out a lot.
Come inside my mouth!
M-More... That feels good, Yahiro!
I'm also about to...
Here it is!
Wow, it's filled with your scent!
W-We shouldn't be going any further...
Gosh, don't touch me at any weird places!
Yeah, don't sweat it.
Well, we're the only ones home...
You're so stiff!
It became like this because of me...
It's alright, I want to make you feel good.
I want to give you lots of pleasure using my hand!
My tits!
They'll get disfigured...
You're molding them into an indecent shape...
Come...
Fill my mouth with your dick!
It's okay!
Yahiro!
Huh!?
You're still aroused.
So, I'm making you feel so horny!
Hey, do it.
Put your dick inside me!
Yes!
Squeeze your dick deep into me!
You're making a mess out of me
just like from our first time...
I'll do it just like this, Yahiro.
I'm alright.
It's a part of your own body,
so I'll be able to bear with it.
Your thing went in!
Your dick is inside me...
I can feel how you're inside me!
We're connected!
You were also going hard on me back then!
You're like another person
when you're being lewd!
Yes, you are.
Aren't you lewd as well, Maika?
You're wrong! Gosh...
Aren't you the one who made me lewd?
Yes, your dick...
It's going deep in my pussy!
Huh? N-N-No way...
Yahiro, that's...
No way! Yahiro, your fingers... Stop that!
No, I don't want that!
Don't do that! No, no way! You're kidding!
No, don't! I'm coming, I'm coming!
I-I'm coming—!
No!
No way, this can't be happening!
My ass...
You're fucking kidding me!
Forcing me something I don't want...
Pervert! Idiot!
I'm sorry, I just got in the groove...
What groove are you talking about?
Y-Y-Your girlfriend didn't want it,
and yet... You brute!
Maika-sama, it's time for you to change now.
Huh?
How about accompanying her today, Yahiro-sama?
Hmm?
Yahiro-sama, please enjoy yourself
as much as you can for today.
Maika, the way you talk...
...creeps me out.
Oh, that's not good...
You bastard! I'll drive this knuckle
in your face when we get home!
O-Oh... It's the usual Maika, alright...
May you please look forward to it.
Maika is currently stuck with a bigwig.
Sakuno-san is also occupied with an acquaintance...
But still, isn't he being too close?
H-Huh, Maika?
Sakuno-san won't do...
Maika!
Oh, that was scary!
Are you alright, Maika?
Yeah, I'm alright. That was just a little...
He won't be out there for a while.
Where did that girl go?
She kicked me, shit!
Huh?
You act like that even at a time like this.
You're unscrupulous, jeez...
Huh? Th-That's because
you're different from usual.
It's because you look pretty right now.
Huh?
Do you want to stain them?
It already got big.
A-Are you sure about this?
The reason why you went here
is to help me, right?
Then, a-as your girlfriend...
I have to reward your deed.
You don't have to be shy.
Shut up! Just keep quiet and let me lick you!
It's so stiff...
I bet that you'll come in no time.
It's throbbing...
It's alright.
Yahiro, come.
Come from my fingers and tongue.
Huh? No, what are you doing?
Wait, Yahiro! Hey...
What are you doing? Not at this place!
H-Hey, aren't you being too rough on me!?
Teasing me like this...
I want to know everything about you, Maika!
Huh?
Hey, s-stop fooling around!
Do you mean that you want
to know "that part" right here!?
Don't do that, Yahiro! You absolutely shouldn't!
Stop that! Please, listen to me!
No, no... Didn't I tell you
that I don't want that!
Why are you doing that? Pervert! You're so mean!
I'm begging you, we should stop it here! No!
No way, this is...
I'm...
No, even though I don't want it...
Even though you shouldn't...
I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
Huh? No!
No! No, I shouldn't!
No—!
You perv!
What were you thinking, you brute!?
I'm sorry, I just got in the groove...
Don't you "groove" me, Dammit!
You said the same last time,
perverted sleazeball!
Maika-sama, Yahiro-sama!
Sakuno-san, did it go well?
The man that Maika-sama had
an issue with is a foreign diplomat.
I've already patched things up.
Uhh... Umm, I'm sorry.
Maika-sama, you're unusually honest
right now that you're with your beloved man.
Oh...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time on Hime-sama Love Life!
Uhh... Mai...
H-Huuuh! S-Sakuno-san!?
Maika-sama will hear us if you raise your voice.
Let's keep going, alright?
It's your robust dick, Yahiro-sama...
You're already awake down here.
I'll give it lots of service!
I want to experience the same feeling as well...
...from your dick, Yahiro-sama!
Yahiro-sama, I want it harder!
Please drive me crazy!
Now that I know how this feels, I'm already...
Give it to me, Yahiro-sama!
I want it in my pussy!
Having this thing exposed out here...
Aren't you a pervert, Yahiro?
Your dick gets big no matter where you are.
How boorish!
It's alright.
That was close... What am I saying?
He seems to be feeling so good from this, though.
What are you doing in this situation?
I'm telling you to stop!
Aren't you wet since earlier?
Hey, won't we end up getting caught?
Let's just do it the normal way...
People won't see from just this much.
We can't do this! No!
H-Hey, what's this? This can't be...
You're kidding, right?
Didn't I tell you that I don't want that, Yahiro!?
It'll feel good when you get used to it...