No, El.
We must stop this.
You smell sweet.
It smells like a lily.
Please stop, El.
I have a husband.
If you do that, it will come.
It will come again from my breasts!
To think you would ejaculate milk.
Just stop it, please.
I'm going to die from embarrassment.
Not yet.
I want you to help me cum with your breasts.
Chris, more milk is seeping out.
Don't tell me doing this turns you on?
How dare you suggest that!
I would never be turned on from this...
Never mind that.
Just put more force into it.
Is this enough?
It's getting bigger again.
It's not bad, but it's still not enough.
Pleasure me with your mouth now.
You have a complaint about it?
Fine, I understand. Don't glare at me like that.
I'll suck it with my mouth.
How does my penis taste?
It tastes strange.
And very pungent.
Well then, time for the real thing.
El, please, anything but that.
I don't belong to you anymore.
You're deep inside of me again!
Stop it! Stop it!
If you treat me so roughly, I'll
Apparently... you're starting to enjoy it!
It's too rough!
If you're that rough with me, I'll break inside!
Darling, I'm sorry! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from another man!
I'm cumming!
Chris. Won't you become my wife?
In that case, I can love you every day.
No way. How could I be your wife?
Ernest...
Well if it isn't Princess Angelica.
Good morning.
Is it possible you’ve been like
that ever since yesterday?
Please, Ernest, take this thing out!
If not, I'll...
It's flowing out again!
It never lets me finish!
You must learn endurance.
In exchange, I will give you plenty
of affection when night falls.
But why?
I can't wait until tonight...
Angelica won't last much longer in that condition.
The only remaining problem is how to handle the king.
Who are you!?
I'm impressed that you dodged my sword.
For a human, your reflexes are quite nice.
You are a Dark Elf...
Oh? You know of me?
In that case, I need not explain myself.
You are the Ballistic Dancing Assassin.
That was your second name, was it not? Serafina.
Admit it, even you wish to see my dance.
Ernest.
Sorry, but I am not in the mood to
wield a sword at the moment.
Excuse me.
Ernest!
Are you frightened to clash swords with me?
And you call yourself a soldier of Roadshield?
You disgusting human! Leave this land at once!
This is not a place for a rat like you!
Serafina... can most likely be controlled by this.
Onii-sama, will you be out again tonight?
Yes. I apologize for causing you loneliness, Flora.
Don't say that... I will be fine.
More importantly, Onii-sama,
please don't push yourself too hard.
Thank you, Flora.
Onii-sama!
Well then, I'll be off.
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum for sure this time!
Yes! Yes!
This time, I'll cum for sure!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It stopped again. But why?
If you really want to cum that
badly, allow me to help you.
El!
You were spying, weren't you?
Spying on a princess in a naughty position!
It's coming again!
What did you make me swallow?
You must be tired of your body the way it is...
My eyes...
I'll help you finish as you wish.
Inside your dream, that is.
No! What is this?
No! This is disgusting!
Oh no! I can't lick something that smelly!
I don't want it!
How disgusting!
Slippery inside of my mouth!
I feel it! The tentacle penis is stroking me down there!
If you do that, I can't hold back!
If you twirl around inside of me, I'll lose my mind!
I don't care if I lose my mind!
Hurry and put it in!
Please burrow yourself into me!
I feel it coming in!
All the way into my uterus!
Where babies are made!
Yes, there! Yes there!
Harder! Plow me harder!
Wow... Wow!
Deeper... it's even deeper now!
You're cumming... you're cumming, aren't you?
You're releasing your smelly seed into me.
Into this noble princess's womb!
Yes!
Yes, I love it!
Just like that... Just like that...
Let me finish!
Yes! That's it!
Amazing, I feel it!
I'll definitely... I'll definitely cum this time!
I'm cumming!
It seems as though the monsters let you finish.
What was that?
A drug that I invented.
It showed you a very interesting dream.
So you mean to say I haven't actually...
Well then, what will you do?
Haven't you started to crave the real thing?
Please don't!
If you do that right now, I'm
sure to become your slave!
What's wrong with that?
I promise to make you satisfied.
That's it! Why don't you become my bride?
If I become your bride...
Does that mean you will satisfy me every night?
Oh my!
El! El! I can't hold out...
It's coming in!
I feel it! I feel it!
The penis that stole my virginity!
The penis that stole everything from me!
Looks like the prolonged foreplay paid off.
Amazing! Amazing!
Your penis, it's too amazing!
This feels wonderful!
El! El!
Harder! Deeper into me, please!
Just by being bonded with you, I feel like
you can give me everything I want!
Even though you're being fucked by a human?
What a horrible Elvish princess you are!
You're right!
I'm a horrible princess!
I am the worst princess ever!
Oh no! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
A dirty princess like you deserves this!
It's coming in... a human seed... into me...
No way... I thought Onii-sama was satisfied by only me.
You're horrible... Onii-sama!
Ernest...
It's no use.
Seeing a human always makes me feel this way.
No! No! No!
No!
I remember being raped by a band
of humans when I was a child.
You damned human! So you still
haven't left this land yet?
What is this?
Hold it up to the light.
You will see something interesting.
What is this?
Serafina would do something so naughty.
I would never have guessed the great
How dare you! Unhand me, Ernest!
Are you sure?
If you defy me, I will show this crystal
to everyone in the kingdom.
You bastard! What is your aim?
Easy there. I only want you to
help me with my scheme.
However, before that...
Wh-What are you doing?
Stop it!
Don't touch me with your disgusting hands!
What a disgusting body.
Is it because you had your first experience so young?
Fool! What're you... that's preposterous!
So you get wet very quickly with a human partner.
If you touch me like that, you won't... you won't...
You should become my woman.
Allow me to show you why.
Don't mess with me!
Who would be so crazy as to become your woman!?
Oh dear, you're flooding down here.
Even if my body succumbs,
you will never own my heart!
Playing strong again, I see...
When you're so wet like this,
your words don't have much weight.
Don't look!
It's not what you think!
Hey! What are you trying to do?
Don't tell me you're going to do it here?
What a nice face.
No! A disgusting human is inside of me!
How does it feel after so long?
You’ve had this on your mind
the whole time, haven't you?
It's coming inside... all the way inside!
Even to a painful part of me!
I'm begging you! Pull yourself out!
Surely you have been satisfied enough?
You want me to pull it out?
You're a horrible liar, you masochistic woman.
This coming from someone who masturbates while
thinking about being fucked by a gang of humans?
It's not what you think!
If you treat me this rough... I'll...
But being treated roughly and forcefully like
this really gets you off, right, Serafina?
I'll fill your thirsty uterus with
some disgusting human semen!
No! Don't do it! Please don't cum inside of me!
Today is... Today is my most dangerous day!
Stop it!
It... It's coming...
Coming all the way inside...
I'll get pregnant!
I'm going... to get pregnant...
Now you are my woman.
You must do as I say from now on.
You will never be forgiven.
I will see to it that you don't get away with this!
Here, Onii-sama.
Thank you, Flora.
Very nice.
Your tea is so delicious, Flora.
Oh, you mustn't say that, Onii-sama.
But it's true.
I feel all the exhaustion of the day slipping away.
Um, Onii-sama... If it suits you, today... can we...
Will you be with me?
Sorry, Flora.
I have night duty today as well.
Oh, no!
But, Onii-sama!
We'll have to do it some other time.
Flora?
Please don't leave, Onii-sama!
What are you saying?
This is an important job.
But I know the truth.
I know exactly what you're doing.
So please don't go to Princess Angelica!
So you knew, Flora?
Don't worry. I love you more than the others.
So don't cry.
Are you serious, Onii-sama?
Can I make love to you now? My Flora...
When you say something like that
to me, Onii-sama, I cannot refuse.
First, let me see you masturbate, Flora.
I'm a little shy about that, Onii-sama.
No... Flora's down there... it's all dirty.
Onii-sama, amazing!
It's all wet!
From this angle, I can see your
nastiness very well, Flora.
Just by you watching me, Onii-sama,
I am throbbing down there.
It feels wonderful!
I'm going to cum!
Right before your eyes, Onii-sama!
No! Don't watch, Onii-sama!
The naughty juice is flowing everywhere!
Oh, Onii-sama, you've become
so hard waiting, haven't you?
Onii-sama, you're so bitter and wet.
You’ve gotten very good at this, Flora.
Will you bury it in your mouth?
Yes, Onii-sama!
I'm almost there.
Can I cum in your mouth?
Then where?
Do you want me to put it down there?
You really are cute, Flora.
Onii-sama is going inside of me!
Onii-sama, you're excited. You're bigger than usual.
That's... That’s the inside of my small insides.
Oh no, Onii-sama, if you're that rough
with me, I will lose my mind!
Me too! I'm losing my mind!
Onii-sama, today is my dangerous day.
So please cum inside of me.
Are you sure? You'll get pregnant.
I want that. I want to birth your child, Onii-sama.
In that case...
The baby is coming into me!
My long journey for revenge was about to close its curtain.
Oh my, King Ernest!
Good morning, sire!
King Ernest.
Yes.
I have climbed to the top of
Roadshield, becoming its king.
Having taken the three of them to the extremes of pleasure,
they all took to my side, even thought I am human.
Even Serafina lies in the palm of my hand.
No one in this land dares defy me.
Like sows in heat, you all are!
Come in quickly, El.
Please punish your naughty Chris.
How cruel of you, Mother!
I have been anticipating him all day!
Don't forget me.
I want you in me right away, Onii-sama.
A human who usurped the throne.
The princess who fell under his spell.
It is only a matter of time before this kingdom falls.