Presently,
I am about to finalize my plan for revenge.
A plan that I have been formulating for a long time.
Four days have passed since I
imprisoned the elvish princess Angelica.
It appears she is about to break.
I cannot stand it!
It feels great!
Let me cum!
It's coming... It's coming...
This time, for sure.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
Why does it stop it?
I thought I would be able to finish this time.
Oh! It's begun again!
Amazing!
It's throbbing!
I'm going to break down there!
It feels great!
Let me cum!
It stopped again.
How cruel!
Why do you stop it?
Looks as though the torture has taken its effect.
El... El!
Let me cum, please!
I'm begging you, please let me cum!
And how exactly would you like me to help you cum?
You must give me specifics or I won't understand.
I may be a princess, but I am still a virgin.
I want you.
I want your big instrument inside of me down there.
Oh really? So you really want me that badly?
Well now...
Remind me again of who wants
what to be done to whom.
I, Angelica, Princess of the Elves,
wish to bestow my virginity upon
you, Ernest, a male human.
Don't taunt me!
It's inside!
It hurts, but feels great!
It's coming deeper!
Very nice, isn't it?
My hymen has been ruptured!
I am being violated by a human male!
I am no longer a virgin!
Amazing... It's going in deeper...
Angelica!
Your tongue is coming inside...
It's delicious.
I'm losing it...
Angelica!
Do it harder!
I want you to cum quickly!
I want you to release your seed into my dirty vagina!
Just you wait.
I'll put so much cum into your gross
vagina that you'll scream.
Do it inside!
It makes me so excited... to lose my virginity this way!
It's hitting me!
It's hitting my uterus!
A human man's disgusting seed... will fill me full!
It's coming... It's coming...
Yes! I'm cumming!
I m going to cum!
Angelica...
I'm about to cum too...
Cum! Cum, then!
Inside if my uterus...  Fill it with your dirty semen!
Angelica!
Inside of my uterus... Fill it with your dirty semen!
I'm about to... cum!
I'm cumming!
I feel the semen in my uterus...
Listen well, Angelica.
A band of knights will come to this place soon.
Just don't try anything funny.
I'm sure you know what this is.
Th-That's a Memory Crystal?
Don't tell me... You recorded everything up until now?
That's right.
Everything you've experienced here up until
this moment is recorded in this ball.
Oh... Oh no!
How cruel!
You will tell the knights that I rescued you.
If you fail to do this... I'm sure
you know what will result.
What is your mission?
Why did you use me like this?
I just want to send a message
to the Roadshield Kingdom.
If they think they owe a debt to me for rescuing you,
even the King of the Elves cannot refuse me.
Many days have passed since then.
As planned, I was recognized as Angelica's savior.
And I successfully infiltrated the Roadshield Kingdom.
Is it here?
So you are Flora?
Yes, Lord Ernest.
However, there was one provision...
A human like myself is not usually welcome among elves.
Um... I have been blind since I was a young child.
So... Lord Ernest...
So I will marry this girl, Flora, and join the family.
That is how I will work for the King.
It is still not too late for you.
I advise that you find another woman to be your bride.
L-Lord Ernest?
Flora...
This is an engagement ring.
What? A ring?
Yes. But it is no ordinary ring.
There is a power embedded in this ring that
works with your suppressed energy, Flora.
It cannot be!
I can see! My eyes!
What a dream!
Lord Ernest!
Are you happy?
That's good.
What's wrong?
Is there something on my face?
Um... I heard that humans were frightening beasts.
But you seem quite gentle, Lord Ernest.
And very handsome.
Well then. Will you become my wife?
Yes!
If little Flora is sufficient, please
make me your wife, Onii-sama!
"Onii-sama"?
Was that wrong of me?
I just thought that if you didn't mind...
That you would let me call you "Onii-sama".
I don't mind what you call me.
Call me as you wish.
Thank you, Onii-sama!
Um... Onii-sama, if you don't
mind, will you take me now?
Flora?
Onii-sama...
Flora, you're very pretty.
Don't twirl my nipples around so much!
Oh no! Onii-sama!
Your body sure is sensitive, Flora.
If you're that rough with me, I will... I will...
Oh no, Onii-sama! You mustn't touch me there!
Not there! Not there!
You mustn't do that!
Onii-sama... Your fingers are...
What is this wetness?
I'm sorry. I'm such a dirty girl!
You sure are cute, Flora.
Onii-sama! Not so directly...
Yes!
Onii-sama, not my breasts too!
If you do that...
You're going to cum, right, Flora?
Onii-sama! I'm frightened!
Please, hold me tight!
It's no use, Onii-sama!
I cannot go on!
Then... You may cum, Flora.
Onii-sama! Onii-sama! Onii-sama!
That was amazing, Onii-sama.
You were really cute, Flora.
Onii-sama...
This time, let me become your wife by your penis.
Are you sure, Flora?
Yes. I wish to bestow my virginity on you, Onii-sama.
Are you really sure, Flora?
Yes... Onii-sama.
I'm coming in, Flora.
Go ahead.
I want you inside of me, Onii-sama.
Are you okay?
Yes! I am.
Amazing!
Onii-sama! You're coming in so deep!
Ouch...
It feels great!
I feel it! I feel you inside of me, Onii-sama!
Please move more!
Flora!
Onii-sama, I love you.
This feels amazing, Onii-sama! Onii-sama!
Flora! I'm going to cum...
Then cum inside of me. Keep cumming inside of me.
Fill me with yourself, Onii-sama!
Flora... I'm cumming, Flora!
It's coming. Your warm juice is
flowing into me, Onii-sama.
Onii-sama, I love you. I love you so much!
Onii-sama... I love it.
I feel wonderful.
You belong only to me, Onii-sama.
Onii-sama...
It's about time to disclose why I am here.
For revenge.
I came here to get revenge against a certain woman.
Christina Roadshield.
The woman I once loved.
And the woman who betrayed me.
El...
Yes?
El!?
Chris.
It's been awhile!
No! El!
So you're still angry about that?
Of course I am!
That day, you promised me we would
flee this kingdom together!
But that day... Why didn't you come!?
I had no choice.
If I abandoned my people,
my father would have killed me!
So you're saying you sold me out to your country?
That day, I was almost killed by your father's men!
I'm so sorry, El!
I'm so sorry!
El!
I am no longer the El you once knew!
I am nothing more than a man
who's come here for revenge!
No!
Stop it, El!
Your body has gotten so nasty...
What disgusting breasts!
Don't do it, El! Don't!
You mustn't go further!
Why not? Is it turning you on?
That's not it!
If you go further, I'll... cum out of my breasts.
What a surprise.
Did the king bewitch you with this?
El... you mustn't do this.
Please... it won't stop...
Please, El, tease me no more!
Don't touch my breasts!
You perverted whore.
You get so turned on just from
having your breasts squeezed?
Now, Chris, you must clean this with your tongue.
Please... no more.
You used to be so...
Don't be so rough.
I'll do as you say.
You'll do as I say?
In that case, take off your clothes.
And show me your naughty spot.
I can't...
Now, hurry!
You're already wet.
El, don't stare at me so much.
It's embarrassing.
El? You mustn't do that!
I have a husband!
That is no concern of mine!
That hurts!
You may cry like a virgin, but it won't make me stop!
That's not it!
It's just that it's been a very long
time since I've done this!
So rough! Be more gentle.
Please, El. Be more gentle!
If you're that rough with me, I'll break!
You call this rough?
I haven't even started yet!
El... you're coming in again...
El! Please stop!
Not like this!
Not there!
Not again... I'll cum again!
You dirty whore!
Now, time to finish.
I'll fill you full of myself!
No! El, anything but that.
What if I get pregnant?
Too late for that!
You came.
Your semen is coming into my uterus!
El, you're cruel.
You're too cruel.
Put your back into it more!
With that form, you'll never be a good fighter!
You sure have a lot of spirit, Angelica.
Ernest? What did you come here to do?
Calm down. I just wanted to talk to you.
But I do not wish to speak to you!
You are interfering with my trainings.
Vacate this place at once!
Are you sure it's okay to speak to me that way?
Th-That's...
You're making me do this again?
It's very stinky.
Are you washing yourself?
Now that you mention it,
I haven't washed it in a while.
Rotten!
What a horrible man you are!
Wash it at once!
No need for that.
I'll have you wash it with your mouth right now.
Stop it! It's slimy.
It's disgusting...
Be pleased, Angelica, I will cum in your mouth.
Releasing such a foul smelling
substance into my mouth...
You are horrible! You are horrible!
Now your other mouth.
Uncover your ridiculously large ass and push it my way.
It's getting bigger!
Getting bigger inside of me!
It's throbbing... this whole time...
You're horrible! You really are the worst man ever!
Oh no... Oh wow!
Oh no... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too.
Take it, Angelica!
Your disgusting semen...
I'll get pregnant!
Very nice squeeze, Angelica.
You're horrible... Using me like this... Horrible!
You're horrible!
And to reward you for your services,
I have a present for you.
A present?
Could this... Don't tell me...
The thing from last time?
I’ve set it to stop when you've reached
the summit of your pleasure.
No! Take it off! Take it off me!
Well then, how much can you withstand, Angelica?
Just you wait, Chris.
Your family... No, your whole stinking kingdom.
I will bring it to destruction!
Along with your daughter!