Maika-sama, I'll go wake Yahiro-sama up.
Yahiro-sama, you should wake up now.
Yahiro-sama?
Y-Yahiro-sama!?
Maika...
Yes...
It's me, Maika.
I will tend to your needs.
When compared to saving Maika-sama
and talking to me in such a kind manner,
this may not be enough...
Uhh... Mai...
H-Huuuh! S-Sakuno-san!?
Maika-sama will hear us if you raise your voice.
Stay like that, alright?
Yahiro-sama, your robust dick...
It seems to be already awake.
Master, I'll give your dick plenty of service.
It's huge!
So this robust dick made
Maika-sama a woman...
I also want to experience that same feeling...
...from your dick, Yahiro-sama!
Please give me your thick semen!
Yahiro-sama, shoot it out!
Wow! There's so much coming out!
Wh-What are you two doing?
Yahiro! Sakuno!
Stop messing around! Open the door!
Yahiro-sama, please give your dick to my pussy!
Your tongue and finger are caressing me so much!
Right there! This feels way better
than when I finger myself!
I'm being seen by a man for the first time!
This is too embarrassing, Yahiro-sama!
Your dick is going inside me!
Hey! Yahiro! Sakuno!
You can't go any further—!
This is the proof of my first time
being made a woman!
The pain is fading away!
Yahiro-sama, I want it harder!
Please drive me crazy!
Sakuno, stop messing around! You too, Yahiro!
Hey, open up!
Yahiro-sama!
I love this!
Yahiro-sama, you're filling me up deep inside!
If I end up being unable to forget this feeling, I'm...
Give it to me, Yahiro-sama!
I want to have your semen in my pussy!
There's so much inside me!
I'm full of your semen!
Open the door, you two!
Yahiro! Sakuno!
Y-You two!
Huh?
Huh? Sakuno? Yahiro...
Maika-sama, I'm glad that you're okay!
You fainted so I was worried
if you had heatstroke!
You looked dead tired out there.
U-Uhh... Is that so...
You looked like you're having a bad dream.
Are you alright, Maika-sama?
Sakuno... Yes, I'm alright.
Did you happen to have a nightmare?
Huh!? M-Maika-sama!?
I had that dream because Yahiro has been teasing me.
He keeps doing weird stuff to me!
Are you okay? You're acting strange
since you woke up. Are you...
Does this feel good?
I'm gonna tease him as well.
Yahiro, aren't you quite a pervert
to have this thing out in the open?
Your dick gets hard wherever
you are. You're so naughty.
That's not true.
You're letting your dick
get stiff at a place like this.
You're definitely a pervert!
I might not be able to make you
feel as good as Sakuno.
She's on another level...
Sakuno-san?
Huh? Ouch...
Sorry, I hit it with my teeth. Didn't that hurt?
It seems okay...
That was close! What am I even saying?
He seems to be feeling really
good from this, though.
Wow... That feels great, Maika...
I see...
I'm glad...
Even though I'm going hard on him...
Yahiro, you can shoot it out
when you feel like coming...
There's too much!
H-Hey, Maika!
That was more than usual!
You really are a pervert.
You're also being too lewd right now!
Huh? Wait, are those people?
Maika-sama! Yahiro-sama!
Looks like there are other visitors.
I thought that nobody else will be here...
I should go back to the yacht then...
Ah, Yahiro-sama! My pussy feels amazing!
Uhh... I'm tired.
This is a surprisingly popular tourist trap.
Oh yeah, it looks like you can go
to the upper deck from here.
Wanna go there?
Oh... Sounds interesting.
Oh, this is cool! Hey, Yahi—
Huh!? N-No... Wait!
What are you doing in this situation?
I said stop!
Haven't you been wet since earlier?
No, this is too much!
No, Yahiro... My legs will give out!
Please stop that!
Will you be fine like this?
It's deep inside!
Wh-While at a place like this, I-I'm...
Hey, won't we end up getting caught?
Let's just do it the normal way...
They shouldn't be able to see anything with this.
H-Hey! Why are you going harder?
Your girlfriend has been
asking you not to! Gosh!
I love you so much, Maika.
Huh?
Jeez! Stop flattering me, you idiot!
You're always being mean to me! You're awful!
You... No, jeez...
No way! If this goes on, I'm...
While at such a place and looking like this, I'm...
No, I'm coming!
I'm... Coming...
Coming... I'm coming! I'm coming—!
Yahiro, your amazing stuff is pouring in!
I want to know everything about you, Maika!
Huh? Hey... Yahiro! Wh-What are you doing?
No way! I don't want to do it anymore!
Th-That's the wrong hole!
Hey, I can't take any more of this! No!
H-Hey, what's this? This can't be...
Didn't I tell you that I don't want that, Yahiro!?
It'll feel good when you get used to it.
No! I don't want to get used
to something like this!
No—! It went in...
It feels tight! Why are you
making such a disgusting face?
It's coming out! It's coming out!
No! No, I don't want this!
No!
You already got a little bit
slippery down here.
Shut up!
You sound happy while
harassing your girlfriend!
You're a brute!
No way, what's happening?
Even though I don't want this...
Maika, it won't be long...
You idiot! Get this over with already!
I don't want any more of this!
So you're felling good too...
That's never gonna happen!
Not from such a weird part...
I can't put to words how it feels now
compared to earlier! But that's...
Hurry up and come!
And then pull it out! This is already too much!
Alright, let's do it together.
Huh!? Not there!
Don't tease me down there!
Wait! No, no way!
If you keep doing that, I'm...
No way... Why? No...
No! Wait, this is making me... No way!
This can't be real! I'm coming
from having my ass penetrated!
There's so much flowing into my ass!
No way, I came...
Even though it was my ass...
That was great, Maika...
Great my foot!
You're a perverted brute!
I'm getting hit by sunlight.
I-I'm sorry for that.
I'm thirsty.
Here you go.
I'll work your ass off well for the whole day.
You force your girlfriend
even if she doesn't want to.
You're such a beast! Feel some remorse!
It's my fault. I got carried away...
You always say that.
Everything about you is so lovely!
I mean, even your asshole
twitches and it looks cute...
Y-Y-You never understood anything!
You lowly pervert!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji