The Empire of the Dark Elves, Keltula, decided to use the war against the
Garland Empire as an opportunity to begin their conquest of the continent.
After overtaking the Garland and Marshall Empires, they aimed at the
Lindegald Empire of the Mitoras Continent.
However the in the country of Lindegald, created by the Overlord Ashbell,
was a battling nation that has had a long history, they had a high morale
thanks to their Queen and strongest magic-swordsman, Olivia, and are
deterring the Keltula army.
But the Keltula had as their ally Cecil  who was known as most evil
warrior in history. Under his lead, the Fourth Corp turned the war in
Keltula’s favor.
Cecil, who was also smart and cunning, then used treacherous tactics to
break the alliance between Lindegald and its neighbour, the Elfinrine
Empire.
Keltula and Elfinrine then signed a No-War treaty between them.
The Lindegald Army, known to be the strongest in the continent, was now forced to battle with the army mixed of men and elves lead by Cecil.
Then, half year after the war began, after 423 long years of pride and glory, the Lindegald Empire surrendered.
In exchange for the 5000 lives that were captive, Olivia offered herself as a hostage and had to follow any orders no matter how humiliating...
Princess Knight Olivia
You Filthy Monster! Even if This Body is Stained, I Will Never Become Yours!
Training: 01
Translation Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by erobeat | http://www erabeat.net | #erobeat @ ircr.rizon.net
Ally of Keltula: Eilfinrine
Capital: The City of Elfinly
Don't joke around!
You're the one who killed Bruno!
Who would ever become your mistress!
You're not a mistress, just a meat toilet to satisfy sexual urges.
How filthy...
If I had to be dirtied by someone like you, I'd rather die!
Unfortunately, our country is a little short on women.
To make up for that,
the captives have to carry out a certain "sleeping load" with men.
What are you talking about?
I'm just suggesting it might be a little
better than to be raped continuously
by excited men who have just returned from the battlefield.
K-Kill me!
If I'm going to be used as a prostitute for you Keltula people,
I'd rather be executed!
Do you hate Keltula that much?
Of course!
You guys killed my fiancé!
That can't be helped then, then you will have to work with...
Let me introduce them: these are the elite of our troops.
Orcs?
We modified the Orc species with magic.
They're great at battle, of course, but their most amazing feature
is that they are able to impregnate human females as well.
We have to replenish the people we lost in war.
I guess we'll have you give birth to lots of children for the empire.
No way... you're joking right?
Be thankful, a criminal's children will be able
to live as soldiers serving the empire.
Although they'll be orcs.
No! Don't come over here!
Guys, this is your new bride.
Be sure to love her lots.
Eh... Don't come... No!
By the way, did you say your fiancé was Bruno?
He's on the verge of death from battle, but he did survive.
No...
Once he's healed I'll let you guys meet.
Although you'll be an orc's wife bearing an orc's child by then...
You can't...
No... please stop...
Mercy please! I'm... still a virgin!
I don't want my first time to be with an orc... no!
That won't fit! Stop!
Someone help me! Bruno!
Bruno!
I'll break... stop!
Help...!
I'll die...
It came... inside....
No, no...
I don't want this!
No... Stop already!
How is it, Princess Olivia?
How cruel of you, you monster!
Stop blaming the wrong person.
This is naturally the result of pointing her sword
at our army despite you becoming a hostage.
Stop already!
If it is anyone's fault, it is yours for acting thoughtlessly.
Think about it.
How is it that you can exchange yourself for as many as 5000 lives?
It's because you are the queen of an empire.
Think about your position in this situation.
Like I said before, that collar in an artifact
that seals your magic power.
If you try to use magic, it will rebound onto you
and stimulate your instincts to reproduce.
And yet you used such a powerful technique...
Your body must be uncontrollably in heat right now, right?
I cannot stand such humiliation!
Kill me! Kill me instead of the 5000 captives!
Like I said the punishment in our country
is a "sleeping load" you must carry out.
I'll have you work hard with that slutty body.
Stop, stop it! Don't touch... Ah, no!
As a knight who loses to no man, you have quite a feminine body.
Don't touch me with those filthy hands!
As expected you are in heat from the rebound magic.
That's not true!
Then, are you getting excited from getting hit?
There's no such... stop it!
As the leader of a troop, you are doing such
things so a woman who can't fight back...
Aren't you embarrassed?
Not at all. In fact, I'm quite enjoying it.
Pervert! You perverted beast! Be ashamed of yourself.
That's my line, aren't you embarrassed
that your nipples are so hard?
To think that a pure girl, who hasn't even fondled herself before,
would get so wet from a man's hands on her chest...
Aren't you the one who's the slutty pervert?
No, that's not... this is... No!
I'll satisfy your burning urges...
Stop, stop this at once!
What is this... I've never had such a sensation before...
Why does it feel good when I am touched?
Even though I'm being touched by such a horrible guy...
Why can't I resist...
Even though he's a filthy barbarian...
why won't my body do what I say?
A man's hands are... on my boobs...
Even though I don't want this... even though
no one's touched them before...
Why does my stomach tingle when my boobs are touched?!
No! Something's coming! It feels so good, something is...
What? No!
I can't stop!
Was that the first time you came?
That is what's called an orgasm.
Orgasm? Came?
When pleasure overloads and explodes, and your
body wants a man so much it can't control itself.
That's can't be it! I'm a Queen... there's
no way something so filthy...
It's about time I get you to plead your
slavery to us like I told you earlier.
No way!
You want to save your captive people, right?
Or are you going to leave them to be fed to orcs?
Don't...
Then finish your job, your obligation of
protecting your people, as their Queen.
I, Olivia Lindegald, swear to be my master,
Cecil Calbat's personal meat toilet!
Please use any hole at any time and place as you wish!
That's a deal.
How cruel... it was my first time...
Now, open your legs by yourself.
Not something so embarrassing...
Have you forgotten your oath already?
If you break the contract I can't guarantee
the lives of the captives...
I get it.
To think that you'd open your legs to a man... you
can't show this side to your people, can you?
You must bear it, Olivia! For the sake of the
captive people, this humiliation is nothing...
No, not there!
This place is throbbing and wanting it, right?
There's no way...no... stop!
No!
No, no...!
Don't let go of your legs.
No, don't look!
Such a beautiful shape and color.
As expected a Royal's pussy is different.
Don't say such embarrassing things...
Stop... it's dirty...
What is this? Such filthy things are being done to me
at yet my body can't bring the strength to resist!
I don't want this, but that sensation is coming again!
Don't! Anymore is... I'll...!
No way...! Please spare me of that!
I have to give my chastity to the man who will become King! So...!
Are you still dreaming?
You were sold by your country.
This part of you to.
Then as least, let my first time be with a loved one...
Oh, so you want the captive girls to
bear more children of the orcs?
That's...
If you want the captives to be saved, plead as written here.
There's no way I could ever say something so shameless!
Isn't it your duty as Queen?
Please break the hymen of the princess-pussy I've been protecting,
with Master's meat stick, and make me a grown woman!
Guess I can't refuse a princess' request.
Oww! Is this the so-called pain of deflowering?
Remember, this is the meat stick that made you a woman
And your Master's dick which you will be serving for life!
Ouch! Don't move...
What is this?
It hurts down there... but deeper inside it's getting hot...
A first experience while the body is in full heat...
the pain will become pleasure right away...
I'm being violated by a man I hate... and yet
every time he thrusts my mind goes blank!
I don't want this... but my body... on its own...!
N-No! Don't... forgive me already!
What are you saying?
Your job will be to serve me like this every day from now on.
That's... no!
If I go through such humiliation every day, I...
I won't be able to take it!
I'll go crazy!
I'll pour my seed, into that slutty body of yours.
Eh? If you do that... I'll bear a child!
Doesn't really matter, does it?
No! Not that!
I can't myself bear the child of an enemy!
Then bear it, and show it to your people!
Tell them that it was their fault you
were played with and impregnated!
No! I don't want that!
I beg you mercy! I'll do anything, just not that, please!
Get pregnant!
No!
No, it's coming out...
A filthy beast is ejaculating inside me... I'll get pregnant!
What is this sensation?
I don't want this and yet pleasure is flowing through my body!
No... It feels so good I'll go crazy!
How is the pleasure of slavery?
It's beyond anything in this world, isn't it?
Wh-What?
Through my seed I engraved a symbol of slavery into you.
Now your body will automatically orgasm
when I ejaculate inside you.
And a curse has been activated so that your body will
uncontrollably lust after any man if
you are not given my semen daily.
You vulgar...
I'll never forgive you.
Be sure to do your job well, starting tomorrow...
That's right, put a full mind into serving me.
That chastity belt is directly linked to my sexual urge.
It'll tell you how well you are serving me.
I'm cumming. If you don't want to be cursed, don't spill it.
This is just a beginning.
I'll train you so you'll be able to cum from
fellatio even without me ejaculating.
No!
Forgive me! Not out here!
Someone will see!
I've set up a barrier so moan all you want!
I can't do... such things...
I'm cumming, Olivia!
Not inside! I'm really gonna get pregnant!
Not that, forgive me!
Savour my seed well!
No!
No... he came inside again... if this goes on I'll really...
No...
Not there...
If you keep attacking me weak spots...
Again... I was so close...
Please, let me cum! I'll go crazy from this!
Have you forgotten that, as a punishment for refusing to serve me,
you have to withstand this for three days
so that I don't harm the captives?
It's only the second day, you know.
But... Ever since the morning I've been
on the brink of cumming and...
You were the one to say that you didn't want to cum
anymore after cumming all day and night yesterday,
so I've make it that you don't cum today.
That's...
Again!
If you don't take this until night tomorrow, I'll
just take the heads of 10 captives I guess.
Don't!
They've been attacking me for so long, it feels good right away...
Gonna cum... why did you stop?
Not again... no!
She's using magic unconsciously and activating the artifact...
And her withdrawal symptoms from
lack of my semen are increasing...
I guess this is enough to drive even Olivia to her limit.
No! Let me cum!
If you serve me properly I'll make you cum, and the
captives won't have to die either, you know.
If you cum inside anymore, I'm really gonna get pregnant...
As the Queen I just can't bear the child of an enemy...
Don't! No! Stop moving!
If you don't want to serve me, then you're
like this until tomorrow night.
Wait!
No! Don't... not there... stop!
Let me cum! Please! Forgive me!
I won't forgive you... I'll never forgive you!!
Yes...no, don't stop...
Don't!
Don't! There... too good... I'll....
No... I don't want to feel good anymore...!
Don't... cumming...
Forgive me already... I'll do anything... I said I'll do anything!
I’ll die!
Kill me! I'm gonna die, so kill me!
Well done for enduring it, Olivia.
As promised I'll guarantee the captive's lives.
Well why don't you start your service for tonight.
But... just till now I was...
Don't misunderstand, up to just now was a punishment
for refusing to serve me three days ago.
Today's service is separate from that.
Or do you want the save punishment again?
No way...
I haven't slept for three days and yet...
No way... I'll break...
Well, let s use the princess' pussy that
I haven't touched for three days.
No, if you put it in right now I'll cum...
You've been wanting to cum though, right?
No... stop... I don't want to cum from someone like you...
Cumming!
I came... even though I can't... even though it's an enemy's dick...
No, no...
Stop already...
No... I'll... cum again!
I don't want to but...
Please! I came already... so...
Even though you're saying that, the entrance of your
womb is sucking on my dick begging for it!
No way! It won't fit!
Cumming... cumming again!
Stop it! Stop cumming!
What is this?! It's so good I'll go crazy!
Even though I want to kill him!
It's so good I'll die!!
No... I'll cum... I'll die...
Even though as princess I can't allow myself
to feel it from some guy like this...
My body cums on its own!
It's feeling good on its own!
About time I pour my seed inside you.
No! Not inside!
He's violating me all the way inside my
womb; the sperm will go deep inside!
I'll really get pregnant!
Bear my child, Olivia!
No! He came again!
Sperm is rampaging inside as if trying to impregnate me!
I don't want this, I can't do this! But the more
I think so the more my body tries to cum!
I'll die... no...
Someone stop this! Stop me from going crazy like this!
Or else I... I won't be able to remain as princess...
I'll bear a child of a monster...
The night is still long.
I'll make sure you cum over and over again until sunrise.
Don't worry, even if you break, I'll fix
you with magic and keep going.
You can go crazy all you want.
I guess you can't expect her to do morning services after being violated all night.
But with this, I should have her in the habit of wanting to cum.
About time I raise the level of training...
Cecil!
Hmm?
Oh my, Princess Teresa, I mean, Lieutenant of the Second Corp, Ma'am.
What has brought you to such a remote area?