The Empire of the Dark Elves, Keltula, decided to use the war against the
Garland Empire as an opportunity to begin their conquest of the continent.
After overtaking the Garland and Marshall Empires, they aimed at the
Lindegald Empire of the Mitoras Continent.
However the in the country of Lindegald, created by the Overlord Ashbell,
was a battling nation that has had a long history, they had a high morale
thanks to their Queen and strongest magic-swordsman, Olivia, and are
deterring the Keltula army.
But the Keltula had as their ally Cecil  who was known as most evil
warrior in history. Under his lead, the Fourth Corp turned the war in
Keltula’s favor.
Cecil, who was also smart and cunning, then used treacherous tactics to
break the alliance between Lindegald and its neighbour, the Elfinrine
Empire.
Keltula and Elfinrine then signed a No-War treaty between them.
The Lindegald Army, known to be the strongest in the continent, was now forced to battle with the army mixed of men and elves lead by Cecil.
Then, half year after the war began, after 423 long years of pride and glory, the Lindegald Empire surrendered.
In exchange for the 5000 lives that were captive, Olivia offered herself as a hostage and had to follow any orders no matter how humiliating...
Princess Knight Olivia
You Filthy Monster! Even if This Body is Stained, I Will Never Become Yours!
Training: 02
Translation Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by erobeat | http://www erabeat.net | #erobeat @ ircr.rizon.net
It's all alright now, Princess Teresa.
I've taken care of all the people who kept you captive.
I was so scared!
You have endured greatly.
As expected from the princess of the noble dark elves.
Now, let's go home.
Cecil!
Hey now, Princess, that is very unladylike.
I told you to call me Teresa when there's just the two of us!
Yes, I understand, Teresa.
Why is that so?
Even though I’ve agreed?
In Keltula, a human like me can't become an internal guard.
That's ridiculous!
The person who's protected me has always been Cecil!
And it still should to be Cecil who protects me from now on!
The army rules are set to be like that...
I get it.
If Cecil can't become a guard, I'll join the army!
And I'll make you my subordinate, so you'll be beside me always!
You got a promotion again, Cecil?
If this goes on, I'll never get to be your superior!
Please take it more slowly!
Don't be unreasonable.
For a human, chances like these don't come by every day.
Listen, Cecil is meant to become my
subordinate and serve me for life!
Don't leave off to somewhere on your own!
You absolutely cannot leave Keltula!
Cecil!
Oh my, oh my, it is Princess Teresa.
I mean, the Second Corp's Vice Captain.
What is your highness doing at distant area like this?
That sounds fake, Cecil.
Spare that hypocritical courtesy of yours.
Well then, Teresa.
Why are you here?
There's only one possibility.
I'm keeping an eye on the person standing there, you.
You've been doing sh-shady things to captive women, haven't you?
And what is wrong with that?
What I am doing, any frontline commander is doing so.
It counts as part of our rewards in exchange for lower pay.
Y-you can't!
You alone are not allowed such things!
I have no idea what you are talking about.
Anyways it is no!
I will report this to my father, no, to us Majesty.
And then you'll be called back to the main force.
You'd better start packing.
Geez, maybe it's because she's a woman as well,
she's always been fussy about anything involving women, this girl.
Or could she be sent by someone who wants
to hinder me from more achievements?
Either way, I can't let her stop me here.
I guess it can't be helped.
Teresa.
What, what it is?
Are you offering some excuse or explanation?
No, I just had,
some things I wanted to ask you.
Teresa.
I'll be asking your body.
The crybaby kiddo has become quite a woman, Teresa.
Help won't come.
I've already gotten your subordinates to go home.
Using this Marionette Ring to control you.
Don't glare like that.
It ruins your cute face.
Wait now,
I'm going, to help your investigation,
by telling you what I've been doing.
Directly to your body, that is.
The key to interrogation of captive women is humiliation.
If you don't want me to go any farther, answer me:
Who ordered you to come all the way here
near the borders, and what is your aim?
You bastard! Don't you think that you'll get away with this!
I see.
Teresa won't talk until you feel good some more, right?
Well then.
Although I've already asked her while possessing
her with the Marionette Ring and I know it all.
To think that Teresa had been in love with me...
No wonder she was always fussy about women around me.
But with this, I'll be able to make her complete a pawn of mine.
This is a potion that will make your chest as sensitive as a clitoris.
There's also the side effect that you will
produce milk if you reach an orgasm.
It's about time, isn't it?
How is it? Good, isn't it?
Then, what you say is that being caressed by
someone like me will never arouse you?
You have to learn to be more honest, or you
won't get the attention of boys you like.
Well, when breast milk comes out like this, we know
you came no matter how you try to hide it.
Seems like your mind can't handle all the information
of producing milk for the first time.
But, even more stimulation is coming up.
Do you know, Teresa?
The reason why female elves are prohibited
from having a relationship with a human?
That is because...
Once you have sex with a human,
the feeble elf male won't be able to satisfy you.
How is it?
Any thoughts on having your noble elf
virginity taken by a lowly human?
I guess you won't know until I give you a better taste of it.
Is it painful?
It will become pleasure soon.
Even more so, once knowing the pleasure of this,
female elves become slaves of this twisted pleasure.
Teresa Keltula. The noble princess of the dark elves.
What about you?
A captive with such rebellious eyes...
Looks like you need harder interrogation!
What, have you already fallen to the pleasure with a human?
You've got none of the elegance or dignity of a dark elf, have you?
Do you like the taste of a human dick that much?
What a disgraceful princess.
We should let the Keltula people know, too.
That Teresa is a slutty princess who gets
aroused being raped by a human!
So are you saying you're not feeling good while being so wet?
I'll know even if you hide it.
C'mon, just admit honestly.
Admit that sex with a human feels good!
I guess can't be helped.
I will have to use the creampie torture.
What, did you want to get creampied that much?
You've suddenly gotten tighter.
Now, bear the child of a human.
Elf Princess!
It shows so obviously that you've cum.
As expected you were aroused.
My first experience with Cecil that I've always dreamed of...
to think that it'd turn out forced like this... how cruel.
How is it? Having a human as your first.
On top, getting creampied and dimming from it?
You bastard...
Don't you dare think that you'd get away with doing such things!
How stubborn.
Should I try something different and
continue with the interrogation?
Don't think that you'll be able to control
me with... such a... thing...
You're so mean!
You made Teresa such a slutty princess...
You were the one who wanted me to violate you dressed like this.
Saying that you wanted to feel what it's like
to be a princess violated by a lowly human,
how perverted are you?
But... Cecil's human dick... just feels so good!
My pussy that's been thrusted and spread...
just can't be satisfied by by elf dicks anymore!
That not it! That's not what I'm thinking!
I am a noble and prideful knight princess!
I'm not a pervert!
Cecil's dick!
Human dick!
Give more to Teresa's pussy!
I'm a princess, but I'm being violated from behind like a dog!
I'm becoming a bitch!
Even though I'd never get excited from mating like an animal...
If my people were ever to see me like this...
Are you feeling good from being violated in such
a position where even your butt hole is visible?
Yes! Being forced and violated while having
my butthole exposed feels good!
Cecil! Cecil!
No! We kissed...
I'm happy I had my first kiss with Cecil...
But not like this!
Teresa... is going to break!
I love you! I love you, Cecil!
No! I do love Cecil, but...
Having these things done to me... even if it feels good...
No...
Teresa... Teresa won't be able to be
with any other dick than Cecil’s!
I'll do anything... I'll bear Cecil's child!
No! I can't let that happen!
I can't let that happen as the princess!
I'll be the semen toilet for Cecil!
So please keep fucking me with your dick!
That's not it! This isn't me!
It's coming! Cecil's seed is coming again!
I'll get pregnant! I'll bear Cecil's child!
No!!
Even if it's Cecil, that can't happen!
Cecil... I love you...
No... this is wrong...
The Cecil who does these things... I hate him...
Even though I hate him...
A week after that. Teresa's training is going well.
As for Olivia...
Diethard doesn't understand anything!
Sir Calvart...
Please excuse me.
Sophia?
No, that's impossible.
Sophia died a long fifteen years ago.
Besides, she is too young to be Sophia.
And wasn't she an elf?
Nonetheless, how similar.
I-I'm here.
You're late, Olivia.
You've gotten much better.
As expected you learn fast.
Princess Olivia is truly excellent.
Even if you say such things, I won't be happy!
Please hurry and end it...
If so, I suggest you stop worrying about your
surrounding and just make me cum instead.
Here I go.
Drink it gratefully. I came for your sake.
Good job. You drank it all, right?
Where are you going?
I've already serviced you with my mouth, haven't I!?
Do you think you've satisfied me with just that?
Now, if you want to save your people,
let's move onto the next service.
You've also learned the proper ways
to use those busty boobs, huh?
How dare you use... my chest... for such things...
Now let's get you to do the next service.
Put on this bracelet.
You even made me wear this swimsuit, what are you doing?
What is this!?
That is the bracelet of life.
It returns your body to the age when
it is most filled with life energy.
Such an magic item...
No!
Stop! Not this...
So you had such slutty boobs since you were born, Princess Olivia?
Of course not, you pervert!
Are you planning to... violate me like this!?
You've got to try something new once in a while.
I'd like to have lots of different tastes of the princess.
Even though the body was changed,
the developed senses are retained, huh?
This will be fun.
No, not there!
Don't lick... such places!
As expected from the young, a strong smell.
No! You pervert!
I'll kill you some day!
If you receive sperm while you have such high life energy inside,
you'll be sure to get pregnant.
No, stop!
I don't want to bear your child!
Then, let's test this drug.
No!
What? Something cold went deep inside...
What? What did you put in?
It's a 100% effective contraceptive drug.
No... you can't!
Something that large won't fit!
My pussy will break!
If it breaks, I'll fix it with healing magic.
No! You can't, it was too large even before!
If you put it in now...
No!
Oh? Even your hymen regenerated, huh?
To think that you gave me your virginity
twice... what a loyal cumdump of you.
It hurts!
My body... is tearing...
Pull out... your penis...
A cumdump doesn't get to make a choice.
It hurts!
The vagina is shallow... I hit the entrance right away.
Not all of my dick fits.
By the way, the drug just now...
In exchange for preventing you from getting pregnant,
it will react with sperm and swell multiple times in volume.
It's narrow and very tight, this is great.
Now, I'm cumming.
Don't worry since there's no way you'll get pregnant.
No!
We went all the way to get contraception,
yet you still got a big stomach.
I'll make your chest more sensitive, too.
No!
My chest...
It's hot!
Why is there milk!? Could it be...
Don't worry; it's a side effect of the aphrodisiac.
But now you really look like a pregnant woman.
No!
Oh, it's taken me all the way in.
This is great. It's like I'm violating a meathole.
You won't get pregnant, so I can cum inside all I want.
Stop... it hurts... I'll break...
I'll die... I'm going to die...
No!
No... my stomach is already full and yet it's still expanding...
My womb will break...
It's coming out!
Hmm?
The ring lost its effect.
Looks like it still needs adjustments.
Oh, so that's how it traps the semen.
It's almost like you are giving birth to eggs.
One day I will make you bear my child for real.
Violating a big-stomach princess will be some good entertainment
Come in.
Excuse me.
Um... Uh... My name is Rola Elfinrine..
For the sake of the friendship between the two countries...
I've been sent to become the wife... of Cecil Calvart-Sama
Although I am the youngest child... best
regards and nice to meet you...