The inside of my stomach; my pussy is shivering!
My ass is being spread wide.
Why does it feel so good?
Mother, tell me why? Tell me! You never told me about this...
I'm cumming! I'm cimming! I'm cimming!
Fool. Princess Lilia's energy could never be
contained or absorbed by a being like you.
Dirk-sama, you should not have trifled with demons.
You thought you could use me however you wanted?
You're a hundred years too young for that!
What did you say!? Females under the age of
30 are now prohibited from wearing clothes!?
Th-This can't be happening...
No way! This is nonsense!
Sweet! Are you serious!?
Oh shut up, you perv!
What's that? Girls must walk around naked now?
From tomorrow on, by order of Dirk-sama, no female may
wear any clothing between her shoulders and her thighs.
From the shoulders down to the thighs!?
That's almost the same as being naked, isn't it!?
No way in Hell I'm doing that.
Do guys have to get naked too?
Males are prohibited from laving a hand on the females!
What about our dignity!?
Filthy lowly rabble like you have no dignity to begin with!
This is the command of King Dirk!
Vol. 5 Joyful Imprisonment, Chiriko and Leila
Himekishi Lilia
Dirk-sama, did you call for me?
Yes.
What do you need?
Chiriko! What happened to my orders!?
Yes, everything was done according to your orders.
Indeed, the girls of the town are now forbidden
from wearing even one piece of clothing.
The maids of this castle have also been changed to Dirk-sama's tastes.
Do you like it?
Hey! The two of you, turn around and show
yourselves. Give Dirk-sama a good look!
O-Okay...
Pay attention! Don't hide your charms!
Those who objected, tried to run away
or called for help were dealt with.
They were deprived of food until they realized how
much better it would be for them if they were nak-
All right! I get it!
Dammit! Going so far just for something so unreasonable...
Well then, what's going on with Queen Leila!?
Yes, she'll soon be coming to serve you your lunch.
Fine then! Bring her to me!
Uncle...
Uncle... Uncle's dick...
Put it in...
Touch my breasts, lick them, suck them!
Uncle!
No... my nipples and my pussy are throbbing...
Please, someone! Touch me! Put it inside me!
No... no!
Mother... what's going to become of me!?
Dirk... Dirk... please fuck my cunt... do it!
No... not until I rescue mother... but...
I don't care who it is, somebody come do me please!
My pussy is burning hot!
Dirk... Dirk... Dirk!
Do my pussy...
Put your dick deep into me...
Please fuck me silly!
Lick my breasts, suck my nipples, please!
No!
All right, we're going for a walk.
Dirk-sama, I've brought Queen Leila.
You're too slow... Chiriko.
Yes, I took some time to prepare Queen Leila for her appearance.
It's been a while, Mother.
Come on! Make your greeting!
Yes.
I'm glad to see you again, Dirk.
Your well-trained slutty Leila, please play with her as much as you want.
Oh, that's great! Chiriko!
Thank you very much, Dirk-sama.
That's a good view, mother.
Are you having fun?
Come on! You're happy! So wag your tail!
Mother's become a dog, eh?
Dirk...
Well then, now that she's my pet, I'll do whatever I want with her.
Mother!
Stop this, Dirk!
Don't do such cruel dungs to our mother!
My, my... Lilia has come as well...
A long delayed family reunion...
Make sure you get along with my pet.
Dirk...
Mother?
No... don't!
The pets recognize and like one another!
How do you like it? Queen Leila's special training.
Mother appears kind of slow and dim...
Don't! Stop it, Mother!
I've endured so long so I could rescue my mother, but I can't anymore...
Lilia... Lilia... my Lilia!
I'm sorry mother! I'm going to do that too!
Lilia... Lilia... my cute Lilia!
Lilia... Lilia... mv cute Lilia!
Mother!
Chiriko.
I'll indulge him for the time being.
That's right! None can oppose me!
Hurry up and cum! Or I'll crush it with my grip!
Come on, cum already!
W-What?
Hurry up and cum! You premature ejaculating loser!
Dammit!
What!?
It's so wonderful... Chiriko-san, let's have fun together...
What the!? You can't... Stop that at once!
Chiriko, don't take your mouth off my dick.
This... can't be...
Your weak spot is your butt hole?
Dammit! I'm going to bite it off any sec-
Don't! My butt hole... No!
Masochistic women have some unexpected weak points.
Dammit... Stop...
Stop it!
No one's ever... that hole...
What did you say?
Chiriko, you're still an anal virgin!?
The fearsome demon Chiriko was an am virgin!?
Stop! Take it out! Go away! Don't put that filthy dick into me!
Curse you! I'll make you regret this, lowly human!
Cry! Shout! That's the face I've always wanted to see on you!
Dammit!
How is it, Chiriko, the taste of a human dick?
One day! One day! I will fucking kill you!
Before that, let's give you some of the same training as Lilia and Mother.
The kind of training where you end up addicted to my dick!
No way in Hell!
Dammit!
Stop it!
Oh yeah! Lilia, make sure you stick your whole hand in there!
Don't! Stop! It hurts!
That's good! Chirikb's moist butt hole is tightening up!
What!?
Don't put your finger so deep!
No! Don't stick your fingers into my womb!
Princess Lilia! Stop it!
Lilia! Work my dick from the inside!
O-Okay...
No! Stop it! If you do that...
My insides... My insides will tear!
Stop it!
My stomach... the inside of my stomach!
That's good Lilia. Do it harder.
No! Don't!
Chiriko, I'm going to cum inside you!
It hurts so much! Stop!
I'm going to cum into your filty butthole!
You miserable worm!
Not just once... not even twice...
Goddammit all! A worthless fucking human...
You thought someone like you could manipulate me?
You're 100,000 years too young for that!
You know what will happen if I take these rings away from you?
Do you know how fucked up you are now!?
Curse you... you will regret this...
My goodness! It was good of you to come.
Hark! The Demon Lord commanded us to assist you...
The 3 of us, Velcor, Shabrieh, Adan, have arrived.
Until we arrived, there could be no abuse such as
what we will now inflict. Is that not the case?
No, no... we didn't hold back at all.
But please, use Princess Lilia to your heart's content.
Now then, we will commence the ritual!
All right, do it, Chiriko!
As expected from the White Princess Knight
Lilia, your breasts are exquisite.
Look at this. We're going find out what
the Princess Knight's pussy tastes like.
Yes! This is great!
Not bad... it's a wonderfully tight pussy.
Let's do something about that.
Inside... Inside me!
The movement of my dick must feel like explosions
going off inside you, a blade that will lay you open.
That's the spot! My pussy!
I'll do her ass!
It's going in!
As expected from Adan, you're always keen on anal.
The feeling of forcing yourself into a
place you don't belong is too good!
My pussy... and my butt...
My, my... what a shameless mouth you've got there.
I'm going to be fucking this end personally.
As wonderful as expected; the sublime mouth of the Princess Knight.
Good! It's so good! So violent and rough, but good!
Yes! More!
More! Fuck me silly!
How is it, Chiriko?
You've come to desire my cock as well, haven't you?
Who would ever...
Whatever. All right, now you'll feast on my cock juice.
Make sure you drink it all!
Serves you right, Chiriko! Now, come satisfy me here.
Relish this feeling!
Why you little...
King Dirk, can I join in?
It's already burning hot over there...
I see...
You dirty rotten...
Very well.
You maggot!
Chiriko, don't think anyone is going to come rescue you.
I'm just getting too damn lucky for that to happen.
By promising away the Holy Energy of every single woman in town,
I can do whatever I want with the likes of you!
Don't think badly of me for this, Chiriko.
How dare a worthless human do this to me!
This is beyond disgraceful!
Are you in agony, Chiriko?
The source of all your powers, those rings, they're all mine now!
Now you can never ever disobey me again!
Dirk-sama... please do me too...
Do you want it, Mother?
I want it, please put the big cock into my pussy.
What a shameful woman you are, mother!
Well then, spread your pussy open and beg.
Yes. I beg you, please put the big cock
deep and hard into my slutty pussy.
Please make me feel good!
Even in the Demon Realms, a Queen this perverted is quite rare.
How good for you, Mother!
Dirk!
I'm going to cum soon!
We'll do this one at a time, not a single drop will be wasted!
My insides, my pussy, my ass... they're going to tear!
The two giant cocks are rubbing me so hard inside!
It feels so good! My pussy is getting spread wide open!
I'm nothing but a pussy in heart and soul now...
It even feels so good to be giving in like this!
Get ready, it's coming soon!
Me too, I'm also on the edge.
My pure white body is getting raped apart! I'm cumming!
No!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Chiriko, I'm also going to blow it soon.
All the way deep into your womb, you'll be taking in my sperm!
No way! Stop! You think I'll ever let a
mere human get away with doing this!?
You're going to be impregnanted by a human! Chiriko!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop!
I'll also blow a big load into you!
No!
Lilia-sama...
How's that!? Do you get it now!? I am your Lord and Master!
Well, don't get too used to it, fucking human,
because the next ritual will be the last.
So what?
Do you remember? If by the last ceremony you
haven't collected all of the Princess's energy...
Fine, do whatever you want with Chiriko.
However, if by the final ritual, you haven't collected
every last bit of Princess Lilia's Holy Energy,
then you will pay with your life.
As of this moment, you have two more rituals left.
I'll be watching.
At the next ritual, will you lose your head,
or am I the one who's done for?
This will be something worth seeing.