No! Stop it!
You cannot resist me anymore.
Do you understand me, Chinko?
In the next... ceremony...
Will your head fall? Or will mine?
It will surely be a sight to behold.
I am the king!
I am the most important person in the entire kingdom!
King Dirk.
Wh-What is your bidding?
Your presence is repugnant.
I come bearing tidings.
Of what?
The energy that has been obtained through the ceremonies thus far,
only reaches half of what is required.
What?
But, Liliia is...
Even so... Do I really only possess half the energy required?
It is probable that...
Deep within, the princess's hear, lies something
that's holding back the rest of her energy.
And if...
Princess Lilia continues to hold back the sacred
energy she's gathered within herself,
this will most certainly bode negatively for us.
At the next ceremony,
You must steal all of the energy from the princess's body.
If not, your head will fall.
And the Rufen Kingdom will burn to dust.
What's wrong?
Have you no confidence?
Impossible!
I have Chinko's ring now!
I have plenty of power to trick Lilia into giving me the rest of her energy.
Stealing Lilia's energy is the best option...
...for both yourself and for the demons.
You have four days remaining.
I am Dirk!
I am the king of Rufen!
I am the most important man alive!
Dirk-sama, what's wrong!?
Bring me Lilia...
Bring me Lilia at once!
Himekishi Lilia
Vol. 6 A Finale Stained in Demonic Colors
Dammit...
I'll fuck... I'll fuck her up!
Yes... Yes.
Shit.
I'll make her cum countless times!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming again.
Then cum! Then cum!
Cum everything out!
My body is losing strength...
Again...
Oh yes!
Swirl around inside of me!
Yes, oh yes!
So hot...
I'm sex hot inside!
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming too!
I'm at my limit... I can't go on.
Using this ability; time after time...
Amazing...
Dirk-sama... Please fuck me more.
W-Wait!
How many times have I fucked you already?
Is it still not enough?
But it... It feels so good.
I'll always... I'll always want more.
No... Stop...
I can't take it anymore.
Please stop.
I love your cock.
Please put it in my pussy.
And in my butthole too.
This bitch... How many times does it take to satisfy her?
I've fucked her so much already...
Why hasn't she released all of her energy?
Having my whole body violated feels incredible...
Every part of me is pulsating like crazy.
It feels so great!
Do anything you want to me.
My butthole, my pussy... Tear them both apart.
My tits, too...
Squeeze them to death!
I... I can't take it anymore.
Shit.
I'm at my limit!
Dirk.
I'm gomg to cum soon!
Everything's going blank!
It feels as if my body's going to float away!
It's no use!
I can't keep it up any longer...
I'm cumming!
Dirk!
Please... Dirk!
Dirk. More... Fuck me more!
Fuck me more!
Tear my asshole open.
Swirl your cock around inside of me!
Thrust your dick inside me!
I feel...
I feel so hot inside.
I can't stand it.
Dirk... Do me more.
Tease me.
I can't stand you.
But I can't stop wanting your cock...
I want your dick inside of me.
You can have me any want.
Just do something to my pussy!
Mia?
You poor thing... Lilia-sama.
How can I help?
I will console you then.
Mia... Yes!
Lliia-sama, I love you.
Yes!
This feels great!
Lilia-sama!
Shit.
I should have known.
Even though she's a woman, she's also a knight.
If things keep up like this, I'll lose my strength before I can steal Lilia's
Shit!
And after I've finally become the king.
You think I'm just going to let them kill me that easily?
But how do I stop this?
Damn... If only there were more of me.
Then I could give into Lilia's desires without the fear of exhaustion.
That's it!
That's a good plan!
I am the king!
And a king's orders are absolute!
Have you heard?
Huh? What?
King Dirk wants all the men in the kingdom to assemble at the court.
Again?
What the hell for?
Last time he made the women dress lewdly...
But now he wants all the men to assemble there.
And what's more, he's asked us to cover
our faces so we couldn't be identified.
What is Dirk-sama thinking?
What on earth is happening?
I'm scared.
It might be something bad.
Chiriko, take a look.
By my order, I have assembled a magnificent crowd.
Shit.
And with this, I'll be able to gather all the energy for myself.
Does it not please you, Chiriko?
To the men of the great kingdom of Rufen!
As the king...
I have assembled you all here today,
in honor of my ascent to the throne...
To present you with something grand!
What's that?
What's going on?
I'm not sure.
But he said he's going to give us a gift, or something.
I wonder if he's going to give us liquor?
Isn't that...
Princess Lilia?
But why is she dressed like that?
Princess!
Woah, looking great!
Woah, looking, great!
I can see everything!
Now, time to begin.
Chiriko.
Starting now, I shall present you with the white
knight of the Rufen Kingdom, Princess Lilia!
I'll let you do as you wish to her.
What did he say?
Is he insane?
What I am saying,
is that you can play with Lliia inside of this magical circle.
Is he really saving that we can fuck Princess Lilia?
That can't be! What a taboo!
Come! Those who have the courage to satisfy Lilia,
step forward now!
That's easy for him to say...
How can I fuck such a sweet and gentle goddess as the Princess?
I imagined this would happen.
Well, never mind.
Hey! Aren't those the criminals that Princess
Lilia arrested half a year ago?
Those are the really strong ones that not
even a hundred men could capture!
Hey, King, can we really fuck her?
Yes.
Do as you wish.
And you'll keep your end of the bargain?
You'll set us free?
Of course I will.
I will let you off with a full pardon.
Okay, then it's decided
Let's get her guys!
I've often dreamt of getting revenge on
the Princess who screwed us over,
but I had no idea the day would actually come.
How did you brutes get out?
If you commit brutality against me, you will not be forgiven!
That would sound much more convincing if
I couldn't see your ass and pussy, you cunt!
Let's have you suck on this first.
Come on.
And don't bite it.
You really put me through hell half a year ago.
So how does it feel?
How does it feel to be fucked by a wild dog?
Why must I suck such a disgusting penis?
But this taste, this smell... It's intoxicating.
This bitch!
She's even started to lick it!
And her pussy is sopping wet.
She's a real slut.
I remember the pain of the sword she used to cut me.
So now I'll slice her down with my dick.
Wow! She's really tight!
She's got such an amazing pussy!
I'm being completely degraded, so why am I enjoying this so much?
I'm cumming!
I'm not there yet.
It's so deep...
I'm cumming!
I'll cum into your pussy!
Cum! Your cum...
Put it inside!
Cum inside me!
I'm cummin!
It's my turn now!
I can't hold back!
Not so rough!
I... I... I love this!
Use me!
Use my mouth, my pussy, my butthole, and my boobs too.
Use them all!
Make me feel great!
This feels great!
Is that really Princess Lilia?
I can't believe it...
I'm cumming... Here I go!
I'm cumming too!
This feels great!
Me too!
Me too, my dick's so sloppy and wet.
I can't stand it, this is great!
That's right!
You bastards can fuck her as much as you like in my place!
This way, I'll get my way without having to even lift a finger.
The closer I lead Lilia to ecstasy, the easier it'll be to steal her energy.
Lilia-sama...
Let me fuck her next!
This is awesome! I can't believe I'm actually fucking Princess Lilia!
Look at her cum!
Her pussy is so tight, it feels great.
Amazing.
The cock is scraping inside of me.
This feels great!
Amazing!
My insides are so hot...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming again!
Hurry it up!
It's my turn next!
Come on, you've had your turn.
Give us all a chance.
I wanna fuck Lilia too.
Let me go, let me go.
Hurry it up!
Just my hand, if nothing else!
Just squeeze my hand!
Her boobs are so soft!
And her butt is so smooth!
Their dicks are going so deep.
I'm fucking the princess!
I can't stand it!
I can't hold back anymore!
I can't give my dick a break just yet.
Her pussy is throbbing so hard, I feel it all over my body.
Her butthole is so tight too.
Ah, I can't hold it back any longer.
Princess, stroke faster!
Very nice.
I'm gonna cum inside of you again.
Here I cum! Inside her asshole!
Princess! Princess! My Princess!
Take it hard!
Get pregnant from our dirty semen!
Is something the matter, Mother?
Dirk... Dirk-sama, I want some too.
What's wrong, Chiriko?
Do you want some too?
St-Stop it!
Did you already cum?
But the real fun begins now.
St-Stop it!
Not my ass!
Anything but anal!
Not anal...
Not just Chiriko-san, me too!
You really want it that bad too?
If you want my dick, put it in yourself.
Yes.
Dirk-sama, your lovely dick is inside of me!
Harder!
This feels great!
Stop it! Stop it, please!
Everything is going according to plan.
All I need now is Lilia's energy.
Stop it! Stop it please!
Her pussy... Her throat too!
Oh, oh, my dick!
Hey Princess, my dick is really dirty.
Can you clean it? Won't you lick it clean with your tongue?
Princess Lilia, does my dick feel great?
Your ass is squeezing my dick so hard, I'm gonna cum right away!
Princess Lilia... Your boobs... Your wonderful boobs...
Princess Lilia, stroke my dick harder!
I'm... I'm going to cum! Princess Lilia.
I'm cumming!
Oh, this feels great!
Princess! My princess, drink me up!
I'm cumming!
Still... Still not enough.
Who is coming in next?
I want my pussy full again.
Shit.
I'm disappointed in Lilia!
Why? Why not?
Why is her energy not out yet?
She's been fucked so much.
Fucked so much that she seeks out dicks on her own.
But she's still not satisfied?
What's wrong?
What is missing?
Your end will come in just half a day.
Shut up!
I'm cumming!
Oh, men!
Fuck Lilla more!
Fuck her to the ground!
We still need to fuck her?
Fuck me more.
Take my pussy.
And take my butt.
Fuck me a lot.
Boss, is this okay?
You jackass!
How much longer should I put up with your shit?
If you want to run away, now's your chance!
It's not because I can't get a hard-on again or anything!
My dick is just shriveled from being used too much.
That's it!
Fuck her! Fuck her to death!
Fall, Lilia. Fall down. Fall before my feet!
This kingdom is doomed!
Farewell, my king.
Boss, wait for me!
It's no use!
No! Don't take it out yet!
But Princess, my dick won't stand up anymore!
If your dick won't work, then use your fingers or your tongue.
Put it deep inside.
Put it all the way inside!
So deep inside that my innards will burst open!
Princess, I'm cumming!
My pussy and my butthole.
Put a lot of things inside of me!
Princess Lilia!
I'm cummin!
Spread my asshole so wide that it'll never return back to normal!
Harder! Harder!
Oh Princess, have mercy!
I'm cumming... again.
Harder! Fuck Lliia harder!
Dirk-sama... Please... Please play with my pussy some more.
Do me more.
Are all the females of this monarch such a disappointment, Mother?
If you want me to please you, then command
then to fuck Lilia until she falls apart.
Listen, men.
Take my daughter, Princess Lilia...
Fuck her. Fuck her. Fuck her as hard as you can!
Mother...
Fuck her! Fuck her!
Give it to her! Give it to her!
Kill her! Kill her!
I don't care if she dies, just fuck her!
Fuck her!
Fuck her to death!
Until she dies... Until she's ripped apart!
I wonder... if this is enough, Mother...
My... kingdom's... people...
I am the king!
The kingdom, Lilia, and even my Mother...
Everything belongs to me!
Mother, don't you just love anal sex?
I'll thrust my dick deep into Lilia's pussy and get her pregnant!
Demon King, this feels amazing!
My pussy loves it!
My ass feels incredible!
Leila, how does it feel to be such a whore?
It feels fantastic!
My beloved Master, I want you to have
my pussy like this for all eternity!
So, this is what a human woman is like!
I'm cumming!
Please cum deep inside of me too!
My dear Lilia.
How are you feeling?
Well, Father.
I feel better than ever now.
The demonic device is doing well from
the energy we've obtained from you.
This feels great!
Again! It's coming again!
Lilia, you who have become my daughter
now that you have lost your sacred energy,
I shall grant you one million demon soldiers.
As proof of your loyalty towards me,
you will offer me the Kingdom of Zaxsen!
Yes, I understand
Lilia-sama,
I have brought you the late Rufen king's sword.
Having even us take up arms?
What is Princess Lilia thinking?
I'm not sure.
What I do know, however, is that she serves the demons now.
Fools.
No matter what happens to the Princess, we, the
White Knights, have a duty to protect her!
Yes, but that makes us agents of the demons!
We're on the wrong side.
They are the ones we've been fighting against.
Do you really expect us to take up arms
with them instead oft against them?
You fools!
Have you forgotten your sacred oath to protect
Princess Lilia as a White Knight until you die?
You fools.
You think I don't know?
Princess!
Princess Lilia!
I will travel to Zaxsen, ask for their assistance,
and take back our country as well as mv Mother.
Zaxsen used to be our enemy country,
but they don't like the demons either.
So they're sure to help us.
You men...
Before we head to Zaxsen, we've got a little job to do.
I'm here too!