The Dark Elf Empire, Celtoura.
As a result of their war with the Garland Empire, their ambition to rule the entire continent was revealed. Garland and Mashal fell down first, and their conquest continued, until they had captured the entire Midgard continent. After that, they focused on the Mitras continent, in particular to the Lindegard Kingdom. However, Lindegard, which was founded by the Great King Ashbel, incorporated battle and combat as their primary princibles. Their queen, and their strongest magic knight Olivia, brought power and morale to the kingdom with her decisive actions, making the war difficult for Celtoura. However, Celtoura also has a strong ally. The most powerful wicked swordsman, Cecil. He leads the Empire's fourth military division, and with his actions, brought the battle's favor to Celtoura. Using his excellent wisdom and cunning, he was able to break the Lingegard's alliance, with the Elf country Elfinrine. Elfinrine then agreed, to sign an anti-war treaty with Celtoura military force reckoned as the strongest on the now stands alone, and with the combined forces, aries and monsters within Cecil's fourth division, he push. Half a year after the war started, in the year 4122. The glorious Lindegard kingdom fell. In exchahge for the 5000 prisoners of war, he took Queen Olivia as hostage, demanding that she to submit to him. She had no choice but to follow...
Knight Princess Olivia
Discipline 01
This beast. Even if I become tainted, I will never be yours.
Celtoura Empire's ally, Elfinrine Kingdom.
Inside Elfinrine Castle.
– Don't try to fool me!
You're the one who killed Bruno!
Why am I to become your lover?
Not a lover,
just a bag of meat I will use as a sex tool.
How dare you...
I'd rather die,
than be scarred forever by you!
Sorry to tell you,
but women cannot be sentenced to death in my country.
The highest punishment they can receive,
is a life of labor.
What?
I'm simply suggesting something that is far better,
than being raped by all the men that
will come back home from the war.
Just kill me!
If I am to be scarred by someone from Celtoura,
then capital punishment is better for me!
Do you hate Celtoura that much?
Of course!
You killed my betrothed!
That can't be helped then.
Then this will be your punishment...
Let me introduce you.
These are some of my army's elite.
Orcs?
Orcs that are reborn with magic to be specific.
They have good combat prowess of course.
But what they're most capable of,
is that they can impregnate a human female.
I need replacements for all of the soldiers that I lost in battle.
I'm going to have you give birth to many children for my army.
This can't be... this can't be true...
You should be grateful.
A criminal's children will have the right
to become soldiers in my army.
From an orc that is.
No, don't come near me!
All of you, here is your new wife.
Take good care of her.
Don't come, no!
Oh yes, the name of your fiancé was Bruno correct?
Death hasn't quite taken him yet.
I'll be sure to let you meet again someday.
Though you'll probably already be a spouse to these orcs,
bearing their children.
This can't be...
No, stop.
Let me be.
I'm still a virgin.
I don't want my first time to be with an orc!
That won't fit.
Stop!
Save me, somebody!
Bruno! Bruno!
I'm going to break.
Oh no!
This just can't...
They came inside.
No...
This is...
I don't want this anymore.
No, don't!
Please stop already!
No!
How is it Princess Olivia?
What a terrible thing to do!
You scum!
Do consider whom you are blaming for this.
This is simply befitting for someone,
who still dared to draw their blade at the occupying army,
even though you were already held hostage.
Please stop!
There is only one person to blame for your rash actions.
Think about it carefully.
Why did I even agree to exchange the
lives of those 5000 soldiers for you?
Because you are the leader of this kingdom.
Think about your own position well.
As I told you before,
that choker is an artifact that seals your powers.
If you try to use them, a portion of
your power will flow back to you,
and activate your sexual instincts.
Despite that, you still kept on using your powerful techniques.
Now your body can't help but feel very aroused right?
I cannot submit to this humiliation!
Just take my life right now!
Kill me in exchange for those soldiers!
Like I said, the highest form of punishment women
can receive in my country is a life of service,
and I will make you wo hard with that indecent body of yours.
Stop!
Don't touch me.
No!
For a strong-willed princess knight, you
sure have this very feminine body.
Don't touch me with your stained hands!
As I suspected, you're getting horny due to
the reversed flow of your magic energy.
No.
Then are you saying that you are just naturally aroused here?
That just can't...
Stop!
A military leader doing this to a defenseless woman...
Have you no shame?
No, not at all.
In fact, I'm dearly enjoying this.
You pervert!
A perverted man!
You need to be ashamed of this!
How about you? Your nipples are getting hard already.
Aren't you ashamed of it?
A lady that never learned to play with herself,
gets to be this wet by just being fondled by a man.
Aren't you the one who's perverted and indecent here?
That's not it.
This is... no!
I'm going to soothe your aroused body.
No, stop!
What is this?
This is a new sensation.
Why does it feel good where I'm being fondled?
It's this guy we're talking about.
Why can't I resist?
He's a foul and wicked monster, and yet,
why is my body not listening to me?
This man continues to fondle my breasts.
I don't want it.
I haven't let anyone touch them yet!
Why does my body tingle while he's touching my breasts?
No, something's coming.
It feels too good, I'm...
What?
It won't stop.
Is this the first time you've cummed?
That's called an orgasm.
Orgasm?
I came?
It felt so good, that your body burst out in ecstasy,
making you crave for a man's body.
That can't be.
I'm the queen.
This dirty thing is...
How about saying your pledge of subjugation already?
I cannot!
You wanted to save the lives of those
prisoners as the queen right?
Or maybe you want to be fed to the orcs?
No, don't...
Then fulfill your duty,
to your people, to protect them,
as their queen.
I, Olivia Lindegard,
will be the sex tool of Cecil Calvard.
No matter when, or where,
you may use any of my holes for your pleasure.
Contract completed.
This is terrible.
That was my first time.
Now, spread your legs.
I can't do something that embarrassing.
Have you forgotten your oath already?
If you plan to break it, then those prisoners' lives are...
I understand!
For you to open your legs in front of a man like this,
you won't be able to show yourself to your people like this.
You must endure, Olivia.
If I just think about my captured soldiers,
this kind of humiliation is...
No, that's...
It's getting all tingly here now right?
That can't be.
No, don't!
No, no...
Keep your hands away from it.
No, don't look!
Both its color and shape look beautiful.
A fine pussy is truly fine indeed.
Don't say such embarrassing things.
Stop, it's dirty there.
What's this? He keeps on doing these obscene things,
yet my body feels powerless to fight against it.
I hate it,
but that sensation is creeping back again.
No don't! Anything more and I'll...
I'm going to...
Anything but that!
I can only offer my purity to the one whom I cherish!
So please!
Are you still saying such dreamy things?
Your country has just sold you out.
Of course, that includes your pussy as well.
Then at least let my first time be with someone I love!
Oh, do you want to be impregnated like one of our prisoners?
That's...
If you want to save them,
you need to plead to me using these exact words.
I cannot say these foul words!
It's your duty as the queen right?
Please, with your carnal lust, make me into a woman,
and take away my royal virginity, of which I have been protecting.
I am simply unable to refuse the offer of my princess.
It hurts!
Is this the pain of being deflowered?
Remember this.
This is the carnal lust that made you into a woman,
and the cock of the master that you
will serve for the rest of your life.
It hurts!
Stop moving!
What's this?
It hurts down there,
but my body's feeling hot inside.
Because of your completely aroused state,
the pain will soon go away, even right after losing your virginity.
I am being raped by a man that I hate.
But my head goes blank each time he thrusts it in.
I hate it, but...
my body just feels it on its own!
No, stop...
Let me be already!
What are you saying?
This will be your job from now on.
That can't be, no...
If I continue to experience this kind of humiliation every day,
then I won't be able to hold on.
I'm going to go crazy.
Now, I'm going to inject my seed into this horny body.
Huh? If you do that, I'm going to get pregnant.
Not that big a deal is it?
Don't! Anything but that!
I will not allow myself to bear the child of my enemy!
Then get impregnated and show it to your kingdom!
Say that because of you all, I became
a tool of comfort for the enemy,
and was impregnated by them!
No!
I definitely don't want that!
Please don't!
I'll do anything, anything but that!
Get pregnant!
No!
No, it's coming out.
A foul and filthy person like him is cumming inside me.
I'm going to get pregnant.
What is this feeling?
I don't want this, yet pleasure is flowing all over my body.
Oh no...
It feels too good, I'm about to lose it.
How does the pleasure given by the seal feel?
Nothing comparable to anything in this world right?
What is this?
Along with my seed, I marked you with a seal of our contract.
With this, your body will now cum every time I cum inside you.
Also, I need to pour my cum into you once per day,
or else the curse that I placed upon you,
will make you run wild in search for any
man with whom you can have sex with.
You scum!
I won't forgive you!
Please do your job well as my sex toy starting tomorrow.
That's good.
Put your heart into servicing me.
That chastity gear is linked to my sexual arousal.
With it, you will know whether you are doing a good job or not.
I'm going to cum.
Don't spill it if you don't want to be cursed.
This is still far from enough.
I'm going to discipline you,
so that you'll soon be able to service me well
without letting me cum with just a blowjob.
Please don't do this.
We're outside.
Someone might see us.
There's a small field surrounding this
area so just cum if you want to.
I just can't...
I'm cumming, Olivia.
Don't cum inside.
I'm really going to get pregnant this time.
Anything but that.
Have a taste of my seed!
Oh no, he came inside me again.
At this rate, I'll really be...
No...
Not there.
If you keep hitting my soft spots...
Again?
I'm already very close.
Please, let me cum.
At this rate, I'll go crazy if I don't.
As punishment for your defiance,
you will suffer three days of continuous sexual stimulation.
We agreed that that the prisoners will not be
harmed if you can last the entire time right?
It's just the second day.
But since morning, I've been so close to climaxing...
If I'd let you cum this morning,
I'm guessing you wouldn't want to cum anymore,
so I'm not going to let you cum for the entire day.
That's just...
This again...
If you can't endure until tomorrow evening,
then I'll just have to hack off about ten of those prisoner's heads.
Don't do that!
I'm always close to cumming,
so I get quickly aroused again each time.
I'm cumming!
Why won't you continue?
There it is again.
She has been unconsciously letting out her magical energy,
with the choker feeding off every single bit of it.
This is the second day that she hasn't received any cum.
Even Olivia must be at her utmost limit already.
No, please let me cum.
If you just obediently serve me, I'll let you,
and the prisoners won't have to die.
If someone cums inside me again, I'll really get pregnant.
I cannot bear the child of my enemy.
No, don't move!
If you don't want to serve me,
then you'll have to hang on until tomorrow evening.
Wait!
No, don't!
Not there!
Stop this already!
Let me cum!
Please!
Let me cum already!
I won't forgive you!
I'm never going to forgive you!
Oh yes...
No, don't stop.
No.
It feels too good there.
I'm cumming.
I don't want this!
I don't want this ecstasy any longer!
No, I'm going to cum.
Let me go already.
I'll do anything.
I already said I'll do anything.
I'm going to die.
Kill me.
I'm going to die anyway so kill me already.
You've endured really well Olivia.
As promised, I'm going to let the prisoners live.
Then why don't you start servicing me right now?
No way, I just had to endure all that...
Don't misunderstand.
The one earlier was a three day punishment
for refusing to serve me.
Your service today is another thing.
Or do you want to take the same punishment again?
I can't.
I haven't even slept for three days.
So I can't, I'm going to break.
Now, I'm going to use my princess' sex hole again after three days.
Don't...
If you put it in, I'm going to cum immediately.
You wanted to cum badly, didn't you?
No, stop...
I don't want to cum with you.
I just came.
I shouldn't have, this is my enemy's dick...
No...!
Stop already!
Stop...
I'm going to cum again.
I don't even want to, but...
Please, I came already so...
Even if you say that,
your womb is trying to suck me in.
As if it's pleading for me to continue.
No, it can't!
It won't fit in!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
Stop, stop me from cumming.
What is this?
It feels so good that my mind's going blank!
I wanted to kill this guy so badly and yet...!
I'm going to die from this excessive ecstasy!
No, I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
I'm a princess, so I should not feel horny
while being raped by this guy!
But my body just cums and cums on its own!
It just feels pleasure on its own.
Now, it's time to pour my cum in.
No!
Don't cum inside!
I'm being raped deep inside,
and his cum is going to get poured into my womb.
I really am going to get pregnant!
Bear my child, Olivia!
No! He came inside me again!
His dick is moving wildly, trying hard to impregnate me!
I hate it.
I shouldn't do it,
but I'm so aroused that my body just cums on its own.
This is... terrible...
Someone please stop this.
Save me before I go crazy!
If no one will, I will no longer be able to live as a princess.
I'll get pregnant with the child of this scum.
The night is still young.
I'm going to make you cum until dawn,
until you're completely broken.
It's okay.
I'm going to fix you up after with magic,
and then I will rape you again.
Just go ahead, and satisfy yourself with it.
I just raped her until morning, so I guess a morning service would be impossible.
Though now I have comletely taught her body how to cum. I'll have to step up the game and tame her with more intensity...
Teresa: Cecil!
Cecil: Hm?
Cecil: My on my? Princess Teresa, or should I say, Ms. Vice-Captain of the 2nd Army Division.
Cecil: What business have you to come this far?