Yuu, since the weather's great today,
want to go out somewhere?
I'd like to go to the beach.
Yep, to the beach.
That would be nice.
Well then, let's prepare everything for it.
You shouldn't be worrying so much.
You do understand that, right brother?
Ah, yeah. I do.
Because that saddens me too.
I'll be returning to my homeland.
There's no way I can overlook the situation there anymore.
I'm aware that it offends the people who came to my aid.
This is where we part ways.
The time I spent with you was the best of my life.
Though, we did grow a bit too intimate.
You'll be alright without me?
My name is Olivia Ediulf.
As royalty of Marualand,
there are certain things I need to take care of.
Besides, this all happened before that certain someone fixed her eyes on you.
You understand, right?
By that, you mean...?
Though, if I had to say, I'd be the most suited to you.
Well, I suppose she'd be suitable for being number two.
Though, you're not even that good.
I chose you, Olivia.
At present, it's not possible for me to choose you back.
In that case, I'll wait.
That'd be troublesome!
Then, bye.
Yuu, what are you doing?!
Release me!
Yuu...
No!
Stop it!
That's an o-order.
Cut it out!
Even if you do this...
No!
Stop already, if someone sees us here like this...
Yuu!
I'll be sure to protect you forever!
Eh?
No!
Hey, that was an order!
If you put it in, I'll never forgive you!
It's penetrating me!
Yuu's dick's penetrating me.
Ignoring my orders, you put it in...
You're mixing up my pussy!
Yuu, your cock is even coming to my inner depths!
It's still having it's own way with my pussy!
Geez, Yuu!
Don't!
No, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
Yuu, no, not like this!
It's coming out!
Yuu's stuff is coming out inside me!
My knight has turned into a man with no sense of discretion whatsoever.
Innocent Princess Serina
~Pure Blowjobs and Insertion Adventures~
Uhm, I don't get what you're saying.
Let's stop playing dumb for now.
I have no right to stop you.
I-I've never said that to you,
since the one to finally decide will have to be him.
My knight has turned into a man with no sense of discretion whatsoever.
Princess?
When you're beside me, Yuu,
it really managed to make me feel at ease.
Managed?
Lately, I've been so worried and couldn't calm down.
It hurts.
Why did this happen?
I think the only ones who can solve the problem are we, ourselves.
Princess...
Don't call me by Princess,
I want you to call me by Serina from now.
But, that's gonna be difficult.
If that's the case, please come to this beach again later at night.
I'll be waiting.
Ah.
Yuu, I want our bonds to become closer.
It's fine if you do it only when we're alone, I want you to call me by my name.
Serina.
These feelings, these feelings that yearn for you, there's no way I can suppress them any further.
I know that you're suffering from your feelings towards Olivia.
Even then, it's fine if it's for just a bit, but I want you to look at me too.
I'm, well, with Olivia...
Yuu, I don't think those scars will heal that easily.
But if I can help even the littlest bit...
Even the timid me will sometimes take a bold step or two at times.
Serina, wait...
Please leave it to me.
Oh wow, amazing!
So men get like this...
Jan said that it really pleases guys when you do it like this.
Well, that's true, but...
And that this is even better.
How amazing!
It seems like your thing is really enjoying it.
It's gotten so hard and throbbing.
It's even gotten a mysterious feeling to it.
That's dirty, Serina.
It's yours, Yuu. There's no way that can be true.
It's fine.
Since it's yours.
Just like this, Yuu!
That was really sticky, but when I think about how good it made you feel,
I seem to start liking it.
Oh my! I thought it got smaller, but it got big again!
Yuu, my body's gotten hot like a fever somehow as well.
Uhm...
Yuu, that's place is...weird.
When you touch me, something hot seems to flow out from inside.
You've got a swimsuit on under, right?
W-well, I thought about what to wear and...
Yuu, don't!
Yuu, are you alright?
Did my teeth scratch you?
I'm fine.
Y-Yuu, not there.
That place is dirty.
You did the same thing just a while ago.
Yuu, I wonder why?
It feels like I'm floating.
Yuu, I'm begging you, please embrace me.
You're gonna put it inside me?
Your thing is penetrating me inside, Yuu.
You okay?
I'm fine, keep going like that, please don't stop!
It hurts!
Yuu!
The pain's...
I can feel you inside, Yuu!
Don't, Yuu!
Let me rest a bit.
Yuu!
This is...
Am I able to satisfy you properly, Yuu?
You're the best.
The best in the world, in fact.
In the world? Yuu!
To me, you are!
Yuu, don't!
You're making me go crazy with that!
What is this?
Yuu, my senses are flying away.
I'm gonna cum again!
Eh?
S-sorry.
If I'm with you Yuu, I don't think I'll be able to hold myself back anymore.
Take that!
This way!
Brother and Serina, you two have been sticking together a bit too much.
Include me too!
Yuu, do you have fun when you're with me?
Eh? Of course.
I think showing that in your actions would be best.
You're slow!
Yuu, umm, I'm happy that you realized it, but...
Well...
I didn't exactly, well, how can I say this?
If you're like this, umm...
S-sorry, please release that.
This is out in the open too.
If your thing is desiring me, I can't help but respond.
Is this place gonna be alright?
Do you really want me to stop?
And besides, your thing is already like this.
We're doing something really lewd here, huh?
That's true, I guess.
You're so energetic.
Your thing is so violent
Your dick is hitting the insides of my throat
Somehow, your thing is...
Yuu!
Sorry!
It's fine like that.
Yuu, how was it?
It felt really nice, thank you.
No need, I'm happy to have made you happy too.
Ah!
Doing me like this here...
No!  This perverted posture is so embarrassing!
Your thing is penetrating me so much, Yuu!
It's sticky, right?
No, don't say that!
It's way too embarrassing.
Yuu, you're amazing!
My whole body is heating up!
Not like that, Yuu!
At a place like this, I'm....
This is...
Yuu, dong it in this posture is embarrassing!
Your thing is raging around inside me!
It keeps on going deeper inside me.
Right there!
Like this, Yuu, I'm gonna cum!
Yuu, I, I....
This can't be happening!
At a place like this, I....
That was so bold of me.
How did I do that at a place like this?
You too, Yuu.
Hold back a bit.
Brother!
Where did you two go?
It's the festival, so we took a look.
With Serina?
Brother, they've got cotton candy.
Buy me some!
Hey, are you listening?
Serina?
The festival seems really nice, but...
Well...
I didn't figure the summers in Japan would be so hot
I'd like some ice cream, please.
Understood, princess.
Jan and Miku aren't home today, so it's just us two, eh?
Oh no!
What should I do?
I've dirtied myself.
Princess, don't move.
I'll get it for you now.
Yuu, well, I think it'd be better if you did that to something else
Look, it's dropping again.
It's dropped here too.
That place is...
I'm gonna slide these out for a bit.
Yuu, the breasts are..
Not there.
Princess, you've even dropped some here.
Yuu, that joke's going too far!
Miku's gonna return anytime now.
We need to hurry up, then.
That's cold!
What's that?!
Yuu, that feels weird.
So cold, I'm gonna...
Yuu, it disappeared inside.
It's gonna freeze me up
I'll warm you right up now.
Yuu, your thing's inside!
The inside of my pussy's warming up!
Yuu, you're so violent!
Slippery, wet perverted sounds are being made.
No!
Your dick is in my pussy!
I'm gonna...
I'm back!
Panicking, I forgot my underwear
Uhm...
Brother, the candies are apparently that way.
Serina, I'm gonna borrow brother to buy some cotton candies for a moment.
So, well..
Miku, I'll wait Yuu here. You agree, right Yuu?
He said he was hungry, and that he'd come with me.
Hey you two, the fireworks are supposed to start soon as well.
Let me guide you two to our reserved place.
If you say so, Yuu.
If you say so, Brother.
We can have a clear view from here.
But somehow, it's scary.
I'm scared, brother!
Yuu?!
Well...
This is...
Brother?
Wait, Yuu!
What's happening?
Uhm, this place is getting bigger even though it's not me.
Umm, it's gotten like this?!
Brother, you got erect because of my panties?
No, well, uhm...
I've been in... with you for so long.
Miku!
Brother's tongue is inside me!
Brother's getting excited because of me.!
What are you doing?!
Leaving me aside, doing that with Miku...
To begin with, she's your sister.
That's not integral!
There's no need for me to hold back anymore, since you've already done that.
I won't forgive you for turning your back on me!
Brother's licking me!
This is wrong, but I can't hold back!
This is not right!
Yuu, this is not right!
Yuu's supposed to like me!
It's fine to do as you want to me!
If it's you brother, I'm fine with it!
Yuu, you're terrible.
How insolent of you!
It's not fair if it's just Serina.
I want to lick brother's thing a lot too!
So this is brother's...
Yuu, I'll be sure to make you feel good.
Feel good, brother!
Yuu's cock is mine!
No, it's mine.
Brother, brother!
Yuu!
So this is brother's stuff.
Your stuff is so thick.
I want it, Yuu. Your hard and hot thing.
Brother, please, be my first.
Brother's thing is...
It hurts!
Brother.
Your thing is penetrating me, brother!
Your cock is mixing me up!
Your cock is penetrating me, Yuu!
It's hitting me deep inside so violently.
Brother, you're amazing!
You're gonna break me with your penis.
This is the first time you've been so rough.
You're so violent this time!
Brother, my head is going blank too!
I'm going crazy!
Yuu, I can't anymore!
I'm coming!