Vol. 04 Chiriko's Revenge
Himekishi Lilia
Chiriko, you pledged your loyalty to me, didn't you?
Dammit.
Curse you! Wretched human!
How long are you going to do the same freaking thing!?
Chiriko-sama... I'll do anything... so please... help Lilia...
Shut up and die!
Looks like you're about to go berserk, Chiriko.
Sand? What is it now? You have some other demand!?
Relax, these are our duties.
These are the words of the Demon Lord.
Continuing peace and cooperation between the Kingdoms
of Luffen and Zakusen would be troublesome.
It is imperative to secure the Holy Energy as quickly as possible.
I already know about that. It's just... that damned King...
These are plans that you yourself helped bring together.
To cut the bonds that support, eh?
What is that?
Something I caught on my way here.
Use it if you wish.
Lilia... please help save just Lilia...
In return I'll do anything you want...
Do anything?
Right!?
Then... how about this!?
If you can manage to not orgasm from this, then I'll consider it.
It's so disgusting... please save me...
No... not there... no... don't...
So, you don't care what happens to Princess Lilia?
No! I-I'll do it...
No...
No... don't!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
What's this? You came...
Instead of saving your daughter, you'd
rather succumb to lustful pleasures?
What's that? I can't hear you.
More...
Please let me cum again...
It feels so good...
Dirk-sama, why can no one be granted an audience with Princess Lilia?
Recently, news has arrived alleging illegal
border transgressions by Zakusen!
We must consult with our army's leader, Princess
Lilia, as well as our generals, the White Knights.
Of course, the possibility that Zakusen has betrayed
our agreements has also been suggested...
The White Knights were revealed to be conspirators
planning to murder the royal family.
Once the plot was uncovered, they fled into exile.
It can't be...
Having been betrayed by her trusted followers, the Princess
has secluded herself to her quarters in anguish.
Nevertheless, please permit us a customary audience with Princess Lilia.
Without the White Knights either, suspiscions and hostility
will only continue to ferment at home and abroad.
I believe that the situation with Zakusen is fine as it is.
I beg forgiveness from my Lord for this, but, is Dirk-sama
familiar with the forces presently defending our borders?
What? Not "Dirk", Call me "King"! "King"!
As you wish. If you'll only please convey any new information to us...
Dirk-sama...
Is that right...
Minister Roth, you are the younger brother of Queen
Leila, and thus the Uncle of Lilia, is that right?
Yes.
In that case, I'll make a special exception
and allow you to meet with Lilia.
When she finishes with her morning
rituals, then you may speak with her.
My goodness, I hadn't heard anything of any such rituals.
It is a secret ritual, known only to members
of the immediate royal family.
Queen Leila has also never mentioned anything of that sort...
You witless fool! A member of the royal family
wouldn't divulge information like that!
For example, even if that person was a brother of the Queen!
But I'll make a special exception and forgive you this time.
We happily give thanks for the gracious mercy bestowed upon us.
Lilia-sama...
I feel so strange down there... a dick... please... put something into me...
I want to be fucked silly...
I can't...
Mia...
Lilia-sama...
I'm sorry.
I must look so pathetic...
Lilia-sama, it's ok, cry all you wish.
Thank the Heavens you're doing well Princess!
We are so extremely honored to be in your presence.
On this occasion, please grant forgiveness for
intruding upon the rituals of the royal family.
Princess, what should be done about Zakusen's
alleged recent border transgressions?
Later, we'll discuss those kinds of things later.
Yes, but...
Uncle, we haven't spoken for some time now...
Yes, I regret not having done so.
And speaking of matters other than Zakusen, the
Princess has grown beautifully and gracefully.
I've heard that today, you will be participating in the rituals.
Yes, by the grace and favor of Dirk-sama.
The Minister Roth is a member of the royal
family, you others, remove yourselves.
But... we haven't...
Chiriko, we'll just have some spectators, that's all.
You're glad for that too, right Lilia?
Very well, you others go to the back of the room.
Minister Roth, please drink this.
It's spring water which will cleanse your body.
Well then, we will begin the ritual.
Come, Princess.
Princess Lilia... What is this...!?
Go on, just like I instructed you.
My Lord Uncle, how long it's been since we last met...
Look how big I've gotten...
My breasts...
and my privates...
You meant to say "cunt", right Princess?
...and my cunt...
It might look pure and clean, but a lot
of things have had their way with it.
Lilia, what, are you...?
Inside my cunt, just look at it...
I remember the times when I was a child and you bathed me...
Do you like this? Haven't I grown into a fine young lady?
Li-Lilia... you...!
My cunt... is no longer virginal and pure...
Only recently, my Lord Brother Dirk had his way with me...
Look here, especially, it's mature now,
and it makes so many nasty noises...
And look here at my butt hole, it's taken so much into
it and been filled so many times with white juices...
I... I... don't... Don't!
Uncle, remember how sweet and loving you
were to me when I was younger? I want...
I yearned for you... I loved you...
Lilia, I also...
Uncle, come to me, come be sweet to me again...
Lilia!
Uncle!
Lilia! I... I...
Lilial I... I...
You were so cute, so cute that just thinking about it hurts!
Uncle! Uncle! Please ravish me, molest me, pleasure me!
Lilia! I remember! Your succulent young lips, your smooth young
legs, that delicious young butt, I remember it too well.
Minister Roth! You mustn't do that Roth-sama!
Hey, it's our ritual, so just shut up and watch.
Lilia-sama looks like she's getting so turned on...
Let's do this as well, come here and serve me.
The Demon Lord gladly blesses this ceremony,
and Dirk-sama, you look very healthy as well.
Oh, Uncle!
Th-this is the flavor of Lilia's cunt!
Uncle! It's so embarrassing!
Lilia's white juices... so delicious!
Uncle! Uncle! Please play with my cunt more!
Like this? Lilia's breasts have gotten this big...
no one here dared to ever say that out loud...
Uncle! Suck me there!
Lilia's breasts, are heavenly... so wonderfully shaped...
Dirk-sama, the niece's cooperation is becoming
a regular addition to her slave duties now...
Yes, just touching her body gives her such a shock,
she feels it in her heart and soul, and her cunt is wet and slippery now.
Lilia! I'm going to become one with my cute Lilia...
Uncle! Please love me as much as possible!
Lilia! Lliia! Lilia!
Uncle!
Th-This is the inside of Lilia's cunt...
It's so warm and tight, it's too good!
Uncle! You're inside me... Please love me!
Lilia! Lilia! Lilia!
Wh-What are you doing!?
No need to worry, Dirk-sama, connecting this will
transmit all the feelings of violating Lilia into you.
Even from where you're sitting, you can rape Lilia however you wish.
What? Are you sure about this?
What the hell is this!?
How do like it, Dirk-sama?
Amazing! All of those sensations are coming together in my groin.
Even how it feels inside Lilia!
You can have the tentacles enter Lilia any way you wish.
Unbelievable! I can't take it, Chiriko!
You're so cute, Lilia! How many times I've dreamed of this!
Uncle! Uncle!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I've losing my mind!
Your mind is no more.
Minister Roth!
No! Uncle! Uncle!
That old man couldn't fuck for his life.
No... No!
Beautiful Princess... Come on, get ready.
Maybe I'll take you like I took your uncle.
No! No... don't!
I changed my mind, I won't do you like I did your uncle.
Actually, let's took a look at your lower lips first...
No! Don't! My insides, my womb is spasming!
Tasty! Tasty! The Princess's insides are so tasty!
No! I'm getting licked! My womb is being licked.
Don't! If you do it so hard...!
My my... giving off so many juices, it must
be a terrible strain on your body, eh?
I-I'm cumming!
I never heard that the White Princess Knight
had such a problem controlling her bladder.
As I suspected, the cunt is where my dick goes...
Take that!
The Princess's insides feel so good!
It's going in... into my cunt!
Into me... all the way up through my womb!
Oh my, the monster's penis might actually tear her womb...
No... Don't! My stomach hurts... my womb is spasming!
Let me make you feel even better, Princess!
My breasts are being squished... don't!
You're spreading my ass and going to...
I'm going to be violating you non-stop Princess, and in so many ways!
Something's robbing inside my butt... it's going in so deep!
My stomach is... my stomach feels so watery...
It's delicious! It's delicious, Princess!
That feels good doesn't it?
My cunt... my cunt feels so good!
Even though I'm being abused like this, it feels so good...
It can't be... Am I actually feeling good?
Huh? My body feels so weak. Why...
I-I'm cumming!
I'm losing my mind... No!
Idiot!
Lilia-sama...
A large amount of energy was gathered and collected from Lilia.
The rest of you were worthless.
Dirk-sama, you should not have trifled with demons.
You thought you could use me however you wanted?
You're a hundred years too young for that!