www.SubDESU-H.net
Yuu.
It's a weather today.
Why don’t we spend time somewhere outside?
I want to go to the beach.
Yes, to the beach.
That's a good idea.
Then I'll be making the preparations.
Do you get it already, Onii-chan?
You can’t do something that would make them worry.
O-Okay, I understand.
And something that would make me worry, too...
I'll be returning to my country.
I just can't overlook this turn of events.
It would be rude to the person who saved me though,
so this is farewell for both of us.
My moments spent with you were some of the best moments of my life.
It got a little bit too intimate though.
Are you going to be okay without me?
I am Olivia Ediulf.
It is my responsibility to fulfill my duty as a member of Marualand's royal family.
Besides, I am sure you are aware of the one who
already has eyes for you.
Do you mean...
Well, we know that I am the perfect one for you,
but she can probably pass as the second.
I am sure you will feel the same way as well.
I chose you.
But I cannot choose you right now.
Then I will wait.
That would be troublesome.
Well then.
Yuu, what are you doing!?
Let me go!
Yuu...
Don't...
Stop this...
I am... ordering you...
Stop fooling around...
Even if you do this...
Don't... Really...
If we're found here...
Yuu!
I'll be protecting you forever.
No, hey...
This is an order.
If you put it in,
I won't forgive you.
It's going inside me.
Your cock...
You keep ignoring me.
My pussy is getting messed up inside.
Your cock is entering deep inside me.
It's still going wildly about inside...
That cock of yours...
Doing whatever you want...
Yuu...!
I can't...
I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum...
Oh no, if you continue like this...
I won't... I won't be able to...
It's coming...
It's coming out!
Your cum is going inside me.
It seems that my knight really has become an indiscriminate beast.
W
Original Animation Video
Princess Selina ~ Innocent Sexual Sucking Adventure~
Hime-sama Gentei!
To Yuu,
I will be returning to my country.
My gratitude for you
may be insufficient, but
I will not be able to
overlook your lewd actions towards me.
It is unfortunate that I wasn't able to see you.
I hope you reflect well on your actions.
Although, I would be grateful if you prayed
for my safety as I return to my country.
Olivia Ediulf
Umm...  I don't know what you mean.
Please don't play dumb.
You don't have any right to say no.
Th-That's not something for you to say, Olivia-sama.
He will be the one to decide.
It seems that my knight really has become an indiscriminate beast.
Princess?
When I am with you, I always felt at peace.
Felt?
Lately, I have been anxious and haven't been able to calm myself.
It's painful.
Do you know why I feel like this?
I feel that it is a problem that can only be solved by you and me.
Princess...
I am not a princess.
Right now, please call me Selina.
But, that would be difficult.
In that case, let's return to this beach later this evening.
I'll be waiting.
Yuu, I want to be closer to you.
It's okay since it's just the two of us,
so please call me by my name.
Selina...
Selina.
I can no longer...
I can no longer keep my feelings bolted up inside.
I know that you are deeply hurt because of your feelings for Olivia-sama.
Even so,
I wanted you to look at me, even just a little.
But I... am with Olivia-san so...
I understand that your wounds won't be healed easily,
but even just a little...
If I can console you just a bit...
Even I can be bold when needed.
Selina, wait...
Leave this to me.
Wow, so a man's cock can get this big.
Jeanne told me that if you do something like this to a guy, they'll love it.
That may be so, but...
It would even feel better if I do this.
This is amazing.
Your cock seems to be enjoying it.
It's getting harder, and it's twitching.
It feels weird.
That's dirty, Selina.
It's yours, so that can't be true.
It's alright.
It is yours, that's why...
Keep going, Yuu!
It looks somewhat drippy,
but when I think that it means you felt good,
I feel like I'm going to love it.
My, just when I thought that it got smaller, it's still big.
Yuu, it seems that my body is also getting feverishly hot.
Umm...
Y-Yuu...
That place...
It feels weird,
but when you touch me,
it feels like something hot is about to gush out.
So you're wearing a swimsuit inside.
W-Well, I didn't really know what was going to happen, so...
Yuu... No!
Yuu, are you okay?
Are my teeth...
I-I'm okay.
Y-Yuu, you can't.
That's dirty.
But you were doing the same earlier.
What's happening to me, Yuu?
My body feels so light, I might float away.
Yuu... please.
Please embrace me.
Yuu, are you about to enter me?
Your cock... is entering me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Yuu, so please continue.
Please don't stop.
It hurts.
Yuu!
I can feel your thing.
No!
Yuu...
A little...
I...
Yuu..
This is...
Am I properly satisfying you?
It's the best... the best in the world.
To say that it's the best in the world...
Yuu...
It's that way for me.
This... I...
What is this?
My mind is about to be blown away.
I'm...
again going to...
leap!
I'm sorry, I...
When I'm with you,
I don't think I'll be able to suppress myself.
Take this!
This way!
Onii-chan and Selina-san are sticking together too much.
Let me in, too.
Do you find my company enjoyable, Yuu?
Huh? Of course.
But, I think that feeling should come out in your actions.
You're a bit slow.
I'm happy that you were able to look at me, but...
But that....
I did not mean it that way...
For you to have it this big...
I'm sorry, let go now.
We're in a public place.
If your thing says that it wants me...
Then I...
I wonder if it's okay to do it here.
Would you rather stop then?
However, your thing is already this big.
We're about to do something very shameless, right?
I think so.
For it to be this lively...
Your cock is getting stiff,
and it's hitting my throat
as I swallow it whole.
Your cock is somewhat...
Yuu...!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
This is...
How was it, Yuu?
It felt good, thank you.
No need for thanks.
Whenever I sense your happiness Yuu, I become happy as well!
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
To do it here in this position...
Oh no, this lewd position...
I'm embarrassed.
Your cock is filling my insides.
It's going in and out.
You're drenched.
No...
Pl-Please don't tell me that.
It's too embarrassing.
Yuu... This is amazing.
My body is getting hot.
No... Yuu...!
In a place like this...
I...
No way... This is...
Yuu... We're doing it in this...
Yuu is deep inside me.
This is too intense!
It's going inside, even deeper inside.
There!
I'm going to cum if this continues.
I'm cumming!
Yuu...
I...
I can't. Oh, no!
In this place, I....
How bold of me.
I committed that act in such a place...
Yuu, also, need to keep it in moderation.
Onii-chan!
Geez, where were you two earlier?
Sorry, we were looking around because of the festival...
With Selina-san?
Onii-chan,
there are some cotton candies.
Buy it for me?
Pretty please?
Selina?
Yuu, it's fun since it is a festival, but...
I never thought that summers here in Japan could be this hot.
Oh, I want to eat some ice cream.
Certainly, my dear princess.
Jeanne and Miku-san are not here today.
So it's just the two of us together.
O-Oh my, what should I do with this?
I'll get soiled.
Don't move, princess.
I'm going to lick it off for you.
Y-Yuu, it seems that you are licking off something else.
There, it's about to drip again.
It's dripping on here, too.
No...
That...
That part is...
I'll take it off a bit, okay?
Yuu, not the breasts.
No, not there!
Princess, even here as well.
Yuu, this prank is getting out of hand.
Miku-san might return any time now.
Then we'll have to do it quickly.
It's cold!
What's the meaning of this, Yuu?
Yuu, this is not right.
It's cold... I...
Yuu, it's freezing down there.
My insides are getting colder.
Then I'm going to warm you up.
Your thing is going inside me.
My pussy is getting... warmed up inside.
Yuu, this is intense.
Those slippery erotic sounds.
No!
Your cock is going in my pussy...
Yuu, I'm...
We're home!
We stopped in a hurry,
so I wasn't able to...
Onii-chan, the cotton candy is this way!
Selina-san...
Onii-chan and I will go buy some cotton candy.
So...
M-Miku-san, I will be waiting here with Yuu.
Yuu, stay here, okay?
Onii-chan's feeling hungry.
That's why he needs to go with me.
Hey, you two.
The fireworks display is about to start.
We still have to find a good spot to watch.
If you say so...
If Onii-chan says so...
We'll get a good view from here.
But it's a bit scary here.
I'm scared, Onii-chan.
Yuu...
This is...
Onii-chan...
Please wait, Yuu!
What's with this?
It's growing bigger even though it's not me.
Is it going to get big right here?
Onii-chan...
Did your cock become big because of my panties?
No... I...
The truth is, I love...
M-Miku-san!
I want Onii-chan... to put it inside me.
So Onii-chan's getting aroused because of me.
Wh-What are you doing?
Leaving me like this, and doing it with Miku-san.
For starters, you both are siblings...
This is shameful.
You're no longer...
I will definitely not let someone else
take you away!
Onii-chan's licking me.
It's supposed to be bad, but I just can't resist it.
You mustn't!
Yuu, you can't do this.
Please look at me.
Onii-chan, do whatever you want with me.
It's okay if it's Onii-chan.
Yuu...
This is terrible...
This is infidelity!
No fair! It's always Selina-san.
I also want to lick Onii-chan's cock.
So this is Onii-chan's.
Yuu, I'll make it feel good for you.
Please feel good, Onii-chan.
Yuu's cock is mine.
Onii-chan's cock is mine.
Onii-chan...
Yuu...
This is Onii-chan's...
Yuu released a lot of cum.
I want your stiff and warm cock.
Onii-chan, please.
I want to do my first time with you.
Onii-chan's cock is....
It hurts!
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan is inside me.
He's stirring his cock inside me.
Your cock is going inside me.
It's hitting deeply inside me.
This is amazing, Onii-chan.
My pussy is about to break.
It's my first time to feel it this intensely.
For Yuu to be like this...
Onii-chan...
My head is also going blank.
I'm about to go crazy!
Yuu... I'm already...
I'm cumming!
www.SubDESU-H.net