Don’t raise your voice.
Don’t.
Don’t close your legs either.
Just stay like that.
And don’t let your face give you away.
Asakura... your manhood is getting hot in my hand.
Why is Yuu next to Princess Olivia?
Now that you mention it...
What are you doing, Yuu?
N-No... Nothing.
We were just joking around.
Don’t tease Yuu so much, Olivia.
Sure.
Hime-sama Gentei!
Original Video Animation
The stubborn Princess Olivia ~ her noble toes that are strongly shamed~
That is your punishment for getting me into a bad mood.
I was merely teasing you to lighten the punishment.
But take off your clothes now.
Do as I say.
Otherwise, I might lose my temper and summon Franny.
Aren’t you worried your position will suffer?
Did I give you permission to state your opinion?
Must I say it twice?
Do you wish to pleasure me?
Or to anger me?
Just do as I say.
If you do as I say, I'll reward you with a good time.
Asakura’s manhood... is so big.
Olivia-san, please stop it.
With that expression of yours...
When you think sex might happen, you always devolve into an ape.
How cruel.
Don’t make me pretend I’ve forgotten... what happened at the party.
All this small talk is exhausting.
Asakura... what are you spacing out for?
Um... Olivia-san, I’m thinking about how pretty you are.
Anything else?
And you’re sexy.
You're much more captivating to me than anyone else at this party.
Those words... they aren’t a convenient lie for this situation, are they?
I’m not lying. I’m telling the truth.
I feel a bit ill. I’m going to rest for a bit.
I'll come with you!
I asked for Asakura.
Franny, tend to the guests.
Yes, but...
If anyone asks, tell them I’m resting in the car.
Try not to make a scene.
Understood, milady.
Th-That’s the spot...
Oh, not there...
Stop... it...
Wow...
Asakura... don’t do it.
Stop it!
Not... stop it!
Why?
Olivia-san, your insides are throbbing.
Yes, but, if we keep this up...
I really will...
No...
My...
Are you... ignoring my orders?
I want you.
Huh?
That wasn’t an answer!
Are you patronizing me?
No...
Hey! Let go... Wait!
We’re still... in the middle of a conversation.
Olivia-san, your pussy is wonderful...
What a naughty face you have.
You’re a sorry excuse for a man.
Can I move?
No!
You can’t...
Asakura... he wants me to please him?
But I can’t hold back.
I-Idiot! Don’t move so... suddenly...
Asakura... that’s... too deep.
It’s too deep!
You’re too rough... you...
I want him to go deeper... I want him to be rougher...
Does it hurt?
No, it... doesn’t...
Asakura is making love to me...
Let me love you more.
Asakura, you... love me?
But I... I’m not the sort who... deserves your love...
I let you long for me all I want... and I do things that cause you trouble...
But I want to support you.
Asakura...
But you...
It’s going so deep... so deep!
Wow...
Yes...
It’s so deep!
So deep...
It’s in so deep...
Asakura’s penis is reaching my uterus!
No!
Not that deep...
Princess Olivia, how are you feeling?
What’s wrong, Franny?
Um... Well...
I was wondering how you were feeling...
I’m fine. I’ll return to the party soon. So...
Princess Olivia! Are you okay?
I’m fine. I’m okay. Okay?
So go back to the party.
Asakura... not at a time like this...
I’m fine...
If I rest just a bit longer...
I’ll get... better...
Is that so?
Where is Asakura-sama?
Well, he’s...
This’s bad. She can’t find out he’s here.
But Olivia, you asked him a favor. He must carry it out.
It’s okay. I was the one who asked him. So...
Don’t! Not so deep...
Or I’ll...
Sure.
You look a bit red.
I-I’m fine... How many times must I tell you?
I-I apologize!
If I need you, I’ll call for you.
So leave me alone!
Very well, milady.
That was horrible, Asakura.
I was talking to her... and you kept moving.
I just couldn’t hold back.
That was bad for Franny...
Asakura, don’t...
If you come in any more... oh no!
You’re rubbing my insides...
Asakura... I’m cumming.
I’m going to cum!
Wow, there’s so much...
It smells too...
People will find out.
Your face says it all...
Look here.
Understood? I forbid you to avoid my gaze.
Your gaze...
I can’t resist it.
Oh no... Whenever I’m with Asakura, I...
I want to do... so many risky things.
Hey, doesn’t this remind you of the park?
Is this the only place?
Sorry.
Well...
Oh well then.
If you want me that badly... you silly boy.
Making me do this to you... if someone notices, we’ll be in trouble.
You’re so hard... there'll be no hiding it.
This is really thrilling, though.
Oh no!
Someone actually came?
Was it Franny, looking for me?
A cat?
But this is... such an embarrassing position...
I...
Whenever I’m with you, I become so slutty.
So rough...
No!
I want you to do even riskier things with me.
No! Don’t spread my legs like that!
You’re so tight.
Stop saying I’m tight... how would I know about that?
I... I told you I don’t know!
You’re rougher... than usual...
No!
Asakura!
You’re making me scream!
J-Just a little...
Should I silence you?
No...
Don’t... please... you’re making me...
Asakura!
I’m cumming... I...
What’s happening?
This feels... good.
And I can’t stop it.
This won’t do!
I can’t... I can’t...
Why am I so turned on?
Am I...
Amazing. I feel  your pulse throbbing.
You’re so hard...
But you can’t cum yet.
Wait... Olivia-san...
I won’t let you cum without my permission.
You must make me...
Without my permission...
B-But how would I hold back?
What’s happening?
I smell something strange.
That’s right. Something bitter.
It’s hot in here. Let’s air out this room.
But the air conditioner is on. So it’s not hot.
But I’ve heard that staying in an air conditioned room for too long is bad for your health.
Oh? Your shoes are off?
Isn’t that a bit indecent?
Because it was hot in here!
Asakura, come this way.
Y-Yes!
Hey, Onii-chan, do you think this swimsuit will suit me?
Yuu, I want you to look at my swimsuit.
I-I will.
I wanted it to be just the two of us today.
Oh, well, sorry.
What did you say?
Sorry about that, Olivia-sama.
He promised me first.
Is that true, Asakura?
I did promise to go shopping with her for her vacation. So...
Lucky.
I wanna go out with you too, Onii-chan.
In that case, let’s all go out together.
Good idea, Olivia-sama.
Let’s all go out shopping together. Is that okay?
Of course it is.
Though it couldn’t be helped...
I just can’t decide.
Why not try it on?
Good idea. I’ll do that.
Miku-san, let’s also try on our swimsuits.
Good idea.
Now’s my chance.
Oli...
Be quiet!
This way.
Seeing me like this... doesn’t it turn you on?
Not here!
If you resist, I'll cry out.
Not like I mind.
But I do mind.
In that case... you know what you have to do, right?
Don’t...
I... can’t stand up on my own...
Wait... you’re stretching them too much.
You started it.
I guess so, but...
What are you...!
It’s inside... your hot thing is... inside of me...
Asakura... Inside...
Here I come.
No...
So deep.
So thick...
Oh no...
Oh no... it feels so good.
So good... why?
Olivia-sama, have you seen Yuu?
N-No, I haven’t.
I wonder where he went.
N-Now that you mention it, he said he was going to the bathroom.
Is that so... Very well.
Olivia-sama, Miku-san and I will be looking at hats.
O-Okay...
That scared me.
We’ll need to make this quick.
Asakura... not so sudden...
Does it feel good?
No... what are you...?
No...
Asakura...
Oh no... I can see it...
I can see it... going in and out of me...
I don’t want to see this... it’s too embarrassing.
I look so naughty!
Asakura, it’s your fault!
You’re making me do slutty things.
And I...
I... there’s no turning back!
Yes!
I’m... almost...
Oh no!
Hurry!
Asakura!
Asa...
It’s coming.
No!
Yes!
It’s coming...
This won’t do.
Doing nothing but this... I can’t...
Today was exhausting.
I’ll make you some tea after we’re inside.
Good idea.
Watch out!
No!
Don’t come closer!