There's nothing here but darkness.
I know nothing about what is being done by whom to me.
I just kept going along with the pleasure.
Hey, Moegi-san...
Something's kind of weird about this...
What?
What, you ask? It's like there
are lots of girls' mouths...
E-Especially at my lower half right now...
Am I going inside someone...
Before that, I'm coming!
Suguru-kun's semen... It's a creampie!
Suguru-oniichan's baby seeds!
M-Moegi-san...
Just whose insides am I coming at right now?
Who knows... Whose insides could it be?
Library
Th-There's nothing to do, huh?
Y-Yeah...
Huh? You two are like that every time?
What have you been doing,
after all those chances you got?
Kuroko, you have both the face and
an excellent body in the first place!
You can even aim to be the
school's idol if you feel like it.
I-I'm not like that at all.
A-And moreover, Galcchi...
Don't we have an actual school idol named Moegi?
Yeah... That cunning chick, right?
H-Hinagiku, your voice sounds
like Moegi-san's... It's cute.
That's what Suguru-kun said...
You should've gotten angry on that!
This girl is hopeless.
I have to do something...
You have to get him whatever it takes, okay?
C-Could this be...
For me to get a love letter...
And moreover, being called over
such a place... Is this a prank?
U-Umm...
I-It's embarrassing so please don't look over here!
W-Was that letter from you?
There wasn't a name in it, so...
Besides, that voice... Could you be...
Moegi-san?
Huh?
Uhh... Umm...
Yes...
One thing happened after another,
and since that day I became Moegi-san.
Kuroko's Room
Hey, Moegi-san... What is this for...
I-It's embarrassing, so...
Suguru-kun...
Will you be happy if I was Moegi-san?
Will you go out with me if I was her?
If I was Moegi-san instead...
Moegi-san?
W-We shouldn't be doing this all of a sudden!
I am Moegi-san...
So, right now...
I'll be able to do anything to Suguru-kun right now!
Moegi-san...
So, this is Suguru-kun's...
Wait... This is... Moegi-san, you're licking me!
What should I do? I feel too horny
that I can't make myself stop!
I wonder if I am a pervert.
This is the inside of your mouth...
This is bad, I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
I'll shoot my sperm in your mouth, Moegi-san!
So, this is how Suguru-kun's semen tastes like!
Suguru-kun, if it's your body...
I can lick any part of it as much as possible!
May it be the tip of your cock, or the frenulum...
And your balls as well...
Even your asshole...
Suguru-kun, I'll use my body fluids
to make your nether region gooey!
I'm sorry, Suguru-kun!
I can't hold myself back any longer!
Hold yourself back? Moegi-san?
Is this... Am I going raw inside you right now?
This is dangerous! You'll get pregnant...
We'll end up having a baby!
It will be alright, so leave everything to me.
Moegi-san, this is bad...
It feels so good that I won't be able to hold it in!
You don't have to hold it in!
No way...
If this goes on, I really will end up
giving you a creampie!
It's okay, come!
Suguru-kun... I love you...
I love you so much!
Moegi-san, wait!
After that happened...
Library Service Room
He practically banged me like a rabbit every day.
May it be at school, at home,
or out there somewhere...
All this time as I pretend to be Moegi-san...
Hey, Moegi-san... I want to
remove my blindfold now...
Y-You can't, it's embarrassing for me!
And one more thing...
Make sure to not talk to me whenever
we casually run into each other.
I want to keep our relationship a secret!
Okay!
Moegi-san, I'm gonna come again!
Yes, come!
Library Service Room
There, look!
Hey, Tsun-chan...
See, he came out!
I think this is a bad idea, after all!
Look, weren't we talking about your
"older brother" troubles here?
That's right, but...
Alright...
Starting today, he will be your brother.
His name is Otonashi Suguru!
Younger Stepsister
Shinonome Nano
U-Umm...
Elder Stepsister
Shinonome Miu
P
P-P
P-P-P
P-P-P-Please
P-P-P-Please t
P-P-P-Please t-t-
P-P-P-Please t-t-take...
Onee-chan!
I-I wonder if our sister hates me...
Umm... Nano-chan, let's get along together.
If it's okay, you can call me "onii-chan".
I-I guess that's a no...
P-Please take care of me, onii-chan!
Nano's Close Friend
Minamino Tsunko
Since then, Nano has been harboring
feelings for his brother!
Is that clear?
Hinagiku Kuroko-san!
I-It's not like I'm his lover...
What... You're sex friends?!
U-Umm... I'll be alright!
If Suguru-oniichan is happy with that...
Nano?!
Suguru-oniichan is always looking out for me.
We'll always be together if we'll stay
siblings as we currently are now.
That will be enough for me.
Nano!
Girl, you move me to tears! But the thing is...
This woman's relationship with
Suguru-kun smells kind of fishy!
Why do you always put a blindfold on
Suguru-kun whenever you two meet?
You don't go out for dates, but you
two sneakily meet up instead.
Make it clear, what kind of
relationship do you two have?
Suguru-kun doesn't have any feelings for me.
He mistook me for Moegi-san.
Huh? There's no way that's true!
Th-Then, would you like to see it for yourselves?
Huh?
Kuroko's Room
Moegi-san... Wait...
How is it? Doesn't my pussy make you feel good?
Suguru-kun, I want you to feel it more!
M-Moegi-san... I'll end up
coming inside you again!
It's okay, come!
I-It's something like this.
Th-That would be considered as rape!
Th-That might be the case...
But whenever I become that girl for him,
it's like I'm a different person.
I feel like I can do anything to him.
We should leave, Nano.
I can understand that feeling!
Nano?!
Nano, what are you doing?
Suguru-oniichan...
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan is licking my naked pussy!
Onii-chan! Onii...
Tsun-chan!
Don't run to me if anything
bad happens here now!
Moegi-san, I feel like there are
other people here with us!
Never mind that!
This is onii-chan's...
M-Moegi-san!
My nether region feels all slippery now!
His cock is so lewd! My first
ever encounter with one!
I'm coming again! I'm gonna come!
Moegi-san, how on earth are you doing all these...
I'm coming... I'm coming, I'm coming!
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan's thing went inside me!
O-Onii-chan, do you have
someone that you like?
Huh?
Umm... W-Well, yeah...
H-Her name is Moegi-san...
She's the cutest girl in school, though...
She's way beyond my reach, I guess...
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
Onii-chan's semen is pouring inside me!
I am having sex right now!
Moegi-san, what's up with this slippery crevice!
It's coming out again! I'm coming!
Onii-chan!
Isn't it hot?
You're right.
Oh, want to get some ice cream?
Yes, I want to!
Huh?
It's so hot...
That was my little sister.
Huh?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization