I'm home!
Oh.
O-Onee-san, I'm sorry!
Wh-What "onee-san" are you talking
about? We're in the same year.
You're dead if you dare look
at me and especially at Nano in a dirty way!
O-Okay!
B-But that sure is surprising.
Even someone like you, onee...
Miu-san who's cool and beautiful
can make such a cute reaction like that...
You shit! I'm gonna kill you for real!
I-I'm sorry!
H-He saw me...
Hey, look! It's Kuroko.
Why is she with your lil' sis and her friend, Miu?
Who knows?
Oh? That's your little brother, Suguru-kun!
"Stepbrother"!
And he's Ushi-chan's crush as well!
Huh?!
Huh?! Th
Huh?! Th-Th
Huh?! Th-Th-Th
Huh?! Th-Th-Th-Th
Huh?! Th-Th-Th-Th-Th
Huh?! Th-Th-Th-Th-Th-That's not...
No way... What are they doing?
I-In the prep room?
What the hell were they doing?!
I-I don't have any idea!
Suguru-kun was... Suguru-kun was...
I asked Kuroko and the others about it.
She blindfolds him and pretends as Moegi
while they have sex or something.
Uhhh... Suguru-kun...
Why do you even like Suguru, Ushi-chan?
Th-That's because...
U-Ushi-chan, you want yours with
three cubes of sugar. Am I right?
He remembered that about me!
By the way, I just thought up a very lewd...
...or rather, a good idea.
But you'll have to agree with it first.
Huh?
Hey, how do you feel about Suguru?
N-Nothing in particular!
Oh, I see.
We're good to go, then.
Hey...
M-Moegi-san?
This is even more sudden than before.
Y-You're kidding me!
Keep your voice down!
Suguru thinks that we're Moegi!
Whoooa! Whoooa!
Here, take a look.
We can play with a guy's body
as much as we want, you know.
Whoa... that kiss was fantastic!
Wanna have a try, Ushi?
Uh-huh!
Right now...
No matter what we do to him,
Suguru-kun won't know that it's us!
That's the best thing ever!
Oh... Kissing him feels so incredible.
How about a try, Miu?
Cut that out, you totally act
like how a virgin would.
Then, I'll take this spot.
Whoooa!
This looks lewd... I knew it!
Wow... So a real cock can be this huge...
Moegi-san, I feel that somehow...
You're sucking me harder today!
Oh, this is crazy!
I really am sucking a cock right now!
This is so lewd!
Hey, Galcchi! What should I do?
Huh? How about licking his balls?
Okay!
I-I can't hold myself back any more!
Hey... Galcchi?! What are you planning to do?!
We're talking about a summer escapade here, so...
I'm getting rid of my virginity, of course.
It feels so intense!
Wow...
A cock went inside me for real!
Moegi-san, you're especially tight today!
Jeez... Someone like you dare
to act cheeky, Suguru!
I-I want to have sex with Suguru-kun as well!
Damn!
I-I really am having sex right now!
Oh... What is this...
This seriously feels good!
Sperm... Creampie...
M-Me too...
U-Ushi...
I'm having sex with Suguru-kun right now!
I'm having sex with Suguru-kun!
Suguru-kun shot his semen inside me...
It feels so hot!
Come on! It's your turn next, Miu!
I-I'm...
Whoa! Moegi-san?!
Galcchi?!
Yeah, yeah...
I-I understand.
I just have to do it, right?
This can't be...
Suguru is... Suguru is fucking me!
Hey, Nano! What is the meaning of that?!
E-Even if you ask me that...
Wh
Wh-Wh
Wh-Wh-Wh
Wh-Wh-Wh-What should we do now?
That happened a week ago.
They had me confess about everything
and I got roasted in front of everyone.
And it ended with us taking Suguru-kun on a vacation.
M-Moegi-san?
Hey, look at that! Suguru-kun!
What lovely scenery!
I-I can't see anything at all though...
I-I really can't remove my blindfold, can I?
Nope.
M-My body is getting licked all over!
It feels so good that I feel like
I'm gonna lose my mind...
Moegi-san, what's happening...
I-I'm next...
And it's my turn afterwards!
Yes, we'll follow the order.
By the way, Kuroko. Have you
mustered up enough courage now?
Huh?!
Th-That's, well...
R-Remove his blindfold?
Yes, that's right.
He isn't that stupid, you know.
I'm sure that he already had his suspicions.
B-But...
It's not fun for you to always have sex
with him as "Moegi-san", right?
You are but yourself, you know.
Suguru-kun... Suguru-kun!
S-Suguru-kun... Don't get angry, okay?
Huh?
H-Hinagiku-san?!
What on earth is happening here?!
You're annoying! You already knew it all along too.
I'm talking about the fact that
you had sex with all of us here!
Speaking of that, now is my turn!
Nano-chan?! By any chance, did we also...
Yeah, we had sex.
And with you as well, Ushi-chan-san?!
Yes...
Miu-nee, did I...
That's right!
Tsunko-chan, you too?!
Well, I also kind of went with the flow.
Enough of that. Focus here on me right now!
No way... I'm having sex with Galcchi right now!
You'll be giving me a mad creampie,
so it's too late to act like that!
No way...
Onii-chan... Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, I love you!
Onii-chan, I love you—!
Tsun-chan!
To think that you'll be
fucking me in such a manner...
You are so indecent, onii-san!
Am I really having sex
with Miu-neesan right now?
Don't say any more, you idiot!
Suguru-kun...
Keep fucking me more!
More—!
Forgive me, Suguru-kun! I've been
lying to you from the start!
It's alright... The truth is...
...you've been in my mind all this time!
Really?
I am so happy to be able to have sex with you like this, Suguru-kun!
Shoot your sperm inside me!
Sow your seeds into me!
Coming... I'm coming!
Galcchi, I've made my decision!
M-Me too!
Me too!
The shock did hit me so hard.
What should I do now?
S-Suguru-kun!
Huh?
Please go out will all of us!
We removed Suguru-kun's blindfold,
went with the flow and we all ended up dating him.
We went back to having sex regardless of the place.
Infirmary
It's like fate playing its cruel tricks
that she found out all of this.
I-It's been a while since I had a blindfold.
What caused this change of pace?
Hinagiku-san?
That's right, it was Moegi-san herself!
No!
We're doing a Moegi-san
role play today, so call me Moe!
If you don't want to get exposed,
then let me join in as well!
O-Okay!
It feels unreal...
...to think that I'm thrusting my bareback cock
into Moegi-san, the school idol!
Yeah, isn't that right?!
Hey, Suguru-kun!
Don't you wish that you could give
the real Moegi-san's sloppy pussy a creampie?
W-Will that be alright?
It's alright, shoot it inside me with all your might!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
It's alright! Shoot lots of it!
Sex is amazing!
So this is how sex feels!
M-Moegi-san... Why are you doing this?
That's because of that fan club
that I can't even go dating boys!
My sex drive builds up too!
And so, that's why...
I'll use this chance and have
lots of sex with you, Suguru-kun!
O-Okay!
I'm about to come again!
Suguru-kun, give me more creampies!
Moegi-san, if you keep
shaking your hips that hard...
Suguru-kun, having sex with you is the best!
It feels way too good!
Alright, I'll be under your care from now on!
Y-You did a very convincing
performance, Hinagiku-san!
It turned out as intended.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization