Princess Kurama has run away!
After her!
Bring her back alive!
Princess!
Kaede-chan, lets rest for a while!
That's right.
We've been running a long time. The princess seems tired.
No! We cannot waste time here!
You look really pale!
You need to rest whenever you can.
We've got a long way to go.
I'm okay.
Let's hurry!
Don't worry, you won't be going any further!
Get back!
When?
Princess Kurama, you can't get away.
Who are you?
One of the Rikudoushuu, Shura.
Return to the Lord.
If you don't I may have to get violent.
Rikudoushuu?
A servant of Gensai, huh?
So you're shinobi too?
I'm Momoka!
Kaede.
We are ninjas entrusted with guarding Princess Kurama.
We won't let you lay a finger on her.
Guarding her, mere woman?
Hey, you made fun of me, didn't you?!
Hey, you!
Want to see just what these "mere women" can do?
Sounds fun.
Hey, don't hurt the princess at all.
Get them!
Princess, get back!
Pathetic...
Mere kunoichi.
(Kunoichi: A female ninja.)
Ninpou: Jahatsu Henge!
Now I'm going to have to redo my hair.
Do you really want to see my breasts that badly?
I'm coming!
Ninpou: Chichi Henge!
Ninpou: Chichi Henge... How does it taste?
Mere what now, Shura-sama?
You can use the skills of the Kikai.
You're not normal kunoichi.
Well then...
I won't hold back!
You can use Kikai too!
Kaede! Momoka!
You mustn't underestimate the servants of Gensai!
The princess knows better than either of you!
Ippon Yaiba!
Hey, Kaede, what do we do?
Above...
He's defenseless against attacks from above.
Fools!
Oh no!
In a single instant?
So you really are just mere women.
P-Princess, run!
Princess, run! Hurry!
If you get caught here, then it was all for nothing!
Don't worry.
Without you, it's impossible to summon Gausu,
so I m under strict orders to bring you back unharmed.
Now come with me.
Get back!
My father, Takamori Tsukikage, is already gone from this world.
What are you saying?
Your father is quite well!
Silence!
I... I alone will not let things go as you plan!
Even at the cost of my life!
Princess!
Ogaru!
Moon if you have a heart, save my country!
Benevolent moon, answer my prayer!
HININDEN GAUSS
Hazy Moon Chapter
Wow, it's so pretty!
It's been three months since I saw Hazuki fell in love
at first sight and persuaded her to go out with me,
plus one month and three days of our relationship,
and tonight... tonight I'm gonna cross the final line!
Hey, Daisuke?
W-What?
Oh, Hazuki...
There it is!
Lets take a picture!
T-Thats right
It takes nice night shots too!
Well, its the newest model. I borrowed it from a friend.
Oh, this...
I'll give this strap to you.
Really?
It's your favorite.
I want to give it to you, because it's my favorite.
Thanks. I'll take good care of it.
Daisuke... n-no...
B-Be gentle!
That...
Good!
What?
What is this?
It's just a bruise.
It comes out when I get excited.
What's wrong?
No, nothing...
You're more bold than I thought.
Hazuki?
N-No...
Daisuke?
If you're rubbing it that much...
I said stop!
Ouch!
Daisuke?!
What's going on?
S-Something's pulling my dick!
Help me!
Answer my lead, Man of Gausu!
Hazuki!
Hazuki?
That feels good!
Ouch!
What was that, Hazuki?
You're not Hazuki!
How rude!
To play with a defenseless, unconscious woman's body...
You coward!
That's not how it is.
Something pulled me down there, and
next thing I knew, I was here with you.
Could you be...
You're cute.
This foppish-looking boy is the Man of Gausu?
Huh?
Gausu?
I was so terrified of death that I made a wish upon the moon.
And then...
And then I summoned him?
How awful...
I've done something forbidden!
Excuse me...
Who are you, anyway?
You're wearing a kimono, so are you coming
back from a wedding or something?
What? Did I say something bad?
Anyway...
Since I've made it this far...
if Gensai finds out that I've summoned the Man of Gausu...
What are you talking about?
Come with me, Man of Gausu!
What are you talking about? I don't understand.
You have come to a place you must not come!
Place?
Where am I, anyway?
We'll talk later!
For now, this power...
Who's there!
W-What the hell is that?
To think that a mere girl like her would attempt suicide...
It's your fault!
You made the Lord a living corpse and took over the castle!
Silence.
Momoka!
I thought you were a kid, but what do we have here?
Kill me!
"Kill me," she says.
Oh, I will... Nice and slowly.
Stop it!
No!
If Princess Kurama no longer lives, it'll be my head.
Stop!
Kill me!
I can't stay calm just sitting here waiting to see if she's okay.
If you're a kunoichi, I'm sure you know
about these kind of skills as well.
No way! That's got nothing to do with it!
Is the report ready yet?
The cliff is very treacherous. Even with
Momome-samas legs, it will take a while.
Thats right.
Not bad...
I'd expect no less from a kunoichi.
As a reward, I'll show you my skill as well.
But if you try anything funny, your slit's gonna
run all the way up to your throat.
That fear will plunge you deeper into
the abyss of a woman's ecstasy!
Do you want it?
Do you want what's between your
lips to be between your other lips?
No!
You may be a shinobi, but in the end, a bitch is a bitch.
Stop it!
I'd expect no less from a kunoichi.
It felt like you were going to suck all the life out of me.
Momoka!
Now then...
You're next.
I've been looking for you!
Ogaru!
W-What the hell is that thing?
I'm so glad you found us.
Kaede told me that you jumped off that cliff there.
She and I have the jutsu of telepathy
and can hear each others voices.
So who's this strange looking person?
You're way stranger looking than me!
Kappa: a frog-lfke creature found in Japanese folklore.
You look just like a kappa!
How dare you call me, the great water
spirit Ogaru, a mere kappa?
Ogaru, enough!
This person is the Man of Gausu.
Man of Gausu?
You refused to summon him even after all
the suffering that Gensai put you through.
I've done something terrible.
This is all because of my inexperience.
Don't worry, Princess.
We just need to get rid of him.
Get rid of?
Do you mean...
Kid, just give up. You've got awful luck.
You mustn't.
He may not be much, but he's the Man of Gausu!
Now you've made me mad.
Why do I have to be killed by some weird thing like
you without even knowing what's going on?!
Wait!
Don't go that way!
See ya!
Bye-bye!
Really good, kunoichi.
Nice and tight!
How tight!
Tight and warm!
Don't blame me if you end up regretting your terrible deed.
You're gonna die anyway.
Don't you understand that this is my compassion,
letting you have some fun before you die?
What?
I won't let you out.
You bitch!
Did you think my only weapons were my breasts?
Your little friend is melting inside me.
Sorry.
Good job, Kaede-chan!
Momoka, thank you!
You saved me.
You too!
If he hadn't tried to rape you, then
we never would've had a chance.
Even an 80-year old man would get horny from seeing my butt.
Really! Men are such idiots...
How dare you... How dare you!
I wont forgive you!
I cant move.
Yeah, I hit you a lot harder than you thought.
We don't have time to worry about
him. We need to find the princess.
Thats right!
Sorry we don't have time to play, sword-man!
Wait! Wait!
Why you...
Momome, where are you?
What's Hazuki up to, I wonder?
And what is this place, anyway?
A castle?
Who are you?
I see.
When you woke up, you were in an unfamiliar place.
Yes, then I saw a girl in a kimono and
something that looked like a kappa.
What?
A girl and a kappa...
It can't be... Is he...?
This guy's got a weird outfit too, but he's a
bit more understanding than they were.
By the way, where are we?
This is Ooshuu.
Ooshuu?
Never heard of it.
And this is the first year of Keichou.
Keichou: 1596-1615
Keichou?
Then this is... No way, were really in the Sengoku Period?
Sengoku Period (1467-1615). A period of instability and long running civil wars.
No way!
He really is the summoned one.
It'll do you no good blundering about in an unfamiliar territory.
I wont hurt you.
Just come with me.
Where are we going?
My lord is a kind and generous man.
If he hears your story, he's sure to help you.
I didn't get your name.
My name's Nakamura Daisuke.
I am known as Momome.
Geez... I never thought this would happen.
It was a mistake to leave things to Kaede and Momoka.
Where did the Man of Gausu go?
If he's been caught by one of Gensais servants...
No way.
He looked stupid and horny, so if he's caught by them,
Gausu will be taken from him immediately.
Princess!
Kaede!
Momoka!
You're safe!
A lot happened though.
Splendid tits!
The spirit of the water, Ogaru-sama, shall purify you!
Let s eat!
Did you really think I'd fall for that?
I'm glad you're safe, Princess.
But..
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I am Shishidou Gensai.
I've heard your story from Momome.
He says disaster befell you during your journey.
I was just going for a drive with my
girl. It wasn't really a journey.
We shall speak of these matters in detail tomorrow.
For tonight simply rest.
Come, this way.
O-Okay.
We've done it, Momome.
Indeed. I never thought that Kurama, would
have summoned the Man of Gausu.
A miko who can control the spirits at will and summon the Man of Gausu...
The princess of Ooshuu Castle, Kurama.
We even took over this castle to get her.
We need her no longer.
If we haven't found him after all this searching,
he must've been taken.
Was the Man of Gausu you summoned cute?
Not really.
He was a dumb-looking kid.
Really?
How boring.
Well, he's not important. It's his seed.
Is this a dream?
It has to be!
This place isn't a cabaret club, its a brothel?!
Well done, Kimu.
Perfume made from the love juices of
beautiful women all over the world...
And incense that would weaken Buddha himself..
Entrapped by them, he is a prisoner of love.
You mustn't...
I am a servant of Buddha!
No... Not there!
Umm... How do I remove these clothes?
How?
They're just normal pants.
What strange undergarments.
That's not an undergarment that's my dick.
I've never seen such strange clothes.
Where has he come from?
I don't know,
but they say that the Man of Gausu will come
from the moon and descend to Earth.
Tonight is the full moon.
There's no doubt that he is the one Kurama summoned.
Wow!
Don't forget your task amidst your passion.
Yes.
Your task, Miko, is to take his seed, and
carry the Hiyou no Mitama within you.
Understood!
No!
Don't move so hard!
You mustn't hold back.
Give some to me as well.
It feels so good!
More... Harder!
I'm going to come!
He's too fast!
He doesn't know how to hold back.
That's just fine for us.
We're going to need to get a lot more seed from him.
If Gensais servants carry his child...
This land will be destroyed!
I'm coming!