W
Hishoka
Drop
This feels great!
Daisuke-sama.
Please, I can’t hold back anymore.
Yes! Daisuke-sama, your thick cock is inside me!
Aw, unfair!
Daisuke-sama, be sure to do naughty things to your Luna as well.
Luna is already so wet.
Oh well then.
Daisuke-sama, please turn us on even more.
We would do anything for you, Daisuke-sama.
I wish this would last... forever.
Huh? It seems someone is missing.
Master... please do me too.
Saori-san...
Master, please hurry!
Master!
Saori-san, your pussy is very wet.
OUCH!
Daily Life of the Secretarial Department
Break room
OUCH!
That’s done it.
It’s all because of that weird dream I had.
I just haven’t been myself.
I made a mistake in hiring you.
I was expecting someone more suited for the position.
But I suppose it can’t be helped.
Just do some grunt work for me.
I need to take this seriously.
The tea is ready.
Wonderful!
My stomach's rumbling.
You can’t just feed me cake.
I need to eat this other thing or I won’t be satisfied.
H-Hey, Hitomi-san...
Aw, just a taste-test?
Taste-test? But we’re at WORK!
Doesn’t that make it all the more exciting?
Kyoko-san!
Please, do something about this!
Hold it right there!
Kyoko-san!
Good, it’s ready!
It’s ready? What’s ready?
Ta-dah! Masturbatory dick aid!
I prefer the real thing.
Well, I don’t blame you.
Daisuke’s dick is huge and thick and releases so much semen.
Don’t you agree, Luna?
But... before then, I want to taste it.
Aw, you’re so hard.
Well now.
How much longer can you hold out?
Me too.
You’re already dripping.
Kyoko, stop hogging him!
You mustn’t... I’m cumming.
Oh, good. Then cum a lot.
Daisuke-san?!
Saori-san!
Ah, um... this is just...
Hey, wait up!
It’s urgent!
Um... Saori-san... that was just, um...
Kyoko-san and the others sort of forced themselves on me...
Not just Kyoko-san... but Hitomi-san, too.
Will you do it with any woman?
You really are the worst!
It's just part of the job...
but I guess Saori-san hates me now.
She really does take things too seriously.
Kyoko-san!
Now that Saori-san hates you, I suppose you’re feeling down.
N-Not really...
No point in lying to me.
I know EVERYTHING about you, Daisuke.
And when you feel glum like this... the best thing to do... is let it all out.
When you hold back your anger... there’s no telling when it will burst.
Stop holding back... just cum.
Lots came out, see?
But... it’s not over yet, is it?
Come on.
You can lick it.
O-Okay...
You really are like a dog.
You’re so obsessed with licking me.
Oh yes, right there.
Lick me more... more...
Rather than licking, I’ll do something that will make you feel even better.
Kyoko-san, I assume you’d prefer this too.
Amazing! Everything is inside.
Yes...
It’s hitting so deep.
Kyoko-san... I’m... almost there!
It’s okay. Cum. Cum inside.
Shoot all your semen into me!
Kyoko-san!
My pussy’s all full of your semen.
I’m sorry. I think I had a lot stored up.
Then tomorrow, fill me up again - we’d better get it all out.
Yeah...
Such a hot woman seduced me... what’s going to happen now?
It may be just a bit of afternoon tea,
but everyone has their own preferences, so please make a note of it.
O-Okay!
Kyoko-san likes this green tea.
You need to make sure the mug is warmed thoroughly before adding it.
Okay.
What soft looking lips.
I wanna kiss her.
And Hitomi-san likes cocoa.
And that ass... I wanna squeeze it!
Add six spoonfuls of sugar and heat it through.
Luna-san likes espresso.
And I like this black tea.
Her boobs are also very big.
I wonder how I can get closer to Saori-san?
Kodai-san?
Do you understand?
Y-Yes!
Saori-san, I’ll do my best not to fail you!
Don’t worry.
I really like people who work very hard.
I’ll leave the rest to you.
Alright!
I’m gonna work very hard!
The Secretarial Department’s Welcome Party
Good!
Now all I need to do is put on the whipped cream.
At this rate, I’ll make it on time.
I sure got hungry from working for so long.
It will be finished soon, so please be patient.
Mm, yummy.
You mustn’t!
It’s dessert for everyone!
Sorry!
About what? I’d rather eat DAISUKE for dessert.
Hitomi-san, you’re already soaking wet.
Daisuke... it’s your fault for doing things to me.
Hey, you’ll make me feel good today too, right?
Very well.
This is all part of my job.
It is, right?
If you do that so much... I’ll... get so turned on.
Please, get very turned on.
No!
D-Don’t bite so hard.
Hm.... WHAT exactly do you not want bitten?
Kyoko-san!
You’re not putting the kettle on in the break room, so what ARE you doing?
Eh, um... you know,
Daisuke got mad at me for just taking a LITTLE bite of the dessert, so he was punishing me.
Oh? Then I suppose she must be punished.
Daisuke, don't hold back.
Fuck her until she can’t even stand up straight.
Wait... You mustn’t fuck me until I can’t stand! That’s not fair!
But you’re so wet. I don’t think it’s a bad idea.
I’m sorry! My superior ordered me to!
Only NOW do you finally say something a normal salaryman would say...
What’re you doing?
Daisuke’s cock... it’s nice and hard, right?
But... if you fuck me too hard... I’ll...
Me too... your insides... are so tight.
Now, now, just cum, both of you.
I’m c...
I wonder where they all are?
So... what’s happening here?
It’s your welcome party.
We haven’t done anything to honor you since you came here, right?
But... this doesn’t feel like I’m being “welcomed” at all.
That’s not true!
Daisuke, you’re the hero of our game!
What kind of game are we playing?
The game to see who makes Daisuke cum the fastest!
And the reward is fifty thousand yen!
This makes ya richer than the horse races, dear.
That’s not what I meant!
Now! Who will take the challenge first?
What’s happening here?
I will...
Oh, Saori, eh?
Saori-san?
It can’t be... I mean... Saori-san isn’t this type of woman...
That isn’t true at all.
I... honestly love this sort of thing...
I’m a slutty woman.
So hurry... Daisuke, I want you in me.
But if... Saori-san... Saori-san!
I... I’m sorry.
Lots came out.
It can’t be... Saori-san did that to me?
I found an unexpected way to win!
You sort of cheated... but here’s your fifty thousand yen.
Since I’ve come this far... I want to go all the way with Saori-san.
Hm? What’s this, Daisuke? You’ve revived and got even bigger than before.
Oh? Did that not satisfy you?
Well, um...
Then it can’t be helped.
Let’s keep you blindfolded while you fuck her.
Are... Are you serious?
Of course we are.
IF you can catch Saori first.
Saori-san... she’s probably still nearby.
Here, here, she’s over here.
Saori-san.
I caught you!
Huh?
I got the money... so I’m leaving.
The three of you, keep having fun by yourselves.
Why was Luna-san...
Hey, you, don’t space out on me!
Um... where’s Saori-san?
Daisuke, you fell for it.
The real Saori is already on her way home.
That was Luna’s impersonation of her.
But her voice sounded exactly the same.
That girl is so good at impressions.
Impressions...?
But more importantly...
Thanks to you, I lost fifty thousand yen.
You’ll need to pay me back with your body.
Don’t hog him, Kyoko.
You girls...
We’ll take good care of you all night, dear.
So brace yourself.
You’ll need to spend time with us until we’re thoroughly satisfied.
P-Please be gentle.
Daisuke...
Saori... sa...
Napping in the middle of a work day?
Aren’t you slacking off too much?
Um... who are you?
To someone who has the audacity to sleep on the job,
revealing my name is unnecessary!
The Secretarial Department’s Overtime
Are we really... going to do it here?
This sort of place is all the better.
See? You’re already getting so hard.
At this rate, people might mistake you for a molester.
Yes, but... you instigated it... Kyoko-san...
Oh? Do you want to stop then?
Eh? No... I can’t stop now that we’ve gone this far.
Good boy.
So hard...
Hey... how is it?
It feels good.
How about this?
Th-That’s... very...
Daisuke, your dick is throbbing.
I’m... cum...
Oh dear, bad boy.
You mustn’t release something so stinky here.
I... I’m sorry
Hey, Daisuke...
Let’s keep going right here... until we finish.
Unless you... are the sort of man who stops after only he has been satisfied?
Th-That’s not the kind of man I am.
Then hurry.
Oh, whatever!
Kyoko-san... you’re so tight... too tight.
Well, having sex in a train... it really gets me off.
Don’t cry out... people will notice.
But... it feels too good... I can’t hold back.
It can’t be helped then.
Daisuke...
Kyoko-san...
I’m cumming...
Fucking Kyoko in the same train car I was in... You’ve got balls, man.
I’ll put you in your place.
If you’re a dog, act like a dog. And lick me.
What should I do?
But if I refuse, I’ll just piss her off again.
Licking me while on the ground? You must have no pride.
Um, Luna-san... It’s okay, isn’t it?
Who gave you permission to speak?
I think you need hard punishment or you won’t learn.
Luna-san, what are you...?
You’re getting hard again from having all this lube poured over your ass?
Are you actually a masochist deep down?
What a sicko.
If you like it, it won’t be punishment.
But...
Will you like THIS?
Well? What’s wrong? Does it hurt?
Or does it get you off?
You like having my fingers in you like this?
No way can you like it.
Did you actually cum from that? You pervert!
Wow, your body really is simple.
Why do Kyoko and Hitomi like something so perverted?
I’ll need to find out for myself.
Understood? Don’t cum until I give you permission.
If you do cum, you’ll be punished again.
Well? How is my pussy?
Nicer than Kyoko’s or Hitomi’s, right?
Well, it’s...
What? Do you like it? Do you like it more than Kyoko’s and Hitomi’s?
Please don’t. Don’t move so hard...
No!
H-Hey!
Who told you it was okay to move?
But Luna-san... you came... onto me...
No... stop it...
How could I stop... like this...?
Idiot! Stop it! I’m... almost...
Stop! Stop, I said!
If I cum, I’ll stop. But I need your permission.
I give you permission! I do!
I give you permission, so...
I’m cumming!
Luna-san... cumming...
Can't stop...
Me too...
Oh no!
No!
It’s coming out...
You’re just a pervert... an annoying...
What a lovely pose you’re in, Daisuke.
Oh, so this is Luna’s doing.
She touched you without my permission?
That woman sure has balls.
And so?
Between me and Luna... which of us did you prefer?
If you won’t answer me... then I’ll have to ask your BODY.
I’ll take very good care of you.
So much that you’ll never be able to leave me.
With the Secretarial Department giving me so much sweet pleasure, I doubt I’ll be able to leave them for a while.
Manneri-ka shiteta taikutsu na nichijou
I fell into the mannerisms of a boring daily life.
Tsumannai
It was so dull.
Yume mo ren’ai mo akirame kaketeta
I had given up on romance and dreams.
Dame kamo
I almost lost it.
Dakedo totsuzen atte kita no
But then suddenly, I met him.
Betsu ni taipu ja nain’da kedo
He wasn’t really my type.
Konna hazu ja nakatta no ni
It really wasn’t supposed to happen.
Nan da ka kamaitaku naru dare ga
But I found someone that I wanted to take care of.
Himitsu o doroppusu
Turn my secret into Drops.
Baretara saigo desu
If I’m discovered, it’s over.
Raibaru ippai ja masaetaku wa nai shi
I don’t want to win if I have to fight off a bunch of rivals.
Ren’ai doroppusu
Love Drops
Kakugo wa ii kashira
Are you ready?
Tekagen wa shinai iroji kake datte shichau no yo
I’m not holding back, I’ll even cast a lust spell on you.
Hora watashi o erande yo
So please, choose me.
Sasotte ageru kara
I’ll take you there.