Oh? Araki-sensei!
It's been a long time.
I have a little interview with a student here.
Though, it'd be nice if school counselors weren't really needed.
I was lucky to have her as a student here.
Even though there are lots of people here,
I could easily identify places that are rarely used.
Hello there, Sumire-chan.
Did I make you wait?
Se-Sensei...
Please put your stiff cock into my pussy...
Yeah.
Of course.
Awakening
It's already good to go even without pushing in too hard.
Well, it did have its fair share of cocks already, though.
Please.
M-Make me cum.
Then let's move on and continue.
Hey, hey.
If you keep raising your voice,
someone might come, Sumire-chan.
Oh, that's it.
You'd rather be seen.
You masquerade as a top student,
but in reality, you're an anal-sex loving class representative.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
That's right.
Okay then.
There, there.
Let your voice out.
Say "Cocks feel great!" loudly.
Cocks...
Cocks feel great.
Here, I'll cum inside you again.
Please give it to me, sensei.
It's coming out.
Semen is coming out...
We've already used up so much time,
so it's enough, right?
Now, Sumire-chan.
Shall I wake you up now?
3, 2, 1.
What is this?
What's the meaning of this?
Well...
Should I say "Long time no see," Sumire-chan?
Get off me!
Get away from me!
That's impossible.
We're still right in the middle of our counseling.
Wh-What nonsense are you blabbering...?
Wh-Why?
M-My hand's won't let go...
That won't do.
You won't be able to get away until I reach your deepest part.
If I cum once more, I'll let you go.
Th-This is...
This is just another dream.
Here, doesn't it feel great?
Having anal sex while being exposed to the entire school.
What's wrong, Sumire-chan?
Are you holding your voice back?
Even though you were screaming about
cocks left and right awhile back.
I won't listen.
This is just another dream.
Up we go.
Here, this way your juice-filled pussy,
and your butthole
will be clearly seen.
Th-There's no way this can feel good for me.
With my ass getting fucked...
... as I'm being watched.
That's right.
I'm sexually frigid.
You're quite tough.
Oh, well.
I'll use this then.
If I just put up with it until the end,
I'm sure to wake up sooner or later.
If this is me...
If I am myself,
I'm sure I can do it.
It feels cold!
This is a non-produced white substance
that neither has adverse nor positive effects.
What's this?
It feels sticky and gross.
What could this be?
What...?
It feels cold, but...
The parts that are wet are starting to feel hot...
Does it feel itchy?
No.
Not itchy.
M-My whole body is tingly.
I could...
I could lose my mind,
if I'm not fondled...
No...
You can't...
You...
You can't do this...
No...
Yes, keep it up, Sumire-chan.
Look, it feels great in the butthole too, right?
If you're more honest with yourself,
then the tingling will stop.
Here, here, here!
This can't...
This can't be...
It won't stop.
It feels good.
That's right. This is the real Sumire-chan.
I'm going crazy!
It feels good...
With this, I guess I've now brought out your true self.
No...
This isn't...
This isn't me...
Wh-What are you doing?
Hey.
Hey there, Kurahashi.
What am I doing? Well...
This, as you can see.
What have you done?
Hey. What have you done to Shirakawa?
My Shirakawa is...
My...
Se-Sensei?
Shirakawa...
Sensei!
Uh-oh, looks like he's gonna be out for a while.
Hitoriga
It's hot...
What?
Where am I?
Huh? Sensei?
Sensei is ardently licking me down there.
Oh, no!
Am I seeing these kinds of dreams again?
Geez, you're such a nympho.
Reacting like this...
Well then,
alright, time to return the favor.
Here, open your mouth, Shirakawa.
Say, "Ah".
Good girl.
Now, you don't have to move.
Just suck it firmly.
This really feels so good!
Shirakawa...
Try licking the tip of the cock
while continuing to suck it like that.
This is great.
It's a bit underwhelming not having it down to your throat,
but this way, I can taste both your lips and tongue.
Here, I'm cumming.
It came out.
Open your mouth.
Shirakawa, that's very delicious, you know.
Taste it well, and savor it.
It's sweet.
It tastes good.
How was that, Shirakawa?
Did it taste good?
Huh?
What could this be?
Something feels off...
Did I lose consciousness on the roof...?
There, it's already very wet....
How lewd this virgin pussy has become.
But don't worry, Shirakawa.
You look very gorgeous
when you are soiled.
Huh?
Sensei's tongue is entwining with mine...
I'm getting hotter.
My head feels light.
It feels a lot more vivid than a dream.
I can't hold back anymore.
I already felt like cumming when I kissed you.
Here, look.
I can finally put this inside you, Shirakawa.
U-Ummm...
That would...
Wait a minute!
What's wrong?
You were happily sucking this, right?
That's right.
This guy always get very excited when he watches your videos.
If she doesn't really want it, you can simply tune into this.
That's right, Sumire-chan.
Show him how you take it up the ass.
Wh-What?
Look well.
What's this?
My Shirakawa is being soiled down there while wearing that horny face.
I-I was really doing...
It wasn't a dream?
I wanted to see it.
Badly.
To see Shirakawa being soiled by another man...
I really didn't want to...
I really did not want to see it.
But...
No matter how much I like Shirakawa,
I can't simply sit back and do nothing!
This is all a lie.
Stop...
How could sensei say such things?
But it's okay now.
I'll stamp out what little fight you've got left, Shirakawa...
I have to take your virginity after all.
Is that okay?
Why?
The semen I built up for this day... I'll
give it all to you, inside and outside!
Why am I in this mess?
I...
I would have been happy to do it with sensei one day.
But why?
It hurts!
So this is Shirakawa's real pussy!
Its filling me up!
You really...
You really had a bad time, right?
But you understand, right?
It's because I love everything about you.
This man is the worst!
Here, look here.
The act of me drilling inside you like this
is proof of my love!
This kind...
... of person.
I'm such a fool.
I'm being raped without restraint.
These erotic sounds coming out...
Why?
Is it because of my cock?
It's digging deep inside.
Or maybe because of your pussy...
I feel something twitching inside me.
Shirakawa!
Why does it feel good?
I'll push.
I'll push deeper in you.
What's happening to me?
I love you!
Shirakawa!
Sensei's voice...
It's seeping deep into my mind.
I can’t fight it.
Look, Shirakawa.
You want it, right?
You want me to cum in your pussy, right?
Yes, I want it.
I want it inside me.
Sensei...
Sensei.
You're cumming inside me.
It feels so good
that I almost can't move.
I'll do many more rounds with this.
Shirakawa...
Hey, if you want to continue, do it somewhere else.
Employees will be here soon.
N-No way...
It's still...
It's still not over yet?
Hey...
Stick out your butt more, so I can see it better.
Oh, it's dripping again.
We need to wipe that.
At any rate, I had my fun getting you to enjoy
it, and you're totally submissive now.
Th-This is unfair.
Taking a video like that...
You're making it so that I can't fight back.
Here, here.
Your pussy likes it.
I want to hear you say it too, Shirakawa.
It doesn't feel good at all!
Oh, no...
It feels good...
It feels really good.
That won't do.
Even if you deny it, with your body moving like that, it's still obvious.
No, don't move my hips.
I'm just pushing inside lightly...
And your pussy is getting very wet.
It feels sensitive when you move it around like that.
If you move like that...
No, no...!
No, it won't stop.
It won't stop!
Hey, hey, you came already?
This is terrible.
I can't hold on. He already knows it.
He already knows that my entire body is feeling good.
This is really good.
Giving me a very cute reaction like that...
As a reward,
I'll thoroughly play with you using your favorite anal sex toy.
No, my butthole again...
My butthole's being teased again.
What's this?
Incredible.
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum!
I can't get enough of this!
Your pussy is getting even tighter as this goes deeper into your butthole.
I can't hold on anymore.
I can't hold back anymore.
This is good.
I'll make you cum again.
I'll pour my semen deep into your womb.
Cum all you want!
It's okay now.
It's okay if you cum now.
I'm cumming
while my insides are getting soiled.
Now I'm done with Kurahasht's request.
Well, I still have my own part to took forward to.
That's right. Insert it properly. Where do you want to put it?
In your pussy? In your butthole?
My head is now filled with thoughts of cocks.
I want my pussy to be stirred badly by this hard thing.
Here.
There, that's right.
I'll let out all the built up semen inside you, okay, Shirakawa?
It's out.
Wow!
My hips are moving on their own!
I really feel Shirakawa's pussy moving about!
My hips are moving the cock where it feels most pleasurable!
I love you, Shirakawa.
I have a terrible way of showing it,
but I really love you.
Sensei...
This is terrible...
We can't go back now, can we?
It's too late for you to say that.
Shirakawa...
If you will accept me like this, sensei...
I love you, Shirakawa.
I won't let anyone touch you.
You're all mine.
Your pussy, butthole...
Everything.
I'm cumming again, Shirakawa.
Take all of my love-filled semen
into your womb.
Sensei!
Sensei's cumming!
It's reaching my womb!
I love...
I love you!
I'm now his woman.
I'm now Sensei's woman.
What should I do? I'm happy!
Hey, you're doing quite well there.
What is it, Araki?
I won't let you touch her anymore.
Well, I just thought of something interesting again.
Won't you let me try it?
I think you'll enjoy it...
A new experience for you two.
Alright then.
Right? Shirakawa?
Let's make ourselves feel even better.
Yes, sensei.
I want to do it.
Don't mess with me!
What's the meaning of this?
Removing Shirakawa's memories like that...!
No, no.
I didn't remove them.
I made her think that after you rescued her on the train,
both of you then entered a healthy sexual relationship.
What?
Being healthy is good, right?
Sensei?
The Sumire-chan that you continuously raped,
Sensei...
can now act as if it's your first time together.
Are you listening Sensei?
You're spacing out.
Oh, sorry.
What was that again?
Make yourself available this Saturday, okay?
It's a promise.
Okay, I understand.
If you want to do it again, it's fine, I guess.
But if you do it forcefully,
there's a possibility for her memories to return.
Worst case, some damage could be incurred.
Damn, why did he have to do it so incompetently?
I'll be going now then.
Sh-Shirakawa.
I understand.
but I can't hold back anymore.
You can't do that, Sensei.
Please wait until fully graduate, okay?
Yeah, sorry.
That's right.
Isn't it great?
You already have a fake relationship,
and the bar has even been raised a bit.
If you play it out normally like a good teacher,
she'll eventually move closer to you on her own.
Especially with that ruined purity of hers.
N-No,
not again.
I'll wait.
I'll wait, just you wait and see.
Shirakawa...
I'm looking forward to it.
My mind's about to go crazy!