Sensei...
We mustn't do this.
Someone will see us here.
It's okay.
No one will come here at this time.
Besides...
Once I transfer there, I won't be seeing you for a while.
It's alright.
Even if you transfer,
you said that you'll be back here in two or three years.
No, Sensei!
We really mustn't!
I can't wait for you to graduate, Shirakawa.
I...
I can't...
No...
The train will be arriving at Line 01 shortly.
Please wait behind the white line.
Sensei, I'll be waiting for you.
until you come back.
Shirakawa...
Actually, there's something that I want you to do while I'm away.
Wh-What is it?
I want you to masturbate with me tonight.
Bashfulneess
Around 10 o'clock tonight,
I want both of us to think of each other.
It's more exciting than masturbating by yourself, right?
Even if you say that...
I haven't really masturbated that much yet...
F-From Sensei?
"It's almost time, Shirakawa"
"I'm already prepared and waiting."
"I'm waiting."
I-Is this okay?
I'm not sure, though...
Se-Senset is also masturbating at the same time now...
while thinking of me.
I-I need to play with my genitals too, right?
It somehow feels a lot better than when I usually do it alone.
Wh-Why?
I thought I wasn't such a lewd girl.
This is... weird.
Se-Sensei?
Right now, I'm masturbating while thinking of you.
It feels really good.
If you also feel great,
try masturbating naked.
Naked?
No way...
Wh-What is this feeling?
It feels like I'm receiving an electric shock.
Is this what others call masturbation?
Se-Sensei...
I'm also masturbating right now.
I'm playing with my breasts and my genitals,
while thinking of you!
This is all your fault, Sensei!
I'm not really lewd like this.
It's because you ordered me to do so.
It feels really hot.
This feels weird.
My body's feeling light.
Am I getting aroused?
I can't stop it.
Sensei...
Are you imagining how embarrassingly horny I am now?
Are you masturbating at the image of my lewd self?
I'm...
I'm already at my limit!
My body's about to lose it!
Se-Sensei...
If I continue doing this...
I-I'm going to become an...
... indecent woman.
Hey there, Sumire-chan.
Long time no see. Doing well?
I'm sorry, but who are you?
I see.
So you don't remember me.
That's too bad, Sumire-chan.
As for me, I clearly remember you.
Very clearly.
Excuse me,
I really don't remember you.
Can you please stop addressing me like we're dose?
Oh, sorry 'bout that.
I'll be leaving now.
Would you like to drink coffee in the counseling room?
I'll say it again.
I've used subliminal suggestion on you.
So that once you hear these words,
you'll fall into a hypnotic state once again.
Se-Sensei...
He's giving me orders again via text message.
I-I can't possibly do that...
"Shirakawa."
"On that train,"
"I want you to show some skin,"
"and reveal your breasts."'
Re-Remove my clothes here?
I-I can't do it!
"As you remove them, make sure to stand up,"
"and send me a picture of you breasts."
If someone sees me...
B-But I have to do it...
It’s an order from Sensei...
If I...
If I don't do this quickly.
the train will arrive at the next station.
Please...
Don't let anyone notice me...
Don't look here...
Okay.
I feel so nervous...
I can almost feel my heart throbbing.
I'm exposing my breasts on the train.
I'm...
I'm doing this kind of embarrassing stuff...
We're about to reach the next station soon.
Those exiting please head to the entrance now.
I must take this quickly...
So this indecent body will be seen by Sensei...
What are you doing, Shirakawa-san?
Getting all naked here...
Could you be an exhibitionist?
Th-That's not it!
This is... Well...
For the quiet honor student Shirakawa
to actually be this perverted...
I'm surprised.
I have to tell everyone.
Please, don't mention this to anyone!
Well, I can do that.
However, you must do what we tell you...
What?
What's going to happen to me?
Hitoriga
Oh.
It suits you well, Shirakawa-san.
Hey, what are you hiding those for?
You're supposed to bare it all, right?
Do it!
Show it to us!
They're looking at me...
They're small.
Those petite breasts look cute.
Everyone's looking at my embarrassing spots.
I said to show it all, right?
Turn around, and expose your anus and pussy to us.
They're getting all cocky.
I won't forgive them!
Do it!
Let your butt face us, and part your legs.
Oh, the pussy's eating up the stockings!
For real?
I can clearly see her openings.
Man, the pantyhose dinging firmly to her skin is really arousing for me.
Endure it.
Just endure it a bit more...
I won't lose to this embarrassing situation!
I can't hold it in anymore!
What?!
Stop.
No...!
I guess it'd be boring just to look at it.
N-No way...
You told me I just have to show it, right?
This silky feeling...
I can't get enough of it!
I'll be licking it then...
Your legs are even getting licked.
Shirakawa-san sure is popular.
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Sensei hasn't even done that to me yet!
Then I'll be using this.
The rubbing sensation in the tights feels really great!
It's hitting me.
Some hot and hard thing is hitting me...
It feels really good!
I want this to end.
Everyone's already getting serious there.
Shirakawa-san is going to get passed around at this rate...
Isn't that great?
She's a pervert who tried to take a picture
of her naked self in the train, anyway.
I see!
So, she's also getting aroused from this.
Oh, some liquid is starting to leak out.
No...
I'm not...
I'm not feeling aroused at all...
I won't allow you all to have it your way!
Oh, you're doing quite well there, Sumire-chan.
So this is the result of my training after all.
Or maybe this isn't enough for you?
What's this?
Stop.
Why is this person here?
It's no use.
No matter how much you try to escape.
You can no longer do so.
That's okay.
Cum already!
No...
I'm going to...
I'm going to pee...!
I'm still going to make you cum some more.
Wh-What?
In the train?
When did I...?
I said I was going to make you cum some more, right?
Shirakawa seems to love doing it in the train,
so I thought it'd be better this way.
You can't let your voice out like that.
You'll be heard by everyone.
Th-This is...
I won't let you do what you want in this place forever!
It looks like she's resisting,
but all of this is just an act, right?
That's right.
Shirakawa's a perverted exhibitionist.
So it's definitely just an act.
N-No..
Don't say such things.
Really?
Then let's take off something.
N-No...
It's nothing like that.
Let me be.
She's already totally exposed!
Here, Shirakawa-san. It feels good, right?
Let me suck on it directly.
Let's remove these stockings and let me in already.
Hey, stop it!
Let me in on the action too, Shirakawa-san.
No way...!
Shirakawa-san is already wet.
It stinks.
It's dirty.
I don't want this.
I don't want this anymore!
Here I go.
Ah, she's so tight.
It's a quite a tight it over here too...
I have a big one in my mouth and my pussy. This is incredible.
Please, don't do it roughly.
If you do,
I'll cum soon...
Wow!
I'm about to cum already.
It's hitting deep in my throat...
And this one's touching my womb.
Please, don't do it so roughly.
If you do...
I'll...
I'll cum...
I...
I'm feeling...
I'm feeling horny...
I'm cumming!
It's pouring out!
It's hitting my womb.
This one too... It's hitting my throat.
Is it finally over?
We're just getting started.
Everyone's waiting, so fuck them already.
N-No way...
Please...
Someone...
Someone save me!
Kurahashi...
Kurahashi-Sensei...
Sumire-chan, it's okay now.
Th-This can't be...
It's a dream.
It's a dream...
This is all just a dream...!
That's right.
All of this is just a dream.
That was a dream, right?
There's no way something like that could happen.
Why am I wearing my uniform?
N-No way...
Okay, I'm wearing it properly.
Th-That's....
Th-This...
... is semen?
No way...
That wasn't a dream?
What exactly happened to me?