Oh? Araki-sensei, It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Nah, I just have some free time for a walk.
Well, with the counselling thing you wont have any time.
I'm sure lucky with this school.
There are no other place like this.
Hey, Sumire-chan.
Did I make you wait a long time?
Sensei... Hurry...
Please stir up my ass with your stiff Dick...
Sure... not a problem.
Fansubbed by http://shin-hentai.com *X-Death
Looks like you're already set to go...
I've never seen such a sexy asshole in my life.
Please... fuck my ass...
Then, lets go some good place.
If you keep moaning like that, someone's gonna show up...
Sumire-chan...
Oh right, I guess you won't be satisfied until the entire class sees you, right?
Y... Yeah...
That's good.
Take this! Keep mouning louder!
Scream about how much you love my Dick!
D... Dick...!
Your Dick...!
Yeah... I love your Dick... very much!!
Here you go...!
Please cum... Sensei...!
It's pouring into me... Sensei cum is pouring into me...!
We've been fucking for quite a while, haven't we?
Now, Sumire-chan... How about you open your eyes...?
What's going on!? What is this!?
Hey there! Long time no see...
Why don't we try it like this for once, Sumire-chan?
G... Get away from me...!
I'm afraid I can't do that. I'm still trying to counsel you...
I don't know what the hell you're talking about...
W... Why can't I move my hands...!?
Sorry... Without my permission, you won't be able to pull your hands away.
Don't worry. As soon as I cum inside you one more time, I'll pull out,
Is this... another dream?
Look. Wouldn't that be fun?
If you were to show all of your classmates how you have anal sex?
What's wrong, Sumire-chan?
Are you trying to hold your voice back?
You were shouting for dick up until a minute ago.
I'm not listening. It has to be another dream...
Here. Like this everyone below will be able to see you perfectly.
Th... There's no way this should be possibly feel good...!
I can't get turned on by being watched...!
Yeah... Since I'm sexually frigid...
You're pretty stubborn, aren't you?
Oh well...
I'll just have to use this.
If I can just endure this... I know I'll wake up...
I know I can do this...!
I brought this along in the slight chance that you'd reject me.
What's this...?
It's so sticky and gross...
What could this stuff be...?
What is this!? It's so cold, but...
Every part he smears starts to heat up like crazy.
And it starts to tingle?
No, wait! This isn't just tingling...
M... My entire body is throbbing.
If he doesn't tease me... It feels like I'll go insane!
What is this!?
Don't! No more!
That's it... That's the way, Sumire-chan.
Here. Doesn't your ass feel good, too?
If you give in, I'll be sure to make the tingling stop.
Th... This shouldn't be possible!
I'm sorry! Forgive me...! My ass feels so good!!
That's right! This is your true self, Sumire-chan.
N... No more!
You're finally the way you should be.
No... I... I can't believe this...
Wh... What are you doing...?
H... Hey...?
Hey there, Kurahashi.
"What", you ask...?
Isn't it obvious?
What did you do!?
Hey, What did yo do to... Shirakawa!!
My... Shirakawa...
Mine...
S... Sensei...!?
Shirakawa...!
Sensei!!
That won't help for the next little while.
It... It's so warm...
What is it?
Where am I?
Huh...? Sensei...?
Sensei's licking me as if his life depended on it...
Am I seeing another one of these dreams?
You really are selfish, aren't you?
Well then. I'm next now, Okay...
Here. Shirakawa suck this...
That's a good girl...
You don't need to move, so just start sucking on it.
I knew this would be the best.
Shirakawa...
Try rubbing your tongue along the tip of my Dick...
That's great.
I'd like to shove it all the way down your throat, but...
Here... It comes...!
I came!
Open your mouth!
Shirakawa, Cum is a very delicious thing, Isn't it?
Mix it around your mouth and taste it.
It's so sweet...
and delicious...
Was it tasty, Shirakawa?
Huh? What's this feeling of discomfort?
Look at this... You're all nice and soaked.
You've got such a naughty virgin pussy...!
But don't worry, Shirakawa...
I think you're beautiful no matter how filthy someone tries to make you.
Huh? Sensei's tongue is... wrapping around mine...
It feels so warm... It's making my head spin...
It's so much better... than any of my dreams...
It's no use!!
I'm so turned on that it feels like I'll cum just from kissing.
Look at it...
I can finally stick it into your pussy.
Sensei, Wait!
What's the matter, Shirakawa?
You seemed to be sucking on that guy's dick as if it was the most delicious thing ever.
That's right...
Every single day, He's been looking at videos of you.
That's exactly why I show it him those.
Yeah... Sumire-chan, I'll make sure to show it to him.
What... What is this...?
Yeah... You had such a naughty look on your face.
My horrible dreams...
Weren't dreams at all...?
The truth is, I don't want to see it... Whenever I see you, I just can't get control of myself.
But... But...
No matter how much I love you, I can't get a hard-on unless I do this.
Stop... There's no way Sensei would ever... say such things...
But, It's okay.
I'll get rid of all of your painful memories.
I knew it was a good idea to save your virginity for myself, right?
Why? Why is this happening!?
Today, I'll pour you fill with all of the cum I've been saving up just for you.
If... If Sensei and I had done this under normal circumstances...
I'm sure I would have been happy... So then... Why...?
It... hurts!
This is... Shirakawa's Pussy...
This is... really...!
You must have really gone through alot, right?
But... You understand, don't you?
I did all of this because I love you.
This guy... is the worst...
Take this! And this! This naughty pussy is aching with my love, isn't it?
I can't believe it... I... I was such a fool.
It's really mortifying... Why am I getting so turned on...!?
Just listen to those sounds you're making...
Why... Is it because of my dick?
Or is it just because your pussy is that slutty, Shirakawa?
Everytime he pushes it deep inside me...
Shirakawa! I'm gonna fuck you even harder!
Why...? Why does this feels so good!?
What's wrong with me!?
I Love You! Shirakawa...!
Sensei's voice...
Is going directly into my face...
I can't fight back...
Take this... Don't you want it, Shirakawa? Don't you want me to cum in your pussy?
I want it... I want it in my pussy...
S... Sensei!
Sensei... your cum...! It's pouring into my pussy...!
It... It just feels too good! Your pussy is the best...!
I'll be able to cum over and over for you, Shirakawa...
I'm heading back now.
So you can take your time.
No way! It... It's not ever yet...?
Come on. Stick your ass out so that I can have a good look.
Looks like your juices are already spilling out.
Aren't you looking forward to me fucking you, Shirakawa?
You're... a coward.
You took those videos just so that I wouldn't go against you...
Your pussy's really feeling good down there.
Let's hear the same come out of your mouth, Shirakawa?
I told you it doesn't feel good... at all...!
No! So good.. his dicks feels so good...!
That's no good. Even if you try to deny it, the way you're moaning and shaking gives it away.
Just by sticking it in, It's making me throb like crazy...
Whenever I trust It all the way inside, your pussy starts to...
Please don't thrust it into me like that...!
No... It won't stop... It won't stop!
Hey, now... you came already.
How could he...? I can't go on.
My body's loving every second of it...!
I just love those cute reactions of yours.
I just love teasing your ass too, Shirakawa.
No way! Not my ass, again... He's going to tease my ass, again!
What is this!? It's Incredible!
I'm gonna burst... My ass is gonna burst...!
Your pussy's squeezing down even tighter than before!
No more... I can't hold back...!
That's good. I'll make you cum, again...!
Go ahead and cum whenever you're ready...!
Yeah... I can just go ahead and cum...!
My belly... It's being drowned in cum...
With this... Kurahashi issue is accomplished, right?
Well... there are still more fun for me to do here.
That's it... Go ahead and stick it in your own.
You can even pick which hole.
I can't hold back. My head's filled with thoughts of dick...
I want my pussy to be stirred up with this throbbing dick... I just can't help it...
Th... This one...
I see... Well then, you can take all of the cum that's saved up in my balls...
But.. my hips are moving on their own... I can't stop them...!
That's amazing... It feels like your pussy's on fire, Shirakawa.
My hips are moving to make sure his dick keeps hitting my sweet spot...!
I love you, Shirakawa.
My methods may have been harsh, but I really do love you...
Sensei... You're so mean...
I'll never be able to go back to the way I was...
The only one who could accept me for what I am... is you Sensei...
I love you! Shirakawa.
I won't let anyone else touch you...
You're all mine.
Your pussy, your ass... they all belong to me, Shirakawa...!
I'm gonna cum, again...! Shirakawa!
Take all of my LOVE filled cum...
inside your womb...!
It's going inside me...!
I... I love it!
I love so it so much!
I have become...
I've become the woman Sensei wanted me to be...
What should I do? I'm so HAPPY...
Are you still going at it?
What's your problem, Araki?
I'm not letting you touch her, again.
By the way, I just thought of an interesting idea... care to try it...?
I think you'll enjoy it.
It'll be a new experience for the two of you...
Yeah, that sounds good.
Isn't, Shirakawa?
Let's both feel even better together, Okay?
Y... Yes, Sensei...!
I wanna feel even better...
Quit fucking around!
What the hell are you thinking!?
What do you mean you want to erase Shirakawa's memories!?
You've got it all wrong.
It's not like I'm going to erase them...
I'm just going to set it up so that you'll have started a wholesome relationship after you had saved her on the train.
Why?
With this you can start off fresh, can't you?
All of her memories of being raped will be gone and you can start of as lovers.
Are you even listening, Sensei?
You were spacing out.
Yeah... Sorry about that. What's up?
You're sure you're gonna be free on Saturday, right? Is that a promise?
Yeah, I understand.
It'll work out if you try.
But if you force her, she may return to the way she was before.
Damn it!
Why do you have to do something like that...!?
I guess, It's time for me to go...
I know... I know all that, but... I just can't hold back...
I don't think so! Sensei!
Please wait until, after I've graduated, Okay?
Yeah... Sorry... I forgot about that...
What's the big deal?
She already liked you before any of this ever happened.
As long as you're still her "kind and gentle Sensei", She'll eventually come to you...
And she'll never realize what you had done to her.
No! Again!?
I'll wait... I'll just wait and see.
Yeah... Shirakawa, I'll wait and wait until I'm ready to lose my mind...