Don't let go! Keep sucking.
It hurts, Shigezo-san!
Call me Sensei!
Inchou-sensei, it's so great!
inchou = principal
So warm, no!
No, not there!
I-It hurts!
An obedient girl can get boring.
Excuse me...
I came to enroll my child.
No, we're already closed.
What? But...
It's your fault for coming late.
People have been lining up for three days.
What's wrong Tomimatsu-sensei?
If my son doesn't get enrolled, my husband's parents will nag on us.
Must be hard for you.
I'll help you out.
Really!?
Thank you very much.
Oh, are you here for the job as well?
N-No, I'm here to enroll my son.
I see, so you have a son.
I can't have any, because my husband is sterile.
I'm here to apply for a job instead.
I see...
He said he'll hire me. He has connections...
I wonder if it's true...
He told me the same.
I heard rumors, that he is the brother of the principal.
I see.
Well, before you came, a rich looking girl went in for a private meeting.
So, you're saying that you'll "sponsor" the school, with whatever amount we wish?
Correct, looking around... it looks like you need to redecorate this place.
I'll give you the money, as long as you let my son in...
Your husband is an important man at a big corporation.
His father runs a bank.
And you are the only child of a wealthy family.
Looks like you have an easy life.
Don't forget that my mom has relatives working as politicians and doctors.
That is wonderful.
So you want to take care of this with money?
Yes, I knew we would be able to have a grownup conversation.
Understood.
Mizuho-sensei.
Yes...
We are finished with our grownup conversation.
From here on, let her understand the feelings of a child.
Please understand this is our system...
...and we would like the parents to take responsibility too.
Mizuho-kun, please help her change in the uniform.
Yes, Inchou-sensei.
What's the hold up.
What do they ask in the interview?
Dunno.
You're going home!?
It's called the restroom.
They don't need all this tape...
Can't be...
Smoking is not allowed here.
L-Leave!
Don't trash your cigarette there.
That's not the...!
Oh my, you just dirtied yourself.
Let me help you.
Here...
P-Please stop that.
Holding it in is bad for you.
No, let go!
Your ass feels great.
No, I can't hold it...!
I told you to let it out!
Do you want me to make it easier?
It hurts... it hurts!
Is this your first time?
It hurts!
Oh what's this, this isn't piss?
I-I've never experienced something like this...
This is so tight... how about this?
Wonderful...
Cuming, cuming, cuming!
OK, turn around and come back.
Yes, great job.
Pretend to be just like your son.
Why am I doing this...
I felt like this when I was... young...
It's dangerous so please move slowly.
I think I'm stuck...
If you move around, you'll hurt yourself.
Oh, you're not wearing a bra?
Mizuho-sensei told me to not wear anything underneath...
Yes, you told me that this would help them better understand.
That's not good, looks like it hurts.
Loosen her up.
Y-You don't need to do that.
Wow, so beautiful!
You aren't rich for nothing.
Your skin, your tits, they are so beautiful.
A child can't keep their eyes off amazing things.
And their mouth either.
Mizuho, let her experience pleasure.
W-What are you doing?
S-Stop it!
Look at these grownup panties.
This sure isn't suited for the situation.
You need to be punished.
What a bad girl, you're wetting yourself.
I-I didn't wet myself.
Then, why are you so wet?
Let me check and see if you're telling the truth.
I still don't know if this is your pee or not.
Let me smell this.
No, stop!!
It smells sweet and bitter at the same time.
I think I need to taste this to come up with an answer.
No... Inchou-sensei...!
No, stop now...
What's wrong, you want to end your lesson and go back to class?
No, don't stop...
More... no...
Rich girls also have their ass well maintained.
Hurry, come, come...
Front or back, which hole?
I don't care, hurry, hurry...!
She's gone, where is everyone?
This picture... principal and the teacher?
Isn't this...!?
Great, it's great!
More, more...
I've never done this...
Good, but tighter!
Our precious instruments...
You need to be punished.
Regardless of who the child is...
...at this school, any bad behavior will be punished equally.
Lets go take a tour.
Grip the mop harder and make it cleaner!
It's your piss!
I can't clean well like this.
Stop being so uptight.
Fine, I'll let you use modern technology.
See, now it's easier to clean.
Here.
Tomimatsu-sensei, sorry to bother you while you are cleaning, but...
...may I use the restroom?
Look what your slowness caused.
We can't let the principal use a dirty bathroom.
Get down and open your mouth.
Hurry up!
The sand, the sand is...!
The sand, the sand!
How cruel...
No matter how dirty they get, kids love playing with sand.
You have to understand that.
Alright, lets clean you up.
Cold!
Clean her ass too.
Yes, Inchou-sensei.
Coming, it's coming!
It's full!
No more will fit now.
No, no... I can't...
Remember to disinfect the playground.
Now you understand?
If you punish them correctly, they won't repeat the same mistakes.
Well, now it's your turn to be punished for mistreating the instruments.
Cymbals!
It's cold!
It hurts!
You've mistreated the instruments, therefore you'll get punished by the instruments.
Castanets!
P-Please stop!
It hurts, stop... please stop...
Xylophone!
It's the... batons!
The conductor!
First time for you, huh?
It hurts, stop...
It hurts!!
Not so rough...
Didn't you want this?
Here, lick the rod that went in to your ass! Clean it with your small mouth!
Alright, here I go...
It hurts!
Fine, I'll stop then.
Oh, are you intimidated, because you didn't do it for so long?
Hey, if you want it you have to ask for it!
Great, it's so great.
Inchou-sensei-sama, more!!
Alright!
Don't pull out!
Fine, have this instead.
How does the rage of the instruments feel like?
Lets try this hole too.
It hurts... but amazing!
Never felt this... cuming, cuming!
Amazing, cuming, cuming, cuming!
At this rate, it'll take you forever to get enrolled!