Time can often lead to certain emergencies.
For example, there's all kind of things that could happen on my trips to school by train.
But I never expected this to be one of them.
With this many people in the train, I can't even read.
Either way, I should at least figure out a way to get someone to save me.
There are plenty of men who take joy in doing this sort of things.
It really is despicable.
Just touch me and get it over with...
It's not like it really matters.
Sadly for you, I'm stone cold when it come's to sex.
I've tried to stimulate myself before out of curiosity, but...
Whether I touch my breast or my pussy...
I never get any feeling of pleasure or disgust out of it.
It's all just so...
Meaningless...
Fansubbed by htp://shin-hentai.com *X-Death
And then, he stuck his hand down my panties...
Wow! Awesome!
And then he started to rub me really hard until I came...
Well, I'm just so used to it now.
Yeah... I guess so...
Then again... There is a certain someone that none of the molestor go for...
Who could you possible mean? I'm pretty sure Sensei's popular with them, Isn't she?
They're all nothing but worthless scum.
As long as they're happy, I guess...
I've never been like other girls.
I've got a little more pride than they do.
I... I screwed up...!!
N... Nobody heard that, did they...?
Wh... What was that just now...?
I'm not like them...
That's why I can't get off like them...
Wh... What just happen there...
I was just startled. That's all...
No...! What is this...
No way! There's a bag pushing against me!
I can't move... Out here...!
Unless this crowd shift around, I won't be able to move my legs...
Geez! This is just the worst!
N... No...!
I can't believe this... What is he trying to do...?
Why...? Th... This can't be happening...?
Th... This shouldn't be... making me excited...
Wh... Why is this happening...?
I... I can't go on...
If I don't get a hold of myself...
Impossible...! This...
Hey... Wait! What is he...!?
No way! You've gotta be kidding me.
It's not what you think... It's just a sweat...
Because I'm so nervous...
Calm down. I just need to calm down...
I need to... think about something else...
I... I'll list of PI...
I... I can't go on...
Th... This isn't who I am...!
I'm not acting myself...!
What's he doing...!?
Th... This is a Man's...?
I can't believe this...
What is he trying to do...?
No... This is... filty...
It's... disgusting...!
Gross...
Filthy...
Disgusting...
My hand... My hand moved all on it's own...
This... Somehow... I need to...!
There's some strange liquid coming out of it... and It's throbbing harded and harder...!
Wait! Don't tell me...!?
W... Warm...! It's cumming...
His cum... It's all over my hand and clothes.
After all that, He still wants to touch my ass...?
N... No way! Where's he touching!?
How can he stick his finger in such a filthy place?
Even though... It's my asshole..
B... But... Right now... Compared to what it feels like up front...
No... What in the world am I saying...?
My head... It feels like...
Please! Hurry! Hurry up and reach the station...
His fingers are... going inside...!
I... I can't take this... It's impossible...!
It's... coming out...!
I can't... I can't hold it anymore...
Why...!? I don't care who it is...!
I... I'am sorry...!
I... Please forgive me....!
Please save me...! Save me!
N... No...!
What? Did someone wet themselves?
Look! It's that girl!
Whoa!
It... It's not that...
Awesome!
It's not what they think...
Wh... Why did this have to happen to me...!?
Hey, Shirakawa... Isn't it?
What happen...?
Sensei...?
Here take this.
Don't worry. You're gonna be alright, now.
Just by being... Inside Sensei's coat...
I Prayed that... I would just... disappear.
Is it the large crowds of people, that make you panic?
No.
So It's the station, the train, and the sounds associated with them?
Yes.
And you don't want to ride in a crowded train ever again?
Generally, It isn't something anyone wants to ride, anyways.
Yeah... I guess it's always more fun to counsel girls...
But if you'll come back...
That's alright.
More Importantly, can we just get this over with?
You're the one who insisted on booking this appointment in the first place, Kurahashi-Sensei.
I don't really need any counselling.
You've always been a smart girl, haven't you?
Your homeroom Teacher and I often chat about some of the girls in your class.
I don't like to hear about a concerned Teacher speaking about my behind my back.
Sorry. Oh? Could it be that you...?
No.
But, I still respect you and I'm still grateful.
Well... If you say so...
It's seems like you don't trust Men, Sumire-chan.
I guess with that kind of experience...
I just told you... It's got nothing to do with that...
You haven't laid a finger on either the tea or the snacks I put out, have you?
There... the tea and the snacks.
So lets end this.
Alright, fine...
Well then, I'm just going to give my report to Kurahashi, so wait here for a bit.
Geez... What a way to waste time.
Although, I guess I really should follow Sensei's recommendations...
but It's no used...
Is there something wrong?
N... No...
What is this...?
My head feels like it's going numb...
Sumire-chan.
Wait a minute, can you look at this.
Y... Yes.
Okay, try to follow along.
And keep going...
When did I ever get on the train...?
I can't even turn my head around.
A... Again...?
I'm not gonna let the same thing happen again.
My voice... It won't come out...?
No! What's going on here...!?
In... In any case, I might not be able to speak, but I can still fight back...
Yeah. Don't know why you can't speak?
All you can see is a crowd of people feeling you up.
Here you go...
Little by little...
Your body's speaking about your true desires.
Right now. Your entire body is being intensely stimulated.
It's reacting more and more by the minute.
Let go!
Finally, everyone is stretching out their hands to feel you.
Students and Businessmen.
They all lust after your body, Sumire-chan.
There... Do you fell the stimulation from everyone's fingers and tongues?
Your body's getting warmer by the minute.
It's not suprising. You're not as sexually frigid as you seem to think.
You've just been trying to think that way as much as you could in order to brakes on.
But, given the right situation...
See?
Well then, why don't we check to see just how sensitive you really are?
You break down so easily, Don't you? or is this the reason you find it difficult to put up with?
No way! Cut it out...!!
I told you to stop!
If you keep touching me down there...
Where am I...?
Wait a sec...
A Dream?
Why was I asleep? What happened...?
Oh? Sumire-chan? You're here a lot earlier than usual...
Well, I've got everything prepared for your arrival, anyways.
Earlier...
Earlier than usual...?
In the instant I started to panic...
My mind was swallowed up with darkness.
What... Is this?
Come on... Shake your ass to tell me you want me to tease you.
Don't hold back. We'll give you exactly what you want.
Wai... Stop that...!
You really do have a sexy butt.
What!? What are you doing!
No way...!
She's always got that uppity look on her face.
But in reality, she's just a pervert who wants to have her ass drilled all day long.
Everyone looking... my butt... and has a full view of it...
Here you go, Sumire-chan. It's your favorite anal vibrator.
Everyone can see it sliding into you.
Oh my... From this angle, I can see every crease of your ass being streched out through the camera.
And I can feel your spasms making the vibrator shake in my hand.
Check it out.
No matter how much it gets thrust in, It's like her ass is sucking down on it at all times.
Th... This bastard has tied me up and he's using me like a toy....!
Hey, Isn't that enough?
Go ahead and stick it in.
Now the vibrator's out, it almost looks like her ass begging for it.
No! Don't! If your going to...
Here's the dick you've been waiting for...
Today, we'll fuck you until you have trouble keeping your ass closed.
Why...? Why does this have to happen to me...?
Still it feels so good that I think I'm about to faint.
Shirakawa's ass is so sexy!
Whoa! She's really stretching out...
What if... What if Sensei were to see me like this...?
Come on... Raise your head so that Kurahashi-Sensei will be able to see you getting fucked.
S... Sensei...?
That's right, Sumire-chan.
I'm gonna show your beloved Sensei plenty of video of you getting fucked.
And he'll end up stroking himself off while he watches.
Th... There's just... no way...
If it were Sensei...
If... If it were Kurahashi-sensei...
He would never sit back... and watch...
What the hell? Why don't you moan some more?
Come on. Shirakawa, hang in there!
Please... just make it end...
Here! Take it all up your ass!
With this... I'll finally wake up.
Yeah... I've been dreaming all this time...
Wh... Again!?
Why hasn't it ended...!?
And also... Sensei's the one fucking me... This isn't right...
Thy're all... acting different from before...
Sensei's.... fucking my ass...
This isn't what I want...!
This Sensei is an impostor...
Please, pull it out... Pull it out! Pull it out!
I don't want to do this with... Sensei...
How could I get turned in front of the scum...?
I don't want this...!!
Well then...
How did you want to get fucked?
Go ahead and tell me.
I'll keep stirring up your ass until you're satisfied, Sumire-chan.
I'll keep going until your nipples and your clit are standing up.
After all, this is what you wished for.
Show everyone that you do have some appeal.
Is that... How it is...?
I... I'm...
Shirakawa!
Okay, Shirakawa! Here it comes!
It's Okay, Shirakawa...! I'll cum inside you, so let's do it at the same time...!
It's Sensei's cum...!
Sensei's cum is filling up my belly...
Sorry.
Are you startled?
N... No...!
You really startled me...
You suddenly collapsed in the counselling...
It's look like you're alright.
Y... Yes...
What's going on... This counselling...
What happened...