Hitozuma Life
What am I thinking to go all the way and buy this?
Being this desperate on getting
myself off at this age...
I look like an idiot.
I got carried away by pleasure.
I spread my legs open for men other than
my husband, and now I became like this.
Since then, I've been getting
calls from unknown numbers.
It's most likely from those kids.
I know that it'll be over if I answer.
But if they call again now, I...
Y-Yes?!
Oh no! I answered it...
H-H-Hello...
Ah, mama? Are you home now?
Oh! It's just you, Aya...
What do you mean it's just me? Whatever.
Papa won't be home today, right?
Ah... That's right.
Can my boyfriend stay over tonight?
We're already right outside the house.
Why don't you always say anything until the last second?
You're too loud.
Jeez! Why did they have to
be here now of all times?
What should I do about this?
I'm home!
Sorry, we're you busy?
No, It's alright.
That was close. She never saw it, right?
Mama, he's the man I'm currently dating.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kijima Youichi.
Why is this kid here?!
#3 will... give #1 a blowjob.
It's okay, right? Can he stay over tonight?
That would be...
Of course not! Do you know
what kind of man he is?
She said you can stay overnight. Let's go Yo-chan!
Really?
Wait...
Let's go!
W-What should I do?
I'm sure they're gonna do it. I need stop...
No... Now I'm imagining about his thing
which I got to know rashly at that time.
I need to pull this out before they find out,
I'm so wet!
Luckily it seemed that they never
noticed it, so maybe...
I should just continue?
Continue what?
Eh? You're the type who uses toys.
W-Wait!
I-I've been found out!
Don't get that flustered. Didn't you
do stuffs more amazing than this?
I've been seen!
Huh? Isn't that you, Airi-chan?
He
found
out
!!
He found out!!
Who knew that far from even having
a boyfriend, you even have a child.
Wait—
I always check it when hitting on girls.
You're also wearing this last time, right?
And that mole on the left breast.
Hey!
These huge breasts with a
sexy mole at the right areola.
You won't find any woman
with these traits that easily.
You already disguised and picked up guys.
Are you still unsatisfied, Airi-chan?
You're wrong, that was...
Why am I getting turned on?
I need to change the topic...
Hey, are you properly wearing
one when you do it with Aya?
Hey...
Aya's still in high school! What were you thinking?
Well... doing it raw feels way better.
If you say it like that...
What?
Then let me do you raw in
place of your daughter, lady.
W-Why me... Hey, stop this!
I'll be wearing a condom
when doing it with Aya.
What are you saying?!
You already can't control
your desires as well, right?
I'll be using this body well.
No, no! I said no!
Just like that...
He did it like it was nothing!
This one is in good condition!
I'll be use this a lot just like your daughter's.
It's tight! This kid is just too big!
I really regret letting you go away last time.
But I ended up getting to fuck both
the mother and daughter so it's fine.
To think that this filthy thing
has been penetrating Aya...
Did you find the bathroom?
Are you alright? Should I come down?
Wait, stop moving! Aya will hear us!
What should we do? Wanna finish this now?
Of course we can't! Hurry up and pull it out!
Shit! I guess we'll have to save
the fun for tonight! Oh well...
Don't worry, I'll keep that promise.
Wear something sexy and wait for me.
Okay...
Hey, are you really gonna film this?
Of course!
I originally wanted to film Aya,
but I decided to record our sex instead.
So, is that your special lingerie?
You're fine! I like your gal attire,
but this is how a housewife should look like!
Stop ogling on me!
And you look good with your hair down.
You're face is beet red!
Did that make you feel happy?
T-There's no way I—
It reeks of tobacco... How nostalgic.
My husband used to smoke too in the past.
Hey, can you leave Aya alone?
Well... Isn't she looking forward doing it?
I made up an excuse and she went to sleep like that.
Your daughter is so simple. Rather,
both mother and child are simple.
W-We're doing it like this?
What are you saying? You're already this wet.
It feels better doing it together. Here you go.
Oh, seeing my dick made you more drenched.
You don't have to say every details.
I can't help it. This is all I've
been thinking about lately.
My nose is getting filled with a man's scent.
My female parts are responding
to it even if I hate it.
Hey, how did my dick inside you feel earlier?
How did...
Just tell me how was it.
I was surprised...
for something this big to go inside me.
I'm turned on.
I'm gradually losing control with every word.
Every time it pushes up my insides...
Every time?
It hurts but it also feels good!
I-I'm coming!
Hey, don't come by yourself alone.
Let's continue this whole night of fun.
Are we really gonna do it raw?
Why are you getting cold feet now?
That's...
It's alright, I'll just come outside.
I don't want to take any responsibilities.
This kid really isn't taking anything seriously.
Just doing it raw itself is risky already.
This is really huge after all!
Don't be like that. It's already the second
time so it's easier to take it in now.
And if you're this soaked, you
should be feeling good as well.
What's this? It feels so good!
It's far from how it was earlier!
It's been a while since I had
my whole dick inside!
Housewife pussies are
really on a different level!
W-Wait! Pull it out, please!
Why are you pulling your
hip away? Didn't it feel good?
D-Don't!
Y-You're wrong! Don't move!
No, I'm not.
You like it here, right?
What is this? It's feels too good!
Both you and your daughter are loose down here.
Maybe your daughter isn't your husband's.
That's not true!
Really?
Then, I'll knock you up
with another man's seed.
I'm quite confident in my semen.
Stop joking...
I've decided now, a creampie
would be good, right?
Of course not!
It's my ovulating day.
Didn't you let them fill you up last time?
We really can't today!
I see...
Then I'll just come in your daughter.
That's the original plan anyway.
Ah, I'll go when I pull this out.
W-Wait, don't you get it?
You'll get me pregnant!
I told you I'm not taking
any responsibilities.
Just turn me down if
you really don't want to.
I already knew it, he's a beast!
Here, I'm pulling out. What will you do?
If he comes inside me today...
I might get pregnant.
But I can't just let him impregnate my daughter!
This means I can creampie you, right?
Then, I won't hold back and fill you up.
I'll record this moment that you get impregnated.
Something big is coming!
I can't hold it any longer! I'm coming! Coming!
I-I'm coming! I'm coming...
Here, open your womb and catch everything!
I'm coming!
Wow, I came so much!
Unsafe sex really is the best!
I live nearby, so I'll drop by
here from time to time.
Close? Kijima?
Kijima Youichi. Only child. 2nd year College.
Always fooling around with girls.
Close to failing this school year.
she found it out
At home, he shows a strong and
concerning amount of mother complex.
So that was you.
How did you know?
I'm close with your mother.
We're what they call "mommy friends".
So in place of your mom, you're going for
wives and girls with boyfriends instead.
It's a bull's-eye, right? You're such a kid.
If you want to be spoiled like a kid, just say so.
Hey, come here Youichi.
I'll be your mama just for today.
I'll be loving you a lot.
Okay.
Youichi, does it feel good?
Yeah. It feels good, mama.
Mama, can I?
Okay, I'll drink all of it using my womb.
Mama, I'm coming!
Shoot it inside mama.
Pour all of your semen in my deepest parts!
Deeper, Youichi!
Mama!
Coming! I'm coming!
Shoot it deep in me, Youichi!
It's so hot!
There's so much of your hot stuff!
Your mouth feels so amazing, mama!
Your tits are also incredible!
Hey, Youichi. Where do you want to shoot next?
Mama's tits, or inside my mouth?
I-In your mouth!
Drink it all, mama!
Delicious!
Shoot the last one inside me.
So huge! I knew it!
This is bad! I'll quickly come
when you pump like that!
That's because your dick feels
so good, I can't hold myself back!
I'm coming, mama!
It's alright. Do it, Youichi.
Take all of my semen
without leaving a single drop!
Mama will come together with Youichi!
I'm... Coming!
You're pouring so much of it inside me!
Hey...
Can I pay a visit here again?
Only if you start attending college again.
Yeah, I will!
Then, you can come here anytime.
Several Months Later
I'm back!
Pardon my intrusion!
Welcome home!
It already grew that big.
Do you already know what it will be?
To get pregnant at her age, papa really worked hard!
Eh?!
R-Right...
Hey, Aya!
Stop talking like that!
Okay~!
I'll help on anything after you give birth.
Really?
Please leave it to me!
I see, then...
Take care of us, papa.
What's with him?
Who knows?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization