Good morning everyone!
Our interview for today will be...
the beach-side commercial street's Café Sakurai.
Why does everyone say that the service in this cafe is unique?
Well then, let's go in and take a look.
Welcome!
Welcome.
Welcome to Sakurai Café!
－FOOLISHED－
Let me recommend our coffee float.
We made the ice cream in it by ourselves.
Sorry to make you wait.
Here's your order of Tomato Omelette Rice.
S-Such a cute waitress...
The uniform looks good on you.
Shall I bring you more coffee?
That would be 430 Yen.
Thank you very much.
Take care of your breasts.
There.
T-Thank you very much.
Please come again.
What should I do, Kyosuke...?
I heard the TV station is coming over for an interview.
It can't be helped so you have to sound more confident.
And mother, you're the boss around here.
But I'm not too good at these things...
A lot of people would be watching this on TV.
If I fail, everyone will make fun of me.
Well, that could happen too...
Papa in Heaven, Kyosuke has turned bad and is bullying his poor mother.
Oh man, you're pretty hopeless...
Don't worry mother, everything's gonna be alright.
Kyo-kyosuke...
How is it? Are you feeling better now?
Thank you.
Natsuki-senpai! N-No... it's nothing like what you're thinking.
Nothing?
You don't need to make excuses.
Everyone knows Kyosuke lusts for his mother.
Like I said, that's not it!
Oh well... Kyosuke-san, Sakurako-san, we're in the middle of work you know.
Now, now, Shino-san, take it easy.
Sakurako-san, it's almost time for the interview.
Yes, I understand. Here we go.
How did you come up with a Cosplay service?
Umm... It's actually quite a long story...
But everyone just wants to put an effort to make this place livelier,
and to draw more people here.
Hmm? I thought the purpose of that was to
compete with that Ocean Land Café by the bus stop?
Isn't that right, Mayu?
Lisa, you can't say that outright on national TV.
Moreover, the waitresses here look very young and attractive!
Is it true that all of them are housewives?
Thank you.
Actually, one of them is the mother of that guy.
To end it off, do have a few words to say to our viewers.
Yes, Café Sakurai is only a 5 minute walk away from the station.
We're situated at the south side of the commercial street.
Customers can dine in their swimsuits and there's also an outdoor seating.
To those going to the beach, please be sure to visit our cafe.
Well, our work is all done.
Good work everyone.
Thank you for the hard work Claire-san, Mayu-chan, and Lisa-chan.
I'll be here to help with Mayu again.
Lisa, you've got to finish your holiday homework first.
Mom! You always mention homework every time.
Please take care on your way home.
Alright, today's profits are pretty good.
Let's beat that other cafe,
and then become Ocean Land's supervisor.
I guess it's not a simple task to achieve...
Hold it... don't say things like that, please.
The reason why I've taken up the managing role in this cafe,
is because...
Kyosuke, thanks for the work today.
Business is good today too.
Congrats, congrats!
N-Natsuki-senpai...
Let's hold a celebration at my house tonight.
I'll go ahead and prepare first, you come over quick.
A... ce-celebration...
That's right, just like what you think.
How's it Kyosuke, feeling excited?
Senpai, we shouldn't be doing this.
It's too bad, even though my guy at home sees me in these outfits,
he's still too shy about it. What a let down...
I think that's enough, isn't your husband just by the next room?
No problem, he's not going to wake up after drinking anyway.
Anyway, what do you think of my body?
Can't control yourself anymore, can you?
Control you say...
Now let's see, what's going on... here!
Seems like you've been holding it...
S-Senpai...
I'm gonna turn off the lights.
Senpai, I... I haven't cleaned myself yet...
Don't worry, I like it this way.
It's big... so big... It's throbbing inside my mouth...
So good... You're so lewd, senpai.
Shoot it all out!
Sorry, senpai...
It's ok...
Move your hips more.
That's... no good...
Comparing sizes you win...
But you lose at hardness.
Don't say such things.
You're getting harder hearing these things.
Wait... I really can't hold it anymore!
It's ok, shoot it in my mouth... shoot it all out.
Senpai...
Seems like you're not done yet, it's still so hard.
Well...
Next, it's my turn... let me feel good.
W-Wait, don't you think it's not good to do this?
I'm going, look at me.
It's going in...
Try not to move.
We'll get found out if we make too much noise.
A-Ah... so tight...
It's penetrating... does your cock feel good? You want it to be tighter?
Can't believe I did it again, having sex with senpai.
It's hitting and rubbing real good.
So good!
No... Stop moving so much or I'll start making noises.
So amazing senpai, it's already so wet.
If anyone sees this scene...
You're already enjoying seeing it, you horny little kid.
Good, it's going so deep...
Thrust harder... your cock feels so much better than my husband's.
You're bad senpai, saying such things.
You're enjoying feeling so good yourself.
Can't blame me... I can't take it anymore...
It's going in and out... feels so good!
S-Senpai... we're...
I can't stop... my hips won't stop moving.
Don't be so rough, slow down...
I... I can't...
Good... good...
What's up with that expression?
I'm thinking about what we just did, senpai.
Yeah, we did it again.
I guess this is what they call a fling.
Idiot! That's not it.
This is just two persons getting drunk.
And both of them thought about having sex, so they couldn't help but satisfy each other.
Is that so?
Don't give that expression,
or someone's going to find out about us.
Still, I'm feeling a tinge of guilt in me...
At that time, I was oblivious to what was happening at the cafe.
I forgot to bring along my keys. Seems like I'm feeling really tired today...
Lisa...
Mayu, can I lick for a little more?
S-Sure...
I've always wanted to do this to Mayu in this uniform.
Me too.
What?! What are they doing?
Shouldn't they be at home?
Mayu, did that feel good?
That felt good, Lisa.
Please do it here too.
You're so naughty, Mayu...
No way... I have to stop them...
But if I try to stop them now, maybe even I...
W-Why am I in this uniform.
Because our shameful secret is discovered by Shino-san.
It's your turn this time, Shino-san.
B-But...
Wow, it's sucked so tightly! You're so ecchi, Shino-san.
Wait... stop, Lisa-chan. This uniform is really tight.
If that's the case, let us make it loose for you.
Wait, Mayu-chan!
S-Stop...
Shino-san's breasts are so soft and feels so good.
Stop, Mayu-chan...
Such erotic things...
Shino-san, your nipples are getting hard.
Let's check out here too.
No, don't look there!
It's so wet already... all dripping and falling out.
This can't be true...
I'm in the cafe naked and doing such shameful things...
And I'm feeling something...
Kyosuke, Shino-san is ready for you.
Kyosuke-kun!? Why...
What?
Shino-san, I'm coming in.
E-Eh?
Stop!
Wow, it all went in!
No, please... take it out! It's so embarrassing.
Seems like Shino-san is feeling real good.
I knew it, she wanted to do this from the start.
No, it's not true!
I've never thought about that, please let me go.
Shino-san, let me give you more pleasure.
No... my nipples, not so hard...
I can't...
It's inside... your cum is inside me!
Wow... so much of it is dripping out...
No, stop...
I just came, and it's very sensitive now.
Shino-san, Kyosuke won't be satisfied with just that.
W-What?
Let me examine your body again.
Stop... anymore of this would be too much.
It seems you're still restraining yourself.
Stop...
I can't...
Shino-san's pussy is all wet and warm from the thrusting.
No... this can't be...
I can't... I'm reaching my limit!
It's ok, you can come if you want to.
Please... Inside me, release it all inside me...
W-What was I doing?
They shouldn't have noticed me yet.
Oh no, it's already so late!
Let's go home already, Lisa.
We'll get scolded if mom found out that we sneaked in here again.
Welcome!
Please take a seat over here.
This is the menu. Please call me when you've decided with your order.
This is just 2 persons getting drunk.
And both of them thought about having sex, so they couldn't help but satisfy each other.
Is that so?
Don't give that expression,
or someone's going to find out about us.
I guess it's better to properly reject her as soon as possible.
Eh, what's the matter?
Ah, no... it's nothing...
Kyosuke, you're behaving oddly today...
You didn't eat anything for breakfast today.
Did anything happen?
Don't worry about it. It has nothing to do with you, mother.
Yes...
But if there's anything I can be of help with, please say so, ok?
Umm, Kyosuke-kun.
Yes?
I'm about to go home.
I've already done a check in the storage room.
Oh, ok. Sorry about that, Claire-san. Thank you for your effort.
But then, Kyosuke-kun...
W-What is it?
The one at home has a meeting tonight and is coming home late...
And Lisa went over to Mayu's house...
This is a chance for us.
Claire-san, why did you suddenly...
Because... you did it with Natsuki-chan, am I wrong?
H-How did you know?
You can't hide it from me, it's written all over your face.
Claire-san...
I'll be waiting at home. Please come after giving it some thought.
Ah... w-wait...
Kyosuke, have you arranged the stuff outside?
Hmm, did he leave already?
So this is Claire-san's room...
Your ice coffee is here.
Although you may have drunk it many times in the cafe.
Claire-san... your outfit...
I've prepared this outfit for the next time at work.
What do you think, Master?
M-Master?
I'll be your maid for tonight.
Please don't do that.
Why can't I?
It's not that you can't, but...
Don't be so nervous about it.
I will serve you well, Master.
Wait... I'm still...
Are you thinking if we should be doing this?
Because Claire-san is already...
Let's not think about that now.
Claire-san...
Is it your first time doing it like this?
Well... yes...
Please stay still.
Kyosuke's cock is quite sensitive.
It's reacting so fast...
That's because Claire-san's lips and breasts feel so soft and nice.
Thank you.
Feels so good...
Please try not to move.
I know, but...
I'll let you feel real good in a while.
I can't... I'm sorry...
not good enough...
Don't hold it in, come anytime you want.
I can't anymore...
Claire-san!
Wow! You came so much...
I'm so sorry I soiled your outfit.
It's ok, don't worry about it.
Claire-san, what are you doing?
Don't tell me...
You want to go home with just a blowjob?
While I was sucking Kyosuke-kun, I'm already...
So wet...
You're so late, Kyosuke...
Where in the world did he go?
We finally had a chance to enjoy dinner together. I even made so many of his favorite dishes.
It's getting bigger...
It's in all the way...
Claire-san!
Wait, if you do that now...
Stop, I'm feeling too good now...
Claire-san, try to keep your voice down.
I'm so sorry I can't help it...
It feels so good!
Wait, don't suck it so tightly... I'll come again!
Kyosuke's cock is throbbing so hard.
So warm...
I-I can't... I'm coming...
Together.
In the next episode, we'll let you see all of us.
Today, our service will end here.
Hitozuma Cosplay Kissa 2 Last Episode.
Set to be released on Winter of 2007.
Today is Erotic Cosplay Day.