Careful, don't let them discover us...
I didn't expect girls in this coffee shop are so pretty.
Awesome!
Those breasts are huge!
Even the panties are exposed!
That gorgeous one with the eyeglasses... her breasts could explode!
What a nice ass!
Good... very impressive!
It's frustrating, I'm getting hard...
Me... me too...
Umm, excuse me...
Are you secretly taking pictures of us?
No... this is... that...
No, don't misunderstand me.
I just want to see how I looked in those pictures.
Ah, this is probably it.
Oh no, I don't look good... it's embarrassing.
No, you look really lovely.
It'll be immensely popular on the Internet!
With such a beautiful girl working here, I just have to see it myself.
I'm not young anymore, I already have a mature son.
S-Son!?
I'm perplexed... you don't look like a working wife...
Yes, moreover, I'm not really working here. I'm the owner.
－FOOLISHED－
Those asses totally rule.
You're wrong, big breasts are the best.
Oh my, why are all customers the same, it's so frustrating!
It's ok, they promised not to put those pictures on the Internet.
And they have ordered quite a fair bit of food.
Anyway, isn't Sakurako-san wearing quite a daring swimsuit?
R-Really?
Aha, Kyosuke, how is it?
Did you get all excited seeing Sakurako's swimsuit?
How is it?
I was thinking if I tried wearing this, our service might be much better.
Yeah, not bad.
Heh, embarrassed?
There's still an awkward mood between my mother and I.
What if people sees us?
Move a little and let me take a clearer look.
Yes, very good. I can see everything.
This is embarrassing.
Showing all in this place, with a cock in my mouth...
This is so embarrassing, but why...
Senpai, you're already feeling something, your vagina's all wet.
Feels good! Kyosuke, not too rough...
Come, let me see your breasts next.
Ok, I get it.
How about this?
This is good...
You've got me all hard, senpai.
Not so rough!
Natsuki-senpai, don't you like it this way?
You seem excited being treated this way.
No... it's not...
It's not like that...
So good...
Please, come quick... I can't take it any longer...
Senpai, I'm gonna shoot a full load into your mouth.
Senpai, we should be returning soon.
Hey Kyosuke, why did you bring me to this island?
Only to satisfy your cock?
You'd better prepare to get punished.
I found something good.
Honey.
Like this...
Claire-san...
Go ahead, please lick all you want.
Don't rush like that...
T-Tongue...
So hot...
There... keep going...
Claire-san, your breasts...
Please don't say it, it's embarrassing.
C-Can't, it's coming out...
Not there, it's too intense...
My nipples are getting hard...
Claire-san...
My breasts are so numb, I'm coming!
Wow, it's so much.
I'm sorry, my breasts came first.
Claire-san...
Kyosuke-kun, is it ok to continue?
Eh?
I'm already so wet...
So please... put it in...
So... so good...
Move some more...
No matter what I do with Natsuki-senpai or Claire-san,
I'd still feel a lack of satisfaction.
Why is that so? I slowly began to understand why...
Forgive me, Kyosuke. I'm sorry.
I can't... although I know I shouldn't do this, my fingers aren't listening...
Mother...
No, it's too good.
I'm sorry, papa.
Kyosuke... Kyosuke...
Mother.
No, don't look!
No, Kyosuke... stop!
I really want to do it with you, mother.
No... you can't, I'm your mother.
I... I already knew it.
You're in fact not my real mother.
Kyo-Kyosuke...
So... I want to have sex with you.
I love you so much, I'm sorry.
Kyosuke...
This is so embarrassing...
You're already so wet.
I'm sorry, I was doing it myself just now so it's already...
Seems like you're getting excited.
You too, Kyosuke.
I can see it, your cock is so huge now.
So good... it's so good...
There... more...
Where do you like it more?
Don't ask such things, it's embarrassing.
No, you have to tell me.
There... right there, it's so good right there!
Very good, you're so cute when you're like that.
Kyosuke's the pervert one. It's so big I've got to punish it.
It's good, it feels so good.
Your cock is so hard it's throbbing.
I can't take it anymore.
So good, your tongue is coming in...
I'm feeling it, the place Kyosuke is licking at.
The juice I've reserved for Kyosuke is all coming out.
I'm already...
I want Kyosuke's cock inside me.
It's coming in!
So hot...
It's ok, move all you want.
So hard... it's rubbing me inside...
Mother, it's... so tight!
Come to think of it, papa once said:
"The bigger the cock, the tighter Sakurako's pussy gets
that sucks it like a magnet."
G-Good! Penetrate it deeper!
I... I can't hold it anymore.
Don't grab it so hard!
I'm... already...
C-Come...
You came... your sperm is inside me...
I'm sorry, I came inside.
It's ok, it's safe for me today.
Kyo-Kyosuke, it's getting bigger again.
I'll move this time.
If it's sucking so tightly again...
But my body itself is...
Kyosuke, let me do the moving.
But...
Your cock is filling up my vagina.
So embarrassing! My vagina is all wet and it's making squishy sounds.
Kyosuke, not so rough...
No... I'm coming already.
It's ok... just shoot your sperm inside me.
Let's come together.
I'm coming too...
Co-Coming...
Seems like you've been waiting for this, Kyosuke. You came so much, it's my first time seeing it.
I'm sorry, I feel like I'm forcing you into this...
Don't be, I want to do it with Kyosuke too.
But...
That's why, neither one of us are forcing one another. Right?
After that, a day like always have once again started.
I'll do the drinks and account. Kyosuke, you're responsible for preparing the food, ok?
Ok, no problem.
Are the ingredients ready?
Don't worry, we have enough time for that.
Seems like we're not going to win those two.
Natsuki-chan, are you serious about that?
Well, a bit.
How about you Claire?
It's a secret.
Everyone, the results for our competition this month with Ocean Café is already out.
Who won? Who won?
Everyone, don't be too anxious.
Could it be...
We won?
It's regrettable, but this time it's our loss.
As per agreement, we will cancel the plans for the commercial street in this area.
We succeeded! Kyosuke!
Wait... mother...
Finally, Kyosuke.
This way Sakurai Café need not close down.
Your hard work has finally paid off.
Not really. It's thanks to Natsuki-senpai, Claire-san, and everyone, that we made it.
Well, we helped too. That's why we succeeded.
Lisa, really...
Lisa-chan, Mayu-chan, and Shino-san, thank you very much.
Sakurako-san, I didn't do anything...
Another thing, since the competition is over,
then our Cosplay is going to end too?
It's possible...
Then let's do a "Special Cosplay" for the last time!
Eh?
Let's do the last full-fledged COSPLAY service.
How's this Kyosuke?
Are you actually getting excited?
Senpai, isn't that dress a bit too much for this cafe?
It's ok, Kyosuke-kun. This is less revealing than the swimsuits.
That may be true, but... this is much more lewd compared to the swimsuit.
A-Although it's embarrassing to say this,
but quite a lot of customers requested this outfit.
Let's do our best today!
But looking like that... what if they try to do something funny?
It'll be fine! I'm sure Kyosuke is going to protect us when the time comes.
Why do I also need to wear this?
Hurry! Come on, Shino-san.
The more you hide it, the more embarrassing it gets.
I'll have to get back to Ocean Café soon.
Ara... why are you still saying this?
If you're not helping,
I'll let everyone know about you masturbating that day!
That...
Seems like I don't have a choice...
But wearing this... customers are going to think of me as perverted.
Customer-sama, I'm going to start servicing you now.
It's so tasty...
Sa-Sakurako-san...
Shino-san, you want to taste some cock too right?
No... I...
Don't just stand there, let's lick it together.
Yes.
Customer-sama, there's something flowing out from the tip of your cock.
Your cock is so tasty.
You've been waiting for my breasts, right?
Let me fuck your cock with my tits.
Does this feel good?
My breasts feel so good with your cock rubbing on it...
You came so much. Let me clean it up.
Be good and don't move.
Eh? Taking it off myself is so embarrassing.
Come touch the perverted rabbit's vagina.
Yes, good...
Good... it feels so good...
Yes... there...
The place where you stick your cock in... good...
Make it all wet.
W-Wait...
T-That is...
No, don't use that...
It's coming in!
It feels weird...
It's rubbing me... so hard and rough...
Good...
I... I came using a carrot.
Please, use the carrot again and stick it in.
Lisa, here I come. Take it easy.
It's coming in.
Lisa...
It's ok, I'll do it for Mayu this time.
Ok, come, Lisa.
I'm... now one with Lisa.
Mayu, there... it's so good... it's moving real good...
Lisa, not so rough!
Everyone's looking and I'm feeling it too much...
I'm sorry, Mayu...
I feel so good... I can't stop it...
Now, let's get started.
It's coming in!
It's rubbing... feels so good...
No, it's real sensitive there...
Don't use your finger!
No... stop... stop moving please!
Getting penetrated repeatedly...
No... I'm feeling it... can't take it anymore.
This position is so embarrassing.
Please, stop it now! I can't take it much more.
Such a weird feeling...
My asshole is feeling so hot...
Wait, please, do it more gently...
Oh... so good...
Asshole... so hot... feels so good...
Can't stop moving... I'm coming soon...
Don't shoot it in yet.
Nipples... don't play with my nipples...
Stop...
Stop, if you keep on doing that... I can't take it anymore...
Hot... so hot...
I can't take it anymore...
Let's come together...
First time doing it like this...
Asshole... my ass is coming... your cock is so hot...
It's ok to come inside. Hurry, hurry up and come inside me...
Good! So good!  I'm almost at my limit... Everyone let's come together.
Shino-san, what happened?
We're starting work soon, are you ok?
Y-Yes, no problem! I'll go get myself prepared.
Oh dear, I can't believe I thought about those things.
Seems like I'm really sexually deprived.
Today is Cosplay Day!
Welcome!
Welcome to Sakurai Café!