Wait, Daddy! Can you drive me part of the way there?
Aya!
Did you do your laundry?
It's still in your room, isn't it?
Sorries!
Could you, like, do it for me?
My goodness.
Thanks, Mom! See ya later!
Life of a Married Woman
one time gyaru
Seriously, how does she manage
to not do laundry for this long?
She probably just waits for me to
do it because I'm so soft on her.
Wow, this is flashy.
When did she even buy this?
Seriously, who did she learn this from?
Hey, I can pull this off!
I've still got it!
It'd be a shame not to show this off to someone...
It's a bit early, but maybe I can hit up the grocery store.
Wow, that girl over there is so pretty!
I can't believe I'm actually doing this.
Everyone's looking at me...
Maybe this was a bad idea...
Karaoke
I still have a bit of time before the afternoon sale.
I'll kill some time here.
Hey, check this one out.
She looks ditzy as fuck.
As long as we can make a quick buck off her.
What's up?
Yeah, she's perfect!
She doesn't look your type, though.
Yeah, you're into MILFs, right?
Fuck off. All I care about is
smashing my face into big tits.
In order for me to make you a
membership card, I'll need to see your ID.
Oh, no! If I give him my ID, he'll figure me out!
See that woman? She's actually an old hag.
Ew, seriously?
Act your age, granny!
How would I face my family if that happens?
Hey, are you by yourself?
We were just about to start a round. Wanna join us?
No way! Am I getting hit on?!
It's been ages!
A-Are you sure?
Yeah.
It's kinda lonely with just us three guys.
– We'll take the usual room.
– What's your name?
I'll cut the cameras. Just don't do
anything that'll attract the cops.
– Airi. Nice to meet you.
Yeah, I know. Let's do this.
You're so good at this, Airi-chan!
And you're so bad!
Shut up!
This is so much fun! I feel like I've gotten younger.
Wow, you can really kick those back.
Can you really handle all that?
Yeah, no problem!
Keep 'em coming!
She got drunk on her own...
She's making this too easy.
All right, let's get started.
Airi-chan?
Let's play the King's Game. It'll be fun.
Yeah, that does sound fun!
Okay. Let's see... How about you draw first?
That was close. I almost passed out!
Hell, yeah! I'm the king!
What number are you, Airi-chan?
Nope, it's a secret!
Aw, come on. Just a peek.
Okay, how about number three blows number one?
Huh?
Huh? By "blow" does he mean, like, a blowjob?
All right, Airi-chan. I'm in your hands.
Do you three always do this sort of thing?
C'mon, we're all adults here. Let's have a little fun.
You guys are like kids to me...
Although this thing right here certainly isn't...
Oh, wow, you're a real go-getter.
Why don't we let those tits breathe a little?
H-Hey...
I'm a little shy...
Why? You have the largest tits I've ever seen!
Really?
You can look, but no touching, okay?
Will my old woman breasts really turn them on?
Sheesh, I told you no touching...
It'd be a shame not to touch these babies!
God, they're so soft.
R-Really?
Just look how hard I am.
What the heck? It's so hard!
And so long!
Guys can get this big?
C'mon, give it a little suck.
You can do it.
It has such a strong smell, too.
Hmm? Do you like the smell of dick?
Huh? I dunno...
C'mon, you were totally sniffing it just now.
This isn't good.
My body's starting to get turned on.
I need to end this quickly.
Damn, you're good.
You must have a lot of practice.
Hey, mind if I try something out?
Holy shit! You're the first person
able to swallow my entire dick!
Don't choke on it, okay?
Just how deep do you intend on going?
His dick's starting to twitch.
He's about to cum, isn't he?
I think I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Keep it up, Airi-chan!
Be sure to swallow it, okay?
What a strong scent...
I could choke on the stench alone.
C'mon, show me!
Oh, shit, you actually drank it all!
This is bad. If I don't stop now, I'll totally lose it.
Okay, next round. Here's your number, Airi-chan.
– And this time, I'm the king!
– Number one...
Number one will give number three a boob job!
Hell yeah!
Wait! Hold on!
I'm not as long as my buddy,
but I'm pretty thick, right?
Wow, it's huge!
It's completely different than my
husbands or that other guy's!
Okay, but just for the record, sex is off limits.
Of course!
By the way, do you have a boyfriend?
Huh?
Well, yeah... Sorta.
He's my husband though.
I bet he asks for boob jobs all the time!
How many times have you made him
cum with these tits of yours?
I don't know!
Wow, too many times to count?
Oh man, I'm so hard!
Your soft skin is the best!
These kids are so big...
Huh? You're this wet from just sucking his dick?
Damn, that's hot.
You must play with this a lot.
It feels good...
Was I really this turned on?
I bet it'd feel great to shove my dick in here.
Hey, how about I put mine in?
Absolutely not!
My dick's circumcised, so it'll feel real good.
I'm so wet right now...
I haven't been this aroused in such
a long time... It's almost scary.
God, you're so hot!
Just a little more...
Holy shit! My dick is completely buried in your tits!
You're gonna make me blow my load in record time!
I guess it's too late to back out now...
No!
You're gonna make me cum!
I'm really gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Here it comes!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Oh my God!
Here it comes!
I'm cumming! You're making me cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Damn, you came so hard.
Must've been a while since your last time, huh?
We're done with the game, right? I'm gonna put it in.
– N-No!
I told you, no sex!
I was just fooling around earlier, but...
You're just too fucking hot. I can't hold back.
I had a feeling this would happen... This is bad.
C'mon, we've come this far already.
I mean, it's your fault I'm this hard.
What should I do?
Should I put it in?
We'll just do it once, okay?
You haven't done this in a while either, right?
Whew, she's spreading her legs! We're good to go!
Damn, you're wet.
Is this really okay?
These guys are complete strangers,
and here I am spreading my legs for them.
I'll make you feel really good.
Y-You're not wearing a condom...
Oh, sorry, I don't have one on me.
You got one?
No...
Then I guess that's that.
We'll do it raw.
It's inside me!
It's hitting my deepest spots!
We're really having sex!
How's it feel?
Amazing!
Her pussy's gripping me real tight.
We hit the jackpot with this chick.
Oh my God! It's so deep!
Yes!
I love me a good pussy.
I can't get enough of how wet and tight it is!
Wait!
You're being too rough!
You really do have the best tits and pussy, Airi-chan.
You could make loads selling your body.
What are you saying?
Let's do it doggy-style next.
He's being so forceful, but I just can't resist him...
This is so embarrassing... Please don't stare...
Why not? You have a great ass.
So deep!
Wow, it's going all the way inside me!
It's hitting up against my womb...
Hey, no running away.
So good! I like it deep!
Hey, Airi-chan, is it okay if I cum inside?
Huh? Inside?!
My cock is dying to blow up inside you.
No, absolutely not.
Well, time to call it quits, I guess.
W-Wait, hold on...
Does it feel good?
Don't worry.
You won't get pregnant from just this much.
F-Fine...
Really? I'm going to cum inside, all right?
Yeah, that's fine.
Hell, yeah!
Creampies sell pretty well!
What are you talking...
Don't mind them.
All right, let's finish this up.
N-No!
I'm gonna cum!
Yeah, same here.
I'm cumming!
Wow, it keeps pouring out...
I might bear the child of a man I don't even know,
but I've never been more turned on in my life...
I've never felt like this with my husband...
Hey, I got your number.
Whatcha wanna do next?
My phone...
It's already four.
Wanna go to a hotel and make a better video?
Good idea.
Call the other guys, too.
So, Airi-chan, how about we continue this at a hotel?
Hey, I didn't get a turn!
– Just do it at the hotel.
– Four o'clock?
Four o'clock?!
3:00~5:00!! Time Sale!
Meat's on sale today!
I need to hurry before the sale ends!
How much do I owe you?
Huh? Oh, uh... It's our treat.
Thanks!
Also, delete that video, okay?
S-Sure...
Later.
You boys should get back home, too.
Maybe I should go home first and shower...
Oh, what about the laundry?
Huh? You don't want those clothes anymore?
Not at all!
My boyfriend's friend said he saw some huge-titted
slut wearing the same thing!
And then my boyfriend was like,
"It'd be great if you had huge tits, too!"
Is the person they're talking about... me?
I guess those boys didn't delete that video, after all.
Well, good thing I was in disguise.
I'm heading out now, Mom!
You have everything?
I'm good!
Daddy, can you drive me today too?
Have a good day!
It wouldn't hurt to wear this one more time, right?
Just kidding.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч