H Ni Juu
Subdesu Translation
hentai-ni-juu.blogspot.com
Secret Hot Spring Tour
Mao Chapter
Hidden Bath
2nd. The plucked lovely cherry blossom
Won't you eat, Mao?
I'm actually on a diet.
You had too much fun yesterday.
Could it be fatigue?
Th-That's not it.
I'm sorry about last night.
I.. felt dizzy at the hot spring,
so I went ahead and took a rest.
Excuse me for a bit.
Are you enjoying your escapade with your girlfriend?
Then I'll give one very important advice.
I can't do it if I'm not your boyfriend,
but it's like this, you see?
You reek of sweat.
Wana take a bath?
Just because we did it once...
You have no right to think that we're lovers now.
Annoying man.
You're really the worst.
Every woman I met before said the same thing,
but not many of them remained indifferent.
Onii-chan.
I wasn't able to really take a bath yesterday, so...
Is it okay if I wander by myself?
Once your body allows it,
your heart would eventually give in.
That's how it is.
You're getting really wet now.
You get horny too easily.
I don't know anything about that!
I'm cumming...
Oh no, I feel really horny...
I feel like cumming!
Your face looks interesting when you let go of yourself like this.
you really are horny.
What a lewd voice.
This is great.
Let me hear it more.
Why did this have to...?
I even dreamed of having Onii-chan...
... as my first.
Oh, no!
I can't take it anymore of this!
My first time should be with,
Onii-chan.
I really don't want this!
I can't stop moaning like this!
No...
I don't...
Inside me...
Something's coming!
You came?
Geez, how sloppy.
But,
it feels really good...
My butthole...
Yes...
Mao...
Don't!
I'm about to enter the hole
that's not pure anymore.
No, no!
Don't!
I already-
have a boyfriend...
That's exactly why it feels good, right?
Cocks of infidelity are the best, right?
It feels warm,
Your insides.
You just went ahead and inserted it...
You feel good, right?
No, I don't.
It doesn't feel goo!
No...!
No, it's not...
I'll never think that it feels good!
No, please stop that!
Please don't stir me up!
No...
It's going in deeply...
Not there!
No, no!
My mind's going blank...
I don't want to forget Onii-chan's face!
Oh no,
I'm... I'm...
That felt,
good...
Your perverted face looks really good.
It fits you, Mao.
I'm not a pervert, you know!
Yes.
I like anything that feels good!
It feels great!
It feels good...
I-I'm feeling great.
It feels too good that I'm already about to cum.
Oh no,  I'm cumming.
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum...
I'm cumming!
No way...
It's still big...
I can't take it anymore.
Please stop it already!
Please!
Nope.
I'm going to make you lose control.
I don't want this position!
No, it feels hot all the way inside. I'm going to make you feel grateful for being born a woman.
Please let me be already.
This is embarrassing.
Give me a break.
This is embarrassing...
This is mean.
It's the worst.
This is supposed to be impossible...
But, it feels really good...
Oh no, I'm going to cum.
I'm about to cum again.
No...
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum.
I'm already at my limit.
Let's cum together.
Are you okay with that?
Do you really want me to cum inside?
I don't know.
I don't know anymore!
I don't know,
But that's... Oh yes!
Together.
I'm fine with cumming together.
So it's alright to cum inside, eh?
I just want to feel good.
Please...
Release it all in me.
Take me harder!
I'm cumming!
My insides feel hot...
It's coming out.
I'm sorry
I didn't know that you're back already!
Geez, don't you know how to knock?
That could be a perverted offense, you know!
My, my. A fight?
Well, yeah.
I kind of messed up a bit.
Might as well just walk around,
until  Kotobori calms down.
You did well in eliminating that nuisance.
Don't just say that!
I was really just embarrassed earlier.
Oh, have they already made up?
No, please get out now!
That's...
Oh no!
I'm going to cum again...
Stop!
I'm cumming!
No...!
Please, no...
Let me be already...
No way.
I'm going to keep doing this until that guy finally decides to,
break up with you.
No way...
No, not there.
That's my weak spot.
You're just full of weak spots eh, Mao?
It's because whenever you touch me,
I get all drippy and twitchy.
Hey, if you don't stop this foolishness..
Onii-chan will...
A woman should only think about cocks and nothing else.
This is really great.
S-Stupid!
If you just hadn't taken my first time...
Good girl.
Your name... What's your name?
It's Kenzou.
Kenzou, I can really feel it.
It's getting deep inside me.
This hot and big thing is in me.
I feel really great!
Yes, yes!
Your thing feels really great, Kenzou!
My insides are melting.
Getting affectionate as my girlfriend already?
That's not what I want.
My mind's too hazy to think about stuff like that.
It feels too good.
I just need to think about cocks, right?
Wow, please do it more!
It feels really great!
Amazing...
This hot feeling is about to burst!
Yes...
I can't think of anything anymore!
I'm cumming inside now okay?
Just once, okay?
Let's cum together!
Oh no, I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming.
It's coming out...
Lots of the hot stuff is coming out...
Onii-chan...
I am sorry...