Wait, papa! Drop me off on the way!
Aya!
You didn't take out your
dirty clothes, did you?
Sorry! I left them on the bed
so please take them out.
This girl...
Thanks, mom. Gotta go!
Hitozuma Life
One Time Gal
Oh, that girl...
Letting all these pile up.
I just end up cleaning after her.
Am I spoiling her too much?
Whoa! How gaudy!
When did she buy this?
Who was she trying to look like?
Looking good~!
I'm not out of date yet!
Ahh... I want to show this off outside...
It's still early, but I maybe I can go shopping.
Hey, take a look.
Uwaah... Amazing!
I actually did it...
Am I being looked at?
Maybe I really overdid myself...
There's still time before the "time sale" starts.
I'm gonna kill some time.
Hey, take a look at this.
Nah, looks like an airhead.
Who cares. It's still money.
Lemme see.
Looks good to me!
I thought those aren't your type?
Yo-chan loves girls older than him.
Shut up!
I don't mind as long as
I can have those titties.
I'll make your card. Do you have an I.D.?
Eh!
This is bad...
They'll know who I am if I give an I.D.
Do you know her?
She's an old woman in this neighborhood.
Whoa... for real?
You're too old for this, ma'am.
If Papa and Aya finds out,
how will I explain this to them?
Hey, are you alone?
We're about to go in, how about joining us?
No way!
Am I getting hit on? It's been
like a decade since the last time!
R-Really? Can I?
Yeah!
Being just the three of us men is lonely.
The usual room, please.
What's your name?
Okay. I'll turn off the camera.
Airi. I'll be in your care!
Don't break any laws.
Understood. We can handle this.
You're good at this, Airi-chan.
You just suck too much.
Shut up!
This is fun! I feel like
I became young again.
Wow, do you often drink?
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
Keep them coming!
She got herself drunk.
Good, she did the work for us.
Okay, let's do this.
Airi-chan!
It's a bit cliché, but let's play
the King Game to liven up everyone.
Ahh, okay. Let's play!
Then let's start with you, Airi-chan.
Oh no, I almost fell asleep.
Yes! I'm the king!
What number did you get?
No, It's a secret.
Ehh... We get along so it's fine.
Then, #3 will... blow #1.
Eh, blow as in... a blowjob?
Well then, Airi-chan.
Let's start.
Do you always do this kind of things?
We aren't kids anymore,
so sometimes... right?
You all look like kids to me.
But this part is not of a kid.
Oh, you're doing it good.
Let's take your tits out.
I don't know about that...
It's okay! I've never seen
anything as big as yours.
You can only look, okay?
I wonder if they'll get a boner
from an old lady like me.
Ohh... I never said you can touch them.
It would be rude not to
grope these godly tits.
These feels good to touch. They're bouncy.
I-Is that so...
Look at mine. It's hard as rock.
Wow! What's this, it's so hard.
It's so long! My husband's
nothing close to this.
Suck it now, okay? Go.
What a strong stench.
What, you like the smell of dicks?
Eh... I wonder.
Nah, didn't you just sniff it?
This is bad... My body
is reacting with his dick.
I need to end this quickly.
You're good at this, Airi-chan.
It's a tight but soft fit with my dick.
Airi-chan...
Can I try something?
Wow, you're the first one who's
able to fully take me in the mouth.
That's what love is.
How deep does it have to go?
His dick is trembling.
He's coming soon.
I think I'm coming... soon...
I'm... coming!
Airi-chan, don't let go!
Gulp it down, Airi-chan.
Such a strong smell..
The musky smell is choking me.
Airi-chan, open your mouth.
She chugged it down.
This is bad. There's no going back
later if I don't stop this now.
Okay, let's move on!
Here's your number, Airi-chan.
I'm the king this time.
Number one?
#1 one gives #3 a titfuck.
Oh yeah!
W-Wait!
Mine isn't as long, but it's thick, right?
Uwah, it's huge. It's so much thicker than my husband's.
I'll be saying it now, sex is off-limits, okay.
Of course! Anyway, do you have a boyfriend?
Well... I actually do.
It's actually a husband.
For real? He must always
be asking for a titfuck.
How many men did you
make come using these tits?
I don't remember!
You did it so much that you lost count.
Oh! It got so hard!
Being rubbed like this feels good!
Kids these days are big.
Huh? Did you get wet sucking dicks?
Don't!
How lewd! You must be playing around a lot, right?
This feels good. I'm turned on this much.
I bet putting my dick here will feel good.
Hey, can I try putting it in?
No, you can't!
I can assure you mine would feel good.
I'm way drenched than normal.
It's been ages since I last
felt like this, I'm scared!
You're so erotic, Airi-chan!
Just a little more push...
Amazing! My whole dick vanished in your tits!
I'm gonna come like this.
It's kind of late to say this but,
isn't this getting out of hand?
Don't!
You're making me come!
Oh no, I'm coming!
I'm gonna come! Almost there!
Don't! I'm coming! Coming!
I'm coming!
Here it goes!
Oh no! Coming! It's coming out!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
That's an amazing orgasm.
You haven't had one in a while?
Who cares about the game anymore?
You can't!
I'm putting it in.
I said no sex!
The truth is we're just playing around a bit but...
Airi-chan is so erotic that I can't take anymore!
I knew that this might happen, but I shouldn't do this!
We can't stop now after going this far!
Here, look at how I became because of you.
What should I do...
Let him put it in?
Just one round, okay?
You're bottled up to, right?
You're spreading your legs
on your own. You want it too.
She's overflowing.
Is this alright?
I'm spreading my legs for men I just met.
I'll make you feel good.
C-Condom...
Sorry, I don't have one.
Do you have one with you?
Can't help it, we'll be doing it raw then.
It went in.
It's reaching deep inside me.
I'm really having sex.
How is it?
This feels good, her walls
are coiling around me.
She's a winner!
It's hitting me deep!
Feels good!
This meaty pussy fees great!
Fucking her while she's flooding
with juices is feels heavenly!
Wait!
You're way too rough!
Airi-chan, you're tits and pussy are the best!
You're gonna make a lot of money with this.
What are you saying...
Let's do it doggy style next.
He's doing me roughly, but why can't I refuse him?
Don't stare so much, it's embarrassing.
Why not? You got a big lovely ass.
It's hitting me deeper!
Amazing, you're reaching deep inside!
It's reaching up to my womb!
Hey, don't go away.
So good! Deeper!
Hey, Airi-chan. Can I come inside you?
Eh? Inside?
I want to shoot my sperm inside.
You can't come it inside.
Then, should we stop?
Wait, that is...
Here, doesn't it feel good?
It's gonna be fine.
You won't get knocked up that easily.
Y-yeah...
It's alright? I'll be coming inside then.
Uhm... alright.
Okay, I got that one!
The price is higher if there's a creampie in it.
What are you up to—
Don't mind it, it's nothing.
Okay, shall we proceed, Airi-chan?
Oh no!
So deep, I'm coming!
I'm coming too, Airi-chan!
Coming!
W-Wow, there's so much leaking out.
I might get pregnant from a boy I don't even know.
And yet, I'm so aroused.
I never felt like this with my husband.
I got her phone number.
Now what should we do?
My phone...
It's around four o'clock now...
Should we go to a hotel
and do a proper filming?
I agree...
Tell the others there too...
Hey, Airi-chan. Should we go to a hotel next?
I haven't done her yet!
You can do it in a hotel...
Four o'clock...
Four!
There's a special sale for meat today.
I'm gonna miss it if I don't hurry up!
How about the bill?
Ah... It's fine. I'll cover it up.
Thank you!
And also, delete that video, okay?
See ya!
You boys should be going home as well.
I should go home first and take a shower...
Ahh... I need to take in the hanged clothes.
Eh? You don't want these clothes anymore?
I don't!
My boyfriend's pal said they saw a booby woman wearing the same.
And my boyfriend said,
"If only you were as stacked up as that..."
Were they talking about... me?
So those kids didn't erase the video at all.
Well, good thing I wore a disguise.
Mama, I'll be going now!
Did you forget something?
I'm okay!
Papa, drop me off today as well!
Have a safe trip.
Maybe I should wear it one more time...
As if...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization