Yep,
Feeling good
Mao's is big!
Don't say it's big!
Beside, this is a normal size!
Sorry, have you been waiting long?
Not really
I just got here
Tickets are lottery's prize that I've won,
Be grateful to me.
Your luggage...
I'll carry them.
Of course you will.
How lovely....
She seems to be very happy being treated as a woman.
You...
So, is she a new girlfriend?
That's Not, she is my cousin and still a child.
A child, eh...?
Mao Chapter
Hidden Bath
Falling Cherry Blossoms
Secret Hot Spring Tour
Wow.. look look, sunflowers are amazing right?
Beautiful!
Geez, seriously unbelievable.
Since you accepted to my invitation,
I can look forward to it, right?
Looking forward to a lewd thing?
Hold on, what?!
Say you!
Go somewhere else, you're annoying.
A complete eyesore.!
It doesn't matter, seats are vacant anyway.
Oh ~ it's soft  and feels good.
Because Mao-chan is a Virgin?
Wait, stop this...
Don't...
Do you remember it?
Just now was an adult kiss.
Glad, aren't you?
No way, I'm not glad...!
Try doing it to your boyfriend.
He'll be pleased.
I was wrong, I apologize.
I don't care!, geez.
These past days I didn't have a good night's sleep so...
For some reason when I'm with you
I feel like my mind is at ease.
What is that? Even if you say that, it wont make me happy.
I'll check the bus schedules.
I hate it. After the mood finally got better, it become ruined.
Did you have a good time?
Like this.
No way...!
You are!
Remember this, this is the charm men look for.
No!
Onii-chan...
Wait... No!
Your underwear looks hot.
And your butt, is already of an adult.
I..idiot!
Stop that!
This is weird..
Where are you touching?
No, seriously I can't believe this...
Such a place, your fingers don't put them in there..
This reaction, it seems you haven't touched yourself yet, have you?
I haven't!
Absolutely not!
No!
Wait! Is this really...
I don't want this...
You've touched it yourself?
I don't know,
I don't know about that!
Hey you girl,
Can you take a photo for me?
Like that....
With Onii-chan I'll definitely forget about it all.
Mixed bath eh..?
But it's closed from this side.
Maybe it can be entered from the women's side only?
View here is the best!
Want to see it too, Onii-chan?
What are you saying, idiot!
Door was left unlocked,
It's alright if you come in anytime.
Then I'll do that.
Your boyfriend will see this scene, that is if he hears you.
But the guy certainly wont come here.
I'm sure.
Because he's still thinking you are a child anyway.
No, don't...
And you are this sensitive already.
Can't hold your voice down anymore, eh?
No!
Oi,
Take some responsibility, Ok!
What's the matter with you Mao?
You invited me here but...
No!
Cut it out!
Stay away from! Pervert
Lecher...
It's already wet.
That's because you are a pervert, Mao-chan.
No,
This is not the case..
It's okay, it's okay.
Now at Mao's age,
Having sex is just normal.
I won't forgive you for calling me by my first name so casually...
Are you saying calling my woman's first name is not permitted?
Don't say this kind of arbitrary things!
We're already connected as one.
We are in relationships as man and woman.
I don't know about that...
Just pull it out already!
No, Mao's pussy is mine.
No...!
N..no..
Something,
comi...
Something is coming!
I'm getting strange..
I'm... I'm,
about to cum...
Open your mouth.
Wider.