Why don't you give up already?
I want to see how a serious girl like Shirakawa-san pees.
You haven't done it once since this morning, right?
That's because you didn't let me do so!
Whoa, what a rebellious expression.
But you've been all fidgety since earlier.
Seems like you're almost at you limit.
N-No...
I don't want to pee in front of all of them!
Hey...
Don't just sit there, show it to us already.
I'll help you do it.
Don't do that!
If you touch it like that, it'll come out.
Since it's like this, you might as well show everything to us already.
Stop!
If I position myself like this, it'd be like...
You're like a dog.
Try hanging in there, Shirakawa-san,
with your butthole and pussy exposed.
Well then, we'll have you pee no matter what.
Okay.
I-I'm feeling weak.
Don't rub up on me.
No...
I just have to endure it, but...
Look, it's no big deal,
so give it up already.
It's coming out.
It's coming out..
It's coming out!
Illusions
Oh, it's pouring out!
That must have felt good, Sumire-chan.
So the sensation of cumming is really different in these situations after all.
It's all out.
Oh.
What’s this?
There seems to be a different kind of liquid coming out.
This isn't good.
We have to wipe it off properly.
This is quite troublesome.
Your panties will be soaked as soon as you wear them.
Looks like I've already wiped off some here.
So why don't we go a step further?
This time... Oh, yes.
Why don't we do it in the train again?
Hey, Shirakawa-san, do it already.
If you don't do it as we say.
we'll reveal to everyone that you were taking
naked pictures of yourself on the train.
Here, suck it.
It's dirty.
For me to lick something that is use urinating...
If you don't do it quickly, people around will notice.
I know.
Shirakawa-san, you have to lick it like it's tasty.
You can study well, but you can't even learn how to do this right.
Shut up.
Being good at this isn't something to be proud of.
It's just indecent.
It can't be helped.
Here, this is how you do it.
That's good.
Suck it more.
Why?
I'm being treated like a toy right now,
and yet my body is slowly becoming hot.
Have I lost my mind?
It's because of all the thorough training you've received, Sumire-chan.
You may not remember,
but you're body properly reacts.
It's so sensitive that just by smelling a cock,
you'll be able to get very wet.
This feels good, Sumire-chan.
I already feel like cumming just by rubbing it on you.
What's this?
Is this just another...
dream?
Is this a dream?
Shirakawa-san's already under total control.
Like a love doll in her mouth-pussy mode?
I think that's great.
Hey, try cumming inside the mouth-pussy!
If it's...
If it's a dream,
I wish it would end quickly.
Please.
Stop this already.
I'm about to cum now.
Drink all of it up.
You idiot!
What are you doing?
Take all of it in your mouth properly!
She's all wet with semen.
So how do you plan on going home like that, Shirakawa-san?
Th-This is semen?
It's hot and sticky.
It's okay.
I'll wipe it off before you wake up.
But I guess I'll leave it on your forehead.
It's a place where you won't really notice dried semen.
Then that means he's really inviting you!
It's totally fine to go with him.
No way!
That's impossible.
He just wants to do it.
They did something terrible to me yesterday.
Now they're acting like it didn't happen?
What are they thinking?
So it was just a dream after all?
But...
Why is this part of me twitching?
Worried about something, Sumire-chan?
Hey there.
We meet again.
Can you please stop acting like we're close?
I already let you know earlier, right?
Please don't talk to me at school.
Oh, my bad, my bad.
It's just that I heard a weird rumor.
A weird rumor?
I thought maybe you were being bullied by your female classmates.
I'm still a school counselor, after all.
I'll listen to your problems if you like.
No, thanks.
Besides, I'm not really being bullied by anyone.
Like for example, finding a solution to get back at those girls.
Th-That's...
It's not really that difficult to understand.
Look at this for a moment.
Wh-What's this?
Just look at it carefully.
Eh?
What?
What's this?
It's okay.
You can leave everything to me.
Meet me later after school, okay?
We're going after that girl first.
Actually, I already placed a subliminal suggestion on her.
All I need to do is to pull the trigger.
H-Hey...
I...
What am I doing...?
My body's moving on its own.
Stop.
Don't move your hips  indecently like that.
It's like I'm a pervert!
I-Is it okay?
Wow, so girls like you really exist, eh?
I'm surprised.
Stop this already.
Stop this...
Stop doing lewd things to my body!
I need to exit the train at the next station, so let's finish this quickly.
Hey, stop.
This can't be.
Inside, here?
Your pussy is so tight.
You've got a great pussy for someone who plays around.
No, stop.
It's not...
I don't usually
play around like this...
Seems you really wanted a cock in there, eh?
Your insides are already very wet.
Why?
Even when I'm forced to have sex like this...
Why...?
Why is my body becoming aroused?
Please don't be too rough with me.
If this continues...
I'll...
Crap, I have to hurry up and cum already.
Time is running out...
Is it okay for me to cum in you?
No way.
Don't...
Not inside.
Don't cum inside me...
This can't be...
No...
No...!
No!
No...
Th-This is too much for me...
Hitoriga
Well?
Do you feel a little better now, Sumire-chan?
N-Not really...
I've handed the other girl over to someone I know.
They're acting like they're scouting for potential magazine models,
though all of it of course is a big lie.
So, can you change your clothes now?
I should change here?
That's right.
There's no changing room at the studio, you see.
But that's...
It's okay, it's okay.
We're already used to that.
So there's no need to be bothered by it.
Umm...
I'm going to change quickly,
so can you all go out for a moment?
What? Are you embarrassed?
Should I lend you a hand then?
Wha-- Hey!
It's cool, it's cool.
Please stop that.
I can do it on my own.
Oh?
What a cute bra.
Do the curtains match the drapes?
D-Don't touch me!
I didn't know it was going to be like this!
It's perfectly fine.
You said you wanted to do a swimsuit photo shoot, right?
Underclothes are basically the same thing.
Hey, wait. Why are you taking a video of this?
We're filming an "In the making" of this video.
An "In the Making" film?
Since it's already like this,
why don't you just show everything?
No...!
Stop filming!
No!
Stop!
Stop this!
This isn't modeling at all!
No!
I don't want this.
Let me be!
Let me be already!
Here, don't cry.
I'll make sure you feel good.
No!
Oh?
Even after all this, your nipples are still getting hard after all.
Starting to get aroused?
Th-That's not it.
No way that's true.
I...
It's okay!
Get horny all you want!
I'll make sure to take a good video of it.
Ouch...
Your pussy is a bit stiff.
Is this perhaps your first time?
Yes, so please stop this already.
Let me be.
That's not good!
You have to get rid of your virginity right away.
That's right.
It's quite embarrassing that someone your age is still a virgin.
No way...
No...
But I...
It's tight.
I-It hurts.
No...
Whoa, nice expression there!
Focus on her a bit more.
No...
Stop filming...
... my embarrassing parts.
I said it's okay.
You're going to feel good soon enough.
Stop saying such things!
Pull it out.
Pull it out already!
No, no!
We're just getting started.
Save me...
Someone please save me!
Okay, why don't we speed it up a bit?
No!
Don't...!
No way...
No...
No!
Wh-Why?
I'm just watching,
but my body is also getting hot.
Gottch ya!
That probably stimulated her a bit too much.
Oh well, I guess it can t be helped.
You're getting quite aroused already.
For the last part, why don't we make you feel good too, Sumire-chan?
Huh?
This place...
Shirakawa, why are you looking around like that?
Ku-Kurahashi-Sensei!
When did you come back?
What are you talking about, Shirakawa?
You're acting weird.
This isn't right, Sensei!
We already decided, didn't we?
That we would do this after I graduate...
That's exactly why we waited for this moment, right?
Look carefully.
Huh?
Is this me?
Hey now, get a hold of yourself.
The time when you were a student of our academy
was many years ago, right?
Is that so?
Then I'm... I'm...
Se-Sensei...
I've been waiting for this day.
So let's...
Okay?
I see.
So I'm finally going to do it with Sensei.
I'm about to do it.
Your breasts are soft and feel good, Shirakawa.
No...
Please don't say that.
Shirakawa, I'm taking it off.
This is embarrassing.
No, don't...
If you fondle it like that...
Th-That's...
You're already getting hot down here, Shirakawa.
Why?
He just touched it for a moment, and...
... it already feels good.
Has my body really become this indecent?
It's okay.
Even if you become more and more perverted...
It's okay?
For me to be so indecent...?
For me to lose it...?
It's really big.
S-So this is Sensei's cock.
Shirakawa, would you rub your breasts on it?
Okay.
It's my first time, so I don't know if I can do it well, though.
H-How's this, Sensei?
Does this feel good?
Yeah.
It feels really good.
Your cock is so hot and stiff, Sensei.
You're also getting hot here, Shirakawa.
And it's already very wet.
Your insides feel like they're melting.
Please don't look at it too much.
It's been played with quite a bit, so...
Why?
Milk just came out of my breasts.
Isn't that good, Shirakawa?
Now you're ready to bear my children.
So this would be for our child?
Hey, don't just stop there.
Rub your breasts on me, too.
Yes.
Oh, no. This is...
My breasts are now wet and I'm also feeling good.
It tastes good.
I'll gladly give birth!
I'll give birth to our healthy child!
Well, I've properly given you a contraceptive, so
there's no chance you'll get pregnant here.
Still, this is really something.
Se-Sensei.
Sensei, I'm already...
Okay.
I'll insert it now.
Yes, Sensei.
Insert it.
Stick it in me, please.
Shirakawa, are you okay?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Sensei, please move.
I'm really okay.
Se-Sensei's cock is deep inside me...
We did it...
Shirakawa! Shirakawa!
Shirakawa!
What's wrong with me?
This is supposed to be my first time,
and yet it doesn't feel painful at all.
Sex feels...
Sex feels this good...
Why?
It's hitting deep.
Sensei's cock is deep inside me...
Your pussy feels really good.
It's the best.
I'm happy.
Please...
Please do it more!
Make yourself feel better with my pussy!
Sh-Shirakawa, if you wrap around it like that...
I can feel it.
Sensei's cock is twitching inside.
I-I'm going to cum.
Yes, Sensei.
Please give it to me.
I finally...
I have finally become one with you, Sensei.
So let's cum together.
Putting on such a happy face...
Oh, well.
Until Kurahashi-Sensei gets back from his transfer,
you're going to let me have a lot of fun, Sumire-chan.
Kurahashi-Sensei...