Good afternoon.
Hello, um...
I'm Mikami.
I'm Inoue, nice to meet you.
Same here, I'm Sakamoto.
Are both of you here in regard to your child?
Your child is causing problems at school.
I would like to talk to you, please come to school.
Kumiko, you're here for the same reason?
It seems so.
I wonder what this is about?
I don't think my child would cause problems...
It could be a mistake.
Yes, but it may lead into other troubles.
This is an elite school, after all.
Let's worry about it later and find the principal.
That's why we're here... oh?
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
I'm Shinozaki Mizuho.
Oh, so you're Shinozaki-sensei.
My daughter always talks about you.
Thank you very much.
But...
But?
W..well... the door is locked and...
You mean we can't get in?
Tomimatsu-sensei called me and asked me to come to school, but...
I don't know the details.
So irresponsible.
Tomimatsu-sensei and... Shigezo-san?
Ladies, thank you for coming today.
What is this about?
I apologize for the late notification.
We have changed the meeting place and I'm here to take you there.
Sorry for the late notification.
Please step into the bus.
Let's get in and talk later.
You're right, let's get going.
Shigezo-san, does the principal know about this? Besides...
Ladies, please have a seat, we'll leave now.
Shinozaki-sensei, what about you?
Alright, I'm going.
Um, Shinozaki-sensei.
Tell me about Shigezo-san.
Well, he's our school bus driver.
I never knew there was a school bus for this school.
Well, he never makes himself public.
He's always like that, you know?
Like that?
You never know what he's thinking.
He also has the same last name as the principal...
...it's rumored that he's his big brother.
But the principal doesn't want to talk about him.
I see...
I doubt they are related.
He doesn't seem to be clean.
But you can't judge a person by their appearance.
They surely don't resemble each other.
Anyways, this bus has small seats...
A child's seat...
My skirt...
I can see your underwear, Mikami-san.
What, that's not good.
Thanks for coming today, everyone.
I am Kawamura Shigezo,
representing the principal.
What, representing the principal?
What's this about?
Please explain the situation.
I know you ladies aren't convinced...
...but, your children causing trouble is the truth.
Hold on, Shigezo-san.
What is it, Shinozaki-sensei?
What makes you say that, Shigezo-san?
You really want to know?
Of course, the children are very polite in class...
...they are not rude at all.
You don't know that, you're not their teacher.
When I'm teaching them, they are always rude.
That can't be...
I've seen this many times with rich housewives.
They push all responsibilities on us and expects us to nurture their children.
They believe that they don't need to do a thing...
...and only think about how to make themselves look prettier.
Who are the real parents of the children attending our school?
Aren't they your children!?
It is said: "A child walks in their parents' footsteps while growing up."
It also means that you can tell how the parents are.
In conclusion, it means you ladies need to grow up.
It's a pity for the children otherwise.
At our school, we discipline the children properly.
You ladies need some discipline!
Let's have you all as part of the program.
D..discipline?
That's right, our school is very well-known for it's discipline system.
Let's get going with the program.
Tomimatsu-kun, please have them change into the correct uniform.
This is...
Hey, Tomimatsu-sensei are you listening to me?
Isn't this Shigezo-san's old pre-school?
How do you know about this place?
Well, I have my reasons.
Besides, does the principal really know about this?
Just shut up!
Tomimatsu-sensei...
Mizuho, looks like you need some discipline as well.
Let get working on you first then.
What!?
Wai... Tomimatsu-kun!
No... stop... Tomimatsu-kun...
Please... stop that...
Not... there...
N..no!!
N... no...
My, my, you're not yourself today.
No...
No, not tha...
N..no! I'm still a vi...!
I..it... hurts...
It hurts, it hurts!
No, no, no!!!
No!!
Virgins are great.
I don't want this to end!
I'm going to cum!
No!!!
So you fucked her.
Was it too early?
Nah, I was thinking about her getting the treatment sooner or later as well...
...anyways, tie her up.
Sure thing.
Excuse me, Tomimatsu-sensei, don't you have better suited clothing?
Hey, you look great in that.
Alright ladies, from here on Shigezo-san and I will be your teacher.
C'mon, put more energy into it.
Keep going, you can do it.
Sakamoto-san, looks like you're not in shape.
What are you doing!?
Sakamoto-san, you've done the same thing as your daughter.
She won't listen and is rude.
Looks like you're the reason for it.
Tomimatsu-kun, keep working with her.
You two can take a rest.
Sorry, but excuse me Sakamoto-san.
Please... stop...
But you're not resisting at all.
That's not...
Oh my, look at you.
Well, keep up the good work and have some fun.
C'mon, move your body more.
Pardon me for a sec.
Not there... stop...!
You're telling me to stop, but your body is responding.
T..that's not true.
W..what!?
It's... wet? Am I turned... on?
Are you touching yourself?
N..no, I was going to use the toilet!
Please leave now.
Sakamoto Naomi-san, you're just like a kid trying to cover up their mischief.
Of course, I'm talking about yours.
Why not just be honest?
I'm not!
Please leave!
If you need to urinate, be my guest.
Just go, please!
You can't hide your lies, your panties are soaking wet!
That's not true!
Fine, let me check!
No!!!!
So, who opened the flood gates?
No... stop, please stop!
Don't lie to me now, you wanted to touch yourself, right?
No, I didn't... please let go!
So it must be a piss, go for it then!
I can't do it in this position.
Let go, hurry... please!
Naomi, tell the truth... did you want to masturbate or take a piss?
Please, let go!
If you're not going to say it, I'll just find out myself.
I really want to use the bathroom, please forgive me!
I can't believe in liars like you.
No... stop...
Please... no!!
Such bad manners.
You dirtied the floor.
You're a grown woman, but yet you can't hold it in?
I must discipline you.
Look at all this piss!
Don't...
No... s..stop...!
No... stop...
Stop, or else I will...
Or else?
No, what would I tell my husband...
Don't say anything!
Just like the brats who won't tell you anything when they get in trouble.
Besides, I don't think your husband is satisfying you.
That's... that's not...!
Then, why are you moving your hips on your own?
No, that's not... true!
You're still going to lie?
The truth is that you want a big cock!
No, that's not...!
Should I pull out then?
Don't stop, please...
Fine, then tell me what you really want.
I can't say that...
I know you were looking down on me in the bus.
That's not true!
Don't lie!
And now, you piss yourself in front of me and want my cock!
Say the truth, bitch!
Please... fuck me with your thing, Sensei!
Does it feel good?
Feels good...
Wonderful, I've never had sex... this good!
I'm going to cum soon!
Sensei, me too. I'm cuming, cuming, cuming!!
OK, Inoue-san. You start the chain.
OK...
Next, Mikami-san
Alright, you're doing a great job...
OK, let's try that again.
Oh, you may take a rest Inoue-san.
No, please forgive me!
Not possible.
Please try again.
P..please forgive me... l'm in too much pain to... jump...
Just like your child, Inoue Mika-san.
Both of you give up easily and won't listen after failing just once.
Children who won't listen need to be punished.
However, that's becoming hard to do in today's society.
Which is the reason why they become snobby as they grow up.
So you need to take his place.
And hopefully you'll understand.
H..his place? That's...
Inoue-san...
It hurts...
Inoue-san...?
More... more...!
Alright, your punishment is over.
More? Then take this!
Mikami-san, please have fun with the horsey.
O..OK...
Is something wrong, Mikami-san?
N..nothing. I'm just a bit embarrassed.
Don't worry about the small things.
Why aren't you rocking?
It's too small...
You're right, but what if I help?
Right now is play time right, Miss?
Oh, what's with the voice?
Should I rock it faster?
Look, it's so wet right here.
Are we having an emergency?
S-Shigezo-san, please stop... others are looking.
What are you talking about?
Please stop it!
Mikami-san, I think I know how you treat your kid.
She doesn't know what it means, but she keeps calling me a pervert.
And still wears diapers.
T..that's because...
You're just like her.
As soon as the teacher looks away, she does something else.
Looks like you need discipline.
No...
C'mon, say sorry to the horsey.
You made him dirty, after all.
C'mon, say sorry.
Sorry, please... please...
Great, you are improving already.
Let's give you a reward.
Wow, you are already wet.
Looks like you really want it.
T..that's not true...
N..not that...!
Such smooth tightness!
S..stop it...
The others are watching...
Isn't that how you like it!?
T..that's not true!
G..great... Sensei, it's great...
Did you want it that much?
Me and my husband, we haven't...!
Good, you are a good girl.
Look, look at my vagina.
More, rougher!
Alright, I'll discipline you more.
Not so rough...!
This is embarrassing...
But it feels so...
You're so wet.
This... this!
Great, great!
P..please forgive me...
Your ass is wet, this means...
How do you like... this!?
Not there!
My butt!!
It hurts, it hurts!
Great, great!
No, it hurts!
My husband has never done this!
No, it hurts... but strange...!
I don't know!
This is so tight!
I'm coming, this is so great... I've never had it...this good!
More... give me, give me!
No matter what they do, they are all dogs.
Housewives are a pity.
Three new students at the secret school.
And we got a young one too, great job.
Still not enough...
That's it, let's get these three to recruit new students.
The front or the back?
The front... no leave the front to my brother.
As of today, I am the principal of School of Housewives.