Time,
is something that is very precious.
There are plenty of things you can do
to pass the time on the way to school.
However,
this is not one of them.
I can't even read a book,
because of how crowded it is.
It could be one way of passing otherwise wasted time.
There are plenty of adults that enjoy this sort of thing.
How deplorable.
Touch all you want.
It does not concern me.
Sadly, I am someone who is sexually frigid.
I've tried stimulating myself out of curiosity,
but even if my genitals are touched,
or my breasts,
nothing happens.
I just don't care one way or the other...
Diagnosis
And then,
I came a bit when he kept touching me under my panties.
Whoa, that's so low.
But you see...
You'll eventually get used to molesters.
They target us so much.
Well, I guess you can say that.
However, if I was ugly like a certain someone,
those molesters might not come around.
I don't know about that.
Aren't they popular among some teachers?
Scum.
There's no hope for them.
Don't they feel despair at their own feeble-mindedness?
Or maybe they're happier that way.
Ah!
A mistake.
That was a mistake.
N-No one heard me, right?
Wh-What was that just now?
I'm not the same as those girls.
My body is different.
Earlier, that...
It just...
Yeah, it caught me a bit off guard.
What? A bag?
H-He definitely did that on purpose.
This is the worst!
Getting cocky just because I can't move...
I can't even move my leg, let atone change my position.
This really is the worst.
N-No!
This is...
But I'll get stimulated more from the front if I try to escape.
Why?
Th-This wasn't supposed to happen to me.
I shouldn't be feeling a thing...
And yet...
What is this?
I...
That's right.
I'm being touched
in the train,
and it should be impossible
for me to feel anything from it...
H-Hey!
What are you...?
No way.
No way....
No, but...!
No...
This is nothing.
This is just sweat!
When I become nervous,
I just start to sweat.
Calm down.
Yes.
Think of something else.
The value of pi is...
... three point one four,
one five,
nine two,
six five,
three five,
eight nine,
seven nine,
three two,
three eight,
four six,
two six...
I-I just want it to stop...
This is not me.
This is weird...
Hey...
What are you bringing out?
Th-This is a man's...?
I can't believe it!
How does he have the nerve?
No...
This feels gross.
It feels...
Being touched there feels...
I'll try to put up with it for a while,
somehow!
Some strange liquid is coming out,
and it's starting to twitch a bit.
Eh? Wait, this is...
It's hot.
It's coming out.
Semen...
All over my hands,
and even my uniform...
Hey...
Even after doing something like that,
you still want to touch me?
No way.
What is he thinking?
Putting his finger inside my dirty place like that...
It's my butthole...
B-But...
If he keeps on touching me there instead of the other hole, at least...
What am I saying?
My mind's getting all messed up!
Please...
Hurry...
Get me to the station already!
His finger...
His finger is inside me...
Oh, no!
This is...
Don't...
I'm going to pee!
I'm going to pee myself!
It's leaking out...
Oh, god!
I musn't...!
Endure it...
Just a bit more...
No!
I can't take this anymore...
Why does my body feel weak?
Sorry.
I'm sorry!
Please let me be.
Please.
Save me. Save me!
My body is...
Did somebody pee themselves?
Yeah, look. That girl...
No... It wasn't me...
Whoa, that was something...
There's no way I can say what really happened...
Why did this have to happen to me?
Hey, is that you, Shirakawa?
What's wrong?
Se-Sensei.
Oh, here. Wear this.
It's okay.
I wished back there
It's gonna be alright now.
to simply disappear
inside my teacher's suit...
Hitoriga.
Do you start to tremble when confronted with a crowd of people?
No.
The station, train,
and the sounds that are associated with those places...
You don't have problems with those?
No.
So you don't want to ride full trains anymore?
Normally, I wouldn't ride a train in the first place.
Hmm... I guess a female counselor would
be better suited for this task after all.
If you are able to come the day after tomorrow...
No thanks.
Let's just get this over with.
Kurahashi-Sensei the one whom made
the appointment in the first place.
I just came since he went to the trouble.
Yeah, he would do something like that.
He's always been a softie.
I did try to find a female counselor since this is a girl's problem, though.
If I might have a word,
hearing someone speak ill of the teacher
who was just worried about me,
doesn't really feel that great.
Sorry about that.
Huh?
Does that mean you have a crush on him...?
No.
But I do respect him.
And I am also grateful.
Well, getting back to the topic.
It seems that you, Sumire-chan,
have a strong aversion toward men.
Like I've said over and over...
... that just isn't the case.
Then why haven't you even touched the
tea and cookies that I brought out?
So what were you saying about the tea and cookies?
Okay, okay.
I lose.
Alright, I'll just go and fill Kurahashi in,
so just wait here.
Geez, this is such a waste of time.
I can't turn down my teacher's request.
It can't be helped.
What's wrong?
I.. I don't know..
What is this?
Something's...
It feels like part of my head's gone numb...
Sumire-chan, look at this for a bit.
O-Okay.
That's right.
Don't take your eyes away from my finger,
and then, fall asleep.
I'm... huh?
H-How did I get into a train?
My head isn't functioning properly.
Again?
You really think I'm just going to keep still?
My voice has disappeared?
What does this mean?
Anyway,
I need to fight back somehow even if my voice isn't working...
No...
That's right.
Somehow your voice won't come out.
Those who noticed...
... crowded together and started fondling you.
Slowly...
Slowly playing with your body without restraint.
Overstimulation has made you aroused.
This is still completely normal.
Here...
Hey, let go of me!
Those who are simply looking
have now started touching you.
Students and regular employees alike...
Everyone is sexually attracted to your body, Sumire-chan.
Everyone's fingers
started stimulating that lower part.
Then your body gradually, gradually becomes hotter.
The arousal seeps in deep inside you.
But that's just natural,
because you are in no way sexually frigid.
You just want to think that way,
so you're just slamming on those brakes as hard as you can.
When given even the smallest opportunity...
See?
Here, try to relax a bit more.
Just give into those sensations.
I thought you could handle just about anything.
Or maybe this is too hard for you?
Hey!
No!
Stop!
You can't...
You can't do that!
If I get touched there...
Huh?
This is...
Eh, wait a minute...
Was it just a dream?
Why was I asleep?
What just...
Huh?!
Oh, it's you, Sumire-chan.
You're earlier than usual.
I was getting a bit tired of waiting.
so I'm already prepared.
Usual!?
Usual... ?
The moment I tried to speak in my confused state,
my consciousness was suddenly plunged into darkness.
What's this?
Check it out! She's really shaking her ass like she wants us to play with it.
Try giving her what she wants already!
Hey!
Stop!
Stop this...
That's an unexpectedly sexy ass you're got there.
Don't do this in the classroom..
What...
What do you plan on doing?
Is this for real?!
She acts so casual with that know-it-all face.
But in reality, she's a pervert who cums
daily from having her butt played with.
Everyone's watching...
They're all watching me,
as my butthole is being played with.
Here, Sumire-chan.
Your favorite vibrator.
Look at it carefully, okay?
But really,
the reaction that my hands felt before is getting really intense.
Could it be that you feel it more because you're
conscious of the ones looking at you?
My, look at that.
The butt's sucking the vibrator and is being
shaped according to the motion.
You...
Tying me up like this and doing whatever you please...
Hey, that's enough, isn't it?
Put it inside already.
Her butthole started twitching in and out like crazy,
when I pulled out the vibrator.
You're still going to...
Stop that!
If you do that, I'll definitely...
There, your much awaited cock.
Keep it up so that her butthole is kept open.
Why...?
Why am I experiencing this?
Anything but this...
It's all white and clean.
Shirakawa's ass is really sexy, don't you think?
It's really opening wide.
If I get seen by Sensei in this place...
What a pervert.
Hey, raise your head up properly.
You still have to show Kurahashi-sensei that you are being anally raped.
To Se-Sensei?
That's right, Sumire-chan.
Make sure to fully show him,
that you are being anally raped.
In return,
you get to enjoy this boner.
That can't be...
Sensei...
If it's Kurahashi-Sensei,
he wouldn't just sit by and just watch.
What's up?
Try to feel more pleasure.
Do your best, Shirakawa-san.
I'll have Sensei stop this...
Here I go.
Take everything into your asshole!
With this,
I can finally wake up...
That's right...
This is just another dream after all.
It's still...
Sensei...
And Sensei is even the one who...
This should not be...
To do this in front of everyone...
This is...
Sensei is...
the source of my arousal?
I did not wish for this.
This is not the real Sensei!
Please.
Pull it out.
I don't want to do it with Sensei in this place!
I can't possibly be so aroused,
with all these lewd people watching me!
I don't want this!
Then...
How do you want to be raped?
It's okay.
Speak up.
Here you go.
Until you become satisfied,
this cock will continue to stir up your butthole.
Stir.
I'll thrust it in until it pops wide open,
because you are really wishing for it.
You just want to prove to everyone that it's no big deal for you.
That may be true.
I'm...
I am...
I see.
Okay.
I'm cumming, Shirakawa.
Alright.
Should I cum inside you, Shirakawa?
No! No! Stop!
It's...
It's Sensei's...
Sensei's hot thing is
filing up my insides...
Sorry.
Did I surprise you?
No...
I was surprised
after hearing that you lost consciousness during counseling.
Seems you don't have a fever.
Yes.
What's happening?
Counseling...?
What's really going on?