No matter how many times you come, my answer is the same
What!？
Please leave immediately
Chii-chan
Your forbidden to call me Chii-chan
I am the Young Mistress, right?
I am sorry
Don't worry
I have no intentions of forsakening our shop
But, Young Mistress
To continue like this is...
As long as we don't give up and persevere
the gods will smile on us eventually
I was an abandoned child
taken in by the previous Master
Brother，are you here as a trainee?
Chii-san came here as a trainee mistress too
Ten plus years have passed
Oh
Thanks for the hard work
Welcome back，Young Mistress
I am back，Ken-san
The me without any strengths
nor abilities...
Its customers who booked earlier right?
The distance between her and me...is only widening
Welcome
Welcome to Golden Peak Estate
Is that customer from Tokyo?
Our Young Mistress doesn't look willing to do it
Eh? A student?
Its that hilltop school Kunoe Girls School, which is a ten minutes bus-ride away
I only just went into that school this year
Its only a mere pass in terms of looks
Don't tell me he's got some city-dwellers temperament?
In the face of Young Mistress's impregnable defence
Does he think he would stand a chance?
It is okay for you to call me Chitose
Then...Chitose-chan
Wanna have a one-night stand with me?
If you really meant what you said, I'll get angry now
If you were just joking, I'll be even more angry
When in our hotel,
shameless acts like what you did just now...
I hope you can refrain from doing them
Anyway, Ken-san, you worry too much
I am not a kid anymore
Its not like I can't tell who's good and bad
The important first time
should definitely be two people basking under the full moon
at the lakeside...that's what I've decided
I'll definitely not accept that kind of frivolous man
Now then...I had better finish up my chores too
Ken-san, over here...over here...
I thought the Young Mistress was only here to clean
Never would have thought that they would start doing this
（That type of frivolous man）
（I'll never accept him）
（The first time should definitely be two people basking under the full moon）
（At the lakeside...that's what I've decided）
Your too dunce, stop being a lightbulb
Look at her indulging face
That's the expression of a woman intent on having orgasms
To attack suddenly...that's despicable
The mouth above is saying no, but the mouth below is...
clearly realising how good I am
Down there?
No, let me go
What a soft ass..., it feels so good
I'm gonna scream now
Go ahead
I was afraid there wouldn't be any crowd watching the show
（Being hugged so tightly）
（First time I've smelled a man's scent）
（After this...）
（This is like undergoing anesthetic）
（Virgins seems to have fantasies regarding kissing）
No...
（Yeah, they think its dirty to think about kissing）
（Already feeling horny?）
How can this be...
My first kiss...
No...
Its already like this?
I see...then let's...
No...Don't...
Don't be afraid
I will be gentle on you
No...No...
No...
Eh? Your already hard...
Do you find someone to fuck you every night?
I've never let anyone touched me
To actually solely own such a sexy and horny body
Feel excited thinking about it
Its not...horny
I'm already feeling hard there
No
No...
No way, how can I be feeling...
Its not right, its not right...
Come over here
No, please, no...
How horny...your already giving out such a thick scent down there...
This is so embarrassing, please forgive me
Don't, not like that...
Nevertheless, she was eaten anyway
No use worrying, this result was obvious from the start
Now then, I'll leave the rest to you
We'll go to the men's bathroom area
Already checked out early this morning huh...that customer...
So this is what a one-night stand is huh?
Is there any problem?
No...but its time for school and yet Chii...
no...Young Mistress still haven't come out, so everyone was worried
I'm not feeling well
I'll not go to school today
Don't, you'll be heard
Its only a matter of time anyway
Chitose's saliva is licking my thing big
No, don't say these dirty words
Still haven't ended right?
If you don't help me ejaculate till my hearts content, I won't let you sleep
Your working so hard...already gotten a hang of it right?
Don't tell me...you heard it?
I beg you, don't tell anyone...
Your dating him?
I don't know...
but he is my first man...
You weren't...raped by him?
No
To think of escaping will land you in deeper trouble
Break your hymen in one shot
I won't let you off even if you cry and beg me
I'll shoot everything in you and let you become a mother
I don't want to be a mother
Going in from the front, okay?
Something...there's something coming in...
It hurts! Stop it now! Its splitting apart!
Poor thing...I'll make you feel good in a sec
Its hitting, something's hitting me inside...
kissing with your womb huh
It hurts! Please pull it out! It hurts!
Big right? Your grabbing me so tightly
Don't move it
Its a man's pleasure to make a woman cry
Please don't move it, No...
No...
Noo...
Nooo...
Noooo...
No, don't insert it anymore
Don't bully me anymore
I'll stop if you beg me
「Please let Chitose be pregnant」
Cannot, Its going in deep
I don't want to be pregnant...definitely no!
No...I'm dying...I'm better off dead
No
I can't take it...I can't take it anymore!
I'm dying...I'm dying!
Pull it out...I beg you
I'm gonna die if you push any deeper
Didn't you say your better off dead?
No
I don't want to die...stop now...I'll do anything!
Don't hurt me anymore
Then...beg me...
Please impregnate me with your baby
Let me be pregnant...no...
Shoot everything inside Chitose
What you did the last time, do it again for me okay?
Okay
So warm...
Its even better like this...
Think a little about your surroundings please
The two of us sweating together is better?
I don't want to
Your face obviously says you want to
or is it that having sex is dirty except when your doing it to bear a child?
to have sex IS dirty in the first place
I'll let you feel so good you'll cry
One whole night, I'll let you sweat like hell
...sheeze...
Young Mistress still isn't back, do you know anything?
No, I don't know
Chii-chan...Chii-chan!
No...Noooo....!
She is the daughter of your sister's husband before they were married right?
You have a niece who's older than you huh...not bad...
Haruna-san...how did you...
Enjoy the show, little sister-in-law...
If you sign here, I'll let your niece go...
Don't play tabletop transactions with little girls
You'll hurt this naive little girl
Your niece will be a prostitute and help us make money
Why...this has nothing to do with Haruna-san
Precisely...we've already shown her mercy
Of course...we won't let you off either
You'll regret ever being born as a woman
Last night, when your niece became a prostitute here, she was screaming in ecstasy
Its your turn tonight
We'll make you pregnant for sure, Princess
Pregnant!? No!
Please stop, I have...I have someone I like
therefore, I beg you all
There's no use begging, we won't let you off without hurting you
No, nonononono...
There's so much crotch hair...
No there isn't...
Its only average...
Girls are best to be smiling than crying
What?
Please don't do these nasty things
No, Please stop it
I'll make you cry and moan in ecstasy
Nononononono...
Hot...its unbearable, I beg you to help me
Its so hot, help me quick!
Its this aphrodisiac, bring it once every three hours
I'm cumming...something...something's moving inside...
Those are pearls, my honey
Pearls? Amazing...they're moving inside
Don't insert it any deeper...
Stop it now!
Don't move...don't insert it anymore...
I beg you all, I beg you...
Pearls...pearls...forgive me please...
Amazing...its too good...
I'm starting to feel weird...
I don't know what is happening...
Its getting bigger...
The pearls are running all around inside
She must not be allowed to rest. We will do this till morning comes.
A whole night!? Nooooooooo...
At this rate, we can make her
unable to live without a penis