Oh, morning already?
But I strangely feel warm and good down there.
Whoa!
What's up? Being loud so early.
'Coz Risa-nee wearing a maid attire and...
Ehh!?
It's early in the morning and you...
For a mere little brother, how dare you get
your sloppy dick this hard from your sister?
Isn't it your fault for being so cute!
W-What on earth are you talking about?
I'm gonna give this cheeky dick
some tender loving care!
Your dick is gradually getting hard.
Risa-nee!
You're desperately rubbing your dick.
Do you really love tits that much?
But don't you always sleep through the morning
that you won't wake up unless I do this much?
How does it feel to have your sister relieve you?
It's obvious to tell how you're
feeling when I look at this dick.
S-Same here, I've long
figured out your weakness as well!
Your nipples are very shy
that they hide invertedly.
My nipples are... not the same
erogenous zones as your dick.
Forget it, you don't even
understand what I'm saying.
Cumming so much from your
own sister's tit and blowjob.
You're one hell of a little brother.
Since you're already wearing that,
try calling me "master" or something.
O-Okay.
I'll entertain your whim only for today.
I-I'm putting it in, master.
You're just a little brother,
yet you're getting swollen inside me.
Why does it feel so good?
My mind is going blank!
You're feeling good because it's with me, right?
You're a pervert, Risa-nee!
I-Idiot! Don't suddenly start
pounding when I'm still speaking!
Do you think that you can
make me come with this dick?
If you want to make me come,
you'll need to violate me so bad!
How about this, Risa-nee!
Nipple and Vaginal Unison Attack!
Don't penetrate my pussy while pinching my nipples...
Your dick is reaching my deepest part.
It feels good!
You're one lewd sister in heat!
I'll welcome myself in your womb.
I-It can't be helped,
Feel free to push all the way into my womb!
Risa-nee is my personal fuck hole!
You're so tight, I'm coming soon!
Cum.. inside me... In my deepest parts!
Give it to me! Want to try knocking me up?
I-I'm getting filled up so much with hot stuff.
Elder Sister Alarm Clock!
What a wonderful way
to wake up in the morning!
Honoo no Haramase Oppai ★ Ero Appli Gakuen
Wake up, it's late already!
How long do you intend to sleep?
Risa-nee...
Put that repulsive thing away
immediately! Stupid kid.
I'll be going now.
Being able to have such a
hot morning wake-up sex
with Risa-nee who's usually strict on me
is all thanks to this smartphone app!
I was surprised when the cat I saved
that time suddenly talk and gave me this.
A "Love Smartphone" with apps
that will assist me get on good terms with girls!
Since I want to try it already,
I started the app and...
Wait! Don't suddenly transform me into a human!
I see, I get it now!
Stop!
Although the breast size is lacking,
I still came so it's good enough.
How dare you say that after raping someone?
It seems that this phone can fulfill my desires.
It's a smart phone enchanted
with perverted ero-app!
I feel that something good is gonna happen today.
Having that said, the girls of our school
has a wide range of bust sizes!
Hey, didn't your breast grow bigger again?
Cut that out!
If you'll show me such a spectacle
As the school's so-called
number one perverted gentleman,
there's only one thing for me to do!
School conquest via Ero-app, girls only!
Eww, what a creep!
Senpai told us not to approach that guy at all costs.
What's with that long queue?
Anything unrelated to schoolwork or
deemed as improper will be confiscated.
Please bear that in mind.
Majime...
What a way to greet someone, Shiramine.
What kind of place do you think a school is?
All of these are to be disposed in the incinerator.
Burning them isn't confiscation anymore!
Public Morals
Committee Chairman
Intrauterine
Inspection
By the way, Shiramine Sumika,
you're not exempted from the rules even as the
chairman of the public morals committee, right?
W-What's are you up to?
Then I'll be checking on you as well!
Huh? Who gave you such power to—
I knew it, you're hiding such lewd tits!
I-Inside my pussy, even if it's my first time...
I'm being inspected inside up to my womb!
You lead on Public Morals, yet
what's with this lewd underwear?!
That's not true! I'm not wearing
any improper underwear!
Your body is lewdness in itself!
I'm being shamed, but still I'm coming!
Safe!
You're always busy running
around everywhere, aren't you?
Can't you go to school peacefully just like me?
By the way, Yui. Do you know what this is?
Here, here!
Ah, isn't that the one which can do nothing else
but take 2 megapixel snapshots
of rubbish like itself, right?
Don't call it rubbish!
Good morning, Majime-kun.
Oh, you bought a phone.
The design is very cute.
Oh, Ayane-chan!
You understand how great this smartphone is?
What's wrong with you, Yui?!
Are you okay, Majime-kun?
You're an angel, Ayane-chan!
I'm giving my phone's virginity
snapshot to Ayane-chan!
E-Ehh! Majime-kun's virginity...
and first shot...
Even if we're childhood friends that's...
Just hold it! I'm also—
Could that be—
Just in time.
(Good morning!)
Доброе утро!
I knew it. Velka...
Can't you go to school normally?
Yeah, it's disturbing other people.
We were about to take some pictures.
Why not join them?
(Yes.)
Да.
I will.
Okay, ready?
Say cheese!
H-Hey, Masato.
Huh? What is it?
Want to eat lunch together at the rooftop?
Majime!
Majime, want to go to the airport
together on lunch break?
I'll let you on the cockpit.
Really?
Of course. I'll let you on any time you want.
No matter how many times I come here,
this place doesn't look like the back of our school.
(Hello.)
Привет.
Majime, why are you here?
You said you're gonna show me around.
Don't you remember?
Majime,
(Yes, I'm sorry.)
Да, жальщины я!
(thank you)
By the way, Спасибо as always for those tiddies!
Ace Oppai-lot
Eroid Version
I don't quite get details yet...
but for now I triggered an event!
Oh yeah, I forgot to tell you that my unit isn't a two-seat model.
I don't mind it being crammed inside.
Majime... that's my—
Your suit is really erotic.
More erotic than just being stark naked.
Velka, are you wearing panties?
When I'm wearing a pilot suit, I don't—
Don't, stop slurping me down there!
Velka, your pussy's engine is starting to warm up!
I'm being outdone by Majime,
My pride as a pilot can't allow this further.
I won't lose!
Velka, that feels so good!
Majime, does it feel good?
(Is Vivi good?)
Виви хорошо?
Is it too much for you?
(happy)
Are you счастье?
Majime, does it feel good?
You don't have to hold back.
I won't lose!
Does it feel good, Velka?
My pussy is throbbing more than before!
Your pussy, your tongue and your tits,
(good)
Velka's whole body is so erotic, it's хорошо!
You came so much, Majime.
Filling up a girl's mouth—
My bad, I couldn't hold it in and came!
How cruel of you to come all by yourself.
Unauthorized retreat in battle is prosecutable.
Make me come too.
Okay, let's come together this time!
Velka, you're making a face
saying that you crave me!
That's because... Majime is...
(holding back)
сдерживать!
What should I do, it won't stop trembling down there!
I can't take anymore!
Where's that place?
Pussy! It's trembling.
Can you comfort it
using your dick, please?
Your dick is sliding inside me!
Are you okay, Velka?
Does it hurt?
I-It's not like your dick
can hurt me or anything.
It's going in, pumping in and out,
Majime, Majime!
You're tightening down there!
Do you like dick that much, Velka?
D-Don't say that!
I love it because it's your dick.
Your dick inside me twitched just now!
Your insides feel so good, I'm coming soon!
I feel good too!
Stir me more inside with your dick.
So good, you're hitting my deepest part.
What's wrong, Majime?
Whenever I pull out,
your vulva gets pulled out
with my dick and it's so erotic!
Majime, why are you such a pervert?
Just like that, have you no shame
talking about lewd stuffs?
So are you, shaking your hips like that.
Aren't you a pervert yourself?
Majime... Keep moving,
give me more of your cock!
Pour your semen inside me!
I'm gonna fly, I'm gonna fly!
No good! Coming! I'm gonna come
from your sperm dripping inside!
You're coming inside!
You came this much.
Did it feel that good?
You're hard again.
Velka, our flight has only just began!
Wait, Majime! I just came
Don't!
I'm coming again!
Come! I'm coming too!
Your semen is dripping again,
it will make me come anytime!
I'm coming! I'm coming from
this perverted хорошо dick!
Amazing! So much hot and slimy semen.
M-Majime-kun...
I always wanted a pillow like this!
T-That's...
Wait, don't—
What are you doing?
(Greetings...)
Приветствие...
Majime-kun always has boobs
in his mind. It's embarrassing.
Let him do that and it won't be long before you get pregnant.
A baby with Majime-kun...
Ehh, what should I do?
That won't happen!
Taking that aside, your tits are
good today as well, Ayane-chan!
Y-Yes!
Don't get flattered!
And also, if Masato asks me, I'll—
Ah, wait!
Breastfeeding App
Erotic Nursing
from Ayane-chan
This is...
Ah, I just remembered!
Majime-kun, can I ask you a favor?
Favor?
It's about the Housewife Training Club,
I need another person for a practice.
I'll be glad to help you!
Oh my, Majime-kun.
You're still not weaning.
If you'll suck that way, I'm—
You're such a spoiled child.
'Coz Ayane-mama's tits taste good!
Drink more and grow up.
Mama is gonna rub your wee wee, okay?
Oh no, I'm feeling light-headed.
Mama, could it be you're feeling
good when I suck your tits?
No, I'm not.
Stop, Majime-chan. Don't tease me down there.
Because of Majime-chan,
I became a lewd mother!
Eh, I'm gonna come! Mama!
Me too! Mama is gonna come!
It's coming out of my boobs!
I'm coming with my breasts!
Majime-kun, I don't want to
play this mother-child game,
I want to have Majime-kun's child instead.
Ayane-chan!
Majime-kun, not like that!
I can't take it anymore, I want your dick.
I became a bad girl!
I'm at my limit too.
You're going inside me!
My deepest parts are being stretched
to the shape of your dick!
You're poking deep inside me!
Your pussy is grasping me so tight,
I might come soon!
Me too.
Your dick feels so good,
I'm gonna come soon!
Me too! You dick is...
making my pussy melt.
I'm coming! My breast is coming too!
Majime-kyun! Majime-kyun!
Coming! Coming!
You're getting big inside me again.
Yup! You're so horny that you
haven't had enough, right?
I'm gonna be sure to make you pregnant today!
M-Majime-kun's semen is
making lewd sounds deep in me!
I just came earlier.
I'm still sensitive, so if you do it rough...
I'm gonna come again!
Come as many times as you like!
Majime-kun! Do it more, violate me!
Over and over,
I want yo to fill me with hot stuff,
in the room where babies are made!
With this pussy sloshing with my semen,
and these tits that spurts milk when coming,
my dick can come as much as possible!
I'm happy! More! Mess me up!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
My pussy is coming! My boobs are coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Ayane-chan, I'm shooting it again inside!
Do it! Fill me up!
Release your sperm deep in my womb!
Majime-kun, I can feel your dick twitching inside.
And after that, I used this perverted app for...
Sex education lesson in Health and P.E. Class!
Being satisfied by Natsu-nee's
secret menu in the Maid Cafe!
And another one, a nude school
visit huge breasted housewives!
And so I lived a harem school life
just like in ero games.
One day...
Masato!
You need something, Yui?
Just shut up and come with me.
Wait, Yui!
Just when I had everyone
feeding me ice cream...
Boob
Ice Cream
Boob Ice Cream?
I can feed you some ice cream,
if you really wanted to.
Sex inside
the photo booth
Two events at the same time?
It should be fine here, let's go inside the arcade.
H-Hey, Yui!
Well then, I'll go in first and get ready.
Get ready for what? Hmm...
Aren't you done yet?
Hey, Yui!
Here you go! Titty Love Potion Ero-witch!
Have a taste.
...something like that?
So this is the Boob Ice Cream!
My breast is being licked!
What a hot perverted tongue, I'm being violated!
No! You're nibbling me like a puppy!
It's my turn next.
"Do unto breasts as you would
have the breasts do unto you."
I'll be eating you this time.
It's so hot.
Get it up.
Just tell me and I'll let you use
these tit-pussy and mouth-pussy,
whenever you need to shoot
out all your stacked up semen.
Yui, your tits and pussy... nah!
Everything about you is lewd.
I'll squeeze you with my tit-pussy.
Shoot it out on my breasts!
I won't forgive you if you won't come!
Amazing! You're impregnating my breasts.
You can't take it anymore and want
to put it in me already, right?
In your childhood friend's pussy,
beneath the pantyhose.
Tell you what,
I won't settle for coming outside
after being seduced this much.
Try if you can put it in if you can.
Coward.
Hey! You're suddenly being rough!
There's a limit for lack of manners!
You say that while your pussy
makes these sloppy sounds.
Just how wet are you?!
You're gonna see everything, pervert!
Your pretty pink asshole is in full view!
My pussy is being raped by
this perverted peasant's hot dick.
No good! Coming!
No! I'm throbbing inside, it's driving me crazy!
Your pussy has been
gripping me for a while now!
Fill me a lot inside!
Say no more!
I feel it pumping,
your cock is jumping inside!
My womb is gulping down your cum.
The countdown will start soon so please decide your pose.
Looks like the machine has started.
Want to capture your face at orgasm in a picture?
I knew that you are more perverted than I am!
That's not true!
I never meant it like that!
Coming! I'm coming!
Your hot dick is melting my pussy!
Your hot and hard dick is
too much! My senses are fading!
So good! I can't take anymore!
Is your pose okay no?
We'll start the countdown.
Shoot! I want to squeeze all your semen!
Inside, give it to me inside!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
You don't have to tell me, I'll end
this by filling up your womb!
Coming! For real... coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
Impregnate me with a creampie!
Coming! Coming!
Eh? What's wrong?
What's going on?
Seems like the app has
only one usage limit left.
For real?!
For real!
How can this be?!
This is...
This app is...
"With a U-Turn"
For the sake of my Ambition!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization