Holding it!
Sucking it!
And making me pregnant!
"Creampie Debut", let's go!
H! A! R! A! M! A! S! E!
Pai oppai oppai o
Boobs boobs boobs boobs!
haramase masete
Make me, make me pregnant!
shikyuu made todoku youni to
Please reach all the way to the womb,
hoshi ni negai wo kakete itta
I pray to the stars as I cum.
hakudaku suru atsui omoi
This passionate thought to be stained in white,
Best Boobs in the Academy
Aizawa Momoka
mune no naka wo hotobashiru
Gushes through my heart.
takumashiku sosoritatsu no wa
Standing sturdily here,
hikari kagayaku sairiumu
Is a glow stick emerged in light.
shita no saki de name mawashite
Using the tip of my tongue to lick back and forth,
Please...
Harder... Thrust at me harder...
oppai de aibu sutehji
And caressing it with my boobs.
peropero shitara torotoro ni naru
As I lick it, it gets wetter and wetter.
sounyuu resson wa pahfuekuto yo
I'm mastered my insertion lessons!
Because it's right before the show, my
pussy just can't stop feeling aroused!
naka ni irezu ni demachi da nante
If you just wait outside without putting it in,
Producer, please watch carefully,
On the stage... I'll be sure to show you the
best looking and most erotic side of me!
zettai yurusanai kara ne
I'll never forgive you!
itsu datte honban yo
No matter what time, it's always the real deal,
nakadashi ga suki dakara
It's because I like being cgreampied!
nando demo nando demo
No matter how many times, no matter how many times,
The Idol is an Assassin!?
Kuroki Shion
ikasete hoshii kimochi
My feelings of wanting to cum from you won't stop!
afuredasu kaikan ni
Within this over flowing pleasure,
kono ai wo KanjiOP tara
If you can feel my love,
naka ni dashite haramasete
Please cum inside and make me pregnant!
Producer...
shining my star zed
shining my star zed!
You can't...
It's almost time for the show...
I just wanted to pee...
If you're... If you're so rough... it'll come out...
It'll all come out!
No, no, no!
setore no ato ni mo ancohru
After the set list comes the encore.
hibiite binnkan mata itta
Still sensitive from earlier I cum again.
mirareru to koufun shita
being watch makes me really excited,
The Ladylike Airhead
Isuzukawa Akino
dokimune mou tomaranai
and I can't stop my heart from pounding.
kuchi janai oshiri demonai
Not with my mouth, nor with my butt,
chanto hazukashii tokoro ni
Please use the embarrassing place properly.
sono oku made kaki mawashite
Stir it up deep inside.
nakadashi debut sasete
Give me my creampie debut!
Producer...
pachu pachu sarete hiku hiku shichau
Being slushed around, is making it twitch unstoppably.
Even though... the guests are almost here...
machi kirenai hayaku choudai
I can't wait, please give it to me already!
Even though they'll see me in such
an embarrassing situation...
naka ni dasareta atsukute koi no
This hot and thick stuff released inside me,
M-My pussy feels so good I can't stop!
zettai koboshitari shinai
I'll never spill a drop!
I'm cumming!
ishiki sae tobu kurai hageshiku dashiire shite
Thrust so hard that I could lose my consciousness,
hateshinaku hateshinaku dora e noboru kimochi
this feeling of rising into an endless, endless sky.
The Little Sister is a Shy Girl
Hinagata Kobato
shinnjiteru zecchou no shunkan wo mukaetara
I believe that, in the moment I reach the climax,
naka ni dashite haramasete
You'll cum inside and make me pregnant
Shining My Start Z
Shining My Start Z!
What do I do?
Even though... it's almost the show...
I'm really wet...
I'm getting more and more perverted!
Producer-san...
Please punish my slutty pussy!
namade de ii nama ga ii
Doing it raw is fine, I want it raw,
nakadashi ga hoshii kara
because I want the creampie!
nukanaide nukanaide
Don't pull out, don't pull out,
The Competitive Model Student
Kugayama Nanako
haramu made zutto
Not until I get pregnant!
dakishimeta unmei ni
This fate I hold on to,
I... I've been holding back since the show...
eien wo kanjiOP tara
If you can feel the forever after, too.
naka ni dashite haramasete onegai
Cum inside me and make me pregnant, please!
Wanting Producer-san's dick...
I got so soaked...
itsu datte honban yo
No matter what time, it’s always the real deal,
nakadashi ga suki dakara
It's because I like being creampied!
nando demo nando demo
No matter how many times, no matter how many times,
ikasete hoshii kimochi
My feelings of wanting to cum from you won't stop!
afuredasu kaikan ni
Within this over flowing pleasure,
kono ai wo KanjiOP tara
If you can feel my love,
naka ni dashite haramasete
Please cum inside and make me pregnant!
shining my star zed
Shining My Star Z!
It's fine... let it out!
Spray it over me!
My pussy... inside my pussy... let out lots!
Make me pregnant!
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
The Entire Class is an Idol Group! ALL Members Part of Impregnation Production!
Blazing Impregnation: Boob Idols - My Star Academy z
Aizawa Momoka's first DVD!
Peach and Beach!
The V-cups I'm proud of, here and here and there, too!
It's a DVD full of swimsuit wear!
All guys need...
For Appreciation purposes;
For Preservation purposes;
For Missonary purposes;
And for practical purposes.
You have to buy at least four!
That's a promise with me, ok?
Maybe it's because the Producer came for me.
We go a lot of good filming done!
So, I'll give you lots of special service today, too.
Then... I'll accept it right away!
Somehow this is... tickly...
Momoka-san's milk... it's sweet... and sticky...
It tastes good!
H-hey!
Don't say it in such an erotic way...
Even my heart will start to pound...
Hey, what are you doing?
This time, I want to drink milk from here, too.
No... you can't...
I'm a gravure idol...
I can't allow it to come out from my nipples!
I'll hide Momoka-san's nipples with my hands.
You can't...
If the producer does that to me,
my nipples will stay hard!
It's fine... I'm also like this, too...
I'll feel good from my nipples... you can't...
It's okay... you are lusting after my boobs, right?
I might be a little happy for that...
Mo-Momoka-san...
Wait... Producer...
It tickles...
Don't rub your penis so much... you can't...
I... can't hold back.
Geez... the producer is so perverted...
Your penis... it's twitching between my boobs.
There are wet fluids coming out from the tip.
Momoka-san's boobs... they're so
slippery, it feels really good...
Hey... when looking at my photo shoots...
do you also stroke it like this?
Eh?
So do you?
You're the only person I can ask something like this...
If you don't answer I'll stop.
I-I did.
I... masturbated to Momoka-san's albums.
For example where you had a banana
between your boobs...
Or where you had your legs spread
into a letter M on the beach...
I was amazingly excited!
Geez... you don't have to go into the details...
Or where you're licking at a Popsicle...
It's like you're doing it to me... it's just incredibly erotic...
I see... so squeezing is not all to it... you
also want me to suck your penis...
Mo-Momoka-san...
Your penis...
It's getting larger... no...
It won't fit into my mouth...
I'm... going to...
Let it out... let out lots and lots inside my mouth!
Momoka-san, is this really alright?
It's fine. After all, you're not satisfied yet, are you?
To accept all of a guy's lust... this is the only way.
Mo-Momoka-san's pussy... is incredibly hot!
The Producer's penis is really thick!
It's spreading my pussy apart...
Even though you came so much,
your penis is still so hard!
Momoka-san... you don't have to force yourself.
Just wait, Onee-san will... make you
feel good right away with her pussy.
No... you penis is reaching all the way to my womb.
My pussy is getting more and more turned on!
Not that! If you tease my boobs at the same time...
It'll come out, it'll come out!
No... no...
My nipples... if you rub my nipples like that...
I... I'll go crazy... More will come out from my boobs!
You're drinking from my boobs!
Your pussy is squeezing so tightly on me...
That's because... my pussy feels so good...
it doesn't want to let go of your penis!
I'm... I'm about to cum!
It's fine... You can cum inside if you want...
The hot, sticky semen... deep inside...
spray lots to my womb!
Momoka-san!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming... I'll cum!
It's hot...
Hot semen is overflowing inside me...
It feels like I'll get a burn...
What happened to day is a secret
between only the two of us!
You're the only one I'd allow to take
a photo like this, you know.
The Anime that I, Kugayama Nanako is currently voicing,
"My Younger Sister Has Eighth Grade Syndrome and
Few Friends", is now available in DVD and Blueray!
My secrets that are a little erotic and embarrassing...
I'll share with only you.
Note: A tongue twister used for vocal practice.
Amenbo akaina aiueo...
Ukimoni Koebimo oyoideru
Kakinoki kurinoki kakikukeko
Kitsutsuki kotsukotsu karekeyaki
Sasageni suwokake...
Alright! Then let's try the actual script.
Producer, are we really doing this?
Of course!
No... St-Stop it...
Something like this...
Ah...
My boobs...
They'll see!
Y-you can't...
P-Please
Stop it!
Oh! As expected, doing this makes the acting more real.
Don't fondle my chest so much!
I'll lose concentration... on the acting...
It's fine if you actually feel good from this, you know.
The fans will be happier that way, too.
Don’t... don't say something stupid like that.
Voices for these scenes... are
different from that in reality!
F-fine...
I'll do it for you.
You're getting so large.
The producer's penis is sure amazing.
Nanako...
She's so erotic...
You're the only person I'd do this for...
Hey... these things aren't written in the script.
I'm just improvising. You're happy with it, right?
I'll make you feel real good, so you'd better be prepared.
Wait a bit... this is dangerous... you're sucking me dry...
Wow...
His dick is getting hotter and bigger!
No way... My nipples are even getting hard from this...
It's fine, let it all out.
I'll be sure to take it all!
We're far, far from done here!
From now, back to the script!
Eh? We're still going on?
You can't!
Let me go...
I'm a virgin...
Please...
Not that...
Anything but that!
I'll be moving with all I got.
You'd better be prepared.
No...
No!
Th-that's...
So cruel...
All the way inside so suddenly... Ah... Stop... It hurts...
It hurts!
Don't be so rough!
Ah... Ahh...
Ahhh...
No...
I-It's embarrassing...
Stop...
This position...
My pussy will be completely exposed...
Ahh...
Nanako, now this isn't in the script.
You're so soaked and happy down here.
Shut up already.
You can't do anything... about something like that!
C'mon, c'mon, the script still continues, right?
You dick is...
Inside my pussy...
It's rubbing against my insides...
No... Ahhh... You can't... It'll feel good...
My pussy...
Don't stir and mess it up with your dick!
Ah...
Ahhh...
My pussy...
Is going to take the shape of you dick...
It'll become a pussy for your personal use!
Ah... Ahhhhh...
Geez, Nanako. Using the word pussy again
and again, it's so embarrassing!
I'm embarrassed about it, too!
It can't be helped.
It's written like that on the script!
Oh wow, even your breast milk came out.
Was that in the script?
That's not... that's not it, this is...
I'm... really starting to feel good...
I see. Then, I'll go on all the way like the script says!
That's... No, you can't! You can't do that!
Please, stop it!
Like I can stop!
Just like the script, I'll cum inside!
You can't!
You can't do that! You know that, right!?
I... I have to become a top idol!
Something like creampie... No! You can't!
What convincing acting!
It's like you actually don't want it.
I'm not acting!
It's really... you really can't cum inside!
Please, pull it out, pull it out!
No!
Here we go, Nanako!
No way... your dick is getting larger and larger...
If this goes on, even I'll cum... you'll make me cum...
No, no...
You actually... let out so much...
What do I do if I get a baby... you idiot...
The new Enka star Isuzugawa Akino has her
debut album "Drizzling Love Forecast"
now on sale at all major stores, CD shops and online!
Dear passengers at the Nukinuki Station
of the Nikubou Line, nice to meet you.
Today, the three of us, idols from Gingira Academy,
will be your station manager for the day.
Note: both "station" and bodily "fluids'' are pronounced "Eki"
Here, the sash uses the kanji for fluids instead of station.
They're looking...
Everyone is looking at my slutty boobs.
I'm showing my skin at a place like this...
What do I do?
It's so embarrassing, but my nipples are getting hard.
It's like I'm being violated by their gaze...
I never thought that just being watched
would make me strung...
C'mon, Akino-san.
It's included in the idol's job to be looked at by everyone.
Yes, Producer...
Everyone... my legs are opening, so please
retreat behind the white line as you watch.
A pose like this...
My embarrassing parts are all completely showing...
Amazing. You're so soaked already.
I... I get wet easily...
It's because I'm station manager for the day...
My slutty juices... fluids... are overflowing...
Yeah... this should allow it to go in all the way!
No way... again... I'm being photographed again...
Akino-san is hot and tight!
Dear... dear passenger...
Please don't push so much!
My pussy... is already at max capacity with your penis!
Akino-san... please do your best...
I'll... I'll be there with you, too!
Producer-san, you can't... you can't do that!
Me too... I'll help Akino, too.
Shion-san... please don't tease my boobs...
You shouldn't do that! That unsafe driving!
Akino-san, you've got to announce it to your passengers.
Yes...
Everyone, you are currently riding Akino
in the reverse stand and carry position.
Ekiben: Concessions sold on a serving tray strapped to the neck
Akino-san's... your boobs are getting so hot...
My pussy... is also getting wet....!
No... just watching... is not enough anymore!
My hips... They're moving on their own... I can't stop!
Kobato
Shion
Akino
Stand and Carry
Doggy Style
Revers Stand and Carry
Noe arriving
The next station is
Last Train
Well then, let's start transferring to the other line.
Meat Train Express
Transferring
Deep inside...
It's going deep inside...
The penis-train is on course in Kobato's pussy!
Kobato-chan's pussy is sucking on to me.
It's really erotic.
No... Don't say that!
Even though it's embarrassing when
they passengers are watching...
I'm getting... more and more aroused...
I...
No... no...
My nipples... nipples are trembling so much...
Kobato-chan. It's manners to be on
vibrating mode inside the train.
That's... So these are manners for riding...
Dear passengers, thank you so
much for your cooperation.
Your pussy is squeezing really tight.
Are you about to cum already?
I'm sorry... Kobato is a high-speed train just for penises!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Please mind the closing of the pussy.
The producer's penis...
It's so thick, and hot... my vagina's ride
rate is going over a hundred percent!
That must be a problem.
We have to start developing a new line.
That's... that's my butt...
Not my butt!
This is... quite tight!
If you rub so much...
The two lines will get intermingled...
My diagrams will jet messed up!
Alright, it's loosed up.
Now to open the line!
Amazing... it's my first time having anal, but it's so good!
I...
I'm being filmed...
They're photographing my anal line opening ceremony!
No... My body is getting really
excited from all these shots...
Shion... In celebration of the opening,
I'm cumming inside!
It's fine... I'll... I'll cum together, too...
So let it... let it out where you want!
The penis train... is getting faster and faster...
It's coming, it's coming...
No... I'm already at my limit...
It's coming out, It'll come out!
Akino-san, you've got to announce it to your passengers.
Yes...
Everyone... momently we will launch
at my boobs, so please be careful!
The pleasure express is plunging through my tunnel...
Cumming... I'm cumming...
Akino... Akino is at...
The end of the line!
Thank you so much for...
riding with us today...
Th-This DVD... is really going to be sold?
There's no way we could do that!
We're withdrawing it! Yes we are!
Eh? Even though everyone was quite
happy during the filming...
That's because,., well... in the heat of the moment...
It's too embarrassing... for the fans to see...
Although...
If it's just the producer watching
it himself, I can forgive you.
shikyuu made todoku youni to
Please reach all the way to the womb,
hoshi ni negai wo kakete itta
I pray to the stars as I cum
hakudaku suru atsui omoi
This passionate thought to be stained in white,
mune no naka wo hotobashiru
Gushes through my heart.
takumashiku sosoritatsu no wa
Standing sturdily here,
Hikari kagayaku sairiumu
Is a glow stick emerged in light.
shita no saki de name mawashite
Using the tip of my tongue to lick back and forth,
oppai de aibu suteji
And caressing it with my boobs.
peropero shitara torotoro ni naru
As I lick it, it gets wetter and wetter.
sounyuu resson wa pahfuekuto yo
I'm mastered my insertion lessons!
naka ni irezu ni demachi da nante
If you just wait outside without putting it in,
zettai yurusanai kara ne
I'll never forgive you!
itsu datte honban yo
No matter what time, it's always the real deal,
nakadashi ga suki dakara
It's because I like being creampied!
nando demo nando demo
No matter how many times, no matter how many times,
ikasete hoshii kimochi
My feelings of wanting to cum from you won't stop!
afuredasu kaikan ni
within this over flowing pleasure,
kono ai wo kanji tara
I f you can feel my love,
naka ni dashite haramasete
Please cum inside and make me pregnant!
shining my star zed
Shining My Star Z!