Huh? Is it morning already?
But it feels tike my dick is really warm or something...
What's the matter? Something wrong?
You're wearing a maid outfit, Risa-nee and you're...
It's another morning of you...
Getting this hard in front of me
even though I'm your big sister.
That's your fault for being this cute!
Seriously, are you listening to what
you're even saying right now?
I'm going to take this pretentious dick of yours and...
And take real good care of it.
Look, your dick is getting even harder!
R-Risa-nee!
You don't have to shove... your dick into me so desperately.
Do you really like b-boobs that much?
But I guess you're not really a morning person.
If I'm not rough enough, you probably won't wake up at all.
How's it feel to have your big sister
aggressively sucking your dick?
J-Just looking at how you're reacting makes it
pretty easy to tell where your weak spots are.
H-Hey, I can tell where your weak spots are too, Risa-nee!
Looks like your nipples are too
shy to come out and play, huh?
My nipples are...
They're just like your dick... They don't
get hard without a friendly touch.
That's good. Just keep going, cum whenever you want.
I can't believe you came this much
from our big sister's tit fuck.
You're quite the helpless little brother, aren't you?
Risa-nee, you're wearing a maid outfit,
so shouldn't you be calling me "Master"?
Th-That's a good point.
I guess I'll let you off the hook just for today.
I'm putting it in, Master.
My perverted little brothers dick, it's...
It's getting so big inside me!
Wh-Why does it feel so good?
My mind's going blank!
I bet it feels this good for you
because it's your little brother's dick!
You pervert, Risa-nee!
Hey! Don't thrust your dick inside
someone when they're talking, stupid!
Do you really think this dick is going to make me cum?!
If you really want to make me cum with
that then you have to fuck me harder!
How's this, Risa-nee?!
I'm fucking you while playing with your nipples!
Getting fucked while having you
messing with my nipples is amazing!
Your dick's hitting me so deep!
It feels so good!
You slutty big sister of mine!
I'm gonna flood your pussy with cum!
I-I guess I have no choice. Cum inside me to your last drop!
Your pussy's just for me, Risa-nee!
It's too tight! I'm gonna cum!
Do it!
Give it to me! Pour your hot stuff
inside the deepest part of me!
Try getting your big sister pregnant!
There's so much hot stuff coming out inside me...
I love this alarm clock!
Passion of Impregnable Tits Perverted App Academy
Hey, it's time.
Get out of bed already!
Risa-nee...
Put that disgusting thing away and get dressed!
You fool.
I'm leaving now.
Risa-nee usually acts like a drill sergeant.
But she has such dirty morning sex with me.
It's all thanks to this phone and this app!
One day, I saved a female cat who could somehow talk.
As thanks, I got this "love phone" that
helps me get along better with girls.
And so when I immediately tried out the app...
Hey, don't put me in my human
form without my permission!
I-I got it.
I understand now!
Stop!
I guess the boobs left something to be
desired, but I guess I'm satisfied for now.
Hey that's rude considering you just basically raped me!
Apparently this phone has an app on it that
allows me to fulfill any of my sexual desires!
It really feels like something
amazing is gonna happen today!
But damn, the boob level of this academy is high as usual!
Hey, did your boobs get bigger again?
Hey, cut it out.
As the guy who's known as the biggest pervert in the
entire academy gazing upon this sight makes me...
It makes me realize that there's only
one thing left to do with this phone!
It's time for me to conquer this academy
with this perverted app (but only the girls)!
Academy Conquest
What's he doing? He's gross.
I heard that we shouldn't go near that guy.
Wait, that line of people...
We will be confiscating all things
indecent and unrelated to school.
Please comply.
Ugh, Majime?
You don't greet people with "ugh".
Shiramine...
What are you trying to do at this school?
All of these items will be incinerated.
Incinerated?! Not confiscated?!
So, Shiramine Sumika,
I'm sure that means that as head of the moral
committee, you're not holding anything indecent, right?
Wh-What are you saying all of a sudden?
Then let me search you!
With what authority...
I knew it! You really were hiding your indecent boobs, huh?!
You're taking my first time too!
Your hot dick is searching me all the way into my womb!
How can you call yourself the head of the
morals committee when you're this lewd?!
I'm not! I'm not this indecent of a person!
Your body is lewdness incarnate!
It's so hot! I'm getting so wet! I'm gonna cum from this too!
Safe!
You really like cutting it close, huh?
Can't you just plan out your time better
so you can get her on time like I do?
By the way, Yui, do you know what this is?
This right here!
Oh I see you finally got a garbage bare bones
phone that can only take 200M quality pictures.
Don't call it garbage, you meanie!
Good morning, Majime-kun.
Oh, you got a new phone!
It's got a really cute design!
Ayane-chan!
Do you understand just how amazing this phone is?
What are you doing, Yui?!
Hmph.
Are you okay, Majime-kun?
Ayane-chan, you're such an angel!
Because you're so great, I'm going to
give my phone's picture virginity to you!
Really? Your virginity?
Your first girl?
We might be childhood friends, but that might be a little...
Hey, just hold on a second. I...
Wait, is that...
Phew, I made it.
Я провожу рукой по столу, жёсткие крошки впиваются в кожу...
Greetings.
I knew it...
Ну ладно хоть не Миша Ивачкова. :)
Velka, can't you come to school a little more normally?
You really like making a scene.
I was just about to take a picture of them.
You should be in it too.
Sure. No problem.
Okay, I'm taking it.
One, two, cheese!
H-Hey, Masato?
Yeah? What's up?
You wanna eat on the roof together today?
Majime!
Majime, do you want to come to the airstrip for lunch?
I'll let you sit in the cockpit.
You serious?!
Of course! You're welcomed anytime.
But seriously, no matter how many times I come here,
I still can't believe this is really the back of our school.
I'm confused. What are you doing here, Majime?
You're the one who asked me to be here!
I bet you forgot!
Majime, don't worry about it.
But seriously, your boobs are just as spasiba as always!
Ace Tit Pilot
Eroid Edition
This is...
I don't realty get what I'm supposed to do, but...
But whatever, let's do this!
Oh right, sorry, but my craft isn't exactly the most spacious.
Oh I'm fine with it being a little cramped.
Majime, that's...
This suit is really sexy.
It's even sexier up close!
Velka, are you not weaning panties?
I don't wear anything when I put on the pilot suit...
Don't! Don't lick me so much!
I think your pussy's engines are starting to rev up!
I'm not going to let this be so one
sided... my honor as a pilot won't let me!
I'm not going to lose!
Velka, that feels so good!
Majime, it feels good?
Кокаинум...
Good. Harasho.
It feels so good that your tip is getting so wet, huh?
Majime, does it feel good? You don't have to hold back.
I'm not gonna lose!
– No!
– Does this feel good, Velka?
My pussy's tingling even more than before! I...
Your pussy, your tongue, your boobs...
everything about you is so sexy! It's so harasho!
You seriously cum too much, Majime.
All that raw cum shot into my mouth...
Sorry, I couldn't hold back anymore!
You're so mean, Majime. How could you
let yourself be the only one to cum?
You're deserting in the face of the enemy. That's horrible.
Make me cum too.
Sure. This time, let's cum together!
Velka, your face is saying that you
want me so bad, you can't wait!
Th-That's not...
Majime, yes, I want it in me so bad!
What should I do? I can't stop how hard it's craving you.
I can't... hold on!
And where are you referring to exactly?
My pussy's craving it!
So could you sate that craving with your dick, Majime?
Majime, your dick's pushing into me!
Are you okay, Velka?
Does it hurt at all?
Y-Your dick isn't really enough to...
I-It doesn't hurt at all, okay?
Your hot thing's ramming inside me!
Majime! Majime!!
You're getting even tighter now!
Do you really like dicks that much, Velka?
D-Don't say that!
Of course I like it. It's your dick, Majime.
Your dick just twitched inside me!
Being inside you feels so good, I can't hold back!
I feel really good too.
Majime your dick, is stirring me up inside so much!
So good! Your dick is going so deep inside me!
What's wrong, Majime?
Every time I move in and out of you,
your pussy clings on to me. It's so hot!
Majime, why are you such a pervert?
You just say all these perverted things
without even a second thought!
But look at how much you're
moving your hips right now, Velka!
You're a pretty big pervert yourself!
Majime! Move your dick more! Give me more of it!
I...
I want you to fill my insides with your cum!
I feel like I'm about to fly away!
I'm at war!
I can't... I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum from you shooting your cum into my pussy!
It's coming inside me!
You came so much...
Did it really feel that good, Majime?
Y-You're hard again?
Velka, our flight's just getting started!
Wait, Majime! I just came, so I...
No!
I'm cumming again!
Me too! I'm cumming too!
I'm gonna cum over and over again
from your cum flooding my pussy!
I'm cumming!
This perverted harasho dick is...
Making me cum!
Wow... there's so much cum dripping in and out of me...
Yay, it's finally over...
Oh, Majime-kun?
This is just the pillow I wanted right now!
Th-That's... You shouldn't do that.
Just what do you think you're doing?
Geez.
Shame on you.
Seriously, Majime-kun, is there anything
else on your mind besides boobs?
It's so embarrassing.
If he did that any longer, you would've gotten pregnant.
Hajime-kun's baby, huh? Hm I wonder...
Like hell that'd get you pregnant!
But more importantly, your boobs are
just as amazing as ever, Ayane-chan!
Th-Thanks?
Hey, don't get happy from that!
A-And if you wanted it, I could do that for...
Hold that thought.
Use the Boob Lesson App for Fun Times witnh Ayane-chan
This is...
Oh, right. Majime-kun, I actually have a
bit of a request for you if you don't mind.
Request?
Yeah. At practice for the bridal training club,
there's something we're doing that I can't do alone.
Sure! I'll gladly help you out!
Oh my, Hajime-kun, you like boobs too much...
If you keep sucking so roughly like that, I'm gonna...
Geez, Majime-chan, you're so spoiled...
But your boobs are just so delicious, Ayane!
Drink a lot and grow big, okay?
Mama's gonna rub your dick now, okay?
Oh no, my head's getting fuzzy for some reason!
Mama? Are you getting turned
on from me sucking your boobs?
No, of course not...
No! Don't tease me, Majime-chan!
You're going to make me into a dirty mama!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm... Mama's gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum from my boobs!
My boobs are cumming!
Majime-kun...
I don't want to just pretend play anymore...
I want your baby, Majime-kun...
Ayane-chan!
Majime-kun, don't tease me!
I want it so bad right now!
I want your dick so bad... I think
I've become a really dirty girl!
I can't wait any longer either!
Your dick is coming inside my Mama's room!
Every part inside me is being
changed into the shape of your dick!
I... My stomach is getting so tight and going crazy!
Ayane-chan, your pussy's so tight! I
feel like I'm gonna cum at any second!
Me too!
Your dick's so good, I feel like I'm gonna cum!
No, Majime-kun, your dick is...
It's making me go crazy!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
My boobs are cumming too!
Majime-kun! Majime-kun!!
I'm cumming!!
Majime-kun, your dick is cumming and getting big again.
Yep, I am. That wasn't enough for a
pervert like you either was it, Ayane-chan?
I'm gonna make sure you get pregnant today, Ayane-chan!
Majime-kun, your cum...
It's pumping into my stomach and filling it up!
My pussy just came, so it's really
sensitive. If you keep being this rough...
I'm gonna cum!
Sure. You can cum as much as you want.
Majime-kun! Do me hard! Mess me up so bad!
I want you to keep filling my baby room
with your hot stuff over and over again!
Whether it's your pussy filled with my cum
or your boobs that keep shooting milk,
I'm gonna make them cum so many times with my dick!
Oh my god, I'm being messed
up so bad by you, Majime-kun!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
My pussy's cumming! My boobs are cumming!
Ayane-chan, I'm gonna cum inside you again!
Do it!
Fill me up!
Fill my womb to the brim with your cum!
Hajime-kun...
Your dick is shaking inside me...
After that, thanks to this perverted app,
I was able to have my own personal
sex ed lesson in health class!
And at the maid cafe, I was able to
enjoy orders off the secret menu.
And I was even able to have fun times
with these big tittied married women.
And basically I was able to have
my very own harem at school.
Then one day...
Masato?
S-Something wrong, Yui?
Just come with me!
Huh? Uh, wait, Yui-san?!
Didn't you see that they were feeding me ice cream?
Boob ice cream?!
I-I can feed you ice cream if you really want.
Huh? Two at once?
Perfect. Let's go into the arcade over there.
H-Hey, Yui?
I'm going to go in first and get ready, okay?
Get ready? For what?
Are you ready yet?
Hey, Yui?
Okay, come in.
This is the Boob Love Potion: Ero Magic.
Eat it up.
Or are you not interested?
So this is what it meant by boob ice cream?
My cold, boob ice cream!
They're being melted by your hot perverted tongue!
Don't suck on them like an animal!
It's my turn next.
An eye for an eye.
You attack my boobs, I'll attack with them.
It's my turn to eat you up now.
This candy's so hot, huh?
Just hurry up and cum.
I'm going to squeeze out all that backed up cum of yours...
every last drop of it, with my boob and mouth-pussy.
Yui, your boobs and mouth... no,
everything about you is perverted!
Cum in between my boobs!
Cum wherever and whenever you want on me!
If you don't cum, I won't forgive you.
Are you cumming?
Wow, it's covering my boobs!
You want to put it in so bad right now, don't you?
You want to be the first person inside
your childhood friend's pussy, don't you?
Just telling you right now, you've taunted
me too much for me to not cum inside you!
Whatever. Just put it in already.
You coward.
Y-You're really going this hard right off the bat?
Don't you think this is a little beyond rude?
Yeah and look at how hard you're taking me
in and how wet you're getting despite that!
No! You can see all the way inside now!
You pervert!
Yeah, I can see your beautiful pink ass more perfectly, Yui.
No!
My pussy... it's getting melted
by your hot hard perverted dick!
No!
Stop, I'm cumming!
My entire body's getting really
tingly... it's making me go crazy!
Your pussy's been twitching for a while
now, it's just been cumming over and over!
Give me lots of it inside!
I was already gonna!
With each pulse of your dick, I
can feel cum shooting inside me.
My womb's gulping down your hot semen.
Okay I'm gonna count down, so strike a pose!
No! I started the photo booth.
So you want to save this moment in a picture?
You're more of a natural pervert than I am!
No! I'm not!
I'm not like that!
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
You're melting my pussy with your dick!
Your hard, hot dick is like a machine gun!
It just keeps rapid firing against my womb!
It feels so good, I can't help myself!
Got a pose ready?
Okay, here we go!
Make sure you shoot every last drop
from your dick inside me, okay?
10!
9!
8!
Give it to me inside, okay?
7!
6!
Cum! Cum!!
5!
4!
That was the plan! I'm gonna
finish your womb off with my cum!
I'm cumming! My pussy's cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Make your perverted dick cum
inside me to get me pregnant!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
3!
2!
1!
Love
Much Love
Huh? What's going on?
What do you want?
Looks like you can only use the app one more time.
For real?!
For real!
This can't be happening!!
Th-This is...
This app is!!
Activate and do my bidding for my ambition!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hetnaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч