Alright, I'm all in for it!
For the sake of my ambition!
If this is gonna be the last one,
I'm gonna enjoy this to it's fullest!
Senpai! Majime-senpai!
Oh... It's you, Matsuri-chan.
What are you doing?
I finished up my training earlier today.
I'm doing a maintenance for my dear bike!
Huh.. Senpai?!
Your tits are as big as always, Matsuri-chan!
No! You can't, senpai!
Sorry, it became a habit of mine...
If anyone happens to see us here...
[Matsuri-chan Maintenance ♥ App]
Here it comes! I've been waiting for this!
Senpai, this is embarrassing!
What are you saying? I'm helping
you on doing maintenance.
What is that for?
This is for your maintenance, of course!
You're lying...
You're talking like that,
but you're overflowing with grease down here.
Stop rubbing my nipples together!
Uhh, this is bad! We're doing a maintenance.
You leak lots of oil and it's staining all over.
D-Don't tease me down there!
I'm gonna get wetter!
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
We have to do a more
in-depth maintenance, right?
No, we can't! If you'll thrust it in me right now,
I'll end up coming non-stop!
No—!
I-I'm connected with you, senpai!
Your thick thing is so deep in me!
Your huge dick is scraping
so much inside my pussy...
I'm... I'm already gonna—
I can't take anymore of this!
If you keep on rubbing that much...
I can't take it anymore!
My pussy wants to reach the goal already!
Are you gonna come already, Matsuri-chan?
Coming... I'm gonna come
so please shoot your semen!
Alright, I'm going to apply a lot
of white grease into your womb, Matsuri-chan!
Please lubricate my pussy
inside with your white grease!
I can't anymore! Coming... Coming!
I'm gonna come!
Honoo no Haramase Oppai ★ Ero Appli Gakuen
Kimizuka-kun!
Hey, let's make the training tougher!
Oh, it's Tsuka-chan.
He's popular as always.
Though, for someone like him to be handsome in a showbiz level...
We're both men, and yet...
The world couldn't be more unfair!
Senpai, good morning!
Ah, yeah...
[Tsuka-chan ♥ Exposed Ballerina]
Tsuka-chan, exposed ballerina?
What the heck is this?
Even if he's in the cute
side with that girly face...
I don't swing that way!
Will I really do it with Tsuka-chan?
There's no way for something that crazy to...
Eh?
Isn't that a sarashi? Exposed ballerina...
Tsuka-chan, exposed...
Could it be?
Wh-What the hell!
S-Senpai! Wh-Why are you here?
B-Before that, Tsuka-chan... What the hell is this...
I-It's a long story...
I-I never imagined that you are a girl!
You're so gorgeous, yet why are
you pretending to be a man?
I'm going to teach you the
pleasures of being a woman.
Senpai...
Why are you cross-dressing even
when you look this lewd and cute?
Th-That's because I-I've been dressing as a boy since I was a child.
I-I get sexually aroused when being feminine...
Whenever I wear feminine clothes, I get excited
and I end up wanting to do lewd stuffs!
[Breast milk ♥ App]
Well then...
I'm gonna make you even more feminine!
Tsuka-chan, you've become a mother
even before having your first sex!
No! If you pinch my nipples,
they're gonna leak again!
S-Senpai, I'm not even pregnant
but I'm squirting milk out!
No! If you suck on me like that,
My tits will end up leaking more milk out!
Alright then, I'll make you drink my milk in return!
It's making mushy and obscene
sounds... This is so lewd!
Just keep on doing that.
Ah... try licking the tip as well.
Tsuka-chan, your tits are so erotic!
Senpai!
Rubbing me with your nipples
feels good, Tsuka-chan!
If you keep rubbing my nipples there...
I... I'm already going to—
What should I do? I'm feeling good myself
while sucking a man's dick!
Your tit-pussy feels the best, Tsuka-chan!
I'm coming already!
A-Are you gonna shoot it out already?
Catch all of your first ever
semen using your mouth!
So hot... Amazing... So lively!
You can't swallow it yet. Let me have
a good look of my semen in there.
Is this good enough?
You're dripping wet. Good job
on holding yourself together.
Don't worry, I'm gonna
satisfy your body in heat.
Th-That's...
I-It's going inside!
Your huge thing is gradually
digging deep into me!
How is it, Tsuka-chan? Any thoughts
about becoming a full-fledged woman?
You can't! Please pull it out!
A man's thing is inside me...
It's moving inside! It's rubbing all over inside me!
Tsuka-chan, tell me what's going inside? Come on.
I-I can't speak such vulgar words!
It's alright, come on!
A-A man's huge dick!
It's intruding inside my pussy!
Did you come to like my cock?
If you answer honestly, I'll poke it
somewhere inside that feels better!
I like it...
...when your dick is penetrating me,
it's rubbing my insides.
I'm begging you! Screw my pussy more with your dick...
Mess me up inside!
My pussy feels incredible!
My pussy is getting numb!
Your dick is reaching up to my womb!
I want to keep doing this
until we wear ourselves out!
You mean, you love sex even when it's just your
first time? You're an "Exposed Ballerina" indeed!
It's your fault, senpai!
You're pounding me down there!
You too, senpai. Please make yourself feel good
lots and lots more using my pussy!
I'm gonna come inside just like this!
Pour a lot in me! Shoot a lot of sperm in me!
Carve my pussy into the shape of your dick!
I'm coming... Coming... Coming—!
It's a creampie... Amazing!
My pussy is getting filled with your semen...
I'm delighted!
I'm coming again! It's coming out of my tits!
Wow... I can't get enough of Tsuka-chan's
personality gap from her usual self!
It's a new app again.
Make sure to watch
the TV show where
I'm gonna be a guest!
Oh, it's a mail from Kyouko.
Kyouko sure has been getting popular lately.
Ah, another mail again...
[Suddenly ♥ Girls' Restroom Door]
It's an app this time!
Woah! Suddenly, girls' restroom door, it says!
Make sure to watch
the TV show where
I'm gonna be a guest!
Make sure to watch it!
Submit a written reaction of
no less than 800 characters!
[Suddenly ♥ Girls' Restroom Door]
Sorry, but now's not the time for that!
I wonder if Ma-chan is watching the show right now?
I am an idol only for Ma-chan!
I'm coming!
Huh? M-M-M-Ma—
M-Ma-chan?
I have just arrived to heed
Kyouko's burning love call!
No! Don't look!
Oopsie!
Oh-ho! So this is the pussy of a
high-selling masturbating idol!
Slurp!
Ma-chan... It's dirty, I'm dirty down there!
You can't lick me down there!
I never have imagined getting a chance
to lick a high-selling idol's pussy.
No! It makes me feel so good...
...when you lick me down there!
You can come whenever you feel so, Kyouko!
I'm coming! Coming, coming... Coming...
I'm coming!
How was it, Kyouko? Did I make you
horny from licking your pussy?
Yeah... I got so horny!
So let me pay you back, okay?
A high-selling idol's blowjob
is so erotic! It's the best!
You mean it?
I want to give you more and more pleasure.
I'm gonna suck you lots more!
Kyouko, suck me while giving me a titfuck!
Got it!
Like this?
Am I doing alright?
Damn, this feels so good!
I'm already gonna coming—
It's okay, you can come... into my mouth-pussy...
Shoot a lot of it into your exclusive idol mouth-pussy!
This time, you'll perform a lovely
song number using my mic!
Jeez, you idiot...
You're entering inside me, Ma-chan!
Oh! So tight!
You've always been supporting ever since.
So, come to me!
It hurts!
I finally became one with you!
Does it still hurt, Kyouko?
I'm not really sure yet...
But keep on moving!
It's not like it hurts or anything
when you're moving, okay?
Don't try to endure the pain so much!
I-It's not like I'm enduring it—
Y-You're twitching inside me!
Ma-chan... Please, kiss... Kiss me!
Ma-chan...
Stick your tongue out too, Kyouko.
It seems that your pussy is already
getting used with having a man inside.
That's because your mic penis
is rubbing my pussy so much!
My pussy feels incredible!
Rub my pussy more with your cock!
It can't be helped! You're such a lewd idol, Kyouko!
So what—
Aren't you horny as well, Ma-chan?
My pussy is for your own usage.
Your cock is twitching, Ma-chan!
What can I say? Kyouko the idol
is getting satisfied by my cock!
More, thrust it in even harder!
Thrust your cock more into my pussy!
Kyouko, I'm coming!
It's coming! Your hot stuff is coming!
You're coming a lot!
No, no, no...
I'm coming again... No!
I'm sorry, Kyouko!
I already came, but it felt very
good that my hips wouldn't stop!
I love you... I love you so much!
I love you, Ma-chan!
So come in me! Come a lot more
inside me! Shoot a lot inside!
More! Come a lot inside my pussy!
You're hot stuff is flowing out of me!
That surely took a toll on me.
[Amanekoan (Sweet Cat Sanctuary)]
I'll take a break in here.
Tea Fortune Lot
Eh... There's a tea fortune lot.
Welcome, Majime-chan!
I came today as well for Misaki-chan's tits!
I-Is that so?
By the way, what kind of menu is this Tea Fortune Lot?
Great Luck
The written fortune lots are inside these manjuus.
If you got a great luck, you get
to have any drink you want for free.
I'll take one, then.
Not there, the manjuus are here.
Ahah... My bad. I'll help myself with one then!
Bad luck?
By the way, the ones with
bad luck are wasabi-flavored!
I forgot how sinister this woman is!
[Breast ♥ Massage Fortune Lot App]
Breast massage fortune lot app?
This is the kind of fortune lot I'm looking for!
Closed for Preparations
That's enough!
Huh? It seems like I can't draw a lot.
Jeez, Majime-kun...
Enough with the shaking, just pull one out already.
Pull? You mean like this?
Don't tease my nipples so much!
Something's coming!
You're coming just from your tits?
Such a lewd body you have here!
Don't say that!
You're being rough!
Feels good!
It seems that we can't get the results yet.
Maybe we should try to draw some more fortune here!
Not my nipples...
Majime-kun, you shouldn't!
No, you can't! My nipples...
You're rubbing it with the tip, it's gonna swell up!
You'll make my tits melt!
Misaki-san, your titty fortune lot is so warm!
No... My body is feeling numb!
Stop rubbing your dick on me!
If you keep on kneading and making them
slippery, you'll make me come again!
This is great! Your tit-pussy feels
just like a real pussy does!
Majime-kun, I'm begging you.
Please spare me already!
If you do it intensely like that...
If you keep on violating my tits
like a pussy using your dick...
Congratulations...
You drew the winning prize of the
Pleasuring Misaki-san lottery!
Thank you very much.
Majime-chan!
Let me draw from your fortune stick as well!
I won't stop shaking and drawing as I please.
So there won't have any bad pulls?!
Of course there won't be any of that!
Your pussy has devoured my whole dick!
Majime-chan, your dick is delicious!
Jeez! My hips are moving on their own!
My tits are bouncing around. This is embarrassing!
Give me the winning draw, Majime-chan!
Fill me up inside!
Okay then, I'm gonna shoot a lot into you!
Your hot thing is coming inside with every thrust!
So intense...
How is it, the taste of my fortune stick?
It feels good!
Amazingly good!
Your insides too. It's so slippery
and it feels erotically great!
It's going deep! It's reaching my womb!
This is so intense!
No—!
Majime-chan is seeing it...
He is seeing it already!
Is that breast milk?
It's coming out somehow.
It's coming out of my tits!
Squirting breast milk while your pussy
is dripping wet, you're so erotic!
No...
Your dick is getting even bigger inside me!
Cock, cock, cock, cock!
It feels so good!
M-My nipples!
Not my nipples! Don't rub my nipples...
while pounding my pussy so much!
I'm coming already... I'll die from ecstasy!
I'm coming! Here's the result of your
draw from my fortune stick cock!
You're thrusting in and out!
You're mixing me up inside!
Pour it inside my pussy!
I want to see your cock squirt
and pouring all of it inside!
Coming, coming, coming... I'm coming!
You got bigger inside me again...
Huh? Oh yeah, the clitoris appetizer
I ordered is yet to be served.
Oh, is that so?
Excuse me! Is the clitoris appetizer not ready yet?
Misaki-chan, I'm just kidding!
Jeez... She's kind of sinister,
or maybe just kind of eccentric...
[Masturbation Radar]
My radar picked up something!
This signal is the student council prez.
Alright, It's gonna be a clitoris appetizer from prez!
I'll help myself on it!
More... Do it more...
Do more lewd stuffs on my body...
Oh, prez... You're masturbating quite wildly!
I wonder who she fantasizes about though...
Could it possibly be me?
Please, tease my nipples more...
Kyouko-chan!
Did she say Kyouko?
Oh, it's another app.
I see... So that's it.
Did you call for me, President Nikozaki?
Eh, Kyouko-chan? Why are you here?
Never mind that. I'm happy to know
that you look and feel that way towards me.
The way you lick my nipples feel so good!
Your areolae have swollen this much as well.
President Nikozaki, aren't you ashamed of yourself
being exposed in such an indecent state?
I am ashamed of it, but more importantly...
I'm begging you, Kyouko-chan...
No... Don't tease me anymore!
I can't hold myself back already!
Jeez... You're such a handful
and indecent idol president!
Our pussies are scissoring
and rubbing against each other!
I won't get off with something like this!
I want something more stimulating!
Please, Kyouko-chan!
If you want it that much,
Why don't you thoroughly lubricate this cock of mine?
I want this...
What are you referring to?
I'm a little slow so I won't know
if you don't say it straight.
You're a bully, Kyouko-chan! Just cut it out!
I'm coming again!
Here... Me too, with our overlapping pussies...
Is this how a girl feels when being penetrated?
No... Do it already... Jeez!
If you won't plead for it properly,
I'm not putting it inside you!
Kyouko-chan... Don't tease me so much.
Let's both feel good together!
I already told you what to do, right?
I'm begging you, Kyouko-chan. Use your idol cock,
and pound my idol president
pussy until I get knocked up!
You're such a vulgar woman, prez!
You're a bad girl!
I'm glad! Something hard is really entering me!
It's reverberating in here as well.
It feels incredible inside me!
It feels great to have my pussy walls rubbed inside!
It feels great for me as well.
Do all girls get to feel themselves this good?
I might get addicted to this!
You're feeling it, Kyouko-chan? Your tits are bouncing all over!
You are so adorable!
This is also the first time I felt this good!
Your cock is ravaging deep inside my pussy!
My rugged pussy now turned
into something outrageous!
It's overflowing with warm
and lewd juice from inside me!
S-Something amazing is coming deep inside me!
It's hitting my g-spot! How about you?
Can you feel it in your g-spot, Kyouko-chan?
Does it feel good?
Is it this one? The part getting
poked in my walls deep inside?
Kyouko-chan... I love you! I really do!
I won't let you go anymore!
I don't care about everything else now!
I'm gonna come too...
It's grinding inside me! No way!
I never knew that this feels so good!
Coming... I'm coming!
Hey, let's come together... Together!
I'm coming... Let's come together!
I'm coming!
Kyouko-chan, I'm glad that we came together...
The orgasm lasts longer... Girls are amazing!
I never thought that you're such a girl...
Same to you, prez!
Wait, what's happening here?!
Sheesh, I ran out of time...
Where did Kyouko-chan go?
About Kyouko... Let's forget about her!
Does a raw cock feel good ? Which
of this and the toy feels better?
I-I don't know! But don't pull it out!
Slide it deeper inside me!
I'm gonna come even more,
so keep pushing your thing inside my pussy!
Prez!
C-Coming!
My pussy is getting stretched loose!
I'm begging you, more...
Keep on digging inside me a lot more!
After that, my ambition proceeded without any issues.
And then...
This is happiness! My dream finally came true!
Hey, why are you spacing out there!
The ceremony started already!
Yeah... That's right, Yui.
Oh... Jeez... Me too, me too!
Yes! I love you, Ayane-chan!
Hey, quit fooling around. Everyone is waiting!
Yeah, I understand!
Alright then, here's the long-awaited...
Semen Shower!
And just like this, my blazing
impregnation titty scheme
auspiciously ended in success!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization