Activate! Do everything you can to further my goals!
If I can only use this a few more times,
I'm gonna have fun with it!
Senpai!
Majime-senpai!
Well, if it isn't Matsuri-chan.
What're you up to?
I finished practice early,
so I'm doing some maintenance.
Senpai?!
Your boobs are as big as ever, Matsuri-chan!
Ah! Senpai, you can't!
Sorry, force of habit.
If anyone saw this...
Oh, right on time! I've been waiting for this!
Matsuri-chan
Maintenance
Senpai, this is so embarrassing!
What's embarrassing?
I'm being nice enough to help
you out with your maintenance.
But what kind of maint...
Isn't that obvious?
Your body's maintenance, Matsuri-chan!
I'm fine...
You say that, but how do you
explain all this grease coming out?
You can't rub my nipples against each other like that!
Do you see all this oil coming out of you
during your maintenance? That's not good.
No, don't touch me there!
M-More's gonna come out!
I-I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Gotta go deeper for this maintenance.
No... Don't!
If you stick it in now, I'm not
gonna be able to stop cumming...
S-Senpai and I are connected!
His thick dick is deep inside me!
His dick reaching every part of my pussy!
I'm... I'm gonna...
No! If you thrust it in like that, I'm...
I can't take it!
I think my pussy's about to reach the finish line!
Are you gonna cum, Matsuri-chan?
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Please shoot out your cum, senpai!
Sure, I'll shoot my white grease into your pussy!
Please make my pussy slimy with your white grease!
No... I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Passion of Impregnable Tits ☆ Perverted App Academy
Passion of Impregnable Tits.
Perverted App Academy The Animation.
Ichizakura Academy
Kimitsuka-kun!
Can I come watch you practice?
Oh, it's Tsuka-chan!
She's as popular as ever.
I can't believe that I'm basically the same
as him, and yet he's practically a celebrity!
Everything about it is wrong!
Good morning, senpai.
Tsuka-chan
The exposes ballerina
Tsuka-chan, the exposed ballerina?
What's up with this?
Even if he has the beauty of a woman, I'm not into guys!
Am I really about to have sex with him?
There's no way that's...
He's binding this chest?
The exposed ballerina?
Tsuka-chan, the exposed ballerina?
No way!
What the hell?!
S-Senpai? Why are you here?
That's not important right now!
What's going on here?!
There's a good explanation for this.
I didn't have a clue that you were a girl!
Why do you pretend to be a guy
when you're such a beautiful girl?
I'll teach you the pleasure of being a woman.
Senpai...
So, why are you cross-dressing?
It's a waste of your cuteness and sexiness.
I-I've been dressing like a boy since I was little, but at
some point, wearing girly clothes started turning me on.
Now whenever I wear girly clothing, I get really horny!
Breast milk
App
Ah, okay, how about...
Let's make you even more of a girl!
Looks like you became a mom
before you even had sex, Tsuka-chan!
If you pinch my nipples like that, I'm gonna...
Senpai, I'm not pregnant,
but milk just keeps squirting out!
No! If you suck like that,
you're going to make me want to give you more!
Okay, as thanks, I'm going to let
you drink some of my milk too!
It's making such a dirty sloshing noise...
It's so erotic.
Just keep going like that.
Try licking the tip a little.
Your boobs are too sexy, Tsuka-chan!
Senpai!
Your nipples feel so good when
they rub against my dick, Tsuka-chan!
If you keep rubbing against
my nipples like that, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna...
What do I do? I'm sucking a guy's dick
and it's turning me on like crazy!
Your boob-pussy is the best, Tsuka-chan!
I-I'm cumming!
You're cumming?
Take in your first ever load of cum!
It's so hot! It's flooding into me!
Don't swallow yet.
Show me it first.
Like this?
You're so wet!
You're such a patient girl. Well done.
Don't worry, I'll sate your sexual desires, Tsuka-chan!
N-No...
It's entering me!
Senpai's dick is entering me little by little!
How's it feel to be a woman now, Tsuka-chan?
Not good! Please take it out!
I can't have a guy's thing inside me!
It's moving!
It's rubbing my insides so much!
Tsuka-chan, why don't you tell me what's inside you?
Come on.
I-I can't say that!
Go ahead, tell me!
A-A guy's huge dick is...
It's inside my pussy!
Like my dick now?
If you're honest with me,
I'll make sure it hits the right places!
I like it!
I love your dick pounding in and out of me!
Please, shove your dick deeper
inside me, senpai! Mess me up!
My pussy feels so good!
My pussy feels so electrified!
Your dick's reaching my womb!
I want to be stuck with you
shoving it in me like this forever!
This is your first time, but you're already head
over heels for sex! You're exposed, you ballerina!
That's your fault, senpai!
If you keep hitting me there, I'm gonna...
Please make yourself feel even
better from my pussy, senpai!
I'm gonna cum inside!
Senpai!
Flood me with your cum!
Mold my pussy into the shape of your dick!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Creampies feel so good!
My pussy's so happy from being given your cum, senpai!
I'm cumming again! My boobs are cumming!
Oh man, I love that gap between how
Tsuka-chan usually is and how she really is.
Huh? Another one?
Be sure to watch the show I'm in tonight!
Oh, it's just a text from Kyoto.
She's been getting pretty big numbers recently.
Oh, it's actually the app this time?!
The sudden
Girl's bathroom door
Oh, "the sudden girl's bathroom door"?!
Please watch it!
Send me your thoughts on it.
800 characters or more!
The sudden
Girl's bathroom door
Sorry, I've got bigger fish to fry.
Is Ma-chan going to watch my show?
I'm Ma-chan's personal idol!
I'm cumming!
M-Ma-chan?!
I'm here to answer your fiery, hot call of love!
Whoa, there!
Oh, so this is the pussy of a popular idol?
Ma-chan, it's not clean!
Don't lick it!
I never thought I'd have the chance
to lick the pussy of a popular idol!
Stop! Having you lick my pussy feels too good!
Just cum whenever you want, Kyoto!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
How was that, Kyoko?
Did you get turned on by me licking your pussy?
Yeah, really turned on.
I'll pay you back now.
Getting a blowjob from a popular idol
like you feels so good! It's the best!
You mean it?
I'll try to make you feel even better.
I'll make it feel so much better!
K-Kyoko, give me a titfuck while you're sucking it.
O-Okay.
L-Like this?
Does it feel good?
Shit... It feels too good!
I'm gonna cum!
That's okay. Cum.
My mouth-pussy is just for you, Ma-chan!
So cum in your own, personal mouth-pussy!
Cum all you want!
Try singing even cuter than usual with my mic.
Y-You jerk...
Ma-chan's dick is coming inside me!
It's so tight!
It's all warmed up just for you, so put it in me!
Ow...
I'm finally one with you, Ma-chan.
Kyoko, does it still hurt?
I'm not sure yet...
But my mind's starting to go blank...
It doesn't hurt as much as it did before.
You don't have to put on a brave face.
I'm not...
It's twitching inside me!
M-Ma-chan, please... Please, kiss me!
Stick out your tongue, Kyoko.
Looks like your pussy's completely
used to having a dick in it now.
That's because your mic dick has been
rubbing against my pussy so much!
It feels so good!
Shove your dick in me deeper!
You're an incorrigibly dirty idol, Kyoto!
But you're getting turned on too, aren't you, Ma-chan?
Every time I move my pussy, I feel your dick pulsing!
I can't help it when the Kyoto is riding my dick so happily!
Do it... Do it harder!
Make my pussy a total mess with your dick!
Kyoko, I'm cumming!
It's coming out! Ma-chan's hot stuff is coming out!
There's so much coming out!
No... Don't start moving again!
Sorry, Kyoko!
I just came, but this feels too good! I can't stop!
I love you! I love you so much!
I love you so much, Ma-chan!
Cum inside me! Cum more inside me!
Shoot it out inside me!
Fill my pussy to the brim!
Ma-chan's hot stuff is coming out...
I'm pretty tired.
Sweet Cat
I guess I'll take a break here.
Tea and fortunes
Oh cool, tea and fortunes?
Welcome, Majime-chan.
I came here to enjoy your boobs again, Misaki-san!
R-Really?
By the way, what's served with the tea and fortunes?
Great Luck
The fortunes are inside these steamed buns.
If you get the right fortune, you get a free drink.
Okay, I'll take one...
Not so fast. The steamed buns are over here.
Oh, sorry, my mistake.
Okay, I'll eat one then.
Bad luck?
By the way, bad luck is wasabi flavored.
She forgot something pretty important!
Boobs
App
Rubbing Fortune
Boobs Rubbing Fortune App?!
This is the fortune I was looking for!
Sweet Cat
Preparing
Fortunes
What's this? My fortune's not falling out at all!
Majime-kun, stop playing around
and pull out the fortune already.
Pull? Like this?
D-Don't play with my nipples like that!
I can feel something coming!
Are you gonna cum just from
having your boobs played with?
What a dirty body you have!
Don't say that!
So rough!
Still nothing, huh?
Let's get another fortune box in the mix!
M-My nipple...
M-Majime, you can't!
No, stop!
My nipples are getting even more aroused by your dick!
You're going to melt my boobs!
Your fortune-telling boobs are so warm, Misaki-san!
My body's tingling!
Don't shove your dick into me like that!
The way you're rubbing your dick around
is going to make me cum with my boobs!
This is amazing!
Your boob-pussy feels like the real thing!
Majime-kun, please stop!
Your dick is rubbing against me so violently!
It's like it's trying to fuck a real pussy!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Congratulations.
You pulled the grand prize... Misaki-san's satisfaction!
Thank you.
Majime-chan? Let me try my luck at your fortune stick too.
I'm not letting you get away.
I don't even have a say in this?!
Of course you don't!
Your pussy ate up my entire dick!
Your dick is so tasty, Majime-chan!
My hips are moving on their own!
My boobs are just bouncing around... it's so embarrassing!
Shoot out your winning fortune inside me!
Shoot it out inside me!
Sure.
I'll fill you up with it!
I can't wait for you to pack
my insides full with your hot stuff!
So intense!
How's my fortune stick taste?
It feels good! It feels so, so good!
Your insides are so wet... they feel so good!
It's coming in so deep!
My womb... You're so rough!
No!
Majime-chan's moving inside me!
I'm already cumming!
Is that breast milk?
Something's coming out!
My boobs are cumming!
Your climaxing pussy and milk
squirting boobs are too erotic!
Majime-chan, your dick is getting bigger inside me again!
Dick! More dick! Give me your dick!
It's too amazing!
My nipples!
My pussy's going crazy while
you're playing with my nipples!
I'm... I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum so hard!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna load
your insides full with your fortune!
Do it! Do it! Fill me up with it!
Shoot it all out in my pussy!
Fill me up with that thick cum of yours!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
You got bigger inside me again...
Huh? Now that I think about it.
What happened to that clitoris soup I ordered?
Huh? You ordered that?
Excuse me!
Is the clitoris soup ready yet?
Misaki-san, don't take me so seriously!
Good grief. Is she really that mean or just an airhead?
Oh, crap, my masturbation radar's going off!
Masturbation Radar
From the looks of it, this is the student council president!
Okay, let's get that clitoris soup from the president!
Let's dig in!
More... Do dirtier things to my body...
Oh, she's in the midst of some hardcore masturbation!
Wonder who she's fapping to.
Maybe it's me?
Please, play with my nipples more, Kyoko-chan!
Did she just say Kyoko?
Oh, new notification.
What do we have?
Oh, I see. So that's how this'll play out?
Did you call for me, President Nikozaki?
Huh? Kyoko-chan?
What are you doing here?
That's not important.
I'm so happy that you think of me this way.
Kyoko-chan, you make my nipples feel so good!
Your nipples are getting so hard.
Aren't you embarrassed about so openly
showing me this dirty side of you?
I'm a little embarrassed,
but that's not important night now.
Please, Kyoko-chan, my pussy can't wait any longer.
You're quite the dirty idol of a president, aren't you?
Our two pussies are rubbing against each other so hard!
I can't resist!
I want something even more intense!
Please, Kyoko-chan!
If you want something so badly,
then how about you play with my dick for me?
I want it...
Want what? I'm not too bright,
so you'll have to spell it out for me.
You're such a meanie.
You know what I want!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum too!
So this is what it feels like to have one of these in you?
Put it in...
Nuh-uh. You have to beg me,
or else you're not getting it.
Kyoko-chan, don't be so mean.
Let's feel good together.
Then you know what to do, don't you?
Please, Kyoko-chan. Shove your idol dick into my
idol president's pussy so far that it impregnates me!
You're so vulgar.
What a bad girl.
Your hard thing's really inside me!
It's making a mess of my pussy too!
My pussy's going crazy!
It's rubbing inside my pussy! It feels so good!
I feel good too!
I could get really hooked on this sensation!
Kyoko-chan, it's so cute how your
boobs are moving around like that!
I've never felt anything as amazing as this before!
Kyoko-chan, your dick is rampaging around inside of me!
It's rubbing inside me so hard!
There's so much liquid pouring out!
Something amazing's coming!
It's hitting my G-spot!
What about you? Is it hitting your G-spot too,
Kyoko-chan? Does it feel good?
It is! It's hitting it!
Kyoko-chan!
I love you! I love you so much!
I'm never letting you go!
I don't care about anything else!
Me too! I like this... I love this so much!
I never knew that this felt so good!
I'm gonna cum!
Let's cum together! Together!
I'm cumming! We're cumming together!
– I'm cumming!
Kyoko-chan...
I'm so happy we could cum together.
The pleasure isn't stopping!
Being a girl's too good!
I never knew you were so assertive, Kyoko-chan.
You too.
No!
What's going on here?!
Shit. Out of time, huh?
What did you do with Kyoko-chan?!
Let's forget about her for now!
Does a raw dick feel good?
Does it feel better than a dildo?
I-I don't care! Just don't take it out!
Keep shoving it deep inside me!
I'm about to cum again,
so dig deep into my pussy with your raw dick!
President!
I-I'm cumming!
My pussy's gonna get burnt!
Please... Rub it around inside me more!
After that, thanks to the app,
I was able to realize my fantasies.
And then...
I'm so blessed.
My dream's finally come true!
Hey, what are you spacing out for?!
The ceremony's starting.
Yeah, you're right, Yui.
Hey, me too! Me too!
Yeah, I love you, Ayane-chan!
Come on, quit dawdling. Everyone's waiting!
Yeah, I know.
Okay then, here's the semen shower of promise!
And just like that, the harem I could only have
dreamed of had finally come together. Fuck yeah!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч