Stop it...
Stop!
No!
Please stop!
No...
No... No...
This is so embarrassing...
Let me go...
No, stop...
Please stop already!
Stop, I'm begging you!
Please, someone help me!
Ouch!
What the hell are you doing,
you dirty piece of shit!?
Dammit.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
Goodbye.
Tatsuya.
You were the one who did it?
You're amazing, Tacchan!
You're so reliable!
Don't say that.
Thank you.
I'm glad you saved me.
It's no big deal.
You're so cool!
What you just said was so cool,
you just made me fall for you...
Well...
Me too!
I'm surprised you knew she
was being groped, Tatsuya.
Young and cute girls, huh?
Yeah!
The cute chick with her embarrassing blush.
And that big, beautiful, charming rack.
So you were watching?
You jerk!
No, that's...
You pervert.
Don't make excuses.
Take this!
How's this, Tatsuya?
Yeah, I totally lost.
I'll ask again: How's this!?
Kanae...
Please forgive me.
Say it again.
You're taking this way too seriously.
Seems like it succeeded.
He's too full of himself.
And it was beautifully done.
Come on.
Just give in.
Honoo no Haramase Tenkousei
This is Shirahana Academy.
I, Tagami Tatsuya, transferred over to
this school that is filled with females.
I have a huge ambition.
That is to take over the world.
World Uni Domination
Project
This school will be my stepping
stone to achieve my goal.
This place just became a co-ed school,
so there aren't many guys.
And I'm the only guy in this class.
Above that, my classmates are all hotties.
Especially my friend Minase Sayaka
who I knew since I was small.
She's refreshing and cute.
I must thank God for putting
me in the same class as her!
She's the famous bitch Kanae.
She's even more violent than most guys.
Anyways, leaving her aside.
The first step towards my goal will be
to impregnate everyone in this class.
Let's take this slowly.
Tacchan! Lunch time!
Right.
I'm tagging along.
Okay.
You bought your lunch again?
My mom tells me to make food
myself but I can't be bothered.
Wow!
You made it yourself?
I guess you can say that.
What about you, Minase?
Yeah, I did.
Looks really good.
You're good.
Of course.
Just kidding.
You're actually not that good either.
But I am.
You two have always been like this.
Even your homework is identical.
Yup, yup.
We're born for each other after all.
I forgot to bring chopsticks!
Oh well... You can use...
I left mine too!
Sheesh,
so even the things you forget are the same.
Oh well.
You can use mine.
Thanks!
Where's mine?
Let's eat.
You don't get one.
You can use mine.
Are you sure?
Sure...
Co ahead.
All right.
Bye...
Thanks, Wakana!
All right, time to...
Huh?
I want to thank you.
I'll be waiting tor you after school in the gym.
-Wakana
What is it?
Nothing.
Come on, let's eat.
Let's eat!
My chopsticks broke!
This is great!
Tacchan!
Tatsuya.
Not again.
Because you never learn.
Come on, you two.
I can't stand you.
This is what Cod wants.
You can see the path in front of you.
There is an interesting world waiting ahead.
The lucky time is 4:44.
So we just need to go to the
vaulting horse at that time?
Yup.
With Onii-chan...
Anyways, let's go check it out.
Yeah.
Thanks, Yuko-chan.
Let's go.
Okay.
Gym Storage
Does it feel good, Tatsuya?
This is my thank you gift.
Your thing is really big.
Your breasts are really soft.
It feels great.
Your penis is throbbing like mad.
Just like it's about to erupt.
It feels great.
But it's boring if I'm the only one having fun.
Jeez! You're going to pull it off!
Stop... It's erected.
I can feel it.
You're so cute.
It feels weird...
T-Tatsuya-san...
Do you want me down there?
I'm going to cum.
Ruri, let's go.
It's time already?
The vaulting horse is deep inside the gym.
So it should be there.
Gym Storage
I'm scared.
Can you hear that?
No, wait...
I never thought we'd go this far.
Tatsuya, stop it.
Jerk! I told you to stop!
I couldn't hold back after seeing your body.
Onii-chan...
Does it hurt?
You can go a little faster.
I want you to feel good too.
No!
It feels good inside.
Tatsuya!
You sound really lewd.
Can you feel it?
But... But...
But your thing is really big!
No!
I feel so good inside!
It's churning up my insides...
Stop...
Stop... It feels too good...
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming...
I want to come inside you.
No! I'll get pregnant!
I'm cumming, Wakana!
Stop...
Your hot semen is pouring into me...
I'm going to cum again...
Inside...
My insides...
My insides are filled with your cum.
What are you two doing here!?
You're so heavy.
What the heck!
Wakana, don't get mad.
They're your friends, right?
But Tatsuya...
No use crying over spilt milk.
And they looked like they enjoyed it.
No, Tatsuya...
It's nothing embarrassing.
Even if you say that...
Wakana...
I-I want to do it too.
Tatsuya-kun, I want you to do me too.
Me too, I want it too.
Both of you!
Be nice.
Both of you...
Come on.
It's flooding down here.
Here, take a look.
It's so embarrassing...
No, that's...
Stop... already...
Looks like you're good to go.
So, does it feel good?
Yes! Your penis feels great!
Don't stop! No!
I feel so weird!
Alright, I'm coming inside.
Fill me up please.
Here I go!
So full... I feel so full.
Ruri, you urinated!
I'm sorry...
What should I do?
Don't be sad.
Sad?
Yeah,
even I couldn't help it because it felt so good.
Take that!
Rub rub.
Come help out.
No!
Don't suck it together! No!
Then what about this?
Ruri, look here.
Onii-chan...
Stop...
You're doing it too hard!
I feel so good!
I'm cumming!
I'll impregnate you all!
Onii-chan, will it be okay?
Yeah, you'll get the gist of it soon.
Wakana.
Okay.
It feels great...
You've got nice tits.
Yes...
Your thing is filling me up.
No! Not there!
No! I'm going to cum!
Onii-chan, you're doing it too hard...
I want your semen.
Let me impregnate you too!
No!
Something warm is flowing into me...
Hey, Tatsuya.
Are you plotting something?
Tatsuya wants to create an interesting world.
Manaka! Yuko!
What do you mean by interesting world?
He's going to leave you soon.
Now, as a reward...
Crocus.
Manaka, can't you let me rest a little?
You made me lose my new creation this morning.
I won't let you complain.
This morning?
Don't tell me...
Wakana, you are needed in
order to achieve my goal.
Goal?
Crocus!
Feels great!
Wakana.
Tatsuya...
Is this your goal?
It's my turn now.
Right, Tagami-sama?
Let me do this.
Yuko!
This feels great.
Stop!
Tagami-sama.
Do it here this time.
It can't be helped.
It's tight!
Onii-chan!
Haruka, make Manaka's butthole feel good.
It's really tight.
Tatsuya!
Tagami-sama!
I'm going to cum!
Let me end today with cumming inside you.
Please do!
No, not yet!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum soon.
I want to have your children...
Then do so, Haruka!
No!
Tagami-sama!
Let us... Let us be together forever.
Yeah, all right.
Bear my children, Ruri!
Okay!
It feels good...
Yuko, I'm cumming.
Okay, Tatsuya.
No, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too!
Let's create your world together.
Yeah, together!
Together.
Bear my children!
No!
So this is your goal?
I want to bear your children too...
Yeah.
Here I go, Wakana!
I'm cumming!
All of you, bear my children!
Now, let me tell you your duties.
Please cooperate together.
Well, you made us all feel good after all.
We will dominate the world!
Dominate the world!
There!s nothing we can't do!
It will soon happen if we repeat
this again and again!
People Left to Impregnate
Minase, this will take quite some time.
Minase-san.
Yes?
About the graduation celebration
you proposed a while ago...
We decided to turn it into a cultural festival.
Really?
Yeah.
We'll have everyone think about
what they should do for it.
I'll be looking forward to your drawings.
Okay, Sensei!
See you tomorrow.
Good-bye, Sensei!
I want to draw Tacchan!
Episode 1: [Take In My Seeds!!!]