Why am I so unlucky?
Did you say something?
Forgive me!
I can't breathe...
Tacchan, stop moving or else
I wont be able to draw.
Stay put, Tatsuya.
For crying out loud, Sayaka is drawing
a graduation piece of us...
So stop being so damn rude.
That's because I pity Sayaka for being your model.
Though you say it's a graduation piece,
I think it's better to give it up
rather than turn that in.
Shut up!
Stop... Stop!
Don't be so mean, Tacchan.
Kanae's picture has a deep meaning to it.
Even you're so mean.
Deep meaning, huh?
I remember we went to the zoo once to sketch,
but one of us drew monsters instead.
Tatsuya...
And what about you!?
If you dared to make me look bad
in yours, I'll make you pay.
Show me it right now!
T-This is me?
She looks so cute.
Does this mean you have a
crush on me or something?
– No... I'm pretty good at drawing monsters too.
– Monsters?
Come on, stop being so shy!
I'm not being shy...
Yes, you are.
I'm not.
I said I'm not.
As I thought, Tacchan is in love with...
3 Great Friends
I've transferred into this school for nearly a month.
Although I'm not making any progress
with my childhood friend Sayaka.
my ambition is going strong and my number
of cute followers has increased.
And today, in order to achieve my goal,
I will impregnate my classmates!
Honoo no Haramase Tenkousei
It's about time we settle this, Kaede-san.
That's what I had in mind too.
Passed down from the Cods
is the Narahashin Style.
Descent of the Dragon!
Nice dodge.
But will you be able to make it next time, Tatsuya?
Don't look down on me.
Will you be able to dodge my move?
What?
Tatami Flip!
What!? You're too naive!
Did you really think that would work against me?
Not really.
An opening!
I lost.
You know what you have to
do now, right Kaede-san?
Yes, use your tongue.
How does my Naginata taste?
It's dirty...
Dirty, huh?
Then you'll have to clean it with your mouth.
Right?
That's right.
You've got to clean the underside too.
Manaka...
It's okay, as long as you follow him,
you will be able to live in a utopia.
Right, good job.
If you make me feel good, I'll
definitely repay you back.
And you'll be feeling great next.
Manaka...
I want to see the cute side of you next.
Welcome, Master!
"Master" sure is a great word.
It feels like my time is about to come.
Honomi, you look really cute.
Thank you, Master.
But this newbie doesn't even know how to greet.
N-Nice to meet you.
Hey, seems like she hasn't been educated properly.
Crocus!
You know what to do to rude little girls, right?
Kaede-san, I hear some really
perverted sounding noise.
So Kaede-san, want me to turn it up?
Kaede-san?
Welcome, Master.
Look at you, Kaede-san.
This is...
Turn it up, Crocus.
You'll get punished if you act rude.
Kaede-san...
Come.
Master?
Honomi, you promised to serve me right?
Yes.
I wonder how much joy your
breasts would bring me.
It's embarrassing...
They're beautiful.
Do they feel bad?
Not at all.
I'm touched.
See, my thing has woken up.
I'm so happy, Tagami-san.
Master, if you would like so,
please let us serve you too.
Then how about you three all serve me at once?
Okay!
Okay
Crocus, punish her a little longer.
Wow, it's so big!
It's so soft here...
Master, does it feel good?
Yes, it feels great.
I-I can't hold back.
It's so hot that it makes my breasts feel good.
Master...
Amazing...
That's cheap of you!
Your nipples feel so good...
You three are amazing.
Do it harder and let my milk
spray all over your breasts!
I really want Master's milk! I really do!
Honomi, that's...
Thank you very much.
It's still early.
Come here, Honomi.
Okay.
Wow, they're so soft.
These pair of titties are great.
Master...
Master, thank you very much, thank you!
Were really jealous of you, Honomi!
Master favors you so much.
But if you suck them...
It's going to cum... It's going to cum!
No...
Wait, that's such a waste.
It's great, Honomi.
You're right.
No... No...
I'm not pregnant!
Not pregnant, huh?
Master?
If you're not pregnant,
let me impregnate you right now.
Hey, Sae, Erina.
Okay, Master, the preparations are complete.
Master, please take away my virginity.
As you wish, Honomi.
You're inside me...
Kaede-san, you want it too, right?
Not really.
Master, please share Honomi's milk with us.
All right.
Stop sucking or my breasts won't stop...
Honomi... Honomi...
Sae, make Erina feel good too.
Erina-chan, here.
Sae-san, that's beautiful.
Lubricate it and we'll both feel good.
Master! I feel great! I feel great!
Erina!
I'm in heaven! I'm in heaven!
Me too!
Hurry up and admit it.
You're jealous right, Kaede-san?
Yeah, right... I'm just...
Master, I'm about to... So let's cum together...
All right, Honomi.
Be prepared to receive my semen in your womb!
We're going to cum too!
Honomi...
Bear my children!
Next...
It's about time.
Kaede-san, I guess you're
ready since you're so wet.
Stop! You're shameless...
Stop!
I really want to hear you begging for it...
As if I would...
Come on, let me hear it.
Please...
I can't hear you.
Master, please...
Very well.
You're so cute, Kaede.
Hey, Crocus. Do it.
Wait, this is...
Your pussy is begging for it.
Shut up.
This would be easier for me to go in, wouldn't it?
Does it hurt?
Whatever.
Not cute at all.
You'd be happier if you say "It feels so good."
I'd rather die than say that!
You've got such a foul mouth.
Seems like you need more punishment.
Sae?
I'll use this to make her act more honest.
No! That's!
Kaede...
This is getting tight.
Erina, Honomi, come over here and enjoy too.
Come on.
Okay, Master, here I go.
Erina... Honomi...
Come on, let's all have fun.
I'd feel great if you all feel great.
Hey Crocus, they want more.
This is such a great view.
Kaede, you too.
No!
Even though you say "no", you really want it.
No! Stop!
Do you really want me to stop, Kaede?
If so, I'll let out a huge load in you.
I'm about to cum.
No! You can't! Not inside!
Alright.
You want me to let it out inside, don't you?
Not inside!
Bear my children, Kaede!
Bear my children, all of you!
Come on, everyone.
It's time to conclude this.
I want all of you to help me.
We will dominate the world!
We will dominate the world! Nothing will stop us!
Nothing will stop us as long as we work hard!
People Left to Impregnate:
So Prez, you're done with yours?
Hey! Don't call me Prez.
We're all done.
Speaking of which, whit about you?
Are you done yet?
Me?
Of course, it was a piece of cake.
You're amazing!
Tagami-kun, you're great at everything.
No, that's not...
Sayaka, are you done with your graduation piece?
Show me! Show me!
You drew Tatsuya-san, right?
Yeah, but...
I sure want Tatsuya-san to be my model.
Well, too bad for you since Sayaka asked him first.
I'm not done yet...
Somehow the drawing doesn't feel right.
I'll show you guys as soon as I finish.
Excuse me.
Sayaka?
I bet she's a perfectionist.
Tatsuya, I'm so jealous.
You're flattering me.
Tatsuya...
Troubled over love?
Well...
Let me predict your fortune.
R-Really?
Come to the club room after school.
Thanks, Yuko!
I see it.
Your destined one is Tatsuya.
Do whatever your heart tells you to...
Today at evening in the classroom...
But...
But?
The three-way friendship will end as you progress.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Tatsuya, don't be so rough...
You've done such a great job.
I must repay you well.
Tatsuya!
You're so naughty.
Let's see how naughty you can get.
Tatsuya... You're deep inside me.
Very well.
The timing's just right, Yuko.
Tatsuya!
Harder! Harder!
I'm about to...
Let's begin, Yuko.
Tatsuya! Tatsuya! Tatsuya!
I want-to talk to you, so I'll be waiting in the classroom! Come or else!
- Yumeno Kanae
Tatsuya...
Thanks!
– I can't breathe!
– Tatsuya...
Tacchan, Kanae-chan!
The three-way friendship will end as you progress.
All right.
What are you doing?
P-Practicing.
You like Sayaka, right?
Uh...
I see, I guess I was right.
But I...
I love you!
Umm...
Did I leave it in the classroom?
K-Kanae...
I don't care if I'm just a substitute,
I just want to make love with you.
Just for this once...
You're not Minase's substitute.
Minase is Minase and you are yourself.
Tatsuya...
I want to make love to you as Yumeno Kaede.
Tatsuya... Tatsuya...
I came a little...
I've always known you liked Sayaka.
But when I see that picture, I just
can't hold back my feelings.
So now you want this?
S-Stupid! It's embarrassing.
Just hurry up and do it.
All right, here I go.
Kanae, relax.
Are you okay?
Yeah I am...
Your penis is so warm.
Don't push yourself.
Kanae, you feel so good.
Tatsuya, you're getting stiffer.
It feels great.
Tatsuya, your penis is amazing.
K-Kanae...
More... More...
I'm finally one with you.
I've always wanted you.
So I've always been jealous of Sayaka!
She's always with you...
Am I really...
Didn't I tell you already? You are yourself.
Tatsuya...
Kanae, I want to look at your face.
Okay.
Tatsuya, I want to be with you forever.
Tatsuya! Your thing has gotten even stiffer!
My pussy is about to melt!
Kanae, I'm going to cum inside you.
All right...
As long as you're the one coming
inside me, I'm fine with it.
Tatsuya! I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming, Kanae.
Be impregnated by my semen!
Bear my children!
Kanae, I want you to help me.
I'll do anything for you.
Now Kanae is on our side.
She could've joined our side already
if he used my inventions.
Love triangles are really annoying.
Four left to go.
Episode 2 [Reach the Womb!! My Seeds of Ambition!!!]