My name is Kazama Shunsuke.
Even though I'm a student,
I'm also the school's deputy nurse.
The Battle Versus Academy
is a combat-focused school, where students who
want to focus on the martial arts gather.
Students join clubs that match their
fighting styles to improve upon their technique.
The school's intensive health care
also separates it from the rest.
Abiding by the motto "Your body is a weapon,
your stamina the representation of your true strength".
The students are required to have daily body examinations.
As a practitioner of the impregnate, tit fighting style,
my ambition is to turn the entire school into my harem.
This is Shidou Maki, a second year sword user.
You can't do that, Master!
Stop! Please, stop!
It's fine.
If we don't squeeze out the milk,
your boobs will burst, won't they?
If you keep twisting and pinching my nipples like that, I'll...
They taste different than usual.
Since I drink your milk every day, I can tell.
Oh, I know!
Did you masturbate yesterday?
I didn't...
You need to tell me if you did or if you didn't.
My apologies, Master.
Last night, I...
M-Masturbated...
No!
Master, please don't suck on my breasts so hard!
Do you know what I just wrote on your tits?
I'll do it again, so pay close attention to each
and every letter that my tongue writes.
No, you can't, Master!
Please don't twirl it around like that!
I won't stop until you answer me.
Um... Um... Nipple...
I understand. You wrote "dirty nipple".
It's so embarrassing!
But your nipples are dirty, aren't they?
My nipples are so big and hard.
They're really dirty.
I'm so sorry.
No! No more!
Please, Master! Stop teasing my nipples.
I'll cum!
I'm going to cum with my nipples!
This is amazing! Your pussy is so tight!
Thank you very much, Master!
I'll keep doing my best!
Your pussy is so hot and wet.
Are you feeling good?
Yes!
I'm sorry, my body got really turned on when
you were playing with my nipples!
Where are you feeling it?
If you don't tell me...
My pussy!
I'm feeling it in my dirty pussy and it feels so good.
It's so wet! I'm so sorry!
What's making you so wet?
Your dick!
Your big, fat dick is stirring me up deep inside!
It feels really good!
Master, your cum is gushing out inside me!
This time, I'm gonna punish your ass.
No way!
Your ass took me in so easily.
Maybe you actually like it in your ass?
No! If you keep fucking my ass so hard... I'll go crazy!
Master, my boobs feel so good!
Maki, don't hold back! Showing your master
your slutty side is also a service.
Yes, Master!
It feels so good!
Master, please do me harder!
You can be rougher.
Please use me however you like!
Maki, I'm gonna cum!
I'm going to cum too! I'm going to cum!
You're so mean, Shuunosuke-kun.
Become delicious – Moe Moe Kyun!
Become delicious.
Hideshima Rinko.
Also known as Rinko-neesan.
She's wears the most alluring black tights
and has legs to match!
Oh, man. I love black tights!
Don't suck on my breasts so hard!
You can't do this in front of him!
Rinko, your breast milk is coming out.
Are you getting aroused from having
your measurements taken?
I'm not!
The way you're using your tongue is just too good!
Senpai, please try to stay still.
I'm trying to take your measurements.
No! This is too embarrassing!
Don't pull it so tightly!
You're rubbing my clitoris!
What are you doing?! No!
What's this?
Rinko-senpai, your pussy got so wet.
N-No!
Please, don't look!
No!
Don't lick it like that! It's embarrassing!
Your pussy's too hot.
Let's take your temperature.
This has never happened to me before.
Why is it moving so much inside me?!
No!
No, stop!
Any more, and I'll...
Your dick is going wild inside my stomach!
Let me give your womb a direct massage!
N-No!
I'm cumming!
Your cum is spilling into my pussy!
Kenpo Club's Agata Nono.
It feels so good!
My pussy is getting so hot from the
way you play with my boobs!
Feel good all you want.
I'm going to get all of your breast milk today.
N-No!
Don't play with my nipples like that!
The way you play with my boobs makes me so horny!
You can cum whenever you want.
You too, Shun-nii. Feel good!
If I... let out a lot of breast milk,
give me even more of your dick milk!
If you keep squeezing my dick like that, I'm gonna...
Your dick is twitching...
It's getting even bigger!
Nono-chan, I'm gonna cum soon!
That's fine. I'm gonna cum too!
You're going to cum in my pussy and
I'm going to cum out of my boobs!
My boobs are exploding!
Your cum is dripping out of me.
Master!
Time to take a little break.
Honoo no Haramase Motto! Shintai Sokutei 2.
Okay, let's take everyone's measurements at once!
Just today, okay? I'll let you do whatever you want.
I don't care if it's in my ass or my pussy.
Shoot lots of your cum inside me!
Shuunosuke-senpai, please!
My body feels so hot, it's weird!
Me too! Pay attention to me too!
Christine von Lerchenfelt.
Senpai, you can see everything in this
position. It's too embarrassing!
But your pussy is drenched with that love juice.
Please don't say anymore!
That's my most sensitive spot!
N-No! If you do that while playing with my boobs...
I...
No more! No more!
If you let this in, I'll be able to measure your pussy.
If you put that huge meat stick inside me, I'll...
Chris, does it really feel that good?
You're so tight!
Don't move!
It's rubbing in me so deep!
Senpai, your dick is going wild deep inside my pussy!
Chris, your pussy is swallowing my dick up!
Th-That's because I want to make you
feel good, even if it's only a little bit!
Chris!
My mind is going white...
I'm gonna go crazy!
Hold on, Chris! I'm gonna cum inside!
Let it out, senpai!
Please cum inside me!
I'll measure the amount of semen you release!
Senpai, I'm going to take your booty pressure now.
It's getting so big inside my ass.
It feels so weird!
We're not even close to finishing.
I'm going to keep pumping air in.
No, you can't!
Please, stop!
Wow! It's even tighter than before!
No! Don't be so rough!
I'm going to break!
Senpai, I'm going to keep increasing the air in your ass!
No! My pussy and my ass are...
I'm losing my mind!
No, no more! Stop!
Bear with it a little longer, senpai. I'm about to cum!
Let's cum together!
Your hot thing is getting bigger!
No, no, no!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Do me harder!
This is amazing!
You're so deep inside me!
Good! It's so good!
That's...
It feels so good!
– Master!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Bad girl. You need to stay still.
It's still so big, even after you came so much.
It's so stiff and hard.
I'll do something really good, senpai.
More! I'll make you feel even better!
Senpai!
Senpai, your pussy feels so good!
Senpai, you're getting really horny, aren't you?
I never thought you were such a slut.
It's your fault for doing these things under
the pretense of... measurements!
Senpai, I'm gonna be a little rougher!
No, that feels really good.
Rinko-senpai, look at this.
You can see my dick inside of your pussy!
You really can. It's in so deep!
My most embarrassing place is all exposed!
No!
It's fine! Cum inside me!
Together! Let's cum together!
Shuunosuke-kun's baby milk is... flowing into me!
I'm cumming!
Wonderful!
Conquering women's hearts and bodies is just...
It makes me feel so alive!
Sh-Shuunosuke-kun, was that not enough?
Not even close!
From now on,
I'll take all of these beautiful girls,
thoroughly suck their tits dry.
And love them with everything I've got!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: bis | punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent