Honoo no Haramase Tenkousei
No...
Tagami-sama, I'm about to...
Not inside!
I didn't want you to...
But it felt amazing.
Now it's your turn, Reika.
Why me?
Your subordinates did it, but you're not going to?
Of course I will do it.
I'll throw away my standards just for today.
That's no good.
This is how it's supposed to be done, got it?
Listen, you lost to me at marksmanship.
Therefore, you have to serve my big magnum.
You don't seem like you're enjoying it.
Suzuka, Ayami, help me eat her out.
If she feels good, I think she'd
be able to do better than this.
Okay.
Reika-sama...
Please excuse us, Reika-sama.
Ayami, you too.
A-As you wish, Reika-sama.
Both of you are doing a great job.
Reika, don't forget this.
O-Of course, Tatsuya-san.
You've gotten better, Reika.
I'm cumming, Reika!
The real thing begins now.
Your big magnum is churning up my insides!
As expected from someone raised in a rich family,
your pussy is well raised too.
I'm going to die of pleasure!
Ayami, Suzuka.
Very well.
Okay.
Suzuka, your tongue is beautiful.
My breasts feel so good!
Reika-sama's breasts are terrific.
Reika-sama's clitoris is also fabulous.
So Reika, you're a pervert that gets turned
on by your own subordinates.
Your penis is the best though.
All right, I'm about to cum inside you.
Please! No! Not inside!
Oh no... I'm going to...
Bear my children!
Now there's only one left.
Yeah...
But the last one seems rather troublesome.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine by myself.
Even if the girl is Minase Sayaka.
Come on, hurry!
Wait up!
Art Room
Minase.
T-Tacchan...
What's up?
Nothing, I heard from Konoka-sensei that you're
the only one who hasn't finished their drawing.
I'm sorry.
I had to sort out some stuff with the
art club, so I didn't have time.
But it seems like you haven't even started.
Y-Yeah.
I-I think I've been in a slump recently.
But I'll be fine!
I'll definitely finish it before the cultural festival.
But that's only two days away.
Well, I'm sure you'll be okay.
Is it because you don't want to draw me?
N-No! That's not true...
Tacchan...
Minase, I love you.
I'm sorry.
I love you too...
But Kanae-chan loves you a lot too.
Wakana-san and Honomi-san do as well.
I'm a monopolist type of person.
That's why I don't want to share
you with anyone else.
But then I'd feel bad for everyone else...
You're... You're the only one...
Honestly, I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry.
Tacchan, please be happy with Kanae-chan.
Manaka's Locus
You're going to break me, Tatsuya!
I feel all weird now...
No, my breasts are going to come off!
No! I'm going to cum from your fingers!
No! I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Manaka, can you make me some anesthetics?
Tatsuya...
I will get her no matter what.
You can't do that!
Isn't she your good friend?
But I can't make it without her...
But resorting to drugging...
Dominating the world without
Minase is so meaningless!
You're over exaggerating.
Very well.
Wait! How can you even call it a "domination"
if you're using drugs?
Then tell me what I should do!
Leave it to me.
I'll talk to her.
Kanae...
Don't worry, I'll help too.
All right. Thank you.
G-Good morning, Yuko-chan.
You're early.
Here to prepare?
Everything will end if you run away today.
Come to the classroom alter
you've thought about it.
It'll be your final chance.
Yuko-chan?
Public announcement.
The cultural festival begins tomorrow.
Students who are in charge of the materials
please bring the things to the storage room.
And the other students, please leave before sunset.
Tacchan...
Everything will end if you run away today.
Sayaka...
Sayaka... Do you hate Tatsuya?
No I don't.
So you like him.
I like him too.
Everyone likes him too.
Tacchan...
Girls, enjoy some free time first.
– Okay!
– Tatsuya has an ambition.
Ambition?
Yes, he wants to dominate the world.
Dominate the world?
I think it's really stupid.
Even grade schoolers nowadays think it's outdated.
But because I like him,
despite the fact that it's a stupid
wish, I want to help him.
Like me, everyone in there wants to help him.
But Tatsuya said there's one thing that's
more important than world domination.
I couldn't have known better.
That's you, Sayaka.
Tacchan...
But I don't want to lose to you.
Just like the others, I love Tatsuya
and I don't want to lose.
Kanae-chan...
What are your true feelings?
Throw away the past and think about the present.
Do you like him or do you hate him?
I... I...
I...
Don't worry.
He won't mind.
Tacchan, I'm here.
Minase...
I love you.
I want to make babies with you.
Please... Please be with me.
I... I...
I love you too! I really love you!
I want to be with you forever and ever.
But are you sure?
I'm fussy, I doze off a lot...
I'm normal and I'm not good at anything...
I want to be with you.
Tacchan!
Tacchan, my heart is thumping...
Me too.
You're beautiful, Sayaka.
Are you okay? Did it hurt?
When you touched me, it felt like being shocked.
Kanae-chan...
Sayaka...
No... Kanae-chan...
Tacchan! Tacchan!
No... Tacchan... I... I...
Tacchan, Kanae-chan, I feel really good.
You're going to feel even better.
If this continues, I'm going to feel all weird.
Don't worry. Everyone's here with you.
You too?
No...
No... Not there...
You can't do this...
Tacchan! Tacchan!
I'm really happy that you're feeling good.
It's about time.
Sayaka, I'm coming in.
Sayaka, does it hurt?
I'm okay, because it's Tacchan.
Sayaka...
Tacchan...
Are you okay?
Yes.
I finally became one with the person I love.
It hurts but I'm really happy.
You feel great inside.
Tacchan...
Sayaka...
Tacchan, let Kanae-chan join in too.
Okay.
Kanae, come on.
Sayaka...
Kanae-chan, thank you.
No...
T-That's my...
No, Tatsuya!
Tacchan, make Kanae-chan feel good too okay?
All right. I'll make you feel good too.
Tacchan! Tacchan!
Sayaka, does his penis feel good?
Yes it does! It's grinding me inside!
Me too...
His fingers are amazing...
Not in the butt!
Tacchan, not in there!
I can't handle anymore!
Tatsuya!
No!
Tacchan, you can't do that!
Sayaka, I'm going to cum inside.
Please give me your semen.
Kanae! Sayaka!
I'm cumming!
My butt is about to cum!
Tacchan, I'm going to cum too with Kanae-chan...
Sayaka, prepare to become pregnant!
Tatsuya! Tatsuya!
Tacchan! Tacchan!
Sayaka, bear my children!
You two are amazing.
I...
I'll draw you right now!
Tatsuya,
my turn next.
Wakana?
Wait.
I'm next in line.
U-Umm...
I haven't done it since yesterday.
Well, me too! Me too.
Me too.
Me too!
Me too...
All right, let's have a free for all!
Tatsuya... Tatsuya... You're amazing!
Kanae, very good.
Everyone is amazing.
Thank you.
You're done.
Minase, your drawing is amazing.
Nope,
call me Sayaka.
Right, Sayaka.
Tatsuya.
Sayaka.
All right!
Everyone!
We will dominate the world! Nothing will stop us!
Class 3F: Complete!
Our goal is to dominate the world!
Shirakawa Academy's cultural
festival will begin now.
And then, Shirakawa Academy's class 3-F won.
The King of the World: Tagami Tatsuya.
Volume 2: School Domination.
Th King of the World: Tagami Tatsuya
Sayaka, let's go.
Coming!
World domination has only just begun, Tacchan.
Th King of the World: Tagami Tatsuya
Episode 3 [Impregnate x 21 = Girls of 3F Complete]
It's beginning, mom!
That's right.
Now please be quiet.
Okay.
Tatsuya! Tatsuya! Tatsuya!