I Really Met
A Girl
Asuka, and the Secret Forbidden, part-time Work
Okay, let's start with an introduction
I'm Suzuki Asuka.
I want to be an actress someday.
How about your vital statistics?
It's a secret.
Don't tease me, say it already please~
That'd be 75,
53,
and 76.
How about your weight?
That's crossing the line!
I won't tell that no matter what.
Did you bring the stuff I asked you to?
It's in this bag.
Okay! Let's go then shall we?
'Kay.
I really have to do it by mouth?
Yes, please
Jeez, I'm just doing a blowjob, okay?
We're not doing anything more.
It's too big, my mouth is starting to feel tired.
It's thick, and it has a really strong smell.
Well? Did that feel good?
As thanks for your blowjob,
now I'll be the one to make you feel good, Asuka
You don’t really have to do that.
Feeling horny?
That's because you're fondling my breasts.
Does it feel good?
Not too much, I guess.
It feels good...
Asuka-chan, your pussy is wrapping me really
well. It's gripping my fingers tightly
Found your G-spot
Not there...
I'm going to go crazy.
It feels so good when you stroke that spot!
I can't hold it anymore!
No...
It's embarrassing, don't stare at me too much.
It's already this wet, you're ready to do it, right?
We agreed not to do that...
We've already come this far.
You don't want to end this without fucking, right?
But, use a condom okay?
It really feels tight
You're pushing it in too quickly...
The walls here are thin, someone might hear us on the other side, you know?
Even if you say that...
I can't help but moan...if you do it this hard.
It's my first time feeling this great.
Asuka-chan, you're just too perfect for sex, I'm about to cum
What? We're not done yet?
I'm already at my limit.
Hey, you're not wearing a condom!
Please, stop that!
No!
We can't do this raw...!
Are you going to cum inside?
Not inside, please!
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
It's okay, just show me your expression as you cum!
Pull it out as you cum, okay?
Pull it out okay?
I told you to pull it out...