Yes!
It feels... really good!
More!
No!
Don't!
What are you... Ah!
It's hot!
Hot stuff is...
going in my pussy!
My name is Motomura Touko.
I'm 32 years old.
I'm a housewife that's been married for six years.
I don't have any children yet.
My husband is a common salary man.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
The case of Motomura Touko
Immoral Confession of a Married Woman
The most precious part of the woman.
Is also a hole that men want to use.
And amongst the men that come to use it,
there is one that has an object that
can give the woman happiness.
And that object is called a dick.
If you hold tightly and keep it yours,
women can find happiness...
It's what Grandma says all the time when she was drunk.
after my mom eloped and left hope.
Although she had passed away a year
And since three years ago when my father passed away,
The house that no one lived in anymore
had started to moulder.
This time, I had come back on my father's death anniversary.
My father was a teacher in town,
but his scholarly bent mind didn't suit teaching very well,
so he returned to work at the village's
office, and lived a plain life.
My mother who was raised in the city and a bit gaudy,
was unsatisfied with the countryside life.
That was when I had just started going to elementary school.
That day, both my father and my grandmother were out.
And it was a night with a strangely bright moon.
It was when I woke up in the middle of the
night and wanted to find my mother,
I went her room and noticed the unusual atmosphere.
There was a man other than my father
tangled in bed with my mother.
I couldn't tell who the other man was.
My mother's face on that night,
looked different from her usual appearance.
Shortly after I saw such things,
my mother vanished with that man.
My mother's partner she eloped with was the
father of a classmate called "Kouta-kun".
Before that,
had often played around with Kouta-kun,
but we stopped talking to each other gradually,
and Kouta-kun's family moved out of the village.
It was also with Kouta-kun that I played doctor with,
and showed each other our naked bodies.
I remember being so excited that it felt
like my blood rushed backwards.
It's seems like my strong desires were awakened at this time.
The blood of this family... atavistically
inherited from my grandmother,
And my mother's strong desires directly inherited.
A certain time before menstruation,
I experience a change in my body.
During this time,
when I see men on the streets or so,
my body would start tingling uncontrollably.
Not to mention my husband,
not even masturbating could satisfy me.
Only sex with a random partner...
at unusual places...
Yes!
It feels... really good!
More!
Kept me in balance somehow.
At that time, I suddenly remembered my Grandma's words.
You know that people live even deeper
in the mountain from here,
near the prefecture borders, right?
They say that's an Arcadia that will melt away women.
A paradise that women will be unable to escape from,
once they have a taste of it.
that was a village of Ochimusha,
Although since once upon a time
and they had no women.
So it might just be a tale to attract women.
The reason that I decided that after I visited my father's grave,
I'd visit this secret hot spring,
was that the change in my body was nearing.
Good morning! You don't get tired of it at all, do you?
How much longer until the person
you're waiting for will come back?
What's important is that I wait patiently, right?
So who is this person you're waiting for anyways? A lover?
It's not something erotic like that.
By the way,
how are the two college girls that came
from the city yesterday doing?
They're still fast asleep thanks to that
herbal medicine liquor you made.
They must have both been in paradise last night.
It's all thanks to that herbal medicine liquor.
The OL's in the city are spreading that if you come
to this hot spring you can relieve all your stress,
and we are getting customers even on weekdays.
I guess you're right.
This prosperity is thanks to you!
Not really.
I'm Motomura who booked a reservation a few days ago.
That woman...
Thanks for coming all the way to the countryside.
Our specialty here is our open-air bath.
Not to mention relief of stress,
It's been said that it also helps with blood circulation,
easy delivery and all kinds of diseases.
Wow.
In addition there is this herbal medicine liquor.
If you drink this and go in the hot spring,
you'll be so energetic it's like you're another person!
Ah, this feels good.
But is this really the secret hot spring
that Grandma talked about?
It seems like it's just a rustic hot-spring hotel to me.
I wonder if Grandma was just joking around.
She might have been too old to think properly.
I wonder if it's because of the herbal medicine liquor...
I might be a little drunk.
My body is starting to melt away...
It feels really good...
If this goes on I wouldn't be able to sleep.
It's good!
Yes!
Cumming, cumming!
Cumming!
She's sound asleep.
The liquor you drank had seeds of mandala
in addition to the herbal medicine.
Mandala is a dangerous plant that will make
you see what you usually can't see.
I made it specially just for you.
At that time, I had a dream.
The experience that I had when I was young
On a night when the moon was unusually bright,
seeing my mother sleeping with a man other than my father.
What?
Who are you?
No!
Stop!
Be quiet!
No!
Don't!
What are you... Ah!
Amazing...
This is amazing!
This feeling... what it is?
It's completely different from all the dicks I've had before.
...Yes! ...Yes!
Yes...
No, don't pull it out!
Don't be so rough...
Amazing! Amazing!
It's the first time I've had a dick this great!
My pussy feels like it's gonna break...
It's like a hot metal rod stirring inside...
What is this feeling...
It's like you're going to suck me all inside.
Is this the dick that Grandma was talking about?
I can't take it anymore!
I'm gonna pass away!
I can't...
It's hot! Hot stuff is...
going in my pussy!
It's about time you open your eyes.
Finally I'm gratified.
I've been waiting eagerly to take you.
What do you mean?
I waited here so I could mess you up one day.
Who are you...
Your pussy has grown up quite a bit.
Could you be...
Kouta-kun?
I'm the son of the man who was tricked
by and eloped with your mother.
But... why are you doing such things?
Thanks to that, my mother and I
were forced to leave the village.
You'll never understand how hard it was after that.
My mom died from overworking,
and I lived a life of shame.
So I began hating your family who could
live in the village like nothing happened.
When I came back to this village two years ago,
you were the only one still alive.
But I couldn't relieve the grudge in my heart no matter what.
I heard the rumors about you,
and I believed that you should know about
the stories of the secret hot spring,
and that you'd come here one day.
So I prayed and waited.
So that rumor of you being a prostitute was true.
You came here not knowing a thing.
You get abnormally slutty in bed as well.
That's...
It's because you are the owner of a
dick I've never experience before.
Come to think of it my dad did say that,
"That woman's place is like thick gruel,
if you stick your dick in it fits perfectly,
and you can't pull out.
It's not something you can run away from."
I think I finally understand what my dad meant.
Me too, I finally know why my mother eloped.
Is it okay? Not going back and all.
It's fine.
That person is not the one I was looking for after all.
I finally found the dick that Grandma was talking about!
Ouch!