www.SubDESU-H.net
Yes.
Yes!
That feels great...
More...
No.
No!
What?
Your hot thing is...!
It's penetrating my pussy!
My name is Motomura Touko, 32 years old.
It's my 6th year as a housewife.
I still don't have kids.
My husband is a normal company employee.
W
The True Case
of a Wife's Admitted Adultery
Motomoura Touko's Case
The most important part of a woman,
can be used by men to deal with their urges.
But some men who get too attached to it,
ultimately become endeared to treat them preciously.
That is the essence of what is called a cock.
Claim it well,
and happiness will...
Grandma used to frequently say those words.
She passed away the following year after my mother disappeared.
My father also passed away three years prior, so no one is currently living in the house.
It has started to become worn down.
Today, is the day of my father's death, I'm visiting his grave before returning to Tokyo.
He worked before as an instructor,
but he was more into study and research than teaching.
Instead, he came back here,
and found a job at the Town Hall.
He had been living there since.
My mother, who was born and raised in the city,
became more frustrated with the country life, and was not accustom to it.
It was during my elementary school years,
when my father and grandparents were gone...
The night had a strange and bright moonlight.
When I woke up at that time,
I tried to go to my mother's room to snuggle in her bed.
That's when I realized that something not normal was happening.
There was another man that was not my father,
and he was making love to my mother.
I did not know who the man was.
The expression that my mother had,
was not what she normally had.
A short while later, after witnessing that scene...
... My mother disappeared with that man.
The man that my mother went with,
was in fact the father of Kouta-kun, a classmate of mine.
I used to play a lot with him,
but we eventually lost contact because,
he moved away from his ancestral home.
We used to play doctor, and we would show each other's naked bodies.
I remember being so aroused at that time because,  I almost felt my blood rushing backwards.
That's probably the time when I started to become aware of my "cursed" side.
My grandmother had inherited an atavistic gene,
and it seemed to have been passed down to my mother.
Within a certain length of time during my menstrual period,
something strange happens to my body.
At that moment...
In cities and other public places,
my body goes into a rut whenever I see men.
I am unable to calm it down by simple masturbation, and not even with my husband.
Instead, I have sex with any man who I come across.
There, that feels really good. More, more...
My physical state went into complete disarray because of this.
Then, I remembered the words my grandmother said.
Within the inner part of this prefecture,
is a hidden hot spring.
A paradise that causes women to be enchanted in some way.
Take a single dip into this sanctuary, and any woman will be unable to erase the ecstasy that they will experience there.
A long time ago, it was a place for defeated soldiers,
but no women were there during that time.
So the legend may have been concocted to attract female visitors.
After my visit to my father's grave,
I plan to search for that hidden hot spring.
As the time for my strange "bodily change" draws near again.
Good morning,
you look quite devoted there.
If you keep praying, then all sorts of entities might come to you.
I think things like this needs a good amount of time put into it.
And just who are you patiently waiting here for?
A lover perhaps?
It's nothing that romantic.
Oh yeah, how are the two college students, that came here yesterday, doing?
They're still fast asleep, thanks to your yakuzen sake.
Yakuzen = Food medicine
It seems they visited the hot spring last night.
Again, all thanks to your yakuze sake.
They said that their stress disappeared as soon as they took a dip.
Word has even spread among other females, such as the standard employees in the city.
Now we have customers regularly, even during weekdays.
Yeah, that's true.
You have my full gratitude for all of this.
It was nothing.
I'm Motomura, the one who requested for a reservation the other day.
That woman...
Welcome to this inn.
Our outdoor bath is the pride of this place.
Aside from stress relief, it is also able to cure oversensitivity to cold,
provide an easier delivery for the pregnant, and rejuvenate the worn out body.
Oh my.
And this is our yakuzen sake.
If you drink this before you enter the bath,
It will amplify the bath effects, and it will make you feel refreshed.
This feels great.
But is this the hidden bath grandma was talking about?
It seems like any other country bath though.
Maybe she was just joking.
At that time, she's probably already started to lose her mind.
Is this the effect of that sake?
I think I may have fallen a bit drunk.
My body is starting to feel hot,
and it’s a great sensation.
I won't be able to sleep like this.
This feels good.
Yes...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming~!
She's sleeping soundly.
Aside from standard herbal medicines,
this particular sake is also laced with the essence of jimsonweed seeds.
It's a rather dangerous plant that causes hallucinations,
and I prepared it especially for you.
I then saw a dream that night.
A dream of the scene I saw by the strangely bright moonlight.
The scene of my mother making love with another man.
What?
Who are you?
No!
No.
Stop!
Be quiet.
No.
No!
What?
Wow...
This is amazing.
This sensation...
I wonder what it is.
It's a sensation that is completely different from the other cocks I've tasted before.
Yes.
Yes...
No, don't pull it out.
Don't be rough.
Amazing...
It's my first time tasting this amazing cock.
My pussy is going to break.
It feels like being inserted with a hot and stiff iron rod.
What's this sensation?
It feels like it's going to suck me in.
Is this what she refer to as the cock?
Oh no...
I think I'm going to pass out.
No...
This hot thing...
This hot thing is...
It's pouring inside my pussy~!
Are you going to wake up yet?
Seems like you already look quite satisfied there.
I've been waiting patiently for you to come to this place.
Huh? What do you mean?
I waited here in order to completely violate you.
Just who are you?
Your pussy sure looks pretty mature now.
Could you be... Kouta-kun?
That's right.
I'm the son of the man that was deceived by your mother, and then ran away with her.
But why are you doing this?
Because of that incident, my own mother was forced to leave this village.
You don't know how hard it became for us afterwards.
She eventually became sick and died, due to constant work exhaustion.
I then had to live my life as though I was made to drink filthy mud.
I gradually came to hate you and your family, who were still living peacefully here.
I came back here two years ago,
but I found out that you were the only family member alive.
However, that did not erase my hatred.
I heard about the "curse" that your family had.
And I thought that you would most likely come here searching for that hidden hot spring.
It may have been a gamble, but I still decided to wait.
It seems that the rumors about your promiscuity were true after all.
Ever since you came here,
the way your body loses itself isn't normal.
That's...
That's, because you have a cock that I have never tasted before.
Huh?
Oh yeah, my old man used to say that her pussy was so wet and tight that,
his cock just kind of snapped perfectly into place.
He couldn't pull out even if he wanted to.
He said that you can't even get away from it.
I may have finally understood what he actually meant.
Me too, I think I now understand why my mother ran away.
You sure about not going back there?
It's okay.
That man wasn't really the guy that I was looking for.
Besides, I've already found the "cock" that my grandma always told me about.
Ouch.
www.SubDESU-H.net