It finally stopped.
Don't...stroke me...
How was Rina-sensei, was she more gentle?
Oh my, what a dirty boy.
First you piss, now you cum?
Anyways, has Rina-sensei done this to you?
Answer me!
How far have you gone with her?
Tell me, or else...
She...used her mouth!
She didn't go further?
Yes...
She didn't let you touch down there?
Hey, lick this.
You haven't seen it before, right?
Look closely, c'mon...!
Yes...
Open your eyes and lick it.
That's right...harder...
Yes...yes...great...higher.
Now stick your tongue in.
Now, do what you wanted to do with that bitch.
It's...my first time too...
Why...why him?
P..please...forgive me...I'll break...!
That teacher...!
There is much to prey on!
What's wrong?
Can't anyone answer?
What is the value of C?
Alright.
I'll give you guys some time to figure this one out.
What's wrong?
It's not that hard.
Were you listening closely?
Yes...I was...
You guys look ready.
Tell me the answer.
Uh...
Stand up when you're called!
Uh...I don't know.
I see, and you?
Hell no.
That's too bad.
You two stand in the hallway.
Err...Yes...
Mizuki-kun, let's try to solve this.
The numbers are different, but you can use the same formula.
Here, let me show you.
Ok?
For this portion...
Do you understand?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mizuki-kun, look at your text book.
Alright?
This equation looks hard, but with the given variables...
See?
Keep sucking, don't stop.
It hurts...
Yuichiro-san, it hurts...
But...amazing!
Yes...Yuichiro-san...l'm hot...feels great...don't stop...!
Where did she...go?
Stop...
Always acting like a goodie boy!
KO already?
Let us have more fun!
Stop it...
Come on, fight back...we're not stopping you!
That must have hurt, looks like Mizuki-chin took it hard.
Fool, fight back man.
Don't do something...that's not you.
Who are you?
Just a janitor.
And, what do you need from me?
What were you just trying to do?
It's none of my business...
...but people like them make me want to punch them.
Exactly, don't do something that's not you.
Normally, a teacher would stop such misconduct.
But your "teacher" is looking quietly.
I just thought you should stay out of it.
That bitch...
She is not as easy as you think...trust me.
Where are you getting at?
Just don't rush into things.
Take it step by step.
Well, daring is part of being young...
Oh, looks like his savior is finally here.
That's...
She's the teacher of science.
Todou Honoka
Karate, Aikido...a mixed martial artist.
She is...
I almost forgot.
Here are the keys for your room, Social Studies 2nd floor.
That gramps...
Does he know about Nao...?
Stop making up excuses.
Give me all you got.
What are you talking about, we can't do...
What's wrong?
You're telling me you can't hit a girl?
You fucking scum.
You're a teacher, you can't say that.
Are you guys doing the right things as a student?
If you're saying you can beat up a helpless boy, but not a teacher...
Think of me as not a teacher from now on.
How about it now?
That's it bitch, you asked for it!
Don't regret if we rape you!
Fucking whore!
Get her!
Run!!
Everyone, stop talking and get to work.
Alright.
One, Two, Three, Four...
Nagasawa Asami, a math teacher and the coach of the swim team...
Look at those guys hiding their hard-on from her.
She's strict, but yet provoking at the same time...
Don't rush into things, take things step by step...
I'll take the gramp's advice.
Let's take the next step.
Thank you!
Bye, Sensei!
Bye, thank you Sensei!
Don't forget to come early tomorrow.
OK...!
I want to join the swim team.
We're already done for the day.
Come back tomorrow when the club presidents are here.
I want you to look at me.
My techniques...
Alright.
I'll have a look.
Use that locker room to change, you did bring your...!?
Sensei, come swim.
No, not here...!
It hurts...
Stop it...please...!
No!
No, not there!
What's wrong?
Does masturbation feel better?
How's this...?
You saw...?
Yeah, from beginning to the end.
That's why...I'm like this.
It's warm...
Please be gentle...
No, please be gentle!
Suck it!
What's going on?
Drink it, every single drop!
I...can't!
Don't talk back!
Hurry up and drink it!
C'mon, use your tongue!
It's getting bigger...too big...
Don't bite, it hurts! Be gentle...
Give it to me, hurry!
Not that easy...
Beg for it more.
Tell me what you want in this used pussy of yours.
I can't say it...
Don't stop...don't stop!!
Tell me...tell me what you want!
Please...give me...
Please...give me your hard meat...inside my used pussy...hurry, hurry!
Please be...gentle...
Yes...
It's big...it's warm...it's good...
Great...great...cuming...cuming!!
No, I'm going crazy!
More...more...!
I'm going to...cum...!