Give me more!
Give me...
I have returned!
Master Mizuno!
More!
Please give me more!
Master Mizuno!
Oh, right, I'm here already.
Ryo!
Welcome back!
Hey, chill!
What's with you?
That hurts!
Miss Hotaruko.
You shouldn't get so excited.
It's bad for your health.
Ryo, you belong to me now!
Ruka, hurry and get Ryo's bags.
Right away.
I don't need any special treatment.
I'm carrying out
Miss Hotaruko's wishes.
Ryo!
I'll never let you leave this island!
'Cause this is your homeland!
I've been on this island ever since...
Is that scent from flowers?
That's weird...
I know those flowers from somewhere.
What the...
Miss Ryo.
You're already awake?
Your meal is ready.
What was that just now?
How come I can't meet
Master Mizuno yet?
He'll only meet with Miss Hotaruko
and the Chief Priest.
Chief Priest?
Oh, old man Ashihara.
He's come to the island
with Junko Usaya to serve here.
We haven't even been allowed
to meet Master Mizuno.
But you're Miss Hotaruko's relative,
Miss Ryo.
I'm sure you'll meet the Master soon.
No, Miss Kasumi!
We can't do this here!
Oh? Then where do you suggest?
If Bungo finds out...
He's just technically my fiancee.
The one I'm really interested is... Y... O... U.
Not there!
Please!
You're sure getting hot.
Don't tease me!
Miss Kasumi!
I love you!
I love you too.
Ryo!
What's going on?
What're you doing, Misa?
Oh! I'm so sorry!
You've been trained well, Kasumi.
I wish you'd leave
the two of us alone.
This is a good time
to remind you, Hotaruko...
As you know, my Ashihara family has
been around just as long as yours.
Let's go, Misa.
Excuse me!
Hotaruko...
What did you mean by "training?"
Want a lick?
Don't! That's gross!
You're mad at me, Ryo.
What's wrong? You're so pale!
I must've stayed in the sun too long.
Thanks for dinner.
You worried?
Miss Ryo was acting strangely today.
What's wrong?
All right, that's enough talking!
Hurry and clear the table!
- Right away!
Honestly!
Do you take your positions seriously?
What's the matter, Ryo?
You seemed bummed at dinner.
Something bothering you?
Come to think of it,
we both have the last name, "Inasa."
Yeah. I'm Bungo Inasa.
Just call me Bungo.
This island has always
been pretty isolated.
We're related,
somewhere along the line.
Is it about Hotaruko?
She really scares me sometimes.
Why? She's your cute cousin.
Besides, she's got a crush on you.
What?
Bungo, give me a break!
You seem kinda interested yourself.
Anyway, what's the deal with Kasumi?
You know...
I can't stand the old traditions
of this island.
Bungo...
Like those flowers over there...
They say the blood of a female sacrifice
would make the red flowers bloom.
Red flowers...
Make sure you come back, Ryo!
I'll be waiting for you!
To Miss Ryo Kizuki
Make sure you come back, Ryo!
I'll be waiting for you!
Love from your cousin, Hotaruko.
Mom!
I'm sorry, Ryo.
Something's wrong with me.
Forget about her, all right?
Why?
Anyway, it's just a stupid legend.
Looks like they're gonna bloom soon.
Just a little longer.
They'll bloom very soon, big sister.
You guys must be happy, too.
Your Eminence!
You've been
awfully intense lately, Junko.
Misa and Ruka are getting so much
attention from Kasumi and Ryo!
Feels good, doesn't it?
You dislike being older?
It's not that!
Please, don't do anything cruel!
What a filthy woman you are.
Let me down! Please!
You sure love being a slut!
Please, don't move!
That hurts!
My butt!
My butthole hurts!
I can't take it! Forgive me!
I don't get it!
Something's wrong with me!
I'm all hot! My body's on fire!
Make it stop!
I can't take it!
Your Eminence, I'm going to cum!
Your Eminence...
about Miss Itsuki...
She gave birth to twins, right?
I know about it.
Should I talk about it?
What is it you're after?
I want to be Master Mizuno's...
Look at this shrine!
Sure is unusual.
Yes, I suppose
it is a little different.
So, what can I do for you?
I wonder when Hotaruko
will let me meet Master Mizuno?
Master Mizuno isn't healthy,
so he doesn't like meeting people.
Oh, is that right?
Hey, can I help with anything?
Hotaruko would bite my head off
if I put you to work, Ryo.
Father.
Master Mizuno wishes to see you.
It's about time for the preparations.
Now, if you'll excuse me, Ryo.
Wait.
Why did my mom leave this place?
Anyone born in this village
eventually returns, sooner or later.
It's that type of place.
I hoped to fiind out even a little
about mom by coming here.
But I haven't fiigured out anything.
Hotaruko's been nice to me.
But sometimes I don't know
what she's thinking.
Miss Ryo, let me
scrub your back for you.
You don't need to do that.
Ruka.
Please, let me wash you.
Never mind.
I'm getting out anyway.
I've got to dry you off.
Leave me alone, would ya!
If Miss Hotaruko finds out, though...
Sorry, I'm just a bit upset.
But...
Ruka?
Come stay with me in my room tonight.
Okay.
What's up with you tonight, Kasumi?
You're sure going at it hard.
None of your business.
I bet you went at it
with Hotaruko again.
So what if she's the Kizuki
family's daughter!
Cat fiight, huh.
I think I should stay out of it.
They're so pitiful, too.
C'mon, Bungo, what do you say?
I can't take this any longer.
Please?
That's the only time she's cute.
Go for it.
Bungo!
Does that feel good?
You're lousy.
Hey, I'm just warming up!
You're pretty wet for someone
who's just warming up.
Jerk.
You sure like to fuck.
How come you never had Mizuno's baby?
Your big sister was the one
who got pregnant.
Bungo!
We're only engaged for show.
But just for now,
think about me, okay?
Bungo!
That's good!
That's so good, Bungo!
More!
Take a good look!
Your snatch is loving this meal!
Don't say that!
I'm ready!
I'm gonna cum!
That's so good!
Miss Ryo...
Ruka.
Don't worry.
It's only the sound of the wind.
We've never been allowed
to oppose Kizuki family members.
Forget it, Ruka.
Who cares about those old traditions.
No.
I was brought to this island
to serve Master Mizuno.
I must obey under any circumstances.
Any circumstances?
You're part of the Kizuki family,
Miss Ryo.
Ruka sees me the way
she sees Hotaruko.
Ryo...
Hurry and come, or else...
I won't last much longer.
Are these...
Mannequins?
Ruka!
That's good!
It's so good!
What's going on?
What is that funky smell?
It smells like cheese!
Yeah, right there!
Does that feel good, Misa?
It's so good, Miss Kasumi!
It feels so good!
Incredible!
I'll let my father take over now.
No... no!
No!
I only want you, Miss Kasumi!
Please!
I don't wanna feel that thing!
Miss Kasumi!
Miss Kasumi, I don't wanna feel it!
You have to feel it
for Master Mizuno.
Master Mizuno!
Make her cum, Father.
No, please!
Why do I feel like this?
I can't take it!
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum!
I'm ready to cum!
Now, Master Mizuno.
Mizuno?
Hotaruko!
Get started, would you?
Lucky you, Misa.
You'll be helping Master Mizuno, too.
Miss Kasumi?
No!
I can't get enough!
More, more!
Mom always brought home strangers.
Ryo, Mother has this deep itch burning inside
of her. I need someone to scratch it for me.
I can't stop it!
I hate this!
No!
Please, Ryo!
Stay away from the island!
What's wrong, Ryo?
It was a dream?
Look at all the flowers
in bloom tonight!
My big brother
will be happy about this!
Yeah, there's no way
that could have happened!
Hey, will you sleep with me
next?
It's not fair that Ruka
gets all your attention.
Don't be so silly.
Tonight I'm...
Hotaruko, your face!
You've got...
What?
Oh, geez!
Get it off for me, Ryo.
Long ago, when there was blood
from a female sacrifiice, the red flowers...
They said, the red flowers bloomed.
Are you awake, Miss Ryo?
How did I get here?
Last night...
You held me in your arms all night.
Oh yeah, I guess I did.
Hey, where's Misa at?
She's...
She's been sent home.
I can smell those flowers.
Were the blossoming flowers
last night just a dream?
Oh gods that shake free the craggy seats
of the heavens. Set Hiruko afloat to the
netherworld, in the wooden catalpa boat.
And let her drift to the land
of Mizuho Ashihara.
Till she arrives at the foot of the crag.
And let her drift to the land
of Mizuho Ashihara.
What am I doing here?
Sent to the land of wisdom,
and arrives in the country.
What, pray to a god
I don't believe in anymore?
I came to the island to fiind out
more about mom, and yet...
Tendons extracted from humans
during orgasms are the best.
I'm forgetting it.
Tendons extracted from humans
during orgasms are the best.
You'll be okay.
'Cause I'll be there to hold you.
I'm forgetting about everything.
Sleep with me, okay?