Ryo picked me!
That's very nice...
You must be very happy...
...that everything is going
as you planned.
Yeah... my brother isn't
lasting very long anymore.
You'll help too, right Kasumi?
Hotaruko, hopefully everything
will go the way you want...
Ryo, you're going to
sleep with Hotaruko next...
Ryo, I love you.
I want it...
Please, I can't take anymore...
Master Mizunu...
Kasumi...
I can't...
I can't take it anymore...
I have cum.
Run, run! Run!
Mother!
Hey, Ryo.
If you're done with dinner,
let's go to the garden.
Come on, let's go.
I'll take these away.
Hmph. She doesn't know her place.
Obnoxious girl...
Ruka...
Miss Ryo...
Do you love Ryo that much?
Miss Kasumi...
You don't need to be afraid of me...
Bungo is dead and, in the end,
we just can't win...
Master Bungo is...
Hey, Ruka...
Don't you... hate always having
to lose like this?
This is...
Oh no! We must hurry
and prepare the next sacrifice!
Kasumi...
Ruka!
The sword that Bungo used that time...
The one made of holy metal...
It is said to have even cut the body
of a god.
Bungo...
It's so hot...
Please come, Ruka...
I'm going crazy...
Ruka isn't enough for
Ryo anymore...
Unless you call Hotaruko,
I won't forgive you...
Please do something...
My body... My body is so hot!
I need it so badly...
Someone... Please help me...
Help me, Hotaruko.
You finally called for Hotaruko.
But hold on just a bit more.
I can't take anymore...
My body's on fire...
And it's too much...
Ryo, Hotaruko was waiting
for this to happen...
Hey, who do you like better,
Ruka or Hotaruko?
That's...
Well?
Come on, say it Ryo.
H-Hotaruko. I like you, Hotaruko.
Ryo, you're finally being sincere.
Good. Very good.
If we destroy Hotaruko's body,
then Ryo may return back to normal.
You understand, right Ruka...
Come...
That tickles, Ryo.
Naughty Ryo!
I want more!
Sheesh!
Don't worry, Hotaruko
will take good care of you.
Ryo, your breasts
look like your weak spot.
Stop it...
No way.
You won't get away that easily.
Ryo, you feel even more
down here, don't you?
Stop... I-I'm going crazy...
Really?
You really want to stop?
S-Stop... I... I...
Your hips are moving like you
want some more, Ryo.
Please forgive me... Hotaruko...
This time together...
Cumming!
It's not fair to cum by yourself,
Ryo.
Let's cum together this time for sure!
N-No... I just had an orgasm...
No excuses.
S-Stop!
It's not...
The blood won't come off...
Master Koshi...
Oh! Kasumi, you've returned!
Now, take that holy sword and
get revenge on the Kizuki family!
H-Hotaruko, stop moving...
Ryo, tell me it feels good...
You said that to Ruka, didn't you?
Come on...
Ruka...
Come on... Doesn't Hotaruko
feel even better? Hmmm?
I want you to tell me that
it's better than with Ruka...
I'm going to... I can't stop...
Isn't it better than with Ruka?
Isn't it?
It feels so good...
Hotaruko, it feels so good...
Hey... let's cum together...
If you move like that...
Hotaruko will...
Ryo!
Together... Together!
I can't... I-I can't...
Help me... Hotaruko...
I love you...
Ryo...
Hotaruko...
This is...
...what happened...
N-No!
It's so good!
I can't stand it!
Give me more! More!
Harder... Harder!
Mother...
I-I can't hold on any longer!
Itsuki gave birth to twins.
One was a boy, the other, a girl...
The girl was named Hotaruko...
And the boy...
It's amazing...
Master Mizunu!
Where...
Are you awake, Ryo?
Master Koshi...
I found you passed out
in the flower garden.
Why am I in Kasumi's room?
They were such good kids...
When I was gone,
they were supposed to take over...
But they've changed so much
since you came here, Ryo...
Please tell me, Mister Koshi!
Where did my mother go?
If ltsuki hadn't had
those disgusting brats...
you would have never been born!
N-No!
Ryo...
Master Koshi...
You're...
Ryo... your mother is finished...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
Be careful of Hotaruko...
Ryo, you must never go to the island!
My mother...
Who was my mother?
Ruka...
What's the meaning of this?
Please,
don't lay a hand on Miss Ryo...
You still have so much feeling
for someone who betrayed you?
Well...
let's have you do the usual.
Please forgive me... That's...
If you can satisfy me...
Ryo may freely leave the island.
I'm sorry, Miss Ryo.
As always you're very soft.
Oh, I'm cumming!
So cute...
No matter how many times
you've done it, it's like the first...
Look at all this...
No!
S-Stop... Please don't...
You're feeling it already.
Kasumi taught you very well.
N-No, that isn't it...
You have a weakness for
your ass as well it seems...
No, not there!
I can't... No...
What's the matter? If you
want it, do the work yourself.
Miss Ryo...
It's all over for me...
My mother... Who is she?
What's the matter?
Put your back into it!
Please, Master Koshi...
Please move...
Not very patient, are you?
Not yet.
Getting so wet...
How pathetic you are.
How's that?
That should help you to move.
Here, I'll make it easy for you.
It's amazing... It's hitting...
It's hitting me so deep...
More... More!
Not there... There! There!
That's... that's the spot!
I'm about to cum!
I can't... take it anymore!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
So full... All that
warmth so deep inside me...
Master Koshi, that's...
I'll show the entire Kizuki family!
Mizunu, Hotaruko... Ryo!
Hotaruko!
Hotaruko?
Stop causing trouble and
come over here this instant.
Yes, mother!
That means you too.
Come over here.
Hey, Ryo is going
to be born soon.
I see... That's very nice, Hotaruko.
I bet you're happy too.
Ryo is going to be all Hotaruko's.
And I won't give her to anyone!
Yes, I know that.
Mother... Hotaruko...
What are you saying?
Who am I...
No! Don't!
Ow! It hurts...
It's inside of me...
Don't move... It hurts...
So hot...
My body feels like it's burning up...
What do I do...
I think I'm going to go crazy...
l-lt's so good...
More... Move more! I can't stand it!
More, more!
Right there. Right there!
It's hitting... so deep!
So... So good...
Deep... Fuck me deeper...
Hotaruko... Hotaruko... Where is she?
Miss Ryo...
Please get a hold of yourself.
I did it. I managed
to get Master Mizunu...
Quickly, let's get out of here!
Hot... My body is so hot... Hotaruko!
Don't, Miss Ryo!
Please snap out of it!
Let me go!
Without her, I'll... Let go of me!
Don't get in my way...
Miss Ryo...
It's so hot! Someone do something!
I guess we screwed up... brother...
Brother, can you tell?
Hotaruko...
Come here...
Ryo finally came to us...
I'm finally here, Hotaruko...