The flowers that bloomed last night...
Was it...
Was it a dream?
This smell...
Mom!
I'm on fire!
The smell of those red flowers!
Please stop it!
Ryo! My sweet Ryo!
Forgive me!
I can't stop myself!
The sweet smell of the red flowers
is calling to me!
Mom, get a grip!
Ryo, promise me...
You mustn't go near the island!
You mustn't meet Hotaruko!
So it was the scent of the flowers
that did that to her.
Oh gods that shake free
the craggy seats of the heavens.
Set Hiruko afloat in the wooden
catalpa boat to the netherworld.
And let her drift to the land
of Mizuho Ashihara.
Till she arrives at
the foot of the crag.
1... 2... 3... 4... 5...
6... 7... 8... 9... 10...
Thus is the reason.
Wavering, wavering...
It will be so.
The dead will be brought to life.
Aren't you going to pray, Bungo?
What, to a god I don't
believe in anymore?
Don't believe in anymore?
Ruka!
Miss Ryo!
What the heck is that?
Hey, Ruka...
How dare you upset Ryo!
Please forgive me!
Ruka!
That was cruel, Hotaruko!
It wasn't Ruka's fault!
What if someone finds us in here?
How dare she spoil the end of our
important purification ceremony?
It's all because Ruka's
become so close to Ryo.
Are you jealous of her?
You're going to need to be punished!
I won't do it again, I promise!
Please forgive me!
Don't tease me... I can't take it!
You poor thing.
You've gone and upset Master Mizuno.
But Your Eminence,
you're the one who...
I'm what?
I'm gonna go insane!
Your Eminence, it feels so good!
It's good!
Yes!
It's too much!
You'll split me in two!
I can't stand it...
Amazing... so amazing!
You're banging my cervix!
Oh man!
You're scraping my insides!
It's so good!
What were you saying?
That you wouldn't stand me up, so...
Do you think we're gonna act on
your every whim, Junko?
Miss Kasumi!
Forgive me! Forgive me!
You have to be punished for
sullying Hiruko's sacred grounds.
But Ruka did that!
I... I...
I'm gonna explode!
Yeah, it's so good!
That feels unreal!
That's it! I can't hold back!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Hotaruko sure was acting weird today.
Still...
I had to say something to her
for bawling Ruka out.
Tendons extracted from humans
during orgasms are the best.
The other two will soon be
put to Master Mizuno's aid as well.
Big brother's going to
be okay for a while now.
What's the matter?
Keep on working.
That's what you get for chasing
Ryo around outside in the sun.
Maybe you're starting to rot all over.
Ryo...
It's almost time.
You're going to be part of me.
I don't want you to like Ruka
more than me.
What a yucky dream.
Maybe I'm just tired.
This is the same place
as the other night.
Please forgive me!
I can't take it!
You two have been so
neglectful recently.
We've learned our lesson!
Please just release us!
You seemed to be having
a good time with my father, Junko.
The Chief Priest started it, not me!
C'mon, you've gotta keep nice
and close so it doesn't fall out.
Don't move!
Oh dear, it looks like Ruka
has a low tolerance for pain.
Look at the mess on this dong, after
all the trouble I went through to insert it.
No, not there!
Your butthole looks hungry for this.
No, please!
Miss Ryo!
Ruka...
You seem close with Ryo, Ruka.
A servant scheming to work with Ryo
and the Kizuki family lineage?
That calls for harsh punishment.
Stop!
It's got nothing to do with me!
Noisy wench.
Your body is going to aid
the god Hiruko too, Junko.
No, please! The Chief Priest is...
What's going on?
Mom...
Now you can be recognized
as a descendent of Hiruko.
What is it, Ryo?
Are you afraid of that boat?
You'll be okay.
'Cause I'll be there to hold you.
Hotaruko...
What kind of dream was that?
The boat in my dream.
Hey, I wonder why Hotaruko was...
What?
The mannequins.
Hotaruko!
Out of here!
Ryo is off-limits!
Get going!
Hotaruko! You...
Naughty, naughty, Ryo.
You shouldn't be here.
What are you doing here?
Was that all a dream last night?
Aren't you going to eat, Miss Ryo?
Ruka, isn't this hard for you?
My family is greatly indebted
to the Kizuki family.
I have no choice but to stay here.
Ruka.
When I leave this island,
come with me.
I hear you're not feeling good, Ryo.
She seems so innocent
when she's sleeping.
Hotaruko...
Ryo.
Miss Ryo!
Geez, what are you staring at!
Give us some space!
Knock it off, she's shaking!
Are you okay, Ruka?
Stop it!
Hotaruko...
Why pay attention to her?
Pay more attention to me, Ryo!
Do you have to be so mean to Ruka?
Why, why, why?
Pay attention to me!
Nobody but me!
Don't be so selfish!
I hate when you're like that!
Ruka...
We should have killed Ruka first.
Hotaruko!
You...
So that's what happened to
Misa and Junko!
Why are you looking at me like that?
No!
So none of this
was a dream after all.
Then that means...
Ruka, you'll be...
I'm gonna ask Hotaruko
for some answers!
That's not going to be easy.
Bungo!
Use me?
It is Master Mizuno's wish.
In place of Junko...
Just like with Itsuki.
It was the same that time.
You want Kasumi to...
Yup, we need a replacement.
Junko's tendons were too weak.
I couldn't use them.
No one can escape from this island.
Kasumi's got too much attitude.
She deserves this.
And Ruka's got a crush on Ryo,
but she's not gonna get her.
I love you, Ryo.
Let's become one...
the sooner, the better.
Did you sleep, Ruka?
No.
Oh.
I wasn't satisfied with that ancient god.
The god was named Hiruko.
It had fake arms and legs on it.
But it wasn't able to move.
Until someone came up with the idea
of using a certain method...
to make the joints move,
like a mannequin.
Using human sinews.
Miss Ryo, that hurts.
Ruka, you're not
going to die, are you?
Ruka...
Yes?
I'm hot. My body's so hot.
Please, let me do it just a little.
Let me touch you a little.
Ruka!
That was the Ashihara family.
Each generation of the Ashihara family
served the god Hiruko.
The Chief Priest?
However, human sinews
quickly start to rot.
Especially in the sunlight.
So they used live female sacrifices.
And the number of mannequins
that were no longer useful increased.
The souls that couldn't be saved
possessed the discarded mannequins.
And they continued to wear out
in the darkness.
So why are you telling this to me?
Ryo, take Ruka and leave this island!
We shouldn't do this!
If Miss Hotaruko finds out...
Please don't, Miss Ryo! I'm afraid!
I'm scared!
That hurts!
That hurts so much!
Please don't!
Stop, you're making me crazy.
Please stop!
Miss Ryo!
Don't suck them!
I'm hot!
It's so hot down there, Ruka!
Miss Ryo, you poor thing.
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Damn it!
What's this scar from?
Bungo!
You wanna die?
Stop it!
That's Ryo's...
No, Miss Ryo!
Don't do that!
No, stop!
I'm too shy!
Not there!
Miss Ryo! Miss Ryo!
I can't take this!
Please stop!
I can't take it!
Please, don't lick me!
Ruka, I want you to like it.
You're so wet.
Why are you teasing me like this,
Miss Ryo?
Sorry. It's just that you're
so cute, Ruka.
How do you like your own taste?
Ruka, I'm totally grooving on you.
Miss Ryo, it feels so good!
Keep doing it!
Is that good?
You like that, Ruka?
Do ya?
Don't say that!
Like it?
Make me cum!
Please make me cum!
Miss Ryo, it feels so good!
So unbelievable!
I'm gonna explode!
You all right with this, Ruka?
I'm so happy!
Miss Ryo!
Yeah, keep doing it!
I love you. I love you, Miss Ryo!
Miss Ryo, I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Ruka! Ruka!
You're mine! You belong to me!
I feel like I'm gonna melt!
Miss Ryo!
I'm yours! I belong to you!
Let's cum together!
I'm gonna cum!
Me too, Miss Ryo!
Ruka, leave with me, okay?
That hurts!
How do you like being
the one to feel the pain?
She was inside here.
Stop, Bungo!
For a woman who's given birth,
you sure have small tits!
What're you doing?
I'll never forgive you, Bungo!
You've never breastfed up till now.
You don't need these!
Because of your selfiishness...
my sister's dead.
I'll never forgive you for this, Bungo!
I'll kill you for this!
Too late.
As long as Ryo manages to escape,
that's good enough for me.
No matter what happens to me.
Isn't that right, my sister Itsuki.
The gate's open!
You're taking Ruka with you?
Kasumi!
Go ahead and leave.
The mannequins might not be around.
What's with you?
Run away.
'Cause Bungo risked his life for you.
People in the Kizuki family
are unable to cross the bridge.
No matter how much Hotaruko calls,
keep running and don't look back!
Ruka, are you all right?
I'm sorry!
A little further.
Ryo...
Miss Hotaruko is...
Ryo, don't leave me behind!
Please!
You told me you loved me, Ryo!
Hotaruko...
Miss Ryo, don't go!
Ryo!
It hurts!
Please come to me!
Hotaruko is calling me.
Don't, Miss Ryo!
Snap out of it!
Ruka...
You promised you'd escape with me!
You said we'd leave together!
Yeah... we've gotta go.
Ryo!
Please, Miss Ryo!
Leave with me!
Ryo!
I need you!
I can't live without you!
Escape with me!
I wouldn't know what to do
if you didn't leave with me!
I'm sorry, Ruka.
Hotaruko is calling me.
Sorry.
So you do like me more than her.
Right, Ryo?
That's cruel! Too cruel!
Sorry... I'm sorry, Ruka.
Sorry.
Ryo, you're fiinally all grown up.
My body's on fiire!
I'm gonna go insane!
That's the sacred steel sword
that Bungo used before...
Itsuki gave birth to twins.
One was a boy, and the other was a girl.
That's the sacred steel sword
that Bungo used before...
Itsuki gave birth to twins.
One was a boy, and the other was a girl.
Who am I?
It won't drop. The blood won't fall.
Mom!
Bungo!
Ryo, become one
with me, Hotaruko.
Ruka!
Ryo, become one
with me, Hotaruko.
Don't leave me behind, you guys!
I've come, Hotaruko.
Come to me.
Ryo.
I've come, Hotaruko.
I'm waiting for you.
I'll always be waiting for you.