Akitoshi-kun, how bout having lunch together?
I've been married for six months,
but I still rarely speaks with him.
Praying Mantis' Nest
Welcome back, dear.
What's with the exam result this time?
Are you even trying?
Dear...
I'm sure he's..
You shut up.
He's at an emotionally sensitive age,
suddenly having a new mother
would've been hard for him to accept right away.
That's why I need to try my best everyday to get him calling me 'Mom'.
What are you doing?
How is it? Delicious?
That's great.
Ah, right. I'll go get the tea.
Why did you get married with my father?
Why all of a sudden?
Come on, tell me.
Let's see...
Ever since we met at the university lab
I've been admiring him.
Because he was devastated after the divorce..
I see..
to get someone to look after me.
Well... you could say that.
Rather than staying single and studying in a university,
I figured it's better if I settle down.
But isn't it boring everyday?
With no sex.
W... wait, Akitoshi-kun?
I know you haven't done it with my father.
S... sto..
You must have been sexually frustrated
Stop! Stop please.
Ooh, you can actually get mad.
Akitoshi-kun, enough already!
Chihiro-san, did you just pee?
Kind of smell here
No way, I've washed it properly
Ehh, really?
wai..
Akitoshi-kun, it's too big.
I...
can tell from the scent
if a woman is in heat or not
Chihiro-san, you've been frustrated the whole time haven't you
N.. no..
You're trying to act cool,
but you can't hold it, it's driving you crazy.
Oh no, this boy..
This boy knows
how to pleasure a woman
Ah, too bad, I'm taking it out
Afterall, it would be a problem if you got pregnant right?
Since we are family
right?
'Mom'
N.. no way.
Here I go, Mom.
This is Akitoshi-kun's..
When I recall back what happened, I feel weird..
Just like what he said,
am I sexually frustrated?
What are you doing with other people's underwear?
You have that kind of fetish huh..
That's wrong, this is...
What's wrong?
So mean
I'm always up for more if you just ask for it.
This..
This scent..
I'm glad though,
my new mother is someone like you, Chihiro-san.
my previous mother always hits me,
and she wasn't good at cooking.
But you're beautiful and kind, and good at cooking
I really like you
Hey, Akitoshi-kun, I can't take it anymore..
No need to hurry
My previous mother likes to be teased
I played with her like this all the time
but too bad dad found it out.
So he kicked her out of the house.
That's why when he told me he's getting married again
I was honestly surprised
This boy definitely
knows everything about a woman's body
Oh no
No
At this rate, I'll be...
eaten up by him
Haa.. that felt good.
Hey, don't look so serious
This is just a game.
If you ever feel bored, we can play this game again.
Okay, mom?
Eh... you're going oversea?
Yeah
I don't know when I'll be back
Maybe a year, or two.
No way..
I'm sorry
I also feel bad leaving about leaving Akitoshi by himself at such a critical time
I understand
Dear?
Sorry, I can't do it either today.
What is it?
Sorry. I'm just glad that you like my food
There you go again, Chihiro-san's speech of happiness.
I've always wanted to have meals with my child like this.
Even having sex with that child?
T... that's just something different about our family
To be honest, I've kinda given up on having a child
Chihiro-san, what's with you lately?
Why? Did something made you curious?
You seem to be enjoying this lately
Oh, but aren't you the one who made me like this?
Hey, look. Put it in.
What's wrong?
Compared to the usual, you're quite shallow today.
Come on
If you don't put it in deeper, it won't reach my womb.
Shit, don't get so bossy.
I'm the one who should be giving out orders
but why?!
It's like..
I'm the one who's being eaten up!
What's with the long face?
What do you want, Hinako?
I just asked you a question!
I don't feel like being at home lately
If that's the case,
there's a new restaurant that just opened near the station,
wanna check it out?
Sure. But it's your treat okay?
I'm home
I've already had dinner with my friend
Akitoshi-kun!
Coming home this late, I thought you got into an accident
From now on if you're coming home late
make sure you call home first okay?
wai..
While I was waiting for you today,
I've been thinking about you Akitoshi-kun.
What you're doing at school,
what you would like to do when you're back,
or if we could just stay together like this.
Akitoshi-kun?
3 months later
Sorry for staying at your place for so long
It's okay
Okay then, I'll go buy some delicious snacks before I go home
Alright..
I need to pack up my stuffs
Akitoshi-kun
Chihiro-san..
Make sure to thank her parents properly okay?
Aah, yeah..
Seems like her parents are overseas too
I'll thank them when they come back
Don't tell me... you're coming with me
No... I'm just a little worried
I see. That's good.
Dad would be coming home soon
you should get along again
About that, so iu wake ni mo ikanakunachatta???
See these
So?
They're much bigger than before right?
They became this plump.
Akitoshi-kun, because you came inside me,
my body became like this.
You see, I've decided since this child was conceived,
that the three of us will live a happy life
Wait..
What are you talking about?
Come on, isn't it obvious?
I'm talking about our baby
No way
Stop joking!
If dad finds out about this, what are we gonna do?
Like I said already,
the three of us will live a happy life
You and me,
and this child.
Wha-
Akitoshi-kun, until you graduate, I'll find work or something
okay?
Don't just say anything you want.
I've told you not to follow me!
That's right, at first I thought I would just do that,
watching over you from afar
but you see, the baby inside said "that's not enough".
No way, I'm way too young to be a parent
Even if it's impossible to bear with, if you could just go to the clinic
What are you saying?
There's no way I could do that.
If I do that, I..
won't be happy would I?
Akitoshi-kun, you made my dream come true.
I love you! I love you and our baby..
So..
Let's live together again
It doesn't have to be here
We can rent a small room for just the three of us
You don't need to worry about anything
You just need to stay by my side
No..
way!
You're so troublesome. Enough already!
I've got so many thing that I want to do!
Like going to blind dates and meet girls to have sex with
You'll just be a bother
I can't have an old hag by my side all the time!
That's...
that's right
Of course you'd prefer a more energetic younger girl
Not an old woman like me
Chi...  hiro-san..
Mom...
I'm back! Anybody home?
Chihiro!
Akitoshi! Are you on the second floor?
Chihiro, what are you doing in Akitoshi room?
Oh right, Akitoshi already moved to an apartment
What are you saying dear?
Akitoshi-kun, you see,
he's right here.