So, who was the next target?
While looking for the next target...
We all spent time together after class.
Alrighty...
Me!
Lets see...
Lets... start with you.
Ms. Tenkawa, are you satisfied just by taping?
Huh?
I think you should wet yourself more.
O, OK!
Ms. Tenkawa, don't forget to keep taping.
Y, yes...
I want your thing, Mr. Shibui.
Yeah Sis, it's not fair!
I want it too...
it may have started as a rape.
But he showed us great new pleasures.
He was an absolute presence to us.
Move over.
Hurry and start taping.
Ms. Hikawa, please tape her while
she has two objects filling herself.
Teacher, l...
Me too...
Teacher, give it to me!
Teacher, me first!
Teacher...
Teacher?
Next is me...
After Class Lesson.
Lesson 3.
This was in my box today.
It looks like it was taken at school.
I assume she is one of our students.
How do you explain yourself?
Not a word to say?
So be it.
I will have a meeting immediately.
It's a prank!
What?
It's a dirty prank!
Someone doctored this picture!
A prank?
T, the students do hate me...
I see...
I guess you could be right.
Look like someone is trying
to get me out of this school.
If such a thing happens again
for sure I would be terminated.
Who did such a thing.
Reveal yourself.
No, no.
Teacher, please don't leave!
If the loyalty of you four are true...
The suspect didn't do this because of hate.
No, Teacher!
The suspect probably did this because
she wasn't satisfied with the current situation.
For example, wanting to keep me for herself.
But that is impossible.
I still want to experience this pleasure with other girls...
it was only a matter of time before he made
a move on Ms. Tachibana, the shrine maiden.
She is the only succeeder of the 1000 year-old shrine.
She suddenly quit the swim team.
Looks like she's trying to get her
back, if you know what I mean.
Chiaki...
Shh, it's me.
N, not right here!
I'm sorry, but Chiaki, I really want to...
Talk it over.
Ikumi...
Chiaki, lets start over...
I told you, I can't go against the teachings!
Who cares about your teachings!
Chiaki...
Chiaki, come on..
No...!
Chiaki!
Pipe down.
I know you like it.
It's so... hard.
Chiaki...
I love you.
Me too...
Chiaki, it tastes really great.
You're so wet.
An endless flood.
L, it's amazing, lkumi!
Do you want to cum, Chiaki?
Chiaki.
Ikumi, you're alri...!?
Mr. Shibui?
Ayumi.
Rei.
Akari.
Shizune...?
Ikumi, what's this about...?
So you don't have a bra on.
Does that mean...?
Does this mean that you don't need to wear
anything extra in front of your god?
It's beautiful...
A skin so elegant and fine.
It's so soft...
Yet, it's shaped well.
Oh, did it hurt?
Let me lick it.
Oh, she's clean shaven.
Are all lesbians like this?
Ikumi, do you shave too?
Lets check her out.
S, stop, let go!
Oh my.
So much excess hair.
I guess she doesn't play the male role for nothing.
Shut up, don't speak!
Why, I'm congratulating you.
Shut up!!
I think she's just hairy by nature.
That's is sad.
This honey pot was used by a fake cock.
Look at all this honey dripping out!
It means you like it.
That's right, accept the pleasure.
It's more natural for a woman to be
with a man than another woman.
N, no!!
It feels great.
Lets get down to business.
Please tape the whole thing, Ms. Tenkawa.
Yes..
This is... fabulous.
Females "accept" the males.
This is how it should really be done.
I will teach you everything I know.
I knew you were going to be great.
Please stop!
Not yet, we're just getting started!
The thing you did to Chiaki looked
fun, I want to try it on you.
Stop!
What?
L, I'm being forced, but l...!?
N, no, I'm cuming!
It doesn't feel good..
I'm not enjoying this...!
Lets try something else next.
Come on lkumi, open wide.
You're not the male role anymore.
Suck it right.
Don't forget to use your tongue.
You're pretty gentle.
Lets make this rough.
You're have bad manners, lkumi.
You're disrespecting the teacher.
A girl like you needs to be punished.
Here we go.
Sis, switch places with me.
Be quiet, don't talk to me!
Teacher, can I help you with something?
Actually yes, put this in Chiaki's mouth.
OK!
I feel like I'm a man, this is fun!
I see, so it's fun.
No, suck it right!
Sorry about earlier.
I was with other teachers.
Yes... oh, I see.
So I guess the wedding will be next year.
It's alright, I understand.
I see...
I guess you could be right.
However... if you are lying just to get out of this!
You will be terminated from here, understand!?
No, don't say that... it's nothing like that.
OK, but you hang up first.
Ms. Sano?
Ms. Sano, are you here?
What do you think you're doing, Ms. Tachibana...!?
M, Ms. Sano?
Girls, what is the meaning of this?
Sorry, but it's not good for his health to worry
about his job every day... this was our only choice.
What are you saying, Ms. Sano... who is him?
It hurts, stop, stop, no, please stop this!
Oh, there's something red.
Ms. Hayakawa, that means you're a...
Teacher, you have a finance right?
Were you saving your virginity for him?
I'm surprised, but in a good way.
Ms. Hayakawa, I'm sure you know what will
happen if you fire him from this school.
Teachers, parents, everyone will see this footage.
Lets show it to your fiance too.
N, no, don't... anything but that!
Alright.
But in exchange, I'll cum inside.
N, no, please don't do that!
No this, no that.
You sure are a bitch, Ms. Hayakawa.
They won't know if you don't scream.
Are you in pain, Teacher?
But your back side is still not filled.
Shizune, her butt too.
OK.
C, can't hold it...
it's alright, Teacher.
Let it all out.
I can't... let me go to the restroom...
Teacher, you can let it out here.
We want to see it.
W, what are you say...!!!?
No, stop moving, stop moving inside!
I can't, I can't, I can't!!!!
That's a lot, Teacher!
Ms. Hayakawa, you're so dirty.
You couldn't hold your peepee.
But also beautiful...
I'm getting horny...
Me too...
Mr. Shibui.
We want to have fun too.
Alright, I understand.
Ms.Tenkawa, please wash Ms. Hayakawa clean.
Ms. Tenkawa.
Y, yes.
A, amazing Teacher!
Teacher, more, give me more!
Come on, lick it clean girlie!
Make me feel good!
Teacher, you're amazing!
Teacher, I'm next!
No, me!
Me too...
Oh, Ms. Hayakawa.
Joining in the fun?
Y, yeah...
W, what's wrong with me!?
Nothing is wrong with you.
B, but, I, it won't stop!
It's only because you've been holding it in this entire time.
And Ms. Hayakawa's wedding
arrangements has changed.
For this reason, today is her last day at this school.
Lets have Ms. Hayakawa on the stage.
Please come forward.
Yes.
I've been only here for a short time, but thank you.
I will never...
Forget you all, ever.
More, I need to make this dirtier.
Ms. Tenkawa.
I bought you your new tapes.
Please leave those on the table.
What's wrong?
It's nothing, excuse me...
Wait.
Y, yes?
Since you're here, pleasure me.
Alright, how would you want it?
Lets see...
Teacher...
Please...
W, why?
What, is there a problem?
No, not at all...
O, ouch, please be more gentle, Teacher!
Did you say something?
I couldn't really hear you.
N, nothing...!
By the way.
Are you the one who stoled the picture?
N, no!
I would never betray you, ever!
I see...
I wasn't lying when I said I didn't do it.
But I'm sure the person who did, just wanted to end this.
Just like how I felt about it.
Not much as expected.
W, was I not satisfying?
Lately, I haven't been able to enjoy sex with you.
It's just not exciting.
L, I'm sorry!
P, please give me another chance!
It's nothing like that.
You're... going to look for a new girl?
Lets go home.
I need to lock up.
Go out now.
I couldn't stand him having sex with another girl!
So!!!
He is finally mine...