My friend was dragging me through
the gates to the school festival...
The fated path towards a meeting
with my mutual first loves...
We practically eloped.
My current happy everyday life is a somewhat
unusual ending for this kind of story.
He's getting better at cooking
rather quickly, isn't he?
My dear big sister is always like that.
Not really concerned with her present appearance.
Sayuri-san, if you mean my underwear, there's no
one jumping around shouting about it, right?
Aren't you supposed to be the
one complaining about this?
Rather than refining your cooking skills, you
should be focusing on more important things.
I mean even today...
A gentleman shouldn't keep a lady waiting.
How about we go a little slower?
Your back is too wide, that shirt stinks of
tobacco, you're good at housework...
I don't like any of that!
You're the polar opposite of what I'm looking for.
Room? There's more than
enough room here for us.
Well Sayuri-chan said that...
My dear husband, just look after
me only, and things will be okay.
But Yuuko, you used to live in that big mansion -
What's dearest in my heart is how
comfortable our lives are.
That's how I feel.
Is something the matter, Lady Rose?
Nothing at all.
Hey you!
What is it? Too creepy...
Houkago
~ Sayuri ~
Presented by Erobeat
http://www.erobeat.net
#erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: KuriosAkantha
Edit: Ryutso
Timing: Zetsuei
Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Quality Check: Chaosrains
Was that her just now?
What poor taste, even though she's so pretty.
Usually in this 3-part evaluation,
they would call the student's parents.
In other words, rather than my parents, I'd
like to have you consult in this matter.
Sorry for being late.
No, that's fine.
Does it look strange?
I just thought "that's rare".
I wanted to buy it after all...
Who's that?
Such a shy and bashful wife. I really envy you.
The little sister's also a blessing
from Heaven. Isn't that right?
Were you aware?
Your little sister-in-law is being called
this school's "Princess Rose".
Every year, students who've earned the best
grades vote on who to grant this title to.
Our Princess Rose currently majors in
the music elective course "Piano".
If I remember correctly, her big sister
also graduated from our academy
where she excelled in vocal music
a veritable princess of her class.
Brilliant achievements are expected
of them after graduation,
because they are truly wonderful.
They're very quick learners and they're
receiving special "extra" training.
What was that guy talking about?
Sayuri-san seems to have earned many admirers.
There's always been nothing but praise for her.
But she didn't seem too happy about it...
We don't like being compared to one another...
Us girl that is...
You sleazy perv! How dare you say such
suggestive things in front of Onii-sama!
That tone of voice...
That's enough already...
I'll forgive you, Princess.
No... I'm getting hot...
D-Don't! If you go any further I'll...
That filthy thing... Hurry up
and wither away already!
A man without any reason or taste...
Thinking it'd be okay to expose
such a nasty thing to a lady...
You're disgusting... You're like a beast
during mating season. You dog!
I'll take care...
I'll take care of it. Even with dogs,
you'd feel some sympathy...
Do you remember how to stimulate a man?
Lean down and kiss it. Unlike before,
you're a nymphomaniac now.
Don't say things that don't need
to be said, or I'll be bite it off.
Your interests are different now...
You apply what you've learned
with so much enthusiasm...
I didn't like it... Don't compare me to others...
You jealousy is cute.
If I let you do it every day, a dog or
cat would make a habit out of it...
I know. She's jealous.
Okay then, good night.
You started painting your toenails?
Well recently I was told to try to look prettier.
I told you?
Oh... No. A friend of mine.
Aren't you glad he's a worthless dumbass?
If we get found out... I'll kill myself.
Hurry up. I'll soon send you to Heaven.
You remembered your lessons well.
You never did get any practice
from that idiot, right?
No, he never did anything indecent
or embarrassing like this.
You're the only one.
Your whole life up till now, I've been the only one?
Probably for the rest of my life it'll be only you.
You met that idiot when you were
both students here, right?
Your first kiss and your virginity were stolen.
Do you remember how it felt?
Please stop. Don't remind me of him.
I never want to forget about him.
We only just married after all.
Forget that worm, you're going to be mine.
He's there isn't he,
working hard on countless nights, indulging
in othertime every night instead of-
You're so cruel! That's invasion of privacy!
That's not fair...
I know you're not actually upset.
This is bad... This can't go on...
You really did major in singing. Your moan
so much better your sister.
Don't compare us to one another!
You're cute when you act childish like that.
Since this morning up till just a little while ago...
It'd be pretty sweet to have two sibling
princesses at the same time.
You're so cruel... If you compare us like
that... we'll end up hating each other.
I'd never forgive you.
You're not allowed to do that!
There's no way I'd let you! Never!
You're hitting me so deep!
No... No! This is so wrong!
My husband hasn't even done it once...
Please stop this already. My voice is so shameful.
S-Stop it! No!
Don't... please don't! I can't take it anymore!
It looks like this alone isn't
enough to make you mine.
Yuuko's womb is to bashful.
W-Womb? Don't! Don't say womb!
Don't aim for it! Please!
Don't! Don't cum!
I don't want you to cum!
You came so much...
Onee-sama? She doesn't seem
particularly different.
She is how she always is.
I feel like something is wrong though...
If you're so concerned, hurry up and ask her.
I just remembered I have some
things to do. Please excuse me.
I just serviced him not too long ago.
Nothing can satisfy him.
Please stop!
Don't lift it!
What should I do... I can tell
from this residual scent.
It's Onee-sama's... No!
Your breath is hot.
It's really true that bashfulness is one of the
most important aspects of a noble lady.
Please don't tease me...
There really is something going on.
Something I don't know about.
Whatever it is...
You perv! Enough already you...
Doing it like this you...
Dog! Lowlife! Scum!
It can't be! This is...
You pervert! Doing it over and over
every single day... it's indecent!
Don't take it off... It'd be a waste.
And temping your brother-in-low by wearing
sexy panties isn't "indecent"?
Rindou Female Academy, student council
policy Provision 3, Article 2:
Underwear is regulated, deviant
cloth patterns are forbidden.
That's not it, go higher! If you touch me
in weird places I won't forgive you!
Only strictly white or other
appropriate designs are permitted.
Let me check this spot again.
how much longer you going
to be inspecting my uniform?
Hurry up and finish.
In this to tempt your brother-in-law?
Stop taking so much time!
As expected of a virgin. That sweet
inexperience is so lovely.
You're not allowed to sax such nasty things!
That's right. It's nasty like these panties!
Don't look you idiot!
You're worthless scum!
You're too nasty to stay a virgin.
You're a rotten failure!
Don't you dare get close to me!
Onii-sama...
As i suspected, it really was
for your brother-in-law, eh?
What happened to your defiant voice
from before, Princess Rose!?
How do you like your first taste of a man?
Not even a thousand words could
describe how this feels!
You can't do this! Take it out!
It was easier to find than I thought it would
be... The Princess's womb that is.
Wait... you!
You're pretty good at this.
Even though you're supposed to be a virgin!
Please stop! You can't do this!
Please forgive me! Somebody save me!
Don't cum! Hurry up and take it out already!
It's not too late!
Please! Take it out! I beg you!
No! Don't cum! Not so deep inside me!
Hey loser, I thought it might be okay if
I let you realize what's been going on.
Remember what I said about your wife being a great woman?
Actually I've been training her
to be even more bashful.
It's important for the training to be thorough.
And women can really be shameless, right?
It's too embarrassing doing this everyday.
You're bold, not hesitating at all.
I really need to pee, that's all.
I'm not lying... The smell is overwhelming...
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm so sorry for using a Japanese-style
urinal so shamelessly like this.
Please forgive me for letting another
man use me like this, my husband!
What the hell is going on!? Dammit!
Damn.
That woman had such a fine ass.
I've seen that kind of set-up before.
It'd be a waste to not do it here.
If I don't return home soon, he'll...
He's a freaking moron.
Do you thing he'll realize this time?
Thanks for your delicious wife.
She was quite a feast.
She was raised well to be honest.
Even a busy young student, with the right
lessons, can become irresistible.
We shouldn't! I have to finish the
laundry before he comes home!
If you don't stop I'll...
No!
I'll take  them off myself.
Are you sure? Isn't that the bed where
you and your husband sleep?
Hold it.
As I suspected, it's soaking wet.
Even when you're alone, thinking
about me makes you wet, right?
That's not true! No way!
That's good. You've gotten skilled at this.
I can fell your love.
That's not true! I don't love you.
But... you did teach me about being a woman.
You alone.
That's enough. I don't want to hear
any more! Don't tell me, please!
Things were okay how they were!
I can't take this!
The gods will never forgive me,
betraying my husband like this.
Your confession is cute. But where's your hand?
Look how wet and welcoming you are.
That's not true. It's not because I want it!
Forgive me my husband, my heart
will belong only to you so...
My heart is only yours!
I'm so sorry my husband, for getting
it from this man for so long now.
I can't think of anything but sex and I can't
get the thought of dick out of my mind.
Even though... Yes! Why is it so!?
All night long I was cruelly fucked by this
man, but his virility is unbelievable.
I don't think of anything but lust now...
No matter how many times he cums in me...
it's your face I imagine, my dear husband!
I'm cumming!
Hey Onii-sama. Sorry for your wife returning
so late every night recently.
But you know, it's not like you'd
do anything together anyway.
She even brings home a "present"
for you every time, so let it go.
Hurry up and do it. You need to be
a more honest girl. Right, Sayuri?
You're just so vigorous... there's
no way we can defy you...
Please... I want to cum!
Then swear you'll be mine.
I'm already yours.
You love me more than your husband?
You love your husband more?
Just for now... it's you...
Now swear on it for the rest of your life!
It's so good... It's too wonderful!
Better than your husband? Who's better?
You are so much better than him.
"You"? Be more specific.
This dick brings so much into me. It's so reliable!
You'll break up with your husband?
I don't want to!
Then I'll stop.
If you keep going, maybe I'll leave him...
Any man would fall for these healthy young sisters.