The honor students after school 2
I'm cumming!
Did you cum?
Yeah.
Yumisaka's Story
Natsume?
Um...
Can I ask you a favor?
It's been two months since I began dating Yumisaka,
a girl from the class next door.
We got close to each other during
the class representative meetings.
The first time we had sex was at her house,
three days after we started dating.
Surprisingly, she took the initiative.
Since then, we've been having sex every day.
But recently, it seems like it's gotten a little dull for her.
Hey, are you sure you want to do this?
You don't want to?
Um, I'm okay with it, but more importantly, are you?
Yep. No one's gonna be home for a while, so it should be fine.
Still, out here in the living room?
We should at least lock the door.
It'll be fine.
Come on, point it this way.
Okay, if you insist.
Your dick has such a strong smell.
You're up and ready to go.
Okay, I'm gonna start sucking it, okay?
G-Go for it.
W-Was she always this dirty?
I'm going to pleasure your big, juicy cock with my mouth.
You can blow your load whenever you want.
This is even better than I thought!
Doing something so scandalous is giving me a huge rush!
She's usually so quiet during sex.
I can't believe the noises she making right now!
Feel free to cum.
Just let it out.
Cum!
Yummy, yummy, yummy, I got cummy in my tummy.
You got all of it!
The camera is shaking at the end.
Did it feel good?
You really caught me off guard.
I didn't know you could be so lewd, Yumisaka.
Really?
To be honest, I get very turned on
when I act like a slut or get filmed.
Sorry for dragging you into my fetishes.
I just really wanted to try it out.
Why are you into that?
Do you know my friend, Seta?
Yeah, from the literature club.
Sometimes we cosplay at events together.
We had recently come back from one.
While looking for the pictures we took together,
I accidentally found a sex tape she recorded.
It made me want to try it out.
Don't tell her I saw, okay?
Why would I?!
Before I started dating you, I was doing this...
Look at this.
I took these pictures and uploaded them online.
But it just didn't feel the same.
I-Is that so?
I don't anymore!
I no longer need to.
Because I have you now.
Do you not like this sort of thing?
I'd like to do this more often, but we don't have to.
I-If it's once in a while.
Thanks!
This is how it all started.
Multi-Purpose Room
You're being too loud.
Sorry, it just feels so good!
We kept having wilder and wilder sex.
Like having sex in an empty classroom.
You came so much.
So much sticky, yummy cum.
All of her pent up sex drive was starting to burst out.
And before I knew it, I got into the rush of wild sex as well.
We even live streamed having sex.
Begin Stream
Okay, I'm going to make my boyfriend cum with a tit fuck.
My cup size?
H, I think?
Sorry, I'm not showing my face.
Comments
Viewers
Live Chat
holy shit!
damn those are some huge titties!
what cup size are you?
peportes
Okay, here I go.
Your dick's rock solid!
I'm cumming!
Go ahead.
Wow!
You came so much!
Look! He's marked me with his manly load.
Of course, it didn't stop there.
We kept streaming until we got banned.
Once again, we found ourselves wanting even more.
Are you sure about this, Yumisaka?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I'm safe today.
Condoms don't look good on camera anyway.
Make sure you get all of it okay? My first time raw.
No! I don't think I can stop moving my hips!
You're even tighter than usual!
This is insane!
The way we're having sex... It's like we're trying to make a baby!
This is too hot!
I'm gonna cum! Hold on...
Your raw dick is stirring me up!
It feels so good!
This is really bad!
I need to pull out!
If I don't, I'm gonna cum inside you!
Go ahead, it's fine.
Give me my first creampie, Natsume!
I'm being creampied on film!
I've already cummed inside her once,
so a few more times won't make a difference.
You're fucking me from behind now!
Inside me...
You're going to cum inside me!
Yumisaka's slutiness was amazing.
Pump your load into me!
Shove your cock all the way in!
Dump it all in me!
Oh my god, I'm going crazy!
This won't be a one-time thing.
There's no way we can go back to protected sex now.
Let's cum together!
Look.
Three loads of cum is flowing out of me.
Are you getting this?
How much further are we going to take this?
Let's make even more memories next time, Natsume!
Seta's Story
Even though I look really bland,
I've had a pretty normal sex life.
I used to have a boyfriend...
I would record us during sex because
it would turn me on like crazy.
He thought it was weird and didn't like it though.
He'd also cum inside without permission, so I dumped him.
So here I am now at my friend, Yumisaka's house.
This is Yumisaka's little brother, Shu.
He's a cute, shy boy who's about three years younger than me.
Hello.
Where's my sister?
She said something came up and she'd be back late.
O-Oh, I see.
Sometimes, I get extremely horny and can't hold myself back.
I hadn't kissed in a while, so I really got into it.
Before I knew it, ten minutes had passed.
Wanna go further?
Y-Yeah...
Your underwear's soaked.
S-Sorry!
It's fine. Let's make this quick.
I'm glad I had a condom on me.
Though it looks like he's too big for a regular size.
Okay, say goodbye to your virginity.
How's it feel?
It feels really good!
It's so warm!
If you last long enough, I might let you do me raw.
Huh?!
I can't believe I took the virginity of my friend's brother!
God, he's just too cute! I might just give him the works!
Did my pussy feel good?
Yes!
Let's do this again some time, okay?
I took that condom home and...
After that, I started heading to my
friend's house about twice a week.
Sorry, we don't have much time.
Will my mouth do?
S-Sure.
I wanted to fuck him, but I guess I'll have to settle for this.
Okay, here I go.
Cum whenever you want.
I wasn't too sure how good my blow jobs were...
So good!
But I guess I had nothing to worry about.
Mizuho...
I can't be too loud.
I-I'm cumming!
Here it comes!
So much! And it's so thick!
Can you wait until next time?
I'll let you use my pussy, okay?
O-Okay!
I get to have sex again!
It was cute how hooked he was on my body.
I had to be proactive and take the lead every time, though.
When Yumisaka was out with her boyfriend,
I'd come over and fuck her brother.
I bet Yumisaka has no idea I'm sleeping
with her brother every other day.
She's too straight-laced to even imagine that.
Call me Big Sis from now on, okay?
Mizuho...
Big Sis...
Sorry, Yumisaka. Your brother's mine now!
Let's do it raw today.
H-Huh?! I...
Don't you wanna blow your load inside me?
I may never ask you again.
I want to...
Who am I kidding?
I'm a fucking slut that wants a raw dick inside me.
I can feel his tip going in!
Can you move?
Thrust it in me.
Shoot your goo whenever you want.
Dammit! This feel so good!
I'm already gonna cum!
He's pushing down so hard!
He's not holding back even a little!
Sorry! I'm cumming!
Cumming already?
Sorry, but I couldn't hold it in!
I can feel it pouring inside me.
It feels so good!
But...
Okay, let's take a break.
Just kidding! I won't let you!
It's your fault for hooking me on your cock, Shu.
You've awakened the demon.
Just leave it all to your Big Sis.
So cute!
A young boy's dick is so adorable!
Riding on top while watching his
face contort in pleasure is the best!
I'm gonna cum!
Keep cumming until you're done, okay?
Don't worry, my thirsty cunt will drink every drop.
It feels so good...
I don't think I can cum anymore.
You were so good.
I feel amazing.
Wow, look at all this!
It makes me want to go again!
You up for another round?
Y-Yes...
He might've been hooked on me...
but now I'm the one hooked on him!
How shall we fuck today?
translation: hikarucon
timing: ragingheartsexcelion
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editing: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч