Honor Students After School
②
I'm gonna come!
Did you come?
Yeah...
The Case of Yumisaka-san
Natsume-kun...
Umm... I have a request...
I've been dating Yumisaka-san from
the class next to mine for about 2 months.
We met and got together from committee
meetings where both of us are in.
3 days after we started going out,
we had sex for the first time as she invited me to her house.
I was surprised since she's a well-behaved type of girl.
We spent most of the days after that having normal sex
just as how young couples usually do.
But she's kind of getting a little tired of it lately...
Hey, are we really doing it?
Umm... Can't we?
Eh, nah... I'm fine with it...
But are you sure that we will be okay?
Yeah... I'm sure that no one's gonna
come home for the next 2 hours.
B-But doing this in the living room is...
We should at least lock the door...
I said it's alright.
Come on, turn it this way.
Then, I'll start it now.
Your dick smells amazing... We're all good to go!
Then, I'll give you a blowjob.
Y-Yeah...
W-Was she always this lewd?
I'm now going to give this cock
a lot of pleasure using my mouth-pussy!
You can spurt it in my mouth
whenever you want, okay?
Ah... This is way more
unbelievable than I thought!
This is bad no matter how I think
about it! This is a depravity!
Yumisaka-san is usually quiet when we're having sex.
But now she's giving me such an erotic blowjob!
You can come if you want!
Squirt it out!
Sperm... Shoot your sperm out!
You came a lot of tasty sperm!
You got it, it's all recorded!
You were shivering at the end,
Natsume-kun. Did it feel good?
I'm kind of shocked.
About the fact that you're quite
a naughty girl, Yumisaka-san.
Is that so?
It's just something like...
Being filmed makes me feel so aroused...
I'm sorry for dragging you along into my fetish.
But I wanted to try doing this.
And why is that?
Do you know my friend Seta-san?
Yeah, the Literature Club member.
We cosplayed together at a few events.
And when I went to her house to hang out...
I thought about looking for
our pictures from the last time.
And then, I saw Seta-san getting fucked instead...
I wanted to try doing one myself as well...
Ah! Keep that a secret, okay?
I can't tell anyone that!
And then, before we started dating...
Here it is!
Here, look at this.
I uploaded stuff like these online,
but it just doesn't feel right.
E-Eh...
I'm not doing this anymore! There's no need to.
That's because I already have you.
Do you hate having this kind of sex?
I want to do more of these, but we can just stop it here if you hate it.
I-It should be alright from time to time.
I'm glad to hear that.
Now that I think about it, that was the turning point for both of us.
Multipurpose Room
Lower your voice a little more.
Sorry, but it feels great!
Yumisaka-san's demands gradually escalated.
Getting fucked in a vacant room.
You came a lot of tasty and fresh semen!
The lust that she always suppressed
all started to overflow.
I also started to gradually crave for this depravity.
We also did something called livestream sex.
Start Streaming
Alright then, I'll start to make my boyfriend's cock
ejaculate by giving him a titfuck.
My cup size? I'm H if I remember correctly.
Comments
Watching
Comment Box
Oh!
Ohh! Huge tits!
What's your cup size?
Reported (´・ω・`)
A student couple?
I'm not gonna show my face.
I'll start now.
Isn't your cock as stiff as a rod?
I'm gonna come!
Yes, it's alright!
Amazing... There's a lot coming out!
Look, I got a lot of ownership marking from him.
Surely enough, we didn't end up with only that.
We livestreamed our sex until our account got banned.
Whatever we did no longer
mattered after going that far.
Yumisaka, are we really doing it?
Yeah... I think today's a safe day.
Having a rubber won't look good on film.
Get a good footage of this, okay?
It's my first ever raw sex.
No, my hips won't stop!
You're way tighter than usual.
This is crazy!
It's like we're filming about baby making
with my raw cock going in and out.
This is so erotic!
I'm gonna come! Stop for a second...
I'm getting filmed while your
raw cock is penetrating me!
It feels good... It's incredible!
This is getting dangerous! I have to pull it out!
If this goes on, I'll come inside...
Okay, it's alright!
Natsume-kun, capture my first creampie moment!
I'm being filmed while getting a creampie!
Now that I came inside her once, it shouldn't
matter how many more times I do it again.
And next is me getting fucked from behind!
Inside me...
I'm getting a creampie!
Yumisaka-san's lewdness was awesome.
Creampies really feel so good!
While fucking me...
give me a creampie!
Creampies... This is bad, I'm going crazy!
I think this won't be our last time doing this.
We won't get enough of this pleasurable experience!
I'm coming... I'm coming from a creampie!
Look, Natsume-kun!
Are you filming this 3-shot worth of semen spilling out?
I wonder how far will our activities escalate.
I wonder what kind of memories
should we make next time?
Natsume-kun!
The Case of Seta-san
Despite looking like a plain girl,
I already have quite a lot of experience with people...
But I currently have no boyfriend.
I was hooked on how good sex felt at first, and with some kinky play.
I noticed that my ex-boyfriend's
taste doesn't match mine.
He carelessly comes inside me even on my risky days.
It was at that time
when I went to my close friend Yumisaka's house.
We call Yumisaka-san's younger brother as Shuu-kun.
He's kind of cute and a shy boy that's
about three years younger than me.
Hello... Where is my sister?
It seems that she's out for an errand,
so I'm here house sitting.
I-I see...
At that time,
I was in a period of intense sexual arousal
and I gave in to the temptation.
I got so preoccupied with kissing after so long.
When I realized it, we've been entwining
our tongues for about 10 minutes.
You want to go further, right?
Y-Yes...
Your pants are soaked inside.
I-I'm sorry!
It's fine. Shall we get to it now?
I'm glad that I still have a rubber left.
I think it's quite huge...
I'm gonna take it in, then.
How is it?
It feels good... It feels warm.
If you give me your best shot for today,
I'll let you do it raw next time.
It's my first time popping a young boy's cherry.
No way, he's so cute that I want to pamper him!
Did it feel good inside me?
Yes!
Let's do this again, okay?
I brought the used rubber home...
After that, I started coming over
at my friend's house several
times a week just to meet him.
I'm sorry! We don't have much time today,
so are you fine with just my mouth?
Y-Yes.
I wanted to have sex with him, but it can't be helped.
Alright then, I'll gobble you up!
You can come whenever you feel like doing so.
I'm somewhat confident in my blowjob skills.
It feels good...
But to see that I'm actually making
him feel this good is flattering.
That's amazing... Mizuho-san...
Even though we shouldn't be making much noise...
I'm coming... I'm coming!
What an amazing amount, and it's also thick!
Can you bear with this until next time?
I'll make you come using my pussy, okay?
Y-Yes!
Next time... We'll have sex...
He's now so hooked on my body that I find it funny,
but I'm also getting into being
the one that leads him on sex.
We're in his room while Yumisaka-san was out on a date with her boyfriend.
Her friend is feasting on her younger
brother while she's away from home.
I bet that a good girl like her never would
have thought about this ever happening.
I want you to call me onee-chan as well!
Mizuho-san...
O-Onee-chan...
Forgive me, Yumisaka-san. I just stole
your little brother from you!
Shall we do it raw today?
E-Eh? Umm...
Don't you want to squirt inside me?
Today might be the only time that I'll let you do it.
I want to do it...
I just want to do it raw.
I'm craving for him to plunge it inside me!
The tip is entering me raw!
Can you move? Try to hump me repeatedly.
When you start to feel like coming,
it's alright to shoot it all inside me!
This is bad!
I'll come in no time!
The way he's pressing his hips against mine...
He's trying hard to hold himself together!
I'm sorry! I'm coming!
Are you coming already?
I'm sorry... But I couldn't hold it in!
His slimy come is flowing inside me... It feels good!
But...
Well then, let's take a short break...
Just kidding, I won't let you rest!
It's Shuu-kun's fault that I ended up
teaching him about this kind of sex!
I can't stop myself anymore!
You can just let me take care of everything!
How cute! I knew that a younger boy's cock is good!
Raping a boy and making him feel good is the best!
I'm coming... It's gonna come out...
Shoot everything out up to the last drop, okay?
It's alright, I'll take it all inside!
It feels good...
Nothing's coming out anymore...
You did a splendid creampie.
Isn't it amazing? You came this much!
I feel like wanting to do it again.
So then, will you do it again for me?
Y-Yes...
He's head over heels for me...
But I'm fond of the fact that he feels that way... I wonder if he noticed that.
What should I do for him today?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization