After School Initiation
Ugh, what a mess.
You could have left a window open
or something. It stinks in here.
Hey, Konomi, wake up.
You're gonna be late for school.
Huh? Kei-chan?
No, I'm not that thing over there.
Did you guys do it all night?
Yeah, Kei-chan didn't really let me take a break.
What?
He's using you as a pet too much.
Kei-chan is a nice guy, though.
Are you saying you like him more than me?
That's not what I'm trying to...
Don't let this lewd play get too out of hand, got it?
H-Hey!
Just because you were born a few minutes early
doesn't mean you get the jump on me.
What's that now?
Is that really how you talk to your older brother?
You're just a guy with foreskin too tight for his dick.
Say that again, you bastard.
Come on, please. Stop fighting, you two.
Kei-chan, yours is long and cute.
You-chan, yours is thick and cute.
They're both my special friends.
I'll be nice and let you off today
for Puppy's sake, little brother.
That's my line.
That, and, didn't I tell you
to stop calling her that, Kei?
Whatever, I win.
How to train your childhood friend.
Wow, she's acting like nothing happened
now that we're at school.
I bet nobody would be able to guess
what she's been up to until this morning.
Shit, I'm getting hard again.
Huh? Wait, what's wrong, Kei-chan?
Kei-chan, wait!
You promised not to do this at school, remember?
I can't help it if I get turned on.
Huh? You're wearing these at school, too?
Are you even trying to hide them?
What were you going to do
if someone saw you with these on?
I can't help it.
It's the first present you've ever given me.
Saying those things even though
you were a virgin just half a year ago...
You're finally acting like a bitch in heat, huh?
I can sense it. I can sense his mischievous aura.
Eh? Yuu-chan?
Oh, 'sup Yuusuke? Hold up, I'm just about to cum.
Man, you found me so easily.
Well, It's not like I don't understand how your mind works.
Well, whatever. Here, I'll let you in on it.
Wai...
Ugh, you pushed out everything I put inside her.
Look. Look at Puppy here,
she wore my presents to school.
Does that piss you off?
It doesn't.
I'm about to cum!
Oh man, we're definitely not gonna
make it to our afternoon classes.
What's wrong, you two?
Puppy, you need to decide
who you want to date, right now.
You want me to choose? I can't.
No, let's not do this right now.
You two are scaring me today.
We're gonna take turns doing you,
so you need to decide who you want more.
We'll just directly ask this.
Whoever is more compatible, wins.
Simple, right?
Wait! Wait, you two!
You guys don't need to go this far. I already...
It's big... That's you, isn't it? Yuu-chan?
And now it's Kei-chan?
Oh my god, it's going so deep inside me!
So? Did you decide, Puppy?
I'm sorry, but, I can't date either of you...
I'm okay with being a pet
to both of you forever, though.
– Fuck yeah!
You think you can get away
with saying something that cute?
We'll take care of you forever, then!
We'll keep having sex with you until we die.
day 3
day 4
day 5
day 6
day 4
Uh... How many days have
we been doing this again?
Well, whatever. Okay, you're up, Yuusuke.
Okay, I'm gonna put it in.
No, Yuu-chan, you put your dick in the same hole as...
Oh god, your dicks are inside me
and rubbing together, and...
What are they doing inside of you? Speak up.
Yeah, tell us what they're doing.
They're twirling around and rubbing
my insides. I want all of your cum!
Well said!
I'm cumming!
Cumming inside!
Good morning, Kei-chan.
That's not fair, Kei. You can't just pass
out like that. I leave the rest to you.
Yuusuke?! Don't die! Yuusuke!
Sheesh, who's the master and who's the pet now?
Hey Kaname, you should give up, man.
Oshikiri is way out of your league.
She's got the looks,
but she's the student council president.
I heard that she ruthlessly shoots
down anyone who asks her out.
An eternal virgin like yourself has no chance.
The fuck you call me?!
Hey, you two. We're in class!
See what you did?
She's even laughing at me.
Virgin boy and Tiger Ears Woman
I swear, everyone was laughing
at me because of that damn Tanaka.
He even got Oshikiri to laugh.
Man, I wanna know what it's like to have sex with her.
Kaname-kun?
Second Student Council Room
Second Student Council Room?
Did this room always exist?
Hey, Kaname-kun?
I never thought she'd be the one
to talk to me first, though.
Up until now, my school life has been
a tragedy and filled with disappointment.
Now, it seems like luck is on my side!
Happiness is waiting for me beyond this door!
Oshikiri!
Oh? You're here a lot faster than I thought.
Give me a sec, okay?
I'll make this boy cum very soon.
What is this?
Oshikiri is having sex right in front of me...
The younger ones sure tire me out.
Don't you think having sex at school is wrong?
What is this room, anyway?
There's a sofa, a bed, even a refrigerator!
It's more efficient than meeting
up outside of school, isn't it?
I stand out a lot, so it'd be bad if someone
saw me doing something like this outside.
Still, doing this at school isn't right!
You mean, having sex?
Hey, Kaname-kun, would you like to have sex with me?
N-No, not here. If we get caught,
being suspended will be the least of our worries.
I think you should stop doing this... this...
You won't enjoy anything
if you're only going to complain.
What?
Didn't you say that you wanted to have sex with me?
Well, it looks like your lower half is more honest.
It's okay, I'm fine with virgins.
Look how far it flew!
You even moan like a girl!
You little... That's enough!
You've been teasing me this entire time.
Is it so weird to be a virgin?!
W-Wait! My panties are still on,
how are you going to put it in?
S-Sorry. Yeah, I'm going home.
Hold it.
You're really going to leave it like this?
Forcing yourself onto a girl is what scum do.
I don't really hate those primal instincts, though.
How about you stop pretending,
and just be honest with yourself?
Do you not want your first time
to be with me, perhaps?
I have no idea what's going through her head, but...
I'm throwing my virginity away today, Tanaka!
I forgot to mention, but, if you have
sex with me, then you'll become my pet.
Huh? What?! You didn't say anything about that!
I just did, didn't I?
Hey, wai...
It's already too late.
Fuck!
Looks like we did it.
With that, the contract is sealed.
Well then, for the time being,
do you wanna go again?
What do you even mean by "I'm your pet"?
Am I supposed to be your errand boy or something?
No, you don't have to do anything like that.
All you have to do is have sex
with me every now and then.
Not a bad deal, right?
You remind me of my boyfriend, Kaname-kun.
Your face when you're scolded
and when you're aroused are so similar.
He's not in this world anymore, though.
Oshikiri, you...
Maybe that's why I feel like you'll
be able to bring out who I truly am.
Look at how full they are.
I think you can still go about three more times.
It's your turn, Kaname-kun.
Should I face forward or backwards?
We can do it however you want.
Let's do it from behind, one more time.
I thought as much.
Hey, come on. It doesn't feel good
if you just put it inside me.
Hey, Oshikiri... This might not be
a good time to say it, but...
Would it be possible for us to be boyfriend
and girlfriend instead of master and pet?
What the heck? Did you just confess to me?
Not a chance in hell.
If you're going to keep going like that,
take your repulsive dick out and get out, now.
O-Okay, fine!
Yes, just like that.
That's good, Kaname-kun. More... go deeper!
O-Oshikiri...
Just keep going. Cum inside this time!
Wait, was your ex-boyfriend a dog?!
It looks great on you.
I'm so glad I took good care of it!
At the very least, I was able to get rid of my virginity,
but the days that I would be toyed and played
around with by Oshikiri Rikako had only just begun.
You're my only pet, Kaname-kun.
That makes you special!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч