(Sign: Away)
No, drink it.
You want more, right?
Then do as I say.
Teacher...
So sad...
You're hurt.
You must've been lonely.
I can feel your pain.
This school's idol, Akari Mizuno
ls now his most favorite toy.
It's ok... I'll help you.
Teacher...
More... more...
I'm happy.
You must be in pain, but yet you still answer to me.
More...!
You're admirable.
So sad...
So sad!
My father only worries about his work.
And my mother fools around with different guys.
I'm always alone.
Living in the cold...
After Class Lesson.
Lesson 2.
Ready?
OK!
Being lonely...
I joined the pep-squad to forget about it, but...
Ayumi, you have to smile.
Be careful.
But l...
I wanted love physically.
And this concludes today's lesson.
Man, it smelled.
Hurry, open the window!
I swear it smells like semen.
Ayumi!
Lets go to the bathroom together.
OK...
Lets go!
Hope you flowers grow beautifully.
Shizune Fujiwara, Freshmen, in the pep-squad.
Taking pictures of the flowers?
Y, yeah.
Do you mind?
Of course not!
Aren't they pretty?
I took really good care of them.
And look at how pretty they are now.
Y, yeah.
I'm so happy!
You're alright with me being here?
What do you mean?
Everyone thinks I'm creepy and avoids me...
But aren't you the science teacher?
I admire people like you.
Well, sorry to tell you, but vegetation is not my field.
But you are the scene teacher, right?
Oh, did I say something wrong?
No...
Get away from him, now!
Rei Hikawa, Sophomore, tennis team.
Why do you say that, Si...
You never know what a creepy guy like him will do.
That's why I warn.
Come here now.
OK...
She is my long time friend.
I ask you not to get near her.
Mr. Squid.
Why?
Why are you doing such things?
Sis!
Do not call me Sis in public anymore!
I told you many times, get it in your head.
Do you really understand the situation of the family?
Y, yes...
Stop lying.
You'll never understand why.
N, no!
You were planning to go to P.E. like that?
You're grown up now, at least wear a bra.
It hurts, it hurts!
This is a punishment for your slipping mouth.
I'm sorry, I won't do it again!
No, I can't trust you.
You always brake promises.
Class is starting!
There's a test today, I have to attend!
You're saying the test is more important than me?
Such childish-looking panties.
Oh, you're wet.
Why is it?
Don't tell me you actually like it?
No...
Looks like you like it.
How's this?
Do you feel sorry?
Come on, Tell me.
No, d, don't!
You are such a dirty girl...
I'm sorry Sis, forgive me.
Alright, punishment is over then.
N, no!
Don't stop!
See, I knew you like it.
Game set, Rei Fukawa.
2 games, Fifty-Love.
Mr. Shibui.
What are you doing?
N, nothing. J, just taking a walk.
Excuse me.
Rei, here!
Thank you.
Ayumi, what did you want to talk about?
Ayumi?
Um...
Mr. Shibui!
Ayumi, great work.
Shall we?
If you scream, people will find out.
Ms. Rei Hikawa...
What is she to you?
I think you said... Sis?
We're just friends...!
She took care of me... like a sister...
Is that true?
L, it is.
Ouch!
Ouch?
Don't you mean you like it?
So, you liked being a masochist?
I'm sorry, Sis...
This is in the way.
Stupid girl.
Practicing pep-squad while on the rag...
Now that there's nothing blocking here...
Girls on their period are great.
You don't like it?
We have to...
Recording, start.
If you tell me about, Ms. Hikawa
I'll make you feel even more better, but...
Sis.
I'm sorry...
Thanks for telling me.
I'm so happy.
Let me give you a reward.
I am very sure that you would love this.
Stay still.
Keep still.
Something cold... inside.
N, no!
L, it's going to...
Hold it in until I cum.
Not yet!
Not yet.
Hold it!
Alright, slowly move your hips down.
Go ahead.
Remember, just let it out slowly.
Great job, keep it up.
Shizune, show me your face.
What a wonderful expression.
Rei Hikawa and Shizune Fujiwara are true sisters.
Their father married a politician's daughter.
Rei and Shizune were given
birth by his previous lover.
But Shizune was left behind to
keep the lover's existence a secret.
Teacher knew Rei was
tormenting Shizune because of it.
But l...
I can take care of satisfying him...
You, do you have hatred against her?
I think everyone at school does.
Everyone knows she is nothing but a snobby bitch.
Besides, she's the one who gave
him the nickname "The Squid".
Teacher, that is why we have to teach her a lesson.
OK?
He was already determined to do
so without having Akari saying so.
Feeling dizzy...
Hello, Rei Hikawa.
T, The Squid?
Shizune...
Good job with the drug, you can leave.
Well?
Shizune, what drug...?
Don't tell me...
No, I'm staying!
I want to see what you're going to do with my sis.
L, I said don't call me that in front of people.
We already know.
We know you two are sisters and why you're hiding it.
Only us, of course.
But if the public finds out...
I'm sure it will be the most talked about news.
W, what do you want?
Not a sports bra?
Oh, you think you're better than that?
What do you think, don't you want
to do the same thing to your sister?
Shizune.
So, what will it be?
S, she's not brave enough to do such a thing.
L, I'll do it!
I've always wanted to try this on Sis.
Sis...
Sis.
Doesn't it hurt?
Not going to scream like me?
Be quiet, I'm not like you.
Don't worry about a thing.
It's just her pride talking.
OK...
I'm sure your sister will become like you.
You smell like sweat.
S, sweat!?
See, you're sister is saying no but her body is saying yes.
Y, yes.
He sure is amazing.
You're sweaty here too.
Which means...
Down here is probably...
No, don't!
P, please, let me take a shower!
I don't want to regret this.
We can't let this smell go to waste.
Shizune, please ask him to let me take a...!
It's amazing.
N, no, let me shower!
Sis is crying...
My almighty Sis...
Shizune, please tell him let me take a shower...!
See, Shizune? The tongue is at the butt...
I'm getting turned on looking at it.
Teacher... so amazing.
Akari.
Ayumi?
Me too...
Shall we start the main event?
Use a con...!
No, don't!
I'm going to...
Not inside...
I knew it.
Your workout has made your pussy tight.
You like it?
Who would like such a thing, such a...
You say that, but your pussy is so...
But, I like it rough.
A brat like you being fucked embarrassed and punished.
It's great...
it turns me on more.
S, stop!
It's tight!
I'm going to... cum!
You don't need to worry about
getting pregnant with this hole.
But, that's not fun at all.
How is it, isn't it good?
I tasted your pussy earlier.
He has me, but his wishes is to have sex with various girls.
Ayumi.
I have to accept his wishes.
But...
I wasn't able too...