Rindou Female Academy
That's not true. With your great serve...
You were really terrific.
Well, since you weren't too good at countering my servers,
I guess I'm getting better.
Hey! I try my best to return those serves!
Finally you returned to being Kaoruku-san I know.
You looked kind of depressed lately.
I couldn't help but invite you out for some tennis.
Segawa-sensei!
When it's just the two of us together, call me Yasuyuki.
We shouldn't... there are students nearby.
Teachers shouldn't...
Kaoruko-san...
Don't!
I... I'm sorry.
What an annoying girl.
Those earrings, those clothes, the bag... didn't I buy all of it!?
If it comes to it, I'll just have to use forse.
Who is that?
What the...
Kaoruko you bitch...
even when you have me as your fiancé!?
Unbelievable... Dammit!
You were supposed to be mine.
Where... Who stole you from me!?
Houkago 2
The Bashful Princess Yuri is Sweetly Mobbed
Those arrogant prudes...
The hot girls at this academy all belong to me!
Shouji-san, did you like our instrumental trio's performance in the final movement?
I thought it was good.
But if I had to make a critique...
If you had held on to the vibrato a bit longer,
then a distinct clarity would have been extended quite beautifully, don't you think?
Also, it would be good if the 2nd violins would let their sound resonate more.
We mustn't let our sound be overpowered by that of the piano.
Shouji-san's solo part was so wonderful.
That's our Princess Yuri!
Oh no...
I was able to play my part only because everyone's melody was so wonderful.
Wow, Shouji-san is so modest and polite!
Oh no, it's you girls who are so modest and polite!
Well, we'll go on ahead then. Farewell.
Farewell.
Why don't we go get something to eat?
That sounds good!
Okay, let's go.
Segawa-sensei.
It's okay if you want to take more time to practice, but...
You should have more confidence in yourself.
In part because you're naturally skilled, and have potential to be a great musician...
The title "Princess Yuri" was bestowed upon you.
I'm not that great.
With you involved, the greatest orchestra could be assembled...
About that... I've already declined the offer.
I'm really not up to the challenge.
Tonight, until you nod your head in consent, I won't let go you go home.
Don't!
Umm... I think I forget something here.
Am I intruding?
No, in fact I was planning to leave for home just now.
Really? Then let's go together.
Okay!
Every last one of those fools...
Whatever.
This will get the job done.
I'll train them to be my pets.
The great Princess Yuri...
Your body and mind will mature today.
Once I give you your first experience with a man...
The secret debut you don't want your parents to know about...
You want to make the decision with your boyfriend?
Kinky's new line, "After-School", goes just a little too far.
Sorry for the wait.
Come on, let's go inside.
I've never really been to a place like this before...
Don't worry about it! Let's go!
How is t, Shouji-san?
I think it's super cute.
It's too embarrassing...
It's normal for a lady to wear luxurious garments, even in places where they won't be seen.
I'll go and find more cute things for you.
Here, please drink this while you wait.
Y-Yes...
It's bad manners to chug like that, but it can feel really good.
She's in the furthest dressing room.
A suite at the Prince Hokuyo Hotel. I reserved it for you.
Go there and wait for me.
I'm just going to get a taste of Princess Yuri.
I'm more interested in you.
How's this one?
What? A different one?
Rich ladies from distinguished families.
Making such a fuss in front of others...
Shopping for underwear without a care in the world.
Healthy and ripe for the plucking.
That dirtbag... if I remember correctly, he's the new school janitor!
Look at that weirdo...
Going into a dressing room together... It's too risky!
Anyone who sees us will know what we're-
Not like you'll care either way...
Hey, do you remember?
That first night.
No! Stop! No!
I'll always remember fucking you that night.
At he time I wondered... What's wrong with me?
No! Don't!
Even though I had finally decided I was ready to respond to his feelings...
The other students have filed complaints about this.
Did you think you could get away with this?
No way! No! No!
It's even harder now than it was before.
You didn't even check if the others dressing rooms were vacant, you pervert!
Don't you feel any shame!? Say somethi-
Look at the little slut who was screaming while getting fucked
in the school staff room trying to act dignified and embarrassed.
That's not what happened.
It's because you forced yourself on-
Don't! Please stop!
Anyway, what do you think of this shop?
This is a popular place for neighborhood brats to hang out.
Hey, didn't that guy we saw a second ago look pretty cool?
Anyway, doesn't this look ultra cute?
It's such a turn-on...
the smell of sweat from those girls in puberty is so invigorating.
What's with that pose?
No... Please stop already.
Forget about your engagement.
The only thing you have to worry about is my dick.
Please don't! At least leave my breasts alone!
Stop! That part is really sensitive.
Those fuckers... doing it in a place like this...
I you do it like that I'll... No!
Please stop rubbing it against me!
Stop!
I really feel it there!
You spouted so much today... That sex milk.
No! Don't say it!
It fits comfortably enough but...
it clings tightly like a glove,
and they look like wrapped presents that could fit in the palm of your hand.
And people could tell if I'm shaved or not.
This lace is so good...
I'll force the panties into you along with my dick.
No! If you try to push them together... It won't go in!
It went straight towards my womb!
Next, let's find some other-wear to go with it!
Sure, whatever.
Damn bitches. Hurry up and leave already!
Yeah, I heard about that! What an ultra-obliviously loser!
I thought I heard man's voice.
It's beating my insides like a drum!
And with my panties alongside it!
No! Please stop moving so much!
What's this? Aren't you Princess Yuri?
Huh?
Take it out! Please take it out!
Take what out?
That hard, thick, rock-solid... That dangerous thing!
Along with your panties, right!?
No!!
Don't worry. It'll be over soon.
My womb is getting rubbed raw!
It's just that good, isn't it?
Don't pretend you don't love this.
Your students would be amazed.
I can't help it! Your dick is too wonderful!
kaoruko-san, what are you doing in there!?
Yasuyuki-san!?
That's right Kaoruko-san, it's me.
I'm opening this door!
Wait! Don't!
If Yasuyuki-san finds out about this, your bosses, the school administrators will find out!
They'll be especially eager to fire the teacher in this case, right!?
You disgraceful whore!
But I feel ashamed!
I'm not a whore because I'm feeling shameful!
No! Don't force it all the way in!
Please not so hard!
Your dick! Don't!
Stop pushing your dick inside me!
My pussy! My pussy can't take it anymore!
P-Pussy?
Please, my pussy can't... It's going to get torn!
Don't do that!
This is getting dangerous! I'll get pregnant!
My womb... Pregnant!
If you get pregnant, your tits will get big and swollen, even if you don't want them to.
No! Don't do that! Don't push your dick directly towards my womb!
It's filling me up!
Don't do that! You can't!
Don't kiss my womb with your dick!
Don't! Something hot is going right into my womb!
My pussy! Semen is filling me up inside!
I'm cumming!
How did I end up like this!?
Why did you come to this place for commoners?
Princess, you're just ripe for plucking, aren't you?
A giant perv's dick is going to go into you.
This soft and fluffy underwear really makes your pussy look immature.
No! I don't want that!
Hurry and finish up already!
What could be the problem?
Mo! No! Don't!
I'm afraid of that hard, hot thing!
The gods are watching!
You won't be forgiven for this!
You're rocking back and forth down here...
Does your first dick make you feel that good?
D-Don't say such nasty things.
What you said isn't true!
No!
Are you pleasuring yourself with what's entwined in your panties?
I feel the warmth coming from your pussy!
Warmth!? That's not true!
I'm not the one moistening it!
Honestly, your dirty butt is probably also begging to be trained, eh?
My butt isn't dirty at all!
I'm telling you!
No! Don't!
Don't put that scary thing inside me!
Please don't do it! Don't put that stiff thing...
It feels so gross! It's burning hot!
Something warm is...
No, not there!
Stop! Anything but that!
Please, I beg you! Don't do it!
Please let me go!
Please, I'm begging you! Please release me!
No! Don't!
It's pushing... Don't tear it!
I have to protect that part until I get married no matter what!
Take it out! No! The big thing... take it out!
It's too big! No!
It tore...
Don't! Please stop moving!
My virgin hymen is getting destroyed!
No! Stop moving around! It hurts!
So good... This is my first time fucking a virgin in her school uniform.
No! It's swelling inside! Don't!
Don't cum! I'll get pregnant!
I'll get pregnant, so don't cum inside!
Please, let me go!
I don't... I don't want to be a pregnant!
Please let me go!
Don't come in so deep! Don't force it in so far!
No! I'm getting torn up!
Don't! So deep! So much...
No... It came out...
Something hot went inside me.
No...
The hot thing is spreading inside me and still...
No! It's still stiff!
Why...
You can't still be hard!
Please! That's enough, isn't it!?
No!!
Why is there still so much...
You came so much already and still...
Don't think that just two or three rounds will be enough for me.
You can't do this any more.
Please stop cumming... I'll really get pregnant!
The Princess is so stubborn...
After I came in Kaoruko-sensei, she shut up and did as she was told.
No! No! That can't be!
No! It's overflowing!
What a wild girl.
Even pretending she's disgusted by it...
No! That's not right! I'm not...
It's getting really big again!
Don't! Don't! It's hot!
It's coming out!
No!!
Even though you're ashamed, you know I'm right!
My opening down there is really sensitive!
No! It's so hard...
Amazing, it's so hard and hitting so deep... I can't take it!
What is?
It's your... your...
I asked you to say it clearly!
It's... It's your dick.
Don't! My ears are sensitive!
Say it again.
Dick! It's your dick!
How is it? Good, isn't it?
Yes, your hard dick is going so deep inside me...
It's so good... I'm scared!
If this keeps up I... I'll...
Are you going to cum, Princess?
I'll... I'll cum, I'm not sure but...
My nasty place... Something coming!
Rindou Female Academy
Midori?
You didn't know?
How did it happen?
She would never spend a single night away from home.
What did you just say, Sayuri-kun?
If you don't know, then I shouldn't say.
Please excuse me.
Midori spent a night away from home?
Don't tell me that medicine...
That bastard act to her as well!
What is it, you still upset about last night?
That's not it.
I won't toss you away, so don't worry.
I wasn't worried about anything like that!
It's so embarrassed! Don't!
Because you're my first woman...
I'll teach you the joy of being mine!
No!
I can't take it anymore...
Going so deep into me every single day...
Please don't ever tell Segawa about this!
No one else can hit me so deep inside...
Don't! If you push so deep into my womb like that I'll...
Kissing my womb... It's getting spread open!
My womb is getting...
It's going in so deep, there's no way I won't get pregnant!
I won't even know it, but I'll be a pregnant!
My womb! The dick is devouring my womb!
So much came out.
Even though he just came, it's still so hard.
Cumming inside me every day...
It feels wonderful.