Honor Students After School
Concealed Curiosity
Nice to meet you, I'm Izumi Yurako.
I hope to get along with you all.
With a chill personality of someone
from the countryside and simplicity
Izumi Yurako
she stole this heart of mine,
a stranger to love, at first sight.
I wanted closure for my hopeless feelings
but my life's first ever confession succeeded.
Please take care of me as well.
However, I failed to notice that while
still basking in my dreamy emotions...
That expression on Izumi-san's face...
Phew... Oh, Moriyama?
Oh, studying overtime on the teacher's
desk... Playing teacher or something?
Sh-Shut up, just go home
already! I can't focus here.
Yeah, I'm just getting something I left behind.
See ya!
Y-Yah...
What are you doing?
We would've been caught if they
went in from the front door!
Huh?
Moriyama-san, your dick says otherwise though.
Don't run away from me.
You can come in my mouth.
I-It's coming out!
This is bad!
It's so thick, just like jelly!
Storehouse
On the day of my confession,
we went on and ended up having sex.
Izumi-san, you see...
I never intended for a relationship
that's only physical...
The same goes for me.
This is even the first time that I had sex.
My friends back home talk about
nothing but sex all the time.
There isn't anything else to do there.
There even is someone who slept around.
Being someone who never had a boyfriend
made me sexually frustrated.
I got my first boyfriend which is you
after coming to this city.
Let's have lots of sex, alright?
Hey... I started to feel doing it.
Shall we have sex here?
I can't hold myself back anymore.
Can't we?
Please stop teasing me!
Wait, I have to lubricate it...
Whoa... It's sucking me in...
Izumi, there are people downstairs
so keep your voice down!
That's because you're hitting me
deep inside, Moriyama-san!
I'm coming already!
Yes, me too!
You got pretty horny, huh?
It still feels good even with a rubber,
but I prefer having it raw on my safe days.
Do they feel different for you?
That's right. It's like, more intimate.
It feels like the corona of your glans gets
caught in my vaginal creases and I like it.
Hey...
Should we go out somewhere
every once in a while?
Huh?
Oh... Even my balls...
You are right. Then...
We can, if you can make me come
until I'm satisfied using your dick.
How about that?
Can you even be satisfied?
I-I haven't even come more than twice in a row!
Moriyama-san, today is a safe day for me.
If we won't use a rubber,
you might be able to satisfy me faster!
It would feel great if we'll rub
skin-to-skin with all our fluids!
It should be fine as long as you come outside.
Your raw dick is pounding and
being sucked in a tight fit!
It's amazing!
I-I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
This is bad, It's gonna come out!
Sorry, I couldn't pull out in time!
Since you already came this much inside me,
we can now just enjoy raw sex
without any worries, right?
Now is my turn to stimulate you.
These tits have been the envy
of my friends, you know.
I have to get you up with this,
so that we can have sex even more.
Here, how is it?
Th-that's... well...
Stop it... first...
Stop... Coming...
I'm glad that you came a lot from that!
Practicing it for this day paid off!
Izumi, I can't stop myself anymore!
Come!
I'm coming!
Ah, wait!
I just came...
I still haven't had enough!
I'm coming again!
I've been coming all this time,
and yet I'm coming again!
I'm gonna come!
Shoot it out!
I want it in my womb!
Pour plenty of it inside!
Moriyama-san...
I never felt anything like that before...
That was so amazing...
I hope that I won't get pregnant from this...
So, where are we going today?
Ah...
Moriyama-san...
Today is a risky day for me.
What should we do?
Yes...
Essential Lesson for
An Honor Student
Oh, sensei... I've been waiting for you.
Please come in.
Pardon my intrusion.
Sensei, you got so hard down here!
Me too, I can't help but feel restless today!
Sensei, hurry up and undress!
Please let me suck your cock!
It all began on my first day as a private tutor.
Wh-What are you doing?
Just go along with me, please!
S-Stop, don't take it off...
Look, it already got like this... I'm putting it in!
You can't, that's...
I was reverse-raped by Hinamachi-san.
You already came?
Hinamachi-san, why would a girl like you...
A girl like me?
Do you think that a school for prim ladies
have nothing but prim ladies in it?
Everyone's just holding themselves back.
We can't help but want to try having sex,
but there aren't any boys around.
Compensated dating and
picking up guys are risky as well.
One little mistake and it'll impact our futures.
That's why I had this all set up.
You'll be the one in trouble if we get caught.
That's the position you're in right now.
I never needed a tutor in the first place,
so just forget about the lessons.
Just please be my boyfriend in times
that you're supposed to tutor me, okay?
I'm here again today,
doing this and teaching her the wrong things,
all according to her plan.
Sensei's thing is huge!
Sensei... The tip is your weak spot, right?
You can't come yet, sensei.
Look, it'll feel even better
if I do it this way next. Isn't that right?
Whoa... Her tits are amazing!
They're engulfing it!
They're so bouncy and enveloping me with her drool!
H-Hinamachi-san, I'm...
I'll be drinking your semen,
so you can come when you feel like it!
This is bad, I can't hold it in!
It sprayed all over...
There's a huge amount too...
Your semen is too thick, sensei...
I'll suck everything out, alright?
Did that feel good?
Th-That's enough already, sensei.
Does it not feel good?
No, it's just a little embarrassing...
Hurry up and put your dick in...
Mikage-san?
Mom?
I've been hearing some rustling
there. What's the matter?
I-I was just looking for a book...
Wait, sensei! Stop for a moment.
Not now...
Is that so? What about sensei?
He's looking for it right now...
I see... Don't give him much trouble.
Alright then, I'll be out shopping for a little while.
Sensei...
I'm glad to see you motivated at this.
I can't wait any longer, you know...
Right there, just like that...
The whole thing went inside!
Damn... It feels so good that I can't move!
Hey, come on! What's the matter, sensei?
Please hurry up and start moving!
Hinamachi-san, I've always
wondered about this...
Am I really your first?
That's right, how rude of you...
I'll bet that you've been looking at
stuff like porn videos and comics,
and jerking yourself off alone...
But I've been doing simulations for everything.
I've been masturbating every day,
and I've also been studying about
fellatio and sex in advance.
So it's no surprise that I'll do well on those.
Looks like you haven't studied
enough for this, sensei.
Sorry, I feel like I'm gonna come.
You're a pesky one.
I'll be on top.
You can just lie down like that, sensei.
I'll do the moving.
It sure hits me at a very good spot
when in cowgirl position!
I can't stop my hips from moving!
I-I'm already... Hinamachi-san!
No, you can't.
Please try holding it in a little longer!
I-I can't!
Sensei, you're coming!
You're spurting with such force!
Will it be alright? You just came raw
and creampied me, you know!
Just a little more...
Just a little more and I would've climaxed...
It's alright.
Please go ahead and come, sensei.
But don't get limp until I do!
Does it feel so good that it's driving you crazy?
Sensei, do your best! Sensei!
One more shot!
Creampie...
Give me a creampie!
My womb is bulging full of it...
It's overflowing.
Sensei, you did a great job...
Alright, our next appointment will be on Tuesday.
I'll see you again.
Oh, sensei...
I haven't told my mother about it yet
but our schedule will be thrice a week
from next week onwards.
I'm hoping for you to make proper
preparations for my review materials.
And another thing...
Please stop doing something like
that when my mother is nearby.
I won't be able to have sex
with you if we get caught.
I don't want that to happen, okay?
Only do it when my mother isn't around!
She might be twisted in many ways,
but she's an unexpectedly cute
and honest student, perhaps.
Kuwaga Tarou
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization