And then at the bus...
and then what?
What?
Look, it's The Squid.
He is...
Mr. Shibui.
Y, yes, what is it?
Two years in a row, you have the lowest rate
of graduate students making it in to the career field.
I'm doing the best I can...
if the results are the same again this
year, it won't be me you'll be talking too...
This time it'll be the dean talking to you.
You know what that means, right?
Well, do your best.
Also...
Can't you do something?
That coat.
I use a lot of chemicals during experiment so...
Mr. Shibui, you do realize students
have a funny nickname for you?
The Squid.
You do smell funny.
Please do the laundry from time to time.
Alright...
After Class Lesson.
Lesson 1
I'm sure that I've locked it.
It has to be one of the students.
Most likely after the test questions.
Probably.
Last one to leave was...
Mr. Shibui, did you notice anything happening?
N, no... nothing...
I see.
(Sign: Class 3-B)
Sorry, can you lend me your encyclopedia?
OK, hold on a second.
Thanks.
M, Ms. Tenkawa.
Yes?
W, what is it?
A, afterclass, can you please come to the lab?
OK...
I'm here.
Um, what is it? What do you want?
Looks like you are barely passing your classes...
Even science...
I will make it up on next week's test.
Besides, we don't need to practice for a
while, so I'll go home early to study.
You seem positive.
But of course, you're the one
who stole the test answers...
I admire your dedication, but a stupid move.
Once we realize that the test answer
are stolen, the test will get delayed.
Also, the questions will be changed.
W, where are you getting at?
I won't talk.
So...
You know, right?
Is that a threat?
That's fine, but I think you're asking for trouble.
I think this is settled, excuse me.
Let go, stop!
Someone, help!
I don't want to kill you...
There's no merit for the both of us then...
Right?
Look at me... c'mon.
No, not inside!
No!!!
A lot spilled out...
But still more inside...
I told you don't...
I didn't know what to do...
T, Teacher, are you a...
I'm sorry...
A, already!?
No!
Don't!
I am never satisfied!
Great..it's great!
L...l can't... going to... cum!
I came...
I had sex a few times, but this is my first orgasm...
Already...
Your mouth...
Huh?
Your mouth.
Alright.
Smells like a squid.
Stop that.
If you want, I'll have sex with you again.
If I'm bored.
Teacher, you don't have a girlfriend, right?
You probably have a hard time asking out a girl.
It's such a waste because you're so good.
Stuck at the same part, again.
I'm using my break time to help you
but you're still stuck at the same place.
I'm sorry.
Just try again.
Yes, understood.
(Sign: Akari Mizuno)
How may I help you?
Enjoy your stay.
Ms. Mizuno, pardon me.
Yes?
It's about your part.
(A Note: 6 P.M. Gym storage room)
Alright?
OK.
See you later.
Teacher!
What?
I only have 40 minutes to curfew.
Lets keep our clothes on then.
How is it?
You like it?
L, it's great, Mr. Higuchi!
Ayumi, what do you want to talk about?
I need your help, come.
What is it Ayumi?
Ayumi?
Mr. Shibui?
Ayumi, what's this about?
I told him I'll take care of him.
I want to try other girls.
Um, l...
still have work to do.
W, what do you want!?
Look at this.
If this goes around, both you
and Mr. Higuchi will be expelled.
Unlike the other girls here, you're not wealthy.
That's why you work part time
at a cafe to pay the tuitions.
Now, you don't want all your hard
work to be pointless, do you?
L, I'm sorry... l won't do it again so forgive me.
No need to apologize.
Mr. Shibui only wants you to do the
same thing as you did with Mr. Higuchi.
So, this is what Mr. Higuchi had for dessert...
Ms. Tenkawa, please get the face.
OK...
You had gym today, right?
You smell.
So much juice!
What a girl...
C'mon, say it.
I'm going to suck Mr. Shibui's big thing...
What's wrong?
It's almost like blowing on a flute.
Very good...
Looks like Mr. Higuchi trained you well.
But I know you can do better, show me.
Yes, that's great.
Wonderful!
I'm cuming!
Amazed? Isn't it amazing?
Ms. Tenkawa, Ms. Mizuno's expression has changed.
Are you getting this?
G, great... too great.
It doesn't feel good...
it's not...!
Hot... my body is burning!
Not there!
It's OK...
You're well lubed.
It might hurt a bit, but...!
Atight fit.
But now, I can unload everything inside!
No, it hurts!
Teacher, me too...
Alright, after this...
it's great, Teacher!
Great...great!