I'll clean you up.
Yasumi, the bus is coming soon.
I know.
We're off to school now.
– Come on, Yasumi, let's go.
– And right after having sex, they leave, just like that.
I'm currently taking time off from school
and am living on an island in the south.
Right now I'm living as a guest in this place,
helping out with chores and such.
But this small room I'm in
became our sex chamber in little under a week.
The Honor Student After School 1
What's the matter?
Why are you at our school?
The girl with the ponytail is Chitose
and she's my uncle's only daughter.
She's two years older than I am.
Here.
Oh, I forgot my lunch!
Sorry you had to come to give it to me.
No problem. It was on the way to the store.
Well, I'll see you later.
Wait!
Hey, you still got some time, right?
At a glance, she might look like she has
absolutely no interest in sexual things.
That's what everyone thinks.
U-Um...
Chitose-san?
I'm having second thoughts.
She's the one who initiated this relationship.
Where's the problem?
You want to cum, don't you?
But what if your boyfriend saw this?
Boyfriend?
I'm cumming!
I don't have a boyfriend.
Apparently being a couple on this island
came with a lot of obligations.
Even if you want to have sex,
it comes with the burden of having to date someone.
So I became the outlet for her sexual desires.
But even so, I was infatuated with her.
I-I'm cumming!
Chitose-san!
You cum too fast!
Geez.
And then, finally...
Hey, let's do it before Dad gets home.
Huh?
Oh, sorry. I'm out of condoms.
What should we do?
Fine. Let's just do it raw.
It was our first time doing it raw.
That feeling of her wrapping perfectly around me...
The feeling of being sucked in...
But you can't cum inside me, okay?
Pull out beforehand.
She says that, but...
She's holding me in tightly.
I can't pull out!
I need to pull it out! I'm about to cum inside her!
I let him cum inside me.
His semen's flowing inside me!
Wow, I came a lot.
After that, we did it raw on any day that was safe for her.
Um, pardon me...
It's so hot!
Were you two at it again?
You need to air this place out.
Th-They're doing it raw?!
Say, Yasumi...
You're not interested?
I thought you were really interested in sex.
I can't do it like you can, Chito-chan.
Why not? I'm sure that Mitsuru
wants to do it with you too, Yasumi.
I-It's just kind of embarrassing to be stared at.
Then how about you two do it tomorrow?
G-Geez.
She can't take no for an answer.
Yasumi-san is Chitose-san's friend
as well as a shy, but serious honor student.
That about sums her up.
Our physical relationship began just
a little after mine and Chitose-san's did.
Huh? Yasumi-san?
U-Um, good morning.
Sorry, Chito-chan has club activities today.
Oh, I see...
So, that being said...
Um...
Yes?
If you're okay with me, then...
I'm sure that you have a lot saved up right now.
Um...
If you don't mind my mouth, I can help you out.
The face she made completely turned
any assumptions I had of her on their heads.
She looked like she was thoroughly enjoying it.
Is this really her first time?
I love the smell of dick!
There's all this salty stuff, dribbling out.
Wait! I'm cumming!
Chitose-san has pretty big boobs, but...
Yasumi-san was in a league of her own.
Um, so...
I'm about an I-cup.
I think.
Yasumi-san became more and more aggressive.
I think she's just like Chitose-san
in that her lust was always strong.
I don't know if I'll be able to do this well or not.
I'll be taking a shower after this,
so you can just cum in between them.
O-Okay.
By "them", I mean my breasts.
It's twitching!
It's so cute!
Sh-She's wringing me dry!
It has such a strong smell!
I might not be able to get it off of me.
I never had sex with Yasumi-san,
but the three of us started to spend time together like this.
I love this position!
Can I kiss you?
S-Sure!
She's going that deep right off the bat?!
And she's being so rough!
Hey, Yasumi? How long are you gonna keep kissing him for?!
I want to kiss him too!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I thought I got it all, but there's still so much.
S-Sorry.
Well, it felt good, so that's fine.
What about you, Yasumi? Wanna have sex?
N-No.
Huh?!
You just masturbated so hard,
what's there to be embarrassed about?!
Huh? Well...
Mitsuru-san?
Do you want to have sex?
Do you want to... have sex with me?
Are you sure?
Yes. It's okay to do it raw.
Any guilt or doubt I had
flew away with my reasoning and logic.
Ah, sorry. Does it hurt?
N-No.
I only made a noise because it felt so good.
That day, I fucked her for as long as I could.
It might've been her first time,
but she made it feel like it wasn't.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Yeah, this face is without a doubt the face of a sex addict.
Hey, Yasumi, are you trying to skip school?
I-I'll be right there!
I-I'll see you after school.
– It's my turn tonight.
– I-It's going to be a pretty busy summer vacation.
– Huh? B-But...
Chitose-san liked doing it outside.
Chitose-san, you need to keep it down.
I-It'll be fine.
Nobody comes here at this time.
Even though we're having sex out here,
I found out that this is what turns her on.
I-I'm cumming!
Even when her father was around...
Chitose, help Mitsuru-kun clean up the guest room.
Okay.
We don't have much time!
You can cum whenever you want.
Good morning.
These kinds of days weren't rare at all either.
You can just stay still.
I'll make you feel good!
Chitose-san was really good at the cowgirl position.
She moved her hips so well and my tip
would brush against the entrance to her womb.
I'm cumming!
I came inside her again!
It looks like you came a lot again.
Did it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
It felt good for me too.
But even after we started our new relationship,
Yasumi-san was still shy.
She wasn't anywhere near
as aggressive as Chitose-san.
But you could tell from her behavior.
Um...
Once her switch got flipped...
Crap...
She gets really turned on.
She takes deep breaths,
thoroughly licks the bottom of my balls,
and just keeps doing that kind of fellatio for a long time.
And then she keeps playing with me
until I'm about to burst with cum.
Shoot it on my face!
Please!
And then after that,
she gets really wet from just sucking me off,
so I take her from behind just how she likes it.
I ram into her buoyant ass over and over again.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I had to return to the mainland
for a few days, so when I came back...
We went to a rest area in a park
that not many people went to.
I'll be back in the morning.
Take care of the place while I'm gone.
We had sex every day,
but I couldn't bring myself to stop.
We might have gone a little overboard.
Mitsuru-san...
Come on, Yasumi, let's get in the shower together.
Okay.
But there was no way that we
could continue doing that forever.
You have an unread message
Close   View
I had to face reality.
We were thinking about going
to the mainland for school next year.
We could share a room and it'd
be fun to have new experiences.
And we'd like to see what life's like off this island.
Yeah.
If they stayed with me forever though...
Let's go back...
So, we decided together.
If you're okay with it, then...
~ 1 Year Later ~
Chito-chan, you're gonna be late!
Wait!
Just a little more!
Mitsuru-san has work too, you can't keep him here.
What about you?
Didn't you stay up late with him last night too?
W-Well...
Oh, crap! I'm really gonna be late!
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
Okay, see you later!
It's my turn when we get back!
Huh? I don't think so!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч