I'll clean you up.
Yasumi, the bus will be here soon.
Yeah...
Alright, we'll be off to school now.
Hey Yasumi, let's go.
They went as is right after we had sex again.
O-Okay!
I'm currently off from school due to a certain circumstance.
At an island of a southwestern archipelago,
I am staying for free while helping
at my uncle's lodging business.
The 6-tatami wide room I'm occupying
became my sex den with those two after just a week.
Honor Students After School
①
What's the matter?
You came in my school all of a sudden.
This girl with a ponytail is Chitose-san. She's my uncle's only daughter.
She's two years older than me.
Here.
So, I forgot my lunch!
I'm sorry, you had to bring it all the way here.
It's fine, I'm about to go shopping anyways.
I'll be on my way then.
Wait!
Hey... You still have some time to spare, right?
At first glance, she's a typical pretty student
that isn't involved with indecent stuffs.
Or so it seems...
H-Hey...
Chitose-san...
I think doing it in a place like this is...
She's the one who started this kind of relationship.
Isn't it fine?
Aren't you about to shoot your sperm out?
But... If someone sees us, like your boyfriend...
Boyfriend?
I'm gonna come already!
I don't have a boyfriend.
Seems that having relationships in this island
have some inconveniences tied with it.
And even if she want to have sex,
going out with a man is a bother.
I ended up becoming the outlet
of her pent-up lust.
Despite all that, I was so into my relationship with her.
I'm going to come already!
Chitose-san, I'm coming!
You came too quick! Jeez...
And then, finally...
Hey, let's do it before my father gets home.
Huh?
S-Sorry, we ran out of rubbers.
What should we do?
It's alright. Let's do it raw like this.
Eh?!
We did it raw for the first time.
This sensation of having a perfect fit...
She's sucking me down there!
You can't come inside, okay?
You should come outside!
Even if you say that...
I won't be able to pull it out if you're holding me tightly.
I have to hurry... or else I'll end up... coming inside!
I let him come inside me...
His semen is pouring into me!
Wow... I came an incredible amount!
After that, we started to do it raw on her safe days.
Umm... Pardon my intrusion—
Whoa, it's hot!
Have you been at it again? You have to ventilate the room...
Th-They're doing it raw!
Kawahira Park Station
Hey Yasumi...
Won't you do it?
Weren't you so interested about sex?
I can't do it like you, Chito-chan.
Why not? I'm pretty sure that
Mitsuru want to do it with you.
I guess because being watched
is embarrassing after all...
Then, I'll give you two some time together tomorrow.
J-Jeez!
Don't rub them too hard!
Yasumi-san is Chitose-san's friend.
She looks like a demure and
hardworking honor student.
Her carnal relationship with me won't be
until some time after Chitose-san's.
Huh, what? Yasumi-san?
Umm... Good morning.
I'm sorry, Chito-chan has club activities today...
Oh, Is that so...
And, you see...
Well...
O-Okay...
If you are fine with me...
If you feel that you're getting bottled up...
See...
If it's just my mouth,
I can help you with it.
It really betrays her pure image.
Making a face like she's in a trance,
showing how she actually loves cock.
Giving a sticky blowjob in a way to savor it.
Is it really her first time?
I love the scent of his cock!
There's something salty and gooey coming out.
This is bad... I'm coming!
Chitose-san has huge boobs as well,
but Yasumi-san is way even more well-endowed.
Umm... Well...
I think I'm somewhere like I-cup... for now...
Yasumi-san is becoming more and more bold.
I think she already had a high sex drive
in the first place just like Chitose-san.
I'm not sure if I can do this well...
I'll take a bath after this,
so you can shoot it inside.
O-Okay.
Oh... When I said inside,
I meant between my tits, okay?
It's twitching, how cute!
Sh-She's squeezing me dry!
It smells incredibly strong!
The odor is going to stick onto my body...
Even though I wasn't able to have sex with Yasumi-san,
These activities of us three escalated.
Doing it in cowgirl position really is the best!
I-Is it okay for me to kiss you?
Y-Yeah...
She suddenly started with a deep kiss?
And she's doing it intensely!
Hey, Yasumi! How long are you gonna kiss him?
I want to do it too!
Coming... Coming... Coming...
I'm coming—!
I already wiped it but it's oozing out again.
I-I'm sorry...
Well, it felt good so it's fine.
Yasumi, you haven't had your first sex yet?
Y-Yeah...
Huh?! You're even fingering yourself intensely like that.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about now!
Huh? That was...
Umm... Mitsuru-san...
Do you want to do it with me?
I mean... sex...
I-Is it alright?
Yes... I'm alright with doing it raw.
The guilt that I felt in the beginning
got blown away together with my reasoning in no time.
Ah... I'm sorry. Does it hurt?
N-No...
You see, my voice... just leaked out
because of the pleasure.
On that day, we indulged in sex for as long as we could.
Although I'm fucking her clumsily,
She's indulging in pleasure beyond expectation.
Good!
I'm coming!
Oh... This surely is a face of someone addicted to sex!
Hey there, Yasumi! Are you planning to skip classes?
I-I'll be right there!
Well then, let's do it again after school...
It's my turn tonight!
Things will escalate again...
Huh? But...
It will be a very busy summer break...
Chitose-san loves outdoor sex.
Chitose-san, your voice is too loud!
I-It's alright!
No one's coming here at this time of the day.
Although we're having sex in these thickets,
I know that she's aroused from her vaginal spasms.
I-It's coming out!
Even at times when uncle is home.
Chitose, help Mitsuru-kun with
cleaning up of the guest room.
Okay!
We don't have much time...
So you can come anytime you feel so!
Good morning.
Being woken up this way became a usual thing.
You can just stay still.
I'll make you feel good!
Chitose-san is good at fucking in cowgirl position.
Her hip movements are so astounding
that the tip of my cock pokes
her cervix with on her every hump.
I'm coming!
I'll come inside her again...
Looks like you came a lot.
Did it feel good for you?
Y-Yeah...
It did for me as well.
After doing it once with me, Yasumi-san still is bashful.
She isn't as assertive as Chitose-san.
...or so it seems.
Umm...
Once she gets turned on...
This is bad!
Maybe she gets aroused from the smell.
She takes a deep breath on it every so often.
She gives the back of my balls
a sticky slurping until they're swollen.
She takes her time slowly giving a blowjob,
until my sperm is on the verge of blowing out.
Please spray your sperm all over my face!
And afterwards,
with her dripping wet down there
just from giving me a blowjob
I give it to her in doggy style that she loves.
I used her bouncy ass like a trampoline to hump over and over to screw her.
I'm going to come!
Coming, coming!
I had some errand off the island.
And when I went back after a few days...
Without further ado, they took me
to a secluded lounge at the park.
Alright, I'll come again tomorrow morning.
I'll leave the lodging under your care.
My everyday life has been like this,
but I can't stop having sex with both of them.
I might have done it a little too much...
Mitsuru-san, I love you...
Hey there, Yasumi. We'll take a shower together.
Yay...
But I know that this won't last forever.
You have 91 new messages.
Close
Display
I have to go back to my life that's not in here.
You see, the two of us are aiming
to go in a university at the mainland.
We two can share a room. We want
to experience a bunch of stuffs as well...
We also want to go out of this island, right?
And the both of them
can't stay with me forever...
Is that so... It's about time for me to go home...
And you see, we both have decided...
That is only if you're okay with it...
Huh?
1 Year Later
Chito-chan, we're going to be late!
Wait! Just a little more!
Jeez, Mitsuru-san has to go to work.
You shouldn't overdo it with him.
But Yasumi, didn't you enjoy
yourself a lot last night as well?
Th-That was...
We'll be late for the first period!
That's what I told you!
Well then, we'll be going!
We'll be on our way!
It'll be my turn when we get home!
Huh, just wait! I'm not done yet!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization