Please stop.
No, stop it.
Not here...
Stop it. Please stop it.
This is my husband's bedroom.
Seriously...
l seriously beg you.
What are you saying now?
You were shaking your hips and panting like crazy before.
You were loving it with that fake gang rape too, weren't you?
Please don't say that. That wasn't me. lt was...
Please don't make me laugh, ma'am.
Huh? What are you saying?
All the men in the country that watched the video have been getting...
...hard-ons from the scene of you moaning.
And now you're saying that it's not you. l'm dumbfounded.
Oh no...
Ma'am, if you're saying that you can't do it, then your daughter...
What was her name?
Not Mai!
Ah yeah, her. Mai.
Mai, Mai...
We will have to cast her to fill the hole you make.
Please, not that!
l will do anything, so please...
Can't you do it any better?
Don't scrape with your teeth.
You've done this to your husband who's dying in the hospital, right?
Stop it. Don't say that.
Oh, really?
So your husband has never experienced the taste of your mouth.
That's too bad.
Then l'll enjoy the experience in his place.
Shut up and swallow it to the back of your throat.
Ma'am...
lf you keep on being uncooperative...
...we'll have to do something in exchange.
For example, kidnapping your daughter...
l'll do it! l'll do it!
So please don't say something like that ever again!
Then for the time being, let's have you do as l say.
First, let's see...
Lick the back of my penis with your tongue.
Am l going to have to train you from the beginning?
You were panting so much l thought you would at least be decent, but...
How long are you going to keep doing the same thing?
First collect some saliva in your mouth.
Come on, open your mouth and make sure l can see.
Then drip that on to my penis.
Spread it all around, and once my penis gets slimy, rub it gently.
ls this good?
Please hurry and start.
Grab it firmly and stroke it well.
Darling... Mai...
Even if you make a face like that, it won't be over until it's out.
Now please put it in your mouth.
Come on, hurry.
Put it in your mouth as if the tip would hit your throat...
...and then move it inside your mouth.
Yes.
Here it comes.
Darling...
My mouth is being violated by Mr. Kagami...
...someone other than you...
...and l'm playing with myself.
Mr. Kagami's penis is getting bigger, and...
...you can tell that the thick, white stuff is going to come out.
l-lt's going to come.
lf that much pre-cum comes out...
...the movement of my hand on my crotch will get faster.
l-l'm going to come...
l'm going to come! l'm going to come!
l'm going to come! l'm going to come! l'm going to come!
Don't spit it out! Swallow it!
Listen carefully.
lf you mix it with saliva, you can swallow it.
That's common sense for people like you who sell their body for money.
You should learn it.
A poor student that cannot even do something like this must be punished.
lf you don't become a complete product soon...
...l'm going to go bankrupt too.
Please think of this as an action out of love and work hard.
Wait a second!
Please stop!
You said that once you came you would leave!
Ma'am, you think l didn't notice that your crotch is feeling hot?
Do you want to move or would you rather be forcefully violated?
Mother...
Ma'am, if your crotch got hot before, doesn't that mean you want it?
Maybe you want me to stir it all up inside you.
Please hurry up and drop your hips right on to it.
l don't have that much time on my hands.
l guess l have no choice.
This is a service.
Come on, ma'am, you can't rest.
You have to shake your hips yourself.
lt hurts! lt hurts! lt hurts!
My breasts are being violated, and it hurts!
Don't violate my breasts!
Mr. Kagami is... Mr. Kagami is...
Ma'am, your nipples are pink.
l guess it's because you haven't had a child.
Don't say that. l have a child.
Mai is my child.
l wanted to breast-feed her because l'm her mother.
l need to protect her.
While Darling is gone, l need to protect Mai.
So that's why l'm going to shake my hips and protect her.
That's why l need to grind my crotch and...
...protect her!
l'm being pounded by someone other than you, Darling.
A raw penis...
l'm so dirty, so dirty...
l'm wailing to Mr. Kagami's penis.
l'm going crazy.
l'm making a face of good sensations.
While teasing my clitoris, l'm raking it up.
No, no, you can't! You shouldn't!
You can't pound me all the way in the back.
Even though you say no, as long as you're moving your hips...
...you're not fooling anyone.
lf l finger my clitoris when it's enlarged, it feels so good.
lf l finger my clitoris with your penis in me...
Why?
What's wrong?
l'm saying we're done for the day. ls there some kind of problem?
No, but l haven't...
What is it?
Well...
Do you mean you haven't come yet, so you want to do it more?
Your husband's been hospitalized long term, so it's been a while, huh?
l'm not doing this as a volunteer to get rid of your sexual desires.
Really, the one who has to return that is you.
You thought l didn't catch on to it even though you lost it that much?
Maybe you should hurry up and say, ''Please violate me.''
''Please violate me.''
The drought deep inside your uterus won't stop.
Penis...
No... A penis... No...
l can't...
Could you hurry up?
Do you want me to put it in or not?
lt's not like that. Darling, l...
Mr. Kagami, please!
Please what?
So what do you want me to do?
Please put it in me.
l want to continue on with the sex.
You should have said that from the beginning.
No, no!
Not so much!
Not that deep, no, no!
No, no, no, you can't dig that deep!
No, no, no!
No, l can't anymore!
lt's being jammed in.
His penis is being jammed in.
lt's being jammed in!
l'm vulgar.
So vulgar!
l'm becoming despicable with Mr. Kagami's penis!
Love juice is coming out, and urine is pouring out!
lt's my pussy! My whole body is a pussy!
l'm becoming a pussy!
l'm going to come.
With this fat penis...
With Mr. Kagami's fat penis!
No, no! Like this... l'm a sexual pervert...
l've become a pervert.
What should l do? l'm a pervert!
Darling, Mai, l'm sorry.
l'm sorry.
l'm really sorry.
l've become too tainted.
But, but...
lt feels good, so it's fine.
lt's fine now, right? l did my best, right?
l resisted well, right?
Right?
lt's fine, right?
lt's fine, right? lt's fine, right?
Semen...
lt's all in. l'm coming... l'm coming...
l was able to do it.
You dirty bastard!
Could you stop?
This is part of the deal with her. Your mother's payment contract.
You still say that? Even though you gave a threat like that?
You were listening? lf so, then could you let go with that hand?
What!
Your mother is trying really hard to repay the debt for you and your father.
A student who cannot do anything should just sit there and moan.
With a bogus debt...
lt may be bogus, but the contract for 20 adult videos is valid.
And today was to decrease the contract by 2. Your mother agreed.
First of all, if you can't borrow money from a place like ours...
...that's what people call no-good human beings.
But your father, who makes his own wife do this sort of thing...
...is the worst no-good human being.
Shut up!
They're desperately trying to protect you, a child from a former marriage...
...and l think it's lovely family love, but...
...unfortunately, it seems as they're a little slow in the head.
Don't say another word!
And are we able to trust that guy's word?
ln a situation like that, l don't think anyone could tell a lie.
That's true. They're pros after all.
Okay, we'll drag her out to the office tomorrow.
Roger.
l'm sorry to make you wait.
You call me over here and make me wait.
That's a strange idea of common sense.
l'm very sorry. We're also busy.
That shouldn't apply to me. l'm busy too.
Even though it's better than you guys coming to my house every day.
Oh, so you didn't actually want us to be there.
l thought you were purposely unwilling to return the payment.
ls there something wrong with your head?
Whatever.
Regardless of what you do, l can't pay, so if it comes down to it...
What is it?
Filing of personal bankruptcy.
Apparently there are a lot these days.
Lawyers will discuss it with you. Plus l hear filing paperwork is easy.
That's no good.
Well, that's what it is, so bye.
Oh yeah, l'm not saying l'm not going to repay.
Once l make some money, l'm going to pay.
So pray that l get a winning horse-race ticket.
l don't think it'll be too late to go home even if you look at these.
What, is there something else?
T-This is...
''They who hide will be found,'' l guess.
To tell you the truth, these girls' DVDs are going to cover your debt...
...so we actually don't need you to pay it.
Why did you...
You know him, right?
He just wouldn't tell us, so it was hard.
ls that you, Kido? Please help me. lt's all my fault. l beg of you.
This guy thinks that you are making us do this.
He really dislikes you, doesn't he?
He brought this upon himself.
How blunt.
Well, we don't care about a guy like this either.
Let's get into the main topic of discussion.
Miss Ayane, you are such a strange person.
Shut up. lf we're going to do this, make it quick!
l'm sure you know that it's not going to end with just this one time, right?
Just hurry it up!
Come on, do it properly. lt's been a while.
Carefully lick mine too. All the way to the back of my balls.
Stop being greedy. l won't run away or anything, you rotting dicks.
You guys stink so much.
This chick... unexpectedly...
Well, well, you guys are too fast. You're not half of what you claim to be.
You want me to do it with my mouth.
lt's special service, so you better enjoy it to the fullest.
Every last one of you is so thick.
lt's way too thick.
Have you guys been holding it in too much?
Well, because you guys come so fast, you most likely don't get any.
lf you want to do it with me, you have to make me come with foreplay.
Lick my clitoris up more.
Are the crotch of my toes delicious?
lf you want, l can use these slimy toes to rub your dick for you.
Tease my breasts with rhythm!
lt seems as if you're enjoying it a lot.
Because...
...if not, it's too harsh.
You perverts...
You guys are the lowest.
Whatever. l don't care anymore. So just enjoy it!
Amazing... This woman's amazing.
l'm sure her husband is enjoying it a lot too.
She uses her tongue to the fullest extent.
The soft walls come all the way to the root. l'm going to come again.
My pussy... My pussy feels so good!
Next, hurry and let me do it.
W-Wait till my orgasm calms down a little.
Then to the upper hole...
W-Wait, time out!
lt's too late. lt's in all the way to the root!
l'll pound you so much and make you come!
Sister, you're saying that, but you can't wait either, can you!
lt's aching! lt's aching, so if l come like this...
...l won't be able to go back!
You just said that you wanted to be violated!
Violate me, violate me!
Your ass is amazing! lt's so moist.
Pound me faster. l want to come gaudily and vulgarly!
lt's become sensitive.
lf it's in my butt, it has become sensitive too.
Move! Move faster!
Grope the back of my uterus!
You pervs!
You don't even know how to thrust properly!
Pervs! You perverts!
l'm a pervert!
That's right, sister, we are all perverts!
l'm coming gaudily!
lt's fine that you're protecting your own students, but...
...l want to know why both of you are putting others before yourselves.
Your students wanted it disposed of without you knowing.
They said, ''Please help me,'' and this is what happened.
Look here, it's my pussy that you've been dreaming of.
You want to put it in?
But you can't. l'm doing this to make you suffer.
lt's becoming hard. lt's hard, so hard and warm... lt's pretty good.
Here's some nectar. Why don't you suck it?
l'm a person with a big heart for dealing with scum like you.
l'm getting really excited.
l'm going to come because l'm a pervert.
You're welcome to go home now.
l thought it would take longer.
Would you like to be violated more?
Are you an idiot? Of course l'm going to refuse that offer.
Kido
l'm home.
Sorry l was a little late.
No!
Each and every one of them...
Each and every one of them, was it?
They don't even have the toughness to go through with being a good man...
...but they like to act pretentious about it.
Mr. Kagami, you are quite the humanist, aren't you?
lf you keep saying more than you need to, you'll end up the same.
The position that you're in isn't much different from them.
Yes, l know.
But when l saw your eyes just now, l got the urge for a kiss.
You don't understand, do you?
Other than that, are you taking care of the matter of Mizaki's husband?
Yes...
Hey, Mr. Kagami, instead of giving head, please kiss me.
Come on, please...