Brother, how did you find a chick like this?
Ayane Kido
Well...
...she was a blank-looking chick always staring into space...
...so l kept my eye on her.
So let's have her pussy.
Her breasts are big, and l can't resist. She's most likely been around a lot.
Then l will have the upper.
So you set it up as l told you?
Of course, have l ever missed anything?
Well, l'll approve of that.
But l don't know about your regular occupation as a nurse.
Hey!
Don't pounce on me.
Um...
l have no business with you.
Why don't you just leave already?
Master Kagami...
l can't change the patient's dosage if it will lead to death.
Something like that is not going to get out in the open...
...and even if it did, you can blame all of it on her.
But theoretically speaking...
You join forces with a drug manufacturing company and...
...in exchange, dispose of the stock of dangerous blood products.
A person doing something like that speaks of theoretical things?
That was because you!
Poor thing.
Darling, other people's penises are lovely too, but...
...l want to put yours inside me.
Mr. Kagami, maybe she's gone crazy.
Mr. Kagami!
With your husband being put in this situation...
...l'm sure it's causing him pain to see you go through all this.
l'm sure he himself would want to...
Oh, l shouldn't say anything indecent.
lt seems as if you didn't repay the interest last week...
...so l deliberately came, but let's not count today.
Well, l'll come again.
lt's not like that. l just...
Mr. Kagami, my breasts...
Not down there either. l didn't take a bath yesterday.
No, not like this...
Ouch, l don't want anything that hurts.
Stop...
Stop, not my breast!
lt's going to break.
No, it's become stiff.
lt squirted out like a penis.
My nipples are standing up...
They're stiff like a penis.
No, no, not my breasts!
No...
l'm not being led on.
lt's just that my husband can't do anything anymore.
Dirty... l've become dirty...
No, not there!
Don't touch my anal hole!
l've never done anything with that hole yet.
No!
Please forgive me...
l-l don't... l don't want to...
...with my anal hole...
l'm going to come.
Mr. Kagami, please do that to me more.
lf you don't do that to me...
l'm scared. My body is itching.
My husband is like that, and l...
lf it doesn't go in, it's going to stop.
l know that.
l'm already a beast.
Don't take it out!
Violate me...
Please violate me.
l beg of you.
Huh? l can't hear you.
Say it one more time.
Please violate me.
What?
l can't hear you. Say it in a louder voice!
Please, please violate me!
l beg of you!
lt's in me.
lt's all the way inside me.
lt's...
lt's this...
Amazing...
l've become sensitive...
Why?
ls it because so many men fingered...
...pounded, and continuously violated me?
l've become a horny woman that can only think of sex.
lt's because of you, Mr. Kagami.
Next, in my anal hole... ln my anal hole, please.
Violate my anal hole.
Please grind into it!
Please move it faster...
l've already...
...forgotten about my husband.
l'm not thinking of anything but sex.
l'm speaking honestly.
l'm really speaking honestly!
Please pound faster and harder!
l can feel it so much more.
When my butt is being plugged, it becomes so sensitive.
Mr. Kagami, my anus...
My anus...
Please mess up my anus!
lt's going to be messed up!
lt came out!
lt's not interesting. Whatever...
l'm sure l'm more interesting and...
...a better woman, l think.
Give me back my mother.
She didn't seem like she wanted to leave...
...so that's why we're taking care of her.
Don't be ridiculous!
l guess l have no choice. Please look at this.
Your penis got big.
lt's expanding. The penis is expanding.
Penis shower... lt's so warm...
Delicious.
l don't mind giving you back your mother.
The present principal would make the repayment to do so.
Really?
lf l do what you tell me, you'll clear out the debt...
...and give me back my mother?
Yes, that's no problem.
lf she's lost it like that, there's no value anymore.
Don't say that!
Don't say that. Please...
l'll do what you say...
ls that so?
l hope you let me enjoy it in different ways.
Mai, l guess you're more perverted than l thought.
Even though l'm rubbing your breasts like this, you're able to stay calm.
lt's not like that. lt's for Mother, so l have no choice.
l don't want to hear any excuses.
Let's leave that aside, and with that tongue of yours...
...l want you to stick to the lower part of me.
l don't want to.
Just do what l tell you to do.
l get tired of playing around with piss-smelling brats like you.
His penis...
lt's getting bigger...
Getting bigger...
Come on, don't make me tell you the same thing l told your mother.
lf you mix it with saliva, you can swallow it.
This is common sense, so you should learn it.
lt stinks.
The smell is going to stick to it.
lt's won't go away even if l bring the uniform to the cleaners.
This is enough, right?
That should be enough. Are you satisfied?
That's also how your mother was deceived.
Even though you're not blood-related, in that field you're both the same.
No!
So, shall we get started?
l beg of you, please stop. Please stop!
Don't touch me!
Stop it!
Mai, you're an honor student, so you feel it, right?
You're most likely a virgin, right? We'll check for you.
This feels... She is definitely a virgin. That makes me happy.
Stop it! lt stinks, and it's dirty!
You can eat mine too.
Your hymen is totally exposed. How embarrassing.
We're happy to be able to have the virginity of a cute girl like you, Mai.
You can't keep your eyes shut. Open them up.
Okay, it's time for the piercing.
Look, it's going in more and more.
My dirty man-root is going into Mai's beautiful pussy.
Let go! Stop it! No!
lt hurts!
Stop it! lt's going to split!
The dirty penis is inside me!
Mai, how courageous for your mother.
But that mother is cold-hearted, huh?
Mai, every time l thrust into you, juices overflow.
Are you sure it's your first time?
l know, right? lt's soaked all the way inside.
lt's good, isn't it?
Don't say such a thing.
Don't you feel bad for Mai?
She wouldn't know if it's true or not.
l will check for you.
Hey, Mai, you're soaked.
You weren't really a virgin, huh?
lt hurts.
lt hurts!
l'm really a virgin...
...so please stop doing things like this!
l'm about to come, Mai.
Wait, stop it.
No, it stinks...
lf l do something like this, l can't show my face to Marimo anymore.
lt's okay. lt's okay.
We'll love you for the rest of your life in place of Marimo.
lt stinks. My hair is all sticky!
Well, maybe l should come in your lower lips soon.
No!
l'll get pregnant!
No, it's getting bigger.
Your penis is getting bigger!
Mai, you're so soaked.
Were our dicks that good?
lt was good. More please...
But wetting your pants like that... We need your mother to scold you.
So ''Mother,'' please scold her.
Yes.
What, no!
P-Please stop, Mother!
What?
Mai, you're the same as me and have become perverted.
No, it's not like that...
You don't have to hold it in anymore.
You can behave like a spoiled child as much as you want to, Mommy.
Mother...
Ah, it's wet.
No, please stop it.
lt feels too good, so stop it.
Then you want me to stop?
Don't stop!
Mother, please stop. lt's going to break.
l'm going to overflow!
Mother...
Please, not there...
Please...
Stop!
lt hurts!
l got my anal virginity taken by my mother!
Does my penis feel good?
Does it?
Feel good? There's no way...
lt's good... lt's good, Mother...
Right there, it's good...
My butt hole is rubbing against Mother's penis.
lt's amazing!
Mother's penis is amazing!
More, more!
Director, Miss Ayane and Mr. Mizaki died due to a medical error!
My life is over...
What do you want?
How unkind, Mr. Kagami.
Miss Ayane and Miss Shoko's husband died.
Really?
Or actually, l purposely messed up the medication dosage.
So the hospital is in complete chaos right now.
lf the medical error reaches the mass media, it'd be a fatal blow.
Whatever it is, we can always find another money lure later.
Because of your work up to now, l will clear your debt.
Go wherever the hell you want to go.
l don't care anymore. See you, Mr. Kagami.
You're not the Mr. Kagami l loved anymore.
Goodbye.
lt hurts...
What is this?
Why do l have to have something like this happen to me?
Stop playing dumb!
Apparently you're the one who killed our easy mark, Ayane.
We broke ten fingers of this guy named Mitsuoka, and he spit it out easily.
No, stop it!
lt's not going to end just yet, Madoka.
And let's introduce you to the special guest...
lt's Mai!
No...
Stop it. lf you put something like that in, l'll die.
Please, stop it. Don't do it.
l was threatened by Mr. Kagami too.
Die and apologize to my father!
Stop it!
She's dead.
l avenged you, Father.