Hump Bang!
Please pour lots of cum inside the lewd and naughty me...!!
I wonder how married life feels like?
What?
Try to be serious for a bit!
And why should I?
If I end up together with you someday,
I wonder what my position would be.
Wouldn't it be just like yesterday?
Don't worry.
Even if you don't become my wife, you'll still be my
What? What did you say?
By the way, Hiro.
Wh-What?
It's already 11 P.M...
...so aren't you going to masturbate?
Like hell I will!!
Oh, really?
Then I'll be helping myself.
Wait wait wait!
What's the matter?
Keep the show to yourself!
But, there's porn material right in front of me.
Are you referring to me as the porn material?!
So just pull your shirt up and show me your breasts.
I'll just cum here even without you...
I'll really smack you...
But Hiro, you also use me as porn material...
Ah, but even your face is sexy enough for me to get off.
W-Wait...
You really plan on jerking off that way?
D-Didn't we have lots of sex yesterday?
B-Besides,
if both of us are to masturbate together,
then it'll be better if we just have full blown sex instead.
Not at all.
Masturbation and sex are two different things.
No way.
If you don't want to show it, then so be it.
I'll just play with my imagination.
Oh! You're about to be humiliated in a private place.
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop that deluded fantasy!
It seems I can't stop this fantasy.
Everybody who laid their eyes upon Hiro,
have a rock solid hard-on.
Eh? Th-There are many of them?
Now,
from this point on, you are now in our hands.
I'll go first then. Starting from your pussy...
No...
Then, I'll go for her mouth.
She can also do a titty fuck, right?
Oh look, seems like she has come to terms
with what's happening to her.
No...
Hey now, you don't have time to rest.
No rest for your mouth, too.
We are gonna drown you from head to toe in our sticky cum.
Now, up next is your but thole.
No!!
I'll show my breasts already, so let me be...
Don't let them hurt me!
You're saying that,
but you're already wet, right?
You pricky masochist!
D-Don't pull!
Just quietly concentrate on your masturbation.
So, how is it already?
It's wet...
Say how wet it is!
My panties are drenched to the point,
that it has started to run down my legs now.
Okay, Hiro.
Expose your butt and position it right in front of me.
I'll spray it on you!
l-ls this okay?
Expose your butt more.
No, it will be seen from outside.
said expose it!
I-I said no!
Look at how wet it is, Hiro.
Geez... What a lewd butt!
Shake your butt.
Shake it more!
Don't slap my butt!
Okay, here I come.
No, wait! Don't cum yet.
I'm coming to your room,
I'm cumming!
Who told you to take a mouthful of my dick?
Drinking it all without even a single word...
Hiro!
Continue masturbating.
And suck my cock until you cum.
If you don't cum quickly,
someone will see you.
Because of you, my cock here is stiff again, you know?
What are you going to do about it?
Use my pussy next.
Okay, good girl.
Amazing!
Your cock feels good!
Your pussy is also getting better and better!
Here.
Try moving by yourself.
Shaking your hips at a place like this...
You pervert...!
Please, don't say that.
A few people might pass through here as well.
No, no!
Dad might enter the house from the back entrance.
No... we shouldn't!
Yes, we should!
Hiro is a masochist!
Slap it.
Please slap my ass more!
That's not how you ask for something.
Please strike my erotic butt more...
You're okay with just striking?
No, I'm not.
Then spit out more.
Please thrust your cock into my lewd pussy more.
Yes, yes!
Let's show the town how we do it.
No, no...
No, no!
We're clearly seen.
My breast, my pussy... Everything is clearly exposed.
It's really gripping me tightly.
I feel embarrassed, but it feels good.
Hiro!
You're the best slave bitch!
Thank you very much.
use my pussy any time you want.
Okay!
I'm about to cum!
Cum inside...
Please cum a lot inside me!
It's coming out!!
Hiro-chan! Good morning!
R-Rin! G-Good morning.
What's wrong, Hiro-chan?
Your face is all red.
It's nothing.
I'm alright.
Oh, no...
Rin...
Oh, a collar!
How stylish!
You look cool no matter what accessory you wear.
Good morning to you too, Kouji-kun!
You two are getting along well as always.
I'm on duty, so I'll be going ahead.
0-O-Okay......
She says it looks good on you, sex pig.
Thank you very much, Kouji-sama.
So you were getting aroused when Rin-chan saw you.
That's...
And we even did it a lot yesterday...
And now we can do it at school.
You're happy with that too, right?
That's...
Hey, call out Rin-chan.
Eh? Why!
I want to do it with Rin-chan.
You cant do that!
Rin already has a boyfriend!
Rin-chan seems easy to push around,
so it'll be okay.
You still can't!
You can't do it with other women!
Then move on your own and make me cum.
Oh, that feels good.
It's really cute when you're that obedient.
If you can call Rin-chan, I'll move on my own.
H-Hiro-chan?
You know,
to tell you the truth,
I just love this!
Being watched while having sex turns me on so much.
Please, watch us while we do it.
So it's okay to watch, right Hiro-chan?
Rin is watching!
This is embarrassing!
Hiro-chan, you're really erotic,
and really gorgeous at the same time.
Don't Rin...
That's my...
Rin-chan, you were aroused while watching
that erotic scene earlier, right?
Rin-chan seems to be a lewd cock lover.
You're wrong!
If I do this, Hiro-chan will feel happy.
I-I really don't want it,
but my eyes just can't stop looking.
You're fine with this right, Hiro-chan?
Rin is...
That Rin is sucking Kouji's cock...
Hiro, you just watch from there
how Rin and I do it.
Eh? No...
Well then, here I go.
You can't...
...go any further than this.
I have a boyfriend!
Rin, don't...
Your pussy wants it, and tries to pull it in.
You want it even if I just play around
with the tip like this, right?
Hiro-chan, it's just the tip, okay?
It won't go in further, okay?
It's entering!
But it's just the tip, okay?
Even if it's just inserted halfway, I feel it.
You're a real lewd bitch, eh?
The tip of the cock is entering me!
Kouji's cock is mine...
Kouji-kun, please enter no more than that...
Even if you say that,
you're pussy is trying to swallow me in.
It's entering...
Your entire cock is penetrating me!
Hiro-chan, I'm sorry.
I inserted it all the way in!
I inserted Kouji's cock into my pussy!
Her pussy feels too good!
This sensation is even better than Hiro's pussy...
I might snatch your boyfriend away.
Hiro, watch carefully.
If your pussy can't reach this fine caliber,
I won't thrust this in there.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
This, can't be...
I have a boyfriend.
This really shouldn't be done.
Hiro is watching.
This really shouldn't be done!
Kouji-kun, thrust in me more.
Ram that thing into me more violently!
Rin-chan, you're the best!
The school idol Rin!
To be a lewd pig,
that shakes her hips
for a cock that's not even her boyfriend's...
I'm sorry!
But...
Kouji's cock feels really good!
I am about to cum...
Hiro-chan... I'm sorry.
I'm going to cum with your boyfriend's cock.
Rin-chan, I'm about to cum.
No, Kouji...
Don't cum in Rin's pussy!
Hiro, it's now the turn of the human toilet.
Face backwards and ready your butt for me.
Kouji-sama...
Take this... you sow!
Thank you very much!!
You two are the best!
Hiro, it's time.
Yes, please use me now, Kouji-sama.
Good girl.
Yes!