www.SubDESU-H.net
Hiro.
Yes?
Open your mouth.
Okay.
Very good. You’re so talented.
I’m putting it right down your throat.
You need to suck on it all the way.
I’m sorry.
Don’t you want my dick?
Yesh, I wan’ it.
Then show me your ass and beg for it.
P-Please put it in.
Your dick... please put your dick in.
What’s with this pussy?
I’m sorry!
Do you think I’ll get off with you using it like that?
Oh? Does it feel good?
Yes! It feels good!
Do you like this?
Do you like this, you bitch?
Yes, I do!
I’m cumming... I’m going to cum!
I’m cumming. Cumming!
Lately I’ve been doing this every day...
W
Hump Bang!
~No, no!
Don’t cum inside.
I’ll get
pregnaaaaaant!!~
Tonight’s dinner is hamburger steak, eh?
I’m gonna put a fried egg on mine.
Is this your house?
You live next door.
Next door.
I don’t see the problem.
We're like family, aren’t we?
Well, you’ll have to give me an answer soon.
Hmm?
I mean, I think it’s about time.
For what?
Sex.
Huh?!
No way...
We’re not even dating.
You're my childhood friend, aren't you?
You call yourself a childhood friend, but you don’t come to wake me up in the morning,
you don’t make me lunch,
you don’t meddle,
you don’t even put “you know?” at the end of your sentences.
You do none of those things!
Do you even want to be considered my childhood friend?
Why are you getting angry at me?
So...
So?
So, you should at least let me sleep with you.
You’re not making any sense.
“Childhood friend” equals “freebie sex”! I thought everyone knew that!
Koji... your brain is all messed up.
With a face and body made to turn on men shoved in my face every day...
it’s a surprise I survived this long.
Don’t say it like I’m the bad guy!
And besides, I’m not a “childhood friend."
I only moved here two years ago.
We’ve only known each other two years.
Let’s not mention that.
C-Can I hit you?
Will you let me fuck you? Or will you let me fuck you? Which is it?!
It’s two choices. Pick one!
That’s one choice!
Why are you suddenly so interested in it today?
Have you gone into heat or something?
You see, I was masturbating last night...
It was... something that happened around eleven p.m.
Hey, what are you talking about?
The spring breeze felt so nice that I opened my window.
I guess “Moonlight Masturbation” is what you’d call it.
And then, from the room in the next house over...
There was a strange noise.
It hadn't occurred to me that we might both be masturbating at the same time.
You suck!
You suck so much!
Don’t you think masturbating separately at the same time is rather inefficient?
You’re not making any sense!
You know, if we’re both going to masturbate anyway,
don’t you think that sex would be more effective?
Solo-sex is hollow, isn’t it?
B-But then...
At least set some kind of mood.
Cheers, have a nice day.
Hamburger steak with a fried egg.
Don’t try to bribe me with food.
Hiro, you sure smell good.
Hey, wait!
Oh, so soft.
You idiot.
Everywhere I touch is so soft.
At least... kiss me first.
Koji’s lips...
They're huge, Hiro!
Wow!
Tits are the softest of all, of course.
Does it feel good?
My tits... feel good.
Good, good.
Hiro.
You’re so cute.
You never said that before.
You’re so wet.
Well, it’s because you’re...
No, I can’t stand up anymore.
Hiro, what were you thinking about while masturbating?
My arms were... held up...
And then?
In my mouth, you forced me to...
T-To...
Suck it...
Was it like this?
You wanted this done to you?
Hiro, you’re a masochist!
A masochistic pig!
So, what do you want done next?
My butt...
You asked me to... beg for it... while sticking it in my butt...
Then let’s do that.
O-Okay.
Koji... please, put it in.
Put what in?
Your dick. Put it in.
Hiro. You’re the best!
There we go!
Koji’s dick is inside me!
Doesn’t it feel better than masturbation?
Yes, it feels good!
Much better than masturbation.
I’ll make it feel even better for you.
Wow! Wow! Wow!
Koji! Koji! Koji! Koji!
It feels so good.
Hiro, you’re amazing.
You’re squeezing me so tightly.
Masturbation never felt this good!
Right?
You’re glad you did this, right?
Yes, I love this!
More... go in deeper.
I want to be filled with your dick.
Then cum! Cum, Hiro!
I’m cumming...
Koji, are you cumming?
Will you cum with me?
I’m gonna cum because of you, Hiro...
Then cum.
Koji, cum, please!
I feel something amazing coming.
It’s coming, coming, coming.
Now we don’t have to masturbate anymore.
Why the scary face?
Don’t ignore me, woman!
You were moaning and gasping so much earlier.
H-Hurry, give me my panties back!
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I was so embarrassed, I couldn't even savor my long awaited fried egg hamburger steak!
Did I turn you on?
As if!
Are you sure?
Wait... eh?
You’re wet, woman!
N-No...
If you do that, someone will find us.
But it’s thrilling, isn’t it?
Because you’re a super masochist!
Don’t you want more?
No...
Koji... I can’t...
Don’t worry. Don’t worry.
What a sight you are when you're in the kitchen.
In someone else’s kitchen, no less.
Don’t say that!
Wow, you’re really turned on, aren’t you?
N—we can’t!
Yes, we can.
But I’ll moan...
Bite on your apron.
Oh, you weren’t wearing a bra?
Your ass is moving, Hiro.
Suck it.
B-But, not here...
Suck it, I said.
Okay.
You’re sucking it like it’s tasty.
Looks like you’ve accepted your true masochistic self, Hiro.
You’re sucking my dick with all your might.
Hiro.
Do you realize your ass is sticking out?
Oh no... I’m not sure when his mother will come back from the town meeting.
And his brother might find us.
This feels good.
I want more, deeper.
Koji, I want you to touch me more.
I... am really turned on.
When I’m in this state... there’s no stopping.
Hey, hey, hey, let’s go back to your room.
I can’t hold back.
Oh? You want my dick?
I want it, I want it. I want it so bad!
Until Mom comes back, suck on it!
Not yet.
Don’t take your lips off it yet.
Hey, Dad!
Mom says you should take a bath before she comes home!
Didn’t you want to go back to my room?
No... I can’t hold back anymore.
Let’s stay... and fuck here.
But weren’t you going to moan loudly?
Don’t you care if my parents hear us?
I’ll hold it back. I’ll hold it back, I promise.
Hurry, your dick!
Shove your dick in.
There it is!
I finally have your dick!
You’re tighter than before.
Koji... Koji, it's because you tease me so much.
Then I’ll tease you... more!
Oh, yes... I can't!
In a... in a place like this...
I’m being fucked in Koji’s living room.
My family might find us.
Yes, your parents might find us, but...
Yes, there, there, there! Shove it in there!
I’ve been wanting it right there!
Are you about to cum?
Eh, Hiro?
You’re about to cum, aren’t you?
Yes, I'm about to cum.
Oh really?
Me too... I’m gonna cum, Hiro!
Then cum, then cum!
“Please cum” right?
Please cum.
Where should I cum?
W-Well, you...
Come on, Hiro, do you like it when I hit you?
Yes, I do!
I love it!
Hurry, gimme!
I'm asking "where?" though.
Inside, please!
Inside my pussy...
Please cum inside Hiro’s pussy!
Good. Good girl, Hiro!
Thank you very much!
Hiro-chan!
You seem very tired this morning.
Yes, I'm a little...
Is it because of Koji-kun?
No way. That can’t be...
Correct!
Right?
H-Hey, you...
So I was right?
Hey, wait—Rin?
I’m going ahead of you!
Isn’t it true?
You’re gonna be my bride, right?
Yes, if you want that, Koji.
www.SubDESU-H.net