Hight of Hundred Happiness
What are you saying Ryoko-san!
I'm... you know... that!
Only "that" is big, right?
Really? Show me, show me!
What the hell, Mika!
No, not "that", I meant balls!
That's no use!
No it's not!
Having big balls mean sustainability, speed,
and can handle 100 people all together!
I have no idea what I am saying... AHAHA...
– Okay okay, I got it.
– Seems like Shuichi is really going back to the suburbs.
It's not that far though... only two hours away from
here. But apparently there is no reception there.
I was surprised when you said that at first... I assumed that
you were going to start a business there or something.
I just got tired here.
I'm so jealous... I should totally go freelance
and spend my life relaxing.
It's not that easy.
It should be fine, Ryoko-san! I can find
jobs online and work my ass off there!
Kazu-kun you're looking at life too easily!
And... what are you going to be doing?
You'll be surrounded by old women.
You're gonna have a hard time there
not being able to... do things...
You won't be able to find any hookers there either!
You might not even be able to find any girls schools!
Oh... fuck...
You'll be fine... there's always porn on the internet.
Yes, yes, exactly! There's that!
That's just... sad.
Well Japanese people are "sad" in general so.
I don't think Shuichi, being a player will be able to handle that!
Lol, "The man who nails every girl he
aims for", aka Shuichi the Sniper!
Aka, "Shuichi the House-wife Killer"!
Ahaha, that's too much you guys!
At least keep it to "Shuichi the heavy player".
That's too nice, Ryoko-senpai!!
He has countless different tactics
for getting girls in bed with him!
I love how you guys are being "normal"
and not being awkwardly sad.
Bye-bye, senpai!
See you!
It's the middle of the night so speak more quiletly!
I wonder what is not enough...
I wonder why I'm so thirsty.
Ahh... I feel my heart getting cold...
Do I hear a hobo?
I can see... all of that...
Wha... What's happening?
Yo... You can see me?
I can see you... and also see...
Did you run away from home?
No...
If you haven't got anywhere to go, come to my place.
I won't do anything!
Ahh, it's raining!
I guess the water should be warm enough. Here you go!
Let me fuck you!
Um... I...
Isn't that why you came here?
Don't try to talk back!
Ouch!
Wa... Wait! Nurikabe-kun!
I'm so sorry! He didn't mean it!
Konnyaku is a traditional jelly-like food.
What's with that konnyaku!?
This is Nurikabe-kun. He is helping me collect men's semen.
That means... You are...
I am what is called a child house ghost.
House... ghost?
Yes.
Wow you are such a grown "child"...
House ghosts eat semen?
Only because I still have to find a house with a spirit to live in.
A house with a spirit?
I couldn't find one so I kept taking in semen for energy to grow.
Well... It surely grew.
You seem to be in pain...
I need to do this because I have nowhere to live.
The house I used to live in... is gone,
and the town changed so much.
I cannot live in houses made from iron and stone.
I don't think we should do this now.
I'm sorry.
Sorry...
Let's go together.
Huh?
Let's move together! It's a very old house
but I think it might be better than here.
Really?
Yes.
I thought I was sick of crying women.
Let's go!
Let's go together!
Oh... really?
Ah... It's getting bigger inside me.
It's so big it's like a giant potato inside me!
It's so soft but it's holding in my penis very tightly.
It's never been this good before.
Is it tight?
Yes, it's so... good! Let's cum together!
This is so good!
I... I'm cummingg...
We're going together!
So she's here...
Hello.
Hi.
Here we are!
Wow!!
Told you it's old, right?
This house is alive!
Thank you for saving my life.
Please, let me help you with anything.
Oh, okay.
Master.
The meal and bath are ready.
Did you call me "Master"?
Yes!
Look this way, Master.
I'm fine.
Let me do this for you.
Really, you don't have to do that.
It's gradually growing.
Ghost!!
You don't need semen anymore, right?
Yes. Because the spirit in this house gives me power!
I see. That's great.
I... I'm weird.
Nurikabe-ku~n.
God damn... what is wrong with me? Why can't I just do it?
Looks like Nurikabe-kun has the summer sickness.
How can I jerk off with this?
Hello?
This pretty voice...
Hey...
I've never been there, so could you navigate for me?
You're nice... unlike him.
Him?
He... Hey!
He doesn't come see me, nor does he call me anymore.
Wa... waitt!!
I'll "navigate" you, so let's "go" together.
Are you feeling better?
Is that so? That's great!
Eh? Do I seem happy?
Of course I'm happy! We found a new place to live!
Eh? It doesn't seem like it's just that?
You mean... this?
That's because my master is...
It's... not like that.
Master is Master.
I wonder what happened.
That time.
That feeling from that time... is not leaving my mind.
I feel hot...
Why is this happening? I'm not supposed
to need semen anymore.
But... I'm feeling so hot...
I want it again... once more.
Master...
I wondered what was going on with you.
It seems like you're thinking about the human.
Are you the dead spirit?
I'm a fox.
Um... I'm a house ghost.
I know.
You seem dirtied.
No... I don't like being watched!
As if! Your blossomed flower is spilling out nectar!
Let me play with you for a while!
Such a sad voice...
Why not like a human?
But you will be the one hurt, as we
live much longer than humans.
You understand?
That was dangerous!
Fox?
Are you the master?
What are you doin...
– Oh my...
– What are you looking at?
That ghost doesn't seem to have high standards huh?
I wonder why she fell for you.
Ghost... fell for me?
You didn't notice?
Not at all.
You're stupid.
What do you mean by that?
That house ghost wants you to fuck her.
You're messing with me. Aren't you?
Why the hell would I bother doing that?
Didn't you fuck her because you also love her?
It's not like that.
I just felt horny that night.
She needed semen to live. So I gave it to her. That's it.
Don't you feel horny now?
Wha... what are you doing?
Don't do it to me! Do it to the ghost!
I can't handle having this in front of my face.
I just heard a really cute voice!
Stupid human! You're just hearing things!
Stop it!
I told you to stop!
I'm just like this because I havn't done
things in a few hundred years.
Few hundred? Really?
But just once... when I feel in love with a human.
It's a sad story.
You're not listening, aren't you?
I'm listening, I'm listening!
Sorry... Just once.
Okay!
I didn't say that to you!
I will never be able to see him again.
But my love for him still makes me aroused.
Humans live so much shorter lives.
So we spirits need to spend our long
lives just living with the memories.
We're not like humans.
I don't want to throw away my feelings.
Senpai is going to be so surprised when he sees us!
I know, right? He's probably super lonely right now!
Maybe he gave up looking for human
girls and starting fucking monkeys!
Is... is that him?
Master...
Make the house ghost happy.
Senpai!
What the hell are you doing here?
Give me more alcohol! I want to drink more!
Kazu-kun! I want to see your big "thing"!
My balls? SURE!
Kazu!
Go ahead!
Tadaa!
Amazing!
It's so big!
That's too much.
Show it! Hurry!
Here, here, here!
I love it! Ahaha!
I also want to see Shuichi-kun's.
What!?
His penis is really big!
All girls will fall for it!
Kazu! What the hell!
That sounds amazing.
Not really.
Don't lie! Show it to me!
S-stop it!
Did you do it today?
I smell a woman!
Whaa...
Let me put my smell on it.
Woah.
It looks tasty.
Mika-chan?!
I can't hold it anymore!
Damn, damn, damn!
The ghost... disappeared.
I'm...
Hey... Nurikabe-kun?
Please! I need you to find her!
Fine then.
Not her...
Not her!
Master.
Fox!
Master, come with me.
Those things went inside her lonely heart.
I can't do anything anymore.
Ghost!
I'm sorry my house ghost! I'd love to have
sex with you one more time if I could!
Is that true?
Master!
House ghost!
Master... because of me.
Master, could you please leave your "marks" all over my body.
Master!
House ghost!
Let's... Let's come together!
Yes, let's cum together! Ghost!
Fox said that she doesn't want to eat up your feelings.
Let's be together forever! I will do
my best to live as long as possible!
Yes, Master!
Stop calling me Master.
Just call me Shuichi.
Shu...
Master!
You're penis is growing again!
Please visit us at: www.hentaicloud.com/oppaisubs
Translation: pinkunicorn123
Editor: MetaZ
Timing: MrMew
Qualitycheck: Applepiee