Vetoed.
You must cease all concerned actions.
Please be aware of that.
President!
But, that really is too...
I told you, it's vetoed.
I understand your discontent,
but we have more important matters to attend to.
I get that, but with what we suggested...
You're not about to tell me that I
should allow it for some reason, are you?
That's totally childish logic.
– The reason that we are here in the first place
is because the student body has placed their faith in us.
– Are you all right, Itono-kun?
– Ah, yeah. I'm fine.
– And furthermore...
– Thanks, though.
You there!
Shingo, I'd like you to do
more thinking before you act.
I'm sorry!
Then we've reached a conclusion.
I'd really like it if you could be aware of that
and try to be a consistent, exemplary model...
I think a punishment is in order...
Th-Thanks...
I won't be in office for much longer, but while
I am I'd like you to work with me. Dismissed!
Not good...
What am I doing, and in a place like this?
No! People will see!
They'll see me in this embarrassing position!
Forgive me!
I said that I would punish you, didn't I?
No!
You're so rough!
Master!
I'm begging you!
I'm the student council president!
Pounding me with your cock
while we're at school... we shouldn't!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for being so strict
with you in front of everyone!
This isn't going to be enough.
No way!
It's so deep! My pussy's going to break!
Master! Please forgive me!
Someone could walk in at any moment!
It'll be fine.
If someone comes in and sees this, it'll be really bad!
Student Council Room
Just Itono here, huh?
Where's Hyoudo?
The President had some business
to tend to in her classroom.
She'll return shortly, but...
Well, sorting out the lockers can be a hassle, so...
Is that so? Well, I don't want to just wait around...
When she gets back, could you tell her to come see me?
Understood.
Graduation's right around the corner.
If you and the others don't show her
you've got it together, she'll be worried too.
Yes. Please leave it to me.
I'm working hard to take over her position!
You're a promising one, huh?
Yes!
I trust you to relay this message to Hyoudo then.
Understood!
Come on!
I'm vetoing any more of this!
Can you endure it?
I'm not dirty enough to be
doing it in a place like this!
You're too rough! I'm going to cum!
You're going to end up making me cum!
It's coming out!
In the student council room...
I'm the president...
And I'm being filled with cum!
With Master's sperm...
Hyoudou Ibuki
So the Cool Beauty Hyodo Ibuki's Hardcore Masochist
I'm ho...
Hiroto-kun, you're cruel.
I told you we can't do that in school
and yet you go and do it anyway!
Dummy!
Hang on a minute.
You were the one bold enough to show it to me!
Th-That was an act of nature!
I wasn't showing you anything! It was the wind...
You let down your guard too much.
What would you have done if somebody was there?
It wouldn't pass as an act of nature.
We decided that if you did anything unbecoming as
the student council president you'd be punished, didn't we?
That's something you decided for yourself...
I never really agreed to it...
You did, didn't you?
I... might have.
Well, it is true that I might have overdone it.
So as an apology, I'll do anything you like.
Really?
Tie me up!
Hiroto-kun's penis is already stiff.
It's prepared to spoil you.
I'm going to be teased
by this little guy again.
This dick is what makes me feel
so strange and become increasingly perverted.
I love that part of you, Ibuki-san.
Hiroto-kun, you...
saw my secret, and that's when you confessed to me. And
though I turned you down, you forced yourself on me...
You tormented me...
Being together with you makes me happy, but...
But?
To think that your dick would excite me enough
to make me go crazy... I can't believe it!
And to think that you were soaked
through the entire meeting!
That's not true. I'm not that much of a pervert...
You are a pervert.
Ibuki-san is our perverted
hardcore masochistic president.
Dummy. It's not like that.
S-So good...
Are you all right?
I want you to make it feel better with your boobs.
I get it.
It's being forced to do things like this
that has made me into a perverted president.
You'd want it anywhere and everywhere,
and I'd be the one to give it to you.
Not just at school but out in the courtyard...
Inside the train, at the park, all over the place.
Getting excited while talking about this shows you're a
completely perverted, genuine masochist, doesn't it?
You did this to me!
I was a much more normal pervert before...
"A normal pervert?"
Shut up! I'm going to squeeze the cum
out of this filthy dick for you!
I don't even mind if you cum a whole lot.
Let it all out!
Hiroto-kun's semen! It's great!
You've cum this much, but you're still so hard...
It's your turn now, Hiroto-kun.
I'm going to be done by Hiroto-kun...
He's going to pound it into my pussy...
Hi-Hiroto-kun, please don't tease me
Please, give me your cock!
I'm going to give you a thorough spoiling...
Your dick is completely filling my pussy!
How hard am I going to be pounded?
My pussy is being stirred up!
It's great! It's so big, there's so much!
I'm going to go crazy!
My breasts! If you grope them that hard, then...
It hurts... but it's so good!
My pussy is being pounded!
My breast is being mauled!
It's fantastic!
You get off even more when you're tied up,
you really are a perverted president, aren't you?
I'm getting off on being tied up!
I'm a perverted president!
Being in a position like this...
I'm getting off on it even more!
It's so deep it's like I'm being excavated!
My womb...
There's a cock up against my womb
in my perverted, masochistic pussy!
I'm being stirred up inside by your cock
while being degraded and humiliated!
Now, let me see your face when you orgasm, Ibuki-san.
Hiroto-kun is going to see my dirty side!
My shameful, stupid, slutty,
masochistic, perverted orgasm face!
Wow... I'm gonna... I'm...
cumming!
I'm being filled with sperm...
My perverted pussy is so messed up...
Hiroto-kun's cum is overflowing.
It's so good...
That's right! I heard a new teacher is coming.
And that he's going to be
the adviser for the student council.
At this time of year?
Yeah, that isn't the only reason I'm saying this. You should
refrain from doing those things in school from now on.
Okay?
"Those things?"
I'm telling you to keep this little guy
from running amok. Got it?
I mentioned this yesterday,
but this person is our new teacher.
Good morning. I'll be starting my new position
here today. I'm Kirisaki Rie. Nice to meet you.
That new teacher, Kinsaki-sensei, sure is pretty huh?
She's all the boys in class can talk about!
Same in my class. Saying they wish she
would be our homeroom teacher too and...
President!
Come to think of it, didn't you say that Kirisaki-sensei
is going to become our adviser or something?
Oh, it isn't official yet, but it seems like
she'll be informally fulfilling the role as needed.
Ah, is that what you meant?
Um, do I have the right place?
Sensei!
We've been waiting. Come in.
U-Um... Presi...
Really, you are just so...
Seriously! I mean, honestly!
S-Sorry... But that wasn't my...
That's not it!
That happened because you weren't paying attention!
And so, those are our school regulations.
The student body and council
are careful about how we conduct ourselves.
Isn't that wonderful! I've met with all the students,
and everyone seems to really have it together.
They must be modeling themselves
off of the student council!
Even you, Itono-kun.
You look cute, but you're realty mature!
I'll have to work hard too!
Teach me what I need to know, Itono-kun!
Yes!
Ouchies...
Oh no!
You were just drooling all over her...
Honestly...
Ibuki-san, that's jealousy speaking... isn't it?
It isn't! I'm just warning you as the president,
about your indecent behavior as a member of this council!
I only engage in indecent behavior...
with you, Ibuki-san.
C-C'mon! I told you to stop doing this on school grounds...
Come on...
I said no...
I don't think that jealousy is appropriate
for the student council president.
I-I-I said I wasn't!
I'm not jealous or any...
I will have to punish you for this, won't I?
Come on! Punishment isn't...
Stop it!
Today we'll have an outdoor punishment session.
But that's! Outside would be...
There are still students here,
I can't do it someplace like...
Does this punishment arouse you?
N... I'm no...
No!
Your body is honest.
I'm a bad girl.
Hiroto-kun's penis is reaching into my deepest parts!
This is the courtyard, they're going to see! They're going to
see the perverted president going crazy from your cock...
You're getting off while saying that, aren't you?
Something like that is...
It's because Hiroto-kun's penis is that good...
Even though I said no!
You're doing this to me anyway! You're too mean!
It's because you were jealous.
I'm not jealous! It's your fault!
Hiroto-kun, you...
That isn't a very presidential excuse, is it?
That's not it! Even though I'm the president,
I'm so slutty, I'm going insane...
Your dick's so good...
We're so close together...
It's tight...
I never thought you'd be able to make
me do something like this...
I'm going to be graduating from school soon,
but I'll never be able to graduate from your dick!
Obviously. I'll be looking over you for the rest of your life.
I'm glad... I'm so happy when I'm with you like this...
Me too.
I'm going to cum inside of you raw.
Hiroto-kun's seed! Let it out!
Let it out until you pass out!
Give me your seed, please!
It's all flowing into me...
So much of Hiroto-kun's cum...
It's still flowing...
We ended up doing it in a place like this again...
Ibuki-san, it's about time we...
Just a little longer like this...
I was seen... and by a teacher of all people...
There'll be a staff meeting tomorrow...
My parents will be called. At this rate, I'll be expelled!
And then, there's what Hiroto-kun
will make me do with him...
And the teacher was gone afterwards...
What was that about?
What if he uses this to threaten me, and make me go before
the entire student body to do dirty things or something?!
Wh-What am I thinking?!
The expected punishment for
a sexual act would be expulsion!
I should at least make sure it's just me...
If I don't convince her
to not let him get hurt in this...
What are they talking about?
That's amazing.
She's getting along so well with everyone.
I'm tired just watching...
President?
Ah, Anita-kun, right? What is it?
What is it? What about you, President,
what are you doing here?
Ah! It's Kirisaki-sensei!
Kirisakr-sensei is... How to put it...
She's popular, isn't she?
She's older, but she's cute, isn't she?
She's doing her best, but she's a bit of a klutz...
It's like you can't leave her alone!
The boys even started a fan club for her.
They're quite into her!
But it seems like she isn't aware of the situation.
That's another good thing about her, though.
She's a good teacher, isn't she...
Yes. At any rate, she's doing her best for the students!
For the students' sake, huh...
Thanks for waiting.
D-Doing something like that
as the president is... That is to say...
"The president...?" But you did do it, yes?
Th-That's... But this is bullying...
I'm behind you.
B-But...
You're the only one I can ask for somethin like this.
But what you're asking me for is really...
But you were in a place like that,
making a face like that...
So brazenly, like that...
That is... with him...
Please just leave it at that!
This is too embarrassing!
Then I can count on you?
I... I understand.
I'm glad!
Even if you make that face...
I'll be finished soon. Wait until then.
Lately you've been getting pretty cheeky.
Before you were all "President, President".
Even though you were scolding me...
Are you slacking off now that you've conquered me?
This is why boys are so...
That's cheating!
President. I said no, didn't I? I'll punish you.
Um... Hiroto-kun?
"Master".
I told you I was busy.
Ibuki-san, you really are a terrible slave.
I'm sorry, Master....
Wearing this slutty underwear while giving an address
to the entire student body, you perverted slave...
You really do need punishment, don't you?
B-B-But, I'm the president! I had to!
It can't be helped. Or rather, perhaps you were
looking forward to being punished?
That...
That's...
I wanted to be taken care of by my Master...
You want to see?
The truth is... I am a virgin.
At this age... I just have no luck at all.
A vir...?!
There have been a lot of misunderstandings,
and even now I have a problem with stalkers.
And I have fears,
but seeing it for real in
a place like that was shocking...
And for it to be you was even more surprising.
I-I wasn't exactly trying to...
But it wouldn't be strange to be caught
if you were doing it there, right?
In the courtyard...
That is... Well...
How to put it...
Judging from the look on your face,
it must have felt good, right, Hyoudo-san?
No! Well, how to say this...
It felt good, didn't it?
Yes...
Right? So if you would let me see more,
it would be educational for me too.
And then I won't be so inexperienced either!
If you rub my breasts so hard,
I'm going to feel too good!
Master's penis... I'm already so hot for it...
Even though I'm being watched, I...
Your cock is in my mouth...
Punish me a lot!
You're completely wet. Soaked, even.
I wanted Master's penis so much
that my pussy has gotten so slutty and wet...
It's always ready to take Master's penis, any time.
It's all moist and wet...
It tastes so good...
No way. To be leaking this much...
It hurts!
I'll have to punish this pervert
who gets off on this so much.
Master, please, give this perverted
masochistic pussy your dick...
It's even more amazing than usual...
Master's dick is going in so deep!
Being penetrated while being watched...
My body feels so hot!
Master's dick makes my pussy feel so happy!
My asshole! When you tease it,
it feels so good, Master...
I'm going to fill you up anally too.
It's in my butt!
Amazing!
You're teasing it, you're going to mess me up.
You're completely getting off on anal.
It's because it's Master's penis...
I'll end up feeling it anywhere...
Master's cock...
You're stirring me up and pounding me so deep inside!
I'm being ravished and messed up by my master...
My ass and pussy can't take it!
Master's penis inside me is...
I just love it!
It's in this masochistic president's ass!
Lots inside... Please, Master!
I'm being seen as such a slut, and yet I...
Master, you're being rough again!
My ass... your cum's going to going my ass...
I'm going to pour in plenty!
Master... So rough...
This is...
I...
Master...
All while being watched...
Master is...
So much sperm's been sprayed inside me...
It's all up in my belly...
No, under here, is...
Eh? Does that mean...
the whole time, you saw what I was...
I insisted.
It's just that always doing
this sort of thing in school won't do.
Do you have the right to say that?
But Hyoudo-san... You're really something.
A masochist slave, saying "Master"...
I couldn't have imagined that
from the ordinary Hyoudo-san...
I'm the one who ended up feeling embarrassed.
S-Stop it! Please, don't embarrass me any further!
I know! Next time, in the classroom!
Vetoed!
translator: kuro-kun
translator check: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: lamevn
editor: punk4real
quality chek: fyurie