Yeah, gonna need this too.
I could use this... and maybe this?
Hey, wait... Ibuki-san, isn't this a bit much?
It's your fault that I have to get this many.
Hey, stop! I told you, we can't!
Just because school hasn't started yet, it doesn't mean
you can be this rough first thing in the morning!
Weren't you the one who wanted this, Ibuki-san?
I just bent over to pick up something
that fell, you came over and...
You stuck out your ass,
basically begging me to do something.
No, I'm telling you! I wasn't!
You're just twisting my actions to suit you!
Everyone else is gonna be here soon! Stop!
Hiroto-kun, you're being too rough!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
You're cumming so much! There's so much
cum in me so early in the morning!
I told you we can't do it here,
but you still came in me anyway!
Hiroto-kun is such a troublemaker.
He just does me whenever and wherever he wants.
It's gotten to the point where
it's almost like a daily morning ritual.
Even though I'm the Student Council President,
when he puts his dick inside me I can't help it...
If our teachers found out...
Hey, Hyoudo.
Yes?! What is it?
I have something to tell you.
If our grades drop any lower,
it'll reflect poorly on the Student Council.
The teachers are gonna crack down on us
if we don't give them results on the next test.
Don't worry too much. I'll whip you into shape.
Right.
There are a lot of people, huh? It's even worse because
it's gonna take a while for us to get to the bottom.
Yeah, it will... Maybe about two or three minutes?
Hey! What are you thinking?!
His dick is getting so hard!
He doesn't care if we do it in this place?
You're kidding! He's moving?!
No! Stop!
You're just as horny as ever, aren't you?
Stop! Hiroto-kun!
Please unzip your panties.
I won't put it in, I'm just opening it, okay?
What am I doing right now?
Oh god, his dick is hitting
against my dripping wet pussy!
Please, Hiroto-kun.
You can't go any further, people will see!
There has been a blackout. Please wait a moment.
He put it in! No way!
His dick is really inside me!
S-Sorry, I'll tak...
It's fine! Just stay like that.
We're almost at the bottom.
Why am I getting this aroused in a public area?!
Hey, Hiroto-kun, wait a second!
Come on, I told you that we can't!
We can't do it in a public place like here!
You say that, but you can't resist either, can you?
No, stop! Not here!
Just stop this already!
We'll be found out if you don't quieten down a bit.
If you keep moving like that,
I won't be able to resist anymore!
No! Someone's gonna see us!
No more!
Just a little more.
This can't be happening.
In a place like this, I'm gonna...
I'm cumming! Hiroto-kun made
me cum in a bathroom stall!
I...
No, no, this can't be happening! I...
I don't care anymore. I'm going home!
Ibuki-san, wait!
I'm sorry. I just got way too
ahead of myself back there.
I told you to stop!
You need to know that there's
a limit to how forceful you can be!
You really go too overboard.
At this rate, my grades for the next test are obvious.
If you're my b-boyfriend,
I want you to prove it to me with some results.
So until the test's over, I won't have sex with you!
I'll help you study.
~The reason why the Perfect President Ibuki a total masochist~
「The cool, total masochist President Ibuki's erotic fantasies ♥」
I knew he could do it if he tried!
Now we're able to focus on our studies!
Maybe as a reward, I'll let him do it just a little bit.
No, no. I can't falter here, otherwise Hiroto-kun will just
revert back to his old self. I need to stop thinking like that!
Hiroto-kun's so late...
Guidance Councilor's Office
What's he doing?
I'm pretty sure he said we'd study together today.
Kirisaki-sensei took Hiroto-kun somewhere?
What did she need from him?
Thank you, Hyoudou-san.
You really helped me out.
Why are you being so nonchalant about it?
It was really embarrassing for me!
But I'm really jealous of you
for having such a cute boyfriend.
I almost feel like I wouldn't
mind him taking my first time.
Wha... Sensei! Don't joke around like that!
Even as a joke, you can't say that!
He's a popular kid.
There are a lot of girls going after him.
Maybe she took him and...
No, I need to stop overthinking things,
they're probably just talking about grades or something.
Guidance Councilor's Office
Right there, Itono-kun!
Itono-kun, it's embarrassing
when you stare at me like that...
S-Sorry.
Hey, do you want to see more?
I want you to take my first time
with your huge, manly dick.
Doing this with a student at school
is definitely not a good thing, but...
You can do whatever you want to me, Itono-kun.
I-Itono-kun, your mouth is against my pussy!
Itono-kun, if you keep going at that same area, I...
This is the first time I've ever felt this much pleasure!
It's gotten real big down there.
I'll suck your dick just like Hyoudou-san does.
It's so hot, and it's twitching so much. Amazing!
It's so big.
You're making me feel so much pleasure
from there! This is too amazing!
At this rate, it'd be faster if
I deep throated it. I practiced this a little.
Does it feel good when I do it?
Itono-kun, you can cum whenever you like, okay?
There's so much!
You came so much but you're still so hard.
Itono-kun, please...
Make me a woman with your dick...
Itono-kun, your dick is kissing my pussy.
It's coming in... is this sex?
Your dick is coming inside me.
All of it isn't fitting inside.
I want it to go even deeper.
It's inside me! My first time is with you, Itono-kun!
Ow!
This pain is proof that I'm a woman.
It really hurts, but this pain makes me happy.
I'm so happy I was able to give you my first time!
The pain you gave me is starting to lessen.
It's starting to hurt less and feel good!
It's so deep! I can tell that you and I are connected!
My insides feel so amazing!
Itono-kun, I'm sorry I asked you to do this
even though you already have Hyoudou-san.
Oh my god, your dick is rubbing
against me all the way to my womb!
This is my first time, but it feels so good!
My pussy's filled to the brim with your dick!
Wha... My body's... I'm...
This...
Hiroto-kun and Sensei?
Oh? Hyoudou-san?
I'm sorry, I was just checking
with Itono-san about his future plans.
Did you two have plans already?
Yeah, she was gonna help me study.
I guess we went a bit later than I thought we did.
No, no. You're fine. You guys are talking about the
Student Council. That's important, so I'll just come by later.
Guidance Councilor's Office
Wh-What the heck was
I thinking about back there?!
Why did I picture him
and Sensei doing that together?
No, if I don't hold out,
this'll have a bad effect on his grades!
I told him that there was no problem, but is that true?
He's smiling at me now,
but maybe he's secretly thinking that I'm too clingy?
No, Hiroto-kun's probably the only person
in the world to not think about those kinds of things.
He's always on my side...
Hiroto-kun, what are you doing?! We're supposed to
be studying, why are you bringing your dick out right now?!
I told you we can do this after the test's over!
Even if you whip this out, I won't...
What are you doing? Why are you
hitting me with it? Knock it off alrea...
No, don't! There are still people at school! Stop...
I can't breathe!
I can't breathe! It's too big!
No, at this rate...
I can't breathe!
There's so much cum!
You can't!
It's inside me! You're fucking me at school!
No, please, stop! Hiroto-kun.
I beg you, Hiroto-kun, stop! I'm sorry! I was wrong!
Yes!
Hiroto-kun, I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
No, please, don't do me in this embarrassing position!
Please, Hiroto-kun! Please forgive me!
No!
You're going so deep again!
No, Hiroto-kun, you need to stop! Stop!
No! Are you planning on cumming like this?
I'm gonna cum too if this keeps up.
I'm gonna cum from your forceful dick!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming in the student council room
while you're pumping your cum inside of me!
Hiroto-kun, you poured
so much of your cum inside me, I...
Ibuki-san? Are you okay? Ibuki-san! Ibuki-san!
Sorry about that, I spaced out.
Are you okay? Your face is kinda red,
are you sure you don't have a fever or something?
I'm fine! I'm perfectly fine!
Let's get back to study...
Yeah, I already finished doing that.
Really? Then I guess that's enough for today.
All that's left is to take the test. Do your best, okay?
Ibuki-san!
Hiroto-kun?
Sorry this happened.
Seriously. Be careful next time.
Don't overwork yourself.
This is what we call "sexual frustration".
"Sexual frustration?!"
Wh-Wh-Wh-What would make you
ever think that I'm sexually frustrated?
Just looking at you is proof in and of itself.
Hi-Hiroto-kun?!
Hiroto-kun! No, what's going on?! This is so rough!
No, if this keeps up, I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
No way, I...
I really am a pervert.
Because of that I've caused you so much trouble.
No, it's because I pushed you this far.
I was supposed to be supporting you,
but look what happened. I'll do better.
I don't want tot cause any
more trouble for my... girlfriend.
I'm counting on you.
Hiroto-kun, your dick's so big!
It's so tasty.
Hiroto-kun, your tongue feels so good!
Are you about to cum, Hiroto-kun?
Let out your cum, Hiroto-kun!
There's so much of your cum in my mouth!
No, we can't do it in this position!
It's here! Hiroto-kun's dick is filling my pussy up!
Hiroto-kun, your dick is stirring
me up so deep inside. I love it!
The student council president is on the roof with a face
of ecstasy. The students are gonna find out I'm a pervert!
That side of you is meant just for me.
My perverted side is something only for you! I'm a slave
for your dick! You can do whatever you want with my body!
In this position, it's going in even deeper!
Mess me up even more with your dick, Hiroto-kun!
Yes! I want you to cum all over my slippery,
perverted pussy! Make me a mess!
I'm gonna cum!
I... I'm gonna cum!
You're cumming! There's so much!
I can't help but make these lewd noises
while your cum is being pumped inside me!
There's so much cum on me!
Hiroto-kun, you're just too good.
You poured too much cum inside my pussy.
I'll take good care of you
just like that forever, Ibuki-san.
You can "take good care of her",
but try to tonight down when your that school, okay?
S-Sensei?! I thought we locked the door!
I've been hiding here before you two even came.
I just thought that you two'd be at it again as usual.
What do you mean by that?!
But seriously, you guys really went hard again today.
I guess you really are a pervert, Hyoudou-san.
How about you guys do it in a classroom next?
Enough!