Reina!
There's still some trash on the ground.
Thank you for you hard work.
The same goes for you.
Thank you very much!
You were quite uptight back there.
Because it's part of my job.
At the usual place
Jeez, I've waited very long, you know.
We might not have enough time now.
Sorry, work got extended a bit.
I'll Make up for this.
Of course you have to.
I might be busy,
but it's also an important time for you, so I have to do my best.
I know already.
You don't have to tell me that.
Alright, alright.
You're treating me like a kid!
Well, I've been taking care of you for a long time,
and you're kind of like my little sister now.
Is that what it looks like?
Like a little sister... huh.
Ryouta, that's...
When we reach the top, right?
I want to be with you longer.
We've got an early start tomorrow.
I understand then, Onii-sama.
See you.
Ryouta...
I want you to... do it more...
Oh wow...
Ryouta, more...
Ryouta, put your finger inside.
Oh no...
The impact may not be as dynamic,
but this is a rare chance for you to be a gravure idol.
I'm the only one involved however,
will that really be alright?
What are you saying? This is your big chance!
It's the path where you, and only you
alone, will be taken to the top.
You may be right.
Alright, I'll do my best!
So, what about Ryouta?
You'll be needing a manager for this,
in that case, you'll then work for her starting today.
Thank you very much.
However, you must set limits.
Limits to separate work and private affairs.
Yes.
We can't sell with that!
You have to present yourself more as a woman.
Man, that's why idols are so...
We're done for today.
We'll just reschedule at a later time,
so try to consider things until then.
I'm frustrated.
I worked very hard only to be told that I did nothing.
He said he wants me to present myself as a woman.
What does that even mean?
That kind of gravure is well...
The kind of stuff men usually see.
If they say I can't sell that way then...
You can't, Reina!
Not on something like this.
But...
... I'm going to have to break my promise.
Ryouta, I want you to...
Ryouta...
It may be this way, but, Ryouta, I...
His fingers!
Ryouta, I want you to...
That's Ryouta's...
I-It looks kind of incredible.
Ryouta, do me.
Yes?
Okay.
I understand.
I was just told to get up early for a meeting tomorrow.
Maybe they're about to lay me off because I'm no good.
You're not the type to just give up, right?
Fight on.
You're right.
Thanks.
Now I feel really relieved.
Oh no, this is embarrassing!
Look, you're about to become the girlfriend of
thousands of other men through these lens.
This specific meeting,
seems like it'll turn out quite well.
Try to seal a kiss on camera,
project your feelings onto the person that will look to you.
Come on, hurry.
Try doing it.
O-Okay.
I can no longer complain about being embarrassed.
This is my chance.
Alright, let's start filming this way.
This look of yours will be great on the photos.
It's great that the plan is going on as planned.
Good luck with your photoshoot.
Of course.
Face here.
That's good.
Your expression has softened up significantly.
It feels more natural now.
Did something happen?
N-Nothing.
It's just that... I want to take full advantage
of this opportunity given to me.
I'm embarrassed, but I have to hold on.
Great! Just keep that up.
Do it like you're giving your all to your boyfriend.
Ryouta...
So she's going to pose like that too?
That expression is nice.
Oh no, he's pushing my breasts.
What should I do? I don't like this!
Look here.
Reina?
Ryouta.
We shouldn't do this.
This is just about right.
And idols mustn't...!
Ryouta is the only one...
Good. Just keep that up.
No way, this is Terada-san's...
Don't move, just stay where you are.
Reina?
She's looking this way.
I'll ask for a short break.
Good, good, don't let go of that now.
Just...
Hey, stop intruding!
Just go home if you're just here to interrupt.
I-I'm sorry.
Oh no.
My panties are going to be seen if this continues.
Can you face backwards with the same position?
J-Just wait a moment.
You look drenched over there.
I understand this can be quite tiring to do.
There's some towels over there so go ahead and get changed.
Oh, and you get to stay outside.
B-But...
Insensitive, eh.
You need to at least understand this as a manager!
I'm sorry, it's his first time so...
He's not yet used to this.
Then all the more reason to.
Hey, there's the door.
Jeez...
O-Okay.
Oh my, and I'm even in the middle of my job.
But, that earlier...
Hey, stop that!
What are you trying to do?!
So you can put on such a nice expression after all!
Just like I thought.
Oh, so you got wet from being embarrassed while having
your picture taken in front of your boyfriend?
Hey, what are you doing?!
Please stop this now!
Don't tell me what to do.
You're the one who got aroused here.
Pervert.
No way, I...
They say you're barred from relationships, but you're
actually being fucked every day, aren't you?
You even got your pussy wet during work.
You're wrong, I'm doing no such thing!
I'm just-
Stop!
Ryouta, Ryouta!
The room's soundproof.
Besides, he's too much of a dunce to even notice.
No, I beg of you, please!
Don't do this!
I'm about to show you something even better than his.
It hurts.
Oh, you're a virgin.
Even though you got that wet earlier.
Getting really slutty even before getting fucked, eh.
My dick might hurt a bit since I'm your first,
but you'll soon get used to it.
Why did this have to happen?
Ryouta, Ryouta!
Are you alright being seen in this situation?
Stop.
Please stop!
The pain will subside in little while.
You demon!
I'll never forgive you.
If you're prepared to ruin your own
life then try to call the authorities.
You'll then be known as the "raped idol"
You pervert!
Trash!
I'll make sure you get used to this.
Hey, can't they hear?
What happened after I was kicked out?
Sorry, we got a bit too into it.
Also, this might take a little while longer so you can go now.
Wait, but Reina's still...
She also wants to focus on this.
Reina!
Terada-san, what in the world did you...
Getting her pumped up.
Or do you plan to interfere?
I-I understand.
Please, I don't want this anymore.
We're just getting to the main course.
Don't... stop...!
The pain is starting to subside already, right?
I'll make sure you become a woman with this.
Me, become a woman... you don't...?
Oh, and your agency might be in trouble as well.
What should I do?
Ryota!
Oh no, I'm starting to moan strangely...
It'll feel a lot better once you're used to it.
How long will this last?
They're not finished yet?
It'll be tomorrow at 3pm.
Goodnight.
Is the photoshoot
still not done?
Please reply.
Today
You handle this quite well.
I like girls that can resist.
Even if you don't like it now, you'll soon crave for it.
That won't ever happen with you.
Wait, that's mine. What are you going to do?
Hey, stop! Don't look!
From your boyfriend?
Why don't we send a snapshot as a memento
of you becoming woman?
Stop messing around! If you do that I'll never...!
He might have found out.
I wonder how he'll react when he sees your naked body?
Reina?
He saw me.
No way...
You, demon...
Monster!
Why did you have to do that?
I just wanted to get some good photos.
You said the same weird excuse again.
You'll never get away with doing this!
Why don't you realize it already?
You're the one moving your own hips here.
No way, that's just...
I'm not... I'm just not...!
Why?
It did hurt, but my body now feels hot.
I'm going to teach you everything that your
boyfriend was supposed to teach you.
It's not Ryouta, and yet my body is...
Why?
I can't hold back anymore.
No, anything but that... don't do it, please!
Impregnating's not really my style, but this body's really good.
Sorry about this.
He's cumming inside...
Is the photoshoot
still not done?
Please reply.
Are you alright?
Something
happened
Please reply
Something
happened
Please reply
I'm okay.
We're just
about finished.
Reina...
You worked hard.
Ryouta.
Another person just did that to me...
No!
Reina?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm... I've.... Terada-san had...
Were you sexually harassed?
Ryouta, I...
I...
Don't tell me...
That bastard!
You can't, please don't!
Please, Ryouta.
What?! Are you really okay with that, Reina?
You mustn't, Ryouta!
This is my chance.
Our chance.
That's why...
I... I want to...
Forget all about it.
Reina, I'll make you forget.
Ryouta...
Ryouta, please make me forget.
It's okay, Ryouta.
Ryouta, your thing is inside me...
Reina... I just put it inside her...
It's alright, Ryouta, just move.
O-Okay, I got it.
Your thing feels warm,
and it's filling me up inside.
Ryouta...
I-I'm sorry.
I came inside.
It's okay.
I'm going to tell boss about it tomorrow,
and have her forget about this project.
You sure did something troublesome.
I already told you many times to be careful.
I'm sorry.
Why are these...?
Terada-san was able to hold it off so we're saved for now,
but I want you two to be more conscious about it.
I want to give my gratitude for dealing with it for us.
It'd be troublesome if we were to lose Reina, you see.
It's just a give and take.
So, when will we be able to resume the photoshoot?
Umm... we'll still have to discuss it with our boss.
You don't have to push yourself.
That said, we have a deadline to catch up to.
Fans are not that nice, you know.
There you go again, Terada-san.
My bad.
I was thinking maybe we could start right away.
Hmm, it really does look great.
Umm, boss, about the next photoshoot...
Reina, this is your own battlefield.
He's the expert in his own field, so fight on.
Y-Yes, please do.
I'm wearing this in front of Ryouta...
No way...
I'm completely exposed like this and yet...
How indecent!
Hey, do your job!
Because of work? Damn it...
I little bit more... like this.
There.
What in the world is he thinking?
Stop.
Ryouta's watching...
Reina's, blushing?
Please do.
No, Ryouta will find out!
Can't hold-back anymore?
Are you going to cum with another man's
finger in front of your boyfriend?
Alright, we're done, good work!
Why am I...?
I'm sorry.
I seem to have forgotten something.
I'll just go and get it.
Stop!
I'll go with you.
It's okay, I'll be back in a jiffy.
You're expression's were simply terrific.
I'll show you the pictures from yesterday later,
so be sure to come back.
Come over here.
You're going to blackmail me with this?
That'd be a crime.
Besides, I don't need it.
L-Let me go!
You've craving for it, yes?
I already told him everything.
Oh, that's quite unexpected.
So what did he say?
You're asking? Of course he got mad ove-
I see, he just got 'mad'.
Which means he accepted this situation, yes?
It's because of this job, so I just...
Then you have to learn it well.
Th-This is bigger compared to Ryouta's.
You compared it, right?
Was he able to satisfy you?
Wasn't the pleasure just one-sided?
You know, I can satisfy you.
I wonder if she's still inside.
Or maybe we just passed each other already?
You can feel the change happening in your body, right?
I can easily see that your body has become slutty.
That's not true.
I'm not a slut...
The way you resist also looks cute.
You have to thank me for making your body slutty.
Please stop saying such things!
Why is my body...?
Cheating is done by men physically, women mentally.
If you're heart still belongs to him, then it's still okay.
No way...
You don't get to just say things like that.
Why? It's as if my body's not my own!
Stop resisting.
You've kissed with him, right?
How was it compared to mine?
I don't know.
And for me to compare that is just...
Why?
Ryouta...
With that stupefied expression, I feel really
bad for your guy watching over there.
What the hell is this?
Reina?
What kind of expression is that?
Ryouta.
Ryouta!
I'm...!
You might be the same as earlier,
but you're getting even wetter as he watches you.
Stop already, you...!
Ryouta's watching all of this!
Reina! Reina!
Hey, let go of Reina, you...!
Open this up!
Ryouta...
Ryouta!
Stop! I'm right in front of Ryouta!
Ryouta, save me!
I don't want this.
He's even gotten through my tender spots.
Stop this, Terada-san!
Let go of her, please!
Don't go any further!
It seems she gets really aroused when doing it in front of you.
Reina, the perverted, exhibitionist idol.
For me to do this in front of Ryouta...
Stop messing around!
I'm definitely not...
If you want to make excuses to your boyfriend, go ahead.
But you can't deny what your body is feeling.
Hey, what if she gets hurt?
Stop this, Terada-san.
I beg of you, let go of her already.
You make it look like I'm the bad guy here.
She came here on her own accord, you know.
What are you saying?
You told me to, so I...!
Then that still means you decided to come here.
Damn, you think I'd believe that?
You probably just blackmailed her!
You can't overt your gaze from reality.
Re-Reina?
Ryouta, this isn't it.
This isn't me.
I'm not getting aroused from this!
Cum while holding onto your boyfriend's hand.
No, don't push it there!
If you keep on pushing me there...
Reina, Reina!
Ryouta, no this isn't me!
But, this is the first time I've felt like this.
I'm sorry, I'm right in front of you and yet...
I can't hold on anymore.
I'm, I'm about to cum!
You have work today, right?
Yes, I'm sorry, I'm just...
What are you doing...
I'm sorry... but I just can't hold back.
You just came earlier.
But it's still big.
Why?
It'd be weird if I didn't have a boner in this situation.
Then I don't have to worry.
Because I'm now completely yours.
It feels... really good to have it rub and push hard inside me.
I'm starting to feel really horny with this, Ryouta!
Yes, you sure do, Reina.
You're the best.
Pleasure yourself too while watching how slutty I am.
Okay, Reina.
In the ass?
It feels like it's going to burst!
I'm going to sloppily cum while relieving myself!
I love how it penetrates deep within me.
It's in my ass, but it still feels very good, Ryouta.
Oh wow.
Both my ass and my pussy are being pleasured...
I'm just too lewd!
Even though I'm an idol...!