D-don't...
Just a little.
I don't want to.
Hurt... it's hurts.
Just... bit.
Don't do it.
Don't... don't do it.
On summer.
After 1 year...
I went back to our home.
Welcome back... Kou-chan.
Yeah... I'm back.
It's been ages.
This girl is my cousin, she lives next door.
We are both single children.
But we've been pretty close ever since we're little.
What is it?
Don't me what...
You Kou-chan.
You don't even visit on vacation.
Well...
I've been pretty busy lately.
Ehh... Really?
It's actually lie.
But... Kou-chan.
Youb haven't change a little.
Idiot.
There's no way I can change in just 1 year.
Me...
I changed a little?
I can't back because.
Well... Because there's another reason.
Your hair become little longer.
Your cloth is not from last year.
Of course it is.
That's not what I meant.
Kou-chan you're always like that ever since.
I know.
I can finally backwards on the
horizontal bars!
Let me show yuo right now!
Eh...
It's getting late, you know?
Don't worry.
Don't... Worry...
See... I can do it.
Did you see that? Did you see that?
Yes I did.
That's the tenth time now.
Aren't you supposed to lean this stuff
in the second grade though?
Wh... Does it matter?
I was never good at this...
Kou-chan...
Huh?
Is college... fun?
Well... It's pretty fun.
Is living alone... hard?
I guess, I'm used to it.
Last year... Is really hard to bring up.
Kou-chan.
It's been a while.
Let's go to that place.
Th... that's place?
Do you still come here often, Anna?
Here.
Sometimes... I guess?
Say Kou-chan.
Do you remember what we did here last year?
Let's do it again.
Let's do it.
La... last year we did.
You...
What are you saying.
Is that a no?
Last year was... my fist time.
You suddenly... took your penis out.
Th... that is...
K-Kou-chan.
Why are you naked??
It's embarrassing...
It's okay.
Anna.
It's actually my first time too.
Kou-chan penis.
Why it's getting bigger?
What is he going to do with me down there.
What is he going to do?
It... it hurts...
J-Just a little bit...
I don't want.
It hurts... it hurts.
Just... a bit.
S-Stop...
Stop...
That time it hurt so much I cried.
But then we just left it at that, Kou-chan.
Well... you.
Things got kinda awkward.
That's why I didn't comeback last year.
You know eversince then...
I've been practicing lots of lewd things...
Y-You.
Don't tell me you went and
did it with someone else?
N-No!.. I wont!!
I... I just looked stuff up online...!
That why I think...
I think I can don't better than last year.
Her tiny tongue.
Is digging it's way inside my mouth...
Say.
You don't want me to do this stuff
with someone else?
Of course I don't want.
I won't.
Her lips...
are so soft...
And her body...
Is so slender...
I feel like...
feeling it a little...
Have your breast... grown a little bigger?
Maybe a little...
Lately my nipples have started to hurt.
There's a subtle suppleness.
I'm feeling weird...
Are her nipples getting a little harder?
Don't tell me... this is...
Kou-chan... don't suck them hard...
Anna... Are you okay?
Yeah... I'm okay.
Kou-chan... I'm gonna make your thing
feel really good too.
Just like what I thought.
It is really big.
A-Anna.
That is...
Kou-chan... feeling good?
Yeah...
It feels really good.
The inside of Anna's mouth is
so narrow and warm...!
Kou-chan penis is so...
S-Sorry... I came.
It's okay...
I never thought...
semen would come out so much.
Anna.
Spread you legs.
K-Kou-chan... this position... is emabrrasing...
Slippering pussy...
Anna is so small but.
She's already this wet.
Don't tell me...
My finger went without much resistance.
Kou-chan... don't do that...
Anna... Have you been masturbating?
No... I don't...
Really?
You have, haven't you?
That...
N-Not there...
Otherwise I doubt my finger would have
slipped inside so easily.
And the inside of your pussy
wouldn't be feeling so good.
Jus... just a little...
I come here from time to time to.
I knew it!
In that case, you won't mind if I start doing it
a little harder, right?
Don't...
Don't... don't...
The inside of my down there.
It is pussy.
Pu... my pussy... dirty.
It's okay.
Her hips are becoming more relaxed.
I'll push it a little farther inside...
That place...
That place is... don't...
I'll cum.
I'm going to cum...
My finger fees hike it's going to be torn off...
She came...
Does it feel good?
K-Kou-chan...
I can't...
take it anymore...
Kou-chan... I just came...
Don't worry.
You're already this wet, with this.
Kou-chan...
Last year I only inserted the tip.
But today.
Your penis... don't...
So tight.
It's inside.
My pussy... has penis inside...
Don't...
If you move like that.
That is... don't...
I seriously can't get enough of this...!
I'm having... sex.
I'm having sex with Kou-chan.
A-Anna...
K-Kou-chan.
I... I'm...
She's so small, but her body's already
become so erotic!
So rough...
Don't... your penis... don't...
I'm going to feel weird!
It... it's okay... don't worry.
My head is becoming blank.
My body's feeling it more and becoming hot.
Her tiny butt... so smooth and squishy.
So cute.
Your pussy's drenched!
I can't take it anymore...
My body's going to numb.
I can't... take it.
It's tighter than before.
Ahh... his penis is throbbing...
throbbing... we're both.
We're both feeling good.
Ah... I... I can't. I'm at my limit.
Anna... Are you okay?
Kou-chan...
Love you...
A-ah... You're leaving next week right?
I'm gonna miss you...
Then... I'll have to comeback here in the winter.
Realy?
Yeah.
Really? Really?
Then if you lie will swallow 100 noodles?
E-ehh? 100 noddles is kinda lot?
It's just your imagination.
No, no, no.
All you have to do is to comeback.
I promise.
You better not get a girlfriend you hear?
Promise me!
Hey hey.
Just one okay.
I didn't said okay, it's hey.
You really need to change that.
Yeah yeah.
Look who's talking, when you where still a little kid
you even pee on the bed.
Next time, I should stay a bit longer.
Because it will makes Anna happy.