Subject: Looking for a guy to hook up with tomorrow night.
"Looking for a guy to hook up with tomorrow night."
"The meeting place will be at the abandoned
warehouse in the mountains of Minekura City."
"This isn't prostitution, so no need for money."
F-For the subject I'll put... "T-Take..."
I'm not virgin!
"T-Take my virginity, please!"
Subject: Take my virginity, please
I'm looking for a guy to hook up with tomorrow night!! The meeting place will be at an abandoned warehouse in the mountains of Minekura City. This isn't prostitution, so no money needed.
A-And send!
I really sent it...
Toyama Haruka.
That's the name of the girl you just saw send
that unbelievable message. It's my name.
If you're wondering why I'm doing something so stupid...
It all started at break during school.
And so the guy I did it with yesterday
was all like "You're not a virgin?!"
But like are there really any girls
nowadays that haven't had sex already?
The one talking about sex was a
classmate of mine, Miwa-chan.
She's cheerful, fashionable, and
just overall a really popular person.
I'm the complete opposite. I can't
help but want to be like her.
Oh, was this conversation too
much for a virgin like you, Haruka?
Wh-What should I do? If she finds out that I'm
actually a virgin, she's gonna think I'm not cool.
I-I'm not a virgin.
I-I have experience.
Oh?
Then prove it.
You know, like a picture of you having sex or something.
A-A picture?
What's this? So were you lying?
I-I wasn't lying!
I'm telling the truth! I'll have sex
and bring in the proof tomorrow!
One hundred percent chance of meeting someone!
Your sexually compatible partner! Located in a safe abandoned warehouse.
And after racking my brain, the best solution I came
up with was posting on a message board for sex.
Now that I think about it, I'm really doing
something crazy right now, aren't I?
Just because I don't want her to think I'm
lame, I'm trying to have sex with a stranger...
B-But I am a little interested in sex.
I guess it's okay.
I-I wonder if any guys will even want to have sex with me.
Wh-What should I do if nobody shows up?
Next day
at the meeting place
What the heck is this?!
We're gonna work out who's going
first, so just wait a sec, okay?
That fate of my virginity's being
decided by rock paper scissors...
U-Um, why are there so many of you here?
I-I'm a virgin, you know.
That's exactly why!
Isn't that obvious?!
Don't underestimate us!
Th-Thanks for waiting.
I won, so l-let's have fun, huh?
Y-Yes, thank you for your cooperation.
Do you want me to take them off for you?
H-Huh? No, I'll take them off myself.
stare...
Wh-Why are you all still here?!
Huh? We can't just go home after coming all the way here.
Wh-Where's the harm? Everyone here came for you.
Th-That's true but...
B-But forget about that, I'm ready to go!
W-Wow. This dick is going to go inside me?
Let's get started, huh?
Can I take this off?
U-Uh, yes.
A virgin's bare chest!
They're looking at my naked body.
There are so many of them too.
This... This is...
This is making me feel weird!
U-Um, put it in.
Please put it in.
O-Okay.
You're very wet right now.
P-Please don't say that!
Okay. Okay then, here I go.
His dick is coming inside me!
Th-This truly is a virgin pussy!
It's so damn tight!
A-Alright, I'm gonna start moving!
Let's feel good together!
I-I'm already about to cum!
Wh-Where do you want me to shoot my cum?
C-Cum?
Y-You can shoot it anywhere you want.
Anywhere's fine, right?
Then I'm gonna cum inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming inside you!
I'm gonna fill you up with my cum!
That felt... too good.
Seriously...
So this is sex?
So Miwa-chan's always doing
something that feels this good, huh?
Phew, that felt great!
Congratulations on losing your virginity!
R-Right, thank you very much.
Now as long as I take a picture, I can show Miwa-chan...
It's inside!
Wh-Why are you putting it inside me?!
I just couldn't resist any longer!
Let's all have a turn.
N-No! Please take it out!
But you just moaned about how great it felt.
And you know, it's normal nowadays for
girls your age to have lots of experience.
N-Now that he mentions it...
Miwa-chan's done a lot of different role
plays and things with different people.
I want to do it too!
And I guess having a dick inside did feel good...
I want to try having all kinds of different sex!
I-I...
I...
I want to have sex with everyone here!
Please play with my body however you all want!
You serious?!
Fuck yeah!
Okay, I'm cumming!
Hey, me next! I want to put it in from behind!
S-Sure, go ahead.
Please make love to me.
Just by throwing my virginity away, I'm
able to have sex with this many people?
Wow, so I'm actually a huge pervert, huh?
I'm going to be the third dick inside this pussy!
Let's do it!
W-Wow...
Th-The cum inside me is making
everything so slippery! It feels so good!
It feels so good!
C-Could you put mine in your mouth?
S-Sure.
H-Hey, I was just about to ask! That's not fair!
No need to fight.
I'll take care of both of you at once.
You're so good!
There are so many dicks!
I-I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna cum all over your face.
M-My face?
Please cover my face in it.
I can cum inside you, right?
Y-Yeah, do it deep! Shoot it real deep inside me!
No! I'm gonna cum too!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Dicks are so good...
We're next, but...
U-Um, well...
Are you okay with thinner dicks?
We're also virgins...
But they're really long, so I don't see a problem.
Hey little lady, I just thought of something fun.
Huh? That's your idea?!
I'll take both of your virgin dicks
inside me at the same time, okay?
T-Two dicks at the same time?!
Go in... Go in!
They're in!
My pussy ate up both of your dicks.
Well, I'm going to start moving now, okay?
My insides are... being stirred up so hard!
H-Holy crap.
Th-This is so...
I can't just sit here and watch anymore!
I'm putting mine in too!
I'm a quickie, so there shouldn't be a problem, right?
Huh? Wh-Why are...
Wait, that's my ass...
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
This feels too good!!
Sex is...
S-So amazing...
I'm next!
Hey, me too!
O-Of course, that's fine.
But before that, could I ask for a little favor?
Okay, I'm gonna take it.
Okay, smile!
Please, hurry. Let's fuck already!
Hurry up!
I wanna try two dicks in your pussy too!
Of course.
But just make sure you try all kinds
of different sex things with me, okay?
Geez, I ended up staying all night
having sex with all of them three times.
My stomach's filled with cum.
But it felt so good.
Wait, that's...
Miwa-chan!
Huh?
Look! I kept my promise! Here's me having sex!
I had sex with fifty people!
I thought that I was gonna get pregnant
from all of them cumming inside me!
They even used vibrators and special
sex toys to play with me all night long!
And then I had two dicks inside of me and my pussy...
Huh? What's the matter, Miwa-chan?
You're a freak.
Now she's scared of me...
My name is Nakata Shin.
I'm just your average employee
working for an apparel maker.
I think it's about time.
Hi!
U-Um...
Welcome, Haruno-chan.
Th-Thanks. Good afternoon...
New Awakenings
And the girl who's sitting here so uncomfortably
is the landlady's daughter, Tamata Haruno-chan.
It's been one week since this shy girl
started coming over to my apartment.
Apparently she can't speak straight
to anyone let alone her classmates.
And the landlady turned to me
to see if I could give her some kind of mock
counseling to help her get better at talking to people.
I definitely didn't agree to do this because of her huge tits.
Well then...
This'll be your fifth time coming here, how do you feel?
Think you can hold a conversation with someone now?
Um, well, uh...
N-Not today.
Wh-When I think about people watching me,
I-I get so scared and my head gets all mixed up.
I see...
It's not going to be easy to get her out of her shell.
There's gotta be a way...
You're scared of being looked at?
If that's the case...
Hm, where'd I put it?
Oh, there it is!
Here! Try this on, Haruno-chan!
Huh?!
U-Um, what is this?
U-Um, Nakata-san...
Wh-What are these clothes?
They're party goods from my company.
Yeah, they look great on you!
Wh-Why am I w-wearing this?!
You're scared of being looked at!
So that just means you have to get used to being looked at!
Huh?
If you're scared of other people looking at you, you just
gotta keep having people look at you until you're used to it!
In that outfit, it's easy to see every last bit of you.
With that being said, I'm going to look at you all over.
And I really do mean, all over.
You really do have a very beautifully shaped bust.
Your bellybutton is also perfectly shaped!
P-Please stop...
And you have really beautiful skin, huh?
It must be so smooth!
Yeah, nobody could say that you
don't have an amazing body.
Your butt's also so healthy. I like it!
I bet you'll bear really healthy kids!
And then you got the back of your
knees which are so magnificent!
They should be a national treasure!
Wait a second...
I just kind of kept going with this, but now
that I think about this, isn't this kind of bad?
S-Stop...
I-I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
H-Haruno-chan?
I'm cumming!!
Wh-What just happened?!
Orgasm? Did she just cum?!
S-So, Haruno-chan, when people look
at you, how does that make you feel?
W-When...
When people look at me...
The deepest parts of my body start getting excited,
and get really hot...
and my head goes blank.
There's no doubt.
She's not shy, she gets turned on from people's stares!
She's a complete exhibitionist!
In that case...
These need to come off!
N-No! D-Don't look!
Haruno-chan, let's have sex!
If we have sex and make you embarrassed to the
maximum level, you should become desensitized to it!
I can't wait too much longer.
Th-This is all for your sake, Haruno-chan.
I have absolutely no dirty feelings involving this.
Holy shit, I can't get enough of these tits.
I'm not thinking that in the slightest okay?!
And down there, you're... oh, yeah, that's a good flow.
I-I'm going to take off your panties, okay?
Th-That's okay, right?
Look, I can see your pussy and asshole so clearly now!
And now I've seen every last nook and
cranny of your body, Haruno-chan!
Wow, you're cumming again?!
How about I thoroughly look at your insides next, huh?
Holy crap, your face is hot when you cum.
It's hard to believe that you're shy!
And now you're getting even wetter.
I'll clean you up.
D-Don't lick it!
Y-Your tongue's gonna make me...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
H-Haruno-chan, I want to do even
more embarrassing things, so...
It's okay if I put this in, right?
N-Nakata-san...
W-Wait!
Wait, I... I'm a virgin!
S-So...
It'll be alright.
If you're this wet, it won't hurt at all!
Th-That's not my concern...
I want my first time to be with the person I love...
Woah!
Your soaking wet pussy's so warm!
Your pussy just swallowed me whole... it's so dirty!
Don't you worry, I'm gonna fill you with embarrassment!
Damn, you got such a dirty look on your face right now.
You really have a dirty look on
your face right now, Haruno-chan!
Oh, I know! Let's make it so you can see
the face you're making whenever you want!
Huh?
There it is!
This is a new model, so it's gonna come out great!
A-Are you going to use that to...
Yep! Let's start by taking a
picture of that dirty face of yours.
Come on, come on! This is the dick that was
inside you and took your virginity, Haruno-chan!
Let's take a commemorative photo
of it and your dirty face, okay?
No...
Open it bigger! Wider!
Open it so I can see all the way inside.
Yeah, that's good.
Open your mouth as wide as it goes and look over here.
Good, you're doing great!
Move your hips more!
Your pussy's swallowing my dick and
your asshole is right out in the open!
Having someone took at my embarrassing spots
is so embarrassing that it kinda feels good...
Huh? She's suddenly moving harder.
Nakata-san...
Please...
Huh?
Please look at my embarrassing places even more!
Please teach me even more about all the
embarrassing things I didn't know about myself!
H-Haruno-chan!
Fuck yeah!
Well said!
I'm gonna make you feel the most
embarrassed you'll ever feel in your life!
Think about it, the second floor of this
apartment is pretty noticeable, isn't it?
If we have sex up here, lots of people are gonna see you.
I'm getting turned on from people outside watching me.
Looks like you're into this, so let's get
people watching you with my dick inside!
Y-Yeah!
I-I'm having sex in a place where anyone can see me!
Look, we already got a person watching.
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum while people are watching me!
I-I'm cumming!!
Look at me!
Take a good look at me cumming!!
H-Haruno-chan, it's kind of late,
but I'm sorry about back then!
A half month later
I-I did all those horrible things to you!
I can't even look at you right now!
I thought you'd never want to see me again!
There was something I wanted you to see.
Huh? You're not here to yell at me?
A bold exhibitionist arrives at school!
Every day since then has just been so much fun!
My shyness has been completely cured.
This is all thanks to you, Nakata-san.
I've already
done it with 10
people today.
– Wh-What in god's name have I done?!
– I've already done it with ten people today.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч