Welcome to the Minekura Onsen
Finally...
I'm finally here at Minekura Onsen,
the bathhouse I've always dreamed of!
My name is Kaede Endou.
Studies, romance, fashion...
I'm a girl who loves onsen more than any of those.
Today, I'm here at the famous Minekura Onsen!
I want to see for myself how the water feels, so
Fresh-Boiled
Onsen Eggs in
the Mixed Bath
I'm going to take in every detail!
Today's going to be loads of fun!
One adult, please.
Front Desk
Comin' right up! Eh? Are you here
by yourself, young lady?
Yes!
Well, I'll be! It's not often we a young
lady like you here, all by herself.
We mostly get men and old folks
because our bath is...
She's already gone!?
Oh well, she'll figure it out for herself.
Onsen, onsen! Here's a fun onsen!
Outdoor bath flowers, onsen eggs!
Wow! This is amazing!
Better wash up before I get in.
And here I come!
This feeling!
Enveloped by this warm water, it's
like my body's melting away!
I'm becoming one with the water!
This onsen's even better than I expected!
I'll register this as my address and
soak in this water forever!
Other patrons?
Oh! There's a young'un here!
Well, whatd'ya know!
Huh?
Why is there a guy in here?!
Well color me surprised! To think a youn
lady like you'd be up for mixed bathing!
Mixed bathing?!
Wh-What should I do? I've got to get out of here,
but I've hardly enjoyed the water at all!
But it's embarrassing! But I want to
enjoy the onsen more! What should I do?
But I gotta hand it to ya! Not covering yerself
with a towel... Yer a real onsen veteran!
Of course! Covering yourself with a towel while
bathing... In an onsen, that's bad manners!
I have ten years of onsen experience,
so I'd never do that!
Why am I trying to seem like I'm OK with this?!
Oh? We're all onsen lovers then. Let's take it easy!
Y-Yes, thanks.
I'm so stupid! Now I can't get
out or even cover myself!
N-Now that it's come to this, I'll hang
in there until they're done.
Out of respect for the onsen,
I have to hang in there!
15 minutes later
Oi! Are you OK, jou-chan?
She's gone all dizzy!
Why doncha get out n' cool down fer a bit?
Y-Yes, let's do that.
Take a rest on those rocks there.
OK.
It's so hot.
What am I doing here? My head's spinning,
and I can't think straight.
Hey, jou-chan.
Spread yer legs, and you'll feel cooler!
Haha, I'm jokin' with ya!
Like this?
You're right, it's a little cooler now!
But my body still feels hot!
O-Oh, then I'll...
O-Oji-shan, w-what are you doing?
Oh, this...
I'm usin' my saliva ta cool yer body from the inside.
B-But this is making my body feel even hotter!
I'm gonna cum!
What am I doing here?
Oh, she's cooled off! Let's get
back in the onsen, come on!
What's all this?
It's so warm.
Say, jou-chan, are ya thirsty?
Yeah, I'm thirsty.
OK! Leave it to us!
We'll give ya loads of top-quality "onsen juice".
Eh? Aren't these di... Eh?
They carry the "onsen extract" we've collected
by going to onsen for 30 years.
Jou-chan, ya love onsen, so I bet ya wanna try it!
30 years of history? Amazing!
Yay! I wanna drink it!
Good gal! Try lickin' and suckin' the tips!
OK.
Like this?
Y-Yes, that's it. Keep it up an' lick
up plenty of onsen extract.
It tastes strange, but this is onsen extract!
Come on, taste some more in yer mouth!
Lick this one too!
That's good. Just a lil' more. A lil' more!
Here it comes! Drink all of it!
It's cornin' out! Catch it in yer hands!
Drink up what's in yer hands too.
It's bitter, but it has a rich taste. I think I like it!
So this is what onsen juice tastes like...
Yay, I learned more about onsen today!
Well I had fun, so now I'll be leav...
Eh?
Um...
Oji-san, you're, um... inside me?
I'm also... I'm also...
I'm also gonna give ya a taste of onsen juice!
In yer pussy, that is!
Is this... Are we having sex?
Am I being tricked?
My head's spinning. I don't care anymore!
Yer so soft inside!
Yer feelin' hot inside, ain'tcha?
Your hot di...
Oh, yer body's cooled down.
Eh?
Jou-chan, let's do this in the water.
O-Oji-san, we can't! We can't do this in the water!
In an onsen, that's bad manners!
Applyin' onsen juice directly inside
ya has a beautifyin' effect!
Beautifying? Amazing!
If that's the case, give me more, oji-san!
Squirt more inside me!
I can't hold back!
I can put it in yer pussy too, can't I?
It's warm from the water, so it should
stretch ta fit both of us.
Two at once! It'll be twice as effective!
Yes! Go ahead!
Yahoo!
It's stretching... My pussy... You're coming inside!
Two onsen dicks are in me at once!
A-and warm water's flowing
in and out of my pussy!
I can't just watch! Take me in yer mouth!
Jou-chan, yer mouth-pussy's tha best! I thought
tha onsen's warmth felt good, but yers is better!
O-Oh, I'm gonna cum!
M-Me too!
And me!
Jou-chan, three onsen dicks are gonna cum!
Here we go!
Onsen extract is flowing deep inside me.
Onsen really are the best!
U-Um...
I'm in the changing room?
What was I...
O-Oh, yer awake? Next time, careful
not to soak fer too long!
We're heading home now. Um,
well, thanks fer the treat!
Eh? What? It wasn't much?
What was all that about? Oh well, forget it!
More importantly, I'd better go
enjoy this onsen some more!
What a pain in the ass!
Damn it! Why's there cleaning duty every day?
Can't we just clean whenever?
Hey, you guys!
Eh, Mi-Miwa!?
osouji no  jikan
Why are you two slacking off?
You haven't cleaned this place a bit!
Look, the window's still so dirty!
And look at the floor!
Forget cleaning, you're making it even dirtier!
Here she goes again with her cleaning complaints.
She's like this every day, isn't she?
Who does she think she is?
You're completely useless!
You know what, I'll do this all myself!
You two, get lost.
Oi, Miwa! You go to far!
No! Get your filthy hands off me!
Now your filth is on my clothes!
They're so filthy, I can't even wear them anymore.
Wha...
I've dealt with this since I've come
here, but I can't take it any more!
You're all filthy! Girls, guys, all of you!
Your breath stinks. Your bodies stink
How do you live with yourselves?
Being near you makes me sick to my stomach!
Damn it! We're hearing you out,
but you're just giving us shit!
Get away from me. I hate you the most, Shintani.
Your existence itself is filthy.
Just being around you makes me
feel dirty. Get out of my sight.
I feel gross. I'm going to throw these
clothes away, so I'm leaving.
Wh-What's her problem?
O-Oi, Shintani! You gonna let
her tell you off like that?
Hey, everyone, mind helping me out a little?
Phew. Another day spent in
that disgusting classroom...
This is the worst.
Graduation can't come soon enough.
W-Why's everyone gone?
Oh, finally here, Miwa?
Sh-Shintani!
Wh-What do you want?
Hey, why are there only guys here?
Where are all the girls?
Well, we guys all wanted to give you a present.
Isn't that right? Ready?
Yeah!
Ready!
Bags: Burnable Waste
Look, Miwa! It's your present from all of us!
It's raw garbage, fermented for a week!
N-No!
It's filthy! It's filthy!
Oh, that's rude, Miwa!
Throwing away our present like that...
No! Don't touch me! Sensei!
They won't be coming. The girls
are keeping them busy.
When I told them I wanted revenge,
they were eager to help.
And now we guys are going to soil you
even more... with our dicks, that is!
They really stink, don't they?
That's because none of us have
showered for a week!
A whole week!?
We're doing this for you, Miwa.
Give it a lick!
N-No!
Shut up, and have a taste!
How do you like it, Miwa?
How does it feel to have a dirty dick
with loads of smegma on it in your mouth?
Woah there! Don't bite or I'll stick
raw garbage in your pussy!
Just like that, lick up all that smegma.
I'm gonna cum! Have a good taste of my semen!
I'm cumming!
Aw, she spit it out.
Weren't you going to clean this room, Miwa?
We don't have much time,
so let's get this over with.
Alright, strip her!
What nice breasts. I'll cover them in drool!
N-No! Stop it! I'm getting dirty! I'm getting so dirty!
OK! It's time for you to clean my dick!
Wow, look at this! A week's worth
of smegma's coming right of!
No!
Quit spacing out, Miwa. Can you hear me?
It can't be helped. We'll sit you down.
There we go!
Wow, she's on full display! Snow white
panties! That's Miwa all right.
Oh, she's all wet down here. Wha... It's urine!?
Seriously? She peed herself in
shock! Aw, it really stinks!
Filthy... Take them off. Take them off!
C-Can I have them? Miwa-tan's panties!
U-Uh sure. Take them. They're yours.
Ready with that camera?
OK!
OK, let's take a look.
Clean freaks are amazing! Even inside
her pussy she's super clean!
Look, Miwa. We're taking pictures
of your urine-soiled pussy!
N-No! No!
Oh, you're all energetic again, Miwa!
I think it's time I got in here.
S-Stop! Anything but that!
No!
Then apologize for treating us like garbage.
Apologize! Then we can talk about mercy.
I-I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry I said those things!
I'm... sorry I called you filthy!
I-I won't say those things again,
so please have mercy!
Oh, you really apologized.
But I'm not going to forgive you, bitch!
You thought I'd forgive you? Is the
inside of your skull clean too?
Take it out! Take it out!
Are you an idiot? I just put
it in! I'm not taking it out!
Look at this, Miwa! A week's worth of smegma
is rubbing off inside your pussy!
Oi, Shintani! Aren't you done yet?
We can't wait much longer!
Sorry, my bad. Cum all over
her, as much as you want.
What are you doing?
Y-Your smelly, dirty... There are so many of them!
I'm gonna cum!
Me too!
Let's all cum on her together!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming on her face!
Me too!
Idiots, I'm the one who's cumming on her first!
I'm cumming on her breasts!
Cum with all you've got!
Let me in!
Give her a good whiff of our smelly semen!
I'm cumming on her legs!
I'm cumming on... Whatever, anywhere's fine!
No! No! Stop it!
Shut up!
I'm gonna cum. Shut up, and take it!
In your pussy, that lis!
– Take this filthy guy's sperm!
– No!
It's coming out.
They'll forgive me now, won't they?
I'll go take a bath.
That's right, forgiveness... I'll forgive you at least.
Wow, she stinks! She smells like semen!
Finally! I can't stand this smell!
You really came a lot.
Her hole is mine!
Your ass feels so good, Miwa.
Wow, you could fit two dicks in there.
Wow, you're really fitting two dicks in there!
I gotta piss. Miwa, let me use
your face for a second.
Well, shall we call it a day here?
Yeah. Our professors should be coming back soon.
So Miwa, since you got this place
all dirty make sure you clean it.
She can't! She can't even hear you!
Yeah, we came inside her about 20 times,
and she stopped being responsive.
It'll be bad if someone sees her,
so shove her in the closet.
Heck no! She's so filthy! I don't want to touch her!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч