Just a bit more.
No, it hurts. It hurts!
Just a little bit.
Stop... stop.
Stop!
Summer vacation.
I returned to our ancestral home after a long year.
Welcome back, Kou-chan!
Yeah, I'm back home.
Long time no see!
This is Anna, my neighboring cousin in these parts.
We've been close with each other since we were little kids.
Perhaps because both of us lack siblings.
What's up?
Don't ask me that.
You never returned last New Year's, you know.
Well... I've been busy with things.
Really now?
I really wasn't, though
But, you haven't change a bit.
Stupid. I wouldn't change that much in a year, you know.
What about me, then?
Have I... changed?
There's another reason as to why I
wasn't able to come home sooner.
Your hair seems longer.
Your clothes are also different from last year's.
Of course they're different!
Come on, that's not what I'm asking about.
You're always like that.
Oh yeah, I can spin on horizontal bars now!
I'm gonna show it to you right now.
What? But it's almost noon already.
It's okay.
It'll be fine!
Whoopsie.
See? I can do it now.
Did you watch me?
I did.
That's the tenth time already.
You'd usually be able to do it in second grade, though.
Give me a break. I'm bad at horizontal bars, you know!
Kou-chan.
Having fun at college?
Well, kinda. Yeah.
Is it tough living alone?
Well, I'm used to it.
She's not bringing up last year's incident, huh?
Kou-chan.
Since it's been a while... can we go "there"?
"There?" You mean.
Have you been coming here since then?
Sometimes, I guess.
Hey, Kou-chan.
What we did here last year.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it.
Last year, you mean.
What are you trying to?
We can't?
It was my first time last year.
You suddenly pushed your dick inside me.
Th-That's.
Kou-chan, why am I naked?
I feel embarrassed.
It's alright, Anna.
I'm undressed here, too.
Why is your dick getting bigger?
What's going to happen to my peehole?
What are you going to do?
It hurts!
Just a bit more.
I don't want this.
It hurts. It hurts!
Just a bit more.
Stop, stop!
Stop!
Anna!
It hurt back then, and I cried.
We never hung out together afterwards.
Well, I...
It was kinda awkward for me, too.
That's why I never returned during New Year.
After that I...
I tried to study more lewd stuff.
Wait, don't tell me you did it with!
No! I didn't do anything like that!
I just looked up things on the internet!
That's why... I've improved since last year.
Such a petite tongue.
She put it in herself.
Hey,
you don't want me doing lewd stuff with someone else?
I don't.
Then I won't.
Her lips feel tender.
Her body's so slender.
Somehow... I'm starting to feel hotter.
Your breasts look a bit puffy.
Just a bit. My nipples have been hurting a lot lately.
They're strangely soft.
This feels strange.
Her nipples are starting to stiffen?
Could she be?
Kou-chan, if you keep doing that I'll.
Are you all right, Anna?
I'm fine.
Let me pleasure you, too.
O-Okay.
It really is big.
Anna.
That spot!
Does it feel good, Kou-chan?
Yeah. It feels so good.
The inside of your mouth feels tight and warm... No, it's hot.
His thing also feels.
Oh sorry! Did it all squirt out?
I'm okay.
So it can cum this much.
Anna, part your legs.
Okay.
Kou-chan, this position is embarrassing.
Such a smooth pussy.
The hole's so small, but it's already this wet.
Could she be?
It's clamping down on my fingers.
Kou... chan.
Not... there.
Did you try playing with it by yourself?
N-No, I didn...
Really now?
You did, right?
That spot... no.
Oh no.
My fingers can't just slip right in, you know.
And you won't feel aroused this much with it inside.
Just... a little.
I do it here sometimes.
I knew it.
Then I can be a bit rougher, right?
No, stop.
No... you mustn't.
That's my peehole.
This is your pussy.
My pussy's dirty.
It's alright.
Her hips are twitching.
I'll try to reach a bit further around... here.
No, not there.
It's coming.
Something's coming!
My fingers feel like they're going to be torn apart.
She came.
Did it feel good?
Kou-chan.
Oh crap, I'm already.
Wait, please, Kou-chan. I don't think.
It's alright.
You're already this wet so.
Kou-chan.
I only inserted the tip last year.
But today, I think I can.
Please, don't push your dick further inside.
So tight!
It's in.
My pussy feels full with his click.
You mustn't!
It's so thick.
I can't restrain myself!
I'm having sex.
I'm having sex with Kou-chan.
Anna!
Kou-chan!
I'm...!
She's so petite, and yet her body's already so lewd.
This is so intense.
No, no more dick.
I'm going to lose it.
It's okay. Just let the pleasure wash over you.
It's alright.
My head feels all fuzzy.
My body feels so much hotter than when I masturbate.
Her butt is so small, yet so smooth.
It's so cute.
I'm already!
Kou-chan!
Your pussy's so wet.
I can't take this anymore.
My body's all tingly, and I'm about to!
It's clamping down even tighter than before.
His dick keeps on twitching.
We're pleasuring each other, together!
I'm at my limit!
Are you okay, Anna?
Kou-chan.
I love you.
Oh, so you're going away again next week.
I'll be awfully lonely.
I'll be back by winter.
Really?
Yup.
Really really?
Cross your heart, hope to die, stick a needle in your eye?
What? Why do I have to do that?
That's too much!
You're just overthinking it.
Absolutely not.
Just be sure to return home.
I promise.
'Kay!
You can't have any girlfriends, either! That's a promise, okay?
Fine, fine.
You just have to agree!
Nope, I'll just say "fine".
Jeez, you better change that part of your attitude!
Oh, quite the cheeky girl, eh.
Looks like the great Anna's already
outgrown her bed-wetting days.
Hey!
Next time, I'm going to take a longer vacation,
in order to make her happy.