Welcome to Minekura Hot Springs
Finally...
After all this time, I can finally go to Minekura Hot Springs.
My name's Endo Kaede.
I'm a girl who loves hot springs more
than studying, romance, and fashion.
Today, I'm going to the very popular
and prestigious Minekura Hot Springs.
I came here with no prior
knowledge of what this place is like
Steamy
Mixed
Bathing
with
Tamako
so I can fully experience it with my own body
and form my own unadulterated opinion.
Today's gonna be so much fun!
Admission for one, please.
Asmission
Coming right up... wait, are you by yourself, little lady?
Yep!
Seeing a young girl like you by herself all
the way out here is quite the rare sight.
The only people who come here are the old or men.
After all, our baths are...
Where'd she go?!
Well, that's fine. She'll figure it out
as soon as she gets in the bath.
Hot spring, hot spring, the really fun hot spring.
Gotta get myself in some hot spring water!
Th-This is amazing!
First, I gotta wash myself off with the water.
And now I can finally...
This is the best!
The water rushing into my vagina
makes my body feel like it's melting!
I'm becoming one with the hot spring!
This is even better than I imagined.
It makes me want to move up
here so I can come here every day.
Huh? More people?
Th-There's a young girl in the bath!
Well that's not something you see every day.
Huh?
Wh-Why are these guys coming in here?!
Never thought I'd live to see the day a
young girl would come into the mixed bath.
Mixed bath?!
What do I do? I should get out right now... No, I
can't. I haven't even enjoyed the bath enough yet.
But this is so embarrassing, but I
want to enjoy this bath so badly!
What do I do?!
I'm surprised you didn't cover yourself with
a towel. You're basically a hot spring fanatic.
O-Of course. Covering oneself
in a bath is just poor manners.
Someone like me who's a regular
hot spring goer could never do that!
Why am I bragging about that?!
Great. Then let's have fun as fellow hot spring lovers.
Oh yeah, sure, gladly.
I'm such an idiot! Not only can I not run
away now, I can't even cover myself!
Okay I have no choice. I'm going to have
to stick it out here until they leave.
I can show a little skin if it's for my hot spring experience!
15 Minutes Later
Hey, are you alright little miss?
Did you stay in for too long?
Try getting out for a bit and cool off.
O-Okay... I'll do that...
Try lying down on that rock over there.
Okay.
So hot...
Wait... what am I doing again?
My head's spinning so hard, I can't even think straight.
Hey, little miss, you might feel cooler
if you spread your pussy wider.
Just kidding.
Like this?
Oh wow, yeah, I feel a little cooler now.
But my body still feels so hot.
O-Oh, really?
Then how about I...
Mister?
What are you doing...
Oh, this?
I'm, you know... trying to lower your
body temperature with my saliva.
But my body's feeling even hotter now.
S-Something's coming out!
Huh? What was I doing?
Oh, better now? Time to go back
in the hot spring then! Okay? Yeah!
Wait, what are you doing?
So hot...
Hey, little girl, are you thirsty at all?
Yeah, I am.
Then how about we...
...give you some of our hot spring soup to juice?
Wait, aren't these dicks... Huh?
These are, uh... things that have thirty years worth
of our five thousand hot spring visits inside them.
You like hot springs, don't you? Don't you wanna try it?
Th-Thirty years? Wow!
I wanna drink it!
That's good. Try licking and sucking the tips.
Okay.
Like this?
Th-That's good.
Keep it up. You're going to be able to
drink lots of our hot spring juices like that.
It tastes find of strange, but it's not bad.
Come on, take it in deeper to get a better taste.
Try sucking mine too.
Good. Very good.
It's about to come out!
Make sure you drink it up!
Some of it's coming out. Make
sure you catch it with your hands!
And then be sure to drink whatever's left.
It was pretty bitter, but it was pretty
rich in flavor so it wasn't too bad tasting.
So this is the taste of hot spring juice, huh?
I learned even more about hot spring culture now!
Horny
Well I think I've had enough fun, so I'll be going...
H-Huh?
M-Mister? You're kind of... inside me.
I... I...
I'll let you drink my hot spring juice too! But in your pussy!
Huh? Wait, is this sex?
Is he having sex with me?
They tricked me and...
Ugh, I can't think straight. Whatever, I guess.
Your insides are so wet!
Your pussy feels like it's on fire.
Your dick is so hot!
Woah there, your body's getting pretty cold.
Let's go back inside the bath.
We shouldn't be doing this inside the baths, Mister.
This is bad manners!
Having the minerals from the hot spring put
directly into you is good for your beauty.
R-Really? That's amazing!
If that's the case, then more! More, Mister!
Put more in me!
I can't wait any longer. I can put
it in your pussy too, right? Right?
You're already pretty stretched out
now, I bet two will fit inside there.
Two at the same time?!
That means that it'll be two times as effective!
Yeah, sure!
Yes!
My pussy is being spread out!
They're both coming inside me!
There are two hot spring dicks inside me!
I can feel the hot water coming
inside me all the way inside me!
I'm done waiting! Suck me off too!
Your throat pussy is marvelous!
This warm tightness is better than
any hot spring I've ever been to!
Oh no, I'm gonna cum!
M-Me too!
Y-Yeah, me too!
Get ready, three dicks coming at you, hot!
Take it in!
It's going into the deepest nooks and crannies of my body.
Hot springs really are the best!
H-Huh? Is this the changing room?
What was I...
OH, you're awake?
Don't stay in so long next time.
We're heading home now.
Well... thanks for everything.
Uh, sure?
You're welcome?
What was that all about?
Well, whatever.
What's important is that I have
lots of fun at the hot spring!
This sucks!
Geez, why do we have to clean every day?
Nobody said we have to do it seriously. Just do whatever.
Hey, you two.
M-Miwa!
osouji no jikan
cleaning time
What are you two doing, goofing off?!
You haven't even cleaned a single speck of dirt yet!
Look at how dirty the windows are still.
And don't even get me started on the floor.
It looks like you guys actually made it dirtier!
And there she goes again complaining about
the cleaning. It's a daily thing at this point.
Who does she think she is?
You guys really are worthless.
Whatever. I'll just clean ever thing by myself.
You guys just go home.
Hey, Miwa, now you're crossing the line!
No! Don't touch me with your dirty hands!
How dare you put your dirty hands on my clothes. Now
my clothes are so dirty. I can't wear them anymore.
I've been trying to hold it in all
this time, but I can't anymore!
All of you are filthy!
Everyone in this class... boy, girl, it doesn't
matter. Your breath stinks, your body reeks!
How can you all be this filthy?! I can't believe it!
Just even being near you guys makes me want to vomit!
You little... You really think I'm just gonna
let you run your mouth off like that?!
Stay away from me.
You're the worst of them all, Shintani.
Your very existence is filthy.
Just being near you makes me feel like I'm being tainted.
Do me a favor and never come near me again.
Oh, god I feel gross.
My clothes are dirty, so I'm going to go home now.
What the hell's her problem?!
Hey, Shintani, are you really going to
let her just say that and walk away?!
Hey, everyone, mind helping me out a bit?
1 Week Later
Ugh, another day of having class in that filthy classroom.
This is the worst.
Can I just graduate already?
Huh?
Why's nobody here?
Oh, you're finally here, Miwa.
Sh-Shintani?
What do you want? Wait, where are the girls?
Why are the guys only here?
Well you see, all the guys here have a present for you.
Everyone, you ready?
Yeah, we've been waiting!
Here you go, Miwa. A present from all of us!
It's one week's worth of raw garbage!
N-No!!
So dirty! So dirty!!
Oh, you're so mean, Miwa. Why are
you throwing away our presents?
Stop! Don't touch me!
Sensei!!
He ain't coming.
The girls are holding him up right now.
After we told them that we'd be taking
revenge on you, they gladly agreed.
And now all of us are gonna make sure
you become nice and dirty... using these.
Smells horrible doesn't it?
That's 'cuz all of us haven't taken a bath in a week.
An entire week?!
Come on, I worked hard to get it dirty, just for you, Miwa.
Lick it for me.
N-No!!
Don't be like that, just have a taste!
How's it feel to have a dirty dick in your mouth?
Don't bite now, or this is going in your pussy next.
Yeah, that's good. Lick all the dirt off my dick.
Get a good taste of my dick before I cum, okay?
I-I'm cumming!
Oh, geez, she spit it out.
I thought you were gonna keep the floor clean, Miwa.
We're running out of time, so we gotta do this fast.
Okay, let's get started!
I'm gonna make these pretty boobs
of yours covered in my drool.
No, stop...
That's dirty! You're going to make me dirty!
Up we go.
Alright, how about you do some dick cleaning?
Wow, take a look at this everyone.
The dirt that's gotten on my dick
this past week is coming off.
N-No...
Hey, stop spacing out, Miwa.
Can you hear me in there?
Fine, whatever, let's have you sit down then.
There you go.
Oh, what a perfect view.
Pure white? That suits you, Miwa.
Wait, her panties are kinda wet... wait, is this piss?!
No frickin' way.
She pissed herself from shock!
It reeks.
Just take 'em off.
Can I have Miwa-tan's panties?
U-Uh, yeah... sure, knock yourself out.
Is the camera ready?
Yep, right here.
Okay then, start shooting.
Clean freaks are something else!
Even the deepest parts of her are so clean.
Look, Miwa, your piss reeking
pussy is getting a photo shoot.
No! No!!
Oh, back to normal, huh, Miwa?
Alright, I guess it's time for me to get my time in.
No, stop! Please!
Anything but this!
Please, stop!
Then apologize.
Apologize for treating us like idiots.
If you do, I'll think about it.
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry for saying all those mean things!
I won't say any of that stuff again!
So please! Please forgive me!
Oh, good. You really apologized to us.
Like hell we'd forgive you, you fucking bitch!
You really thought you'd get
away with saying all those things?
Did you forget to clean your brain?!
Take it out! Take it out!
Are you an idiot or something?
Why the hell would I take it out?!
Take a good look, Miwa!
My one week's worth of dick dirt
is being pumped inside your pussy!
Hey, Shintani, aren't you done yet?
We can't wait any longer.
Sorry guys.
Jack off as much as you want.
I-It smells so bad.
Everything's so dirty.
I'm cumming!
Me too!
Let's cum on her together!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum on her face!
Me too!
Cover her! Let's cover her in our stuff!
I can't hold it in!
I'm gonna keep cumming until I'm empty!
Get her dirty!
Soak her skin with the smell of our cum!
I'm gonna take a taste.
I'm gonna... ah, I don't care anymore!
No! Stop already!
Shut up! I'm gonna cum again, so take it in!
Take it with your womb!
Get pregnant with our cum!
You dirty girl!
No!!
It's coming out...
Now...
You're finally going to leave me alone now, right?
I need to go to the hospital.
Yeah, I'm done with you for now.
I am, at least.
Damn, that smells.
Can't smell anything but cum!
Finally our turn?
I'm about to burst!
I'm ready to cum all over her.
Yeah, I'm just getting warmed up!
Let's get this started.
Her asshole's pretty great!
I'm cumming!
I think if we widen it enough, two can fit in here...
Hell yeah, two dicks fit inside here.
Oh, god, I'm peeing.
Sorry Miwa, I couldn't hold it in.
Let's wrap it up, I guess.
Yeah, the teachers should be coming back now anyway.
Alright, Miwa. Cleanup the mess now, you got it?
Dude, she can't even hear you.
After getting cummed inside for the
twentieth time, she stopped being responsive.
This is gonna be annoying, so let's
just stuff her in the cleaning closet.
Ew, I don't wanna touch her. She's so dirty.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч