Looking for a guy tomorrow night.
Let's meet in Minekura, at the
warehouse in the mountains.
This isn't compensated dating,
so you don't need to pay me.
S-Subject:
Please...
Please take my virginity!
Subj: Please take my virginity
Looking for a guy tmrw nigth!!
Let's meet in Minekura, at the
warehouse in the mountains.
This isn't compensated dating,
so you don't have to pay me.
A-And post!
I actually did it...
My name is Tooyama Haruka,
and I just made that unbelievable post.
Where's my common sense, you ask?
Well, this all started at lunch break.
...so, like,
the guy I'm fucking goes all, "you're
not a virgin?!" Like, what an idiot!
These days, it's a surprise when
a girl doesn't have experience!
The girl who's talking about sex
is my classmate, Miwa-chan.
She's cheerful and stylish, and
the whole class loves her.
I'm a basic, average girl,
so I kind of look up to her.
What's this?
Is this too mature for the virgin
in the room, Haruka?
Wh-What should I do?
If they find out I'm a virgin, they'll think I'm a loser!
I-I'm not a virgin!
I'm experienced!
Really?
Then show us some proof,
like a picture of you having sex or something.
A-A picture?!
Surprised? You're lying, aren't you?
I'm not lying!
Fine! I'll have sex tomorrow, and I'll take a picture!
Everybody Loves Somebody!
Find a partner!
I really thought about what to do,
then I posted on a dating site's message
board that I want to lose my virginity.
Come to think of it, I'm doing something
really out there, aren't I?
Just so I can fit in, I'm going to have sex with...
B-But I am interested in sex,
so it might be nice.
Will anyone want to be with someone like me?
What if nobody comes?
next day - warehouse
What's all this?!
We're deciding who'll take your virginity,
so just wait a second!
They're deciding with rock, paper, scissors!
U-Um, why are so many of you here?
I-I'm just a virgin!
That's why!
But of course!
Don't underestimate lolicon!
Thanks for waiting.
I-I won, so...
R-Ready when you are.
O-OK, I'm ready.
Should I undress you?
No, I'll take them off myself!
stare
Wh-Why are you all still here?
We came all the way here.
We can't leave now.
Wh-Why not let them stay?
They all came here just for you.
Th-That's true, but...
More importantly, I can't wait any longer!
W-Wow.
I'm about to have that cock inside me!
Let's do it, OK?
I'm taking your top off. It's OK, right?
Um, yes!
Look at her virgin breasts!
They're looking at my bare skin!
They're all looking! It's... It's...
It's making me feel strange!
H-Hey, put it in me.
Please, put it in me!
O-OK.
Oh, you're so wet!
Don't say that!
I-I'm putting it in, OK?
His cock is going in!
What a virgin pussy!
It's so tight!
OK, I'm going to start moving.
Let's enjoy this, OK?
I-I'm gonna cum!
Wh-Where do you want me to finish?
A-Anywhere is fine.
A-Anywhere, right?
Then I'm cumming inside!
I'm cumming, inside you!
Here it comes!
That was so intense, so suddenly!
S-So this is what sex is...
Miwa-chan, you've been enjoying this for so long...
Whew, that was great!
Congrats on popping your cherry!
Oh, thanks.
Thank you very much.
Now I'll take a picture, show it to Miwa-chan, and...
It went in!
Wh-What are you doing?!
I couldn't hold back.
Do it with us too!
N-No!
Stop it!
Even though you were just moaning in pleasure?
Plus, these days it's normal to be experienced.
Th-That's right.
Miwa-chan's done lots of sexy things
with a bunch of partners!
I want to do those things too!
And his cock felt nice...
I want to try having all kinds of sex!
I... I...
I want to have sex with all you!
Teach my body everything you know!
Seriously?
Oh yeah!
All right! I'm cumming!
H-Hey, I want to put it in from behind!
OK, go ahead.
Fuck me lots, OK?
I just planned on losing my virginity,
but I'm having sex with so many people!
I'm such a slut!
She's only had two dicks inside her!
Her pussy's still fresh!
Here I come!
It's...
The semen inside is all slippery!
It feels good!
It feels so good!
Will you take me in your mouth?
Yes!
I thought I was next!
Don't fight, please.
I'll take you both at once.
This is the best!
There's so much cock!
I-I'm gonna cum!
I'm going to cum on your face.
My face?
Yes! Cum all over my face!
I can cum inside you, right?
Y-Yes!
Cum! Cum deep inside me!
I'm cumming too!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I came... Your cocks made me cum!
We're next, but...
um, well...
Are you OK with thin cocks?
Also, we're virgins...
But they're really long, so you're fine!
Girlie, I thought of something fun.
See we take...
What? You want to try that?
I'll take both of your virgin cocks inside
my pussy at the same time.
B-B-B-Both at once!
They're going in!
They went in!
My pussy swallowed your two cocks!
Alright,
here I go, OK?
They're stirring up my insides!
W-Wow!
As if... As if I could hold back!
I'm putting mine in too!
I'll cum really fast, so it's OK, right?
Wait, what? Wait!
That's my ass...
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
This is too intense!
Sex is amazing!
I'm next!
Me too! Me too!
Of course!
But first, there's one thing...
OK, I'm taking it.
Smile!
OK, we did what you asked. Let's fuck!
Quickly!
I want to try two cocks, one pussy too!
All right!
In exchange, let's try all sorts of erotic play, OK?
I stayed up, doing it three
times with each of them...
I'm still full of semen!
But it felt so good!
Oh, it's... Miwa-chan!
Huh?
Look at this! It's that sex picture you wanted!
I did it with 50 people!
They all came inside me! Thank
God I'm not pregnant!
Then I used a vibrator and
a bunch of other sex toys.
We stayed up all night having all kinds of sex!
And when I took two cocks inside
my pussy at once, it...
Um, what's wrong, Miwa-chan?
Pervert!
Was it something I said?
His name sounds like "nakadashi" (creampie). It's a pun.
My name is Nakada Shin.
I'm an average employee at an apparel maker.
It's about time, isn't it...
Hello!
Um!
Welcome,
Haruno-chan!
Y-Yes, hello.
And this nervous girl is the landlord's daughter,
Kamata Haruno-chan.
It's been two weeks since she
started coming to my room.
She was shy, not just around strangers
but she couldn't hold a conversation
with classmates.
Realizing this, the landlord asked me, someone
she was on good terms with
to be a kind of counselor.
I'm totally not obsessed with her breasts.
So,
this is our fifth session... How do you feel?
Do you think you'll be able to
keep up a conversation soon?
Um... er... I...
I-I couldn't do it today.
When people look at me,
I-I get scared, and I can't think straight...
Oh...
It sure is hard to deal with these sorts of issues.
There's got to be something I can...
Being looked at scares you?
If that's what it is...
Where did I put that...
Oh, got it! Here it is!
Here, Haruno-chan.
Try this on!
What? Um...
Wh-What is this?
Um, Nakada-san?
What are these clothes?
They're party costumes that my company makes.
They look good on you!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Why am I wearing this?
Being looked at gets you embarrassed!
Then you just have to get used to it!
Huh?
If people's gazes scare you, just get
looked at a lot to get used to it.
Since you've got that on,
I can see your every nook and cranny!
And so...
Here I come.
Like I'm licking you all over.
You have a great bust. They're well-formed.
Your navel's beautifully shaped too!
S-Stop it...
And your skin is gorgeous!
It looks so soft!
No matter who's looking, this
is a body to be proud of!
Your ass looks healthy! It's great!
Your children will be beautiful!
And look at the back of your knees!
They're sexy, even through the costume!
It's a national treasure!
Oh, um...
This was on a whim, but am I doing
something that I really shouldn't?
I...
I'm...
H-Haruno-chan?
I'm cumming!
What?!
W-What just happened?
An orgasm?
Did she just cum?
U-Um, Haruno-chan?
When someone looks at you,
how do you feel?
L-Looked at?
Wh-When someone looks,
I feel tingly inside.
It gives me thrills.
My mind goes blank!
There's no mistaking it.
She's not shy.
She gets turned on from being watched!
She's an exhibitionist!
If so,
I'm taking this off!
No! What...
Don't...
Haruno-chan, let's have sex.
If we have sex, it'll be the most
embarrassing thing you do,
so you should be cured!
I can't hold back!
This is all for your sake, Haruno-chan!
It's not like I'm thinking anything lewd here!
Wow, get a load of these erect nipples!
That's something I'd say if I was lewd, but I'm not!
Your pussy,
It's like the great flood!
I-I'm taking off your panties, OK?
Alright?
Look, your ass and your pussy are on full display!
Now I've seen every last bit of your body!
You came again!
Now I'll take a good look inside.
You make a great face when you cum!
I never would know you're shy!
You're so wet!
I'll clean you up.
Don't lick me!
Your tongue's going inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
H-Haruno-chan,
I want to do something even more embarrassing.
I can put it inside, right?
What?!
Nakada-san,
w-wait! Wait!
This is my first time, so...
It'll be fine.
You're so wet down there, so it won't be painful!
Th-That's not it...
I want to give my virginity to someone I...
You're so slippery and warm inside!
You're taking my cock inside.
Your pussy is so sexy, Haruno-chan!
OK, I'm going to show you something
even more embarrassing!
Wow, you're making such a lewd face right now!
It's such a lewd face, Haruno-chan!
That's right! Let's save that face of yours for later!
Here it is!
It's the latest model,
so it'll take great pictures!
Wh-What?
Are you going to...
That's right!
First let's take one of that face
melting with pleasure.
Look, it's the cock that stole your virginity!
Let's get them both in the picture!
N-No!
Open it more! Wider!
Let me see deep inside.
That's it. Open your mouth as wide as you can.
Look here!
That's nice!
Shake your hips some more!
You have my cock in you,
and I have a clear view of your ass!
It turns me on when people look
at these parts of my body,
so this feels so good!
Y-You've started really...
Nakada-san...
What?
More, more!
Look at me more!
Teach me more embarrassing things!
H-Haruno-chan?
All right! Well said!
I'll give you the most embarrassing memory ever!
Look, there's that spot on the second floor, right?
If we have sex on this windowsill,
who knows how many people will see us?
I'm getting naked outside, where
anyone could see me!
It seems you liked it before.
I'm going to put it inside again!
Yes!
Don't look!
I'm having sex where anyone might see me!
Look,
that passerby is watching!
I'm gonna cum!
Someone's looking, and I'm gonna cum!
I-I'm cumming!
Look at me! Look at me cum!
H-Haruno-chan, I should have said this
earlier, but I'm so sorry for before!
I-I got carried away,
and I didn't know what to say after that.
I-I never thought you'd come to see me.
There's something I want you to see.
What?
You're not mad?
I'm having so much fun!
I've completely gotten over my shyness!
It's all thanks to you, Nakada-san!
– I-I've done something terrible!
– I did it with 10 people today!
Translations: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч