My name is Hibino Yua.
I'm an idol who not only sings but does
gravure photo shoots as well.
I'm just your everyday idol.
During my time as an idol, I adopted a certain character.
What kinda guys do you like, Yua-chan?
I like... guys that are big and thick?
– Huh? Yua-chan, that's not something you shoud say.
– The character I played was a dirty girl.
– You really shouldn't be saying that!
I had a soft face with a big rack.
I just overflowed with a sexual aura, so my manager
suggested that I acted like some kind of dirty girl.
At first, I really didn't intend to do it.
What is Yua-chan's
eak point?
Interesting Idol Rumors
If somebody touches my ears, I get really hot.
But thanks to it, I stood out even more
on TV and I started getting more work.
Cum Cum Keep cumming!
But... there were some bad times too.
The reactions of people when they saw me.
Hey,
wanna
suck
my
dick?
Hey,
it's the
pervert
girl
Chuckie
Hey, it's Yua.
Wow, she's hot.
Hey, wanna suck my dick?
The person they saw was just some
personality I made up, but...
Everyone saw me as some kind of slut.
Hey, wanna go to a
hotel after this? Hehe <3
Hey, let's go to a hotel after this.
But the real me hadn't even had her first time yet.
Demon's Smartphone.
With it, you can take a picture of any girl and...
Make them do anything you want them to do.
It's an item from the demon realm.
This is a tale of girls who were victims
of such a smartphone.
Idol Manipulation
Dressing Room
Hibino Yua
The director tried coming onto me again today.
That was a big problem.
Yua-chan, this box is from the event today.
I'll leave the gifts over here.
Okay.
If there's anything you don't want, just
leave it and we'll get rid of it later.
There's a lot of weird stuff as usual.
I have another meeting I have to
go to, so I'll be going now, okay?
Go home by yourself today, okay?
Okay.
Another day, another box filled with weird presents.
I'm not even gonna use any of this.
They're giving this to my persona, not me.
I'm not even a dirty girl like they think I am.
I haven't even had sex with anyone yet.
Their dirty eyes, dirty flirting, and dirty
presents... I don't want any of that.
They just slapped that label on me by themselves.
They think I'm really a slut.
Maybe I should quit.
Hey, nice to meet you, Hibino Yua-chan.
Good morning!
U-Uh...
If I remember right, this guy is the president
of the really popular idol agency, Big Penny...
You're President Penokin, right?
He has some weird rumors floating around him especially
ones with him being involved with the idols he works with.
You've been really making a name for yourself.
I see you on TV.
You like big and thick men, right?
You like sucking them too, right?
U-Uh...
Well, uh...
How about this? You wanna try sucking my dick?
Uh, I have plans, so...
Then how about just a picture then.
Huh? What? What's this feeling?
This is bad. There's something really off about this guy!
I shouldn't let myself get involved with him.
I'll be leaving now.
I order you, Hibino Yua's legs can no longer move.
Huh?
My legs... I can't move them!
You can't run away anymore.
Now that I have my eyes on you now.
Once my eyes are on you, you only have two options.
One, become my woman. Two, get raped by me.
Huh? Wh-What are you saying?
What's going on?
My legs won't move!
Do you know the reason why my idol
agency has shot up in popularity?
It's because I can manipulate women.
See, just like this.
Huh? What was that right now?
It was like someone was feeling my breasts.
Why?!
No one even touched me though!
But it feels like my breasts are...
It feels like they're being felt up, it feels so dirty!
I like that expression.
But we're only just getting started.
Let's play with a part of you that's a little more sensitive.
What's going on?!
What's happening?
Nobody's even touching me, but
my boobs and my pussy are...
You weren't lying on TV when you
said you're really sensitive there.
N-No, that's...
This can't be... My entire body is getting so hot!
Why does this feel so good?
Feel good?
You really are a dirty girl, Yua-chan.
No!
Why am I getting so turned on?
I can't hold on anymore!
If this keeps up, I'm gonna...
What's the matter? You've been making
some very dirty sounds for a while now.
Should I let you cum right here?
No! I don't know what's going on,
but I won't give into this man!
My legs may not move, but my hands can!
Seriously, stop! I mean it! I hate this kind of thing!
Well well. So does that mean all that stuff you
said on TV about loving dirty stuff was a lie?
Lying to your audience? That's not good.
I think you need to be punished.
Hibino Yua folds her arms behind her back.
No! My hands too?!
I told you, didn't I?
I can manipulate women.
You're out of moves, Yua-chan.
Now it's time for me to play with
you without any resistance.
What's wrong with this person?
What's going on?!
Why is he here? Why is he doing this to me?!
I can do more than just manipulate your body.
I can do this too.
Your boobs are now as sensitive as your clitoris.
Huh?!
What's going on?!
Now your boobs are incredibly sensitive, Yua-chan.
Are you gonna cum just from me playing with your boobs?
Like this.
My breasts... They're so sensitive. What's going on?!
I'll change your body and heart
so that they'll both desire me.
Your ear's sensitivity is now the same as your pussy's.
No, my ear is...
See? Now you're the way that you said you were on TV.
If somebody touches your ears, you get hot, isn't that right?
I'm gonna cum!
I think I'm gonna cum!
He's only licking my ear and playing with my
breasts, so why do I feel this turned on?!
N-No, I...
I'm cumming!
No... in a dressing room... with a man I just met...
I just came.
So you wear these provocative outfits and say all these
dirty things, but you actually don't like dirty stuff?
This isn't something that can be forgiven.
Did cumming make you a little
more interested in dirty stuff?
Huh? Not one bit. Just give u...
Huh? You're a lot more strong-willed than you are on TV.
– It looks like this needs a little more training.
– No! Stop! That's...
No, it feels so good!
It just feels too good!
My ear, my breasts, and my vagina just feel too good!
They all feel too good!
I'm not this kind of girl! I'm not dirty!
But I can't... I can't hold back anymore!
I can't!
Well well. So you let out that kind
of moan when you cum, huh?
I think you've become quite the dirty girl.
Dressing Room
Hibino Yua
Let's continue this at your place. Okay?
So like that he forced me to take him home with me.
Even in the taxi, he played with my body without
even caring that we weren't in a private place.
He made me cum so many times while our driver watched.
He stopped me from being able to resist with
whatever strange power he was using.
It was so embarrassing, but I couldn't do anything to resist.
Yua-chan, the driver's watching.
Don't mind us, please keep driving.
This doesn't happen every day, so how about
we put on a show for our driver?
No!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
And like that, he forced his way into my house...
And then he found all the dirty
objects that my fans sent me.
Vibrators, rotors, and bondage.
You have quite the dirty toys in your possession.
N-No. My fans gave...
I've... never used them!
I've never used them!
But they're gifts from your fans.
You gotta use them.
For the following three hours, he rubbed, licked, and
played with my entire body as if it was his toy.
And since I couldn't move my legs or arms, I just
had to lay there and cum over and over again.
How's this, Yua-chan?
I think you might've cum close to a hundred times by now.
Just feels too good to stop, right?
Are you starting to like dirty things now?
Try and say it. Say "I really love dirty things. I'm a dirty girl."
Why... would I? I hate it. I hate dirty things.
I...
Oh, I see. Well, I guess I'm left with no choice.
You're only saying this because you don't
know what it really feels like yet.
Wait, no. What are you doing?!
Isn't it obvious? I'm gonna teach
you about sex and what it is.
After this, you'll really become a dirty girl, Yua-chan.
Stop! Please!
Anything but this! No!
No! My first time... it was taken by this horrible...
You said on TV, didn't you?
You love them big and thick! So take a
good taste of what a real one is like!
Stop!
Take it out! Take it out!
I guess it's kinda rough since it's your first time.
Oh? Is that your phone?
Looks like it's from your manager.
Wait...
Should probably take this call.
No!
Oh, Yua-chan? Good work today.
No! Not now!
Yua-chan? Hey, what's wrong?
Crap, this guy...
He's thrusting it in me when I'm trying to talk!
– I need to hold my voice back!
– Well anyway, I have some big news for you!
– She's going to find out!
Your next role has been decided!
You're going to be the secondary heroine!
This is a big deal!
Apparently, you'll be working directly with the heroine.
This is a really important job for you.
No! I can't hold my voice back!
This drama doesn't need you to act flirty.
There's definitely gonna be a bigger audience.
Maybe it'd be a good idea to change your
persona to a more eloquent character?
You did say that you wanted to stop your flirty character.
Yua's sensitivity is now 10 times higher
What's wrong?
Yua-chan, what's wrong?
N-Noth...
Is someone there, Yua-chan?
Yua-chan?
What's wrong?!
What are you doing?
My body's gotten so sensitive, I can't hold my voice back!
– Come on, tell your manager.
– Yua-chan? Yua-chan?
– Tell her that you love dirty stuff.
– Yua-chan? Are you there?
– Tell her that you'll play the flirty, slutty character more from now on.
– Yua-chan? Yua-chan? Hello?
– Is there something wrong? Are you okay?!
– No! No!! I don't like it!
– Yua-chan?!
– I really don't like it!
Yua-chan?
If you don't say anything, I'm gonna cum right inside you.
Yua-chan? Hello?
I actually really like dirty stuff!
Yua-chan? Yua-chan?!
Yua-chan? Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?!
Yua-chan?
Did something happen?
Are you okay?
Yua-chan, he...
Well said.
This persona of yours isn't fake anymore.
It's who you really are now.
Isn't that great, Yua-chan?
Now you'll be able to be even more
lewd when you go on TV.
If you ever want to know more about this
dirty stuff, I'll help you out anytime.
I'll train your body until I get bored of it.
Yua-chan makes a peace sign with her fingers and looks at me.
Okay lets get a photo to remember this by. Look at
me and make a peace sign with both your hands.
Yua-chan makes a peace sign with her fingers and looks at me.
No!
To commemorate your first time, I'll cum inside you while
you're making the peace sign with both your hands!
N-No!
This pose is so demeaning!
But it just feels too good, my head is going blank!
I'm cumming!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
qualitycontrol: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч