Due to extreme decline in marital and birth rates
the modern era is unable to mitigate the decline in population.
The government passed a bill to counter this existing problem.
Libido Facilitation Family Plan Act.
Dubbed the Double SK Program.
An idol unit who can have sex, sing, as well as dance is assembled.
Aimed at increasing the sexual desire of males to increase population.
It's an ultimate project to save the human's population.
I'm Ami, nice to meet you.
O-Onii-chan!
Waku-FAPsubs (Naoya)
Idol Cadet - Ami Arc
I was so surprised it's Onii-chan.
Really?
Yeassh! The thought never crossed my mind.
Well, we aren't exactly true siblings. More like childhood friends.
But Onii-chan is Onii-chan! Hmph!
Am I not cut out for it?
Of course not...
Hey, Onii-chan.
Could you take off your shirt?
Sure.
It's embarrassing, Onii-chan.
I'm sorry. My breasts are small.
Nonsense, they are lovely.
O-Onii-chan, it feels good.
Onii-chan, it's embarrassing. Stop staring there.
Oniii-chan!
I feel so strange. I'm becoming weird!
So a virgin can climax too.
Onii-chan, you meanie.
It's my turn to make you feel good.
I'm sorry. Yours are huge, so I couldn't fit it in totally.
I wanted you to feel good too.
Don't worry. I feel great already.
It's about time we fuck.
OK, I'm putting it in.
OK.
It hurts...
S-Sorry. I'll pull it out right now.
Don't. I can't become an Idol Cadet if you take it out now.
I'm alright. Please, Onii-chan.
OK.
I'm gonna move.
Just feels strange.
Onii-chan, I'm all weird now.
I'm becoming a whore.
I'm cumming!
It's alright, Onii-chan. You can cum inside, inside of me!
Thank you so much, Onii-chan. I love you best!
Due to extreme decline in marital and birth rates
the modern era is unable to mitigate the decline in population.
The government passed a bill to counter this existing problem.
Libido Facilitation Family Plan Act.
Dubbed the Double SK Program.
An idol unit who can have sex, sing, as well as dance is assembled.
Aimed at increasing the sexual desire of males to increase population.
It's an ultimate project to save the human's population.
Sorry for the wait.
Oh, it's you!
Idol Cadet - Shizuka Arc
I'm glad you're my first.
Me too.
We are close friends, aren't we. And we'll continue to-
Don't talk about close friends! I-I've always had a crush on you, but I couldn't confess.
When you applied to become an Idol Cadet, what I can do is only this.
Please be more gentle.
Eat it.
Look. You're already so wet down here.
No, it's embarrassing.
No matter how much of an elegant lady facade you appear
you're still a shameless woman.
Please don't say such things.
I'll have to punish a slut like you.
Here I come!
NOOO!!! It hurts. It really hurts. Please stop.
No...
That's right, cry. Scream! Moan!
It hurts, please...
No, please be gentle.
It feels...
...kind of good.
No, I'm about to climax.
Fuck yeah. I'm cumming.
Oh Jesus, I can see you.
I gonna cum!
Please cum inside.
Look. I can see it all.
Are you OK with this?
Thank you. With that, I can become an Idol Cadet proper.
Due to extreme decline in marital and birth rates
the modern era is unable to mitigate the decline in population.
The government passed a bill to counter this existing problem.
Libido Facilitation Family Plan Act.
Dubbed the Double SK Program.
An idol unit who can have sex, sing, as well as dance is assembled.
Aimed at increasing the sexual desire of males to increase population.
It's an ultimate project to save the human's population.
'Sup.
Idol Cadets - Kei Arc
I haven't seen your face before, are we classmates?
Yeah.
I'm at your care today.
Same here.
I-Is something wrong?
Don't tell me it's your first time?
Yeah.
Really? Me too.
Let's try our best, regardless.
Oh, sorry. You were suddenly so close, I just...
Hey, such behavior of yours...
I can see your panties.
They are not.
Brushing that aside, are we going to bed?
You're pretty good, aren't you?
Could you help me undo my bra?
I'm fine. Do whatever you want.
Nice. It doesn't feel bad at all.
Feels good. I like it. I want... I want yours too.
This is something out of the ordinary?
I'm about to...
Sorry.
It's fine. Look, you're still so hard.
Could you also help me remove them down there?
Now, come.
It hurts.
Are you alright? Should we stop?
As if... I'm alright. Just carry on like this.
OK. I'll continue.
Ouch.
Are you really alright?
Yeah, just continue.
OK.
Somehow, I'm starting to feel good.
T-That's it. Just like that.
Let's do it, let's do it from behind this time.
Fucking good.
Something is coming, something is coming!
I'm cumming.
Go on! Come inside of me! Inside of me!
It's coming in!
I climaxed even though it's my first time.
Thanks.
The gratitude is all mine, since I became an Idol Cadet.