From the people's idol group, IKB31,
comes the new group, Platinum Kiss.
Our motto is:
We'll make you ours, to the highest quality!
My name is Takano Ayaka.
Former IKB31 member
Takano
Ayaka
Ayachii
I've also debuted in TV and posed as a gravure idol,
so I'm always very busy.
I'm not quite there yet,
but I'm doing my best to become the best idol there is!
Kamii
MaKi
MaKinya
She's Kamii MaKi,
the lively type that's also very athletic.
She can be quite shy,
but her flustered expression is an invitation for people to hug her,
it's one of her many charm points.
Ooizumi
Maina
Maimai
Finally, we have another former IKB31 member,
Ooizumi Maina.
She's absolutely the bomb when it comes to her breasts.
You never know if she's the clueless type, or the careful type.
Anyway, she's also lively and "jiggly"!
I've dreamt of being an idol for a long time,
under the flowery scene that you usually see,
there's actually a strict realm where one
must compete to remain popular.
The reason I'm able to survive in this harsh battlefield,
is probably because of him.
My big bro.
The manager of Platinum Kiss.
Thank you for the hard work.
Hey, why don't we grab some ice cream on the way home?
The shops were handing out flyers.
That's a great idea!
I love ice cream, too.
It seems they're having a promo campaign.
Wow, they already have a new flavor!
Wait, what does a "mysterious cheese'' flavor taste like?
Oh, aren't you on a diet, Maki-chan?
Please don't count that against me today!
I already heard that excuse last week.
She really did.
But, I don't really think I need to go on a diet.
You're always physically active.
But my work as a gravure idol is getting more hectic nowadays.
Of course I worry about it.
As for me, I'm worried that I'm piling
up more pounds than I should.
You, Maimai,
already have that nice body of yours!
Were you trying to make me feel bad with those words earlier?
No, I didn't mean to!
I want to be fit like you, too!
There she goes,
it's time for her harassment again.
I think I've had my share of that, too.
Instead of ice cream,
I think I'll just eat you instead.
She's always goofing around whenever she's not working.
The three of us are especially close with one another.
It feels great when we wind down and go on a trip after work.
I was really happy when this group was formed.
Oh yeah, I've heard from Onii-sama,
he said he might not be there for tomorrow's event.
He seems to be busy with other things.
Is that so...
But since it's him we're talking about,
maybe he'll just drop by suddenly without telling us?
I hope so.
It'll feel quite lonely on stage if he's not there for us.
Now I'm getting worried if things will go smoothly.
Hey now, you two,
you're just overthinking things.
It'll be okay!
We'll make it somehow, even if he's gone for a while.
Oh yeah, let's go to a karaoke afterward!
I think we'll feel a lot better after singing our hearts out!
I see, so all of us really feel uneasy without him after all.
So yeah, that goes for me, too...
Excuse me.
There's one more hour before the event starts.
Please have your preparations complete by then.
Okay!
What are we going to do, Ayacchi?
I never thought I'd feel this nervous without Onii-san.
A-Anyway, I think we can feel at ease by just hearing his voice!
Please, answer it... or else.
Please
don't open
Broken
Eh?
Is it just me, or is the ringtone coming from inside that locker?
It can't be...
Alright, I'm opening it up.
Okay.
Hey there.
Man, I messed up big time.
I forgot to switch my phone off.
You...
We would have reported you already if you weren't our manager!
Wait, you were inside there the whole time?
I was peeping, so of course I was.
I really don't know where to start complaining.
Besides, there are at least fifteen hidden
cameras all over this room.
I don't want to waste a single moment of your career.
Wait, so that means... even when we're changing?
Of course.
Ayacchi, your Onii-san really is a pervert.
Idols should always be active, whenever
an opportunity presents itself.
With this, your steps in becoming the perfect idol will...
Hey, you're not saying you were busy yesterday because of this?
Indeed I was.
Are you all right, Onii-san?!
So today's color is pink...
Just die!
Yep, that's my big bro.
An idol otaku, and a hardcore siscon.
He also applied as a manager at the
same time I debuted as an idol.
Jeez, Ayachhi, you were too harsh!
And now he's with us as our own manager.
Just leave him be!
My head hurts just trying to explain it.
Please hang on!
Maki, the way your short pants are squeezed
between your nether regions is the best.
Please don't look, get away from me!
Maki is...
I'm sorry!
Enough of that, please listen!
We're in big trouble!
We're about to perform, but we just
can't get into the rhythm today.
What should we do, Onii-sama?
Even now, here.
Can you feel it?
My pounding heartbeat.
Please send us to the stage as you always do.
It's starting to feel really good just by touching your lips.
Please support us like you always do with your body.
Because it's all your fault that I've become this erotic.
I'll have you take responsibility for this... okay?
We're okay with this, right?
Jeez, you're such an honest person, Maimai.
Oh wow, it's bulging, as if it's feeling really happy.
Onii-sama, your thing has become really big.
Please make yourself feel good with our mouths.
I think our mouths are about to melt with its warmth.
Amazing, it's getting even bigger...
Just please do...
Maki, Maimai, you two are really cute.
Onii-san's thing is starting to get really wet at the tip.
Oh wow...
It's going deep inside Maki-chan's mouth.
These raw breasts sure feel soft and tender.
Both my hands are really happy.
Does it feel good?
The way it goes in and out looks very erotic.
Maki, your mouth feels incredibly wet and good.
Big bro, me too...
What should I do?
Just looking at my brother is making me aroused.
We're just kissing, but it's already starting to feel really good.
I can embarrassingly tell that I'm getting wet.
Please violate my breasts this time.
Maina, your breasts feel really soft.
It feels as if it's being wrapped around marshmallows.
How is it, Onii-sama?
Can you feel it?
My mind is starting to feel numb, as I
continue licking the tip of your dick.
Nii-sama...
Please make yourself feel good with my breasts.
Aniki, your fluids taste great.
I'm going to do everything in my power to pleasure you.
Onii-sama, your dick...
The way it rubs my breasts feels good.
Me too, Maimai.
Please soil me with all of your impregnating milk.
I'm going to squirt it all over you.
Here I go.
Okay, just let it all out wherever you want to.
Release it more.
Just keep on cumming on me, please.
I'm starting to feel even hornier.
Big bro.
Because of you...
My undies... are now wet.
I can't go up on stage like this.
So... j-just do what you have to do!
Pleasure yourself all you want!
Jeez, why do I have to say such embarrassing things?
But, I really can't hold back anymore.
Huh? It easily went all the way in.
Oh crap, I'm about to cum after it just went in.
Big bro, big bro!
If you keep on moving your hips like that, I'll...
But your dick just keeps on hitting my soft spots.
It keeps on kissing the entrance to my womb.
Your dick is hitting me deep inside!
Moving your hips on your own like that,
just when did you become this sluty?
I'm like this because of you!
It feels good, big bro.
Lick my breasts more.
I'm going to cum again.
Here I go, Ayaka.
I'm going to cum inside you.
Cum, just cum.
Cum lots inside me.
Oh no, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, too.
I'm cumming while your dick plays with my womb!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
His warm fluids are pouring inside me.
It's pumping everything into my womb.
I'm so happy...
Aya, if you keep on wrapping around
it tightly, I might not stop cumming.
I'll get every single drop of yours big bro.
Lots of warm cum is inside me.
No, please don't.
We're about to start already.
The staff might come in here.
Oh? Then why is this so wet, then?
Th-That's because you keep on doing embarrassing things to me.
This lets me know that your body is giving me an A.O.K.
Amazing, her wet pussy is wrapping around me well.
I'm going to stir it up from inside up to your womb, so don't worry!
What should I do?
My wet insides are being stirred hard.
I'm constantly touching the entrance to her womb.
It'll be bad if someone sees us like this,
yet it just keeps on feeling better and better.
No, please...
My mind's going blank, I can't think straight anymore.
Onii-san, your thing is hitting all my soft spots.
Is it really all right for me to feel this good while people wait for us?
Consider this your warm up.
Onii-san!
Here I go, Maki!
Oh no...
I can't hold on anymore.
My body is taking in all the pleasure!
I'm cumming inside!
It's pumping everything, filling my insides with cum!
His hot cum makes me feel like I'm going to melt.
The way it wraps tightly around me is still the best.
You came so much inside me...
I'm going to cum lots inside your womb too, Maimai.
Okay, please do.
I want all of it, whether you squirt it outside or pour it inside.
Wow, you're really wet now.
Onii-sama, your dick is hitting me deep inside.
My breasts are jiggling a lot as you fuck me.
Your breasts, your womb, all of these are for me.
Yes, and I'm happy.
It's trying to suck me in hard.
It feels like it's going to squeeze me right to the very tip.
Your nipples are also stiff, you really are slut too, Maimai.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to become even more slutty for you, Onii-sama.
That's why, do it more, please!
I'm about to cum.
He keeps on stirring me inside with his dick,
and it's constantly hitting the entrance to my womb, too!
I'm cumming!
My womb feels all twitchy as he fills it with cum.
And my insides are now completely filled.
I've become one with you.
Me too, it felt really great.
Now then, time for round two!
We're about to perform already!
Don't worry, you'll make it somehow.
Jeez, you really are a pervert for craving
sex just before a live performance.
Why are you always...?
My oh my, you three look so sloppy.
Our live performance is about to start shortly, you know.
Come on, Aya, squeeze it some more.
Hey, big bro!
Wow, your butts are all completely exposed.
Idiot!
Stop saying embarrassing things!
Maki and Maimai's pussies also look very erotic!
Oh wow...!
I'm going cum first inside Maki.
It's already gone all the way inside!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
You're going to cum inside again.
Now your insides are even wetter as my
cum and your love juices mix together.
Onii-sama.
Here comes another round!
No, don't, my body is already...!
Here we go!
Amazing.
My insides are still being stirred as he cums.
At this rate my insides are going to be completely filled.
Oh no, the pleasure's taking over.
My body is no longer listening to me!
I'm going to cum as my pussy brings his dick further inside.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
It's pouring inside, lots of his cum is being pumped inside again.
I can't stop cumming.
It's completely filling me.
Big bro, it's really hitting deep inside me.
Big bro, you're such a meanie.
I'm going to stir your insides up too, Maimai.
Your dick is going deep inside me.
Oh wow, it's my first time feeling like this.
Can you tell how my dick is pushing in really hard?
My womb and his dick are constantly kissing.
Aya, open your mouth.
His dick is starting to rub my throat!
Drink it all, make sure no drop goes to waste.
It feels really great, with your tongue rubbing under it and all.
I want to drink his cum.
I want it all!
I'm cumming!
It's his smell.
It's overflowing inside my mouth.
It's flowing all over my tongue.
He already came many times, and it's still this thick.
It's so hot, and it's swirling around in my mouth.
I'm going to let your womb have a taste, too.
Just put it in already, big bro.
What?
Keep it up.
I want... I want both of us to feel great.
Oh yes, big bro.
Big bro.
I don't want to be separated from you.
I want us to be together forever like this!
It's going inside my womb.
Filling me up even further.
Big bro, please...
Please pour every single drop inside me!
Here we go, Ayaka!
I'm going to cum it all inside!
Cum!
Cum it all!
Fill my insides with all of your sticky cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's coming out...
It's pouring inside my womb.
Big bro, you're the best.
Here I go, Maimai.
Okay.
Onii-sama, push it harder, please!
Maki, I just can't get enough of your taste.
Jeez, you're such a pervert.
Now, you three,
we can't continue until the live performance ends.
We can't do it while we're on stage, anyway.
So lick it all you want now.
I'm going to cum!
Heads up!
Onii-sama, you've just poured lots of your love in us.
We feel okay now thanks to you, Onii-san.
We don't need to feel worried anymore.
Big bro, we're going to do our best.
Gotcha.
Oh crap, this is bad.
I can feel myself getting horny.
Onii-sama's cum is shaking inside.
Oh no, its starting to leak out slowly.
Big bro's cum is starting to overflow.
I'm cumming!
Everyone, thank you!
Good work everyone.
The event was a big success!
It's all thanks to you, big bro.
No, you're the ones who gave it your all.
That's not true.
Because you "cheered" us up just before our performance.
I felt really at ease, just by thinking that
your cum was inside my womb.
Now, now, stop being all cuddly,
and you're also drooling.
R-Really?l
Onii-sama, you always get swept away easily.
It's all thanks to him that I was able to come this far as an idol.
Okay, now that the event is over, time for some celebration!
He's an idiot, a dunce, and a total pervert,
but he thinks very dearly of us.
And he will never change.
I love him very much!