Hey, everyone!
Thanks for coming today!
My name is Amou Maria.
Amou Maria
I act, I sing, I dance... I'm your average idol.
I wasn't too popular the first year after my debut,
but I've recently started gaining popularity.
I've even gotten more fans!
The one who made this all possible
is my unit partner, Hibino Yua-chan.
Yua-chan has a serious personality, so when she had to play
dirty characters, she started appearing on more variety shows.
What is Yua-chan's
weak point?
IF SOMEBODY TOUSHES
my ears, I get really hot.
Interesting Idol Rumors
Wonderful Idol Gathering!
Resolutions for 2016
Grand Revelation SP
Cum Cum
Keep cumming!
Lucky 2016
Girl
After that, my violent personality came into the spotlight.
Hell no! I'll kill you!
TV
Surprising
Commercial for Lies and Idols
Big Idol Breakout!
The fuckers on the internet who say that are DIECES OF SHIT!
They're going straight to HELL!
Recently, I've been on TV and in magazines a lot more.
It was all going well, but...
But recently Yua-chan hasn't been
acting like her usual happy self.
Hey, Yua-chan?
You've been acting kinda down recently.
Everything okay?
Oh, really?
I don't think I'm acting any different.
Well, if you say so.
If you need anything, I'm here for you, okay?
The smartphone of demons
The smartphone of demons...
If you take
If you take a picture of a girl with it,
a picture of
a girl with it
You can make them do anything you want them to...
truly an item of nightmares
You can make them do anything you want
them to... truly an item of nightmares.
This is the story of the girls
This is the story of the girls who
were toyed with by that smartphone.
who wer toyed with by that smartphone
Idol Manipulation
Episode 2
Amou Maria
Ever since a few days ago,
I've noticed that Yua-chan's been acting strange.
But after our concert one day,
I witnessed something completely unexpected.
See you later.
Wait, where's Yua-chan?
Not sure. I haven't seen her.
Maybe she's still in the dressing room?
P-Please stop.
Not here!
Please!
What if somebody comes?!
It's fine, don't worry. Everyone's already left.
You put on a good show out there.
Everyone loves you, Yua-chan.
But nobody knows that you're doing
this behind the scenes, do they?
I always wanted to do it with you in this outfit.
P-Please stop.
How long are you going to keep doing this?
How long?
Until I get bored, of course.
I've done you so many times now,
but you're still trying to resist me?
Th-That's because, I-I don't want...
It's a shame that my phone can only
manipulate your body and not your heart.
My only choice is to keep pounding this
into your body until your mind plays along.
No... I-I can't...
He pulls me aside every day and rapes me.
And with the power of that phone of his,
he makes my body incredibly sensitive.
I want it to stop!
I don't want this, but my body wants more!
He's going to make me cum again today!
This horrible man's dick is going to make me cum!
That was good, Yua-chan.
Well then, what should we do next?
How long is this going to go on for? If this keeps up,
I'm going to really lose my mind and body to this man!
N-No, stop! Stop!
P-Please! If this goes on any longer, I...
I-I'm gonna cum!
Yua-chan?
Oh?
You're...
What are you doing to Yua-chan?!
Are you okay, Yua?
I was just passing by and I heard you scream.
Uh, Maria-chan...
That wasn't very nice.
You should really think before kicking.
I was just talking about business with Yua-chan.
Don't lie, you fucking geezer!
Yua didn't want it at all!
I guess that's that.
I was in the middle of it,
but I guess I'll end things here for today.
You're Amou Maria-chan, right?
The abrasive idol in the same unit as Yua-chan.
You look like you'd be pretty fun too.
Hey, what'd you take a picture for?!
Yua
Yesterday
Are you okay?
Today
Sorry about yester
Don't worry about me...
That was the president of the really
popular idol agency, Big Penny, Enoki.
I've heard nasty rumors about him before.
I guess he really is just as nasty a guy
as the rumors make him out to be.
What's his deal?
Private Caller
A call?
From who?
Hello? Is this Maria-chan?
Know who I am? I'm the guy you met
in the dressing room yesterday, Enoki.
Why do you know my number?
I got it from Yua-chan.
I have a lot of things I want to say to you,
but don't you think it'd be a good idea for
you to apologize for kicking me yesterday?
Huh?! Why the hell would I apologize to you?
You damn geezer. You should be apologizing!
You've got quite the mouth.
Guess I don't have a choice. Bad-mouthed girls like you
need to be punished until they're more obedient.
For now, I'll play with your boobs.
I'll make you ten times more sensitive and make you cum
over and over again with nothing but your boobs.
Where might you be right now?
Judging by the sounds, you wouldn't happen
to be in a café of some sort, would you?
I hope you can keep jour voice down.
You, see, I...
I have the power to control women.
Can you stop being a creep for one second?
There's something wrong with you.
Amou Maria's sensitivity is now ten times higher
Huh? No way.
What?
Right now it felt as if someone just touched my breasts.
Was it just my imagination?
No, I'm not imagining it.
This feeling...
What? This is definitely... is someone touching my breasts?!
That can't be...
No... Now my nipples are being touched?!
Why do my nipples feel so sensitive?!
I'll make you ten times more sensitive and make you cum
over and over again with nothing but your boobs.
Wait, did he really make me ten times more sensitive?
No way! It's happening exactly like he said!
This can't be real!
It can't be!
But... No!
Crap! This is bad!
I'm cumming!
This can't be happening.
I just came...
No! I can't believe this!
I can't stay here.
I need to get back home...
Huh? What?!
My legs won't move!
This can't be...
Is he really controlling my body?!
No!
It feels like I'm being licked!
This is bad!
It feels too good!
No!
I... cant hold back!
I'm going to...
I'm going to cum again without
even knowing what's going on!
And with the waitresses and
the customers giving me weird looks,
I kept cumming at the table without
being able to leave or even move.
I kept cumming for an entire hour.
And from then on, my days of humiliation began.
Every day, I was assaulted by some unknown force.
And there was nothing I could do to fight it.
All I could do was bear through it.
At night when I was sleeping,
my arms and legs would suddenly be held down.
And then my body would feel
like it was being groped all over.
And when I was taking a taxi,
some unknown power made me spread my legs
and then I felt as if someone was licking me.
It felt as if there really was a person right there licking me.
But there wasn't anyone there, so I couldn't fight back.
No... This is too embarrassing!
But my body's reacting and I can't stop it!
I'm going to cum in public again!
Even when I'm on the train,
this invisible power attacks me.
It comes regardless of whether
there are people around me or not.
It seeps through my entire body.
It's such an uncomfortably lewd sensation...
It almost feels if I'm being assaulted by a group of people.
Why now?!
What the hell is that geezer?!
He's going to make me...
I don't want to cum at all!
But I can't stop myself!
Crap! Crap!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
He's going to make me cum!
Even when my friends come over to hang out,
I'm suddenly assaulted.
What's wrong, Maria?
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
J-Just wait a second.
Even at a time like this?!
I can't show my friends this!
Please! Calm down!
Can I really do nothing but wait for it to be over?
No... I need to be quiet!
My friends are right outside!
His fingers...
No, not there!
I'm gonna cum!
It's over.
It's calmed down now.
Does that mean it's over for today?
It's been an entire week!
Every day I was assaulted by these weird sensations.
And it's started to feel better and better.
Huh? No way!
It's not over?!
What is this?!
Something is inside me!
No way... this is almost like a...
It's like his thing is coming inside me.
Wait! Wait!
I'm getting so hot deep inside me!
Crap, this is not good!
What's the matter?
Are you okay, Maria?
I-I'm fine...
I can't hold back my voice!
No... hold it back!
No! I-I need to keep it together!
Why?!
Why is this happening?!
I can't run away and I can't push him away either.
My body won't listen to me!
How sensitive have I become?
I can control women.
Is he really controlling me?
I won't lose to that bastard!
I definitely don't want to lose!
But, this is...
Even after that, the urge didn't subside.
My friends who came over went home at some point.
Even after they went home,
my body continued to feel pleasure.
I kept cumming all through the night.
No more! How many times am I going to cum?!
It feels too good, I can't do anything!
I've came way too much. I can't think straight!
By the time it was two in the morning,
I must have came a hundred times.
I thought it was finally over and I could rest.
But then, I got a call.
Maria-chan, this has been going on for two weeks,
but you still haven't come to apologize.
You!
I thought you just played a tough, abrasive character,
but I guess you really are a woman with a backbone.
How was it today?
Did I embarrass you in front of your friends?
How do you know that?!
I have my ways.
I got your schedule from Yua-chan.
So, did you enjoy the past two weeks?
Change your mind and feel like apologizing yet?
What are you? What are you doing?!
Is this all your doing?!
Oh, right.
I heard from Yua-chan.
You have a really really important concert
the day after tomorrow, don't you?
You sure about that?
What if what happened in front of your
friends today happens on the stage?
You might be cumming the entire time
you're on stage... in front of all your fans.
Maybe I should keep playing with your
pussy the entire time you're singing?
You might become famous on the internet.
I could even make your hand the same sensitivity as your
clitoris when you do the hand shaking event afterwards.
I bet it'd be fun to cum every time
you shake someone's hand.
I'd personally recommend that
you apologize as soon as poss...
Wait! Just wait a second!
Are you really....
The concert two days from now is our concert
commemorating our first year since we debuted.
It's a culmination of all our hard work and
it's a concert that we can't afford to mess up.
For the members, the staff,
and the fans... We can't let it fail!
I don't want to... I really don't want to, but...
I...
I'm glad you came, Maria-chan.
So, are you finally ready to apologize?
U-Uh, I went too far when I kicked you.
I-I'll admit that, but...
That's not nearly enough.
You really think that's an apology?
Your heart wasn't in it at all.
Amou Maria's body cannot move
Fine. I guess I'll have to punish you a little more.
A-Again?!
My body can't move again!
You had a strange experience these past two weeks, right?
It just so happens that I have a strange smartphone.
I can control any girl that I photograph using my phone.
Huh? Control?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Amou Maria will take off her clothes.
Shit! Stop!
What's going on?!
Stop! Don't look!
Don't look!
That's good.
You have a body that's just as good as Yua-chan's.
Okay, now walk over here and sit on my lap.
No! That's...
No way!
No! My body's moving on its own again!
Good, good. Just like that.
Point your ass this way.
No!
And lower your hips down slowly.
No! My body's doing it on its own!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Frustrated?
But you're the one who came here, Maria-chan.
Stop!
No!
Take it out! Take it out!
You shitty geezer!
Die!
Looks like your switch got flipped.
You've been trained pretty well these last
two weeks since you've been cumming non-stop.
I don't think you can resist the pleasure
from your body anymore.
No! I'm... This guy's going to make me...
It's only been ten minutes since your punishment started.
We've only just started.
You're not at your limit already, are you?
P-Please stop.
I wonder if you've gotten any politer.
Looks like you're a little more honest now.
But I want you to be even more honest.
Let's turn your sensitivity up a hundredfold!
No! Wh-What is this?
My body's going crazy!
Crap, even breathing makes me...
Just him touching me a little
is going to make me cum!
This isn't...
Let's pick up where we left off.
Wait!
Please! I can't!
Please stop!
No! I apologize!
I'm sorry!
So, please...
It'd be a waste to make you feel pleasure with
just my dick now that your body's so sensitive.
I'll spread the pleasure across your body.
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
So, please...
Looks like you finally apologized from the heart.
I'm a nice guy.
So maybe I'll let you off the hook.
So how about you show me your youth
and do a double peace sign while you cum?
No... What's going on?!
My head's going blank!
I'm cumming!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч