This boxed lunch doesn't even have fried meat in it!
They're getting too lazy.
with a girl in my class,
can you teach me
a few hypnosis tricks?
a girl in your class...
I want to have sex
with a girl in your class...
with a girl in my class,
can you teach me
a few hypnosis tricks?
This must be an idiot.
Here I will teach you a real
Hypnosis Technique
The details are
in the URL below
inter at your own risk!
Just bait I guess.
That bitch.
I-I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm glad.
See you then.
Takuma-kun, you've got rice on your cheek.
See?
Bye now!
Itou Megumi, one of my classmates.
If I could just date her,
I bet every single day would feel magical.
Eating her homemade lunch together...
Arms together while going on dates...
Since we're already going out, we could even have sex.
If I only had some special ability...
I could then bring all my dreams into reality.
Even though I really think this hypnosis thing is a sham,
Real Hypnosis
Download Complete
I couldn't help but give it a try.
Real Hypnosis
Complete Control
Brainwashed and Subordinated - Raw Sex Life!
Part 01: Grab that unrequited love
from the girl of your dreams
Why am I here...?
Takuma-kun.
Megumi-chan.
From now on you're my girlfriend.
What's the matter, Takuma-kun?
What... is this?
Can't move?
You can't move, right, Megumi-chan?
Alright then...
Can you give me a good smooch?
This can't be.
My body is moving on its own!
No!
Let's see, next one is...
I want to see your panties.
N-No...
This can't be...
This is embarrassing and yet my...!
Wh-Why?!
No, don't come closer!
Don't...
Stop rubbing my legs.
It smells great.
No, stop sniffing!
Stop, don't touch me there!
Your virgin pussy feels so tender.
Stop...
Oh?
You're getting aroused from the pleasure.
This just can't feel good!
P-Please, stop this already.
Please?
I just need to do this, right?
No, no...
Don't...
Stop...
It's very wet,
it feels really good after all, right?
Megumi-chan,
I wonder what we should do next?
Wh-What is it?
Save me...
Stop...
It's dirty.
How rude.
Clean it then.
Huh?
What is this?
No...
There now, you have to clean it properly with your mouth.
That's good, Megumi-chan.
Just keep on using your tongue.
I think we're ready now.
No...
Somebody save me...
I can't put it in properly.
Let me take a closer look.
No, no!
Now I can see it better.
Please let me be already.
Alright. Can't be helped then.
Takuma-kun...
I'll put on a condom for you.
No, that's not what I meant!
Stop...
Huh? But we're just about to get started!
It hurts!
Your virginity is now mine, Megumi-chan.
Please, somebody save me...
Now then, let's enjoy our time together as one.
No...
Don't push it deeply.
It hurts!
It feels gross.
Stop pushing already...
Amazing,
your insides feel really great!
Don't push too hard!
Don't be so rough with me...
If you keep talking loudly like that,
somebody might come here.
No, don't...!
Please...don't push too hard like that!
Sorry, but I think I'm about to let it all out!
No...!
Please let it be over already!
Oh, the condom got left inside.
That felt so good that I came a lot.
All this cum, is all because of you.
Please, let's use some protection.
I can't wrap myself around my 'condom'
if you don't lower your hips more.
No, any more and...
Let my dick kiss you already.
Oh no, I can't fight it.
I can perfectly see where you're 'eating' my dick.
My butt...
Please don't slap my butt.
It's the duty of the man to please his girl, right?
Then I'll just have to do my best.
Your insides feels like they're having a good time.
That's not true.
Stop this already.
Don't push it too hard.
If you keep pushing that hard...
This feels really great.
Looks like our bodies are actually meant for each other.
No...
You don't sound too convincing with
your pussy tightly gripping me.
Here I come.
Take it all in, okay?
No, I don't want that!
Please let me be already!
I'm going to get pregnant!
No...
Pull it out immediately!
Don't stir it like that.
How terrible.
Cu-Cumming that much inside me like that...
I'm getting excited about our future already.