Megumi!
Let's go for lunch together!
Sorry, but I have something to do.
Ah, man! You haven't been hanging out with me lately!
That's not true! See you later.
I couldn't ask her for help.
I couldn't
ask her
for help.
I tried to escape from it so many times.
I tried to escape from it so many times...
I tried
to escape from it
so many times...
He was always here before I even noticed.
Megumi-chan...
Let's have "lunch" together again today.
Takuma-kun...
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Complete Control
Brainwashed and Subordinated - Raw Sex Life!
Part 02: Prescription for a cheeky little sister!
Megumi, your bentos...
...sure are tasty!
How is my "lunch"?
I'm rather proud of the smegma I've accumulated down there.
I can't take any more of this!
I'll give you my special "homemade sauce" today too.
It's starting to swell up.
Is he going to make me drink it again?
Here it comes!
You can't take your mouth off it!
You sure like my "sauce," don't you?
You took a lot from me again today.
Well then, maybe I'll have you suck it
with the semen still in your mouth.
I'm kidding. You can swallow it.
You're hopeless. I'll do the eating this time.
Don't... look.
Your asshole sure is nice and tight.
Maybe I'll have a taste of this today.
Don't lick me there!
I've gotta make sure to loosen it up!
What do you mean, loosen?! No! Stop!
It's twitching like it wants something in it.
Like hell it is! Please! Stop already!
You really want it up the ass, don't you? See?
Well, am I right?
No! Take it out!
Ah, I get it.
This is what you want up there, right?
No!
It hurts!
I'm going to void my bowels!
I'll make sure to make you feel good.
No way! It doesn't hurt!
It feels good, right?
That's... just...
My buttocks are going to get turned inside out!
You're feeling just as good as I am, right?
You're going to destroy my buttocks!
You really like it up the ass, don't you?
This... just can't be!
Don't!
Don't penetrate me so deeply!
Something hot is filling up my buttocks!
You're sucking me dry!
You sure are a glutton, Megumi-chan!
Where's my "thank you" at?
Mom said she's going to be a little late getting home.
What the fuck do you think you're looking at?!
You're so disgusting!
Huh?! I wasn't looking!
Who would want to?!
Ah, I think you might like this one, Shizuka.
It's just an anime song.
But it's really good. I think you'll like It, Shizuka.
Do you wanna listen to it?
See?
What... is this?
This isn't good at all.
Little sisters are supposed to be nicer
to their big brothers, you know!
Fuck off and die!
Why don't you have some fun with your big brother?
No! What are you trying to do?
Let's play doctor.
Cut it out, you fucking pervert!
Wow, you're poorly developed.
Shut up, you jerk!
I'll make them bigger for you!
Cut it out, you disgusting asshole!
Don't lie to me, your nipples are erect!
Asshole! Cut it out!
Stop it!
Let's exchange bodily fluids!
How cruel... That was my first kiss!
Oh? I smell pee.
Y-You fucking pervert!
Are you bathing properly? You've accumulated
some smegma down there.
Don't lick it!
Don't be shy! I'll clean it up for you!
Stop it! No! Not there!
I could drown in your pussy juices, Shizuka!
No, stop!
Are you a virgin, Shizuka?
Fuck you, you asshole!
Alrighty then! Let big brother help you graduate from that!
Fuck off! Stop it!
I'm going to tell Mom!
You sure are a bitch. I'll make you all lovey-dovey
for your big brother with this!
I want to become one with you even more, Onii-chan!
My beloved Onii-chan, your cock...
...is just so great!
Pay more attention to me!
Sorry, I'll make you cum!
Yeah! This is great!
It's hitting me all the way to the back!
You sure are spoiling me, Onii-chan.
This is great! I'm going to cum from
your full-on cock, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
I want more of your cock, Onii-chan!
Mom's gonna be home soon.
Alright, then let's pick it up where we left off in my room!
Onii-chan, hurry up and fuck me some more!
That a girl! Your big brother will do his best!
I love you, Onii-chan!
I love you so much it hurts, Onii-chan!
My pussy says it doesn't want to let go of your cock!
Fuck me harder! Kiss me, Onii-chan!
Your saliva is so delicious, Onii-chan!
I'm going to cum, Shizuka! Where do you want it?
Give it to me!
Give me your milk inside of me, Onii-chan!
It's okay! I love you, Onii-chan!
I'm cumming!
Lots and lots of hot jizz is filling up my pussy!
I see.
I'll be able to use an even more powerful hypnosis by updating.
Maybe next time I'll fuck the girls in my class all willy-nilly!
I'm your only girlfriend, Takuma-kun!
You can't cheat on me, Onii-san!
You two just think of me as a dark-natured otaku, don't you?
Not at all!
Not a bit!
I love you, Takuma-kun!
Me, too! I love love love you, Onii-san!
Hurry up and spoil us already!