Toyomoto-kun, time to get up!
Time to get up!
What are you doing here, Iizuka-senpai?
It's not time to go to school yet.
We're not even in the same school anymore.
That's why I'm here!
I wanted to show you my new blazer.
Toyomoto-kun.
– Good work out there.
– Iizuka-senpai was a year older than me and
the manager of the baseball team I was on.
– Here, drink this.
– Is that for me? Thank you so much.
– Drink it slowly, okay?
– Yeah, I will.
Because my house was on her way to school...
Time for morning practice!
– Hey, so isn't practice kinda hard?
– She came to wake me up.
– It really is.
Graduation Ceremony
I always wondered why I was the only one
she gave special treatment to. And then...
Graduation Certificate
I just couldn't take my eyes off
of you when you worked so hard
and before I knew it I...
I started getting interested in you.
I... I've always...
I've always liked you.
Huh?!
Graduation Certificate
So, uh, would you...
Would you be interested in going out with me?
Of course!
That's a relief!
I'm so happy!
You're aiming to attend the same high school as me, right?
We'll be able to go to school together again.
Yeah, but...
it's a pretty high ranking school,
so I'll have to make sure I study hard.
Oh, I see... Then...
Promise me that you'll let me be
your girlfriend after the exams, okay?
It's quite different from the sailor uniform isn't it?
More grown up?
Y-Yeah, that's it.
Oh, so you're finally a third year now, right?
It's not all fun and games.
I've had to drop everything to study.
That makes sense.
It makes me sad to think that I can't
watch you play baseball anymore.
But...
After you're done with exams, we can start dating at least, right?
Y-Yeah.
I've been hitting the books real hard during spring break.
You're really trying hard.
Anything you don't understand? I can help.
Senpai, uh, isn't your skirt a little too short?
Huh? You think so?
I think this is pretty normal though.
Isn't it?
I-It's cute, but I just don't want other guys ogling you.
I know this might sound kinda presumptuous
when I'm not even your boyfriend yet, but...
Thanks.
Holding hands is something a couple would do, right?
You think so? I think friends can hold hands too.
This is my first time holding a boy's hand though.
She smells... so good.
Your face is bright red.
Y-You're pretty red too.
Am I?
S-Senpai!
W-Wait, Toyomoto-kun?
I can't anymore! Senpai. I...
G-Geez,
I guess there's no choice if you're this hard.
You won't be able to go to school like this.
U-Uh, so can I undress you?
I wonder what he would do if I said no?
I guess I'd feel kind of bad if I did.
But we're not dating yet.
I can't really say yes to that.
You're right, but... But I can't wait any longer.
It's already gotten this far...
But...
He's getting all stressed out now. He's so cute.
If you're a little forceful, I might let you, Toyomoto-kun.
Senpai!
Calm down! You're going to rip off a button!
They're so soft!
That tickles!
The hook's on the back.
They're kind of wet.
That's because I sweat a little bit underneath the bra.
It feels so tingly!
Do you... really like nipples that much?
No, stop...
W-Wait!
I'm making weird sounds!
I don't like this.
Senpai, please show me down here too.
H-Hey!
We can't yet.
You can only see it after we start dating.
Okay?
What?! But we've already gone so far!
A-Aren't you being a little too mean, senpai?
But...
I'll let you touch it.
There's... a hole here.
Put your finger inside.
Gently, okay?
It's so warm!
And it's so tight.
Don't... Don't say that to me.
Y-Your finger feels so good!
It's making so much noise!
This is so embarrassing!
No!
No! I'm getting too wet!
What about you, Toyomoto-kun?
Your dick is pulsing.
Wai...
Does this feel good?
Your tip is really wet.
I can tell without looking.
If you touch it any more, I might cum!
Yeah, it'd be bad if it got on my uniform.
Hey...
What do you think about putting it inside me?
Inside... my pussy.
If I push it in, it might just go inside me.
It's touching it... It's touching senpai's...
Oh my god, it's filling it up.
Holy crap!
This feels amazing!
We're connected now... I can't stop moaning!
This really escalated quickly, huh?
I just lost my virginity.
Senpai, you're acting too sexy!
Yeah, I guess I am. I wonder why?
Maybe it's because after putting on this new uniform.
I felt a little more grown up
and wanted to give you my first time.
Senpai!
Not my boobs again!
This feels too good, I'm gonna...
Cum!
I love you.
Senpai! This is bad! I can't! I can't!
There's so much coming out.
My stomach is so full now.
Senpa...
When we're dating...
I'll show you everything, okay?
Alrighty.
Let's get going.
Yeah.
We really did something amazing today.
Yeah, we did.
Do you think you can hold off on doing anything
like we did this morning until your exams are over?
Good question.
We'll just have to see.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч