Director's Office
Sarina.
Why did you wet the floor?
Did you wet your pants?
Oh no! How embarassing!
What's this?
That's, well...
You didn't see a thing.
What's going on?
Why did she have this?
Medical Humiliation Vol. 2
Hey Sarina.
What happened to the vibrator
that was in your cunt?
l wet myself during work and dropped it somewhere.
You're a big girl and you wet yourself?
Who do you think is going to clean up this mess?
You don't get a reward if you can't follow the rules.
What?
Master...
l'll try to hold it in next time...
So please give me the reward...
Oh all right.
Thank you very much, Master.
Normally, l wouldn't let you do it with your mouth.
Be thankful and savor it.
Yes, Master.
lt was delicious master.
But now l want your cock inside me.
All right then, l'll treat you with plenty of affection.
Thank you very much, Master.
What is all this?
Why are they doing it?
l'm coming!
Mortuary
lt's not fair, it's not fair!
Why?
Why is that stupid Sarina so happy?
Plus that...
That's a position l like to be in...
Then you should've said so.
Rinka.
Right, Master?
No!
Now Rinka, shall we get started?
No! Let me go!
You know you want this.
You're so cute Rinka.
Don't make fun of me, Sarina!
You think you can get away with this?
l'll tell the other superiors about this!
Now calm yourself down by sucking on this.
Now Rinka, lick it.
Don't be so stuck up.
You can be happy, you know.
l'm going to climax soon.
No!
Well?
Master's juice tastes good right?
Let's get this started.
No, no, no!
Don't move too much!
This pain is going to kill me!
You say you're going to die?
l can't believe you're not enjoying this.
But this really hurts!
No!
Rinka, looks like you're starting to enjoy this.
What's wrong?
l want you to be quiet.
John Doe, John Doe...
What is it, Rinka?
l...l...
l think l'm going insane...
lt hurts, but it's also getting hot and feels weird...
You're starting to feel good.
Really?
lt's my first time and l'm feeling it.
John Doe, John Doe...
l want you to do me a favor...
l want you to be my master...
Please, l'm begging you...
l'll be your sex slave.
Don't worry, Rinka.
You're already my sex slave.
l'll give you lots of love.
Master...
l'm coming!
You weirdo.
Why are you looking at my ass?
l'm not.
Liar.
l'm not lying.
Really?
Then you'll have to prove it.
Can you come to the cabin after work?
l have something to tell you.
What kind of talk?
ls it something fun?
Yes, l'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Huh? That's strange.
No!
What is this? What's the meaning of this?
What are you doing John Doe?
You won't get away with this!
People will hear if you shout and
you'll just embarrass yourself, Head Nurse.
You have the boobs of a cow.
Hey, you're already wet.
You must be kidding.
Ouch! Stop it...
Please don't do this.
l never had such a thing stuck inside me.
Stop looking at me.
l don't enjoy this kind of thing.
What are you talking about?
You really enjoy this kind of thing.
You get excited when you're being
watched and fondled...
...you're really dirty.
Are you still going to deny it?
l know about you.
You think about your brother every night and...
...masturbate in the toilet but you're still holding back.
You like to pick on me because you're frustrated right?
That's not true!
You still won't admit it?
You're a very sad person.
So in order to make you forget about your brother...
...l'll have to take drastic measures against you.
Ouch!
Stop! lt hurts!
Come on. Admit it.
You like it, right?
You enjoy taking it up the ass, right?
You're taking my cock up
your ass, it feels great, right?
Yes, it feels good...
lt feels great in front and back...
Yes, yes...
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
So you admit it now?
Yes, Master.
Okay, then l'll give you some more.
You have the best ass!
lt won't let go of my cock.
Don't say that...
Please don't say that...
But it feels so good...
Yes!
Director's Office
Yes...
l'm coming!
l'm sorry Sarina.
lt's just that you were so cute.
lt's my first time doing this, so l was kind of surprised...
People will see us in here...
...so let's continue with this in the delivery room.
Sarina? Are you in here?
Hey, where are you?
Where are you?
Huh? What's going on?
Are you awake now, director?
l can't believe you fell for it.
Maybe you want to indulge in
sensual pleasures, Director.
What is the meaning of this?
You think you can get away with this?
Why are you doing this, Sarina?
What's going on?
We're in the final stage of the revenge tragedy.
Revenge?
l helped you by providing work and a place to stay.
What are you saying?
You're a rotten person.
Even if you lock me in here, the
other nurses are going to find me.
Unfortunately,
...those other nurses are already the
sex slaves of our master.
Didn't l tell you we're in the
final stage of the revenge tragedy?
All right then.
l'll keep violating you until you remember.
Take a look at my face.
You recognize my face, don't you?
Director?
But l thought the director died.
Then, how...
l didn't die!
The truth is you made him commit suicide!
You bitch!
And l'm his son.
lt took me a long time to get here.
l put a huge scar on my face and
pretended l lost my memory.
Now let me hear you confess...
...about everything you did up until now!
No!
No, no!
That incident...
l don't want to remember it...
Please, forgive me!
l see.
Then l'll release it inside!
No, please!
l'll get pregnant!
Don't be scared!
Now this is where l start asking questions.
Why did you kill my father and
make it look like a suicide?
l didn't do it!
Stop lying!
l checked everything.
You wanted to gain control of all the
money and power of this hospital...
...but my father was in your way.
So you used dirty tactics
to make him commit suicide.
Right?
Am l right?
You're wrong!
You need lots of money for medical treatment!
lt's true...
that your father and l didn't agree
on some management policies...
...but l had nothing to do with his death!
l may have drove him to suicide in the end...
...but l didn't do it on purpose!
Liar, liar, liar, liar!
No...
l'm sorry director.
lt's all my fault.
l pushed you to the limit, and now
l've pushed your son to the limit...
l did horrible things...
That's right.
You're responsible for everything!
Die and apologize to my father!
l'm coming...
l'm going to see the director!
l'm coming!
ln the end, our master gave up the
idea of killing director Himiko.
So she decided to create a better hospital with us...
...and started to work really
hard with our staff everyday.
Director's Office
Now pull your shirt up.
Looks like you're fine.
Yes.
And l became pregnant with the master's baby.
l became his wife and we all
run this hospital together now.