Examination Room
Beg.
Keep begging, Luna.
Now...
Come on Luna.
l want you to lick as much as you like.
Hurry...
Medical Humiliation Vol. 1
Tetsuya Adachi
My name is Sarina Nanase.
l'm a new nurse who started working
at this hospital 6 months ago.
There are many strict superiors...
...but l try to clean up the patient's waste as best l can.
l try to do my best everyday.
l'm coming!
Amnesia?
Stop lying!
What were you doing in front of the hospital?
Stop!
Try to cool yourself off in there.
Well?
You said l'm bad at intravenous
drips and it sounded like...
...l'm abusing my patients.
But l'm not so bad, right?
You're only good for cleaning
up the waste of patients.
l didn't mean it that way.
You put those in so many places...
Ouch, ouch!
Please stop!
Oh, l'm sorry.
l'm not good at setting up an
intravenous drip like you said...
...and l mistakenly stuck it in the wrong area.
l'm sorry.
l'll never say bad things about you ever again.
So please stop doing this. Please!
Huh?
You said that as if you really cared about me.
And now you're going to be
my experimental dummy, right?
Your clit is getting bigger.
No!
Mortuary
l wonder what kind of life you had.
Moments before your death...
...were you able to
understand who you really were?
l'm coming!
He'd rather be with Mako than me?
l took care of him ever since l can remember.
Well, mostly his private parts.
My clit got bigger...
l need something other than my fingers...
lf he was here, l wouldn't have
to put my fingers in and out...
l'll never forgive him.
Help me!
No!
Who is he?
He was wandering around inside the hospital.
He came into the bathroom all of a sudden.
Sarina, hurry up and clean him up.
Yes.
You shouldn't be embarrassed to wipe his cock.
l don't feel that way at all.
Let's just hand him over to the police.
l checked him out but he has no lD nor a name.
Maybe he's a sexual predator.
Let's kill him and sell his organs.
Yes, let's do that.
Hold on a minute!
Please, don't kill me.
l'm not a suspicious guy.
l just can't remember anything.
Don't hand me over to the police.
They couldn't tell who l was, so they
thought l was a suspicious guy...
l was caught by the police and they tortured me.
And l just escaped...
Then l got into this hospital.
So l'm begging you.
Please help me! l'll do anything!
Please let me stay here for a while!
Please!
Please let him stay here.
The janitor just quit last month.
Can't you use him as a new janitor?
All right.
l'll hire him as the new janitor.
Now get back to work, everyone.
Sarina, you take him over to the rooftop.
Yes, thank you very much director.
Thank you, Sarina.
No problem.
l know you helped me, but
l want you to do me a favor.
What is it?
What are you doing?
Please stop!
l'm coming!
Hey Sarina.
How are you feeling?
Master, your cock tastes so good.
Master, thank you very much.
But l want you to stick your cock inside me.
My body is feeling really hot and...
What should l do?
After watching them do
it, l want some action too.
Master, your cock feels so good.
With your cock inside me, l
can forget about everything.
ln the beginning, you tried to resist me.
That's because...
l didn't know how powerful your cock was.
John Doe...
l want you to do me, too.
Stick that cock inside me
and make me feel all gooey!
Master, l think l'm going to climax.
l see, then climax as much as you like!
l'm coming!
l climaxed too!
Are you okay, Nozomi?
You were passed out.
What were you doing outside?
Well l was...
You fainted after watching us have sex?
What are you doing?
John Doe, Sarina...
John Doe's cock feels good...
More, more...
Push it in deeper...
l'm coming!
Master, Nozomi seems to be getting
it on with Luna all the time.
So maybe you want to give it to her
doggy style next time.
l feel like a dog.
Grrr....
Yes.
Use your hips more...
Be like a wild beast...
John Doe's cock feels so good...
Now, l have to work real hard today.
lf you have something to say, then say it!
When l masturbate, l have to really hurt myself.
Sarina, can you tell me more?
l'll tell you the rest later. Come to the rooftop.
Bye.
Hey, this isn't a one-sided conversation!
Yes, Master...
Yes, harder...
Master...
lt hurts but it feels good...
lt hurts but it feels good!
Sarina, you're hungry for pleasure.
But...but...
lt hurts!
Master, it hurts!
You want me to stop?
l want you to hurt me more...
Please master...
lt hurts but it feels good!
Sarina?
What are you doing?
Can't you tell? Master was giving me pleasure.
l want to give you pleasure as well,
that's why l told you to come here.
What are you talking about?
No! Don't come near me!
Don't worry.
l won't do anything hardcore in the beginning.
Besides,
...you were looking at the master's
cock as if you wanted it, too.
Please, let me go.
Now let's begin.
Your nipples are getting so hard.
l have to punish you now.
Ouch!
lt hurts.
lt hurts, take them off.
Stop it.
Ouch!
Ouch, stop!
Please forgive me!
l'll do whatever you say!
No.
Master isn't completely satisfied.
What is this?
Now Rumi, l want you to satisfy the master.
Now hurry.
lf you don't do it, l'll smack you!
More...
Yes, use your tongue.
Don't cough it up, drink it all up.
You had your fun...
Please let me go...
l'm satisfied...
...but you want his cock inside now, don't you?
Yes...
More...
Do me harder...
My hips are moving...
They're moving on own...
Moving up and down your cock...
Climax...
l'm about to climax...
l'm about to climax with your cock inside...
Rumi, don't climax yet.
Rumi, can you lift your ass for a second?
No, not my butt!
This is what the master wants.
Yes...
That feels good Sarina...
Rumi, your ass is feeling good?
l'm coming!