Adolfo!
Adolfo.
That angel that you're
working on now is fantastic.
It is as if she's alive.
T-Thank you very much.
I heard the work is going smoothly.
Yes.
Soon this wonderful
painting will be complete.
Mr. Galliano...
What do you think of my painting?
Please, tell me truthfully.
Fernando!
You're so rude.
Pinneri, it's okay.
I like an outspoken young man.
Of course...
Let me see.
Fernando's painting is wonderful too...
...but regarding the angel...
...it seems that Adolfo's is better.
Is that so...
Mr. Galliano, you have
a good eye for paintings.
I know Fernando works hard, but
so far he hasn't reached Adolfo's level.
This painting of an
angel is really wonderful.
I don't think even I could
paint such a beautiful angel.
Adolfo.
I heard you want to
be a priest, is that true?
Yes, it is true.
Adolfo!
What are you saying?
Think about your position.
Although you are a talented painter,
you are willing to give up painting?
How can I compare painting with God?
I think devoting myself to
God is the only way for me to live.
Your idea is worthy of praise.
Let me think about it.
It all depends upon your effort.
Really?
Thank you so much.
Congratulations, Adolfo.
I hope you will more than live
up to Mr. Galliano's expectations.
Definitely.
Oh my God!
What was I thinking?
Dreaming such a dream must
mean that I have negligent in my efforts.
I should study harder and
become more like the great Mr. Galliano.
Mr. Galliano.
You have been my
mentor throughout my life.
I still have so far to go
before I can live up to his help.
You're late, Fernando...
He asked me to wait for him...
Stop it, please.
Stop it?
But you're dripping so much.
No.
You're so nasty.
Don't be shy.
This is the proof you love me.
Good, hurry...
Come inside me now.
Not yet.
But Adolfo is waiting for you...
Come on.
Who cares about that dick?
It's all right to make him wait a little.
Do you feel good?
It's so good...
You know what, Fernando?
Are you listening to me?
Yes, I am.
But why are you talking to me?
Dammit, Fernando.
Why did you bring her?
No, wait...
I have to stop thinking like that.
It is my mission as a friend
and a servant to help guide...
...somebody like him who
doesn't know that he is God's child.
Beautiful.
Your picture is so beautiful.
I like it very much.
T-Thank you.
She is so beautiful.
Do you live near here?
Yes, I live in the
village across the river.
How about you?
I live in Loa.
I'm envious of your
life in such a busy town.
I guess it's really full of energy!
No, not really.
Hey!
I'll see you again.
Bye, Mr. Adolfo.
Y-Yes.
Adolfo.
I've been talking to
you, what's going on?
Sorry, I was just
thinking about something.
About that girl?
Is her name Michaela?
She is so pretty.
I don't think about things like that.
Don't be shy.
Did you fall in love
with her at first sight?
What are you talking about?
I am a person who
devotes himself to God.
I don't have time
to think about women.
Anyway, you'd better forget about her.
That woman, Michaela,
has a steadfast fiance.
Really?
His name is Guiseppe,
a hunter who lives in her village.
They've known each
other since they were children.
It's okay.
You'll find a good girl someday.
Fernando, see you.
See you tomorrow.
Somebody's in here?
Michaela?
No.
Who are you?
Stop it!
That's indecent!
Don't be so full of hate.
Look at this.
You are so horny.
Stop.
Stop it.
Oh God, what have...
You came so soon.
Why do you have to seal your desire?
Shut up.
It is so I can serve God.
Do you think you can oppose
the laws of nature and life?
Absolutely not.
You're suppressing
the natural desires of life.
You have no right to
talk about God's laws.
Come on.
You want to lick it up, don't you?
This is how a real
living creature behaves.
Who was that, Ms. Crabelli?
Mr. Galliano...
You are really a sex animal.
Do you understand the
life of luxury you are leading?
Yes, I am very pleased to be
taken care of by Mr. Galliano.
Mr. Galliano is...
This must be a nightmare.
Adolfo...
So, you say you are willing
to work hard at the Church.
Thanks for the effort.
You are welcome.
By the way, is everything is going
all right with the work I left to you?
Y-Yes, it is going smoothly.
That's good.
Actually the other day
Marquis Rune came here...
...and praised you
for the angel you painted.
Did you see?
Well...
Are you sure you saw something?
Please forgive me.
Listen, Adolfo.
Don't tell anybody
what you saw last night.
No, I won't.
That was a secret ritual.
Although you may not understand...
...there are some secret activities
at higher levels of our teaching.
I understand.
Do you want to be a priest?
If so, keep what you saw
today a secret and work hard.
That is the fastest way
for you to get what you want.
I understand.
Stop it.
Take a look.
I am dripping so much.
Don't you think I'm a poor soul?
Ridiculous!
You want to feel good, don't you?
I know that you're
really thinking about that.
Leave!
You slut!
Disappear!
It's natural!
This is not just for excretion,
but for sticking into the female body.
It's also for rubbing up against
a woman's soft membrane.
You're so adorable.
Your face is so contorted.
Feel good inside of me?
So warm and soft!
Look, look at it!
It's overflowing from inside of me.
How long have you stored it up?
What's wrong?
l-I will fall into hell.
Don't worry.
Don't be afraid.
Coming up is the
same thing as going down.
Stroke yourself all you want.
...and spray everything inside of me.
Michae--
I'll forget about being a priest.
I am going to live a
normal life like Fernando.
I will live out my days
with a beautiful wife, Michaela...
...and pretty children, and make
a living as a painter at the Church.
I'll get married to Michaela,
and she and I will be happy.
I don't think there is
anything greater than that.
Hey.
Adolfo.
Hi, Mr. Adolfo.
Do you really love your fiance?
Pardon?
Your parents decided on your fiance
when you were a child, didn't they?
I don't think that's a true marriage.
Why are you telling me such a thing?
Because I love you.
Answer me!
Do you really want to marry him?
Will you really love him to death?
I can't say that, but
he is a good person.
I'm not worried
about being married to him.
That marriage is a lie.
I am the person who loves
you the most in the world.
Why don't you understand
how deeply I love you?
I'm sorry.
I'm glad to hear you like me,
but I'm going to marry him.
Please forget about me, and
be happy with somebody else.
All right?
Good-bye.
Wait!
No!
Oh, my God.
I never thought Adolfo was a
person capable of such an action.
But what shall I do?
He is just an apprentice painter, but...
...people think of him
as a member of our clergy.
If we punish him harshly,
we will hurt the Church's reputation.
It is okay if he is not guilty...
Is he not guilty?
What do you mean?
Michaela was responsible.
She made Adolfo go crazy.
Maybe she is a witch.
A witch...
Burn her!
Witch!
So good...
Adolfo, you are so good.
Light it!
Mr. Galliano, you have come
to share the secret with Adolfo...
The secret about me!
Luckily, I was able to avoid
hurting the Church's reputation.
It's all okay now.
Michaela, she must have been a witch...
Mr. Galliano declared it.
I'm not wrong.
I cannot be wrong...