Ikkyuu
Nyuukon
Special
Chapter
It's about time you stop feeling upset.
I'm not really upset or anything.
Well then, if that's so.
Gather around, everyone!
Our meeting is about to start.
Now then...
We fooled around yesterday,
so we'll have to work hard today.
Yeah!
I prepared a training camp menu for everyone!
Especially for you, Asakura! Yours is special!
Special?
A menu to overcome feelings of pressure!
That sounds like something awesome!
But it might be a little too tough for you...
Eh... What kind of—
Eh?
How about it? Will you put your
faith into me and do your best?
Ah, y-yes!
Good answer.
Personal Training Camp Menu
Satou
Receiving Practice
Asakura
Boob Massage♥
Ozawa
Muscle Training • Running
Boob massage!
Personal Training Camp Menu
Satou
Receiving Practice
Asakura
Boob Massage
Ozawa
Muscle Training
Running
Please stop fooling around!
How is that considered a training?
Huh? Is there something wrong about it?
It is the problem! That... boob... mass... thing!
You don't get anything about it, Asakura.
Succumbing in pressure is your weakness.
And this training will give you the guts you need!
If you do so, our team will become stronger!
That's ridiculous!
Doesn't everyone think it's absurd
as well? This is tyranny!
I-I don't really think so...
It's just the breasts, what can go wrong?
Nothing to lose there.
And with that being said,
shall we get you ready?
Eh?! Wait—
It's okay, should start
feeling good in no time.
I don't want to! I'm going home!
This is a trial you have to overcome
to become the next captain!
Menu
• mess her up
• tire her out
• make her mushy
• finish it!!
And so, you will be supervising
her special training for the whole day.
This is the training menu.
This really is strange when I think about it!
What does this even have to do with volleyball?
You shouldn't run away from this.
You have to pull the whole club up with you.
No way...
I'll leave the rest on you, then!
We're gonna start with our own training!
Wait, senpai!
Th-This feels awkward!
I already have the Club Prez's permission,
but I can't simply just go for it...
Massaging her breasts...
Those tits...
As much as I want!
Wh-What are you staring at?!
Ah... I'm sorry!
What the hell should I do?!
Alright!
We're already here, so let's
get this done and over with.
I'll let this happen just this one time.
For real?!
Then, I'm gonna touch them.
No...
I'll try not to make it hurt...
Okay.
They feel so heavy.
Hey... Can you do it more gently?
S-Sorry! I'll be more careful.
Are your nipples getting hard?
Don't ask me that!
Stop licking me!
Well then, let's start with the massage.
Huh? Your underwear...
It's been taken away.
Let's use some lotion as well then!
This feels gross!
Why do I even have to suffer this?
Let's take this off!
You can't!
I don't want this!
What's with this?
There's no way this is a special training!
They're so big and soft...
Your tits are the best, Asakura!
Sh—Shut up! Stop with all
those weird commentaries!
Uhh... Sorry.
No... Something's hitting my butt!
But, this feels like a dream for me!
No! I'm making weird moans!
Hey... Isn't it about time we stop?
I think this already is enough.
We've only just begun!
No! Not there!
I'm gonna do my best so that
I can be of good use for you.
My body's getting weird...
No more!
I can't take this anymore. My mind is spinning!
My nipples feel numb...
This concludes the massage...
Hey... next is... it's kid of hard to say this...
Huh?
You see...
Press your breasts around my thing...
Do you know what a titfuck is?
Huh?! What are you talking about? Are you crazy?
It'll be done in no time. Just bear with it a little.
No way! This can't be happening... No!
It's all buried in your breasts. This is the best!
No, that's gross!
Stop thrusting that thing!
I'll be done sooner if I do this!
It's the same scent as before.
No!
Stop already!
Just a little more, bear with me.
No!
Lick the tip, that will speed things up.
Like this?
What am I doing?
This is bad... I can't think straight anymore.
That's good! This feels amazing!
I'm gonna come already!
I'm gonna come!
No!
And we ended up doing titfucks five times.
We somehow cleared the menu.
Jeez, idiot!
Umm... I'm gonna rinse you, okay?
Ah.. Is it not too hot?
Yeah...
What am I even doing? After he did
all those horrible things on me...
Umm... I'm sorry about earlier.
It's too late to apologize now!
After doing all that on me...
Moreover, if you really were sorry...
Why is it getting hard again?
It's just... a physiological reaction...
I knew you weren't really sorry! Show it to me!
Now that I'm seeing it again,
it has an imposing presence!
This is my payback for earlier.
It won't be fair if only I gets
to be on the receiving end.
Nah... I'm rather happy with this...
It feels great when you lick it around the back.
Is that so?
It's kind of fun when it twitches.
That's incredible!
Wait, stop! Any more of this and I'll come!
Does it feel that good?
Yeah...
I'll be doing you here as well.
Stop!
Licking me down there...
I'll do my best to make you feel good...
I-It's not like I wanted you to do that for me...
I want you to feel more pleasure.
Stop...
I can't take it anymore!
No... You can't!
I-It went inside!
Having sex with you feels good, Asakura-san!
I'll stop if it hurts for you.
I see... I'm currently having sex.
No...
Something like this this... I'm...
I love you.
What are you thinking? Stop—
You really are the worst!
But I really do love you.
I hate someone like you!
You've done nothing but horrible things
...and roundabout moves like this!
Just get this over with already.
I feel nothing but disgust on this.
This isn't at least good!
It was supposed to be my first time but I was...
...forced against my will!
Oh no... My mind is going blank!
Are you alright?
I don't... think so...
Then, I'll do the moving.
Hey, don't just start—
I want to make you feel good a lot!
I don't need that!
I love you, Asakura-san!
No, I can't!
I'll do it a little rougher, okay?
R-Rougher?
Not so deep!
Bear with it a little.
I can't anymore!
I'm about to come!
You're squeezing me tight!
I feel like I'm melting down there!
Hurry up and end this already!
I'm already at my limit.
Ah... I'm coming!
Coming!
Coming! Something's coming!
I'm coming!
What am I even doing here...
Wow...
Okay, well do it in the tub next.
Huh?! You still want to go on?
Can't we?
Of course we can't!
Alright, for the last event of this training camp,
everyone gets to do it together!
What... Senpai, and everyone?!
Don't tell me you saw everything?!
Senpai!
Wait... So cramped!
Right...
The real fun is yet to come!
I'm gonna tease this a lot!
Start with me, senpai!
E-Even if you tell me that...
Cut it out already, everyone! This is ridiculous!
It's alright! We'll let you
join in so no don't worry!
Eh? That's not...
Nothing beats being proactive.
So, choose the one
who will go first.
So, please choose
the one to go first.
Eh...
Good evening!
Welcome.
Ah! Welcome, Hiro-nii!
Nana-chan! You're helping out
today as well? Good girl!
You really worked hard up to this late.
You're okay with a beer?
Just a glass then. I need to
be early tomorrow too.
Are the preps for the shopping
district event going smoothly?
Nah...
We're already short of
time and we're in trouble.
And about the event's host...
Maybe I can ask for Nana-chan to do it?
That's beyond my capabilities...
It's embarrassing for me
to talk in front of a crowd...
I'll be assisting you you as well,
so you don't have to worry!
But...
I'm begging you! I got nobody
else to ask for this but you!
E-Even if you say it like that...
Isn't it alright? Why not accept the job?
It looks interesting.
You too, mom!
Th-Then...
If you're willing to hear a request of mine...
Shopping District Cooperative
As I was saying...
She's Sakashita Nana-chan,
the one agreed to be the host.
N-Nice to meet you.
Oh, you really saved us by accepting the job!
Let's all make this event a great one!
Then, let's check if the size of the outfit is right...
You can use that room to change.
O-Okay.
She's a pretty girl! Good job on recruiting her!
We're going to get a nice footage.
Mr. President...
If I do my best on this, I can
have a date with Hiro-nii!
I changed into the outfit...
But this feels a little small...
It might slip off when I move.
Wait—!
Good!
What the hell are you thinking?!
It's for an all-ages event in the shopping district!
But it's cute!
Oh, the phone!
I'll leave the rest on you, then!
Wait, Mr. President!
Sorry, I didn't check the outfit beforehand...
I'll try to look for a new outfit.
Will we make it in time?
Well, you can just go casual
if we won't make it in time.
That's kind of a relief.
Then, this outfit is exclusively for Hiro-nii to see.
Hey...
Hey, am I cute in this? Does it suit me?
Eh? Ah... You're cute! Very cute!
But it's also distracting, or how should I say it...
I mean, even now they look
like they're gonna spill out...
And it gives me the chills...
A-Are my breasts weird?
Th-They're big so I thought
that you might hate them...
No way!
M-My breasts are not weird?
I like them! Or rather, I love them!
Really? You really like them?
Y-Yeah.
This is bad! She's sticking to me like
a glue that my nether region is reacting!
Listen, I've always been...
I've always liked you, Hiro-nii...
I love you too!
I always pretended not to but I've
always been thinking about them!
N-Not that...
I mean... Shouldn't we start
with something like a kiss...
Do you like to get licked on?
Then, I'm gonna give you
a lot of good lapping!
No, you can't!
No... K-Kiss...
I want to kiss!
Oh, I see. You should have said it earlier.
Don't rub them!
You're so mean!
I'm sorry. Want to kiss?
Yeah... I want to.
More... More!
Hiro-nii... I like you. I love you!
Me too...
Can you help me make it feel better?
Okay, just tell me anything you want!
Okay then, hold them
between your breasts first.
Like this?
That's right.
Lubricate them enough,
then move them up and down.
Something like this?
Yeah, you're doing great.
I'm glad!
They really are the best!
They're so soft and my thing sinks into them...
These onahole tits!
Don't do that! You're rubbing them with your dick!
You like getting your nipples teased, don't you?
This is bad!
I'm coming!
Sorry... It felt so good that
I just sprayed them like that.
Umm... That's fine.
I'm glad that you enjoyed it.
Then, I'll be doing you next as well.
No! Stop!
Huh? Are you feeling it?
That's...
It's okay, Just let yourself feel even better!
No! If you do it that much...
I'm gonna go crazy!
Hey, should we just go all the way?
Do it...
I want you to put it inside of me...
Alright then, just relax... I'm putting it in.
Are you alright? Should we stop?
I'm alright, put it all the way inside!
You're squeezing me tight!
You're deep inside me!
We can stop this if it hurts.
It's alright... I'm happy!
To become one with Hiro-nii, just like this...
So I want you...
...to mess me up even more!
Okay... As you wish!
How is it? Are you feeling good too, Hiro-nii?
Ah... That's good... You're so hot
that I feel like I'm gonna melt!
My body is trembling. I can't move!
I'll help you, then.
You're reaching so deep inside me like this!
No! I'm gonna lose my mind with this!
It feels too much that
my head going to white out!
You're making some incredible
sounds down here, Nana-chan!
No! Don't say that!
It feels so good!
So intense!
Oh... I'm about to come!
I'm coming!
You've properly prepared an outfit for today, right?
Yeah, it's all perfect!
Umm... Hiro-nii...
Oh? How's the size—
This one is more revealing that before though...
Will you cut it out already?!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization