Ikkyuu
Nyuukon
First
Chapter
Isn't that...
Asakura-san of Class 2.
She looks good in her jersey.
She also has huge breasts.
Hmm... It's Kaori.
Satou... do you know her?
We're on the same club.
Want me to introduce you?
Really?!
Then, how about you buy me three desserts?
Damn, you know I can't refuse that offer!
[Girl's Locker Room]
So, what I'm saying is...
Can you meet with him for a little while?
No way!
This is how he looks like. Not your type?
I already said I can't.
Ehh... He looks like an interesting guy.
Geh... Club Prez...
I'm borrowing this for a bit.
Ehh.... wait—
I'll be on my way.
What?!
"I showed your pic to Kaori and she wants to meet you."
"Hurry up and come to the club room ❤."
Seriously?!
[Women's Volleyball Club]
Pardon my intrusion...
There's no one here.
Is this... a bra? It's huge!
I caught an underwear thief in the act.
And I got this photo as a proof.
No, I was just...
Ehh... You're still try to make excuses out of this.
Mr. Underwear Thief.
Oh my, isn't that my bra?
You'd get in trouble if a teacher sees this picture, right?
He might get suspended.
That's absurd!
Well, we ain't that harsh.
We're gonna let you off if you're
willing to do what we tell you.
You're our team's manager starting today.
You'll have to obey all my orders.
Okay?
Or else, I'll tell the teach—
U-Understood.
I'll do as you say...
Now we're talking!
W-What are you doing all of a sudden!
That reaction... you're a virgin, aren't you?
I knew it!
Wait—
Megumi, hold him down!
Okay!
What are you...
Ehh... this is something.
Looks like we'll enjoy with this.
How cute!
Stop...
Hey, Satou! Why did it end up like this?!
Sorry, I can't oppose senpai.
It's alright, we'll make you feel good.
Here! Just stay still, okay?
It's hot in my mouth—
How is it?
Does my mouth feel good?
It's twitching.
Oh no...
Your moaning with a pathetic voice.
Does it feel good around here.
Are you coming already?
Alright, come. Shoot it out.
I'm coming! Here it goes!
You came so much.
That's sooner than I expected.
Try to endure it more.
Saki's getting all the fun. That's unfair!
Should I join in with you?
Here, touch them.
I'm not wearing a bra!
You can do as you please with them.
Wow, my hands are sinking into them.
Knead them rough and good!
Amazing...
Oh, you won't satisfy me with just like that!
O-Okay!
That's good!
You're hard again.
S-Senpai!
That's good. Do it harder!
Whoa... hoh!
You see, my nipples are inverted.
It's a little embarrassing but...
Would you suck them out for me?
O-Okay!
Just like that. Feels good!
Then, I'll be taking care of yours as well!
Your dick got so hard.
Do you like big boobs?
Yes...
Hmm... I see. You love big boobs.
Here... How do they feel?
There, there! Feels good?
Delicious!
This is awesome!
You're squeezing me too much!
You can't come yet!
Let us enjoy this first!
You can shoot it on my boobs, okay?
Hey, open your mouth!
You're twitching. Are you coming soon?
Y-Yes! I'm... coming!
Ahah! My boobs are slimy!
You can still go on, right?
Wait, Stop! Senpai!
This is bad. What a strong smell.
It makes me feel light-headed.
They're both going on it...
Satou-san, would you do me a favor?
Whoa! Yes, what would it be?
How's it, is it recording?
Y-Yes! I think it's working.
Then, we're gonna make him graduate from virginity!
He already had the mouth and breasts!
Look here, isn't it your first time seeing one?
This is where you put it in.
But doing this in school isn't good.
Just do it already.
Senpai!
That's too sudden, idiot!
Wow, this is what a girl's pussy is like.
It's so slippery, it's captivating!
Stop describing every detail! Slow down a bit!
That feels good!
Go on, fuck me deeper!
Okay!
Now, it's my turn to move.
How's it? Feels good?
Doesn't it feels different than
when you're the one moving?
Yeah...
From now on, I'll teach you more stuff,
until your head is filled of nothing but sex.
Okay, we'll let him do his first creampie like this!
Don't you want it, coming inside my pussy?
It'll feel very good for sure!
I-I want to do it...
Good, you're being honest!
Make sure to record this moment.
Senpai, I'm already...
Alright, just come like that!
Wow, I'm overflowing.
You're better than I expected.
Okay, how about we do it next?
Here, put it in already!
You're so huge!
I want it rougher!
I love it on my nipples!
Hey, does it feel good inside me?
Y-Yes! It feels very soft.
I'm glad.
It's going deep inside!
I love it! Your dick is the best.
I won't be able to stop myself with this.
Hey, are you gonna fill me up inside too?
Is is okay?
Yes, it's okay.
So keep going 'til the end, okay?
Okay...
Ah! I'm coming!
Let's do it together! Come with me!
Coming!
I'm coming!
Gather around, volleyball club!
I'm introducing him to everyone.
He's our new manager.
Ah, nice to meet you all.
He's Takahashi-kun, a classmate of Satou.
Ehh... Interesting.
Ah! The guy yesterday...
What's going on here?
Well, one thing led to another...
What's all this about?
Doesn't it seem fun?
It's a good change of pace for everyone as well.
Jeez...
Where's the fun in that?
I wonder what will happen from now on...
Ah, Kouhai-kun!
Ah, wait... senpai?
Do your best for today as well.
Club Room Cleaning
Let's make it neat!
Segregate the trash!
Umm... Asakura-senpai!
Yes?
Isn't this area clean enough already?
And even if we clean around weekly,
the prez gets it all messy in no time.
You shouldn't give up, Misa-chan!
We're protecting the club room this way!
Well then, help me move this one.
'kay!
Isn't that Satou-senpai's?
Something smells fishy!
Excuse me, senpai!
Eh? Wai—
Wait!
I can't carry all these myself!
Jeez!
Ah! Just in time. Give me a hand—
Ack! You're that stakler!
Who's the stalker?!
Suddenly joining in a club is suspicious!
Joining as manager of the girl's volleyball club...
Well, the prez forced me to join...
Hmmp! I wonder...
If you really don't want it,
you should've just declined.
Well that's... because some stuff happened...
I bet you joined having some dubious motive!
T-Taking that aside, shouldn't
we get this cleaning done?
I don't trust you even a little.
Try something weird and I'm
reporting you to the teacher!
Ah... Okay.
Then, get started by throwing these out.
All of these?
I think that's all of it.
I've been wanting to organize stuff around here!
Eh, it's already this late? I have
an appointment with the teacher.
Err... Thank you for helping me clean around.
Ah... Okay...
Well then, can you please lock the room.
Got it, I'll lock it up.
Aren't you getting along earlier, senpai.
How long have you?! Uhm...
I'm Ozawa Misa, a first year.
I found something intriguing.
Is this camera familiar to you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Feigning innocence is futile.
Satou-senpai already spilled the beans.
Sorry.
Hey! You should've at least tried to cover it up!
And so, this cute junior of yours have a request.
What?
The truth is, I also am interested in such things.
If it's alright with you, can we do it too?
Am I not up to your taste?
That's not... But doing this suddenly...
It's alright!
We just can think of it as playing around.
But why with me?
Well, that's because of...
That thing they call love at first sight.
That doesn't sound convincing.
And, you already got big.
I'm glad!
Se-n-pa-i!
Abstinence is bad for your health.
Hey!
There!
How are by boobs?
Though it's nothing compared to my seniors.
Damn! I won't be able to hold myself back.
Are you finally getting in the mood?
Are you really okay with this?
Senpai, stop.
No kissing, please?
Ah, alright.
Why is sex okay but kissing isn't?
Uhm... Please be gentle on me.
If it's like that, I'll absolutely make her come.
No!
Don't suck them!
Uhm... You're only doing it on my breasts.
You hate it?
I don't hate it, but...
You're so drenched down there.
That is...
'Coz I'm kind of easy to get aroused.
And after seeing that video, I've been...
Ah, I get it.
You already got this big.
Is it because of my boobs?
If that's so, I'm happy!
I want you to feel good as much as possible.
Your thing is so hot and twitching so much.
How does this feel?
Good! They're so squishy!
I think I'm coming soon.
Go ahead. Come like this.
Amazing!
Wow, so this is what they call semen.
It's kind of awesome.
Now, here!
You shot it on me, so you should clean me up.
Eh.. yeah...
Just like that. Please wipe everything up.
Okay...
The way your hands touch me is lewd.
What are you saying?
Finish up by licking me clean.
Eh... Seriously?
Damn it...
Just like that.
You look like a baby. That tickles!
Wait, you're sucking me so hard, senpai!
Then, how about I touch you here?
Eh? That's...
Don't! Not so rough!
Stop! This feels too much!
Let me rest a bit.
No, you can't!
Please...
Here, raise your legs up.
Eh? Wai—
Don't lick me there!
I'm coming!
You're teasing me so much...
Uhm, senpai. I can't wait any longer.
Please, put your dick inside here.
You don't have to say it.
You're so tight! This feels far from my last time!
You're poking deep inside me, amazing!
Are you alright? I'm gonna start moving.
Yes... I'm alright.
I'll do it slowly.
So tight! I think I'm coming again soon!
Don't come yet. Try to endure it more.
You're so deep!
You're a pervert, senpai! Doing it right at the window.
We'll be caught! My breast will be seen by someone...
It makes me feel so excited!
I love this! Do me rougher!
Sorry... You're so cute, I can't help it.
No way! I won't forgive you!
Please take responsibility.
Just kidding!
Misa-chan!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
Okay...
Make feel good a lot! I love your dick!
Does it feel good when I rub
around this part inside you?
That feels good!
I won't let you off yet.
I can't... anymore!
I've been coming non-stop!
Your orgasm face is cute!
Idiot—
How many times did you come?
Maybe around five...
Then, we should come together next.
Senpai, not my ears!
Can I come inside?
Okay, come inside me!
Please fill me up!
It's coming out!
Coming!
Wow, there's so much hot stuff inside.
Satou-senpai, did you film everything?
I think everything went well.
You're still here?! And don't film us!
Nice job. Can I also have a copy later?
Hey!
Well then, senpai! I'll leave the cleaning to you.
Asakura-senpai will get mad
if she sees the room dirty.
Hey, wait! Delete that video!
No way!
She's a devil!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project