Only my oppai soul
Special Arc
Stop being mad already.
I'm not mad.
Well, if you say so.
Everyone, gather up!
We're starting our meeting!
Now then...
We played hard yesterday, now it's time to work hard.
– Okay!
I've already developed a training regimen for each of you.
And yours is extra special, Asakura!
Special?
It's a regimen dedicated to help
you function under pressure.
I-It sounds really incredible.
It actually might be too tough for you.
Huh? What kind of training...
Are you going to be able to trust
me and keep going no matter what?
Y-Yes!
Good answer.
Training regimen for the camp
Sato (receiving drills)
Asakura (boob massage ♥)
Ozawa (strength training/running)
Boob massage!
P-Please be serious!
How is that practice?!
Huh? Something wrong with it?
Everything's wrong with it!
Especially the boob massage...
You don't get it, Asakura.
Your weakness is your inability to tolerate stress.
That's why I came up with this regimen.
It's to help you with your nerves!
We'll be a lot stronger this way.
But this is just insane!
Don't you all think so too?
This is just messed up!
I think it's fine...
What's the harm? It's not too much to ask.
It's not gonna hurt you.
Well now that we've gotten that out
of the way, how about we get ready?
Huh?! Wai...
Don't worry. I'm sure it'll feel good real fast.
No! I don't want to! I'm going home!
This is a trial you must go through
if you want to be the next captain.
Regiment
- Mess her up
- Tire her out
- Get her wet
- Finish!!
So with that being said, you'll be helping
her out with her training for the entire day.
It's all a part of her training.
I still can't accept this!
What does this have to do with volleyball at all?!
Don't run away.
This is something that you have to get over.
But...
Okay, I'll leave you to it!
We have our own training to do.
– Okay, let's go!
– Wait, senpai!
This... is so awkward.
This might be the captain's orders,
but I don't think it's a good idea...
Massaging her boobs won't...
Those boobs?
Rub them all I want?!
What are you staring at?!
Ah... Sorry!
What the heck am I supposed to do?!
Okay!
Let's just get it over with.
I'll give you special permission just this once.
For real?!
Okay then, here I go!
I'll do it gently.
Okay.
Wow, they're so heavy!
Um, could you be a little more gentle?
S-Sorry.
I'll be more careful.
Huh? Your nipples are hard.
Don't ask me why.
Don't lick me...
Let's start with the massage.
Huh? Where's your bra?
They took it away from me.
Then let me use this lotion.
It feels gross!
Why do I have to go through this?!
I'm gonna take off your shirt!
Don't!
No, this is...
What's going on?
This isn't training at all.
They're so big and soft!
Your boobs are amazing, Asakura-san!
Shut up! Keep your thoughts to yourself!
Ah... Sorry.
What? Something's touching my butt.
This is... seriously like a dream come true!
No... Why am I making these sounds?
Hey, don't you think this is enough?
I think we've done this long enough.
We're only just getting started!
No... That's...
I'm gonna do my best!
I'm going to make myself useful!
My body feels weird!
No, I...
My head's in the clouds!
I can't even feel my nipples anymore.
Was that the end of the massage?
Um, what I want to do next is a little hard to say...
Um, could you sandwich my thing in between your boobs?
Do you know what a boob job is?
Huh?!
Do you hear yourself?! Are you crazy or something?!
It'll be over in a flash!
Just bear with it for a little!
No! Stop!
It's so tight!
This is so good!
Stop! It feels gross!
Stop pushing it against me!
This'll be over real fast!
This is the same smell as back then.
No!
Stop this already!
Just a little more! Hang in there!
No!
If you lick the tip, it'll end even faster.
L-Like this?
What am I...
This is bad. My head's going blank.
It's so good... This is so amazing!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
No!
After that, he went about five more times with
my boobs and we somehow finished the training.
You... idiot...
Okay, I'm going to rinse you off now.
It's not too hot, is it?
No...
What am I doing?
He did all those mean things to me, but I...
Um, sorry about earlier.
You're apologizing way too late.
You just kept going without stopping.
Do you really feel bad for what you di...
Why are you hard again?!
This is just a natural reaction...
You don't feel bad at all, do you?!
Show me it!
Seeing it again really makes me realize how impressive it is.
This is payback for before.
It's not fair if you get to have your way
with me and I don't get my turn with you.
Well, this actually kinda makes me happy...
It feels good when you suck me there!
It does?
It's kind of funny how it's twitching.
That feels... so good!
Wait, stop! If you keep going, I'm gonna cum!
It really feels that good?
Yeah.
Let me do you too, Asakura-san...
No!
Don't lick me there!
I'll do my best to make it feel good!
That's not what I'm trying to say!
I want you to feel good!
Stop...
I can't wait any longer!
No, don't!
So tight!
It's inside...
Having sex with you feels so good, Asakura-san!
Tell me if it hurts. I'll stop.
Oh... I'm having sex.
This is...
I like you.
What are you thinking? Stop...
You really are the worst.
But I really do like you.
Yeah, but I hate you.
You're only ever doing these mean things.
This isn't normal.
Just hurry and end this already.
It feels really gross.
It doesn't feel good at all.
This was my first time, but...
You took it so forcefully.
No... I can't focus!
Are you alright?
I'm not so sure...
Okay, let me move then!
Hey, don't...
I want to make you feel really good!
I don't need to.
I like you, Asakura-san!
No, stop!
I'm going to be a little rougher.
Okay...
Stop! It's too deep!
Just bear with it!
I can't!
I'm gonna cum!
You're so tight!
I feel like my pussy's gonna melt!
Hurry up and finish.
I'm at my limit too.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Something... Something's coming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
What am I doing?
Then how about we do it in the bath now?
Huh?! You wanna keep going?!
Is that a no?
Of course it is...
Okay, let's put a cap on this trip with an orgy!
Senpai?!
And the rest of you too?!
Wait, were you watch...
Senpai!
I can't breathe!
The fun's only beginning.
We'll play a lot with you.
Please let me go first, senpai!
Yeah, but...
Knock it off, everyone!
There's something wrong with all of you!
Don't worry, we'll make sure you get a turn.
Huh? That's not what I...
I like your spirit.
– Okay, pkease choose who's first.
– Okay, choose who gets first.
– Okay, choose who's first.
– Okay, choose who goes first.
Small Restaurant
Seasonal Disbes
Good evening.
Welcome.
Oh, Hiro-nii, welcome!
Nana-chan, helping out again today?
You're such a good girl.
You're sure working late tonight.
Beer good?
I guess a glass wouldn't hurt.
I've got an early start tomorrow.
How's the shopping district's event coming along? Good?
Nope.
There's not nearly enough time. It's really rough.
So remember that thing during the event?
Do you think you could do it, Nana-chan?
Huh?!
No way!
I'm really bad at talking to people!
I'll be there to back you up. There's nothing to worry about!
But...
Please! You're the only one I can ask!
Maybe, but I...
Why don't you just try it out?
Sounds fun.
Not you too, Mom!
O-Okay, if you do me a favor, Hiro-nii, then...
Shopping District's Association
So now, I'd like to introduce you to Nana-chan
who has graciously accepted to participate.
Th-Thanks for having me.
You're a real life saver! Thanks for accepting!
Let's make this event great!
So if you could check to make sure the
outfit fits you in that room over there...
O-Okay.
She's perfect!
Good job finding her!
We're gonna get some good footage!
Come on, sir...
If I do this well, I'll get to go on a date with Hiro-nil!
I tried it on, but...
I think it's a little too small...
It might come off if I move too much.
Good!
What the hell's wrong with you?!
This is an all ages event for the shopping district!
B-But isn't it cute?
Oh, my phone.
Take care of things for me, okay?
Hey, wait!
Sorry, I should've checked.
I'll look for a new outfit for you.
Do you have enough time?
Well, worst case scenario, you
can just wear your street clothes.
I feel relieved.
I guess this outfit's for your eyes only, Hiro-nii.
H-Hey!
Do I look cute?
Does it look good on me?
Huh? Yeah, you look cute.
Really cute!
It's kind of hard on the eyes or...
what's a better way to put this...
I'm worried that something's about to burst out.
A-Are my boobs weird?
D-Do you not like them because they're big?
N-No, I do!
They're okay?
My boobs are normal?
I like them!
No, I love them!
Really?!
You really like them??
Y-Yeah!
Shit, they're wrapping around
me and my lower half is reacting.
Um, listen, I've always...
I've always liked you, Hiro-nii!
I like you too!!
I tried to put you out of my mind, but I couldn't.
W-Wait, I'm not...
I wanted to start with a kiss or something!
Do you like being licked?
Then I'll lick you all over.
No, don't!
I... I want to kiss!
What? You could've said that sooner.
Don't rub them!
You're such a meanie.
Sorry. You want to kiss?
I do.
More... More!
Hiro-nii, I like you!
I like you so much!
Me too!
Could you help me out a little?
Just tell me what to do.
Okay, sandwich it between your boobs first.
L-Like this?
Yeah, good. Make it really wet
and then move it up and down.
So like this?
Yeah, that's good!
That's good.
This feels really good!
These onahole tits are so soft and sticky.
Don't do that!
Your dick's touching my...
You like your nipples being played with, huh?
Crap...
I'm gonna cum!
Sorry, it felt so good. I couldn't stop myself.
It's okay.
I'm just happy it felt good for you.
Now it's my turn to make you feel good, Nana-chan.
No, stop!
Huh? Did that feel good?
Th-That's...
It's fine. Let yourself feel good.
No! You're being too...
I'm going to lose it!
Hey, how about we go all the way.
Do it...
I want you inside me!
Okay, then loosen up.
Here I go!
You okay?
Should I stop?
It's okay, put it in me deep!
So tight!
It's so deep inside me!
Tell me if it hurts. I'll stop.
I'm fine.
I'm so happy!
I'm connected with you, Hiro-nii!
So... mess me up even more!
Sure. Just as you want.
Does it feel good for you too, Hiro-nii?
Yeah, it does!
It's so hot, I feel like I'm gonna melt!
My body feels like electricity's
running through it! I can't move!
Then let me help out.
It's coming in so deep!
No!
This is gonna make me go crazy!
It feels too good... My mind's going blank!
Nana-chan, your pussy's making some interesting noises!
No, don't say that!
It feels too good!
So rough!
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!
It's a normal outfit this time right?
Yeah, of course it is.
Um, Hiro-nii?
Yeah? How's the size...
I think this, is even more revealing than the last one...
Cut this shit out!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control:
softsub: торрент иваниваныч