Ikkyuu
Nyuukon
Extra
Chapter
Final Match of the District Tournament...
The opposing team is our district's
regular representative!
We have to win and go to nationals whatever it takes
for the sake of our manager, Shinozuka-senpai!
Go, Shunya-kun!
However...
The obstacle was far too high for us.
Regular teams in the nationals surely are strong!
Shut up!
We definitely won't lose next year! Damn it!
I never thought we'd lose without scoring a point.
And I was planning to show off to senpai...
Shunya-kun!
You did great at the match. We almost had it!
I'm sorry, I couldn't keep my promise.
Well then, I'll be on my way first.
Let Shinozuka-senpai console you!
Shut up, just go home already!
See you next time!
I'll make sure that we'll get to the nationals!
Thanks for today!
I'll be on my way then.
You see...
No one's home today, so...
If it's fine with you, how about coming over inside?
Is it okay? Then please!
Yeah! Come in!
P-Pardon the intrusion...
I need to brace myself!
As long as I do just as that book says,
he should be pleased!
Alright!
Umm... Senpai...
Hey, don't move!
Wh-Why are you suddenly...
You see, I wanted to cheer you up
as a reward for working hard in the match!
Just wait a little, okay?
Wait... Senpai!
Come one, lie down!
Huh?!
Hey...
You can do anything you want on my tits.
Huh?!
Umm...
Eh? Why?
Here, don't hold back.
That book says that I should do it like this.
I wonder if I can make him happy with this?
How is it, am I cheering you up?
Yeah, this is the best...
Really? I'm glad!
You can do it as much as you want.
If you keep licking them like that, they'll get soggy!
I can feel that he got big already through his pants!
Senpai!
Alright then... I'll be the one
licking you this time, okay?
Wow, it got hard!
Umm...
From what I recall, I should be gentle
and avoid hitting it with my teeth...
How is it? Feels good?
Yes... It feels good!
Senpai, your mouth is so warm!
This is bad, I'm gonna come already!
This is what they call semen...
It's viscous and sticky...
It tastes weird.
Senpai...
How was it?
Did it feel good?
Y-Yes!
I'll clean it up then, okay?
If you do that much, I'm going to... again...
This is...
What's this?
You can't look at it!
I forgot about the lewd book that I borrowed!
This is from my friend in the cheering club.
She let me borrow it since I wanted
to cheer someone up. It's not mine at all!
Since you already have this here, try wearing it!
No way, it's embarrassing!
Please do it, I'm sure you'll look good in these!
Umm, this is much smaller that I thought!
I guess it can't be helped...
You look amazing, it's sexy!
Hey, that doesn't sound like you're praising me!
Thanks to you, I got like this...
Jeez, this is a one-time thing for today!
Wearing this is embarrassing!
This is senpai's...
Hey there, I'm the one that should do the work today!
If you keep doing it that much...
Senpai, I want to make you feel good as well.
Hey... Can I put it inside?
Huh? Wait!
My heart isn't ready yet—!
Your insides are coiling around me!
So intense!
Please, slow down!
It's reaching deep inside me!
A-Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm fine...
I was just a little surprised...
Then, I'll do the moving!
How is it? Feels good?
I feel like I'm gonna melt!
Hey, you're moving on your own again!
There's no way I can hold back from this!
Hey, I'm gonna come already, senpai!
You can't! Do it outside!
You came a lot...
I'm sorry, I couldn't help myself...
Jeez...
Umm, can we go for another round now?
I haven't had enough yet!
Wait—!
I'm begging you, let me rest a little!
I'll go crazy from this!
Please feel even better!
No way!
I love you, Eri-san!
No!
If you say something like that,
I'll feel so good that it'll drive me crazy!
I love you, I cherish you! Eri-san!
Jeez, you're being too pushy!
I'm gonna come again!
It's alright!
Go ahead and come inside just like this!
Eri-san, I'm...
Jeez... To call me by my name
at that moment, you're so unfair!
I-I'm sorry...
You don't have to apologize. It made me happy.
Umm... We'll win next year for sure,
so please continue cheering—
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it!
I-I'll be on my way!
See you again!
I'm glad that my feelings reached him!
All thanks to this being lent to me.
I need to wash and return the clothes too.
Huh, it got so stretched out!
This is bad! She'll definitely get angry at me!
This one's cute too,
but this one has a cute ribbon...
Senpai took the trouble of inviting me to the beach,
so I have to put an effort on picking one!
Is there something you're looking for?
Umm, do you have this in other colors?
I'll check about it immediately.
Hey, Nozomi!
Senpai, have you found something cute?
Yeah, it's perfect for you!
Look, isn't it so cute?
Huh?!
No way I'm wearing something
embarrassing! What are you thinking?
You don't have to worry, this will be my present for you!
Thank you for your patronage!
I'm looking forward to the beach tomorrow!
There's no way I'm wearing that!
Then how about wearing it now and showing me?
I don't want to! There's no way I'm wearing that—
There's a karaoke over there!
Just right when I feel like singing! Come on, hurry up!
Will that be all for your order?
Yes.
Well then, please take your time.
It's so hot that I'm dripping with sweat.
What are you going to sing, senpai?
Who cares about singing.
This isn't what you said earlier!
Wait... Please stop, or I'll get angry!
Your angry face is cute too!
You always talk that way,
but what are we going to do
if the employee comes back?
Well, we should be fine until the time's up.
We really shouldn't be doing this here!
Jeez, you're such a worrywart.
You're just a worrisome one!
No!
Then, I'll stop this if you wear the swimsuit.
That's...
If you don't, maybe I should do
something way more embarrassing.
I get it already!
I just have to wear it, right?
Your submissive side is cute too.
W-Will this do?
You look way better in it than I imagined!
It feels like it's digging in a lot though...
That's what makes you look great!
Thanks to you, I'm already like this.
Y-You don't have to show it to me!
Jeez! Senpai, you're actually an idiot!
Hey, hey!
It can't be helped so I'll give you a little service.
You're doing good! Just keep
that up and put it in deeper!
S-Senpai, you're too big!
You're the one to talk...
but you're about the same with your tits, Nozomi!
Wait... Senpai, stop!
Don't do that!
S-Stop playing with my breasts!
Jeez! You're so mean!
I've been conscious about them myself, you know!
Is that so?
You should be more confident about your breasts.
On top of being huge, they're also sensitive!
I won't get tired from always rubbing them, really.
Not my nipples! They're sensitive!
You know, saying those things is so way off!
Oh, you think so?
But...
It kind of makes me happy if you like them.
That's why I'll make you feel
good a lot using my tits!
Those are such incredible words you said, huh?
Enough already! Please just stay still, senpai!
I'm gonna give you a lot of service.
That's amazing!
This is bad, I'm already—!
It's alright, come on my breasts just like this!
There's so much...
Did it feel good?
Yeah... It felt so good!
I'm gonna squeeze out all
that's remaining inside, okay?
Wait! Not now!
Oh, you got lively again down here!
You did it in purpose...
What should we do? The employee
might come in any moment.
Aren't we still fine until the time's up?
That's it!
I'm putting it in.
Okay!
Senpai, you're being too rough!
Slow down a little!
Not so deep, I'm sensitive there!
You want it deep?
It's okay for you to come a lot!
No, I'm gonna come already!
My shameful voice will come out!
It's okay! You can moan a lot more!
Please stop hitting me—!
Don't! My head is going blank!
I'm about to come too!
Yikes!
Yes?
You only have 10 minutes left.
Would you like to request for an extension?
Hmm... Then, I'd request for 30 more minutes.
Yes, understood.
Would you like to order some drinks?
That won't be necessary. Well then.
You're so mean! You did that
earlier on purpose, right?
Since we're already on it, I thought that
I'd have you make some cute moans.
This is my payback on you!
I might have found your
unexpected weakness, senpai!
Come on, come on! It's okay to let your voice out!
You cheeky girl!
No! This is too intense!
Coming... I'm coming!
Did you come?
I haven't yet though!
No! Stop!
I'll go crazy!
It's impossible for me to stop in this state.
I'm almost there!
I'm gonna come just like this!
You can't! If you come inside me now...
Come one, clean it up.
Jeez... You sure do whatever you please, senpai!
Your bill is 3500 yen.
Huh? I don't have enough with me.
Sorry, lend me some cash!
Huh?!
But doing it while wearing different from usual
was fun. What do you want to wear next time?
I'm never wearing those ever!
How about a nurse uniform?
I don't want to!
Then, how about a bunny girl suit
I'll never ever wear that!
Then, how about a wedding dress?
Like I'm saying, I won't!
Th-That's is, well...
something that we'll save up for later.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization