Only my oppai soul
Extra Episode
Love cheering
It's the finals of the district tournament.
Our opponents are regulars at nationals... a strong school.
We have to win and go to nationals
for our manager, Shinozuka-senpai's, sake!
Go, Shunya-kun!
But...
We couldn't break the wall to nationals.
Damn, no wonder they always make nationals.
Shut up. We're gonna win next year! Damn it!
I can't believe we lost without even scoring a goal.
I really wanted to impress her.
Shunya-kun!
Good work out there.
It was a close game.
Sorry, I couldn't keep my promise.
Well, we're gonna go on ahead.
Make sure you get Shinzouka-senpai to comfort you.
Shut up! Get lost!
See you later!
I promise I'll bring the team to nationals!
Thank you for today.
I'll see you around.
U-Um, so nobody's home today, so...
Would you like to come in?
Can I?!
I'd love to!
Great! Come on in!
Th-Thank you.
Come on, you prepared for this.
Just do it like it said in the magazine and he'll love it.
Okay!
U-Um...
Hey, you need to stay still.
Wh-Where is this coming from?
Well, I wanted to make you happy.
A reward for trying so hard in the match.
Just wait a second...
S-Senpai?!
Okay, now lie down.
You can do whatever you want with my boobs.
Huh?! Wh-What?
Why?!
Come on, don't hold back.
The magazine said that doing this should work,
but is this really going to make him happy?
So, what do you think? Is this cheering you up?
So good... I love this...
Really? Thank goodness!
You can do whatever you want to them.
You're gonna make them swell up
if you keep licking so much!
He's gotten so big.
I can tell without even taking it out of his pants.
Senpai?
Okay, it's my turn to lick now.
Wow, it's gotten so hard.
Uh, I think it said to be gentle
and make sure I don't use any teeth.
So? Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good!
Senpai, your mouth... it's so warm!
Shit... I'm gonna cum!
So this is semen?
It's so thick and sticky. It tastes so strange.
Senpai...
So, how was that?
Did it feel good?
Y-Yeah!
Okay, let me clean you up.
I-If you do it so hard, I-I'm gonna cum again!
Huh? Is that...
What is this?
Don't look at that!
I forgot to hide the dirty magazine that I borrowed!
That's something that I got from
my friend in the cheerleading club.
She said it'd be something to help cheer you on!
It's not mine!
Why don't you try wearing this?
No! It's too embarrassing!
Please!
I know you'll look good in it!
This is a lot smaller than I thought.
Oh well...
It looks so good!
It's so hot!
Uh, that doesn't sound too flattering to me.
It's made me this hard.
Good grief. This is a one time thing, okay?
This outfit is so embarrassing!
So this is senpai's...
Hey, I'm the one supposed to be making you feel good!
I-If you keep doing it like that...
I want you to feel good too, senpai!
Um, can I put it in?
Huh?!
Wait!
I'm not mentally prepared yet!
Senpai, your insides are wrapping around me!
This is so intense!
P-Please do it slower!
It's going so deep inside me!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I was just a little surprised, that's all.
I'll do the moving this time.
How does it feel?
Good?
I-I feel like I'm gonna melt!
Hey, you're moving again!
I can't help myself!
Uh, I-I'm gonna cum, senpai!
H-Huh?! D-Don't!
Do it outside of me...
You came so much...
Sorry, I couldn't stop.
Good grief.
Um, could I go another time?
H-Huh?
I want more!
Let me rest a little!
This is gonna make me go crazy!
I want you to feel good!
That's...
I love you, Eri-san!
N-No!
Just hearing that gets me so turned on
that it's making my head spin!
I love you! I love you so much, Eri-san!
That makes me so happy!
I'm about to cum again!
That's fine.
Go ahead and cum inside me!
Eri-san, I...
Good grief, it's so unfair of you
to call me by my first name like that.
S-Sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
It made me happy.
Um, we'll definitely win next year,
so please come and cheer...
Sure. I'll be looking forward to it.
Th-Thanks for having me over!
See you later.
I'm glad my feelings got through to him.
Technique compilation to please guys!
I guess I gotta give the credit to this.
I'll need to give this back.
It's so stretched out!
She's gonna be so mad at me!
Mizugi
This is cute, but the ribbon on this one's pretty cute too.
Secret study
Senpai invited me to the beach,
so I have to be serious about this.
Finding everything okay?
Actually, do you have this in a different color?
I'll be right back.
Hey, Nozomi!
Senpai, find anything cute?
Yeah, the perfect one!
Take a look!
Frickin' cute, right?!
Huh?!
You wouldn't catch me dead
in something that embarrassing!
What's wrong with you?!
You don't have to worry about it.
It'll be my present to you.
Thank you for your purchase.
Can't wait for the beach tomorrow.
I'm not wearing that!
What?
Then how about you show me
what it looks like on you now?
No. There's no way I'm putting...
karaoke
pirapupu
Oh wow, look! Karaoke!
I have a sudden urge to sing! Come on, let's go!
Huh?!
Is there anything else you'd like to order?
Nope.
Then please enjoy.
It was so hot. I'm sweating bullets.
What do you want to sing, senpai?
Who cares about singing?
Didn't you say you wanted to?!
Hey, stop! I'm gonna get mad!
You're cute when you're mad.
You just love saying that.
What happens if a staff member comes?
I doubt they'll come until our time here's up.
Huh?!
W-We really shouldn't be doing this here!
You're such a worrywart.
You just don't worry enough, senpai!
N-No!
Then how about I'll stop if you wear the bikini.
Th-That's...
If you're not on board,
I'll just do even more embarrassing things.
F-Fine, I'll do it!
I'll put it on!
It's cute how obedient you are too.
I-Is this enough?
I knew it! It looks so good on you!
I feel like everything's falling out of it.
That's what makes it good!
Look what it's done to me!
Y-You don't have to show me!
You're such an idiot, senpai.
Hey, who was the one who tutored who?
I don't have much of a choice, so I'll help you out here.
That's good, take it deep!
S-Senpai, you're too big!
You know, my dick's one thing, but...
What about your huge boobs?
W-Wait, Senpai... Stop!
Stop! Please don't play around with my boobs!
You're so mean.
I'm not a fan of these.
You're not?
You should have more pride in your boobs.
They're big and sensitive to boot.
I don't think I'll ever get tired of fondling them.
N-Not my nipples!
I'm sensitive there!
Also, was any of that supposed
to make me feel better about myself?
U-Uh, yeah...
But I guess it kinda makes me happy if you're happy, senpai.
So I'll make you feel really good with my boobs.
Wow, you can really say the wildest things now, huh?
J-Just forget it!
Just stay still, okay?
I'll make you feel good, just stay put.
That's so good!
Shit, I'm gonna...
It's okay. Just cum in between my boobs!
There's so much...
Did it feel good?
Yeah, so good.
I'll get the rest of it too, okay?
W-Wait not now!
Oh, look. It's ready to go again.
Don't act surprised when you did that on purpose.
What do you wanna do?
A staff member could come in at any second.
I think we have plenty of time left.
That's the spirit!
Here it comes.
Okay.
S-Senpai, you're being so rough!
D-Do it slower!
D-Don't go so deep!
I'm weak there!
What's that? You want it deep?
You can cum if you want.
N-No, I'm gonna cum!
I'm letting out really weird moans!
It's okay. Be as loud as you want.
Please don't hit me!
No! My head's going blank!
I'm about to cum!
– Shit!
Yes?
You have ten minutes left,
would you like to extend your time?
Uh, yeah, give us another thirty minutes.
Okay, no problem.
Would you like to order any drinks or food?
No, I think we're good.
Thanks.
You're such a meanie.
That was on purpose, wasn't it?
I thought it'd be a good chance to hear your cute moans.
Here's your retribution.
I think I found your weak point, senpai.
Take that! You can moan if you want to.
Don't get full of yourself!
N-No!
This is too rough!
I-I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Did you cum?
I haven't yet.
N-No! Stop!
I'm starting to feel weird!
There's no way I can stop myself now!
I'm gonna cum now!
N-No! If you cum in me right now, I'm gonna...
Okay, clean me up.
You're really selfish, you know that, senpai?
Cashier
Your total is three-thousand five hundred yen.
Oh crap, I'm short on cash.
Sorry, lend me some?
Huh?!
It's fun doing it in different clothes, isn't it?
What do you want to wear next?
I'm not wearing anything you give me!
Maybe a nurse outfit?
No!
Bunny girl?
Definitely no!
Maybe a wedding dress?
I'm not wearing that!
H-Hm, but... maybe in the future...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: shiroyasha
edit: braden
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч