Only my oppai soul
Huh? Isn't that...
Asakura-san? From class two?
She looks really cute in a tracksuit too!
She has huge boobs too.
Hey, that's Kaori.
Huh? You know her, Sato?
Yeah, we're in the same club.
Want me to introduce you?
For real?!
How about I do it for three snacks from the school store?
Ugh, you're taking advantage of the situation!
Women's Locker Room
So, that being said...
would you mind meeting with him for a bit?
Not a chance!
This is what he looks like.
Still no?
That's not it, I just don't want to.
Oh? He looks like a pretty interesting guy.
Prez...
Let me see real quick.
Uh... wai...
I'll be going on ahead.
Incoming Message
Huh? After showing her my
picture, Kaori wants to meet me?!
"Hurry up and come to the club room <3"
No frickin' way!
Girls Volleyball Club
Excuse me... Huh? There's nobody here?
Is this a bra?!
And it's so huge!
Looks like I found myself an underwear thief.
I even have a picture of proof.
W-Wait, no, I only...
Huh? So you're trying to weasel your way out of this?
Mr. Underwear thief.
Oh no. That's my bra.
It'd be tough on him if this
picture got leaked to the teachers.
He might even get expelled.
W-Wait! This is crazy!
Well, we're not heartless, so we wouldn't mind
letting this slide as long as you listen to our orders.
You're going to be our manager starting today.
You must follow any and all of my orders.
So?
If you don't want to, I'll tell the teachers...
F-Fine, I get it!
I'll do it.
Good choice!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Judging from that reaction, you're a virgin, aren't you?
Just as we thought.
Hey...
Megumi, hold him down.
You got it.
What are you...
Oh? This isn't too bad.
We can have fun with this.
It's so cute.
Stop...
Hey, Sato?! What the hell's going on?!
Sorry, I can't really go against them...
Don't worry, we'll make you feel really good.
Okay, just stay still.
It's filling my mouth...
So? Does my mouth feel good?
It's starting to twitch.
Crap...
You're moaning so pathetically.
Is this where it feels good?
Are you already about to cum?
That's fine. Cum!
Just cum!
It's coming... I'm cumming!
There's so much...
That was a lot faster than I expected.
But you're going to have to try harder.
Let me have a turn, Saki.
Let me in on the fun.
Come on, try touching them.
I don't have a bra on right now.
You can do whatever you want to them.
My hands are kneading into them.
I want you to really mess them up.
Holy crap...
Come on, that's not enough for me.
R-Right...
That's good!
Looks like you're getting hard down there.
S-Senpai?!
It's fine. Do it harder.
You see, my nipples like to hide.
It's a little embarrassing, but...
Would you mind sucking them out for me?
O-Okay...
You're doing great.
You're very good at this.
I guess I need to take care of you too.
Your dick's getting really hard.
Do you like boobs?
Y-Yes...
Oh, I see.
So that's what you're into?
So? How's this for you?
See? Doesn't it feel really good?
It's so tasty.
This is so good...
It's so tight...
You can't cum yet.
Let us enjoy this longer.
Okay, you're going to cum on my boobs next.
Come on, open your mouth.
It's starting to really twitch now.
Are you about to cum?
Y-Yes!
I-I'm cumming!
My boobs are drenched.
You're not done cumming yet, right?
Wait, stop!
Senpai!
Crap, that's a strong smell.
It's making my head spin.
They're going so far with him...
Sato-san?
I have a bit of a request.
Huh? O-Oh, yes, what do you need?
So? Are you recording?
Y-Yes, it should probably be okay.
Okay then, we're going to start his
virgin graduation ceremony right now.
We already made him cum twice though.
Take a look. This is your first time seeing one, right?
You're going to put your thing in here.
But isn't it bad for us to be doing this at school?
Whatever, just do it already.
Senpai!
That was too sudden!
Holy crap, so this is what it's like to be inside a girl?
It's so wet and I feel like I'm gonna melt!
I don't need your commentary!
Do it slower!
Yeah, that's good!
Come on, go deeper!
Okay!
Okay, I'll do it now.
So? Does it feel good?
It feels completely different than doing it by yourself, right?
Y-Yes!
I'll teach you a thing or two from here on out.
I'll teach you until you can't think of anyone else but me.
Alright, I think it's time for his first creampie!
What, you don't want to?
I bet it'll feel really good!
I-I want to do it.
Points for being honest.
Make sure you record this to commemorate it.
Senpai, I'm gonna...
That's fine, just cum!
Wow, it's flowing out.
You might be more than I expected.
Okay, then I'm next.
Wanna do it?
Come on, hurry up and put it in.
It's so big!
I want you to thrust it in me harder!
I like it when you play with my nipples too.
Hey, does my pussy feel good?
Y-Yeah, it's so soft!
That's good.
It's coming in so deep!
I like this!
Your dick is the best!
I don't think I can ever give this up!
Hey, do you think you could fill me with your cum too?
A-Are you sure?
Yeah, it's fine. So just keep going until you finish!
Okay?
Okay...
I'm about to cum!
Together...
You should cum too!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Volleyball club, line up!
I'll introduce you all.
This is our new manager.
I-I look forward to working with you all.
He's Takahashi-kun from the same class as Sato.
Oh, this is interesting.
Oh, he's the same guy from yesterday!
What's going on?!
Well, a lot happened...
What's up with him?
Should be fun, don't you think?
I think it'll be a good jump to everyone's motivation.
Sheesh, I don't see anything redeeming about him.
What's going to happen to me now?
Oh, Kouhai-kun!
S-Senpai?!
Let's do our best today as well, okay?
Club Room Cleaning
Um, Asakura-senpai?
What?
Isn't this good enough?
Even if we clean the room every week, the
president just makes it dirty again anyway.
You can't give up that easily, Misa-chan!
We're the ones who protect the morals of this club!
Okay, could you help me move this?
Okay...
Is this Sato-senpai's?
This smells of something interesting!
Sorry, senpai, I'm going to go to the bathroom real quick!
Huh? H-Hey!
Wait! I can't do all of this by myself!
Geez!
Perfect timing! Help me out...
Hey, you're that stalker guy!
Who the hell are you calling a stalker?!
Isn't it suspicious that you joined our club all of a sudden?
And you're the manager of a girl's club.
That's because I was forced to join by the president.
Hmph. A likely story...
You could just say no if you didn't want to do it.
Well, that's...
A lot happened...
I bet you only joined for some kind of obscene reasons!
W-Well, shouldn't we finish cleaning first?
I don't trust you one bit!
If you do anything even a little funny,
I'm going to report you to the teachers!
R-Right...
Good, then throw this garbage out.
All of this?!
That should do it.
It's been due for a good cleaning for a while now.
Wait, it's already this late?!
I had to go meet a teacher!
So... Thanks for helping me clean.
Y-Yeah... Sure.
Sorry, but can you lock the door for me?
Sure, no problem.
Hm? Not a bad atmosphere you got going there, senpai?
When'd you get there?!
Um...
I'm Ozawa Misa, a first year.
So I found something pretty fun.
You have any recollection of this camera?
I'm not exactly sure what you're talking about.
You can't fake your way out of this.
Sato-senpai already filled me in on everything.
Sorry...
Hey! At least try to fake her out!
So, here's a request from your dear, sweet underclassman...
What?
I actually have an interest in this kind of thing.
If you're okay with it, would you...
Do it with me?
Huh?!
Do you not want to do it with me?
That's not... But this is all so sudden.
That's not a problem.
We're just fooling around.
But why me?
Um, well, that's because...
Love at first sight, you know?
That's suspicious.
And you're getting big already, aren't you?
Thank goodness!
Senpai?
It's not good for your body to hold it in.
Hey!
How do my boobs feel?
They're not as big as those two, but...
Shit, how could I ever hold myself back?
Do you like them?
You're really okay with this, right?
Senpai, stop.
Um, just no kissing, okay?
Huh?
Okay...
Why is sex okay, but not kissing?
Please be gentle, okay?
I'm going to make her cum so hard!
Don't suck them!
Um, you've only been playing with my boobs.
Don't like it?
No, I do, but...
You're getting really wet.
That's, um...
I think I get turned on really easily.
Ever since I saw that video, I've been...
Oh, so that's why...
Senpai, you've gotten really big too.
Did rubbing my boobs turn you on?
That would make me happy if it did!
Please make yourself feel good with me.
Senpai, your dick is getting so
hot and it's really twitching now.
How does it feel?
It feels really good the way you're rubbing it!
I feel like I'm gonna cum already!
That's fine. Just cum!
Wow!
So this is semen?
It's really something.
Okay, here.
You made this mess, so please clean it up, okay?
Huh? Oh...
Yes, that's it. Wipe it all off please.
Sure.
Senpai, your hand movements are so dirty.
What's that supposed to mean?
Could you lick them clean too?
Huh? You serious?
Sheesh...
Just like that. It's almost like you're a baby.
It tickles!
You're sucking too hard, senpai!
Then let me try touching down here.
Wait, that's...
Wait! Don't! Don't be rough there!
N-No!!
It feels too good!!
Please let me take a little break...
Not happening.
Come on, open up your legs.
Hey, wai...
No! Don't!
I'm cumming!!
You're such a meanie.
Um, senpai? I can't hold on any longer.
Senpai, please put your dick in here...
You don't have to tell me twice.
It's so tight!
It's completely different than theirs!
Senpai, your dick's going so deep... It's so good!
Are you okay? I'm going to start moving.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll do it slow.
It's so tight! I feel like I'm gonna cum already!
Not yet! Hold it in!
It's so deep!
This is bad, senpai.
Doing this by the window...
People are going to see!
Thinking that someone's going to
see my boobs makes me so excited!
I like this!
Do it harder!
Sorry...
You were just so cute, I did it on instinct.
No, I won't forgive you.
Please take responsibility.
Just kidding.
Misa-chan!
I don't think I can hold myself back at all anymore.
That's okay.
Please make me feel really good!
I love your dick!
Does it feel good when I rub it here?
That feels good!
I'm not letting you rest just yet!
N-No, I'm...
I can't stop cumming!
Your face when you're cumming is really cute too!
You dummy!
How many times have you cummed?
A-About five times...
Then let's cum together for the last one.
N-No, senpai, not my ears!
Can I cum inside you?
Sure, go ahead!
Please fill me up with your cum!
I'm cumming!
Wow, there's so much hot stuff coming inside me.
Sato-senpai, you get all of that?
Yeah, it should probably be okay.
You were still here?!
Stop recording these things!
Oh, wow.
Can you send the data to me later?
Hey!
Okay senpai, I'll leave the cleaning to you.
You're going to get Asakura-senpai
mad at you if you leave it dirty.
Hey! Wait!
Delete that footage!
Not happening.
This is a nightmare.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч