Only my oppai soul
Tests start next week but nothing's sticking in my head!
This is all his fault.
I can't believe him.
I have to sit through that stuff every single day.
Why me?!
But now that it's in my head again...
I can't stop myself!
I won't be able to study with all of this in my head anyway.
I bet I'll be able to clear my head after a quick fap session.
Wow, I'm already this wet?
I think my body's getting more and more sensitive!
My nipples... feel so good!
Oh no, I'm gonna cum!
No...
No, that wasn't nearly enough.
I need to do it harder.
If this keeps up, I'm going to lose my mind.
Here it comes!
Okay!
Sorry!
Ow.
Kaori, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I think I twisted it a little.
Just wait here. I'll call the teacher!
Up you go.
Let's go to the nurse's office.
Huh?! I'm fine. Put me down.
Where the heck did you come from?
W-Well he's offering, so why not just go with him?
O-Okay...
Hold on tight.
Hey, keep your hands off of there!
Yeah, I know.
Nurse's Office
Yep, just a small sprain.
But if you continue to feel pain, go to the hospital.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank goodness, right? You'll still be okay for the game.
T-Thank you, I guess.
Oh, crap!
The club president was calling for me.
I'll see you later!
Huh? Wait...
You've got guts, making me wait this long.
It wasn't on purpose, senpai.
No excuses.
Looks like you need to be punished.
Huh?!
Oh my. Does that make you happy?
Alright, then let's do it like this today.
H-Hey...
It's been a while, so we'll take real good care of you.
J-Just wait...
Hey, stop struggling!
Is this a prank?
Oh crap!
Hey, what's the matter?!
Oh my.
Let's get away now!
Do your best, Kouhai-kun.
Wha... At least take this off of me!
Sorry, you're on your own!
No!
It's you two again?!
Really?!
This is your chance. Run away now!
Huh? Who are you?
Gym Storage
Um...
Keep quiet.
What are you...
Shut up. Just stay still.
Wait I know this voice. Are you...
Sato?!
Finally, the real thing.
Those two are definitely gonna kill me later, aren't they?
My relationship with him is gonna change too.
But I can't wait any longer!
It's all this thing's fault!
It's so tasty!
What's going on? Am I being sucked off?
Maybe it's because I'm blindfolded, but
my other senses are getting sharper.
It's like I'm being melted down to a liquid.
This is the best!
There really is no substitution for the real thing.
Every time I touch it, it twitches a little. It's kinda cute.
Hurry up and shoot out your semen. I want to see you cum!
I want to chug it all down!
Crap, if you keep doing that... Hey! Stop already!
Was she always this dirty?
I'm cumming!
There's so much!
And it's so thick.
Delicious.
It's making my head spin!
Sato, why are you doing this?
I-It's all your fault!
Huh?!
You're the reason that I've become this crazy!
How?!
So take responsibility!
Responsibility?
What I'm saying is...
S-Sex... Have sex with me!
Huh?!
Do you even hear yourself right now?!
Hey, Sato...
Fine, whatever, I'll do it myself!
Wai...
Look, you're hard.
So what, you're in the mood?
It's a natural reaction as a guy.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Are you saying that it'd do this for anyone?
W-Well not exactly, but...
Well, it'd be better for me if that's how it is.
Come on, come here.
You like boobs, right?
Okay, I'm putting it in.
It might be bigger than I thought.
So, does it feel good inside me?
Yeah, it's so hot, I'm gonna melt!
Oh, right. Since we're here...
I gotta record this, right?
Why?
It's my first time having sex.
Yeah, so? Doesn't mean you have to record it!
What's the problem? This isn't
the first time you've been filmed.
I can't put my finger on it, but...
Hey, is it okay to move?
Yeah, go ahead.
I want you to do me hard.
I'm at my limit! I can't wait any longer!
I knew it! His dick...
It's the best!
More! Do it so hard, you break me!
Hey, does it feel good inside me?
It's so hot inside you, it's amazing!
I feel like I'm about to lose my mind!
You're thrusting so wildly inside me!
Does your dick really feel that good?
It... It's coming all the way inside me!
I can't stop cumming!
It's completely different than when I do this myself!
I'll have sex with you whenever you want!
So let's have more sex, okay?
You're so dirty!
That's your fault!
I blame you!
Don't blame me!
More!
Just by getting involved with you guys, I...
No... It's going so deep... I'm gonna cum!
I think I'm at my limit.
Don't stop moving! We need to cum together!
You can cum inside me.
So give it to me inside!
Hurry!
Give me all of the cum in here!
I'm cumming!
Go ahead. Cum!
I'm cumming!!
Let's go one more time!
Let go!
Nope.
You!
Found you, Sato!
Oh my.
Looked like you had lots of fun
while we were getting yelled at.
No, wait. I can explain!
I never thought you'd pull something like this.
Hey...
Senpai? Stop...
Tell me how your first time felt.
You even let him cum inside.
Oh my. Getting aroused from them?
You're rock hard.
Looks like you still got plenty left in the tank.
I'll make you feel good.
Alright then, how about we start the second set?
Prepare yourself.
Hey, everyone, got a second?
The summer tournament is just around the corner.
So we're going to have a training camp!
We're going to have it at my villa.
Villa?!
Yay for the wealthy!
We even have a pool.
The only thing is that it's a little deep into the mountains.
So with that being said, I have a
little favor to ask of you, Asakura.
Yes? What is it?
Just a little shopping.
We're finally here.
I didn't think it'd be this far into the mountains.
Are you sure you're okay carrying all of our stuff?
This is nothing.
It would've been nice if Sayama-senpai came too.
But apparently she had something to do at home.
You guys were taking so long, we got bored.
Well, that's fine.
Let's have lunch now.
Okay everyone, it's time for the long awaited barbecue!
Yay!
Meat!
Do they even plan on practicing?
Come on senpai, you too!
There's not gonna be any meat left for you.
Don't worry, there's still plenty left.
Here, these are already cooked.
Why are they all over him?
Asakura?
What's the matter? You seem kinda sour.
Not really.
I've just been noticing that everyone's changed.
Say "ah".
Ah...
What's good about him? Everyone's getting tricked!
Really? I think he's pretty fun.
It's so obvious that he has ulterior motives. Disgusting!
Well, I guess...
Here, here.
Come on, eat it. Please!
Oh dear.
You have such a ridiculous face when you sleep, senpai.
You're finally awake.
Wh-What are you two doing?!
You weren't getting up any faster and we couldn't wait.
So yummy!
You reek of sweat, senpai!
So cute.
Training camps don't come often,
so let's enjoy ourselves, senpai!
I'll make you feel real good.
This also counts as thanks for carrying our luggage.
Come on, the lotion feels good, doesn't it?
Cum as much as you want, okay?
Alright, sit up.
It's okay if I go first, right?
Huh?
Alright then.
Do your best to satisfy us.
You're already twitching a lot!
Do you really wanna put it in that bad?
Wai...
Come on. Use your mouth on me here.
It's inside me, senpai!
Use your tongue better!
Push it in deeper!
This is really the best!
Your dick is so big and hard!
Hurry up and give it to me too!
If you keep going that hard, I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
There's so much cum!
You're too fast.
S-Sorry.
It's been building up.
That's not good. Boys shouldn't be letting it build up.
Come on, don't tease me. Give it to me already.
Okay!
It's so hot inside you, senpai!
I was holding myself back this entire time.
I feel like I'm already about to cum!
That's fine! Cum inside me just like that!
Your hot stuff is flooding inside me!
I knew this would happen!
You really came a lot.
What are you gonna do if Kaori finds you guys doing this?
Come on, let's get back. Geez.
Senpai, let's go again!
Hey, are you listening to me?!
Don't try and act like you're above us.
You bought that swimsuit just
so that he'd see it, didn't you?
No, I just thought it was kinda cute.
It's written all across your face. Why don't
you just try and be a little more honest?
Or are you good with just videotaping us?
I wanted to do it with you all this time
too! I've really been holding myself back!
Why are you stooping to their level too?
Shut up.
What are you doing?!
Shut up! Whose fault do you think this is?!
I've really changed for the worse because of this dick.
Come on, you like boobs, right?
Hurry up and cum already!
They're so soft!
That's... Oh my god!
Okay, all ready.
His dick really is the best!
Come on, shove it in me deeper!
You're such a good-for-nothing.
Shut up.
I love this!
I can't stop my hips!
You're getting so tight!
No, not my nipples!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!!
Sorry for the wait. Are you guys already going at it?
Wha...
You're finally here.
You're late, Pres.
– What in the world are you doing?!
– W-Wai...
– You pervert!
Don't ever come near me! You freak!
I've hated you ever since I saw your picture!
Are you sure? I'm sure there are some
parts of him that you don't hate.
There aren't any!
This kind of guy is the worst!
This is why men are...
Now, now, calm down.
Wh... Pres?
How about you confirm it for yourself?
Oh, lost strength in your legs?
Fine, I've got no choice.
I'll do it then.
Just sit there and watch.
Pres?
You can keep going, right?
I'm not sure. This is a kind of bad situation...
What are you saying? You just went at it with
all there of them without a care in the world.
Look, I'm all ready down here, so
hurry up and come inside already.
Pres!
This is the best!
More!
Do it harder!
I'm running out of strength.
You're so pathetic.
Then take a break.
I'll move for you.
You like it when the girl moves, don't you?
Your moans sound so pathetic. Just cum already.
Come on! Come on!!
This kind of thing can't possibly feel good. But then
why do they all look like they enjoy it so much?
Okay, I'm next.
How long do you think you can hold it in?
Do your best, senpai!
I-I can't...
P-Pres?
So? Really turns you on, doesn't it?
You look so happy. I'll make it even tighter.
Y-You don't have to...
You're so pathetic, senpai.
Where's your pride as a guy?
I'm gonna cum!
Not yet! Hold it in more!
Come on, senpai! You can do it!
Thrust it in harder!
I like it rough!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Cum! Flood me with all that cum you've been holding in!
Do it.
So this is a guy's...
It feels gross.
It's really sticky and has a weird smell.
But it kind of excites me.
I-I'll be going now!
A-Asakura?
Senpai!
Not happening!
I wonder if that was too much for her.
Why am I dressed like this?
Also, isn't this a little too see through?
It's your punishment for skipping the training camp, senpai.
You really know how to pick them.
You really thought you could
run away, Sayama?! Think again!
I-I wasn't trying to run away.
I've brought the punishment.
It's Takahashi-kun.
He's a completely different person!
Wait...
What is this... He's too big!
No...
Stop!!
Inside me... I can't...
Come over here, senpai!
S-So mean.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч