Ikkyuu
Nyuukon
Final
Chapter
Midterm exams will be next week,
but nothing's going in my head.
This is all their fault!
I can't do this...
They make me watch those stuffs everyday...
Why is this even happening to me?
Now that I remember it, I'm...
No... I can't take it anymore.
I won't be able to study like this.
I'll settle down if I do it once.
Oh no... I'm already this wet.
My body is gradually becoming sensitive.
My nipple feels good!
Oh no, I'm coming!
No...
I can't... Just this much ain't enough.
I need to do it rougher.
I'd go crazy at this rate.
Here it goes!
Okay!
Ah! Sorry!
Ouch...
Kaori, are you alright?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I think I twisted my ankle a little.
Wait here. I'm gonna call the teacher.
Heave-ho!
I'll take you to the infirmary.
Huh?
I'm fine, put me down!
And where were you earlier?
S-Since he's already here, how about it?
Uhh... Okay.
Hold on tight, okay?
Hey, don't touch me on weird places!
Yeah, yeah.
[School Infirmary]
It's just a minor sprain.
Go to the hospital if the pain persists.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Great! This means you'll still be able
to participate in the coming match.
I-I owe you a thank you at least.
Ah... Oh no!
I forgot that the club prez was
looking for me. See you later!
Eh? Wait!
You have some nerve to make me wait.
That's not it, senpai.
No excuses!
I think this calls for a punishment.
Oh my! Are you actually wanting it?
Then let's go for this one today.
Wait—
It's been a while so I'll be
loving you much today.
Wait...
Hey, stop struggling!
Is this someone's prank?
Whoa! This is bad!
Hey, what's this all about?
Oh my...
We'll be going for now!
Good luck, kouhai-kun!
Wait, at least take these off me!
Sorry, try to do something about it yourself!
No~!
It's you two again! Wait right there!
Here, hurry up before it's too late!
Who are you?
[P.E. Equipment Storage Room]
Hey!
Be quiet.
Whoa! What are you...
Just hold still!
This voice, could she be...
Satou?
It's the real thing at last...
This will make senpai mad at me later for sure.
And our relationship as classmates too...
But I can't take it anymore!
It's all the fault of this thing!
It's delicious!
What's happening? Is she blowing me?
I can't see a thing so my mind
is focused on the sensation...
It's like she's making my dick melt!
Oh... This is the best!
I knew it, nothing beats the real thing!
It twitches when I touch it. It's kind of cute.
I want to see his semen shooting out already!
I want to drink it all up!
Stop! If you keep doing that... Hey!
I said stop—
This girl... Was she actually this lewd?
I'm coming!
Wow... There's so much! And it's slimy!
It tastes good! It's tingling in my head!
Satou... Why would you do this?
I-It's your fault!
It's all your fault that I became crazy like this!
Why the hell me?
That's why, well... Take responsibility on this!
Responsibility?
What I mean is...
H-Have sex with me!
Huh? What the heck are you saying?
Hey... Satou...
Fine... I'll just do this myself!
Aren't you getting big again?!
You got in the mood?
It's just male physiology!
Huh? What's with that?
Huh?
You mean it doesn't matter
who you're doing it with?
T-That's not true...
Well, it would be good for me
if that's actually the case.
Here, come closer.
Don't you love breasts?
I'm putting it in, okay?
It's bigger that I thought...
Hey, does it feel good inside me?
Yeah... It's so hot like it's melting me!
Oh yeah, since we're finally doing it...
We should record this.
Why should we?
Because it's my first time having sex.
You don't really need to...
Isn't it alright? I've always been
recording everyone before.
I don't really get it...
Hey, can I start moving?
Yeah... It's okay.
I want you to do me hard.
After all of that teasing, I'm at my limit already!
I knew it, his dick...
is the best!
More! Do it like you're breaking me down!
Hey, does it feel good inside me?
Your insides are so hot!
It's like I'm gonna faint!
You're pumping me like a dog!
Does your dick feel that good?
It's going so deep in me!
I've been coming non-stop since earlier!
It's totally different from doing it myself!
From now on, I'll let you do it anytime.
Let's have a lot of sex!
You're actually a slut, aren't you?
It's your fault!
Don't pass the blame on others!
More!
I was just dragged along by all of you!
No! So deep, I'm coming!
I'm at my limit!
Don't stop! Let's come together inside!
You can shoot like this.
I want it inside me!
Hurry! Shoot all the stacked semen from these!
Coming!
It's okay, come!
I'm coming!
Let's do it again just like this!
Hey!
I'm not letting go!
I found you at last, Satou!
Oh my!
Aren't you having so much fun
while we were being lectured.
No, this is...
I never expected you
to do something this bold.
Senpai... don't!
Tell me about your first time.
You even asked for a creampie.
My, my...
Did you get horny seeing them like that?
You got such an amazing boner.
Looks like you can go on with this.
I'll make you feel really good.
Then, let's start the second set now.
Brace yourselves.
May I have a moment, everyone?
The summer tournament is coming.
We're going on a training camp!
It'll be at my vacation house.
Vacation house? As expected from a rich family!
We also have a pool there. Though it's
just somewhere deep in the mountains.
And so, I have a favor to ask from you, Asakura.
Okay, what would it be?
Just some shopping, I guess?
We're finally here!
I never expected it to be this deep in the mountains...
Are you sure you can carry all of our stuff?
This much is nothing for me!
Too bad that Sayama-senpai couldn't make it.
Seemed like she had some family issues.
No!
You're finally here!
You took forever that we got tired of waiting.
Oh well, let go have some lunch.
Listen, everyone! The long-awaited
barbecue party begins!
Yay!
Meat~!
What the... She doesn't have any plan to practice.
Hey, you should hurry up too, senpai.
You're gonna miss all of this meat.
We still have more so it's alright.
Here, I cooked these myself.
What's with everyone? They're fawning all over him.
Asakura?
What's wrong? You look so grumpy.
Nothing. It's just like that
everyone has changed recently.
Say "Ah"~!
Ah...
What's even good with that thing?
Everyone's just getting tricked!
Eh... I think he's such an interesting guy.
I can totally read that guy's
hidden motives! He's creepy as hell!
Well, that's...
Over here!
Please eat mine!
I can't eat anymore...
Oh, this is bad.
You make a dumb face when you sleep, senpai.
You finally woke up.
What! What are you two doing?
You're not waking up
so we got tired of waiting.
Yummy!
You reek of sweat, senpai!
How cute!
We don't always have a training camp,
so let's make the most of it, senpai!
I'll make you feel very good.
And this is for carrying our baggage as well.
See? Doesn't this sliminess feels good?
Please do it as much as you can, okay?
Here, open your mouth.
Can I have it first?
It can't be helped.
Do your best and satisfy her, okay?
It's twitching so much!
Do you want it inside me that much?
Wait...
Right here.
Do me too using your mouth.
It's inside me, senpai!
Right there, use your tongue more! Deeper!
This is the best! It's so hard and thick!
Hurry! Let me have that too!
If you do it that hard, I'm gonna...
You're squirting so hard in me!
Oh, you came too quick!
Sorry, I'm so backed up.
That's bad! Boys should take good care of it.
Stop teasing me. Give it to me already!
Okay!
It's so hot inside you, senpai!
That's because I'm craving it since earlier!
I'm gonna come again already!
Alright, shoot it inside just like that!
It's so hot!
It's pouring in me!
I knew it will be like this!
You came so much.
What will we do if Kaori finds out about this?
Let's go back out there, jeez!
Senpai, let's start the next round!
Listen when people are talking!
Please stop acting like a good girl!
Didn't you buy that swimsuit
to show them off to senpai?
Not really... I just thought they're kind of cute...
You're too obvious.
How about being true to yourself?
Or are you satisfied being just a camerawoman?
E-Even I want to do it but
I've been holding myself back!
Even you are joining up with
them. What are you doing?
Just shut up.
What are you doing?!
Shut up! And who's fault is it
that it turned out like this?
Everything is this dick's fault. This is the worst!
Stupid dick!
Here! Don't you like breasts?
Hurry up and come already!
So soft!
Damn, this is bad!
Preparations are all done!
Hey...
I knew it, his dick is the best!
Hey, thrust it deeper in me!
You're so useless!
Shut up!
I love this. My hips won't stop!
You're squeezing me so tight!
Not my nipples! I'm coming!
Thanks for waiting!
Is everyone doing it?
Whoa!
Finally!
You're late, club prez!
What are you doing here naked? Pervert!
Uhh... Wai—
Don't come any closer, you're disgusting!
I hated you from the moment I saw your photo!
You say it like that but the truth is
he's something more than that for you.
No way!
He's the worst! This is why boys are...
Calm down, don't talk like that.
Wait... Club prez?!
How about you check it out yourself.
What...
Oh my, did your knees gave out on you?
It can't be helped.
Well then. I'll be doing it, so you just watch there.
Club prez?
You still can go on, right?
I doubt it. Especially with this situation.
What are you saying?
After fucking everyone so much...
Look, I'm all ready down here so do it already.
Club prez!
This is the best!
More! Fuck me harder!
I'm already exhausted...
Darn it! You're pathetic.
Just take a rest then.
I will do the moving.
Don't you love it when you're
the one getting banged?
Let me hear your miserable voice in orgasm!
Here, here, here you go!
This should be disgusting, but why does everyone seem to enjoy it?
I'm next, okay? How long will you be able to last?
Good luck, senpai!
No more!
Club prez?
How's it? Getting horny?
You face in agony makes me
hornier! I'll tease you a lot!
Stop...
You're pathetic, senpai! Don't you
even have a pride as a man?
I'm gonna come!
No, you can't! Hold it in as long as you can!
Go, go, do your best, senpai!
Thrust it more! I like it hard!
Coming! It's coming out!
Wow!
Shoot them out! Everything
that you held back so hard!
How desperate!
Whoa... This is a man's... How gross!
It's all sticky and has a weird smell.
I'm next, right?
But somehow my heart is racing.
Stop this already!
I'll excuse myself.
Ah, Asakura!
Maybe the stimulation is too much for her.
Why do I have to wear this?
And isn't this so thin that you can see through it?
It's your penalty for missing the training camp.
Doesn't it look scandalous?
Sayama, it's unfair that only you
got away from the training camp!
It's not like I ran away from it.
I brought the punishment.
He's Takahashi-kun.
He's like a totally different person now!
Wait!
What is this? He's so big!
Don't!
Stop!
Not inside...
He's coming after us, senpai!
How cruel!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project