The World Tree that rises so gallantly, the Yggsirad.
But now, it's withering, slowly losing its vitality.
Isn't it one hell of a show?
Odin, ruler of Gods.
They are the valkyries who came to save you. Isn't it hilarious?
Hell, King of Hades,
why did you decide to attack Heaven?
It was just on a whim.
Loki! You traitor!
How rude.
You're telling me you killed my son, Balder, on a whim!?
That's right.
Even so, I wasn't expecting you, Odin-sama,
to come down here personally.
That loss of control is what caused this situation.
I feel sorry for you.
You're going to be defeated by your
own ultimate spear, the Gungnir.
They, who did not know men due to their
mindset of devoting everything to battle,
have all lost their virginities, becoming playthings for the demons.
There is no longer anyone left in Heaven who can fight.
But victory lies within me.
I shut the gate to the River of Wisdom that flows beneath Yggsirad.
Yggsirad will completely wither in five days, and the world will end.
In order to prevent that from happening, you have to free me.
We already have that handled.
What?
How could this be?
She told me everything.
The leader of the valkyries, Freya.
Apparently, the gold and silver keys which open the
gate are located in the uteri of two valkyries.
I'm sorry, Odin-sama.
I told them everything.
It just feels too good...
Did you use a love potion on her?
Like I'd need to.
All I need is my cock.
I didn't hive enough time.
That feels so good!
I'm going to cum!
Seems like even the leader of the valkyries
couldn't win against the lust inside her.
So, what are the names of the two valkyries?
Tell me, in front of your previous lord, Odin,
the names of the two valkyries who
have the keys stored in their uteri.
While you're at it, tell him who your current master is.
Yes, sir.
The gold and silver keys...
are inside the uteri of Suvia and Sigurd.
I'm sorry, Odin-sama...
Freya...
Suvia, eh?
Sigurd.
The two strongest.
Ikusa Otome Suvia
The Two Valkyries
Why, Suvia!?
Are you implying that you're going to betray us, Gods army?
You were gone for a month,
and now you insist that we valkyries, must fight one another?
I spent the past month analyzing the situation of the war.
Then I realized that it would be wiser
if I were to just fight against you all.
W-What did you say!?
Sigurd, I'm going to give you a word of advice.
Don't go easy on me,
because I'm planning on killing you.
Yes, I'm serious as well.
Wonderful.
The general of Odin's army, who is famed to be able to slice
thousands to their graves with a swipe of her sword, Sigurd.
And a lone soldier who stays calm and analyzes her tactics, Suvia.
If the two who have the keys in their uteri end up taking
each other out, it would be easy to capture the two.
You rely too much on power.
You~
Saw that coming, too!
Not done yet!
There's no way!
You sure are affectionate, Sigurd.
I thought I told you I was serious.
Looks like I win, Sigurd.
Let me join the Hades army!
You can have her, Sigurd, as a souvenir!
What!
Are you happy you won, Suvia?
Yes, very.
Throw away your illusions.
Focus on reality.
Sigurd will be held as prisoner of war,
and Suvia will become a general of the allied
forces made up of giants and demons,
because she captured Sigurd.
This is reality.
Sigurd and Suvia.
It's been a while.
Loki!
You traitor!
Betrayal?
That has nothing to do with it.
All that matters is whether it's fun or not.
Isn't that right?
Wow, Suvia.
You're quite intelligent.
In many ways.
Welcome, Sigurd.
It can't be...
Freya-sama!?
That's right.
It's Freya, Sigurd.
Freya, one of your underlings are here.
Oh, if it isn't Sigurd and Suvia.
Did you two become Flungluni-sama's slave as well?
Hey, lets suck on it together.
Flungluni-sama's cock is like a feast.
Freyi-sama...
You're going to penetrate me next?
What do you think, Sigurd?
I'll shower you with love potion and rape you like I did Freya.
Don't kid around!
I wonder how much longer you'll be able to act tough like that.
You're going to pay for slashing my eye out.
Sigurd.
Your first task is to clean this semen-covered cock of mine.
There.
Seems like you still don t understand your current position!
Please wait, Flungluni-sama.
Why is Suvia referring to Flungluni so politely?
I'll take care of your thing in the place of the unruly Sigurd.
Oh, so you're going to lick my cock?
Suvia...
Very well.
Lick it gently.
I won't go easy on you if you even leave a droplet behind.
This is...
Hey, Sigurd,
you were doubting me, weren't you?
They say, one must start by deceiving
her friends to deceive the enemy.
I see.
So that's what this is about.
You cunts!
Let's go save Odin-sama!
Loki...
Odin-sama!
We'll free you right away!
Good work.
No, 'tis our duty.
I must reward you two.
Hold out your hands.
Thank you.
You too, Suvia.
Y-Yes, sir.
Odin-sama, what is this!?
It's our reward for entertaining me.
Loki!?
It was an illusion!?
Have you come to your senses, Suvia?
Looks like you're finally awake,
Princess Pricencia.
Don't call me that!
I'm a valkyrie now!
Damn valkyries, cutting me up like that!
He must have...
...put us under an illusion back then.
So it was I who wasn't watching reality.
So now you've got the valkyries alive and captured.
That's right.
But we wasted a night thanks to Flungluni's blunder.
Thanks to that, we only have four more days until the world ends.
Okay, it's time to retrieve the keys.
Loki, I'll take Sigurd.
I won't be satisfied until I make a work out of her.
Very well.
I wish you luck, Sigurd.
Don't lose, Suvia!
I won't either!
Valkyrie Suvia.
No, I shall call you by your other name once more.
Princess Pricencia.
Do you remember the time when I took you by the arm
and kissed you at the dinner party in the court?
That was a bother.
Back then, you were absorbed in reading
a book about eastern military tactics.
But it was a bit too wild for the lady of the Pricencia house to read.
So I threw it away.
Threw away my boring status as a lady, I mean!
I guess I should be thanking you for
that dynamism this time around.
Thanks to that, we can be alone together.
You'll woo a woman no matter who they
are, and whatever situation you're in?
Of course.
I'll also make any woman wait.
I'm no woman. I'm a valkyrie!
Nope.
In my eyes, you're the same as you were before.
I'm going to rape you.
I see now.
So that's your true nature, Loki.
Well, it's not like I didn't know.
Hurry up and rape me, then.
No matter how much you defile my body,
you'll never be able to defile my heart!
As long as my heart stays pure, you wont
be able to get the key to the gate!
You don't need to tell me that. I know.
Now, let's enjoy the show.
This is pointless.
No matter what you do to me, I won't hand over the key.
I wonder how long you'll be able to endure this for.
You're going to set monsters on me?
Precisely.
Experience it with your body!
This is...
How does it feel to have both your tits
and pussy pierced with a needle?
This pain is hardly significant.
I bet.
The real deal starts now.
I'm being injected with something...
Sigurd!
What's being injected into you is a love potion of
destruction obtained at the end of this world!
A love potion!?
Something's...
It can't be!
A special female cock has been created!
But it's still not over yet.
Sigurd!
I'm going to fill the inside of your vagina with love potion!
This one has special flesh-altering qualities in it!
It can't be...
What's going on!?
You're shameless, Sigurd.
Isn't it piinful?
My cock is the only thing that can satisfy you.
Damn you... stop kidding around!
He's going to stir me around with that.
No, what am I thinking!?
Don't overstrain yourself.
Now, Sigurd, I'm going to turn you into a woman.
S-Stop!
You're still going to resist?
No!
I'm cumming!
Does it feel good, Sigurd?
Does it feel good to have my cock inside your pussy?
By "pussy", are you talking about my vagina?
Wow, you don't even know about your own body?
What's being stuffed inside you is a cock,
and the hole that's being stuffed is your pussy.
Cock...
Pussy...
Stop the jokes!
I see, so you're still not feeling good.
You sure are stubborn.
Learn that your stubbornness will in
turn leave you at a disadvantage!
No!
This can't be!
How...
is milk coming out of my breasts?
Look, Suvia.
Your perverted pussy is visible now.
All I can say is that you've got some bad hobbies.
I see, so this doesn't affect you at all.
Then I'll do something to remind you that you're a female.
Suvia, your body is reacting to your nipples being sucked on.
You're so unsubmissive.
Then what about this?
This... means nothing to me.
Then how about this?
It's futile.
Oh, my.
Looks like your clitoris is quite sensitive.
S-Something like this isn't enough to...
I wonder how much longer you can keep that attitude up for.
Your pussy is starting to get wet.
I love that persevering expression on your face.
You're disgusting, Loki!
I won't deny that.
I'm being defiled by tentacles...
No!
Oh?
Looks like you killed your voice.
You're something else, just as I expected.
Did you want me to howl like a beast?
Nope, that's fine.
Suvia, I'm becoming more and more
interested in you by the minute.
This could be destiny.
It had been decided since that day,
that it would be I...
who'd make you into a woman.
Do you understand?
I just stole your virginity.
Shut up!
You're so stubborn.
You refuse to scream even when someone just took your virginity.
But that's what I like about you.
I may have fallen in love with you.
What selfish words!
Yes, I am indeed selfish.
There, I'll shove it in deeper.
Taste my dick with your juicy meat!
What?
I get it now, Suvia.
This part.
It can't be...
You've started to raise your voice now.
Sh-Shut up!
That's right.
Enjoy it.
Have a taste of what it means to be a
woman with both pain and pleasure!
No!
S-Something's coming!
It's rushing into me...
Something filthy...
Dammit!
Sigurd, is this what you're going through right now too?
They're being sucked on!
My breasts!
Wow, Sigurd.
You keep cumming after being milked.
But...
I'm going to keep pushing you to the edge.
It's your punishment for making fun of me!
I won't lose!
I'm a valkyrie...
Valkyrie Sigurd!
Even if my body is defiled by pleasure,
my heart will never give in.
You're going to become my woman.
I refuse.
I'm a valkyrie.
I won't let you do as you please.
Suvia, now I want to make you mine no matter what.
My objective to return the key just went down on the list.
This woman...
This me, courageous woman...
I'd like to taste her, and make both her heart and her body mine.