She was full of energy, but it ended all too soon.
She's probably an inexperienced battle maiden.
But she has an experienced slut's body.
Only her ass is ripe.
An experienced woman is more like...
They're much tighter down there.
They're very nice and tight.
When they're petite.
You're right about that!
While we're here, l think l'll train one of them.
W-Why you...
Thanks for guiding me here.
How dare you say that a lady's ass is huge?
lt's just rude!
l can't believe that our castle fell in the hands of these demons...
No!
l have to save Valkyrie...
Mighty god Odin...
Please guide this inexperienced woman...
l pray for the courage to overcome the ordeals...
Odin's voice keeps fading away as the days go by...
And again, the night has come...
lf l can escape from here, it would be much more comforting...
l shouldn't sound like a coward...
As the person in charge of the battle maidens, l am not allowed.
You're here.
Don't worry. This is your bedroom.
Provide us with your blessing tonight as well.
Get out of here already.
You people have defied god and his presence...
You are not allowed to be here.
Stop this!
l-l don't want to take part in this shameful act...
l still smell it.
Excrement from a shameful bitch.
No!
Don't!
l-l'm going to poop...
No...
Stop slurping my excrement...
Let me go...
l'll serve your cocks for the rest of my life...
Not my poop...
Please let me go...
Are you kidding me?
D-Don't come inside anymore! No!
l'll get pregnant!
l'll really get pregnant!
Soon, Valkyrie will fall apart...
Once she tastes that, she has no choice but to be their bitch.
lt's unbelievably tight...
D-Don't make it too tight... l don't like that feeling...
T-Take it out...
l-lt hurts!
Hot... So hot.
No!
No! lt's going wild...
Don't push that much...
lt's coming!
So hard... P-Pull it out...
So good... l just love how this feels...
lt's scraping inside...
No, don't tighten up!
l-l'll come!
Then take it out...
Stop moving! lt's painful and hot!
No, don't suck it up!
No!
N-Not that big!
l-l felt it coming inside...
God is going to hate me now...
l-lt feels so good...
Your pussy... lt's so good...
lt's so amazing...
There are many organisms in the Underworld, but this is the finest.
No!
N-No more!
Take it out!
lt burns...
Amazing...
F-Freiya...
lt's getting big...
Freiya, it stings...
B-Big...
V-Valkyrie?
l want a woman.
l want one...
Give me your pussy...
Why do l feel this way?
But l want it!
l want your pussy!
So dirty...
Your body is so dirty...
D-Don't say that...
Hot!
Yes! lt feels nice and creamy inside!
lt feels amazing...
So hard!
So big!
How rude.
This is a place where we purify our bodies before heading out to battle...
V-Valkyrie?
Valkyrie... Let me do you this time...
T-This can't be...
Freiya...
You're such a slut, Valkyrie...
l'll have to teach you how this huge things feels...
Yes, that's it...
Move!
Get your dirty hands away from Valkyrie!
l'll save you now, Valkyrie!
Now that your hindering tits are useful, you must be happy.
Unforgivable.
Doing such terrible things to the two known to be key to the Overworld.
Valkyrie! Let us flee!
S-Skuld?
Fight...
Yes, l'm a battle maiden...
My only enjoyment is for my masters to stimulate my pussy.
l'm going to serve those strong cocks for the rest of my life.
l-l'm just a sex slave for the cocks of these demons...
N-No!
l-l am...
Hurry up and grab the sword, Valkyrie.
S-Skuld!
V-Valkyrie!
S-Skuld...
F-Freiya...
l'm sorry, Skuld...
Please understand...
N-No!
We have no other choice...
There's no way to save you now...
No, no, no!
Don't do that!
No!
Even though she's a brat, it looks like you brought her up well.
She certainly looks good.
No!
No! Valkyrie is watching!
Don't let it out!
V-Valkyrie...
You had a demon inside you...
l-l'm using your ring as a source of life...
...since it can neutralize things with god's power.
That was handmade by Freiya.
Run away, Valkyrie.
You can't run.
Seems it likes the taste of a goddess's excrement.
What did you do to Skuld?
No!
There's no need to talk.
N-No!
That hole is dirty...
l'm inside a forest...
l can't help it...
God, for what shameful act your servant is about to do...
...please forgive me.
l hope no one can hear this...
D-Demon?
M-My power...
N-No!
No!
Don't come any closer!
Stop! No! No!
N-No!
N-No! Stop it!
Don't suck it up!
No!
No...
l-l have the urge to release it...
lt's going to suck it out!
l-lt's amazing...
l-l released tons of it...
lt feels good...
Yes... Yes...
Y-Yes... Yes!
Valkyrie!
No, stop it...
G-God will punish you...
My chastity belongs to god!
Don't worry. We'll start...
...with your ass.
Valkyrie...
Skuld...
lt hurts!
Stop moving!
No!
My ass will be torn!
lt's hot!
My stomach hurts!
N-No! Don't suck it up!
My ass...
lf you keep moving like that...
...m-my poop will come out!
No, not...
Not that!
P-Please! Stop moving!
No! Stop moving your cock!
l want it...
l want some pussy...
Please... Let me do your pussy...
Skuld...
Valkyrie?
No!
No! Look how excited l am.
Look how excited l am.
N-No!
No! Don't do it, Valkyrie!
lt hurts! You can't fit that hard thing in there!
No, Skuld...
That look makes me really hard...
Stay still! Otherwise, l'll have to violate you real bad!
lt hurts!
No, Valkyrie!
lt's hard, scraping inside me, and hot!
That slutty voice, youthful face, and dirty private area...
Don't tighten up too much!
No!
lt's hot! My pussy is burning!
Your pussy has been very tight...
...and it just won't let go of my cock!
Yes!
No!
Don't get too big!
Can you feel it, Skuld?
My cock is feeling good, and it's swishing in there...
So good... l'm happy...
lt feels better than Freiya's...
That's it. Make her pregnant!
That's right, Skuld...
You can make a woman pregnant with this...
No, Valkyrie!
Let me go!
l'll make you pregnant...
No! Don't do it!
No! l really mean it!
l'm having my period soon!
lf you release it inside...
l'm definitely going to come inside. l'm going to make you pregnant!
l want you to give birth to my child!
Pregnant! l'll get pregnant!
lf you get that excited, l'll make you pregnant in a heartbeat...
Don't release it that fast!
Don't get me pregnant!
l'll release that sticky, smelly stuff inside you!
l'm coming!
No, l'll get pregnant! Take it out already!
We'll stay like this till the egg fertilizes.
l'll keep releasing my semen into your pussy until you suck it all up.
My stomach is burning!
lf you give birth to a female child...
...let's all three of us get impregnated.