I shut the gate to the River of Wisdom that flows underground.
Yggsirad will wither and die in five days,
and the world will end along with it.
So the gold and silver keys that open the gate
are inside the wombs of the two valkyries.
The gold and silver keys are inside the wombs of Suvia and Sigurd.
No matter how much you defile my body,
my heart shall never be defiled.
As long as my heart stays pure, they'll never
be able to get the key to the Water Gate!
I'm a valkyne.
Even if my body becomes defiled, my heart will never give in.
Suvia, now I want to make you mine no matter what.
I'd like to taste you, a woman so fine and
courageous, to my hearts contempt,
and make both your heart and your body mine.
How do you like my cock, Suvia?
It's filthy!
Hurry up and pull it out!
You won't be able to say stuff like that in the near future.
Now I'm going to start moving the tentacles on my cock.
I like that voice!
You're making me even more excited!
How do you like Minmotta's tentacle-covered dick?
Something like this doesn't affect me at all!
"Something like this", she says.
All the valkyries we've raped said that in the
beginning, and turned crazy by the end.
I'm different from the other valkyries.
Don't look down on me!
"Look down?" Nope.
You're going to lick my cock.
Yeah, that's exactly right!
There's no way I'll lick something so filthy~
I like this. Her tongue is twitching.
Yeah.
The inside of her mouth is hot and tight.
I like this...
Loki!?
Loki's watching...
He looks so happy...
I... won't lose.
Inside Sigurd's womb lies the key to open the Water Gate,
which leads to the River of Wisdom that
waters the almost-withered World Tree.
Even if my body gets defiled and trampled on,
I won't let them de lie my heart!
Ikusa Otome Suvia
The Pleasure Trap
I found it!
Your sensitive place!
This is it. This is it, right!?
Stop!
That's~
No.
I'm not feeling pleasure...
I'm... not feeling pleasure...
Don't try to hide it!
Both your face and ears are red!
Her nipples are so hard now.
I think she's about to cum.
The great valkyrie is about to reach orgasm,
by being raped by beasts.
Shut up!
You shut up.
Yeah, yeah!
There!
This is great! My dick feels so good!
The root of her tongue keeps twitching, and it feels so good!
Her pussy feels great too!
It keeps eating my cock!
She just came!
The great valkyrie came because of my huge cock!
We're going to...
...give her our load, too!
Me too!
How does it feel to take in the cocks of
giants, to get raped, and to suffer?
I'll never hand you all my heart.
No matter how much you defile my body!
I see.
You're leaving Suvia's rape to the giants,
and just sitting back to watch?
Seems like you've got a lot of time to spare.
You know there's only three days until
Yggsirad dies and the world ends, right?
I've got a bit of a history with Suvia.
It would be boring to bring her down so easily.
I don't know what 'history' you have with her,
but what good will there be if the world ends?
And what about you?
Any progress with Sigurd?
I'm letting my goblin henchmen take care of her for now.
Well...
I guess it's time to bring the flesh modification to phase two.
Flesh modification?
You sure have evil taste.
Say what you want.
I even brought down the leader of the
valkyries, Freya. My skills are absolute.
I'll obtain the silver key for sure.
The last thing I want is the world ending because of your blunder.
Stupid giant.
I wonder if you'll be able to handle Sigurd.
The great valkyrie's tits are amazing!
The body that's been modified by Lord Flungluni is awesome!
Don't say that!
This one's mine!
This hole is fine too!
Stop it!
Pull it out! Now!
No way!
Besides, you're getting pleasure from it!
Your asshole is tightening too!
All of the great valkyrie's holes feel good!
Dammit!
This feels amazing!
What a perverted pussy.
Don't say it!
Sigurd-chan, your clitoris shrunk after Lord Flugluni enlarged it.
I wonder how sensitive it is.
N-No! Anything but that!
She came, she came!
The great valkyrie came because we caressed her!
We're going to cum too!
Awesome!
Give the great valkyrie all your cum!
Are you happy, eh, Sigurd-chan?
I won't lose.
I'll never lose.
I'm Sigurd, a valkyrie.
Father, Mother, and Fia...
Please give me strength...
And you too, Freya-sama...
That was back when I was still a human,
and worked in a small, rural town.
My parents were killed right in front of me.
My little sister, my good friends, and even the kind old couple were killed.
N-No!
It was Freya au Valkyrie that appeared when I was about to die.
Freya-sama is my lifesaver and also my swordmaster.
Even then...
Even then, Freya-sama is...
I won't forgive Flungluni!
So if you're not going to forgive me, then what?
Now, tell me what you're going to do.
I'm going to kill you!
That's impossible.
The reason behind that is because you're about
to get phase two of your flesh modification.
W-What!?
Now, Sigurd.
I'm going to equip you with something even
more lewd since you've been defiled today.
I'm going to give you an obscene meat hole that
could pack dozens of giant cocks at once.
What!? No way!
What is this!?
It's being widened... Something's being injected!
How does it feel to have liquids injected into your pussy again?
I won't forgive you, Flungluni!
What?
How unsightly.
Your vagina isn't even that of a human anymore.
Shut up!
Now, look at that.
Your G-spot is all puffed up now.
Now you're going to keep cumming every
time a cock is shoved in there.
No!
Without doing anything, I...
I'm going to cum!
You came because you were so touched?
What a perverted valkyrie.
So unsightly.
Shut up!
Spare me from further humiliation!
Whoa, hang on.
Your modification doesn't end here.
There's another hole we must widen.
It cant be...
Stop! Don't!
Stop!
Then I'll give you one chance.
It's a simple problem.
You should be able to solve it right away.
What is it!?
What is the name of this lewd hole that leaks
out these fluids, written in five letters?
What!?
Don't you know?
Want a hint?
It starts with a 'p' and ends with a 'y'.
Come on, say it, Sigurd.
Shout it ten times!
I refuse. Why should I...
Why should I say something so humiliating!?
You could have saved yourself from becoming even
more unsightly by saying a five-letter word.
You deserve what's coming, then.
Do it.
It's being opened up...
My butt is being opened up...
I can't explain this with a word other than 'unsightly', Sigurd.
You're forcing me to make even the depths of your ass perverted.
But this isn't it.
What!?
You said just one more!
This is a penalty.
No...
Don't tell me!
It's exactly what you're thinking.
I'm going to enlargen your clitoris again!
Stop! Don't!
Want me to tell you the specs of this
lecherous, lewd body of yours?
Your vagina is a thousand times more sensitive,
your ass is two thousand times more,
your clitoris is three thousand times more,
and the opening of your womb and your g-spot
ire twenty thousand times more sensitive!
Keep cumming,
and kneel down to me!
Bow down to me!
What is this feeling?
Th-This...
isn't even comparable to before...
B-But I won't lose...
I won't lose to pleasure.
Okay, looks like you're clean now.
I'm not going to thank you.
Since you're the one who sent me to those giants in the first place.
Yeah.
And?
How were the huge cocks of those giants?
Nothing in particular.
No matter how much you defile my
body, my heart will never change.
What you did was useless.
I wonder if that's true.
Seems like you've gotten more sensitive.
Achieving that alone makes it worth it that I sent you to the giants.
Humans can never resist the three desires:
Hunger, sleepiness, and lust.
I'm no human. I'm a valkyrie.
I wonder if that's true, Princess Pncencia.
Stop calling me that!
I'm Suvia the valkyrie!
Seems like your breasts have gotten larger
after having the giants fondle them.
They've gotten firmer, too.
I won't let you slap me twice.
As I thought, I want to keep her for myself.
If I'm able to tame this me and courageous
woman, and also obtain the key,
I'll teach her more and more about what it means to be a woman.
Suvia, after thinking about you,
look how big my cock has gotten.
Then do what you want.
Your thing is no different from those giants.
Just a lump of meat.
I wouldn't be so sure.
What are you~
Your breasts improved; I can't not use them.
How do you like my cock, Suvia?
Oh?
Suvia, have you begun to crave for my cock?
Who'd crave for something so filthy!?
No way...
This can't be true.
I'm... craving his cock?
Craving...
I'm... feeling pleasure from this man's cock?
I'm coming.
What?
It's supposed to be filthy...
I-I'm getting hot!
Your tits feel so good.
Filth!
That's right.
Good.
Your tits are getting used to my cock's heat.
You've started to get wet down there, Suvia.
Shut up...
I'm... feeling pleasure?
Now, make me feel even better.
What are you doing, Loki!?
Your mouth pussy.
How could I~
It smells...
A bitter liquid is coming out, and yet...
I can't stop...
So this cock...
is going to enter my vagina...
No!
What am I thinking?
I'm... wishing for it?
For Loki's... cock?
Now, I'm going to fill you up with my semen.
Open your mouth and take it all in!
N~
I'm being showered with hot liquid...
Hot... semen...
Loki's...
W-What are you doing!?
It's what a man and a woman do. You get it, right?
S-Stop!
Stop it...
Why?
Because you told me to stop.
Don't tell me a valkyrie like yourself wants to be raped?
You're wrong.
Don't be stupid.
What are you thinking, Loki?
Suvia was clearly wishing to be raped by you.
Wasn't that the greatest chance for you to bring her down?
If I had raped her now, her sexual desires would
be fulfilled, but her heart still wouldn't change.
Well, just watch.
I'll show you something fun tomorrow.
The problem lies within Flungluni, though.
I'm...
I'm cumming!
No!
It's digging in!
My stomach...
My organs are being raped!
Now, Sigurd,
become my slave!
Hand me the key to the Water Gate!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Dimmit!
Instead of continuing to orgasm, just answer my question!
Sigurd!
I'm telling you to answer me!