Have you decided to hand me the keys yet?
If you don't want to get raped even more,
say that you'll give me the key to the Water Gate.
What do you say, Sigurd?
Whit about you, Suvia?
I won't... give you the key...
I see.
Good. Perfect.
Tomorrow is the day the world will end.
And the greatest time in my life will also come tomorrow.
It'll really be fine, right?
What will be fine?
Why are you being so carefree?
If you don't obtain the two keys from their wombs by today,
the World Tree, Yggsirad, will wither.
Once Yggsirad withers, the world will fall apart.
Despite what you have to do,
make sure you have them deliver the two keys
to you out of their own will by today.
Hey, just watch.
I'm confident that I'll be able to take the valkyries down.
I am confident.
But the one I'm slightly worried about is Suvia.
However, a bet is no fun if I already know I'm going to win.
It's only called a 'bet' because there is a chance you might lose.
Besides, I feel like I wouldn't mind losing to Suvia.
Now, valkyries!
It's time for the final showdown against me!
Ikusa Otome Suvia
Enslaved Bride
Amazing!
My nipples are so sensitive!
Incredible!
I'm being raped!
Even my mouth is being raped!
More!
Rape me more!
Your suckers are sucking inside of me!
Freya-sama...
The person whom I admire has become so filthy...
But now, I understand.
Now that I've had my body modified and defiled...
Oh...
I long to be raped like Freya-sama...
Sigurd...
Are you unable to hold back?
I can't blame her. By being showed something like this continuously...
No!
I'm a valkyrie.
I won't forget that pride!
It feels so good!
But she looks like she's feeling so good...
No!
What am I thinking!?
Is this Loki's influence as well!?
Amazing!
My stomach is enlarging!
My organs are being raped!
Freya-sama...
My pussy... My clipenis... I want to touch it.
Sigurd...
My clipenis tastes so good...
Something is being done to my womb!
Even my stomach and my throat were raped...
I'm so happy...
Freya-sama...
Me too...
Sigurd...
But I can't blame her.
Even I...
No!
I can't do something like this!
But I can't stop!
Do you want to cum, Suvia?
Loki...
You look miserable, Vilkyrie Sigurd.
Why should I~
Do you want it?
My cock in your pussy?
If you tell me so, I'll shove it in right away.
No.
Suvia's watching me.
I see.
So you can't tell me to put it in because Suvia's here.
That's~
Looks like I'm right.
You've had your entire body modified.
Both our ass and your pussy are now
that of a pig, and you still have pride?
Suvia, it seems like Sigurd can't ask for cock because you're here.
Don't mock her!
We're both valkyries.
We won't lose no matter what you do!
Don't tell me you want my cock as well?
Shut up!
I won't forgive you for this humiliation.
I see.
Well, I apologize.
I don't want it...
I don't want his cock...
Whatever you do is futile!
He's probably planning on raping us, anyway...
I see.
So whatever I do is futile.
Then I'll do this.
Until the two of you beg and cry for it, I won't rape you two.
If you absolutely insist that you don't want cock, then that's fine.
There are only a few hours left until the world ends.
I guess you shall greet the coming of the apocalypse
while your desires are left unfulfilled.
N-No way...
I was expecting to be raped.
I was expecting a cock to be shoved up my pussy...
I'm not going to be raped?
His cock isn't going to be shoved up my pussy?
Y-You're just saying that. I bet you're planning on raping us anyway.
Nope, I won't.
I'm astounded b the stubborness of you two.
No! That's not fair!
If I just tell him to put it in now...
No.
I don t want to!
But... I want him to put it in...
His cock... into my pussy...
Farewell, brave valkyries.
No way!
Loki, don't go!
I want cock...
Why didn't I just stop Loki?
Suvia, Sigurd, you mustn't hand over the keys
hidden in your wombs to the demons.
In order to protect those you love.
"Those you love"?
People like that don't exist.
Only fools who'd betray those who
protected them just to get ahead.
That's right, Odin-sama.
We were disgraced by the humans!
Must we still protect them even after that!?
No...
Suvia...
I want it!
I want cock!
I don't care about the key!
Stick one in!
Stick a cock in my pussy!
Me too...
Loki, please come back...
And rape...
Loki!
He came back!
You two were left stranded without even being able to masturbate.
You must be feeling irritated.
Just throw away your pride.
Tell me honestly that you want cock.
Please, stick it in!
Your cock into my pussy!
Sigurd...
Sigurd has fallen.
That's not the correct way to ask things.
I don't even want your loose pussy that was modified by Flungluni.
N-No!
But if you cry and beg, I may reconsider.
Try it.
Please stick your grand cock into my wild, modified, loose vagina!
I want it!
Even my clitoris!
I want to cum after having a cock inside me!
Then Sigurd, you'll give me the key to the water gate?
I don't care about the key!
So, please! Put your cock in me!
Sigurd...
Very well, Sigurd. I'll rape you.
It's sliding in!
So big!
Amazing!
It's hot, stiff, and it's sliding around inside me!
So, do you enjoy being raped?
Yes!
This feels so good!
Whose what feels good?
Cock!
Your cock is grinding around in my pussy!
No...
That cock is mine...
It's going in...
Loki's cock is inside Sigurd's pussy...
Incredible...
It's poking at my uterus!
Poke it more!
Grind inside my pussy harder!
How is it, Sigurd? Does it feel good?
Yes!
Please, poke at my uterus!
Jam your cock in it!
Why?
I can't cum hard unless you poke at my uterus
because of Flungluni's modifications!
I see.
How many times is your uterus more sensitive now?
T-Twenty thousand times.
I see.
So that means you haven't been able to experience your
greatest orgasm despite being raped countless times.
Yes.
Please, make me cum.
Make me cum hard in my uterus!
W-Why?
Sigurd, that's not the right way to ask things.
You're a pig, so beg like one!
Loki-sama!
P-Please.
Slide your cock in and out of this pig's pussy!
And please, give me the greatest orgasm with this pig's uterus!
I like your honesty, Sigurd.
This is it...
It's right at my uterus, and it feels so good...
It's poking at it... Your penis is poking at my uterus...
Loki-sama, your penis is wonderful!
I'm cumming, Sigurd!
I'm going to inject you with my cum.
So much cum that the key will flow out!
Please do!
Inject all your cum into this pig's pussy!
I don't even care about the key! Just make me pregnant!
Armzing...
This is it...
This is amazing...
I'm cumming...
No way...
I want it...
I want it in my pussy too...
Incredible... My pussy is being injected with semen...
How was it?
Did it feel good?
Yes.
I'm so blessed...
No way... Sigurd...
What's the matter, Suvia?
If you just tell me so, I'll shove this cock right into your pussy too.
You came really hard, Sigurd.
Yes, I did.
I was able to experience orgasm thanks to you.
Then do you mind giving me the key?
Okay.
Oh my gosh...
The key... it's coming out!
I can feel it pressing against my cock.
Now, push!
Amazing...
I...
Sigurd...
My turn...
Finally...
Looks like you re really wet.
Don't you want me to rape you?
Tell me the truth.
Who would...
I want his cock!
I want it!
Don't you want me to put it in?
Don't you want me to make you feel better?
Now, say it.
Beg me to put my cock inside your pussy.
It's obvious you want it.
Thit's...
That's...
Now, Suvia.
Tell me whether or not you wish to be raped.
Do as you please.
As I please?
Rape me if you want.
No!
I want you to rape me...
Shove your cock in me and stir up my insides!
I've told you I'm indifferent.
But...
I want it... His cock... in my pussy...
Rape me!
Nope.
That's not good enough.
Rape me.
Please, rape me!
Then will you give me the key to the Water Gate in exchange?
You mustn't, Suvia!
Anything but that!
Yes, I will!
And what do you want me to do?
Please... haven't you tormented me enough?
No.
I want it now!
I can't hold it back anymore!
Put it in me!
Please, put your cock in my pussy!
Whose cock into whose pussy?
Yours into mine! Please!
I finally did it!
I took Suvia the Valkyrie's heart!
Very well, Suvia. I will.
I'll rape your pussy with my cock.
Now, put it in yourself.
Okay...
Amazing...
What's amazing?
It's in...
Your cock...
Does it feel good?
Yes...
Yes, it does...
You've started to move your hips, Suvia.
You perverted bitch.
That's because... my pussy...
...feels like it's about to melt...
Feel more pleasure.
Incredible!
My pussy feels so good!
It's moving...
Your cock is moving inside my pussy!
That's right, feel pleasure!
Amazing...
Having my clit rubbed while being fucked feels amazing!
That feels so good...
Did you cum?
Yes, I did.
Who gave you permission to do that?
But...
Ask me for permission before you cum.
Got it?
Okay, I will.
I will.
That's a good girl.
I'm going to cum!
Hold it in. You came just a moment ago.
But my pussy feels too good...
I'm going to cum again!
Nope, don't cum yet.
But...
What's wrong?
Aren't you a trained valkyrie?
You should be able to endure this.
No!
Please, let me cum!
Not yet.
Can you feel it? The opening of your womb has gotten looser.
The key to the gate is right there.
I'm going crazy!
No!
Suffer in anguish!
I'm really going to go crazy!
Okay, I'm almost at my limit as well.
Cum when I ejaculate, got it?
I'm allowed to cum?
Loki, I'm allowed to cum?
Yes, now become pregnant with my child!
Yes, inject me with your semen!
I'm being injected...
Semen is flowing into me while I'm cumming...
I-I can't think straight...
Now do you understand what it means to be a woman, Suvia?
First-hind.
Now you belong to me.
Now for the deal.
Give me the key.
Okay.
You're beautiful, Suvia.
I'm being watched...
While pushing it out...
That s right, I'm watching you.
It's coming out!
I'm pushing it out!
Loki, is this what you wanted?
Precisely.
Looks like you won.
I guess you could say that.
Loki, hey...
Yes?
Rape me...
Please, fuck me some more...
I could, but I'm going to need you to repeat the following:
"Rape this pigs puss with your cock."
Okay...
Rape this pig's pussy with your cock...
I win.
And just like that, the world became property of the demons.
Hell, the king of the underworld, established a
government with the giants, and took over the world.
However, none of that was important to me.
I obtained something even more precious.
Your cock tastes so good...
Sigurd, your clitoris is so big too.
I'm going to bite it.
That feels so good...
What? Suvia bit your clitoris?
I'll have to punish her for that.
Y-You're going to make me cum!
If you don't want me to make you cum, make Sigurd cum first.
Okay, got it.
Loki-sama, no!
Then I'll...
Sigurd, try to make me cum then.
And I'll make Suvia cum.
Suvia, that part feels so good...
Loki-sama, your tongue is rubbing against my G-spot!
You've gotten better at using your tongue, Sigurd.
I'm going to cum!
I'm at my limit!
I'm cumming. Both of you, too!
Armzing...
My pussy is being fucked...
Your clipenis feels like a real cock, Sigurd.
My pussy feels too good...
But that...
Makes me feel so good...
I'm cumming...
Your clipenis is digging in so deep!
Okay, I'm going to cum.
I want both of you to enjoy it.
Whit a waste of Loki-sama's seedlings!
It smells bad, but tastes so good!
I don't like using magic or tools, but something
like this is fine every once in a while.
Loki-sama, that looks so majestic...
You're going to rape us at the same time? I'm honored.
Amazing...
My puss feels so good...
I'm being raped together with Sigurd. I'm so happy!
It's rubbing against it...
Against my weak spot...
I can feel our movements too, Suvia!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Me too!
I-I'm cumming!
It's all over.