They turned their backs against the gods
They stood up, not to be overrun
by everything that they created
The one who can defeat us
She is an apostle of god, with the power of the great Odin
Battle Maiden Valkyrie
Licensed by Lune
But if she falls into our hands
her innocent heart, no different than others her age
with a body that is clean, with no sign of impurity
will be rewarded with hostility
Freiya...
Why?
The Overworld's symbol who guides many battle maidens...
...the goddess Freiya.
Valkyrie... l'm sorry.
She's known as the Overworld's greatest beauty.
And even this slutty body is now...
Don't touch her with your dirty hands!
lt's all right, Valkyrie.
l-l am their sex slave.
lf they're satisfied by doing whatever they want with me...
...then l'm pleased as well.
S-Sex slave?
Even battle maidens become regular women without the rings.
Then...
S-Stop!
Here's the man you've been waiting for.
S-Stop that. lt's dirty.
She obviously doesn't know how wonderful our cocks are.
lf we stick them deep inside her and keep releasing our stuff in her hole...
Release their stuff? lnside my hole?
You see, l keep thinking about cocks when l'm both awake and asleep.
My master sacrificed sleep to satisfy my pussy...
...and l understood the joy of being a woman.
G-Get a hold of yourself, Freiya!
Our joy as goddesses is to receive Odin's blessing...
Odin...
He didn't satisfy my pussy.
l'm not offering my body to a god or a devil.
P-Please stop, Freiya!
l just want this hard cock.
N-No!
Don't touch me!
l'll take this off and stick it inside you as well!
lt won't come off.
A battle maiden's chastity is protected by divine powers.
No!
lt kind of smells bad for a maiden.
H-How dare you. Stop saying vulgar things!
You've never felt pain like this, have you?
That's because you've been protected by a fake god all this time.
Fresh ones are always the best.
No!
My god... Odin...
Please help me...
l'll train you real good.
You can go suck Odin's cock.
Stop it! No!
W-What are you doing?
Well, well.
Was that your first kiss?
What? All of a sudden...
These fine bitches sure scream nice!
B-Bitch...
No, l'm a battle maiden...
Odin...
Forgive me...
M-My insides...
...are getting sliced up!
She's really tightening up.
N-No matter how much you do this, it's useless!
Do all the goddesses have nice pussies like you?
l will never give in!
l-l won't lose!
No matter how much you violate me...
...you can't take away my heart.
You can't violate it.
You've got a nice pair of tits.
They must've been useless in battle.
l-l won't take this kind of insult!
lt's not an insult.
S-Stop it!
No!
You won't find that many bitches with bodies like this in the Overworld.
Here's one of them.
Right?
No!
You've got that indecent look on your face.
l-l'm just feeling uncomfortable.
Then you want me to release my load inside?
lnside?
l won't let you...
Stop this!
No!
This kind of dirty act...
...should not be...
...allowed!
l'll make you dirty with my semen!
Stop that!
Anything but that!
Don't release it inside!
l-l'll get pregnant!
No! Don't!
Not...
Not inside!
l felt something inside.
l felt something hot!
lt keeps coming inside!
No! No!
l'm sorry, Odin...
Give birth to a healthy child.
Give birth? Child?
lf it's a girl, then we'll take turns violating her!
l won't lose.
l'm sure that my comrades will come...
...to save me.
l just have to wait!
Hey.
Your comrades...
ls she one of them?
S-Skuld!
Freiya is the one who is in charge of the Overworld.
She can tell where the goddesses are...
...and what they're doing right now.
Even though the battle maidens are invincible in battle...
...as long as they live like regular humans...
...there will be times when they're defenseless.
l want that mouth to do sucky-sucky on my cock.
N-No, not Skuld...
Don't lay your hands on Skuld...
Then you'll have to participate in our show tomorrow.
What do you say? Yes, right?
Looks like we'll have to carve a symbol of a slave on to your body.
D-Don't come any closer.
We have plenty of time till the morning.
Valkyrie?
So big...
You're going to destroy me...
l-l don't like this kind of position.
Please stop!
Stop it!
lnside...
Give it to me inside.
Don't release it.
Don't release it inside anymore!
God... l...
What happened to your earlier high spirits?
You're overwhelmed by my cock's greatness?
No! Stop it!
l-lt's going deep inside.
Looks like you're becoming familiar with how a man feels.
T-That's not true!
Let me go!
You're going to destroy me!
Destroy me!
lt's coming!
You're going to come inside me again.
W-What is this feeling?
l'm scared!
lf they keep coming inside me like this, l really will get pregnant!
Get on all fours and stick your ass out.
Mercy...
Do you people have no mercy?
Mercy?
Something's in my ass!
l do get tired of banging your pussy all the time!
lt's impossible!
l don't want any pain!
lt's nice and tight.
l-lt hurts!
Please take it out!
You'll feel a little better if you relax.
lt hurts...
Stop moving...
Your entire fat cock is going inside.
My ass... My ass...
No... Let me go...
No!
l found her!
She was hiding.
l beg you! Don't touch my daughters!
l'll do anything you want!
No!
Alphocine! Laura!
Hold it.
Forget about them and just enjoy the show.
No! Mother!
No! Stop it!
Watch your daughters become women!
Take it out!
No!
Stop it. Don't torture them like this.
Please don't.
Looks like she grew up to be a real slut.
That's because they were sucking on things like these!
My milk is much more nutritious.
No, it stinks.
Come on.
Come on. You have to drink it all up.
Otherwise, you won't be like the other girls.
lt's the battle maiden.
Valkyrie!
Your one and only hope, the battle maiden Valkyrie is no more!
The maiden who lost the purity sworn to her god...
...no longer has the power to fight us.
There's no one left to save you now.
Since you people were lucky enough to survive...
...we're going to show you our great utopia.
Consider this a dying gift.
Now, do exactly what l told you to before.
l-l can't do it!
You want me to tell them about everything that took place last night?
l can tell them about the nasty things you said while you kept moaning.
l'm a sex slave for the cocks of these demons...
My only enjoyment is for them to stimulate my pussy...
l'm going to serve those strong cocks for the rest of my life.
That was forced!
Never mind that.
Let's just go and capture Skuld so that we can humiliate her.
Skuld?
What should we do to her?
Should we make her pee?
No, maybe we should give her an enema...
...and show her excreting to the entire public.
l'm guessing she'll be crying out loud with a cute voice.
No!
l will...
l'll do it...
Don't hurt Skuld...
Take a look! ln our new world, there are no goddesses or queens!
Women are treated like livestock!
They're all sex slaves!
They'll just live for satisfying men!
The battle maiden...
She took in everything from that demon...
Not just in her mouth.
Her master and the others released their loads many times in her pussy.
She's just like those women.
Our job is to create new offspring...
...who will become future livestock for these masters in the new world.
lt will not be long before the humans are gone.
So we must create new life for the future.
This is your last chance.
lf you can impregnate the battle maiden...
...l'll let you live to be one of the livestock!
S-Stop this!
l won't let you do this!
You may be bluffing, even with this thing on...
...but it's over, Valkyrie.
Please give birth to a healthy child.
Get a hold of yourself.
Your pride as a human...
No! You came inside!
l'll get pregnant!
Move! lt's my turn now!