Stop!
Pull it out! Now!
N-No! Anything but that!
No!
Even without doing anything, I...
I'm cumming!
I-It's hot.
Your tits feel so good.
Seems like you've started getting wet down there.
Shut up.
This cock...
I'm cumming!
I'm... cumming!
Answer me!
Well, just watch.
I'll show you something entertaining tomorrow.
The problem lies within Flungluni, however.
This is my first time seeing you.
I am the king of the underworld, Hell.
Hell?
I've heard of you.
You're the great king of the underworld whose
authority rivals that of Odin-samas.
But I guess the things you do are on par with Loki and Flungluni.
Precisely.
A great valkyrie transformed into an
ordinary woman thanks to Loki.
Wrong!
I'm a valkyrie, not a woman!
I wouldn't be so sure.
How does it feel to be on the stairway of pleasure to Heaven?
This has no effect on me...
Your body is moistening.
This is... nothing!
I see.
Then what about this?
Th~
This is...
Followed by...
This...
...is nothing!
Now, cum, Suvia!
Transform from a valkyrie to an ordinary woman!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!!
A dream?
How obscene...
I was masturbating?
Am I not getting enough?
W-What are you doing!?
It's what a man and a woman do together. You get it, right?
S-Stop it!
Stop!
Stop...
Why?
Because you told me to stop.
Don't tell me a valkyrie like yourself wants to be raped?
You're wrong.
Don't be stupid.
I'm a valkyrie.
I have a duty to protect the people of this, world.
Despite that...
Flungluni ran away?
Yes.
Seems like he already has his mind set that the world will end.
He was panicking about the fact that
he couldn't conquer Sigurd, after all.
Now, Sigurd, become my slave!
Hand me the key to the Water Gate!
Instead of continuing to orgasm, answer me, Sigurd!
Sigurd!
I'm ordering you to answer me!
What an idiot.
Sigurd is almost at her limits.
Flungluni had the right approach.
Perfect.
I guess I'll bring Sigurd along for today's event.
Bring her?
Where are you planning to go!?
Don't tell me you're planning on escaping as well?
There are only two days left until Yggsirad,
the World Tree, withers.
If I don't have Sigurd and Suvia willingly remove
the kevs from their wombs within two days,
it'll all be the same no matter where I escape to.
Ikusa Otome Suvia
Gang Rape of Despair
Where are you taking me?
My nostalgic home.
That's...
That's right.
It's the city you and Freya protected until the very end.
And now that the valkyries have vanished, despair rules the city.
Your hearts will soon be filled with despair as well.
Now, everyone!
I'll show you guys something nice today.
The last dance before the world ends!
S-Suvia-sima!
N-No way, that Suvia-sama is...
How unsightly.
Your vagina and your breasts are showing.
If you want to look, look.
I see.
Well, whatever.
Now, all of you!
As you all know, this valkyrie, Suvia, has betrayed all of you!
She lent Flungluni a hand and lead the
annihilation of the godly forces!
Whit?
Traitor!
Fiend!
Shameless bitch!
People really become foolish in crowds.
Without confirming the truth, they become easily manipulated.
Everyone!
This treacherous valkyrie says that she plans
to do anything to clear her name!
What is... this?
The party has begun!
I deserve all the glares I'm getting.
But I did all of that to save you all.
I'll at least protect the golden key to
the Water Gate located in my womb.
I wonder how long our heart will stay strong for.
Depending on your act, we may save your life
if we deem that you've redeemed yourself.
Oh, but you will.
Wh~
What!?
My hands are...
Look!
The treacherous valkyrie, Suvia, is feeling
pleasure due to you all watching her!
She's feeling pleasure because people are watching?
Is the traitor an exhibitionist!?
You shameless bitch!
To hell with your title of War Maiden!
No...
This isn't what I want!
Please, look!
Watch the traitor's pussy open up!
No!
My pussy!
I'm a pig that feels pleasure from rubbing
my pussy in front of the crowd!
What is this?
How could I be saying something like this?
This ring...
So, he's controlling my speech and my movements through this ring.
Watch!
Look, my pussy is making noises...
Look...
My clitoris too...
No, I can't...
Look!
My clitoris is erect!
It's all hard because you're looking at it!
Suvia is amazing!
Isn't she embarrassed from masturbating in front of us?
You whore!
No...
No, I'm...
I'm being raped by myself...
My...
My pussy feels so good...
Are you watching?
Are you watching my pussy twitch?
I'm not even thinking about anything like that...
So, Suvia,
how does it feel to masturbate in-front of a crowd?
It must fulfill your desires.
Stop fucking around!
Yes.
I, the traitor, get excited from having them watch me!
You pig! Cry!
That's right!
Do it, Suvia!
Cry, pig!
Cry!
Suvia, they want you to cry like a pig.
What do you say?
No! I refuse!
Everyone gathered here,
I, Suvia, a treacherous vilkyrie,
am a whore who gets pleasure after touching her own pussy!
Stop... Stop right there...
I'm a pig!
With a wet pussy!
No!
No...
I'm feeling it...
My pussy...
She really did it!
Isn't she ashamed?
Pig!
What an embarrassing cry...
No, this isn't right!
I'm...
No, I can't stop!
Hey, is everyone watching?
Is everyone watching my perverted puss ?
My pussy juice is drooling out...
You really are perverted, Suvia.
What...?
Look, the rings are out of magic power.
No way, then that means...
No way!
But no,
I... I can't stop!
N-No!
She came! That traitor!
You lecher!
You deserve to go to the hell of lechers!
I...
I really masturbated in front of them?
I came in front of the people?
No...
If I keep touching myself, I won't be able to go back!
Valkyrie, drowned in .sexual desires,
rejoice.
The humans you loved have prepared a feast for you.
W-Whit?
They're virgins I gathered to have their dicks sucked by you.
What did you say?
Additionally, they've got erections because
of a certain medicine I gave them.
If you don't take some of their sperm for them,
their testicles will burst, resulting in death.
You coward!
Say what you want.
Eveuvone!
Now, we shall punish the traitor!
Guys, have Suvia give you the time of your life.
I need to suck out their sperm...
So thick...
Hot...
Watch out, Suvia.
Because of the medicine, all the have in mind is to cum.
No...
Too strong...
This is too much...
I can't even think...
She's feeling pleasure from sucking on cocks!
That's right, pig!
Be ashamed, pig!
No...
This isn't what I want...
I'm doing this just to save them...
Despite that...
Cocks taste so good...
And... And this...
This is just an act.
I don't actually want it.
But it's not!
Cocks taste so good!
Please! Someone put their cock into my pussy!
Seems like Valkyrie Suvia's body is stained by sex now.
No! That was...
I put a spell on the men so that they can't even touch your vagina.
She just said the word pussy!
She wants to be raped!
Move! I'll rape her, then!
It would be unfair for Suvia to be the only one getting pleasure.
I'll call her comrade over.
Comrade?
No...
It can't be...
Sigurd...
What are you, a slug!?
No, no, that's a cow.
A pig and a cow? Great!
Sigurd...
Are you happy to see her after such a long time?
What the hell did you do to her!?
Well, basically what I did to you.
Actually, she went through much worse.
How terrible...
Suvia...
Sigurd, what about the key?
It's fine...
I won't give it to them.
I see. I knew I could trust you.
This is all my fault...
I'm sorry, Sigurd.
Everyone!
In order to clear her name, Sigurd
agreed to have her body modified,
and now she s the biggest whore in the underworld!
How awful!
Now, everyone,
the actors are all here.
It is time to engrave the valkyries with the seal of a servant!
These men are heroes who stood up to the plate.
Now, show the traitors justice!
Stop it!
What's wrong, Sigurd?
Your pussy is all wet!
That's...
Sigurd!
Hey, shouldn't you be worrying about yourself?
She's real wet, too.
She's happy about being raped in front of a crowd!
You're wrong!
Stop it!
Stop...
Stop!
Not there!
No!
Don't put it in!
Cock...
No, I can't say such a thing...
Sigurd...
You're already...
Suvia...
I'm sorry...
...already...
It feels...
It feels good!
What feels good? Tell us!
No! I can't!
Your puss , right?
Just say it!
I can't say such a thing in front of Suvia!
If you don't, then I'll do this!
I'm cumming!
No!
I'm going to cum!
I won't let you cum so easily.
No...
Don't stop...
I cant cum!
So, what feels good?
If you want to cum, tell us.
Th-That's...
In that case, I'll pull this thing out.
No.
Don't pull your cock out!
Then enlighten us.
Which part of your body feels good?
My pussy.
My pussy... my pussy...
My pussy feels good!
It's going to make me cum!
Well said.
This is your reward!
This hole too.
Armzing...
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming.
I'm going to keep cumming!
You're not even a valkyrie anymore.
Sigurd...
No...
Don't look, Suvia...
Sinurd...
It's fine...
Why don't we have fun too, Suvia-chanf?
No...
But I...
Amazing!
Your cock...
You're going to put all your strength into rubbing
my cock with this tiny hand, right?
That feels good...
Your cold hand feels great wrapped around my hot cock...
This...
No!
I'm cumming!
Incredible!
Sigurd!
Come on, don't you feel good too?
Raise your voice like Sigurd!
No!
How stubborn!
This turns me on!
You just came, Suvia.
How lewd.
S-Shut up!
Her expression is the same even after she came.
Don't act tough.
Come on! Keep feeling good!
No!
Don't rub that!
I'm going to go crazy! No!
This is too amazing.
You perverted pigs!
You shameless sluts!
So, how does it feel to be raped by
those you were trying to protect?
No...
These aren't the people I was trying to protect!
Are ou sure?
It's almost time, men.
Okay, I'm going to cum.
I'll give you all my semen!
No!
Don't cum!
I'm going to drown!
Good! Then drown!
I'm about to cum, too!
Okay, Suvia.
I'm going to fill your pussy up with cum!
Stop it!
You beast!
Exactly.
What you two were trying to protect are nothing more than beasts.
Amazing!
I-I won't forgive you!
Have you decided to hand me the keys yet?
If you don't want to get raped even more, say
that you'll give me the key to the Water Gate.
What do you say, Sigurd?
What about you, Suvia?
I won't... give you the key...
I see.
Good. Perfect.
Tomorrow is the day the world will end.
And the greatest time in my life will also come tomorrow.