ONII-CHAN.
YES,
I'M READY.
TAKE ME, ONII-CHAN.
I AM ABOUT
TO BE PENETRATED BY MY BROTHER.
DOES IT HURT?
DON'T HESITATE. YOU CAN GO DEEPER IF YOU'D LIKE.
ALTHOUGH OUR RELATIONSHIP IS TABOO,
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I LIKE TO PLEASE HIM.
IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME TO DEEPEN OUR SEXUAL LIFE.
ONII-CHAN...
I LOVE MY BROTHER MORE THAN ANYTHING THE WORLD.
YAYOI-CHAN, DO YOU GET ALONG WITH YOUR BROTHER?
YES.
WHEN WE GET OLD, WE'LL GET MARRIED TOGETHER.
WE'LL LIVE HAPPILY TOGETHER.
HAS NO ONE TOLD YOU?
A BROTHER AND SISTER CAN NOT MARRY.
EH?
THAT DAY,
TALKING TO MY CHILDHOOD FRIEND,
I REALIZED THAT MY GREATEST WISH
COULD ONLY BE A DREAM.
BUT HAVING MY SWEET LOVING BROTHER
BY MY SIDE BRINGS ME JOY.
O-ONII-CHAN!
YAYOI!
ONII-CHAN!
YOU'RE GOING BACK TO SCHOOL, RIGHT?
STUDYING IS IMPORTANT.
ESPECIALLY TO TAKE CARE OF YOU LATER.
AT LEAST WE CAN BE TOGETHER.
ONII-CHAN,
KISSING YOU ISN'T ENOUGH TO CALM ME DOWN.
YOU'RE HARD AGAIN.
AND HOT TO THE TOUCH.
DOES IT FEEL GOOD WHEN I CARES YOU?
DO NOT HESITATE.
YA... YAYOI.
CARESS ME.
YOU'RE SOAKED.
YOU HAD AN ORGASM.
BUT NOT YOU.
IT DOESN'T MATTES.
LET ME DO IT.
YA... YAYOI.
I'LL GIVE YOU MORE PLEASURE.
YAYOI!
DOES IT FEEL GOOD?
BIG BROTHER, I LOVE YOU.
I WANT TO FEEL YOU INSIDE ME.
YAYOI,
I CAN'T.
WE'RE RE...
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
BUT STILL, I AM A GIRL LIKE NO OTHER.
LET'S STAY TOGETHER FOREVER.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO ANYWHERE.
OKAY.
I HAVE TO GO BACK THOUGH.
WE CAN STAY A LITTLE LONGER.
BUT IF I DON'T GO BACK
THE OTHERS WILL LOOK FOR ME AROUND THE SCHOOL.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT THE OTHERS TO FIND OUT.
THEY'LL COME SOON.
OKAY.
TO ME NOTHING MATTERS, AS LONG AS HE BECOMES MY HUSBAND ONE DAY.
NOT EVEN SEX.
TO BE AT HIS SIDE IS ENOUGH TO FILL ME WITH HAPPINESS.
SO,
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS TO US IS LIKE
A DREAM THAT HAS FINALLY COME TRUE.
I HOPE IT WILL NOT BE LONG.
IS SOMEONE THERE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, TAKATSUKI?
CLASS RESUMED.
OH! E-EXCUSE ME!
IT DOESN'T HURT?
NO, GO DEEPER!
YOU CAN SEE EVERYTHING IN DETAIL
WITH THESE VIDEOS IN HD.
WHAT IS...
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL RELATIONSHIP YOU TWO HAVE.
I'D LOVE TO TAKE HIS PLACE.
THAT'S BLACKMAIL!
IT'S NOT WORSE THAN SLEEPING WITH A FAMILY MEMBER.
YOU'LL BE THE ONE AFFECTED THE MOST IF ANYONE FINDS OUT.
I COULD DENOUNCE YOU.
UP TO YOU.
I DON'T CARE.
YOU SAW HIM,
I ONLY BELONG TO MY BIG BROTHER.
I'D NEVER ACCEPT TO BE WITH A PERVERTED TEACHER LIKE YOU!
I WONDER WHAT THEY'D DO TO HIM...
YOU WOULDN'T WANT THAT HMM?
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS ELSEWHERE.
WHAT'S WRONG. TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES!
BIG BROTHER, SAVE ME!
YOUR LOVABLE BIG BROTHER IS TOAST IF YOU DON'T OBEY.
OH HOW BORING ARE THOSE PANTIES.
YOUR BROTHER DOESN'T HAVE ANY LUCK.
SHUT UP!
MY BROTHER ISN'T A SEXUAL DEVIANT LIKE YOU!
TAKE IT ALL OFF.
ONLY MY BROTHER IS SUPPOSED TO SEE ME NAKED.
NOT A DISGUSTING OLD MAN LIKE THIS.
MUST ADMIT THAT YOU ARE DAMN GOOD FOR A KID.
I WANT TO RUN AWAY...
STOP HIDING.
BUT... MY BROTHER'S FUTURE IS AT STAKE.
I'LL HAVE TO DO IT FOR HIM.
SHOW THEM TO ME!
EVEN FOR A KID.
YOU HAVE LOVELY PINK NIPPLES.
DO NOT MAKE THAT FACE.
THE FUN PART WILL BEGIN.
IS THIS THE FIRST TIME YOU SEE SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
WHAT IS THIS THING?
IT'S NOTHING LIKE MY BROTHER'S!
I'M GONNA VOMIT.
START LICKING IT!
IT STINKS!
TAKE IT IN YOUR MOUTH.
HE'S FEELING ME WITH HIS DISGUSTING FOOT!
THE STENCH IS UNBEARABLE!
IT'LL BE TIME TO SWALLOW, YAYOI.
HE'S GOING TO CUM IN MY MOUTH!?
NO! I REFUSE TO SWALLOW HIS SEED!
GET READY!
NO!
REMEMBER THE TASTE OF MY CUM AND SAVOR IT.
THE WAY HE FEELS UP MY BODY
INFURIATES ME IN SO MANY LEVELS!
YOUR MOANS ARE ADORABLE.
I DO NOT WANT TO,
SO WHY?
NO WAY!
IF YOU WANT TO PLAY.
LOOK AT ALL THESE JUICES FLOWING BETWEEN YOUR THIGHS!
IT'S NOT FOR YOU TO LICK THEM!
IS IT FOR YOUR BELOVED BROTHER?
THAT'S CUTE...
YOU COULD NEVER MAKE ME FEEL AS GOOD AS HE CAN!
YOU WANNA BET?
EXCUSE ME?
LET ME FUCK YOU, AND I'LL ERASE THE VIDEO.
EXCEPT THAT IF YOU DO ENJOY ME FUCKING YOU,
I HAVE THE RIGHT TO DO IT IN YOUR PUSSY.
I'LL NEVER LOSE TO A PIG LIKE YOU!
MY FEELINGS ARE STRONGER THAN EVERYTHING ELSE.
WE'LL SEE.
THAT BASTARD CAN SEE MY ANUS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
THE SIZE OF HIS THING IS SO DIFFERENT.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO PENETRATE ME.
IS IT GOOD?
YOUR ANUS IS HOLDING ME TIGHT.
YOU CAN TRY,
BUT YOU CAN'T EVEN REACH HIS ANKLE.
WHAT A STANDARD!
HIS HUGE DICK WILL DEFORM MY ANUS!
STOP PUSHING.
THIS DOESN'T FEEL LIKE THE USUAL.
PLEASE STOP!
M-MY ANUS WILL DEFORM.
IF HE KEEPS GOING LIKE THIS.
NO!
SAVE ME, ONII-CHAN!
MY ANUS CAN'T STAND IT ANY LONGER!
CUM QUICKLY SO I CAN GET OUT OF THIS HORRIBLE SITUATION!
LOOKS LIKE I'M GOING TO WIN THE CHALLENGE.
I FEEL NO PLEASURE FROM YOU FUCKING ME.
JUST STOP TRYING!
SO STUBBORN.
I'LL TRY ANOTHER APPROACH.
WHY DID HE STOP?
I WAS ABOUT TO HAVE AN ORGASM
AT THE TIME I WANTED TO HAVE FUN WITH HIM.
HURRY UP AND ENTER ME.
HOW COULD I REFUSE WHEN YOU'RE ASKING SO NICELY?
WHO ASKED GENTI...
IS THAT ME IN THE REFLECTION?
YOUR COCK WILL DISTORT MY ASS FOREVER.
HURRY UP AND CUM!
OTHERWISE I'LL END UP...
I CAN FEEL YOUR PENIS DIRECTLY.
THE CONDOM WAS TOO SMALL FOR ME.
IT TORE.
NO!
GET YOUR PENIS OUT OF THERE!
DOES THAT FEEL BETTER?
IT DOESN'T!
IT THIS BAD!
I'M GOING TO FILL YOUR RECTUM!
NO, ANYTHING BUT THAT!
STOP GOING SO DEEP!
NO, I CAN FEEL AN ORGASM BUILDING WITHIN ME.
PLEASE, STOP BEFORE I ORGASM!
ALL YOUR HOT LIQUID IS IN MY ANUS!
IT'S FINALLY OVER.
MY BROTHER AND I CAN FINALLY BE TOGETHER.
ONII-CHAN.
TIME TO DO YOU IN THE OTHER HOLE.
NO WAY! I REFUSE!
WE MADE AN AGREEMENT.
YOU PROMISED YOU WOULD MET ME IF I WON.
EXACTLY,
YOU ORGASMED BEFORE I CAME.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I DEFLOWER A GIRL
YOUR AGE, SO I APOLOGIZES IN ADVANCE.
TO THINK THAT MY VIRGINITY WAS RESERVED FOR MY BROTHER.
AND OF ALL MEN IN THE WORLD,
I END UP WITH HIM.
FORGIVE ME, ONII-CHAN,
MY VIRGINITY WAS JUST STOLEN BY THIS MONSTER.
OUCH...
IT HURTS!
NO!
WHOOPS, I ALREADY CAME WHILE WEARING A CONDOM.
WHAT A RELIEF
TO KNOW THAT HE DIDN'T CUM INSIDE ME.
BRING THAT PUSSY OVER.
THIS ISN'T WHAT WE PROMISED!
I NEVER PROMISED TO STOP AT THE FIRST CUMSHOT.
AT LEAST PUT A CONDOM ON!
THERE AREN'T ANY LEFT.
N-NO...
NO!
SO WHAT? HURRY UP AND GET ON IT.
NO, I DON'T WANT TO!
WHY DOES MY BODY REFUSE TO OBEY ME?
NO!
IF IT'S LIKE THAT.
NO! NOT SO DEEP!
WHAT A BABY!
YOU LIKE THAT?
NO WAY!
IT DOESN'T FEEL GOOD!
WHY DOES IT FEEL SO HOT IN MY BODY?
BIG BROTHER, FORGIVE ME.
IT IS UNFAIR.
IT'S TOO MUCH.
AT THIS RATE, MY BROTHER WOULD NEVER BE ABLE TO MAKE ME CUM!
BIG BROTHER, I'M HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
DESPITE DIFFICULTIES,
I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU, BIG BROTHER.
E-EH?
SOMEONE SEEMS TO HAVE LET THEMSELVES GO.
IF YOU WANT SOME,
I'LL GIVE YOU LOVE.
WHICH PENIS EXCITES YOU MORE?
I HAVE NO IDEA!
BROTHER, I'M SORRY!
THIS MAN IS ABOUT TO MAKE ME CUM.
EVEN MY OLD BODY CAN STILL GIVE YOU PLEASURE.
SHUT UP!
YOU NASTY PERVERTED TEACHER!
NO, IF HE CONTINUES TO PENETRATE ME THIS DEEP.
STOP!
I'M GOING TO CUM!
WHAT DO I DO? IT FEELS SO GOOD!
NO, I'M ABOUT TO.
YOU WANT MY WHITE SAUCE?
HERE IT COMES!
NO, I DON'T WANT HIM TO CUM INSIDE ME!
GET READY!
NO!
NO I'M STARTING TO.
I'LL CUM IF HE CUMS INSIDE ME.
JUST THINKING ABOUT IT.
YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT GETTING MARRIED!
YOU ALREADY GAVE OUT YOUR VIRGINITY TO ME!
STOP!
I BELONG TO MY BROTHER.
I'M CUMMING!
SORRY, I FORGOT THAT I WASN'T WEARING A CONDOM.
HOW AWFUL.
ALL THAT SEMEN IS INSIDE ME.
I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW.
YOU BETTER ANSWER THE CALL.
MY BROTHER AND I WILL SPEND TIME TOGETHER...
THEN TOMORROW I'LL BE...
ABUSED AGAIN...