No Trespassing
Onii-chan...
Yayoi, here I come.
Come, onii-chan!
Right now, I'm about to have anal sex with onii-chan.
Does it hurt?
You can be rougher if you want.
This isn't something siblings should
be doing but I begged him to.
I really just want to have sex with him,
and feel his dick inside my womb.
Onii-chan...
Desire Career Paths
Onii-chan's wife
I love onii-chan more than
anyone else in the entire world!
You're really close to your brother, aren't you, Yayoi-chan?
Yup!
That's why my dream is to get married
to him someday and live happily together!
Yayoi, didn't you know? Siblings can't get married.
That day, my friend shattered
my one and only dream with the truth.
She told me it was impossible.
It was nothing more than a dream.
Though, as long as he loves me like this, I'm happy.
Onii-chan!
Yayoi!
From now, I'll...
Part 1: I'll give you my first time
Onii-chan, you're going to graduate soon, aren't you?
Yeah, a college accepted me thanks to
the recommendations, so I don't need to worry.
I guess I won't be able to see you like this anymore.
Onii-chan, kissing isn't enough anymore.
You got hard again.
It's so hot.
Does this feel good, onii-chan?
It's starting to get wet.
Yayoi...
Touch me too, onii-chan.
You're so wet.
You just came, didn't you, Yayoi?
You haven't yet, onii-chan.
It'll go down after a while.
I'll...
Yayoi...
Just feel good, onii-chan.
Yayoi!
Does it feel good?
I love you so much, onii-chan!
I really want your dick in here, onii-chan.
Yayoi, that's the one thing I can't do.
We're si...
I get so scared thinking about how
you might forget me after you graduate!
I want to be with you forever! I don't want to be apart!
Okay.
That's the bell. We have to get back soon.
No! Let's just do it right now!
If we don't go back, they might come looking for us here.
Yeah, I guess... It'd be bad if people found out about us.
Let's do it tomorrow.
Yeah!
Even if he gets a girlfriend, I'll be satisfied
as long as we can keep having sex.
That's why I hope to keep this relationship
with him going on forever.
I'm about to give onii-chan my virginity...
Is somebody up there?
What are you doing up here, Takatsuki? This place is off limits.
Sorry!
Does it hurt?
– You can be rougher if you want.
– This is what HD looks like, huh? It looks great.
What is that?!
You guys really get along well.
Why don't we all get along together?
Secretly filming people is a crime!
So? Are you going to report me and
let everyone know what you've been doing?
Your sex tape would be seen
by a lot of adults if you did that.
Yeah, and you'd be in a position way worse.
That's surprising. You don't mind destroying
your life if it meant destroying mine?
Of course I don't. My body is only for onii-chan!
I won't let a gross, perverted teacher
like you lay even a finger on me!
What does your brother think about that?
I'm sure he'd lose more than just his scholarship.
Come on, let's talk about this.
What's the matter? Hurry up.
Onii-chan, save me!
Your beloved onii-chan isn't gonna come.
I sent him off on some errands.
What's with the kiddy panties? You're not gonna
make your onii-chan happy with those.
Shut up! Onii-chan isn't a pervert like you!
Strip like you were trying to turn me on.
My body is only for onii-chan.
I can't believe I'm doing this!
You're just a kid, but you have a really hot body.
You're really turning me on.
I wanna run away!
You're not done yet.
This is for onii-chan. I need to do this.
Don't hide anything!
Your personality might be bratty,
but your nipples are such a nice, clear pink.
Don't make that face.
Let's have some fun together, naked.
It's not your first time seeing one, right?
What is this? It's completely different from onii-chan's!
It's so gross!
Lick it already!
It stinks!
Put it in your mouth and suck it.
Don't touch me there! It feels disgusting!
It smells so bad, I can't even breathe through my nose!
Get ready to drink it, Yayoi!
He's going to cum in my mouth?!
No! I don't want to drink this guy's cum!
Here I go!
No!
Don't forget the taste of my cum, okay?
I never knew that being touched
by someone you didn't like felt so horrible.
Your moans are so cute.
I don't want this at all, but...
Don't even think about it!
Whatever. You're soaking wet.
That's not because of you.
That's because of your dear onii-chan, then?
You're so devoted.
It doesn't even feel good.
Onii-chan is way better than you.
How about we make a bet?
Bet on what?
If I cum in your ass before you cum, I'll delete everything.
If you cum first, then I'm taking your virginity.
I'm not gonna cum from a creep like you!
The only person who can make me feel good is onii-chan!
You're pretty confident.
I'm really showing my ass to a creep like this...
What is this...?! It's completely different from onii-chan's!
It's spreadi... No!
Does it feel good? You're getting tighter.
Your dick is nothing compared to onii-chan's!
That really hurts.
If he keeps shoving his dick so far
inside me like that, he'll break my ass!
Stop moving!
This feels so different from normal!
Stop! You're going to tear my ass apart!
I'm going to lose my mind! No, save me! Onii-chan!
My ass is gonna break!
Hurry up! Hurry up and finish!
Looks like I'm gonna win.
This doesn't feel good at all.
Just cum and get it over with already!
That's no fun. Come on, entertain me a little longer.
Why isn't he moving anymore?
Stop teasing me!
What? I want him to make me feel good?
Hurry up! Start moving and cum already!
Are you begging? That's so cute.
Who'd beg for yo...
I-Is this what I look like right now?
My ass is being pounded by his fat dick!
Hurry up and cum! If you don't, I'll... I'll...
I can feel the shape of his dick even clearer than I could!
This condom is really small. I think it broke.
No!
No, stop moving!
You're even tighter than before!
That's not true, you pervert!
This pervert is going to make you cum!
No!
I'm never gonna cum!
No, don't be so rough!
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
No, stop! I'm gonna cum!
There's hot stuff pumping into my ass!
It's finally over. Now I can be with onii-chan forever.
Onii-chan...
You came pretty hard, didn't you?
I didn't cum!
You came so hard that you
didn't even realize that I tied you up.
Well, we had a deal.
I'm going to have some fun with your virgin pussy.
Oh, you should do your best to make
me cum before the condom breaks,
If you don't, your pussy won't know
how it feels to not be pregnant after this.
I don't want any raw dick other than onii-chan's!
I don't want anyone else to get me pregnant, either!
Onii-chan, I'm sorry!
My virginity was stolen by this creep!
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!
Ow!
No!
Oh, look at that. I came without even realizing.
Thank god. He didn't cum inside me.
You've got a great pussy.
This isn't what we agreed on!
I never said that it would be just once.
Please put a condom on!
Looks like we're out of those.
No way...
No!
What's the matter?
You need to run before it goes inside you.
N-No! No!
Why can't I move? No! No!
Time's up!
No!
No! Stop doing it so hard!
Oh? Does it really feel that good?
N-No! I was just surprised, that's it!
Why does my body feel like it's on fire?
I'm sorry, onii-chan! I'm so sorry!
No, if this keeps going on, I'll never be able
to feel good with onii-chan again!
Onii-chan! I'm so happy!
Even though I'm dirty, you still love me, onii-chan!
No!
Look at you, taking the initiative.
I'll make you feel good, just like you want me to!
Feels better than your brother's, doesn't it?!
N-No, it doesn't!
Onii-chan, I'm so sorry.
He's going to make me cum by cumming inside me!
If you wrap your legs around me, it'll feel even better.
Shut up, you disgusting, perverted teacher!
No, stop moving!
No, he's going so deep!
What do I do? It feels so good!
No, I'm...
You want my cum? I can feel your pussy twitching!
No! I don't want to cum from his dick!
Get a good taste of my cum!
No! No!
No! It's coming! I'm gonna cum!
Oh yeah, wasn't your dream
to become a bride or something?
I'll help you out with that,
with the honors of a perverted teacher!
No, stop! I'm onii-chan's and onii-chan's only!
I'm cumming!
Oh, well. Looks like you'll be a mother
before you get to be a bride.
This can't be happening...
There's so much inside me...
I'm going to call you tomorrow.
Come immediately, understand?
I want to be with onii-chan forever, so...
I'll let him rape me again tomorrow.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hibrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч