What's up?
I thought I heard a girl's voice.
A few days after that nightmare...
I'm still being raped by this man.
Can't you hear it?
Wanna check it out?
Are they doing it?!
Let's take a look!
Shit! We gotta get back!
You got loose all of a sudden.
Did you want to be watched?
It just doesn't want to touch your disgusting thing!
Don't! Don't put it in so deep...
I'm gonna fill you up!
Don't put your disgusting cum inside me!
Here I go!
No!
His hot stuff is going to go inside my ass.
Every day he has sex with me washes away
the sex I've had with my onii-chan.
My ass is so full...
Looks like your ass couldn't get enough of it.
No, you just made it take all of it in.
Looks like you still need some "counseling."
And after that, his harassment continued.
What's the matter, Takatsuki?
This problem should be easy for you.
Wh-What is this?! I've never heard of something like this!
Please! Don't look at me!
I can't...
Hey, come on. If you don't hurry it up,
your precious onii-chan's gonna see this.
This is disgusting.
Hurry up! Hurry up and cum already!
Let me repay you for this.
It's... My ass feels hot!
I'm not gonna lose to you!
I'm cumming! Drink it up!
If you let even a drop fall, your onii-chan's gonna find out!
I can't breathe!
I want to be with onii-chan forever!
So I'll endure these hellish hours.
From now, I'm...
Part 2: I'll give you my second virginity too
You haven't been yourself lately.
Something wrong?
Huh? That's not true.
I'm sorry I couldn't be here these past few days.
Onii-chan, what's this?
Something to cheer you up.
Onii-chan, thanks!
Can I open it?
Sure.
It's so cute!
I'm glad you like it.
I'm so happy!
I'm gonna put them on, okay?
How do I look?
They look good on you.
I'm glad that cheered you up.
Sorry to make you worry like that.
Once I pick up, the nightmare starts again.
But if I don't then I'm not going to be able
to keep spending time like this with onii-chan.
Do you need to get that?
Come here. Now.
Understand?
I have somewhere I need to be, so I'll be going now.
What is this?
This is your own private sex room.
I need to thoroughly beat out the warped thinking
that leads you to have sex with your brother!
You're already so hard. Do you like this place?
Why'd you make this place?
There's something wrong with you!
You want me, don't you? You're already wet.
I'm not! That's just sweat!
I'm gonna start licking you.
I'm not gonna cum!
My body's just reacting on its own.
It feels good...
I don't want this! I shouldn't want this! But...
It's like a water fountain down here.
Let me start drinking.
Don't!
My head's going blank!
I came again even though I didn't want to.
I'll fuck you from, behind,
just how you like it, to christen this room.
No, stop!
We just did it this morning, but he's this hard again?!
It's not usually like this...
It's so hard!
Why's it so hard?!
I'm starting to feel weird! I'm so hot!
Every time he rubs me, I get so hot!
Stop! Don't go any deeper than that!
My womb! His filthy dick is inside my womb!
My mind is going haywire!
I'm cumming!
Wow! My stomach is burning up!
Come on. Take care of this for me.
Why's he in front of me?
Wait, so who's behind me?!
No!
A stranger is...
That's rude. The headmaster is having sex with you.
This is a naughty body.
You definitely need some guidance.
You're not too bad, headmaster.
Your breasts are so large. What cup size are you?
Why would I tell you...
Maybe I should have your onii-chan tell me?
F-cup...
You've been swinging those naughty tits in front
of your instructors all this time? Such a dirty girl.
We gotta give her good counseling.
Stop going so deep! Don't push into my womb anymore!
That was quite good.
I'm glad that satisfied you.
It's finally over.
We're not done yet.
It looks like the younger teachers
want to help guide you too.
Y-You can't be...
No! I can't do this anymore!
You're so tight!
This pussy is just waiting to be guided.
Th-That's not true!
Looks like you need to be taught a lesson.
Screw you! You just want a reason to rape me!
Scum like you...
You...
She's gotten tighter!
Take care of me too.
I guess it's time for me to return to the fray.
I'm not even close to being done yet
I'll be using this then.
No! Stop!
This can't be!
Two at the same time?!
Stop! My ass is gonna...
I'm cumming!
Does it feel good to have a cock in your ass and pussy?!
Like hell it does!
Why are you so wet?!
Stop!
Let's all join in to properly guide her.
Of course, headmaster.
She's gripping me so tightly!
Stop moving!
These tits are so naughty!
Stop rubbing them!
Take it in!
No, stop!
Listen to your teachers.
This is gross!
Please stop going inside me!
Looks like she's obedient now.
Our guidance was a success then.
Let's see.
Onii-chan...
No!
Great view, isn't it?
Shut the curtains!
Please!
It's a one-way mirror, so too bad he can't see you too!
So rough!
While your brother's having a meeting about his future,
his little sister's getting all kinds of cocks shoved into her!
You're such a fucking slut!
Shut up! Having sex with the brother.
I love feels so much better than with you...
Love, huh?
Then let me love you as my wife.
Who the hell would marry you?!
I'm never going to lose to this guy's dick!
You're such a huge pervert. I only put my finger into
your ass and yet you howled like some kind of animal.
Don't play with my ass!
You're going to make me go crazy!
My pussy is going to split! It's going to split!
You're such a needy wife.
My body's just starting to feel good on its own!
Why...
Are you gonna be my wife?
No!
No way in hell...
Stop! If you do it anymore...
If you become my wife, I'll give it to you so hard.
I'll do it!
Give it to me hard!
So good! It feels so much better than onii-chan's!
Let's kiss to seal the deal.
Why?!
Oops, sorry, it was just a regular pane of glass.
Looks like he could see us too.
No!
Onii-chan saw me!
Cum in front of your precious onii-chan!
No! No! No!
Don't show him me cumming with your dick!
Let's show him the orgasm to seal the deal!
Onii-chan, I'm so sorry.
Congratulations! May you two live a happy life.
Oh my god, this is so amazing. I love this.
After that, onii-chan saved me
from the nightmare and it all ended.
The teachers all got arrested, but we still got expelled.
Onii-chan!
It feels so good!
Yayoi, your insides are really wrapping around me!
But now I have so much time with onii-chan!
I'm so glad that I can be with you, onii-chan!
Me too! I'm so glad that I can be one with you, Yayoi!
Onii-chan!
Your semen feels so good, onii-chan!
I love you, onii-chan!
I never want to be away from you.
Me too. I never want to let go of you, Yayoi.
Even if you get married or get a girlfriend,
I'll always love you, onii-chan.
We'll always be together.
Thank you! I love you, onii-chan!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
You really came in your school uniform.
Yep.
Looks great on you.
Come on and show me it already.
You pass.
It's already coming so deep inside me!
I'm sorry, onii-chan.
I'm being violated by a stranger.
So intense!
I'm so happy to be with you now, onii-chan.
But...
I need more than just emotions now.
If you keep thrusting it deep into me like that, I'm gonna...
If I don't have a big dick to fill me up, I...
I can't feel happiness with you.
So good!
My heart lost.
That's why now and forever
I'll continue to let myself be violated.
I'm sorry, onii-chan.
I love you!