When it comes to books read by someone I like,
I just can't help but get all curious about it.
Even more so when these kinds of books are involved.
Now here I am, reading this after waiting for everyone to leave.
What in the world am I doing?
Oh, this had been borrowed by Mikage-chan?
Um excuse me, I'd like to borrow this book.
Oh, oh yeah.
How should I put this...
Ah! Yes, yes...
So you heard the rumors about this book as well?
Rumors?
You have perfect timing.
I happen to have a few high quality XXX here.
Here, try this one for yourself.
Drink it if you want.
It'd also be interesting if you can get a girl to take it.
What?
Do you know how to use it?
The details are in that book.
Oh and remember, it's not *** but XXX, got it?
Don't forget.
You can't afford to waste the chance,
use it properly, okay?
Anyway, what's your name?
I'm Tatsuki.
Let's be friends.
What?
Imako system
It says if in powder form,
mix it with something that can hide its bitter taste, like juice.
I feel awful...
Like a kid that drank bitter medicine,
I feel really sick...
That was a good meal!
Delicious!
You're really nice to me no matter what I do.
You're the complete opposite.
Can't you at least worry about me a little?
Are you okay?
Should I call an ambulance?
N-No, that won t be necessary.
Why do I feel weird?
It feels like my body has gotten stiff.
And my skin suddenly feels numb.
Anyway, why don t you lie down for a bit?
Come, over here.
Are you kidding me?
Why are you suddenly asking me to lie down on your lap?
I'm definitely not doing that!
Stupid jerk!
Are you really okay, Imako-chan?
Well, excluding the fact that I'm grossed out right now...
My head, and his hand...
This is bad! This is bad! This is bad!
When did just being patted on the head feel this good?
My heart is throbbing more than when I was a kid.
Why...?
I just got this way when I saw your aroused expression.
A-Aroused?
Hey, can you give me a blowjob please?
Okay, can't be helped then.
Your poor dick is already big, even before I start sucking it.
How cute.
It stinks.
This is Ichina's smell.
And I'm taking his thing deep inside my mouth.
I'm masturbating while giving a blowjob?
I like this...
I love this.
I'm getting lost between its smell and the pleasure that I feel.
You're totally engrossed on your blowjob.
You sure like dicks, Imako-chan.
It feels very good.
Good girl.
This is not good, not good!
His dick is starting to secrete Cowper fluids,
and it's twitching wildly.
I can tell that he is feeling really good,
that he is happy with pleasure.
I'm glad.
I never thought I'd feel this happy making someone happy.
If he already feels pleasure with a blowjob then...
Imako-chan?
It's better this way, right?
It'd feel better if I rub my pussy on your dick.
I'm going to make you feel really good.
Mine is starting to drip fluids onto his dick,
and it's making sloppy sounds.
The sloshing sounds inside my pussy are very erotic.
Can you hear the sound as your dick rubs against it?
Yeah, loud and clear.
The lewd sounds of your cute pussy rubbing against my dick.
I'm going to cum.
I'm about to cum.
I'm about to soil your virgin pussy.
Lots came out and it feels warm.
You were already at your limit?
Sorry.
How cute of you.
If it's this wet already, then I guess it's okay.
So please,
put it in, Ichina.
Drill it and stir it in as you like.
Make yourself feel completely good this time.
It hurts!
I'm sorry, seems I'm the only one who feels good so far.
My insides feel good.
So my pussy's okay.
Yeah, your virgin pussy is the best, Imako-chan.
I see, that's great then.
That's really great.
Okay, I'll make it feel better for you then.
Does it feel good?
Yeah, your love juice gets mixed in as it moves so it feels very nice.
I'm happy.
Hey kiss... I want to kiss.
Sorry, I just sucked your dick so it's a bit dirty.
Woah, Ichina's twirling his tongue around mine.
I'm too excited to move it properly.
I'm sorry.
He's licking the tongue that reeks of his dick's smell.
I'm happy. I'm happy, I'm happy.
His dick is really drilling in, making a total mess of my pussy.
Despite that, I still feel happy.
I wonder why.
It's because I love him, right?
It hurts, doesn't it?
You don't need to move.
You can just be my sex toy.
Oh, so he's actually worried about me.
I'm okay.
I'm happy, I'm happy...
It feels good.
I'm happy...
You just keep on fucking because it also feels good for you, right?
I'm just fine, really.
Just make yourself feel really good.
I don't care how many times you fuck me.
Just make a mess of me as you want to!
Thank you then I'll push harder, okay?
Huh? Ichina's starting to look scary.
Why?
But... I actually kind of like him with that expression.
I don't care, I love all of his expressions.
I love it!
I love you... Nii-chan, I love you.
I haven't heard you call me that in a long time.
I kind of felt like a little kid again.
Amazing just amazing.
Just knowing that Onii-chan is feeling good,
I'm starting to feel good too because I'm so happy.
Push it harder, make it more painful.
Just penetrate me all the way with your dick.
Release all of your cum.
Keep on making yourself feel good.
I think it's time already.
Huh?
You really worked yourself out earlier, right?
It'd be bad for your body if you don't properly rehydrate yourself.
Oh yeah.
Take a bath and clean yourself after drinking this, okay?
Ichina's so sweet.
I love you, I love you!
I'm happy that our feelings are now
transparent to each other Ichina!
In the end,
I'm way past just being overdue.
Well, he did give me the drug while letting me borrow this.
It feels so awkward to return it.
I am asking why did you lend it to Ichina?!
That voice... Imako-chan?
It's my policy to lend what I have or
know to people who really want it.
You think he'd like that stuff?
Then why did he borrow it?
I don't know, he must have a reason to...
Wait, are they talking about the medicine he gave me?
Besides, if you're really that worried then why don't you ask him?
It won't do you any good to lash out at me like that.
Why is she asking about it?
Oh, I get it now.
Why don’t we talk about this inside, eh?
Hey! Stop that!
I never got to return the book.
Wait, leaving that aside...
What are they going to talk about in private?
Wait, what are they going to do?!
What are you doing there, pure boy?
Mikage-chan.
Want to go home together?
So, what were we talking about?
I told you, it's about the medicine you gave to Ichina.
Oh yeah, but let me correct that,
it's actually about the medicine that he gave to you, am I wrong?
That's not my point!
What are you saying? It's totally about that.
If you have any problems with him having that XXX,
then you should have talked to him
about it directly in the first place.
Why are you trying to vent your frustration on me first?
The order is completely jumbled.
Or, were you actually expecting something like this to happen?
You've already used up all of yours while reading
that book through and through, right?
I can give more to you, on one condition.
Condition?
Take it right here.
You understand already, right?
A cat that I had been taking care of half a year
ago suddenly left the house and disappeared.
It was already at an age where it could die at any moment.
Those leaves were from his earlier days?
Yeah, and the catnip's never been consumed since then.
But, is it okay for you to put a grave here?
I've got permission from the landowner.
Besides, Mi-chan isn't here.
You've heard about how cats are always leaving
their owners when they are about to die, right?
Oh, I see.
It's a grave in name only.
Well, cats are kind of moody anyway.
They move from place to place whenever they want to.
Oh yeah, the cat that my friend was taking care of wasn't spared.
One day, it suddenly turned up pregnant.
Pregnant?
There she goes talking without constraint again.
I'm scared, what is going on?
Well, I guess that's enough.
I think the medicine has started to take effect,
so this should feel good for you now.
It's true, this feels even better than masturbating.
You're now ready for the next step, right?
No, I'm scared, please stop!
There's no need to be so stiff.
I'll be using a condom.
Just think of this as your cool off session.
It's still fresh?
Here I thought Ichina's already having a good time with you.
This is sexual harassment you know?
So this means the girl I gave it to earlier just used it on herself?
Guess there are people like that.
Those who jack or slosh themselves off after it kicks in.
Well that's good.
You're the best actually.
Now then, I'll enjoy taking everything from you bit by bit.
His dick is slowly sliding in.
What was that?
No way, this is just after my first time,
it doesn't feel painful at all after he penetrated me.
Did I just cum?
Wow, you can already remember how a dick feels?
I knew you had the potential.
Huh, why are you pulling it out?
Shove it in, ram it into me!
If you're really into it, then I think we won't need this.
No, that's...
Don't, I won't be able to resist if you put it in that way.
You can't insert it raw!
My mind's going crazy thinking about how it will feel.
How that dick will fuck me until my mind goes blank,
and I'm completely consumed by how good it will feel.
Hey, I can put it in now, right?
No... No, no, no!
You definitely mustn't!
I want it, I want you to fuck me...
I don't want to get pregnant.
Please, pour all your cum, make it seep inside me.
I want to get impregnated.
I see, so you don't want to.
Don't look at me like you're a kid who got their candy stolen.
No need to worry, I understand your situation.
This is good.
The feeling as you loosen up little by little.
Your insides are wet and sloppy.
It feels great for you too, right?
It hurt at irst, but now the pain's completely gone.
Maybe he's better at this?
I can feel how he gently fondles me, how he caresses me softly.
Tihis feels good, I love how your dick fucks me.
What is this?
I feel totally at ease.
Why?
Why does it feel this good?
You look like you're having real fun doing this.
I would have thought that the XXX would not be sufficient for you.
If I say "diluted" would you understand what it means?
Dilute...
They say that the XXX is kind of hard
to make despite being effective.
Which is why it is actually sold in small amounts,
only mixed in with other drugs.
With other drugs?
Those other drugs are mainly***.
So consider yourself really lucky.
It is know that having sex while taking *** is the best.
Okay, come in.
I knew you were here.
You can't slack off from your library duties!
Oh, sorry about that.
I totally forgot.
What in the world am I doing?
I don't know anymore.
Because I can't help but feel pleasure,
after remembering how his dick tastes.
I can even drink cum now without hesitation.
Hey, doesn't it smell weird?
Oh yeah, I spilled an aromatic earlier.
Is that so?
Even more so,
this level of ecstasy is already too much for me.
Oh no, oh no.
I'm now hopelessly craving his dick.
What was that sound?
Who knows?
That doesn't really matter.
Y-You're right.
Oh well then.
Just properly close the library later, okay?
Your dick feels great.
Well, she just chickened out.
Don't you think so too, Imako?
I love this.
Your dick,
I love rubbing it inside my pussy.
I'm not asking you about that.
Hey, move a little faster.
I can't cum with that pace.
I can move faster?
My head is going blank with its smell.
I can't think of anything other than dicks now.
There, you're doing good.
Well? Do you love my dick now?
Yeah, I do.
And I also love to ram it inside me too.
It's a bliss to have it in me.
Good answer.
Let me give you this as a reward.
So, how does it feel?
Oh wow, the two of us are moving!
It feels better when both of us move, right?
Yeah, it really does.
Both of us are independently moving.
Now my hips want to keep moving even more.
I love this, please do it more.
You know what? I think we're really compatible.
He's right.
Our rhythms are synced with each other.
Does this mean I'm totally okay with him now?
Tatsuki's dick has completely changed me.
I get it now, my body is starting to remember
his dick's shape and movements!
My body is starting to know which of
his movements make it feel better.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming with your dick!
My womb is drinking all of its cum.
His cum is all the way inside.
Inside my womb...
My body feels light, and it feels really good.
We really are compatible.
We even came together.
From now on, you can only take that drug if you're with me.
That's OK with you, right?
Okay, good girl.
But you see Imako, I didn't get this drug for free.
So let's make a deal.
And so, during lunch the next day,
Mikage-chan brought this guy along for some reason.
What? Are you so happy that you've got a new friend?
Don't try to dictate my thoughts!
Here, the lunch that I said I'd make.
Eh?
Wow, thanks!
That closes the deal then.
Shut up and just eat it.
Wait? What's going on?
Here, there's really nothing different
when making 2 or more lunches.
So eat it if you want to.
Woah, she's really good at this.
Hey!
I guess lunches are all about taking each other's food.
It's definitely not!
So, are they on bad terms after all?