He's sleeping... right?
It's large... and filling my mouth...
How many times have I taken a penis in my mouth?
Just might be more than I've eaten... just kidding...
He's about to cum, isn't he?
I can tell, although there Isn't really
a sign that it's happening...
But you're cumming, right? You can let it all out.
Let me drink it all.
Here it is...
This... sperm... I love it... it really love it...
Please give me more of Ichina's smell...
There's so much in my mouth...
Just a bit more... like this...
Huh? Good morning, Imako-chan!
You're early today.
Your timing is horrible!
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Imako System
I'm not sure why you're upset but...
Can I get you not to step on it?
Oh, so you're not actually upset Then...
Hey, what are you doing?
It's a punishment because you don't
seem to be reflecting on yourself.
Stop it! Let go! Hey, I'll get mad
I said I'll get mad, you...
It doesn't hurt, like always...
You, you...
So, are you that happy from getting
attention, Imako-san?
What a great reaction! It's so fun I
can't help but tease her too much!
Get a hold of yourself and...
Woah, that is actually gonna hurt!
Imako-chan?
This is a book from the library so I can't hit you with it...
I see... uh, sorry...
Good morning, both of you!
Wait, why is Imako-chan crying?
Oh, I was being concerned by why she was pretending
to be upset and, that actually got her upset...
What?
You can't do that.
Imako-chan is the super troublesome girl who
is very frail despite always being gallant!
You have to be careful about her feelings.
You’re already not being very careful
about her feelings, Mikage-chan.
It's fine! Girls are as cute as they are troublesome.
What?
Oh, I see.
He's loved you so much this morning
you couldn't help but cry, huh?
How jealous I am.
Thump.
What, what are you talking about?
Huh? But, you smell strange.
From your mouth, in particular.
Could it be that the first thing in the morning...
How vulgar!
One hit K.O...
Wasn't that a borrowed book?
Well, this is a bit improper but I guess if
she's only reading it for knowledge...
Wait, this is from the library!?
That's just not right...
I hope washing it this much gets
rid of the smell in my mouth.
Hey, Imako-chan!
You didn't show up in the classroom for quite a while
and I was wondering where you went, so here you are.
What?
What do you mean "What?", that's mean.
The first bell already rang.
I went all the Way here to look for you, too.
Oh, sorry.
Thanks for coming all the way.
Then, let's hurry and go back... Ichina?
Wait, what's with the sudden...
Change of plans. Let's skip.
No, I don't think that's a good idea...
This is quite exciting, isn't it?
Hey, listen to what other people say...
Wow, it went right in.
Were you drenched since the morning fellatio?
How do you know that?
Mikage-chan told me.
Looks like classes have started.
Guess we have to give up on that now.
You idiot...
Skipping class for sex is strangely exciting...
If you're always trying to be a good student, even the
small bad things make you really scared, don't they?
And the nervousness from fear just
feels like excitement right now.
What' with that?
It's the thrill.
Don't... your penis is... deep inside...
I'm cumming.
Not inside...
C'mon, get pregnant.
Bear my child.
Are you scared?
Of course!
That's what makes it feel good!
I'll let it all out, so be sure to get pregnant!
Geez, I went so far to clean it all
up, and now I'll smell again!
The smell of semen is soaking all the way into my womb!
Let's keep it like this until class ends.
I feel like they're giggling about me...
Is it just me being over conscious?
Geez, how many times did he cum after that?
My legs are so sore...
Hmm? Which part of you is horny now?
Don't change other people's inner dialogue!
Hey, stop trying to smell other people, too.
Huh? But... well, okay, I won't stop you or anything.
It's not like you guys just started today or anything.
But keep it reasonable, okay?
Keep what?
You have quite the smell of sex at the moment.
Anyone can tell you've been doing it.
No way...
She said that to you?
So, from now on let's not...
Why?
What?
There's nothing to be afraid about our
relationship being known, is there?
Your tights feel great!
Here we go!
Wait a mome-!
Semen is soaking into my tights...
No... it'll leave a smell...
I actually want the smell to sink in.
C'mon, leave more of my smell on you.
No?
Well, not no, but...
But?
But...
You don’t want a girl reeking of semen either, right?
It’s fine! To me, it's just my own smell.
I'm totally used to it.
So reek more, until no one but me will go near you!
It feels good!
The way his penis comes in just feels natural...
My pussy is already in the shape of Ichina's penis...
C'mon, move on your own.
He's so much stronger than me, I always end up
doing whatever he wants during times like this...
But that just feels too good... both
my body and my heart feel good...
I get teased around but eventually
I still start moving on my own...
Getting excited from being teased and ordered around...
No way, he’s cumming again!
He's messing up my insides...
I... can’t...
I think... I'm done for...
Because, this smell that everyone's supposed to hate...
I'm starting to love it...
Hey, can I mark you again?
No way, one more time? He can still go?
I see...
I'll stink...
More of Ichina's smell is soaking into me, so, so...
Let it out!
All of it, inside!
Give me your sperm!
Let it out! Let it out!
Make the smell of Ichina go all the way to my head!
It feels good... I'm so happy...
C'mon, clean it up.
Wanna stay tonight?
Then, let's go home.
What's wrong?
I can't stand up...
So, what are you planning to do?
About what?
Even though it's only in-law, we are siblings.
If the whole class knows... that's kind of bad...
If things really go bad...
Let's run far away together.
Far away? How?
Just the two of us, on my motorcycle or something.
That'd be great.
How can you say that so carelessly?
Ouch!
Stupid.
If you tap my cheek twice, I'll ask for oral.
Would you like my mouth-pussy?
Okay, I'll such on your mouth with my mouth.
I'll drink all of your semen, so thrust as much as you like.
Woah, amazing...
She's sucking a cock like it's delicious, this feels great!
You can let it all go and she'll do everything...
Imako-chan,. does it taste good?
Does my dick taste good?
Don't be stupid, she can't hear you.
Through my headphones, I can hear
recordings of previous sex I've had.
I can't hear everyone's voice, but we've
decided on signals, so it's alright.
If you tap my but once, it's for my pussy.
If I raise my hips and shake my butt, everyone
will put their penis in happily.
It would be great If I could ask for
it, too, but I can't talk right now.
It's a pity.
I can't get tired of the sensation of a penis pushing into
my pussy no matter how many times it happens.
When a penis comes in a rubs, I get
excited and my mind goes blank.
But they will be unhappy if I don't focus
on my mouth, it's a lot of trouble.
I've gotten used to have sex with everyone and
being touched by many more at the same time.
If everyone is happy, I feel good, too, so I'm really happy.
I'm starting to like the taste of penis, recently,
and I like it when it rubs the roof of my mouth.
Gonna cum. Cumming!
If you grab the back of my head,
I'll try to take it even deeper.
If you cum hard, I'll think that you
feel good, and it'll make me happy.
After you let out your semen, I'll
suck out the remaining for you.
Sometimes people pee right after
that, and I will drink that, too.
In the end, I'll kiss your balls lots.
C'mon, let's love each other lots.
Usually, it's all tapping signals from
everyone, which is a little lonely,
but it makes these sudden talks
very surprising and I feel happy.
Maybe my body feels the love, too, and it
feels lonely inside when you talk to me.
My womb will yearn to bear the child of this person.
I'm cumming. I'm letting out all my sperm!
I'm getting pregnant... the way sperm
flows into my womb feels so good!
Semen is coming out... where the baby is formed...
my most precious place... semen is flowing right in!
You're putting two in, right?
Alright I cleaned my butt, too, so thrust
as much as you want and feel good!
It's here...
I'm itching for your penis... I've always been waiting...
Together... hurry...
I've had it shoved in my front and
back at once many times now.
It was really painful at first, but it got better,
and right now this feels the best.
Having my pussy and butt rubbed at
the same time is good of course,
but the best is being hugged from front and back.
my body feels warm, and my heart, too.
When I loose strength from being too
tired, I'm completely toyed around.
I used to be scared that it'll happen, but when it does,
I can concentrate on only the sensation of the penises.
After getting used to them doing whatever
they want, it's actually very relaxing.
I feel really happy.
Ichina, thank you for teaching me so much.
I’m so happy thanks to you.
You want to join, too, Ichina?
Did you know? The three of them
were walking with another man...
Who?
Tatsuki and Mikage.
Well, about those three, Mikage is
just dragging Tatsuki around and...
Tatsuki is the guy who was giving
out drugs for free, right?
Where did he get that money?
He just got some extra cash from a friend,
and I heard he stopped the drugs, too.
No way!
Did Tatsuki have friends?
Nah, Mikage's probably the only
one willing to deal with him.
The three of them haven't been at school
It's'been about a week.
A small rumor that Tatsuki was giving
out some dangerous drugs,
was alternated, exaggerated, and spread out.
The whole school is talking about it now.
That’s the problem! I can't help
but thinking about bad things.
I want to believe them...
But...
If a text like this comes...
You'd think that everything's too late!
Kuromitsu Imako
Subject: Help
It this the police?
Yes, a friend of mine, a girl was taken and...
The place? It's at Tatsuki's house!
You'd think that the nightmares came true!
I think I heard a scream I'm not familiar with.
The atmosphere around is strange...
Who is it?
Should I take of my headphones and blindfold?
I don’t think I've seen the world in a while...
I see... that's how you'd save me...
I can't. I can't do this. I'm scared!
When she asked for help, it's as if
all my crazy fantasies were true!
I don't want to believe that!
I don't want to see Imako-chan like that!
I'm just so worried my mind is going crazy,
I can't stand not being able to do anything...
Huh?
What is this?
What's happening?
Kuromitsu Imako
Subject: Help
Mikage and stupid tatsuki are making out too much, It's kiling me.
Help! LOL
Huh?
If you’re wondering what happened
to Tatsuki when the police came,
He was arrested right away.
Turns out he was hiding some bad drugs in his room.
Imako-chan and Mikage-chan weren't treated as
suspects, only as personnel involved in the case.
My imaginations, although maybe not all
of it, were just imaginations after all.
Even so, what keeps me worried is that those
fantasies have the chance to be true!
Because, she's always been that kind of girl!
Before I noticed, Tatsuki got closer to Imako-chan...
Of course you'd think something bad would happen!
I'm scared. I'm so scared and I can't
do anything about it and...
I was so suspicious and doubtful and I had no
means to confirm what was happening and...
and I got more worried... and I didn't know anything...