Math
Modern
japanese
Why do I even have to do this?
I can't believe I have to be taught by you.
Onii-chan,
if you don't take being a tutor seriously,
I'm gonna tell mom on you.
Don't come crying to me if you lose your allowance.
But, you know...
The way you teach makes everything so easy
to understand. It really helps me out.
Well if you put it that way... that makes me happy.
You're even easier to understand
than the teachers at school.
Right?
Don't you think so too, Miu-chan?
Yeah, I guess.
I do think it shows our good side,
but it doesn't excuse your behavior at all.
Stop blushing from being complimented!
I'm not embarrassed at all.
I'm just telling him thanks.
This girl is so two faced!
Oh no, I wasn't talking about you, Riko-chan.
I was talking about my stupid brother
over there for getting full of himself.
I'm not getting full of myself or anything!
A-ny-way, don't do anything vulgar
like that in front of my friend.
You say that, but it's hard to resist Riko-chan's advances.
"It's okay if there are
some "benefits", right?"
"Be cautions of Riko-chan
and avoid all skinship."
But at the same time. I don't want Miu to
hate me anymore than she already does.
What is this crappy situation?!
"It's okay if there are
some "benefits", right?"
"Be cautions of Riko-chan
and avoid all skinship."
"It's okay if there are some "benefits", right?"
Or maybe I'll be cautious of Riko-chan and avoid all skinship.
Miu, you know...
Hi, it's me...
Huh? That can't be... You're serious?!
Okay, I understand.
This is bad. I need to go home.
Sorry, Miu-chan and onii-san.
Riko-chan?
Something just came up!
My little sister and her friend are too
erotic, my dick won't go down!
Original Animation Disc.
Brunette, twin talled, and huge tits!? My little sister's cute friend, Rico Arc.
My little sister and her friend are too
erotic, my dick won't go down!
Brunette, twin tailed, and huge tits!?
My little sister's cute friend, Riko Arc.
I feel so much better!
But all things considered, even if she is my own
sister, I have no idea how to interact with her.
Wow, onii-san, you just cut right to the chase.
You could've just asked me to wash your
back for you instead of doing this.
Huh?!
Onii-chan, what's going on?
Did something happen?
D-Don't look at me!
Wait, don't...
What? What shouldn't I do, onii-chan?
Uh, so you see, like ten cockroaches just popped out of nowhere.
I just finished squishing all of them under my feet.
So you can't look in here, okay?
You squished them with your feet?
You just got out of the bath, right, onii-chan?
Starting tomorrow, don't come within
a ten meter radius of me, okay?!
What an unaffectionate sister I have.
What, Riko-chan?
Well you see, if I set an alarm on my phone like this, then...
O
See? It rings as if I got called.
And then after that, I just snuck away and
waited for you to come back here.
But for what reason?
What I'm going to say might end up betraying Miu-chan.
But...
My heart just skipped a beat.
How do you feel about me?
Y-You're popular even in my class, Riko-chan.
Even I...
Are you serious?
But it'd make me happier to be loved
by just you instead of everyone.
So when you said that you might be betraying Miu,
what did you mean by that?
Wait, so you have no idea?
About what?
Oh, no, nevermind.
But more importantly... okay?
Um, onii-san, please don't be embarrassed.
If you can't hold back from being embarrassed,
I don't think I'll be able to endure it either.
Riko-chan...
You're so beautiful.
Geez, onii-san, you're already so big.
No this is...
Anyone who sees your beautiful naked body would get like this!
It's really embarrassing if you stare too much.
But I'm happy that you see me that way.
Riko-chan, you're too damn cute!
I'm done waiting!
Onii-san, I love you!
Me too, Riko-chan.
Make my boobs feel good too.
No problem.
My heart's beating even harder than before.
Can you tell?
It's because your tongue is making me feel so good.
It's telling me that every time I lick.
I'm so happy.
It feels very good!
Riko-chan!
Shh! Shh!! Miu's gonna hear us!
Sorry. But could you tell that my nipples are getting hard?
Of course. I can also tell that their color is getting a little darker.
They're almost like cherries.
No, that's so embarrassing!
Your weak points are here, aren't they?
Riko-chan, watch your voice!
Lower your voice!
My nipples... they feel so good when you pull them!
It's so good! So amazingly good!
Riko-chan, you're so cute.
Riko-chan, just let my hands take you to pleasure town.
Or you want me to stop?
You're such a meanie.
You already know what I want!
Wow, Riko-chan, your panties are already soaked.
But that's because you...
After touching me that much, do you think that I'm a dirty girl?
Not at all.
You're only getting this turned on because you like me, right?
Really?
Yeah.
I want to see what your downstairs looks like right now.
Downstairs?
This is embarrassing. This is so embarrassing!
W-What do you think?
What are you doing?!
Onii-san!
Don't lick it! It's dirty!
Oh no. Why does it feel so good? What should I do?
What should I do?!
If it feels good, just let yourself go.
Just let myself go?
You're licking my embarrassing place.
But, it feels good!
Your juices just keep pouring out. I can't keep up.
No! This is so embarrassing, don't be so descriptive.
Riko-chan, it's about time.
Here I go.
Wait, just wait...
Your dick is so hot, onii-san!
Riko-chan, it feels really good.
It's coming inside me! It's gonna come inside me!
Onii-san! Onii-san!!
It's inside!
It went all the way inside you, Riko-chan.
Onii-san, it hurts!
It hurts?
Wait, Riko-chan, this is your first time?!
Yes, it's my first.
You're my first love, onii-san.
It hurts, but I'm so glad that I can be one with you, onii-san.
Riko-chan. Riko-chan!
Onii-san, please... kiss me!
Onii-san, I love you!
Sorry, I'm going to move.
Onii-san!
No! There... What's going on?
What is this feeling?
It doesn't hurt?
Does it feel good right here?
I don't really know. But I'm...
Got it. Alright!
Right there... My mind's going crazy!
I'm going to go crazy!
I can't believe my first time feels this good!
I... I...
I'm so turned on.
It feels good for me too.
It's so hot and it's squeezing me so tightly.
Something's getting tight. I can feel something coming!
Something's wrong!
Something's wrong with me!
Riko-chan, do you feel good?
Are you about to cum?
I-I am!
So good!
I...
I-I'm kind of tired.
Yeah, sorry for pushing you too hard.
No, you didn't.
It felt really good.
Also, it makes me really happy that you felt good too.
Really? Thank goodness.
Riko-chan, you were so erotic... You were so cute.
Th-That's embarrassing, so please don't say that.
Was I really that erotic?
Did I make you hate me at all?
Not at all! The opposite, if anything.
It'd make me happy if we could, you
know, be together from now on.
Huh, you mean it?
So you'll take me as your lover?
That makes me so happy!
Really happy!
I thought this before, but Riko-chan's sexiness is natural.
That's why I never even thought that
she was a virgin until today.
And I'll get to partake in this natural sexiness every day.
Wish me luck.
My little sister and her friend are too
erotic, my dick won't go down!
Well then, now that Riko-chan and
I had officially started dating,
I found a letter in my shoe box, calling me out.
Am I at the age where this should make me happy?
Oof.
Onii-san.
Oh, Riko-chan, what's the matter?
Why did you call me out here?
Is it weird that I did?
There aren't many places that we can be alone,
so I thought that maybe out here where
nobody usually comes could work.
O-Oh. So what did you need to talk about?
Onii-san, were you listening to what I just said?
Asking to talk, was just an excuse to get you here.
Ahem. I'll say this one more time.
I just wanted to be alone with you. Okay?
Riko-chan, does that mean...
It looks like you feel the same way, onii-san.
If you do, that makes me really happy.
I can't see anything at all.
It'll be fine, onii-san.
But could you just wait a second?
With this...
Nobody will be able to open it from that side.
Did you know that?
That makes sense.
Yeah, like that, it'd be impossible for
anybody to open it from that side.
So now... Um...
We can take our time. Come on, onii-san,
don't just stand around.
Here, sit down.
Oh, okay.
We're finally alone.
It's so quiet here, it kinda makes you want
to do something naughty. Doesn't it?
Huh, naughty? We can't. We're at school.
But nobody's coming.
And I even locked the door.
Onii-san...
Okay?
A girl's basically throwing herself at you.
So you can't make a face like that.
Seriously, she's a devil in disguise.
Onii-san, I love you!
Do you kind of think that I'm some kind of dirty
girl now that I'm taking the initiative like this?
Huh?
Well not so much dirty as much as really cute.
I'm so glad.
Huh?
Are you already hard down there, onii-san?
Well you mounting me doesn't really help.
Well, if I do it like this...
Does it feel good, onii-san?
It kinda feels good for me.
Riko-chan, if you move that much...
Your dick is getting harder and harder under my butt, onii-san.
I feel it digging into my bloomers.
I want to see your boobs, Riko-chan.
Of course you can.
Can you see them?
This is kind of embarrassing.
Riko-chan, your nipples are so perky.
How do I put this...
they're so cute.
My nipples are already erect!
They're so hard!
This is just because it's cold!
Don't look so much!
I... I...
So your nipples get hard if it's cold?
Stop being mean!
Well they get hard when I think about... dirty things too.
So now's one of those times I'm guessing.
No! My bloomers are drenched! You can see it!
– They're all wet!
– Nope.
Let me get a better look at them.
It's a really hot sight to see, Riko-chan.
I want to hurry up and stick my dick inside you, Riko-chan.
O-Okay.
Onii-san...
I can't hold on either!
It's so hot! I can't believe it's this hard either!
Your dick is coming inside me!
It's so thick!
It's not going to fit!
It's too big!
Are you okay?
Just take your time.
I'm fine. I'm a little nervous about putting
it in because I can't see inside.
You're putting it in perfectly.
It feels good.
It's going so deep!
The wet fabric of the bloomers makes this feel even better!
O-Okay, I'm going to move now.
Huh? Why?
N-No! It's going to come out!
I just got it inside me but it's going to come out!
You're so tight right now, Riko-chan!
It's like your pussy's saying it doesn't want to let go!
B-But... That's not true at all.
Riko-chan, are you okay?
Are you going to be able to move and keep it in?
Yes. I'm going to try moving now.
It's making so much noise! It's so embarrassing.
It's so embarrassing.
Please! Don't listen!
I'm happy to be able to hear the sound
of you feeling good though.
The sound of me feeling good?
H-How is it for you?
Am I doing this right?
Yeah, you are. This is really good.
Your boobs are the best, Riko-chan!
Onii-san, you're so lewd.
Well we're doing something lewd together.
If you keep thrusting there...
If you keep... thrusting... Something's going to happen!
You're already so soaking wet.
Don't say that!
I'm already saying so many dirty things.
It's so embarrassing!
Don't be so rough with my boobs!
It feels too good!
My boobs are very sensitive, so they feel so good!
Every time I rub your nipples, your pussy gets tighter.
There! There! It feels good there!
So good!
Hey, onii-san! Onii-san!
Move! Please, I...
You feel too good, so now you can't move?
It feels too good!
I can't even move a muscle.
I'm sorry!
Like this, I...
It feels really good.
No! It's going to come out!
It's coming out! Your dick is going to fall out!
Maybe it's because just the tip's inside you right now.
No! I don't want it to fall out!
I want it! Please give it to me!
Look, your pussy's already gripping me
tightly. It's practically begging for it.
I really want it. I want your dick, onii-san!
I want your dick! I don't want it to fall out!
Yeah! It's so good! It feels like my pussy's going to break!
It's going to break! It's gonna break!
You're being so rough!
It feels so good!
Your dick feels so good, onii-san!
So good!
Your dick feels so good!!
Riko-chan! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Cum!
You can cum inside, onii-san!
Plaster the walls of my pussy with your hot,
sticky cum! Cover it with your cum!
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Onii-san's cum! It's coming!
I'm cumming!
I-I'm cumming!
I-I can't hold on!
I can't!
Are you okay, Riko-chan?
Your cum is so hot, onii-san.
You came so much, didn't you?
Sorry, I really got your bloomers dirty.
Yeah, they're drenched.
Even the mat is getting wet from your cum dribbling out of me.
Your cum's going to overflow.
It's overflowing!
Ah, we need a cloth. Where's a cloth!
Cloth, where are you? Um.
Oh, it's okay.
It's fine like this.
I'll be fine if I just wear it like this.
See? The fabric's thick, so it won't leak.
Sure, but doesn't it feel nasty going around like that?
Not at all.
But more importantly, I feel like I got
really loud somewhere near the end.
Now that I think about it, I completely
forgot to keep my voice down too.
This could be bad.
Huh? That's weird. Is it locked from the inside?
Why is Miu here?!
Why? Oh, wait now that I think about it, she's
the organizer for the athletics festival.
Excuse me? Is anybody in there?
I think there's a back door over there.
Alright, let's hurry.
Oh, right. I have the key to the back door too.
Maybe I'll just go in through there.
Ow.
We're done for.
Huh? Is lunch over already?
I guess I'll try again tomorrow.
That was so nerve-wracking.
I was really worried for a second.
Oh no! I just remembered, my next class is gym!
Oh, so that's why you were wearing your gym
clothes underneath your school uniform.
How can you be so nonchalant about this?
I can't go to class now!
S-Sorry.
But weren't you the one who started
everything with your gym clothes...
Oh, I know! I'll just borrow them from Miu-chan!
Hey that's not fair! You're just glossing over your own oversight!
I'm not doing anything of the sort!
Anyway, you're a guy. You shouldn't
dwell on the small things forever.
Isn't it a man's duty to listen earnestly to his cute
girlfriend's problems without complaint?
Th-That was a mouthful of a sentence
just to try and deflect responsibility.
Wh-What do you mean, "deflect responsibility"?!
In the first place, aren't guys supposed
to not be so nitpicky about things?!
It looks like we were able to become a real couple.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч