Karaoke
I'm at a mixer my friend organized.
The chicks here are pretty hot, but one
of them looks like she's not having fun.
All right, next up is Mina!
Go introduce yourself!
That's right.
I'm pretty sure we've met before.
And not just once, but...
Wavy hair with a sweet scent...
A devilish fang...
And a voluptuous body!
There's no mistaking it. This girl is...
I'm Mina.
This is my first time doing this kind
of thing. Let's have a good time.
This girl is my god damn little sister!
Looks like that Mina chick is into you!
No, that's not it at all.
He's been staring at you all night.
I bet you'd really hit it off with him!
Geez, why is he here?
First, I get dragged to a mixer,
and now my brother is here!
This sucks.
Okay, time for the main event!
King's game!
I came be jerked off by my slutty little sister ♥
King Game with the little sister ♥
~The story of the king game with my little sister in the mix~
This is so embarrassing!
What the heck?
We really have to go that far?!
We're gonna see all of your titties, tonight!
All right, next round.
Who's the king?
It's me!
Okay, then... Number one will...
show number five...
their underwear!
Hey!
I'm number five...
The king's orders are absolute!
Why?!
I don't want to!
You have to do what the king says!
My brother's right in front of me!
I put on a really risque pair, too!
Panties! Panties! Panties! Panties! Panties!
Guess I have no choice...
Panties!
Fine!
That's good enough, right?
What the hell, Mina? You really went all out for this mixer!
Stop staring!
I bet she isn't wearing a bra, either...
And under those panties is her pussy...
Look, that guy is totally hard.
Way to go!
Why the hell are you getting a boner from your sister?
All right, let's have three and four
share some Pocky together!
Here you go.
Huh? Is he really going to do it?
I'm kissing my brother! This isn't right!
This is so messed up!
Okay, now fondle her tits!
My sister's tits! Bared before me!
He's looking right at them!
Stop...
This isn't right!
If you keep rubbing them like that...
Okay, now help him get off!
Hey, don't you think this is going a bit far?
C'mon, help him out!
Look at my body to help you jerk off...
Watching a guy masturbate is really intense!
Gimme your cum.
Mina!
This is bad!
This is really bad!
I'm covered in my brother's semen...
The smell is so strong.
I can't believe it's turning me on.
My panties are soaked.
Have I completely lost my mind?
Welcome back, Mina.
Geez, tell me when you're cumming!
My bad.
Next, number three will masturbate in front of everyone!
Oh? You're number three, huh?
There's no way I can do that!
I just gave a blow job, you know?
Yeah, but...
Do I really have to?
My brother is here...
Am I actually going to do this?
Wow, you're soaking wet!
Y-You don't have to point that out!
Being watched is really turning you on, huh?
That's not...
Who are you thinking of right now?
Nobody!
I'm imagining a guy being rough with me in my room.
Hmm... Could it be that brother of yours you like so much?
N-No, of course not!
C'mon, we all know you have a thing for him!
N-No I don't...
No...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
I came!
That was so cute!
Okay, next we'll...
Does this feel good?
It does! Your tits feel so good, Mina!
Are you getting turned on from my boobs?
You're making such a pathetic-looking face.
If you're that rough, I'm gonna...
C'mon, let it all out!
I'm cumming!
Incredible!
It's still throbbing!
Mina, that's...
So big!
I can't resist my brother's dick anymore!
I want this dick to mess me up even more!
I want it to fuck me up so bad!
Mina, you're being too rough!
Cum! I want to drink your hot cum!
Mina!
My brother's semen!
It's so yummy!
Damn, you're so good at this.
We really shouldn't go any further...
Hey!
How am I supposed to hold myself back?!
Just make it look like you're dancing.
Wait!
Stop! You can't put it in!
We can't be doing this!
My brother's dick...
It's inside me!
I was trying to hold myself back,
but your dick is just too much!
C'mon, shake that ass, you slut.
So good! Your dick feels so good!
You're ramming against my womb!
I love this feeling!
Yes... Yes... Yes!
More! Give it to me harder!
It's going wild inside me!
Fuck me up!
Make me lose my fucking mind!
Mina, I'm going to...
That's fine. Let's do it together!
I'm cumming!
Yes! Cum inside me!
Big Bro!
That was amazing...
I fucked up!
They definitely know now!
Huh?
Am I safe?
Oh, sorry, Mina...
I'm a bit busy here, so I wasn't paying attention.
Thank god! They didn't hear me!
Okay, what do we have next?
It's time for Mina's confession!
C-Confession?
Wh-What am I c-confessing?
It's so obvious you've got the hots for him.
Totally! C'mon, ask him out!
Later, Mina!
Best of luck!
We're back to being siblings, right?
Yeah...
So, listen, I, uh...
I like you.
I've liked you for forever, Big Bro!
I've wanted to call you Big Bro for so long now!
You lusting over my body made me so happy!
I feel the same way. I like to have a dirty little sister.
I'm so happy!
Starting today, I'm your personal cock sleeve, Big Bro!
This cock... Big Bro's cock!
I'm going to fill your womb to the brim with cum.
Do it!
Ram your massive cock into your slutty sister's little pussy.
You love it when I'm rough, don't you?
You're turning my cunt into a hot fucking mess!
You're gonna break my pussy!
This is like a dream come true!
I've finally told him how I feel!
I love you, Big Bro!
I love you so much!
I'm going to cum inside!
Yeah, give it to me!
Give it to me, hard!
Being cummed inside feels so fucking amazing!
You're going to impregnate me!
I'm so happy!
Congrats, Mina!
Mission complete!
So he was your brother!
Wait, what?
Now then, to commemorate you two finally
hooking up, let's have a little show.
C'mon, Mina! Sing!
This can't be happening!
Karaoke
Big Bro!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч