What are your hands doing down there, Nii-san?
Not only are your boobs big, but your butt is too, Ririna.
You've got something big right here too.
I got to see something good this morning.
How many times do I have to tell
you to knock before coming in...
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: May | Timing: vltouch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Younger Sister Paradise 2
ep 2: A Possessive Virgin's break
Seeing how you had to change,
did you do it in the morning?
It's because you're so perverted.
I have been trying to forget about the other day, but...
It has been stuck in my head...
Sisters that I'm very proud of.
Sorry, Momoka!
At the age when even flowers lose their beauty,
she is a breathtakingly beautiful girl.
Even my underwear is wet.
Huh?
Oh, no. Looks like I put on some
weight around my bum again.
I have to cut down on the sweets.
Momoka, sorry about earlier.
Don't look at my bum or tummy!
This is my other sister, Momoka.
I'm so sorry, Momoka.
She does everything around the house by herself.
That's all right, Onii-chan. I'm not mad at all.
She is like my mom.
But you'd better knock next time.
I had a favor to ask of you,
so I couldn't help but barge in.
Me?
I'm at my wits end.
I was going to see if you could help me...
What's the matter?
You rarely call me to your room.
Are you looking to have a Life Consultation, Momoka?
Onii-chan, I am ready for this, so anytime is okay.
Huh?
No? Is this not enough?
W-Wait a sec...
Showing you my body like this doesn't help?
But, I don't know what to do when boys get aroused.
No, I just wanted to borrow some lead for my pencil.
Really?
You were badly mistaken, Momoka.
What are you doing, Momoka?
I got in the mount position.
You'd better be ready for it.
No one has managed to escape from this.
Ready for what?
It's all your fault.
While I was cleaning your room,
I found a bunch of naughty books.
I took a look, and there were many
things that I didn't know about.
That got me curious.
Hey, Momoka?
Can I try some things with you?
Wow, this is really hot.
And it's getting hard.
You talk about Ririna-chan's boobs all the time,
but mine are growing too.
No, Momoka... I'm cumming...
Huh? What am I supposed to do?
Like this?
Looks like it's still full of energy.
Does that mean my boobs were no good?
No, that's not it In fact...
I'll try harder this time.
I kissed Onii-chan's penis.
No, Onii-chan...
No, Onii-chan... No...
No! No!
I want to have sex with you, Momoka.
Sex? But Onii-chan...
Otherwise, I wont be able to relieve myself.
But either way...
You're going to have your way with me.
You gazing at me like Mr. Wolf, Onii-chan.
That's because you are so cute, Momoka.
Really? Thank you.
So a kiss awakens not only a princess,
but also a naughty wolf, huh?
Onii-chan...
Does it hurt?
I don't mind if you get rough, Onii-chan.
I'm okay...
So please, become one with me.
Onii-chan's penis is so... so.
Together with you...
Together... Closer together!
I want you to hurry up and push it deep inside of me.
I feel it!
I feel your penis... I feel it deep inside of me.
Your penis.. Your penis is so big.
Onii-chan... Onii-chan...
This is the first time I've had you inside me.
I want more... morel
Please cum lots!
So much... So much... So much...
If I don't get filled with you...
You know, both my body and mind are filled with you.
But, it looks like you're not satisfied yet.
Do you want to do it again?
You can be wilder, okay?
Reach deep inside of me.
Oh, no. I feel like I can talk dirty when I'm having sex.
How deep is deep?
Um, that's..
Well... Deep inside of my cunt.
Onii-chan...
If you suddenly thrust so hard...
The sperm inside me is going to flow out.
Again...
This time, I want to cum with you while we kiss.
Together with Onii-chan...
This is amazing! Your penis reaches to so deep.
Not yet.. Go deeper!
Momoka, let's cum together this time.
I want to cum with you, Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, Onii-chan...
Having your penis to myself...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan!
Hey! Geez you're so perverted.
Don't tell me, you want to do it again?
I'm glad that my first time was with you, Onii-chan.
The summer break with my sisters has just started.
Nii-san, we can't.
We shouldn't be doing this every night.
Geez, you're so perverted.
Nii-san...
I love you.