Onii? Did sex with me feel good?
H-Hiharu...
Stir up my pussy with your dick more!
Onii-chan? My boobs feel so fluffy and good, don't they?
Y-Yeah...
Let me know if you're in the mood.
I'll always be ready.
S-Sakura...
H-Huh?
I... I can't move.
Huh? I kinda feel...
I kinda feel good...
Z-Zakuro?! Hinata?!
Oh, nii-sama, I see you've finally awoken.
Good morning, onii-chan!
Imouto Paradise 03 2
W-What are you two doing?!
Hinata expressed an interest in the male body,
so I'm using yours to educate her.
Hinata, if you stroke the dick, it gets bigger.
Wow, it just keeps getting bigger and bigger!
S-Stop!
W-We're siblings!
That does not bother me too much.
After all, I love you, nii-sama.
I don't mind either.
I love you, onii-chan!
It's not a matter of love or not!
Uh, why does my dick feel so tight?
I tied the base of it up with a hair tie.
It's so you don't cum too quickly.
Do you really have to go so far?!
Onii-chan's dick's so big...
It looks like your pre-cum has begun
to trickle out of your dick, nii-sama.
Hinata, this tastes quite pleasant.
Hey! Stop!
Nii-sama, your dick is twitching so violently
and there's so much of your dirty liquids.
I'll be sure to suck out all of this liquid for you.
I just felt another throb inside me.
Nii-sama, how does it feel to excite
both of your little sisters this much?
Zakuro, your mouth is so good!
It's hanging onto me so tight!
Your dick is swelling up inside of me.
Amazing!
I-I...
I'm already so wet!
I'm getting so wet!
Onii-chan, can you see it?
Hinata!
Nii-samas dick is reacting to seeing Hinata's pussy.
Onii-chan, I can't stop this feeling!
In that case, you should have
nii-sama suck that feeling out of you.
Okay...
W-Wait, Hinata!
Maybe like this?
Onii-chan, hurry up and lick my hot pussy.
H-Hinata, wai...
H-Hurry!
Wai...
It's like electricity's running through my body!
Why do I feel like this?!
Hinata, your wet pussy's drenching my face!
Nii-sama, don't you feel bad about leaving Hinata like that?
Guess I have no choice!
I'll make you cum! Get ready!
Onii-chan, you're so amazing!
My stomach feels so hot!
Hinata, that's not your stomach, that's your pussy.
M-My pussy feels like it's going to melt!
Nii-sama, I'm quite turned on, myself.
I'm going to use you to quell this fire within me.
H-Hey, Zakuro! D-Don't... Stop!
Nii-sama's dick is entering me...
Slowly...
Y-You're so tight!
Don't worry, I'll welcome your entire dick inside of me!
Your dick is filling every last part of me!
Amazing. I never knew your dick
felt this pleasurable, nii-sama!
I can feel you, nii-sama!
Your tip's rubbing against me!
It's knocking against my womb!
I-It's so tight!
I feel like I'm gonna cum!
I'm not finished yet.
Do your best to make both your sisters cum, nii-sama!
I-I can't... I'm gonna cum!
It's not coming out!
It's going back inside!
Nii-sama, I can tell that you're about to burst.
You want to cum, but you can't.
That really turns me on.
I want to put onii-chan's dick inside me too!
You really love to learn, don't you, Hinata?
I like that.
Learn to your heart's content.
Now watch as you get penetrated by nii-sama's dick.
Onii-chan, put it inside me...
I'm not responsible for whatever happens now!
Onii-chan's dick's inside me!
It's so tight! I can't go in!
Hinata, are you okay?
It hurts, but I want your dick!
You got it!
Nii-sama, how does your perverted sister's pussy feel?
It's so tight, narrow, slipper, and hot!
I'm already gonna...
Onii-chan, my pussy feels like it's becoming really weird!
It seems that you have become
a complete captive of his dick as well, Hinata.
No... onii-chan's coming so hard inside me!
Hearing your moans makes me want his dick again.
Nii-sama's dick's inside me!
It's rubbing against my womb!
It's so tight!
I-I'm gonna...
Wait, nii-sama.
Nii-sama, your dick is throbbing.
Are you about to cum?
It's going back in my balls!
Onii-chan, I want your hard dick thrusting inside me again!
Fine! Whatever happens, happens!
So good!
I can tell it's making me feel so good inside!
Nii-sama, you're so hard!
I keep feeling this hot thing coming from inside me!
Hinata, that's what it feels like to cum.
I'm about to cum as well!
I'm gonna cum too!
That certainly was a bit rough
this early in the morning.
Geez, both Zakuro and Hinata...
Nii-san...
That was Rika.
Is she in my room?
Nii-san's smell gets me so hot!
I can't stop my hands!
This is all his fault!
If he saw me like this...
Um... Rika?
N-N-Nii-san?!
Um, this... this isn't what it looks like!
Uh, I don't think it's anything else but what it looks like.
No matter how you look at it, you were mastur...
D-Don't say it!
Just keep the rest to yourself!
Do you want to have sex with me, Rika?
Huh? No, I...
We're siblings.
I want to have sex with you, Rika.
W-Wait, nii-san!
W-We can't!
Dummy! You big dummy!
You can't do these things with your sister!
Your boobs are so small and cute, Rika.
Don't call them small!
That's just rude!
Don't play with my nipples like that!
Don't rub my boobs like that either!
They're small, but they're very springy.
What about...
N-No! Don't bite them!
It looks like they like it though,
with the way they're getting hard.
Th-That's not true!
I can't wait any longer!
I'm going to put my dick inside you, Rika!
Huh?!
N-No, you can't!
You definitely can't do that!
We're siblings!
It's inside!
His entire dick is inside me! It's so big!
It's so big that it feels like it's gonna break me!
Having sex with him is turning me on so much!
Wh-Why are you so turned on from
having sex with your sister, you pervert?!
You're turned on too, aren't you, Rika?
Your pussy's so wet and your dirty juices are pouring out!
I'm not turned on!
D-Don't be so rough all of a sudden!
You're going to make me go crazy like that!
If you're not turned on, this should be nothing to you!
Okay, I admit that it feels good.
Having sex with you turns me on!
Shit, I'm about to cum!
I'm gonna cum too! We'll cum together!
It feels so much better than masturbating!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum with your dick!
I'm cumming!
Y-You came inside me...
I'm not done yet.
We can go again, right?
This time, I'll do you from behind.
I just came, so I'm still really sensitive...
Hey, this hole up here's sticky as hell.
Nii-san, where do you think you're touching?!
That's my asshole!
I bet since you masturbate all the time,
anal turns you on too.
L-Like hell if would!
N-Nii-san's finger's in my ass... It's so tight!
It's pretty loose.
I bet my dick would fit.
No! No!
Don't put it in!
Nii-san's dick is coming in!
It's spreading out my asshole!
N-Nii-san, stop!
It's so tight!
Nii-san's entire dick is coming inside!
My ass felt really tingly when you
pulled your dick out of me a little.
Looks like you're getting used to it.
Your ass is so dirty!
I-I don't know anything about that!
It feels good for me.
Does it feel good for you?
O-Of course it doesn't!
It just feels like my insides are being stirred up.
It hurts, that's all!
I guess I'll just have to get you more used to it!
Y-You're being too rough!
You got even tighter!
Your ass-pussy's the best, Rika!
Why is it starting to feel good?!
Tell me!
Tell me to pump my hot cum into your ass!
I-I can't say that!
My ass is getting hotter and hotter!
Say it or else I take out my dick!
Nii-san, shoot your cum inside my ass-pussy!
Fill me with your cum!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Nii-san, you were too rough...
That was my first time doing anal...
But it felt good, didn't it?
Th-That's...
No comment.
If you ever wanna masturbate again,
you know where to find me.
I don't care.
So who are you going to choose, nii-sama?
Me, of course, right, onii?
Onii-chan, do you hate me?
O-Of course I don't!
I love you, Hinata!
I love Rika and Hiharu too!
I love Zakuro and Sakura too!
I love all of you!
How am I supposed to choose one of you?!
Then how about we each take
a different day of the week by age?
I'm down!
I'm on Monday then!
You're the fourth oldest, so you'd be on Thursday.
Then I'm on Friday!
Then I guess that would put me on Wednesday.
And then Saturdays and Sundays
you do it with all of us, onii!
A-All of you?!
I-I guess so?
Yay!
Then I guess I'll have to do my best
to rest you up on Monday.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч