So, you use that here and... huh?
Where's my ruler?
I'm pretty sure it should be here...
– Hey, Riko-chan, I can see your panties!
– Where is it?
Onii-chan?
Where are you looking?
As we were getting closer to summer break, my mother set
some conditions for me getting an allowance from her.
And those conditions were...
Riko-chan?
Onii-chan's looking underneath your skirt!
Math
It's my turn now. Riko-chan, you can take a break.
Modern
japanese
Why do I even have to do this?
I can't believe I have to be taught by you.
Onii-chan, if you don't take being a tutor seriously,
I'm gonna tell mom on you.
Don't come crying to me if you lose your allowance.
But, you know...
The way you teach makes everything so easy
to understand. It really helps me out.
Well if you put it that way... that makes me happy.
You're even easier to understand
than the teachers at school.
Don't you think so too, Miu-chan?
Yeah, I guess.
I do think it shows your good side,
but it doesn't excuse your behavior at all.
Stop feeling embarrassed over being complimented.
I'm not embarrassed at all. I'm just telling him thanks.
This girl is so two faced.
Oh, no I wasn't talking about you, Riko-chan.
I was talking about my stupid brother
over there getting full of himself.
I'm not getting full of myself or anything.
Don't do anything vulgar like that in front of my friend.
You say that, but it's hard to resist Riko-chan's advances.
At the same time,
I don't want Miu-chan to hate me either.
What is this crappy situation?
"It's okay if there are
some "benefits", right?"
"Be cautions of Riko-chan
and avoid all skinship."
Be cautious of Riko-chan and avoid all skinship.
It's okay if there are some "benefits", right?
Riko-chan, your boobs are pressing against me,
so do you think you could just go a little,
just a little farther away from me?
What? You're such a perv, onii-chan.
I don't think I'm being that clingy to you.
P-Perv?! Y-You see, Riko-chan, you're a pretty girl,
so a lot of guys would misinterpret this situation.
Gotta be careful, right?
You're right. I'll be more careful from now on.
W-W-Wait, Riko-chan, you're not in the wrong here, okay?
It's really your fault because you peeked up her skirt
and got happy from her boobs touching you.
Agh, quiet down, she can hear you from downstairs!
Also, I wasn't peeking up her skirt!
It just so happened that I saw her panties
because of the way her skirt was. It wasn't my fault!
Also, I didn't touch her boobs at all.
She just forced them onto my back.
It might've felt good, but I didn't touch them!
I'm really sorry about today.
I'll see you later.
My little sister and her friend are too
erotic, my dick won't go down!
Original Animation Disc: My little sister and her
friend are too erotic, my dick won't go down!
The flat chested, long black hair
tsundere little sister, Miu Arc.
Girls are so complicated.
Onii-chan?
Got a second?
Miu?
Something wrong?
Riko-chan says that she's not
coming back for tutoring anymore.
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Why do you look so disappointed?
Just because Riko-chan's chest is big,
doesn't mean you had to look at it so much.
I-I didn't! I swear!
You're totally lying. You're staring at women's
breasts even just walking around town.
But I guess Riko-chan is pretty on top of having a big chest.
Are you bothered because your chest is on the smaller side?
Wh-Who said anything about that?
You're such an idiot, onii-chan!
Well, I think you're fine the way you are, Miu.
They're cute and I don't think their size is particularly bad.
Wh-Where are you looking while saying that?!
You lecher! Pervert!
All I was trying to say is that when it comes to cuteness,
you're not inferior in any way to Riko-chan.
So a big boob lover like you really
does like someone like Riko-chan?!
What are you saying, Miu?
If you're not infatuated by big boobs,
then my boobs should be fine, right?
You've been staring at my boobs all this time.
Miu, what are you...
What am I... Just forget it!
Why are you mad?
I said forget it, didn't I?
Didn't you understand?
You're such an idiot, onii-chan! Blockhead!
Miu? You...
If you love me, I want you to kiss me this time.
Miu, I love you.
Onii-chan.
Miu, can I touch your breasts?
I want to know you better.
As long as you're gentle.
Wait! Wait a second!
Directly?!
It tickles!
Don't pull my nipple!
So? Are you disappointed by how small they are?
How could I be disappointed?
You're so cute, Miu.
This is so embarrassing.
Show me both your breasts, Miu.
Okay.
They're so smooth.
They're the perfect size for my hands.
Well, I'm sorry that they're so small.
I bet it'd feel better if they were bigger, wouldn't it?
That's not true at all.
It feels as if they were made for my hands.
What are you say...
Your nipples are getting hard.
So it feels good?
That's not...
It feels all tingly! Stop...
That feels... It feels good I think.
Could I look at this too?
I want to see what's happening down here.
Huh? Down here... do you mean...
No!
This is too embarrassing!
It's too embarrassing in this position!
Don't look at it!
It looks kind of tight.
I think you're getting wetter from being aroused.
That's not...
It all comes at once after you start getting wet.
Onii-chan, no! Don't let it make any sounds!
Look, my finger went in.
You sucked it inside you. Can you tell?
That... My insides feel good!
Stop twirling around my nipple like that!
Onii-chan, I... I can't!
I can't!
Miu, I love you.
I'm sorry if this hurts.
It's coming inside!
It hurts! Onii-chan's dick is coming inside me!
Miu, your insides are so wet.
It feels so good.
It's coming! It's coming in!
Ow! It hurts!
It really hurts!
Sorry. I just couldn't hold myself back.
I'm okay.
It's okay. Make yourself feel good inside me.
I'll be gentle so it doesn't hurt.
No, I...
I'm losing my mind!
Onii-chan! Onii-chan! Onii-chan!
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
I'm right here with you, aren't I?
Miu, your insides are so wet and tight... it feels so good.
No, don't say something so embarrassing!
This is it, right? This is where you feel it the most.
No, not there!
You're making me go crazy!
Miu, I'm cumming!
Onii-chan!
So...
So, listen, onii-chan.
Does this mean that you're mine, and mine alone, now?
Yeah, I'm yours and you're mine. We're lovers now.
I'm going to beat you up if you look
at another woman's chest, okay?
I don't like the sound of that. I'll make sure that
I don't look at any other woman's chest but yours, Miu.
Th-That sounds fine.
Okay then, starting today, we're lovers, right?
Hmph. If you insist so much,
I guess I'll play along and be your girlfriend, onii-chan.
That image of Miu was the cutest version
of her I'd ever seen in my entire life.
My little sister and her friend
are too erotic, my dick won't go down!
Mom, look!
Look, I got my first ninety percent on a math test!
What? Onii-chan's effort has nothing to do with this.
This is all because of my own efforts.
How can you even say that, my little sister?
But if everything goes smoothly, then...
Onii-chan, I have a question about Math
that you really need to help me with,
so make sure you're awake,
because I'll come back later, okay?
Yeah, that's fine, but, Miu,
I heard that you got a good score on our test.
Don't you think that's because I pulled
an all-nighter to create a review sheet for you...
Hey, Miu, your onii-chan's
about to pass out. You ready yet?
Miu?
Huh? Where is she?
She's sleeping?! She didn't even change her clothes.
Miu, wake up.
If you don't wake up, you're gonna suffocate.
Crap.
If she's not waking up even after I pinched her nose, then...
Time for a little prank.
Time for a little prank!
Still not waking up?
Onii-chan...
So, she's not actually awake, right?
My hands are just moving by themselves!
I kinda stripped her, but this is a bad idea, right?
Yeah, no, this is definitely a bad idea.
Wh-What should I do?
It looks like she's about to wake up.
It's her fault for calling me out here
and then being so defenseless.
Okay, before she wakes up, let's just...
At least this way, even if she wakes up, she won't hit me.
She's wet.
So I guess it feels good even if she's asleep.
I'm not too sure how I feel about this, but...
Onii-chan...
Is she awake?
She's still asleep.
Yep, I'm never letting her sleep over at anybody's house.
She's not even awake, but she's squeezing me so hard!
Onii-chan... I love you.
Onii-chan...
My boobs feel good...
It's so tight!
Her nipples are so hard!
I can't hold back anymore! Miu! Miu!
I'm cumming!
She may be my little sister,
but is she really going to be okay like this?
I guess for now, I'll just put her pajamas on her.
Onii-chan... I love you.
She's so honest when she's asleep though.
It was just another normal morning.
The weather was nice and it was a beautiful day.
It was the morning after I had tasted something delectable.
Okay, see you later.
Miu, wait a second.
What? Were going to be late if you don't hurry.
Wait, what are you doing? Stop it, onii-chan!
Stop what?
What am I doing? I'm taking off your panties.
I know that! But that's not the point...
The skirt's not that short,
so it shouldn't be that much of a problem, right?
Of course it is.
There's no way I could go commando to school!
Your buttons clash with your outfit,
so I'm taking them all off.
What are you doing? You're ruining my clothes!
This bra is too flashy too. I'll be confiscating it.
Y-You pervert!
Come on, if you're too loud, they'll notice.
Y-You!
I can't believe you're doing this to me.
Both my hands won't be enough to cover this.
What'll happen if there's a strong breeze or something?
Come on, Miu, we're gonna be late.
Let's go already.
Let go of my hand!
Will this really be okay?
I hope we don't run into anyone we know.
Things are just getting started.
It's so packed in here.
Isn't this bad?
We're gonna be late if we don't take this train.
Look, if you stand here, you'll be fine, right?
Seriously, there are always so many people on this train.
It'd be easier if we were on the train
going the opposite direction.
Yeah, that's true. Getting used to a packed
train isn't something that usually happens.
Wait, onii-chan, stand a little farther away from me.
It's so packed in here. I don't think that's possible.
– Hey, onii-chan, what are you doing?
– You have a quiz coming up soon, right? Are you studying for it?
Huh? What are you...
No, first, what are you doing with this hand?
Don't be so loud. You're the one who'd
hurt the most from being heard, right?
What are you going to do if someone finds out?
Really, stop, onii-chan!
The doors aren't gonna open on
this side of the train, so don't worry.
So basically you're saying that you're not gonna stop?
You're kidding! I don't believe you!
I hate you, onii-chan! You're such an idiot! A big idiot!
Are you okay, Miu?
What are you thinking?
People are gonna find out!
I'm serious. Please, stop.
If you pretend like we're talking to each other,
people are gonna be suspicious.
Ever since you stated teaching me, I think I've started
to understand things a little bit better, onii-chan.
That's right. You learn by doing something
over and over again, don't you?
Y-Yeah. I did the practice questions
you made for me several...
Don't rub it so hard!
But isn't that the way you like it?
You're a fast learner after all.
I don't think I'm that fast of a learner.
But more importantly...
Don't stir me up there!
Hm? Sorry, I didn't catch that.
You're such a meanie, onii-chan!
Stop touching there!
Yeah, you should depend on me when
you're having any kind of difficulties.
There there.
Just you remember this. I'll... I'll get you back for this.
Hurry up and let me go.
Yeah, but you're just clinging
onto me with your entire body.
Who said I am?
You're so mean, onii-chan!
You say that, but it's your fault that you're this cute...
Onii-chan, I can't breathe. Back up a bit.
People can see my boobs from outside.
Aren't you showing it to them?
N-No, of course I'm not!
D-Don't! Don't spread it! Stop!
It's gotten really wet.
Let's plug it up.
Y-You're so mean, onii-chan.
I don't even know what you mean by that.
You'll understand soon.
N-No, stop! Don't move it like that.
Don't be so rough!
Well, you're not wearing any panties,
so this is the only way to plug it up, right?
And who's fault is that? If you keep moving like that,
you're going to make too much noise!
I think your voice is louder than any sound I'm making.
If you let out an erotic voice like that, they're gonna notice.
Why are we doing something so strange?
You really think this is strange?
This isn't too unusual.
How isn't this unusual?
This is weird!
Well if you stop acting cute, this is what you get!
No, not there!
Your dirty juices just keep pouring out.
You're in public. Aren't you embarrassed?
But, but... Oni-chan,
it's so embarrassing with you being so rough!
But I can't stop! I can't stop!
Are you okay, Miu?
We're almost at our stop.
No, I'm...
Onii-chan!
I'm cumming!
Me too. I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Did that feel good, Miu?
We're almost at our stop.
No, I can't. I can't walk anymore.
Do I really have to?
This is all your fault, onii-chan.
Here, hold onto me.
I think it'd be better if you rested on a bench.
Onii-chan, you're such an idiot.
You pervert. Lecher.
You made us go so far in front of all those strangers.
What were you gonna do if somebody found out?
Let's rest here for a bit before going, okay?
Here you go. Water.
I forgot that I'm naked!
Y-you idiot, you're being too loud!
Hey, that girls naked underneath her uniform.
You're kidding! There's no way!
That's a sign that something good's gonna happen!
Nothing to see here! There's no way
that my little sister is naked! Please back away.
She's not nake...
You idiot! You idiot! What are you saying, onii-chan?!
N-No, that's not what I meant!
Um, I...
No!
Don't look!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Thank you for this bliss!
Please come with me to my company!
K-Knock it off!
Don't invite her, you creeps!
Hey, you! Stop taking pictures!
Don't touch my little sister!
Stop! Stop making such a crowd. Go away!
Onii-chan, you idiot!