Yay!
Today my friend set up a mixer's party.
The girls were all beautiful,
but one of them seems not so into it.
Okay, next is Miina-chan's self-introduction!
Right, it seems like I already met her somewhere.
Not just once, maybe a couple of times.
A wavy flaxen hair.
Seemingly mischievous canine teeth.
And this voluptuous body.
Yeah, this girl is...
I am Miina.
It's my first time in a mixer party. Nice to meet you.
Isn't this my little sister?!
Hey, doesn't that Miina have the hots for you?
No, that's not the case.
You've been looking at that guy all this time.
Feeling some good vibes with him?
Oh, why is he here?
To think that I was forced to come,
only to find my brother here...
This is the worst.
Okay, it's the time for that staple
event. Shall we get started!
The king's game!
Imouto Bitch ni Shiboraretai❤
I Want to be Squeezed by My Bitch Little Sister❤
King's Game with My Little Sister❤
~The Story of Me and My Little Sister Unexpected King's Game in a Mixer Party~
This is really embarrassing.
S-Seriously?!
Will we have to do things like these?
Everyone will show their tits today!
Let's do the next round!
Who's the king?
I'm the king!
Okay, #1 will...
show her...
panties to #5!
Wai—
I am #5.
The king's order is absolute!
Why? I don't want to!
You will have to follow the order
regardless of what it is.
Even though my brother is here...
I'm even wearing this kind of panties.
Panties!
I think I have no choice...
H-Here.
This should be enough.
Miina has been expecting to get laid.
Stop staring at it so much!
I'm sure she's not wearing a bra.
Underneath those panties is Miina's pussy.
Miina, that guy's got a boner.
He totally fell for you.
Why are you getting hard from your little sister's panties?
Next is, #3 and #4 plays a pocky game.
Okay...
Is he really gonna do it?
Doing it with my brother...
No! I shouldn't be doing this!
Next is, bare chest massage!
Miina's tits... Bare tits!
My brother saw my tits!
No!
This is bad!
If you grope me that much...
Next is, super pee pee rub-a-dub time!
Wait, you're getting too much into this.
Hey, you should help him get off.
You can... fap on me.
A guy's masturbation looks intense.
Give me your semen.
Right here.
Miina!
This flow of events is bad news...
For siblings to do those things...
It has a strong smell...
My brother's semen...
I think I got aroused from it.
I stained my panties...
Have I gone out of my mind?
Oh, Miina-chan! Welcome back.
Tell me if you're gonna come!
My bad, sorry!
Okay, next #3 will be masturbating!
Oh, Miina-chan is #3.
I can't do such a thing!
Even if I did a fellatio?
That's...
Do I really need to?
In front of my brother,
am I gonna masturbate?
Miina, are you wet?
Y-You don't have to say it.
You get excited while being watched.
That's not...
What do you imagine
while rubbing one out?
I imagine...
A guy violating me in my own room...
Is that guy... your beloved brother?
N-No, he's not!
You have a brother complex, right?
T-That's not true.
No good!
Something's coming.
I'm coming!
I peed myself.
That's so cute!
Well then, next will be...
Does this feel good?
It's good! Miina's tits!
Do my tits make you feel good?
You're making a very pathetic face.
If you do it that much, I'm...
Here, here! Shoot out a bunch!
I'm coming!
Amazing!
You're still energetic!
Miina, I'm...
How big!
My brother's dick has blown away all the worries I have.
I want to be violated by my brother's dick.
I want him to make a mess of me.
Miina, you're being too rough!
Shoot it all out, I want to drink your semen.
Miina!
Onii-chan... Onii-chan's semen.
It's delicious.
[King's Game]
Yay!
Miina, you're a genius!
Just shut up!
Wait!
I can't hold myself back from something like this!
No matter what happens,
just pretend you're dancing.
W-Wait!
No! Anything but that!
You can't!
My brother's dick went inside!
I tried to hold back all this time!
We're gonna get in trouble for this!
Hey there you pig, keep on dancing!
Okay!
Your dick feels good!
It's reverberating deep in my womb!
This is the best!
Good, it feels good!
More... fuck me more!
My pussy is coming!
It's trembling!
I'm going crazy!
Miina, I'm coming again!
Okay! Let's come together!
I'm coming!
Come! Come inside me!
Onii-chan!
Coming inside me feels the best!
Oh no, I did it!
I'm sure everyone saw us!
Eh...
I-I guess it's still fine?
Sorry, Miina.
We're busy here that we didn't see you dance.
Thank goodness, they never saw us!
Well, well, what's next?
Miina's confession time!
What do you mean confession?
You obviously like him.
That's right, Miina. It's your
chance to get a boyfriend!
Well then, Miina. I wish you luck!
We're back to being siblings, right?
Yeah...
Miina, you see...
I love you.
I love onii-chan ever since!
I always wanted to call you onii-chan.
Even today, I was happy when you accepted my body.
Me too. I love my sexy little sister.
I'm glad.
Starting today, I will be onii-chan's onahole.
Dick...
Dick! Onii-chan's dick!
I'll be filling up your womb again.
Yay, creampie!
Plunge your dick in your little sister's pussy!
You can't get enough of it
hitting deep your womb, right?
Your dick is rubbing my pussy so hard!
You're tearing my pussy!
This is like a dream!
I'm glad that I confessed!
I love you, onii-chan!
I love you, onii-chaaaaaaaan!
Miina, I'm gonna shoot it inside!
'kay! I want it! I want it inside!
It's good!
I love creampies!
If you'll come that much, I'll be pregnant!
I'm happy!
Congratulations, Miina. You did it!
So he is your brother.
Wai— Ehhh...
So, should we put a show for this
special day you got to be together?
Miina, sing properly!
Woo-hoo!
This is impossible!
Onii-chaaaaaan!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project