No... Not there...
It feels so good...
I'm gonna cum!
Big Bro...
I Wanna Be Jerked Off by My Slutty Little Sister ♥
My Little Sister Is a Human Cock Sleeve ♥
Sayaka Is Big Pro's Personal Sex Toy
A hole?
There's a hole in the wall...
Is this one of her pranks?
Quit staring at me, you creep.
Yeah, probably not.
Is she not back home yet?
I hate to be a peeping Tom, but...
Oh, looks like she just got back.
Wait, she's masturbating? Am I really gonna watch?
This isn't enough...
Holy shit!
Is that my little sister's bare pussy?!
No... I can't stop!
I'm gonna cum...
I'm cumming!
Big Bro...
I'm just gonna pretend I didn't hear that last part...
Coward.
The more I think about it, the less it makes sense.
There's no way she wouldn't notice
such a huge hole in her wall, right?
Wait, could she possibly be an exhibitionist?
No, there's no way...
I'm home!
She's back!
What should I do?
Is it really okay for me to keep watching her masturbate?
So that's how you're going to play it?
Wh-Why is there a mushroom growing on the wall?
Well, I am pretty hungry. Guess I'll have a bite.
It's Big Bro's dick!
I can finally be true to myself!
Thanks to this hole, I can finally
have what I've always wanted!
I'm... cumming!
So warm...
So this is Big Bro's semen...
More...
I want more!
I'm so happy! I never thought
I'd be able to taste Big Bro's cock!
I love you, Big Bro!
I'm always rude because I'm too shy to say how I really feel...
The truth is, I've always loved you, Big Bro!
I'm cumming again, Sayaka!
Give it to me! Let me drink it!
I want to taste it even more...
My muscles are still sore from the club.
Maybe I should stretch them out.
Yeah, stretching against the wall
sounds pretty good right now.
She's talking about this, isn't she?
Today should be a safe day.
Er, I mean, that's what my horoscope said.
I wonder what it meant by that.
Oh, where did this cock sleeve come from?
C-Cock sleeve?
I can't believe I found a cock sleeve
just lying around. It's my lucky day!
Let's use it right away.
Wow, it's really tight!
Oh yeah, I wonder if Sayaka is done stretching.
Deep... It's going in so deep!
Your cock is smashing against my womb!
It's plowing so hard into me!
This cock sleeve is unreal!
More! Give it to me harder!
Stretch my hole wide open and make a mess out of it!
My pussy's taking the shape of Big Bro's cock!
Sayaka!
Cum! Pour lots of your stuff inside me, Big Bro!
Big Bro!
There's so much... My pussy's gonna break!
It's gonna pour out...
Wait, you were a...
Uh... You have opened the freshness seal of this product.
Huh?
You are now the registered user of this cock sleeve.
Sayaka...
Cock sleeves are the best when they're brand new!
Guess I'll be using this to get me off from now on.
Big Bro...
Since then, I've been using my sister
as a cock sleeve every day.
Let me pleasure you even more.
Enjoy your cock sleeve sister's tit fuck.
Wow, a tit fuck function?
This cock sleeve is cutting edge!
It even has a high-pressure feature!
Please cum to your heart's content.
Blow your load into this tit-pussy.
I'm cumming!
Rubbing my clit against your raw cock feels so good!
I really want it inside me!
I want it so bad!
Ding, ding! The cock sleeve is now ready for your dick.
Hey, you two! Dinner's ready!
B-Be there in a min...
It's inside!
Are you okay, Sayaka? Is something the matter?
No, I just need a few minutes.
I'll come real soon!
Geez, don't take too long, okay?
O-Okay...
Hey, we need to talk.
A boy from school confessed to me today.
Is that so? Good for you.
That's all you have to say?
Why'd I even bother?
You stupid horndog!
Geez, Big Bro...
I went to school wearing no panties like you asked.
See?
My heart was racing when he confessed.
I almost died from embarrassment.
So please reward me by messing up my pussy real bad!
Fine.
I want your dick so bad!
I'll mess you up just like you asked.
Your cock's inside!
I'm cumming just from that!
I'm cumming so hard!
Your dick's too good!
My mind's going blank! I can't think straight!
My pussy feels so good!
I'm going crazy!
You've been cumming nonstop!
Is that because you wore no panties to school?
Y-Yeah!
I'm gonna cum!
Don't spill a single drop!
I'm so happy!
I'm cumming!
Your semen...
Being filled with your thick semen is making me cum...
It feels so good that I'm peeing!
This isn't something siblings should be doing, but...
I've never been happier in my life!
I'm your personal cock sleeve, Big Bro, so...
Keep using me, okay?
Keep making love to me.
Of course!
Your body was made to squeeze out cum, wasn't it?
Yes! I was born to squeeze out your cum, Big Bro!
It's my privilege!
Give it to me! Plant your seed in me!
I'm at my limit!
I'm gonna cum!
Yes! Pour it all inside me!
Fill me to the brim with your seed!
I love you, Big Bro... I love you so much!
There's so much semen inside me!
Big Bro!
Big Bro...
I love you!
translator: hikarucon
timing: ragingheartsexcelion
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч