Onii-chan!
Mom and Dad said they won't be back for a month!
S-Sakura?! Why are you naked?!
Oh, nii-san?
R-Rika? You're naked too?!
Nii-sama?
Wh-Wha... You too, Zakuro?!
Onii, hurry!
H-Hiharu... You're even more daring than usual.
Onii-chan...
H-Hinata?
A dream?
The perky nipples... must've been Zakuro.
The flat chest must've been Hinata's.
Rika and Hiharu's breasts also have
their own unique traits to them.
And these plump breasts are Sakura's!
A dream that had all five of my
little sisters advancing on me.
I wish I could've stayed in that dream a little longer.
I wonder if that's something I actually want, deep inside me.
R-Rika?!
Wh-What are you...
What am I doing? I'm obviously pee...
Hey, nii-san, what are you looking at?!
Ah... Sorry, Rika!
Good morning, my perverted nii-sama.
Hiharu... Zakuro...
Th-That wasn't what it looked like.
Nuh-uh-uh, onii. If you wanna peek so badly,
do it when I'm in there.
Your jokes are as unhinged as ever, Hiharu.
Well, knowing you, I bet you were lost in your dirty
thoughts and didn't even notice that she was in there.
Ugh. I can't deny that. Pretty pathetic of me.
Hey, hey, so what are dirty thoughts?
H-Huh?!
Well you see, Hiharu, it's when our dear onii-sama begins
imagining the shape and such of our precious private parts.
Knock it off!
Don't stuff her head with this useless nonsense!
Geez, this morning just gets worse and worse.
I caught you, onii!
H-Hiharu?!
What are you doing?
Today's the day when I finally have sex with you, onii!
Huh?
I've been waiting forever for a time where nobody
would be around to bother us! Nows my chance!
Do you hear yourself?!
W-We're siblings!
Yep, we are.
A forbidden relationship.
Pretty hot, right?
But, I'm already prepared for this.
What'll happen if I do this, onii?
Oh? What's this hard thing, onii?
It's nothing!
It got hard so fast!
Now that it's this hard, there's only one thing left to do.
Onii, your thing is so hard and it's twitching!
Can I try putting it in?
I can't wait!
It hurts, but...
I'm really happy that the dick of the brother
I love so much is coming inside me!
Onii's dick is coming deeper and deeper
inside me... it's widening my pussy!
It hurts, but...
Onii's dick is all the way inside me!
Is this sex? It hurts and it's so tight...
It's like an electric current is running through my body!
It feels... good...
I can feel it twitching!
Maybe if I move, it'll be even more...
So, this is onii's dick...
It's so hot!
I can feel it! I can feel it moving around inside me!
I'm really having sex with you right now, aren't I, onii?!
I'm so happy!
H-Hiharu!
What about you? Are you happy, onii?
I'm happy! Your pussy's so wet! It feels amazing!
Onii, your dick got bigger again!
It still really hurts, but it also feels really good!
N-No! My mind's going blank!
Th-This is going to be a little embarrassing,
but I want you to give it to me from behind.
H-Hiharu!
I thought this was your first time!
I-I didn't think I'd feel this good!
Even though this is my first time,
it's starting to feel really good!
It turns me on every time it goes in and out of me!
Onii! Onii, give me more!
Hiharu, if you grip my dick that tightly, I'm...
I'm not gonna be able to hold back!
Onii, that's too early!
I guess that means my pussy just feels that good?
That's fine, then. Just cum inside me.
Actually, don't cum anywhere but inside me!
My pussy's gonna melt!
It-It's hitting my...
My body's getting so hot!
This is so amazing! I've never felt this way before!
N-No, I-I'm gonna...
Hiharu, let's do it together... you and me!
Onii!
I-It feels good to cum, doesn't it?
Hiharu...
Your hot stuff's coming out...
Onii, whenever you're feeling horny, just let me know, okay?
Making you cum's my job.
Well, onii, I'll see you around!
I was waiting for him to be all alone too!
I can't believe out of all the people,
he did it with Hiharu-chan!
But I can make him feel better than she can!
I know that was practically a surprise attack,
but having sex with my sister...
S-Sakura?
You could at least knoc...
S-Sakura?!
What's gotten into you?!
I had no idea that you wanted to have
sex with your own sister, onii-chan.
Don't tell me you know what
just happened between me and Hiharu...
I'm so jealous that Hiharu-chan got to do it with you.
I want to do it too!
H-Hey, don't touch there!
But it looks like you're already getting hard, onii-chan.
N-No I'm not!
You're always on my mind too, onii-chan.
This is my first time, but I'll try my best, okay?
It's practically bursting out. That can't be comfortable.
U-Uh, well...
I'll help you out, onii-chan!
W-Wait, don't...
W-Wow, your dick is this big, onii-chan?
Onii-chan, your dick is really sticky.
W-Well that's because of what I just di...
It's like this now because of what
you did with Hiharu-chan, right?
I'll clean you up.
It feels good for guys like this, right?
Your dick's gotten bigger, onii-chan!
Wow! It's getting bigger and it's going crazy inside me!
I'm starting to go a little crazy myself.
My heart's beating so fast!
S-Sakura, it's going down your throat!
There's something coming out from your tip!
C-Crap, I feel like you're going to suck it all out of me!
S-Sakura, if you rub it that tightly...
Sorry!
I-It'll feel better if I use something softer, right?
Huh?
It's a little embarrassing, but...
I-I'll try giving you a titfuck.
So? Does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
How about this?
Th-That's so intense!
Your dick's filling up my entire mouth, onii-chan!
There's a lot of slimy stuff coming out of it too!
C-Crap, I'm already about to cum!
Not yet!
I need to make you feel more and more pleasure!
I want to see you cum, onii-chan.
Wow, it's twitching!
I-I'm cumming!
Not yet!
Nope, not yet. Hold it in longer.
A lot of juices started coming out!
It's swelling up and twitching even more now!
Onii-chan, the twitching isn't stopping!
S-Sakura, I'm cumming!
Wow! You came so much!
Onii-chan, it's all pretty clumped together.
I'll help you cum even more!
Put your dick inside me, onii-chan!
S-Sakura...
Onii-chan, hurry! Hurry!
Your hot and hard thing is coming...
It's in!
Onii-chan's dick is coming inside!
Wow! Onii-chan, your dick is so big!
It's going to break my pussy!
It's all inside me!
It's reaching all the way inside me!
Your dick's hitting my G-spot!
It's reverberating inside me with every thrust!
Sakura, does it feel good?
My pussy feels so good!
It feels really good because your dick is so thick, onii-chan!
It's exciting my pussy!
S-Sakura, you're getting so tight deep inside!
Just hearing your voice makes me get tighter!
This tightness is really something!
Who's tighter? Me or Hiharu-chan?
Huh?
I'll make it even tighter!
I'll make it so tight, your dick will feel like it's being choked!
Your dick is practically glued to my pussy!
It's so good! It's driving me crazy!
I can tell the exact shape of your dick!
It's twirling around my insides!
Then let me mix it around some more
and make your pussy the shape of my dick!
You're being so rough all of a sudden!
Onii-chan! Onii-chan!
Your dick's going even deeper now!
It's hitting me so deep!
Your dick feels like it's on fire!
It's moving so wildly inside me!
Onii-chan, I feel so good!
My pussy's on fire! It's going to melt!
Sakura, you're so tight... Shit!
Onii-chan, it's okay!
Cum in my pussy!
Make me overflow with your cum, onii-chan!
I want to cum with you, onii-chan!
I'm cumming!
Make sure you cum a lot, onii-chan!
Onii-chan, did my pussy feel good?
Yeah, it was amazing.
I'm so happy!
Your dick was so warm and it had such a strong smell.
If you ever want to have sex, just let me know.
I'll study to make sure that
I make it feel even better next time!
You're such a hard worker, Sakura.
I look forward to our next time.
Onii-chan?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч