These are my proud little sisters.
Nanase
Their youthful beauty is spectacular.
You can't go wrong...
Hey.
with picking any of them!
Brother...
Sister Paradise
Secret Loss of Virginity
Like this?
Yeah, like that.
Yes, yes.
Harder, Momoka.
Ririna's kicks are getting more brutal by the day.
She should really be doing something else with her body.
When will you learn?
It is considered polite to knock before entering a girl's room.
Yeah, right.
Knock it off with the sarcasm.
This is one of my little sisters: Ririna.
She's an admirable student in all respects, and considered the achiever in our family.
Are you thinking about something immoral right now?
Nah, I was just thinking that you have great boobs.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'll kick you!
You already did.
Then don't make vulgar jokes like that!
Listen up.
Our parents won't be back until the end of the summer holiday.
You're the only man in the house, so you... you have to...
You have to act resonsibly.
So...
Otherwise I can't...
Um...
Otherwise you can't masturbate in peace?
When I went into the bath after you yesterday,
I found this.
Are you saying you think it's mine?
Well, you're a previous offender.
Let's not talk about that!
Let's assume it's mine.
What are you going to do?
Want me to explain the particulars?
I have some theoretical knowledge.
Are you sure?
You'll stick to your end of the bargain, right?
I'll do as you say, so don't abuse this situation.
You're making it look like I'm a bad guy.
Well, you are.
You're so selfish.
Even when I criticize you, you...
You don't change at all.
All you do is tease me.
You sniff my clothes while I take a bath.
You lick the things I used.
You're paranoid.
I'm not.
And anyway, I'm not really into sex at all.
You look like you enjoyed it a bit.
No!
I feel neutral about it...
It's my first time doing it.
Right.
They're getting pretty hard.
Stop that.
I'll be angry.
I hope you do, especially after I do this.
Stop that.
I have my own way of doing things.
No!
It tickles!
Stop it!
I don't want this!
I really don't!
No!
It's okay if you masturbate?
Don't talk about that!
No!
Stop—
Don't!
We have to stop!
Brother!
Do you want to come?
No, of course not!
No!
Brother...
You're the worst.
I really like your expression right now.
Don't say that.
I don't want to be seen d—
I'm going to come.
I'm going to come!
I'm coming!
Brother...
Brother?
I want to put it in.
But...
Are you saying no?
But it's my first time...
I'll be as gentle as I can.
Coming from you that's not saying much.
Ouch!
Are you not going to move?
Do what you want.
I want to get this over with.
Brother!
No!
You're so good!
You don't have to talk about it!
Do you hate this?
I don't know!
Hey...
It's good.
It's good!
It makes me happy when you say that.
Then I won't say it again.
I don't want to make you happy at all!
I'm gonna come.
I'm gonna come too.
No!
Wait!
Don't!
I said wait!
Don't come inside!
Not inside!
Brother...
I can feel your sperm inside.
I told you to stop.
Take it out.
I don't want your thing inside me forever.
I know you want it.
I...
No!
Your vagina has been loosed up good by masturbating.
That isn't true!
Are you trying to turn me into a slut?
You're the worst!
You're horrible!
You came inside again.
It was my first time...
Let's come together this time.
No! Brother!
Don't!
It's too big!
It feels weird!
No!
Stop!
No more!
I'll come!
I'm coming!
Please don't come inside me.
Do you understand?
No telling others about this.
Yeah, right there.
I got it.
I think I overdid it.
You got carried away.
I wanted you to be happy too.
If you try to wriggle out of this, I won't forgive you.
You have a responsibility now.