Last time...
After my father got remarried
he went right back to work,
so I had to live with my step mother and my 3 step sisters.
I am Kohinata Akira.
Later, I found a mysterious box in my father's room.
Then the goddess Inana suddenly appeared and made me sign a strange contract.
It said that before the next full moon
I had to get three bottles of
juice from the three girls,
in other words, their love juices.
If I succeed, any wish I have will be granted.
But if I can't...
...you will be visited with the greatest terror.
For the time being, I've only gotten one.
There are still two more to go.
Can I really finish this mission?
I.. mo.. u.. to.. (sister)
Younger Sister Juice
Second Squeeze
Encoder:
finwe
Translator:
sevle
Eh! Mama is not even tired yet. Amazing!
When I was in elementary, I was the best.
Strange. Aren't they supposed to be sleeping?
Ani, good morning!
Akira-kun, good morning!
Good morning...
Why are you two playing
jump rope dressed like this?
Why are you asking us why?
You want us to be like this!
Yeah! It's your wish!
Me? That's impossible!
That's right! It's not weird for me to wish for something like this.
Wait! My wish has come true, so will it...?
Then does it mean you guys
will do everything I say?
That's right, Akira-kun.
Yes, Ani.
Akira-kun, hurry up and untie the rope or I will get your father to scold you.
That's right Ani, why do you
have to do something like this?
Ani!
Even though they don't like it, they'll still do it.
This is my dream anyway, so I'll do anything I want.
Nana-chan, you're sweating a lot!
Then what about there?
Uwa...! Even this place is sweating a lot.
Let me take a closer look.
There's not only sweat...
You look like you're getting
excited. I'm gonna lick you now!
Ani, it tickles!
Akira-kun, what are you doing?
Please stop this instant, Nana-chan is your sister!
Ah? Are you jealous? Because I only do it with Nana-chan?
That's impossible!
For real?
No... don't.... no....
It hurts! What are you doing, Akira-kun?
Ani, it feels good...
Akira-kun, don't ignore me, answer me now!
Akira-kun, what are you doing?
I am playing with Nana-chan's secret place, Yukie-san!
It can't be...
I can't go on anymore, Ani...
I am going to come!
Don't do it, Nana-chan!
For doing something like
this, mama won't forgive you!
But...mama...I'm going to...
No fair, Nana-chan, only you get to feel good.
I'm sorry mama, but it feels too good.
Oh I see! You ARE jealous.
You look very sad, Yukie-san. Let me help you too~
Wah! It's so soft.
Not really, I am so happy!
So this is what housewife feels like...this sensitive!
No, that's not true!
No?
Then why is this part wet like this?
Is this sweat too?
Wah! Amazing! It's not only sweat.
Mama, it hurts!
Ani, only mama gets to feel good. That's not fair!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Then let me give you this one.
Ani, it feels good!
Is this because Nana-chan takes after mama?
That's right! Fingers alone are not enough, right...mother?
Ani!
Don't give up yet!
Nana-chan wants more right?
Don't, Akira-kun, don't pull it out yet!
I just know it, the real one is a lot better!
Akira-kun, only one is not enough.
Damn it! This mother is hard to satisfy! Then how about now?!
It feels good, it feels so good.
I am going to...
Going to cum? What about Nana-chan?
I'm going to cum too!
Then both of you, let's cum together.
Mama, when is father going to come back?
Mm... I am not sure when his work going to be over.
Mama, are you lonely just by yourself?
I'm all right, because I have you guys.
If it's just by the look, they are eating peacefully.
But we've already had a threesome, even if it was just a dream!
You said it this casually, are
you sure you are all right mom?
It's because this species called men are all perverts.
We don't even know what father is doing right this minute.
That's impossible
because he loves me so much.
Really? Father is very honest right?
Then who are you thinking about now?
What's wrong?
Akira-kun, can you remove
the thing that's next to you?
A spider?
This is really troublesome.
Miu is always a scaredy cat.
We are eating dinner now, so go back to your seats.
Yes!
Yes...
Akira-kun must be surprised. Miu-chan has always been like this since she was small.
Oh! So that's why...
Let's eat more everybody!
Yes.
Miu is always like that...
I hate having to walk this far to get to the toilet.
Mm? Who is it this late at night?
Miu-chan? Are you washing your clothes?
Miu-chan...
You wet the bed?
Even if it's only a little bit, it comes out immediately.
That's why I'm still shaking right now.
This is too embarrassing!
Have you told Yukie-san yet?
I never thought about telling her, so now it's too embarrassing to say it.
This kind of things happen a lot too.
Please don't tell anybody about this~~!
Okay. But you still have to tell her another day
and let her bring you to the
hospital to see what's wrong.
Get it?
I am happy for having a nice brother.
R..really? I'm happy too, for
having such a cute sister.
It's already very late, let's go back to sleep.
Yes, good night~
Good night.
Mm..? A cute sister?
Playing a sibling game?
Inana?!
There is not much time before the next full moon.
If you don't hurry up and fill
up the other two bottles...
If you don't finish what you
promised in the contract...
I know that already!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Where is mama?
She went shopping.
How do you do? I am Yuki's friend, Sudo Azusa! Nice to meet you!
H..hi! Nice to meet you too.
I came here to try out my new swimsuit today.
Enough already!
It doesn't matter!
Swimsuit~~?
Don't pay attention to this
guy, hurry up and let's go!
Wait...hold on a sec..!
Damn it! That guy is very horny. This is too embarrassing!
Every man in this world is horny.
If you are always this critical, you
will be alone for the rest of your life.
But it might be Akira-san is not
handsome at all because of that.
Or is it because you don't want me
to move in on him, so you lie to me?
T..that's impossible!
His outside looks ok, but
what's inside of him is a mess.
Then does it mean if I go out with your
brother, you won't have any problem at all?
It's ok with me. As your friend I
just disagree with you doing that.
How cute!
Really?
This one is good too. It fits you very well!
You can say that again.
Ah..! This kind is the worse!
Azusa, you have lots of hair over here.
Do you think so?
It must be because I'm always doing it with other guys!
It affects the hormones and causes the hair to grow longer and faster.
Yuki's is smooth.
I've already done everything that I can.
Not good! This is not the time to think about something like that!
If I don't fill up the bottles...
Oh yeah! Miu-chan might
be able to help me with this.
But it would somehow look like I'm forcing her.
What should I do?
If this one got wet, would it become transparent?
Let me see, let me see!
Hmm...it might...
Let's try it~
In the bathroom...
I am going to turn on the water.
Ok...
The water is very cold!
Yeah...
But if we are in the pool, there will be more water.
Yeah...that's true.
Stop it, Azu-san, it's cold!
Are you cold?
Really?
Yes.
Let's hurry up and take off our
clothes, we have to warm ourselves.
Let's hug each other in the nude~
Like if we were trapped inside
a hole in a field of snow?
Ok...
Then I am going to take off mine too.
I understand.
It's hot.
Is it?
But your lips are already turning purple.
No....not there...
Don't worry.
I only do these kind of things to boys.
Can you be a little more gentle?
No~
You're already this wet!
This is embarrassing.
You have to make me feel good too.
I-it feels good...
You taste delicious here. I like it!
More.. more... don't stop... lick me more..
No.. I'm too sensitive. Use your finger.
Like this?
Move it...back and forth...
More.. More.. Move it faster...
Amazing! Azu-san's so smooth!
Your finger...move it faster..
O-ok, I understand.
More...deeper...
Unbelievable! My whole finger is getting sucked in!
Good.. It feels good.. My body is going break down!
More.. Let me become wetter..
I think I should really listen to Akira and tell mama about it.
But, it's still too embarrassing to say it.
Will big brother do me a favor
and tell mama about it with me..?
Ah...! It surprised me!
Ah...stop scaring me..!
Ah, not good. I'm going to wet my panties again.
Ca.. can't hold it any more.
Made it in time...
No...don't lick it!
No.. not there...
Sigh...have to go to toilet again.
We....why are we doing something like this...?
I don't know either...
H..Hentai!!
Why am I always doing stupid things in front of Yuki-chan?
Am I playing too much?
So it was you again! What have you done again!?
Now, now, let's calm down now and listen carefully.
Are you ok? Are you hurt anywhere?
I..I am ok.. Th.. thank you very much..
Am I bothering you?
Brother will continue it with you.
Um...
I..it feels really good..
Brother!
Come.. come...
come.. come...
This is looking good, the whole bottle is filling up.
No, I...
I'm going to pee!
What should I do? What should I do?
I'm going to pee on the bed!
Somehow I made it in time.
I'm sorry, it's because it feels so
good the pee just starts to come out.
It's ok, you don't have to say sorry.
If you still have to go, just pee in the bucket.
Yes!
It's very hot...
That's right, brother just set
a fire on Miu-chan's body.
What's wrong?
I think I'm going to pee again.
Please don't look at me like this.
It already looks like this!
Huh? You stopped peeing already?
Yeah.
Is it because you saw this, so you closed up?
Yeah...it seems so.
Then let's use this time efficiently.
Try touching it.
Ah... it's big.
And it looks like yours is hot right?
Yes!
It's twitching.
Then will you do me a favor?
Eh?
This is just like a dream, I can't believe it!
Thank you, god!
It feels good.
Brother, did your pee come out too?
It seems so.
You were surprised, right?
Yes.
But it looks like I didn't wet my pants, but why?
Maybe that is because it closed up.
Then let's use this time too...
That's good, just like that!
Brother, it feels very good!
More.. more.. Give me more..
I got it, Miu-chan.
But this might become very troublesome. I
don't have much time to fill the other bottle!
Then, see you tomorrow!
See ya, and say good bye for me to Akira-san!
That Azu, every man in this world is ok to her.
What's this strange sound?
It's from Miu-chan's room?
Ok, only a little bit more...
The door is open?
What is this?
Th.. this is...!
The next day...
No way?
It's morning already?
Huh?
Ah.. Eh? WHY!?