T r a n s l a t e d  b y :  S o j i r o  L o v e s A z m a r i a
T i m e d  b y :  m a d n e s s
Don't dawdle around, Miu-chan.
There's still a lot of luggage left.
Yes~
Next would be this one...
Wait, be careful with that Nana-chan...
Yuki-chan too, are you all right?
What are you talking about Nana-chan?
Don't worry about matters that don't concern you and quickly carry that in!
Yes~
Sheesh, that girl...
I'll... carry that in.
Eh? Ahh, this?
These are books, so it might be a little much for Miu-chan...
That's right, for Miu-chan...
Miu-chan, that's unfair! Hogging our older brother to yourself...
Nana-chan, too, is doing something like that...
Onii-san!
Mou~ Miu-chan, you can't! Ani, over here!
Over here!
Look here, the both of you!
The both of you shouldn't create trouble for Onii-chan.
We're going to be living together
after all, so what will we do if the both of you are already acting like this?
Well, the both of them are still adjusting to their new lifestyle
so there's no need to get angry at them.
Both Miu-chan and Nana-chan are good girls, right?
Yes!
Yes~
Well then, I'm going inside for a look
so the both of you, make sure to listen to your older sister well, okay?
Yes~
Well, then...
Somehow, it's nice to have two younger siblings...
And, as a bonus, to have a new older sister, no, mother, eh?
Yukie-san, how goes things?
Ahh, Akira-kun...
It seems I've become a bother....
There were more boxes than I thought, could you carry some out for me?
Yes! Understood!
Making Mama carry everything alone...
Adjusting to a new lifestyle isn't an excuse!
Sheesh~
Yukie-san is pretty, but somewhat unreliable...
I can't rely on my little sisters, either
so it seems I have to be the leader and grab this by the tail!
Mmm~ It's really warm, with a sweet smell...
I can't hold it back in~
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?!
Lecher!
Ahh, so that's it...
That smell was...
I
mo
u
to
Younger Sister Juice
First Squeeze
One month ago, my father suddenly wanted me to meet with Yukie-san to declare his second marriage.
Yukie-san had three daughters
Yuki-chan
Miu-chan
Nana-chan.
Me, an only child, was happy that I could get three cute little sisters,
that is the life of an older brother which I wanted, and a summer with the girls...
...was what I had thought.
After the marriage ceremony had settled, my parents went on their honeymoon,
but the only one who returned was Yukie-san.
My father, an archaeologist,
had a big discovery at their destination
and had decided to stay on to properly reasearch the find.
And this how our new life as a family started without my father...
Akira-kun~
Ah... Err... I don't really get what's going on
but Yukie-san and I aren't in-laws, we're parent and child...
I can't seem to hold it in any longer...
Please... I want to do it... I want it...
B-But, my old man...
That person isn't around right now~
Nee~ You can feel the heat from my body, can't you?
It's so hot, I can't stand it anymore~
Look, you too, have become so hard~
You want to do it, don't you?
T-That's...
You can't hold it in any longer, can you?
Isn't that right, Akira-kun~
That's right. I'm already at my limits!
Yes, yes that's right. I'm so giddy~!
The Yukie-san my father was all over...
The Yukie-san who belongs to my father...
What belongs to my father, belongs to me!
Yukie-san!
Come here, Akira-kun~
This feels good!
Come in more! Be rougher!
Yes!
Yukie-san is the best!
I'm... I'm going to come!
Come! Come inside me, with all your strength!
Beat me into submission!
Keep going, keep going, don't stop~
Akira-kun, come on~
Come on, everyone eat up.
Itadakimasu~
Itadakimasu...
Ahh, the onigiri Yukie-san makes are delicious~
They're so much better than those I make myself...
Everyone! Please forget what you saw just now!
I don't know what came over me...
Somehow, I smelled something really sweet.
I just forgot myself, and I did something like that...
Please! Keep this a secret from your father! Please! Please!
That's fine with me, but you'll have to give me something to seal my lips~
I want a cat... It's all right if it's just one, isn't it?
Y-Yes... I'll talk it over with your father, okay?
Ahh, err, it's about what happened just now...
It wasn't on purpose, really!
I really wouldn't want a misunderstanding, because I'm not that...
Hey! Why are you entering on your own!
At least knock before you enter!
Sorry... I didn't think you'd be sorting your underwears...
Stop giving excuses!
That's not right. I'm not that perverted...
Then what was that you did with mother?!
Well, that's... err...
Go away! I'm busy now...
But if I don't clear up this misunderstanding now
there may be some problems in the future...
GO AWAY!
Yes, understood!
Sigh... I give up....
Hmm? Something's giving off a sweet scent...
Is this it?
Somehow, I smelled something really sweet...
So this is it?
The way Yukie-san acted is the the fault of this?
If there's something like this, it means...
What I think of this place...
No, there's definitely something interesting here.
Watson-kun! Let's search this place while father isn't around!
That's it!
This is suspicious...
An old box in a place otherwise filled with books...
Mmm... Is this something from the Mesopotamian civilization?
Inside, there are three empty bottles and a scrolled up parchment.
The writing on it is from the Sumerian civilization.
I'm going to use what father taught me and read this...
"I am the timeless Inana. What do you wish of me?"
W-What are you! Who exactly...
I am Inana, the Divine Goddess Inana.
I-Inana?
What you have just read has consummated our contract.
Contract?
Contract as in, wha...?
Your father is a great archaeologist
but he could not make out all the words
and was thus unable to form a contract with me.
Eh... Is that it...
That's right! And that contract...
Lusting after the Divine Goddess will not be forgiven!
Listen up.
Before the next full moon
fill up Inana's three empty bottles with the juice from the three girls –
in other words, their carnal secretions.
If you can do that
any wish you have will be granted.
Juice from the three girls...
However!
If you can't do that...
You will be visited with the greatest terror!
Wouldn't that mean... death?
In this universe, there are more terrible things than death, you know.
You will be visited by the greatest terror...
don't forget that.
A cat is somehow cooking...
Ahh, Onii-san, are you awake?
Well, I smelled something really nice, so...
I'm making a cake for you right now.
Eh, is that it...
Ahh! You mustn't look yet!
Mmm, I understand.
Why did Miu-chan turn into a cat?
Come to think of it, she wanted a cat.
So that thought may have become her intention, turning her into a cat.
Or not. This is definitely a dream.
Some cream got on my ear...
Some cream got on my ear~
If this is a dream, it would mean that anything goes...
That tickles~
Onii-san, what is it?
Onii-san would like to create a lot of cream in Miu-chan's hands...
There!
Miu-chan, Onii-san would like to eat Miu-chan as well as the cake.
First, we'll decorate this with cream.
Ahh, it's incredibly hard~
It's like the log cake eaten at Christmas.
Ahh, a cake, you say...
I'll let you eat it, so open your lips wide~
It's delicious, isn't it, Miu-chan?
You really like cream, don't you?
Lick it all up~
If you don't hurry the cream will drip~
Something that isn't cream is coming out...
It has a weird taste~
That isn't vanilla essence, it's Onii-san essence!
It's not poisonous, so just drink it.
Well, more will be coming out so keep sucking~
You want more Onii-san essence, don't you?
Yes!
Well then, it's now Onii-san's turn to eat~
Miu-chan's cake...
Yes!
Mmm, this looks nice...
There's something red on the icing of the cake!
I'm going to eat it~
Noooo... Nooooo~ That feels good~
That feels incredibly good, Onii-san...
Oh! There's even cream there?
Woahh, lots of Miu-chan essence is coming out~
This place of Miu-chan really wants it.
This!
Miu-chan's cake is really delicious...
I... can still... finish the rest...
This is great... Miu-chan's cake is really delicious...
Yes...
This feels good...
Very good...
Onii-san...
Miu-chan!
Yes~ Amazing... it's amazing...
Already... no more... I'm going to come!
That's fine... come!
That was an incredibly realistic dream!
That dream just now was an effect of the bottle of pleasure.
Just so you don't forget
before our contract has been fulfilled
if anyone as much as finds the bottles
the greatest terror be upon you!
Eh?
Collect the juice... collect the juice... collect the juice...
Nana-chan...
This is...
Ani is...
Ani and mama are...
This much isn't enough at all...
Hmmm...
Looks like I'll have to collect it from here, after all...
She's sound asleep so there should be no problem... probably.
Ani...
What are you doing?
Well, that's... If you're talking about WHAT I'm doing...
Nana... somehow... feels like peeing...
Huh? It's not an urge to pee...
What is this?
Ani, do you know about this?
Well... I don't know either...
This is somewhat slippery... a weird feeling...
Ani, do something about this~
Nana doesn't want to touch it. Ani, make it clean~
Why doesn't she want to touch it even though it's herself?
So that's it! She's still asleep..
Sure thing.
Lots more will be coming out, Nana-chan. Onii-chan will scoop it all out, okay?
There... There, there, there!
Yes!
There...
There there there!
That's enough, isn't it?
Do to Nana what you did to Mama~
If it's this wet, it should be okay, right?
Nana-chan...
were you awake?
Yes! All this time~
All the time being... could it be...
That's right! Ani looked to be in bliss, and couldn't hold it back any longer, is why.
Ahh, is that so...
Ani, do something perverted to Nana~
Nana wants to know more about what adults do~
W-What are you saying, Nana-chan...
There's no way I can do something like that, right?
If you don't do it, I'll tell everyone about this!
T-That'll be a problem...
Mou! Do it~ Do it, do it, do it~
Gather the juice... Gather the juice...
Gather the juice, gather the juice!
Nana.. wants to taste Ani...
Eh... What?
That's because Ani looks like you've been holding it in since just now.
Ani is now as hard as a bottle, because you're erect, right?
It's alright, even if you didn't notice that...
The amount now looks like it's still short a little...
Honestly speaking, it's your first time, so it's fine to just do as I say.
Is it still all right if I blabbed this to everyone?
You're saying that again...
Shall we call mama now and have her come naked?
Ahh, fine, fine, I understand, I understand!
But in return, don't tell anyone about this, okay?
Yes!
Waah, amazing!
But this erection doesn't seem that hard...
Look here
the person who said she wanted to taste it was Nana-chan, right?
Please hurry up!
Yes!
Is this fine?
Does it feel good?
Yeah...
This is kinda good...
Whoooo~
Because she has a small mouth this feeling of being constricted, it's unbearable!
Ani became too big in Nana, so I had to stop...
What are you saying?
You were supposed to do it, as promised, right?
Here, suck it.
Yes~
This feels good...
But be a little rougher...
Yes, that's it, there!
This is the best!
This feels great, Nana-chan!
I'm... coming...
Some of it got into my mouth...
what should I do?
Lick it.
That's also part of what you wanted to do.
Ahh, I hate myself for being able to say something like this!
To my own little sister, even!
Understood...
There's still some left here.
I'd like you to lick it all up nicely.
Nana-chan's techniques is too good
it become like this again...
Looks like we'll have to proceed to the next stage, eh?
The next stage being...?
Well then, we'll be entering the next stage now.
Even though it's also the last...
Well then, I'm starting!
Not yet, I haven't started yet...
It only gets amazing from here!
No! It hurts! Stop it, Ani...
You can't! Since we've come this far, we're going to take it all the way!
This is something adults do!
It hurts, Ani! Ani, it hurts...
It hurts...
I'm starting to feel good...
That's it, you can feel it, eh?
It's amazing...
My body is heating up, I can't stop it!
How is it, Nana-chan?
It doesn't hurt anymore, does it?
It doesn't hurt at all, it feels great, Ani~!
To have sex with Ani, Nana is extremely happy!
Ani, something's weird...
It feels like something amazing is coming...
That's not it... You're coming...
It's coming...
Something's coming...
Something will come...
Coming... coming... coming...!
It's harder than Ani...
That's of course!
Look, that's because it's a recorder.
Does it feel good?
Yes, but it's too hard...
Is that so... I thought it would be all right...
Oh? This is interesting!
No~ This is embarrassing, Ani...
Somehow
this is like farting...
What are you saying?
It's a wonderful sound. There isn't even any smell.
It feels like we've gone another step... Is that... Ani's...?
That's right, Nana-chan, we're changing directions.
Amazing... it's amazing!
But, if we make so much noise
Mama and the rest will hear us~
It's all right
this room was originally Dad's audio room
so it's soundproofed.
Well then, Nana will make louder sounds!
I'll give Ani my wiener!
Here! Say "aaah~"
I-It's fine...
Eh~ You don't need it...?
I'll tell everyone about last night.
Ahh, that looks like a wonderfully delicious wiener! I'll accept with pleasure!
You can't!
Onii-chan hasn't eaten any vegetables lately
so eat this tomato!
Yes...
Miu-chan, you can't do that!
Here, Ani, eat this!
Nana-chan, you can't hog Onii-chan all to yourself!
Why, Miu-chan
aren't you the one to be concerned about Ani's body?
Ani's really getting along with me!
That's not true!
Onii-san is older brother to the three of us, is how it is!
"Older brother to the three of us", eh?
Both of you, stop this.
We're in the middle of a meal, you know.
Sorry.
Really...
Yuki-chan...
Stop looking at Akira-kun with those eyes.
That was Mama's fault.
Thank you for the meal!
Yuki-chan, there's still some left.
I don't need anymore.
At least finish your food...
Onii-san..
What's with the small voice?
I had a dream.
A dream?
What kind of dream?
I became a cat and was making a cake
Onii-san came along and did perverted things!
Oh, so you became a cat... eh...
This is something I'm telling only to Onii-san.
It's the same dream...
is this the power of the bottle of pleasure?
There's still half a month before the next full moon...
Does that mean I'll still have to do it with my little sisters?