Onii-chan!
Dad and mom said that they'll be
away for a month starting today
Woah! Sakura, why are you naked?
Jeez... Nii-san!
R-Rika, you're naked as well?
Nii-sama...
Eh... Z-Zakuro, you too?
Onii, hurry!
H-Hiharu, aren't you even more daring today?
Onii-chan...
H-Hinata?
Imouto Paradise! 3
~First Volume~
A dream...
These protruding nipples were... Zakuro's.
This flat chest is Hinata's.
Both of Rika's and Hiharu's tits
have their own charms.
And these full-grown ones were Sakura's.
A dream of me laying my hands on my five little sisters...
If I woke up a little later...
Could it be that I actually have
those kinds of desire in me?
R-Rika?
Wh-What are you—?!
Wh-What... Of course I'm peeing...
H-Hey, nii-san! Just where are you looking at?!
I-I'm sorry, Rika!
Good morning, eronii-sama.
Hiharu, Zakuro...
I-It's not what it looks like!
Boo-boo-boo-boo, o-ni-i! If you wanna
peep, do it on me instead, okay?
Hiharu, you make jokes like an old geezer as usual.
It's you we're talking about, nii-sama.
I bet you're imagining something
indecent that you didn't notice us.
I'm so pathetic that I can't talk back on that.
Hey, what do you mean by "something indecent"?
You see, Hiharu.
He's imagining about the shape and color
of our important place down there.
C-Cut it out! Stop teaching
Hiharu unnecessary stuffs!
Jeez... What a way to start the day.
I caught you, onii!
Hiharu! Wh-What's with you all of a sudden?
You see, I'm gonna have sex with you today!
I've been waiting for a time when nobody can stop us,
and today is my best chance!
Wh-What are you talking about?
A-Aren't we siblings?
You're right... Doesn't a forbidden
relationship like this feel exciting?
But I already made up my mind!
I wonder what will happen if I do this?
Oh my... Onii, what is this hard thing down here?
N-Nothing!
You're bulging so much down here!
Now that it came to this,
there's only one thing to do!
O-Onii, you're stiff and twitching down there.
Can I try to put it in already?
I can't hold myself back anymore!
I-It hurts, but...
I'm so happy that my beloved onii is now inside me!
Onii, you're going inside more and more!
My pussy is being stretched out!
I-It hurts though...
You're whole thing is deep inside me.
Is this sex? I feel so cramped down
there and it feels nothing but painful!
It's like an electricity ran through my body!
I-It feels good... I can feel it twitching down there...
If I move, I will feel more of it...
So this is how onii's cock is.
It's hot!
I can feel it! You're moving inside me!
I am having sex with onii right now, right? I'm so happy!
H-Hiharu!
Are you happy too, onii?
Yes, I am! Your pussy is slippery and it feels good!
O-Onii, your cock is getting even bigger again!
It started to hurt a lot again, but it also
feels very good at the same time!
Th-This is bad, my mind is going blank!
This is a little embarrassing for me,
but I want to do it while facing my butt in front of you.
H-Hiharu, isn't this supposed to be your first time?
But it feels this much good!
I'm feeling so good from this
even if I was still a virgin until now!
I get so aroused when you're going in and out of me!
Onii, onii, give me more of it!
Hiharu, I won't be able to hold back
if you squeeze me that tightly!
Onii, you're doing it too fast!
But that means I'm making you
feel that good down there, right?
Then you should come like this and fill me up inside!
Or rather, you can't come
anywhere else but inside me!
No! My pussy is melting down!
It's hitting me right there!
It's like getting jammed
with a hot and long thing!
That's amazing! If you make me
feel even better than this...
I can't take it anymore!
Hiharu, let's do it together!
It feels good! Onii...
Doesn't sex... feel good?
Hiharu...
Something hot came out...
Onii, just call me anytime you feel like having sex.
It's my duty to make you come.
Alright... See you next time, onii!
I've also been waiting for a chance
to be alone with onii-chan.
And then he did it with Hiharu-chan instead...
I can do a better job of make onii-chan feel good!
I've been suddenly pushed down by
my little sister, and then we had sex...
S-Sakura, at least knock first—
S-Sakura! Wh-What's the matter?
Onii-chan, I never have guessed...
That you're someone who wanted
to have sex with his little sister.
S-Sakura, did you see me and Hiharu...
Hiharu-chan did it with you... She's so lucky...
I want to do it as well!
H-Hey... You can't touch me there!
But look, you already got big down here!
Th-That's not—
I've always been thinking about you too.
It will be my first time, but I'll do my best!
It looks like you're cramped and hurting down here.
Eh... N-No...
I have to help you here.
H-Hey, you can't!
W-Wow! Onii-chan, your dick is this big?
Onii-chan, your dick is sticky.
Th-That's because, earlier... well...
It became like this because
you did it with Hiharu, right?
I'll clean it up for you, okay?
Boys feel good when I do this, right?
Your dick grew bigger, onii-chan!
Wow, your big dick is swelling
more and it's filling my mouth!
I feel kind of amazing as well.
Doing this makes my heart throb!
S-Sakura, push it deeper into your throat!
The tip is pushing in my mouth!
Th-This is bad, it feels like you'll tear me off!
S-Sakura, if you stroke me with that tight grip...
I-I'm sorry!
If it's something softer,
i-it should feel good for you, right?
This is a little embarrassing for me but...
I'll try to give you a titjob, okay?
How is it? Does this feel good?
Yeah, it feels good!
Then, how about this?
Y-You're doing it too hard!
O-Onii-chan, fill my mouth with your dick!
Shoot a lot of slimy stuff from your dick!
Th-This is bad, I'm gonna come already!
You can't come yet!
I'm going to make you feel good a lot more!
Onii-chan, I want to see how you shoot out semen!
Wow, you're twitching down here!
I-I'm coming!
Not yet!
No, no... Hold it in a little more.
There's a lot of your juice here.
The head is twitching like it's gonna burst!
Onii-chan, the twitching won't stop!
S-Sakura, I-I'm coming!
It's amazing, you came this much!
Onii-chan, it turned out into something chunky.
I'm gonna make you shoot even a lot more!
Onii-chan, put your dick inside me here.
S-Sakura...
Onii-chan, hurry up already!
Your hot and hard thing is going in my...
It's inside!
Your dick is going inside!
This is amazing! Your thing so huge!
My pussy is gonna be torn apart!
Th-The whole thing went inside!
You're reaching deep inside me...
Your dick is hitting at a spot that feels good,
and it' reverberating quickly in me!
Sakura, does it feel good?
My pussy feels good!
Your dick is very thick
that it makes my pussy feel numb!
Your insides are squeezing me so tight!
Whenever I hear your voice,
it makes me squeeze down there!
What an amazing grip!
Who squeezes harder
between me and Hiharu-chan?
I'll squeeze my pussy even tighter.
I'll squeeze your dick until it gets squashed!
Your dick is making squishing sound!
But this is incredible! It's driving me nuts!
I can fully feel the way your dick moves inside me!
It's rubbing and stirring me up inside!
The, I'll stir you up inside even more
until your pussy takes the shape of my cock!
You're being reckless all of a sudden!
O-Onii-chan... Onii-chan!
Your dick is reaching my deepest parts!
You're rubbing deep inside me!
You're dick is burning hot!
Are you feeling that much aroused?
Onii-chan, you're stirring me up inside,
my pussy feels hot, it's gonna tear apart!
Sakura, you're tightening... I can't hold back now!
Are you coming, onii-chan?
It's okay, just shoot inside my pussy like this.
Pour it in me until it overflows!
I also want to come together with you, onii-chan!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
You can come too, onii-chan. Shoot a lot of it!
Onii-chan, did my pussy feel good?
Yeah, it felt so good.
I'm glad!
You're so warm and you're giving off much of scent.
Just call me anytime you feel like having sex, okay?
I'll study a lot more about it so I can
make you feel even better next time.
You really love to study as always, Sakura.
I'll look forward on it next time.
Onii-chan...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization