Oh no...
No... It feels good!
I'm coming!
Onii-chan...
Imouto Bitch ni Shiboraretai❤
I Want to be Squeezed by My Bitch Little Sister❤
My Little Sister is a Living Fuckhole❤
~Sayaka is Onii-chan's Personal Sex Toy~
It's a hole...
There's a hole on the wall.
Is this one of her pranks?
Stop staring on me, pervert.
I don't think so...
Is she home yet?
I'm aware that I'm about to do something perverted.
She came home at a perfect time.
I never thought I'd see my little sister masturbating.
I knew it... This isn't enough...
Sayaka's...
My sister's bare puss—
This is bad... I can't stop my fingers...
I'm gonna... soon...
I'm coming...
Coming!
Onii-chan...
I never heard what she said that day.
You're such a coward.
It's really weird no matter how I think about it.
She should have noticed a distinct hole like this.
Maybe she got so horny despite
knowing I'm peeping on her?
No, that can't be.
I'm home.
Sayaka just got home.
What should I do?
Should I just peep on her while
she's masturbating again?
So that's how it is...
T-There's a mushroom growing on the wall.
I happened to be hungry.
Maybe I should eat this.
This is onii-chan's dick.
I can finally show my true self.
I finally got what I want thanks to this hole.
Yum...
Yummy...
Yummy!
I'm... coming!
Feels so warm.
This is onii-chan's semen.
More... I want more!
I'm glad that I made him come while savoring his dick.
I love you, onii-chan.
I've been acting cruel on you
to hide my embarrassment away.
But the truth is, I love him so much.
I'm gonna come again, Sayaka!
Give it to me! Shoot everything out!
I still want to taste more of it...
I worked hard on club activities today.
Maybe I should do some stretching in my room.
I can use the wall and do some good stretching.
That's what she meant, right?
Today is... just fine...
Today's horoscope said so.
And it's also a day when I'm not fertile.
I think they call it a "safe day".
There's an onahole in such a place!
O-Onahole?
I'm lucky to find a living onahole here.
I guess I should give it a try.
This onahole is tight!
Eh? I just remembered about Sayaka.
I wonder if she's done on her stretching.
So deep... It's going deep!
I can feel your dick kissing my womb!
My pussy wall is getting pulled
together with your dick!
I'm getting addicted on this onahole!
M-More, shove it in!
Stretch my hole more and make it sloppy!
Stretch my pussy to the shape of your dick!
Sayaka!
Just like that! Pour your semen in me!
Onii-chan!
There's so much, my pussy will break!
I'm gonna break.
Sayaka, you're bleeding...
W-Well... the security seal has been properly torn up.
Eh?
With this, you're officially registered as its owner.
Sayaka, you...
B-Brand new onaholes are the best!
I want to take good care using this onahole from now on.
Onii-chan...
After that, I continued using my little sister onahole everyday.
I want you to feel it more!
Slide in between your little sister's titty onahole!
As expected from a living onahole.
It also has a titfuck function.
It's also equipped with a self-learning functions.
Please come as many times as you like!
Squirt them on my tit-pussy!
Coming!
It feels good when my clit and
your hard dick rubs together!
I really want to put it inside.
I can't take it anymore!
Ding-dong! Preparations for penetration, all green!
Hey, you two! Dinner's gonna be ready soon!
W-Wait—
It went in.
Hey, Sayaka. What's the matter?
Wait, I'll be coming soon!
Oh no! I'm coming!
Jeez... Hurry up and come downstairs.
Okay...
Wait, I want to talk about something.
A guy from school confessed to me earlier.
Is that so? Good for him.
Just that? I feel stupid sharing this on you!
Jeez... Perverted idiot brother!
Onii-chan, look...
I did just as you told me.
I went to school without wearing panties.
See?
I was so nervous while being confessed at,
I thought I'd die from embarrassment.
You're gonna mess my pussy up
as a reward tonight, right?
I get it.
Dick... I want a dick!
I'm gonna mess you up just as you wished!
Here comes the dick!
I'm already coming just after sliding it in!
Something big's coming!
I longed for this dick!
My head went numb, I can't
think about anything else!
My pussy feels amazing! It's driving me nuts!
You've been coming for a while now, huh?
Is it because of going to school
earlier without panties?
That's because.... feels good!
I'm gonna come soon. Take all of my load!
I'm happy!
I'm coming!
C-Come!
I'm filled with semen!
It felt so good that I peed myself.
We're far from being normal siblings, but...
I am so happy!
I am onii-chan's personal onahole,
so please use me with care,
and love me more!
Of course I will!
You have a body made for squeezing semen out.
No...
I was born just to become your cum dump!
Come, come in me! Shoot it out with all you can!
I'm already at my limit!
I'll shoot it out!
Come, come! Give it to me!
Give me creampie! Plant your seeds thoroughly!
Onii-chan, I love you... so much!
I'm filled with baby seeds!
Onii-chan...
I love you!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization