Onii-chan.
Mom and Dad said they'll be gone for a month!
Whoa, why are you naked, Sakura?
Jeez, nii-san.
Ri-Rika, you're not wearing any clothes, too?
Nii-sama.
Y-You too, Zakuro?
Onii, hurry!
You seem even more daring, Hiharu.
Onii-chan...
Hi-Hinata?
A dream?
Those erect nipples, Zakuro.
Such petite breasts, Hinata.
Rika and Hiharu's breasts are also unique.
These heavy ones are Sakura's.
That dream where all of them tried to seduce me.
If I hadn't woken up...
Maybe "that" desire lurks somewhere within me.
Ri-Rika?
Wh-Why are you...?
Why, of course I'm... I'm peeing...
H-Hey, nii-san!
What are you staring at?
Oh, I'm sorry, Rika!
Good morning, my pervy nii-sama.
Hiharu, Zakuro.
This isn't what it looks like.
Boo, boo, boo!
Onii, if you want to peep, make sure that you do it to me!
Your jokes are always so blunt.
Nii-sama's not hurt at all. In fact, he's probably
having dirty thoughts already.
It's pathetic that I can't even refute that.
Hey, what exactly are those dirty thoughts?
What?
Well, Hiharu,
all he can do is fixate on our private parts.
Stop that! Don't suggest anything unnecessary to Hiharu!
Jeez, we're having quite the busy morning.
Gotcha, onii!
Hiharu! What's with you so suddenly?
I'm going to do lewd stuff with you this time.
Huh?
I waited until everyone was out so we could this,
and now's the perfect chance.
What are you saying?
You and I are siblings, you know.
I guess so.
Doing something taboo turns you on, right?
But I'm prepared for this.
I wonder what will happen if I do this to you?
Oh? What is this hard thing, my dear brother?
Nothing.
It bulges so quickly.
So lewd!
In that case,
there's only one thing to do.
Your thing is so stiff, and it's twitching hard.
Can I put it in?
I can't hold back anymore.
It hurts!
But,
I'm happy that my beloved brother is inside me.
Your thing is slowly penetrating me.
It's prying open my pussy.
It hurts, but...
Your thing has reached my womb.
So this is sex.
It's so hot and painful.
It felt like a surge of electricity coursed through me.
It feels good.
It's twitching inside.
I'm going to move.
So this is onii's dick.
So hot.
It's pulsating wildly inside me.
We're having sex, right?
I'm happy.
Hi-Hiharu...!
Are you happy, onii?
I'm happy.
Your pussy is so wet and nice.
It seems to be molding itself to the shape of my penis.
It's still painful,
but it's also quite pleasurable.
Oh no, my mind's going blank.
It's a bit embarrassing this time,
but I want you to fuck me from behind.
Hiharu, but this is your first time...!
But, I never thought it'd feel this good.
I just lost my virginity, and yet,
I feel so horny.
The way it penetrates me turns me on so much.
Onii, give me more of you, onii!
Hiharu, if you keep squeezing me that tight,
I won't be able to restrain myself!
Onii, you're too fast.
But that just means it feels great for you, right?
Then keep fucking me until you cum and it fills me up.
No.
I don't want you to cum anywhere else!
It feels like pussy's melting!
It's hitting me so hard.
The heat is starting to course throughout my body.
Incredible. I've never felt such a wonderful sensation.
– Oh no, I'm about to...
– Hiharu.
Let's cum together!
Oh yes!
Onii...!
S-Sex... sure feels great.
Hiharu.
So much hot stuff is coming out.
Onii, call me whenever you want to have sex,
because it's my job to make you cum.
Well then, see you later, onii.
I've been waiting for a chance to be alone with onii-chan, too.
I never thought he'd do it with Hiharu-chan, of all people.
I can pleasure onii-chan even better.
Even if she took the initiative,
I still ended up doing it with my sister.
Sa-Sakura, you should have knocked first...
Sa-Sakura?
What's wrong?
I never knew,
that you wanted to do dirty stuff with your siblings.
Wait, don't tell me you saw what Hiharu and I were doing...?
I'm envious of what you did with Hiharu-chan.
I want to do it, too.
Hey, you can't do that.
But your thing seems to have already gotten big.
N-No...
I've fantasized about you, as well.
It may be my first time, but I'll do my best.
It seems a bit swollen. Are you in pain?
Not really...
I have to help you out, onii-chan!
Wait, you can't...!
W-Wow...
So your dick is this big?
Your dick feels so wet.
That's because earlier I... well...
It's like this because you did it with Hiharu-chan earlier, right?
I'll clean it for you.
Guys find it pleasurable when you do this, right?
Your dick is starting to bulge.
Amazing. Your dick is getting bigger, and it's writhing inside me.
This is turning me on a lot, as well.
Sakura, you're taking me deep inside!
Your dick's secreting a strange liquid.
I can't take it anymore.
It's going to get squeezed out.
Sa-Sakura, if you keep rubbing it hard like that...
I'm sorry.
It'll feel better if I use something softer, right?
It's kinda embarrassing,
but I'm going to give you a tit fuck, okay?
Well? Does it feel good?
Yeah, it does.
Then, how about this?
Wow, that's so intense!
Your dick is filling my entire mouth, onii-chan.
The sticky stuff is starting to overflow.
O-Oh crap, I'm about to cum.
You can't do that yet.
I still need to pleasure you more.
Huh?
I want to see how you actually cum.
It's twitching hard.
I-I'm cumming!
Not just yet.
No, no, no.
You have to hold it in.
So much of the clear stuff is coming out!
The tip is bulging so hard.
Onii-chan, your dick keeps on twitching.
Sa-Sakura, I'm cumming...!
Amazing. There's so much cum.
Onii-chan, it feels like I'm handling glue.
I need you to cum some more, then.
Please, put your dick in here.
Sa-Sakura.
Onii-chan, hurry up!
This hot and stiff thing is about to...
It's coming in!
Your dick is making its way in.
Incredible. Your dick feels so big.
My pussy is being torn apart.
It's all the way in.
It's reaching my depths,
and it's hitting my pleasurable spots.
The sensation is reverberating throughout my body.
Does it feel good, Sakura?
My pussy feels great,
and your dick is so thick.
It makes my entire pussy tingle.
Your insides are clamping down on me.
My pussy started pulsating as soon as I heard your voice.
It's wrapping around me so tightly.
Is mine or Hiharu's tighter?
What?
My pussy's going to squeeze you even more, okay?
I'm going to clamp down until your dick shrinks!
I can feel your dick rubbing my pussy.
Amazing. This might make me go crazy.
I can feel it gradually moving inside of me.
It's stirring up my insides so much.
I'll stir it up even more then, until your
pussy molds itself to my dick.
You suddenly became so intense!
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
It's penetrating me even deeper.
It's prying open my insides.
It's scorching hot, too.
Are you that aroused right now?
This feels amazing, onii-chan.
It feels like my pussy's on fire.
It's like it's going to melt.
Your tight hole is gonna drive me over the edge!
Are you cumming, onii-chan?
It's all right. Cum inside of my pussy.
Cum it all till you pass out.
I want to cum with you, as well.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
It's okay. Just release it anytime.
Onii-chan, did my pussy feel good?
Yeah, it felt great.
I'm glad!
Yours felt warm too, and had a strong smell.
Just call me whenever you feel like doing it, okay?
I'll learn many more things, so that I can do better next time.
You're as studious as ever.
I'm looking forward to next time.
Onii-chan.