Onii, did sex with me feel good?
H-Hiharu!
I want you to stir my pussy up
even more with your dick!
Onii-chan, aren't my tits soft
and don't they feel good?
Y-Yeah...
Just tell me whenever you want to do it, okay?
I'll always be ready for it anytime.
Then, I'll leave it to you...
Wh-What's happening?
I-I can't move my body.
Huh? The pleasure is...
This kind of feels good...
Huh?!
Z-Zakuro? Hinata?
Oh my, nii-sama. You finally woke up.
Good morning, onii-chan!
Imouto Paradise! 3
~Second Volume~
What are you two doing?
Hinata is curious about how men's bodies are,
so I'm using your body as a visual aid.
Hinata, cocks get big when you stroke them.
Wow! His dick is gradually getting bigger.
S-Stop! W-We're siblings, you know!
I don't really mind it.
That's because I love you.
I don't mind it too! I love you, onii-chan!
That's not the problem here!
Or rather, my cock feels constricted.
I wrapped it around with my hair tie.
I did it so that you won't easily come.
Y-You don't normally do as much as this!
Isn't onii-chan's dick big?
Your cock started to drip with
sweet-smelling precum, nii-sama!
Hinata, this is something very delicious.
H-Hey! D-Don't do that!
Nii-sama, you're twitching.
You're oozing with lewd juice.
I'm going to suck all of your Cowper's fluid out!
I-It felt like my groin throbbed...
Jeez, nii-sama! You're making two
of your little sisters throb...
Zakuro, your mouth is incredible!
You're sucking and squeezing me tight—
Nii-sama, you're thrusting
into my mouth. That's great!
I'm already...
I'm getting wet somehow...
I'm getting wetter and wetter.
Onii-chan, can you see it?
Hinata...
Nii-sama, Hinata's pussy is twitching
in reaction from seeing us!
Onii-chan, the throbbing won't stop!
In times like that, you have to make nii-sama lick it
and let him take the burning sensation away!
O-Okay...
H-Hey, Hinata!
Like this?
Onii-chan, hurry up and lick
the heat away down there.
Hinata! Wait, wait—
Hurry!
W-Wait!
My body feels tingly and numb!
Why am I feeling like this?
Hinata, your sopping wet pussy
is making my face sticky!
Nii-sama, you have to cool Hinata down.
Don't you feel bad for her?
It can't be helped!
Hinata, I'll make you come so prepare yourself!
It went inside!
O-Onii-chan, that's amazing!
My groin feels hot!
Hinata, that's not your groin. We call it "pussy".
M-My pussy feels like it's gonna melt!
Nii-sama, I'm now feeling horny.
I'll proceed on calming myself down.
Hey... Z-Zakuro, you can't do that!
Nii-sama, your cock is s-slowly going inside me...
Z-Zakuro, you're so tight!
It's alright, I'm going to take
your whole thing inside me!
Your cock just filled me up inside!
This is amazing! Nii-sama, I never knew
that your cock feels this good!
I can feel it rubbing against my cervix
and it's pushing my womb up!
The tightness inside you feels incredible!
I feel like coming already!
We're far from getting done!
You have to make us two of your
little sisters come a lot more, nii-sama!
Th-This is bad! I'm coming!
I-It won't come out! My semen is getting pushed back!
Nii-sama, I can feel that you're about to burst!
You want to shoot it out, but you can't...
You're trembling!
Me too, I want onii-chan's dick to go in my pussy!
Hinata, you haven't studied about this yet.
It's alright, learn about this to the utmost extent.
Okay, let's put nii-sama's cock
inside Hinata's gooey pussy.
Onii-chan, I want it inside me...
I don't care what happens anymore!
Onii-chan's thing went inside!
Guh! It's so tight, I can't go any deeper!
Hinata, are you okay?
It hurts, but please push it inside!
Here it goes!
Nii-sama, how is Hinata's lewd pussy?
It's clamping me tight, it's narrow
and it's pulling me in!
I'm already...
Onii-chan, it feels like my pussy is getting weird!
It looks like you totally got captivated
by nii-sama's cock as well, Hinata.
No! No!
Onii-chan, you're going deep inside me too fast!
I started to crave for it again
after hearing your moans, Hinata!
Nii-sama, your cock went inside me!
You're rubbing against my womb!
You're squeezing so tightly, I'm already...
Not yet, nii-sama!
G-Guh...
Nii-sama, your cock is twitching...
Is it already gonna come out?
It's flowing back to my balls!
Onii-chan, please...
I also want to feel that dizziness again.
I want you to thrust it into me even more!
I don't care whatever happens anymore!
No...
It feels good! The pleasure deep inside me is back!
I want more deep in...
Nii-sama, you're thrusting so hard!
It feels like...
Something hot is slowly coming!
Hinata, that's what we call "coming".
I'm about to come as well!
I'm gonna come too!
It's already tedious early in the morning,
all because of Zakuro and Hinata. Jeez...
Nii-san...
That's Rika's voice. Is she in my room?
Nii-san's scent makes me feel aroused!
My hands won't stop! This is all nii-san's fault!
If nii-san sees me like this...
U-Umm, Rika?
N-N-N-N-Nii-san?!
Umm... You see... this is... nothing in particular!
Nah... Even if you say that...
It looks like nothing else but mast—
D-Don't say it! Seriously, don't say anything more...
Rika, do you want to have sex with me?
Eh? Ah, no... N-No way...
You see, we're siblings...
I want to have sex with you, Rika!
J-Just wait for a second, nii-san!
Th-That's something we can't do!
You idiot! You can't do something
like this on your little sister!
Rika, your tits are small and cute!
Don't say that they're small! You're being rude!
Stop rolling your tongue over my nipples!
Stop rubbing my tits like that!
They're sensitive because they're small.
Then how about when I do this...
I-It hurts, don't bite them!
You say that yet you're pleased
and you got hard right here.
Th-That's not true!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
I'll put my cock inside your pussy, Rika!
Huh?!
Y-You can't! Anything but that!
We're siblings!
It went inside!
His whole thing is inside! I never knew that he's this big...
It feels like I'll get torn apart down there!
Nii-san thing got big...
He's now having sex with me...
I made him feel aroused!
Doing something like this
on your little sister...
Nii-san, you're a pervert!
But aren't you aroused as well, Rika?
Your pussy is dripping wet and
overflowing with lewd juices!
There's no way that I'm aroused!
Y-You're suddenly being rough!
N-Nii-san, you'll drive me crazy
if you keep doing it that hard!
If you feel nothing, you'll be fine
with something like this.
I'll admit that I'm feeling good from this!
I'm feeling good from having sex with you, Nii-san!
This is bad, I'm about to come soon!
I'm coming too! You're making me come!
This feels way better than masturbation!
I'm coming from your dick, Nii-san!
I'm coming!
I got creampied!
I never had enough yet. We can go
for another round, right?
I want to do it from behind next!
Jeez, even though I just came
and I'm highly sensitive now.
Hey, hey! Isn't this hole sticky as well?
N-Nii-san, just where are you
touching? That's my butthole!
Since you've been masturbating,
maybe you feel good in your ass too.
Th-There's no way that's true!
No...
Nii-san, your finger is in my ass... It hurts!
Rika, your asshole is loose! You should
be able to take my cock inside it.
No, no... You can't put it in!
Your dick is going inside...
You're stretching my asshole wide!
N-Nii-san, stop this already!
You're squeezing tightly right here!
Nii-san, your dick is going inside my ass!
My ass feels numb whenever you pull your dick out!
You already got used to this. Your ass is so lewd, Rika!
I-I don't know what you're talking about!
Your ass feels good! Are you feeling good as well?
N-No way!
I'm getting stirred inside my belly
and it feels disgusting!
Then, I need to get you even
more accustomed on this!
Y-You're being too rough!
You got tighter again! Your ass-pussy is the best, Rika!
Wh-What? Will his come also feel good
in my ass just like in my pussy?
Say it, then!
That you want me to pour my semen
inside your ragged ass-pussy!
There's no way I'm gonna say that!
My ass is getting hotter and hotter!
Say it! Or else, I'll pull my cock out!
I want it! Shoot your semen in my ass-pussy!
Spray me a lot of it!
I-I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Nii-san, you were so rough on me!
Even though it's my first time having anal sex...
But it felt great, right?
Th-That's... No comment...
Just come to me next time when
you feel like masturbating.
I don't know!
And then, which one are you
going to choose among us?
Of course, it's gonna be me! Right, onii?
Onii-chan, do you hate me?
Th-That's not the case!
I love you, Hinata!
The same goes for Rika and Hiharu.
And even Zakuro and Sakura as well. I love everyone!
Jeez, I can't choose only one of you!
Then, how does assigning a day of
the week for each one of us sound?
Sounds great! Then, I'll be on Mondays!
You're the fourth daughter so
you'll be on Thursdays, Hiharu.
Then, I'll be on Fridays, right?
Based on that, I will be on Wednesdays.
Onii, everyone will be your partner for today!
E-Everyone? I wonder if I'll be fine...
Alright!
Then, I'll be healing you a lot from your
exhaustion when Monday comes!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization