Julka-chan, shall we?
Will you let me use your front hole today?
I'm coming soon!
That ring is a custom made one.
'kay...
Something good happens on someone who wears it.
Something good?
I'm sure it brings happiness.
I'm already happy.
It will make you even more.
Will I become the best doll then?
I'm sure you will.
3rd of February,
Suzuki-san: short-standard, 2 pops.
Urakabe-san: dropped by before going to work.
He seemed to really like blowjobs.
He came on my tongue twice.
It's been a while since I last tasted
semen without any seasoning.
Lounge: A tea with Miku.
Training Room: fellatio practice.
I have much time to try but
I couldn't beat last month's score.
Kimura-san: long-superior, 4 pops.
He drops by on occasion while roaming around.
I licked his balls trying to make him come, but failed.
He was glad that I let him use my pussy.
I think I already got the timing
of doing vaginal contractions.
He gave me a ring.
Medical Room
Main Prep. Room
You squeezed out quite a lot since this morning.
Hey, have you heard?
About what?
About the issue last time.
Seems like that circle did it.
I see... But did they really not kill her?
Supposedly. They always overdo their stunts.
The report said "strangulation" so they
might have squeezed her neck too much.
That's scary...
How pitful...
What a joke.
Working as an unlicensed prostitute, yet
unable to do crisis management properly.
It's no surprised if she get's killed.
What's pitful on that?
Hey, saying it that way is—
Calm down, Miku.
Sheena, weren't you with the monk till noon?
That's why you're in a bad mood, right?
Don't give in.
The hell with you bitches...
Just die, seriously. Drop dead.
What's her problem?
How weird.
There hasn't been a doll like her before.
Don't let it get in you.
Getting bothered will affect your work.
We should always think about making
the clients have a good time.
As expected from Julka
Yum...
Ah, I can't believe she's younger than me.
I'm here.
Thanks for the hardwork.
The first one for tonight already called.
Yeah...
Urination...
Go to the Medical Room and
tell them to scent you up.
Sensei, please do something to
make this good to drink.
And how can I quickly make
myself feel embarrassed?
What's that for?
Wow, you're so cute!
Thank you.
Whoa, delicious!
I'm glad. Feel free to ask for a refill.
As expected from the #1. To be able
to think about such a unique service...
How kind of you.
I was aiming for the one named Sheena
at first, but I'm glad I chose you instead.
Oh, how rare...
That girl don't have much patrons.
You thought it's natural
that you got me instead?
Well, yes.
How confident you are.
Oh, this is it!
A girl's scent gives off a peculiar fragrance.
Ohh... I always wanted to do this.
You'll like what's beneath it as well.
I already saw it in the sample.
It looks like you asshole had quite an experience.
I thought of ways to make it prettier,
but everyone said that it's good as it is.
I think it's beautiful.
That feels good!
Delicious!
Can't get enough of this!
Good!
You're good at this...
Put it in your mouth.
Wow...
It's all in!
Amazing!
Wait... Julka-chan. I want to move.
Your deepthroat feels good.
Sorry, I came in your throat before I knew it.
Wow, I'm glad. You shoot out this much.
Did my throat feel that good?
She's a pro.
I like you. Let me screw your ass.
Should I clean it first?
No need for that. Hurry up and spread your legs.
You're a sadist, Aki-san.
And you're a masochist, right? We're a good match.
Nah, I'm not.
Then, what are you?
I just love feeling good.
I'm fine as long as I can make the clients happy.
That feels great!
Aren't you a total masochist!
Despite how it looks, you're tight inside.
It's 'coz I've been practicing.
What's this? Looks like you're feeling it.
Coming!
Why aren't you coming that much?
It's just a delayed spurt.
You're lying...
Oh well...
Julka-chan, technology is so advanced
that you can now customize
anything to specific detail.
But that power also gives people ideas
like using it to break things apart!
You're making a good face!
You're cuter this way, Julka.
No... don't!
We're already the 10th round before I knew it.
Shoot it already...
Where do you want it?
In my pussy...
That's good.
Tighten up just like that.
This is the best!
I wonder how many more times can I come?
I'm close again.
This asshole is first-class!
Julka, you worked hard.
Back at you.
Oh, Sheena, you worked hard as well.
Not really.
Taki-san (New Client): long-exceptive, 12 pops.
I already had a hunch that he's someone
strong since he's came from a reservation.
But he's far beyond my expectations.
He violated and made me come so much.
It's not a service if it's the client
who made me feel good instead.
Though it felt so good like I'm gonna die.
I'm exhausted.
Well, he gave me quite a satisfaction so it's alright
Doing it with Taki-san made me realize that there
are still a variety of pleasures I'm not aware of.
It's not that much different than usual,
but it was really amazing.
It's been 5 years since I came here.
Maybe I've become too relaxed living here.
We exist to serve as a bin to take
all of humanity's sexual desire.
It is my happiness to give pleasure to clients.
Tomorrow I'll regain my strength and do my best.
All to become the best doll.
Hey, what's up?
Have you seen Taki-kun's post at the Training section?
Nah, I'll look for it.
What were you doing?
Ah, I was backreading that year-end post.
Oh, that one? That's so good,
the one that keeps getting reposted.
Yeah, it always get's removed, it's crazy.
AA
That's amazing!
Let's hurry up and make
reservations for these girls
tomorrow... should we?
Kun!
AAAAAAA
I made a reservation for threesome.
With those two girls of course. (Experiment)
That's good. Let's do it.
Yeah, we should.
Alright, take care.
Don't goof around.
Okay!
All good here.
C-Coming... I'm coming!
Sheena-chan, your reactions
are so innocent and really good!
Both of you two were handpicked
by tomorrow night's client.
He requested you to wear a young girl's
uniform from the last years of A.D. era.
He doesn't want to see your chokers even a little.
We normally decline these clients,
but we approved this one specifically
since he's offering quite a price.
You will receive some bonus from it as well.
Wow!
Drop by here before going to your designated room.
When you're done, you will both be taken
back to your rooms so just wait in there.
I understand.
Yes.
Then, that's all.
Isn't it a paradise in here.
Oh, now this is something...
Are you about to come?
Yeah, I'm coming.
Okay.
Delicious.
I'm gonna come.
Wonderful.
That's good.
I feel like throwing up...
You really do hate semen.
There's a rumor going around about Sheena-chan.
What kind of rumor?
About a doll in the Dollhouse who doesn't
seem like an artificially designed one.
That she's like a human-born girl.
Isn't Sheena-chan's body temperature high?
Right. How cute.
You're lovely.
Alright, let's enjoy this time to its fullest.
There's still an hour left.
Let's give our best.
I don't think I can...
You're drenched all over.
Maybe you love getting showered with semen?
Just die.
Your cuteness will go to waste
so stop talking that way.
What now?!
I'll clean you up.
Hey, Julka...
Have you ever thought about quitting as a doll?
Never!
Stop that, Sheena. Dolls never think that way.
Don't worry, I'm sure you'll be popular in time.
You're very cute when you're having sex.
I'll be helping you from now on, okay?
Okay...
Well then, shall we continue copulating?
Please do.
Julka... keep going!
Julka?
Are you now in heaven?
What... What did you do?
Just a little magic.
It makes her orgasm feel nonstop.
It's so tight.
Well then, Sheena-chan.
It's alright. I won't use that in you.
That drug only works on dolls.
I feel bad for father but,
it was a wonderful work in the end.
To think that his 8-year-old daughter that we put our
hands on was driven down here to the lower levels.
Like you're going straight within our reach.
I'll be sneaking you out here and
bring you to my friend's place.
The participants this time were the past ones again.
They're your big fans who know your deflowering day and even the number of creases in your asshole.
Work hard for them.
Are you happy?
If you're that willing to go with me,
then I should not waste anytime.
You're gonna be raped so much.
C-Coming!
That was great!
Shall we go, then?
Julka...
What have you done?!
It's because Sheena will be...
What should we do?
Sheena, are you really...
Wait!
This is...
What's that?
Not done yet?
The security system will return
back to normal in 5 minutes.
Chiba-san is already at the lift station.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization