Yuruka-chan, I'm just about there.
How about we use your front hole today?
I'm already about to cum!
That ring is special.
I hear that when you put it on, really good things happen.
Like what?
Like finding happiness.
I'm already happy.
You'll be even happier.
Do you think I can become the best doll?
Yeah, I know you can.
February third.
Suzuki-san, two pumps in a short time.
Urakabe-san: Comes in before going to work.
He seems to really like fellatios.
He's done it in my mouth twice already after all.
It was my first time in a while tasting raw cum.
Lounge, meat, and tea.
Research facility.
Fellatio techniques.
I've taken time to try and learn a lot of different things,
but it barely affected my score last month.
Kimura-san: Long session, four times.
He comes around during patrols.
I tried to make him cum by licking his balls, but couldn't.
It made me happy that Kimura-san used my pussy.
I think I know when to tighten my insides now.
I got a ring.
Body Ajustment Room     Infirmary
You got quite a lot today, huh?
Hey, did you hear?
About what?
About the news.
I hear that circle's involved.
Really?
But I thought they don't kill.
Yeah, they don't, but their signature
graffiti was all over the place.
They're under investigation now. They might
have gone too far playing around this time.
Oh, geez.
I feel bad for them.
They're so stupid.
They can't do crisis management right
and these casualties are the result.
Of course they were killed.
Why feel bad for them at all?
Hey, watch the way you're talking!
Calm down, Miku.
Shiina, that kid visited you again this morning, right?
You're just pissed off because of that, aren't you?
Chin high, okay?
Fuck all you sluts.
Just fucking die.
Die.
What's her problem?
There's something wrong with her.
We've never had a doll like her before.
Don't let her bother you.
If you let it get to you, it'll affect your work.
Our first priority is pleasing our customers.
That's our Yuruka!
So yummy!
It's hard to believe you're so mature.
I'm here.
Thanks for coming.
There was a call for you for tonight.
I see. I see.
Yes
Yuruka
Dress
I really want to enjoy the smell of a real girl.
Particularly the smell of pee on her genitals.
Pee, huh?
Go to the infirmary to get the smell, okay?
Doctor, please make this drinkable.
And what should I do to collect smegma immediately?
Huh? Why?
Wow, you're so cute!
Thank you.
That was delicious!
I'm glad.
There's more if you'd like.
This is why you're the number one girl here.
You really went above and beyond.
Thank you for your kind words.
I was actually thinking about going for
Shiina, but I'm glad I decided on you!
Oh, that's rare.
She doesn't get that many customers.
So you feel like it's natural that you were chosen instead?
Yeah, pretty much.
You got some confidence, huh?
Yeah, this is it! The good stuff!
It has a completely different smell than a woman's!
I wanna stay like this forever.
I think you'll enjoy what's underneath as well.
I saw some of the samples, but the
real thing is much more amazing.
I thought about maybe keepings it clean, but
everyone says that they like it this way.
It's plenty beautiful.
It feels so good!
It's so tasty!
What a nice color!
I'm gonna cum!
You're really good at this.
Suck it.
It's all inside!
Shit...
Hey, Yuruka-chan, do you mind? I wanna move.
Your throat feels so good!
Sorry, I just went as hard as I could in your throat.
I'm so happy. You put so much down my throat!
Did my throat really feel that good?
You really are a pro.
I really like you.
Let's loosen up that ass.
You don't need to be cleaned?
Hell no.
Just spread your legs already.
You're a sadist, aren't you?
And you're a masochist, aren't you?
We're perfect for each other.
No, I'm not a masochist.
Then what are you?
I just like doing things that feel good.
If I can make my customer happy, it makes me happy too.
It feels so good.
And that makes you the perfect masochist!
It's a lot tighter than it looks.
Yeah, it's been made to be that way.
Huh? You starting to lose your cool?
How can you cum so much?
Just some good ol' delayed ejaculation.
It's so big.
Yeah, you know.
Yuruka-chan, your techniques are great and you even have
the perfect behavior and mannerisms. Pretty impressive.
But that just makes me want to break you down.
I like the way your face is looking now.
You're so cute right now!
No... Don't...
We're already up to our tenth time.
I-I'm cumming!
Where do you want me to cum?
My pus... sy...
Good girl.
Keep it up.
This is the fucking best!
How many more times can you go?
I'm about to cum again.
This tight ass hole is in a league of its own!
Yuruka, later!
See you later.
Shiina, finally can take a breather, huh?
I'm not even tired.
Taki-san (hatsu).
It was a long session with twelve ejaculations.
I knew from the request he sent that he'd
be a very demanding customer, but...
He was more demanding than I ever thought he'd be.
He made me cum so much.
It's not good for me to cum more than the customer.
It felt good enough to send me to heaven though.
I'm beat.
Well, I guess I satisfied him so it's okay.
Thanks to Taki-san, I know that there are tons of
different techniques that I don't know about.
It's not even like what we did was outlandish or anything.
But it was really amazing.
From inexperienced to experienced...
I might have been getting too full of myself.
We exist to take on the sexual desires of humans.
The customer's happiness is my happiness.
I need to get my head straight tomorrow
and do my best again.
I need to become the best doll ever.
Yeah, it's me. What's up?
You see Taki-kun's video? The one of the research lab.
No, let me check it out.
What were you up to?
Oh yeah, I was just rewatching an older video.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh yeah, that place was really sweet wasn't it?
Yeah, yeah, exactly, I couldn't stop cumming!
That sweet!
I'll be reserving this girl for tomorrow...
Shit, that's the date of the plan.
Fuck!
I reserved a three way. Of course, it's with those two. (Implementer)
Okay, sounds good. I'm in!
Agreed.
'Kay, later.
Stop slackin' off.
Yeah, yeah.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
I'm gonna...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I love how natural your reactions
are Shiina-chan! They're perfect!
These are the people who reserved you two.
They want you wearing the AD-Mac uniform and
don't want to see those collars on you at all.
Usually we'd refuse, but they paid a lot
of money, so we made an exception.
You two will get a bonus as well.
Wow.
So before you go to the waiting room, get ready in here.
When you're done getting ready,
we'll send you to the room.
Understood.
Okay.
Good. That's all.
This is paradise.
Well, this is something.
Would you like to cum?
Yes, that'd be great.
Alright.
So good.
I'm cumming.
Excellent.
Really good.
Ew, it's gross.
You really don't like semen, do you?
I've heard some rumors about you, Shiina-chan.
What kinds?
I heard that there's a doll in the dollhouse who feels like
she was made completely different than all the others.
Almost like she was a real life human.
Shiina-chan, you're pretty warm.
Yeah, you are. That's cute.
How beautiful.
Let's enjoy ourselves with the time we have.
You have an hour left.
We're almost there.
I don't think I can go on.
Yeah, we just keep cumming over and over again.
You actually really like this, don't you?
Shut up and die.
Come on, don't talk like that when you look this cute.
What?
I'll clean you up.
Hey, Yuruka...
Do you ever think about quitting being a doll?
Of course not!
Stop right there, Shiina. Dolls mustn't
think about those things.
Don't worry. You'll be popular in no time.
You're so incredibly cute, I know you can do it!
I'll teach you about anything you want to know, okay?
Okay.
Okay, let's go another round, huh?
Go ahead.
Yuruka, stop. Don't lick there...
Yuruka?
Was that too much for you?
What... What did you do to her?
Just a little something to tighten her up.
She's basically stuck climaxing.
Oh, it's tight!
Now then, Shiina-chan?
Don't worry, Shiina-chan, I won't use it on you.
That only works on dolls anyway.
I'm sorry about your dad, but he worked hard until his end.
He shed his sweat, blood, and tears
for his beloved daughter.
All that just for you to fall into our hands.
Now I'm going to sneak you out and
carry you to the rest of my friends.
There are a lot of people participating this time.
All of them are your fans. They know
every last bit of your body.
Let's do our best, huh?
So happy, you're peeing?
If you're getting this happy, I should
bring you over there right now.
Let's make sure that you get your fill of rape.
I-I'm cumming!
That was so good.
Okay, let's get going.
Yuruka?
What have you done?
B-But...
He was gonna...
What are we going to do?
Hey, Shiina, are you...
Wait!
This is...
What is it?
Message from Josh_id
Done yet?
The security system's going back to normal in five minutes.
Apparently, Chiba-san's already at the lift station.
Message from Josh_id
Hurry up~
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч