Me?
Are you sure?
You're who I want, Emmy.
It's so beautiful!
I'm home!
Th-Thanks for having me over.
Hm? Mom?
Not home?
Looks like it...
That sucks, I really wanted to tell her about us.
Well, I'm going to take a shower then.
Can't you just use Dash Mist.
You saw the video when you were little too, didn't you?
The popular brand name deodorants and cleaning products.
Have been manufactured with the main
goal being the removal of smells.
As a result, they do not sufficiently sterilize the area.
Be careful so as to not forget to use the special
shower head to thoroughly clean inside.
Type Three Soap
Shower head for
Vaginal Cleaning
Be sure to always keep safe sex on the mind.
See?
You still remember this?
Yeah, I practically have it memorized.
I've seen it so many times by now.
Really?
Beginners guide on sexual intercourse
Then we don't have to look at the guide then, right?
Yeah, I got this.
When you're ready to do the deed, the
first step is to take off your clothes.
Then be sure to apply the sticker
from this box to your abdomen.
Make sure to put the sticker for the
appropriate gender onto each other.
It will take about five minutes for the results to appear.
Until then, alleviate your partner's nervousness
by kissing or licking the penis.
Here you go.
Wow, you really have it memorized.
Stop, it feels good.
Wow, they're already this hard.
Emmy?
I think my dick's ready.
Huh?
Already?
He's so cute.
E-Emmy...
That's tasty!
Oh wow, it is.
What does yours taste like?
Why don't you try it for yourself?
Hm, let's see.
Vanilla?
Yep!
Doesn't this make you feel like we're perfect for each other?
O-Oh, you're so cute.
Can I kiss you?
Of course you can.
You're so good.
It feels really good.
That's good.
I've been practicing.
How?
Like this.
You look so stupid!
That stupid?
Yeah.
My dick feels like it's about to melt.
Breathing...
Let's match our breathing.
It'll apparently make this hurt less.
Okay.
Emmy, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!!
Do it!
Cum inside me!
So, I was at the archives, reading a book
from the twenty-first century.
You really do love history, don't you?
Apparently back then, sexual relations
between kids our age was forbidden.
Oh, really?
I feel bad for them.
It feels so good.
Yeah.
So when are we gonna make a baby?
Huh? Aren't you jumping the gun a little?
Not at all!
We can get a license for it next year!
Y-Yeah, we can, but...
I want to hurry and see what our kids look like...
That's what I've been thinking...
Hey, mister?
Can you get the ball for me?
Okay.
Here it comes!
It fell!!
It's fine, I can apparently have it reissued to us anyway.
What were you thinking, you idiot!
Let's get the license over spring break, together.
Yeah!
Let's do it!
I love you!
Nothin' today either, huh?
Let's head back, Youni.
I think I'll hang around a little...
What's the matter?
I got something!
So they use this up there to form a pact, huh?
Pact?
Like a promise between the person
you give this ring to, to make kids.
Oh yeah, I've heard about that!
If it's something that important, maybe we'll
be able to get a lot of money for it!
Hm, not sure.
It seems like one of the free ones
that they give out to people.
It's not even made of anything valuable.
But it's really beautiful.
I guess it'll all depend on the data inside it.
What, another customer? It's not even five yet.
It's better than waiting around doing nothing.
You always tell me that it's dangerous, but
it's easy money. They always overpay.
So look into this while I'm gone, okay?
Sure.
Hello.
Welcome.
Please come in.
Is this your first time, sir?
Oh, y-yeah.
Okay then, I'll get you ready with the pin.
Okay, you're good to go now.
What'd you like?
Y-Your mouth.
Got it.
H-Holy shit!
I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
That was amazing!
Youni-tan!
I'm cumming!
Youni? It's me.
Wait a sec.
This is seriously the worst!
If you had performance enhancement surgery
on your balls, tell me that ahead of time!
Cumming ten times in an hour is messed up!
God damn it, it's so gross! So gross! So gross! So gross!!
You weren't able to tell just by looking?
Not much of a pro, are you?
Shut up, you idiot!
He was hiding the scars from the operation!
I even checked beforehand!
Well if he knew your name, that
means he was aiming for you.
After all, down here, even people from
the surface can retain their anonymity.
I bet somebody just leaked some kind of random
information again! Geez they do nothing but cause trouble!
Yeah and they all know where you live. Thanks
to you, it's been nothing but a pain in my ass.
Oh so they come on to you too? Want
me to patch up your butt for you?
Why do you sound so happy?
Well forget about that. Here.
Oh.
sad
So it didn't sell?
It's not something to be to hung up about.
The partner registration happened sixteen hours ago.
The registration office should be closed
from eleven o'clock at night.
And their account's still active.
So?
So... the ring itself has no monetary value,
but it can still do something for us.
What do you mean?
We can withdraw a fixed sum of money
from their social security account.
Enough to buy us a ride up the lift.
So we can go to the surface?
Probably.
Hey!
Let's have sex.
We don't have the time right now.
But...
Oh god, what should I do? What should I do?!
Calm down.
We need to get the money before the office opens at eight.
Let's start packing for now.
G-Got it.
We have enough time to eat though.
This might be the last time we eat stuff like this.
I'd be fine with that.
Okay, let's meet in front of the fifth
turnstiles at AZ10 at eight.
Huh? We're not going together?
I don't know how long it'll take to get the money.
Going Up
I need to go to an ATM to get the money first.
We also have to take into consideration
how long it'll take you to get ready.
Wear the nicest clothes you can so
you don't attract any attention.
Is this good enough?
Cash Corner
Next person in line please.
There's a huge line here. I might be late.
Okay. I'm just about to leave.
Oh, you're trembling? That's so cute.
I can't believe I got to see a girl piss herself
with my own eyes. I'm so touched!
Sorry, Youni-chan.
Truth is, we'd really rather not do this, but
we came all the way down to this layer.
And then we find out we need
an appointment or some shit.
Hey, I didn't tell you to suck it!
This is something that we should
decide with rock, paper, scissors.
Get me in there too!
Get off, dumbass!
Let's just do rock, paper, scissors already!
What's wrong with these people?
I'm already about to cum!
Such a quickie!
What's wrong with that?
Stop fighting.
She's drinking it!
There's so much...
Drink up.
I'm next.
This is the best.
These guys all had the enhancement surgery!
Not good!
What should I do?!
I need to go!
Look how hard it is.
I love how it's so tight it almost hurts.
I'm kinda pissed right now, so do it right.
Hey, suck on it more!
Oh man, this is too good.
So tasty.
And I've never had a body like
her's before. It tastes so good!
Sorry I'm late.
What took you so long?
Hi everyone, please, dig in.
Hot damn!
Y-You serious!
Good girl. I'm so happy you helped me cum so much.
Chiba-san, you wanna shoot one off?
You sure? Thanks.
I'll just jump right in.
We left her back open just for you.
You serious? Thanks so much!
Man, no matter how many times I see
that thing, it always freaks me out.
Don't worry, it'll feel great!
I'll stretch your asshole out for you.
Your balls look like they're about to burst right now.
Yeah, I just had the surgery done two days ago.
Recovery was a bitch, but...
Youni-chan, you have such a great ass!
My balls are ready.
Damn, that really was good.
It's been so long since I came this much.
Okay everyone, I'm done.
Shit I'm so turned on! I'm so ready to go!
G-Give me her ass.
I-I want her ass too!
First come first serve!
Come on, you serious?
Look at all that cum though.
She's so cute.
N-No...
Central Turnstiies
Damn it.
What are you doing?! I told you not to be late!
What's your relation to Youni-chan?
Who the hell are you?
A customer.
Why at a time like this?!
Where you off to?
To the surface.
How much longer 'till you're done?
Ten hours or so maybe.
Huh?!
Business is booming here. Youni-chan's
crying tears of joy right now.
Don't lie to me.
Why do you think I'm lying?
Youni-chan, you like dicks?
I love them!
Your pussy and ass feel really good too, don't they?
They feel really good!
Listen kid, even if you go to the surface,
there's nothin' good waitin' for you.
Everythin' up there's all soft and cuddly... it's boring as shit.
It's not fun at all.
And what, do you think you'll be able
to make it when you're up there?
You're gonna be completely out of
your element. How's that better?
Huh? He hung up.
I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna fill your stomach with my cum!
Hey everyone, it looks like we're getting
a new wave of people after noon.
Everyone who wants a turn, get in before they come!
Police Office
Don't ever do anything like that again. Get out of here.
Yes.
North Bound Final Stop
North Bound
'Kay, I'll see you guys later.
Later.
Call me over next month too.
I-I'm coming in.
Youni?
H-Hey! Are you okay?!
Don't say anything. I'll untie you...
Hey mister, put your dick inside...
Hey, your dick...
Give me your dick...
Come on, hurry...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч