Donors make human world peace.
Are you fine with someone like me?
It has to be you, Emmy.
It's beautiful!
I'm home!
S-Sorry for the intrusion.
Eh, Mom?
Nobody's home?
Seems so.
It's a pity. I even told them about it.
Shall we take a shower for now?
Isn't spraying deodorant good enough?
No it isn't. Remember what
that video we saw long ago said?
Nowadays, there is a broad selection of
deodorants and other manufactured products
for removal of various unpleasant elements,
but lacking adequate antibacterial properties.
Before sexual intercourse, take a bath
with your own exclusive soap
and be sure to wash your genitals
and clean your mouth as well.
Always keep hygienic and safe sex in mind.
See?
You still remember it.
I mostly memorized it,
since I watched it many times.
We don't need the guide then.
Trust me.
After the preparations, take your clothes off
and stick the patch on your abdomen.
Be sure to use the patch according to gender.
It will take around 5 minutes to take effect.
Until then, ease each other's tension
by kissing and licking one another.
Here!
You really memorized it.
Oh, it feels good!
Wow, they already got this hard.
Emmy, my dick became like this.
How cute.
Emmy...
Delicious!
It is.
How does yours taste?
Want to check it out?
Hmm... Let's see...
Vanilla?
Correct!
Aren't we really compatible with one another?
Yeah... how cute.
Can we kiss?
Sure, we can.
You're good at this. I love it.
I'm glad... I practiced for it.
How?
Like this!
You look like an idiot!
Was it that weird?
Yes it is.
My dick feels melting...
Your brea—
Match your breaths...
and it will be easier to come... says the guide.
Alright.
Emmy, I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Come!
Come inside me!
I read a 21st century textbook from the archives earlier.
You always loved history.
In that period, it seems that people our
age are not supposed to have sex yet.
Ehh... is that so?
What a shame, even when it feels good.
So, when will we have kids?
Isn't it a bit early?
No, it's not!
We're getting our license next year!
Well that is... true....
I want to have your child already...
or so I think.
Onii-san!
Pass the ball!
Okay!
Here you go!
Ahh, it fell down!
It's alright. We can have another one reissued.
What have you done, idiot!
Let's get our license together on spring break.
Let's do.
I love you!
There's nothing today as well... Let's go home, Youni.
I'm gonna stay a little longer...
What's the matter?
I found one!
Youni and Ko
They use this for a contract up there.
Contract?
This symbolizes the promise to
have a child together, maybe?
Ah, I've heard about that.
This seems very important,
won't this sell for a good price?
I wonder.
It's issued by the government almost free of charge.
It's not made of rare material as well.
But it looks very pretty.
It depends on the the inside information, I guess.
Is it another walk-in customer?
I told you to ignore those. It's already past 5 o'clock.
It's more lucrative than grinding tea leaves.
And even if you say that it's dangerous,
walk-ins are easy prey.
They ignorant of prices.
Well then, I'll let you handle this.
Try to make some cash from it if it can be sold.
'kay.
Good afternoon.
Welcome.
Please come inside.
Is this your first time?
Ah! Y-Yes...
Ah, then let's use the pin first.
There. It's done.
What should we do first?
Suck it.
Okay.
A-Amazing!
Coming... coming... comiiiiiing!
You're the best, Youni-tan!
I'm coming!
Youni, I'm here.
Gimme a sec...
Kuh... This is the worst...
He should've told me first that
he has augmented testicles!
He came in me 10 times in 1 hour... What the hell!
Gross, gross, gross, gross, gross, gross!
You fail as a pro to overlook his body mod.
Shut up, idiot!
I made sure to check it but
he hid it in his surgical records!
Well, he knows your name so he must
have looked for you specifically.
It is relatively safe even for the people from
above to pay for anything here in the Under.
I bet there's a bunch of dubious info about
everything sold around. How vexing!
If we only know the source...
Me too. My ass hurts because
of a certain popular idiot.
So you have been visited as well.
Want me to lick your ass?
Why do you look happy?
Forget about that. Look.
It never got sold.
Don't feel disappointed.
The partner registration was 16 hours ago.
The public office will close in 11 hours.
Its account is still alive.
And?
What I mean is...
The ring itself is worthless, but it can give money.
What do you mean?
It's from a social welfare account, so it can
be used to withdraw a fixed amount of cash.
We can buy tickets for low-class seats...
And we can go above?
I think.
Hey!
Let's have sex.
Whoa! We don't have time for this.
But I...
What should we do?!
Calm down.
We won't get the money until the office opens at 8.
Let's pack our stuff first.
O-Okay.
Don't worry, we still have time to eat.
Will it be the last time that
we eat something like this?
I wish it is.
Let's meet at the front of A10 in the 5th floor.
In a different line?
We don't know when the bus might get stopped.
I'll be going to Layer A which have an ATM.
You have some preparations to make as well.
Wear your best clothes to avoid raising any suspicion.
Is this good enough?
The queue is long. I might get a little late.
Got it. I'll be on my way.
Oh-ho, she's shivering in fear. How cute.
Suddenly doing a peeing show. I'm impressed!
Sorry, Youni-chan.
We really don't want to do this,
but we took the trouble on getting off on this layer
and you just rudely told us off that
we don't have any appointments.
Don't suddenly get started!
Let's settle this with rock-paper-scissors.
Give me some here!
Cut that out!
Rock-paper-scissors!
What's with these people?
I'm coming soon!
Quickshot!
Who cares? Stop arguing.
D-Drink it all.
There's so much.
Hmm, nice gulp!
I'm next.
Wooh, this is the best!
These people are augmented men. This is bad.
What should I do?
I have to go.
Your clit is erect.
This kind of painful narrow tightness is excellent.
Stop describing every single thing!
Hey, suck me more!
Wow!
It's hard to stop when you try it.
And this unfamiliar metabolic boost feels terrific!
Sorry we're late!
It's about time.
Okay everyone, come in!
Fuck yeah!
F-For real!
Alright, coming so much feels good?
Chiba-san, can I also pop a quickie?
Of course you can. Suit yourself.
I'll take care of the back.
Really, don't hold back.
Whoa...
I saw it many times yet it still gives off a nasty impact.
It's okay, this will feel like heaven!
It will be like drilling her asshole.
Oh, isn't the head bulging?
I had it implanted the day before yesterday.
These past two days were hell.
Youni-chan, I'll come lots for you!
Ah, you're really a good girl!
It's been a while since I felt like this.
Here, take your turns everyone.
Whoa, I'm excited! Can I really fuck her?
Then, I'm taking her ass!
Wait, I want to fuck her ass too!
First come, first served!
Seriously?!
What an incredible amount...
Pretty!
No good...
Shit!
What are you doing?! Didn't I tell you to not be late!!
What's your relationship with Youni-chan?
Who are you?
Her customer.
Why today, of all times?
Where are you going?
We're going up. How much longer will you take?
Around 10 hours more.
Huh?!
It's a big success! Youni-chan is happy. She's shaking her hips in ecstasy.
Y-You're lying!
Why would I even lie?
Youni-chan! Do you love dicks?
Yes....
Having your pussy creampied feels good too, right?
Feels good....
Hey kid, even if you go above,
there's nothing good there.
Everything is too easy there, nothing's worth seeing.
It's a boring place.
There you can't fuck girls from the Under.
Adults only kiss, it's sucks!
Eh, did he hang up?
I-I'm coming!
Your insides are the best!
Deep inside!
Listen everyone! It's already past noon
so it's the third batch's turn now!
Anyone who wants to fuck should do
it now before it gets more crowded!
Y-You're right!
You're next to me!
Hey!
Cut that out!
Don't do something like that again.
If you understand, get going already.
Okay.
I'll be going then.
Good work!
Be sure to call me in again next month!
I'm going in.
Youni?
Shit! Hey, are you alright?!
Don't speak. I'll untie you now.
Hey mister...
Fuck me...
Hey... dick...
Give me some dick...
Please, do it quick...
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project