Julka-chan, I'm ready.
I think I'll start with your front hole today.
I'm gonna cum!
That ring... it's made in the city.
Oh?
I hear that something good
happens when you wear it.
Something good?
I'm sure it'll bring you happiness.
I am happy.
Even more.
I wonder if I'll become the best doll.
I'm sure you will.
February 3rd.
Suzuki-san: Short-standard, came twice.
Urakabe-san: Came by before going to work.
Really seems to like fellatio.
Came on my tongue twice.
It's been a while since I tasted unseasoned semen.
Lounge: Tea with Miku.
Training Room: Fellatio practice.
I spent a lot of time trying,
but I couldn't beat last month's score.
Kimura-san: Long-superior, came four times.
Drops by when on patrol.
I tried inducing orgasm by licking
the balls, but it failed.
Kimura-san also used my pussy, so I'm glad.
I think I've got the timing down
for vaginal contractions.
I received a ring.
Subject Preparation Room   Medical Room
Since morning, you've been
really sucking out a lot!
Hey, have you heard?
What?
About the incident.
Seems it was that group.
Oh... But don't they never kill?
True, but there was their usual graffiti at the scene.
The report said strangulation.
Maybe they messed up breath control play?
That's terrible...
How pitiful...
What an idiot.
Hm?
An unlicensed prostitute who
can't do crisis management...
It's no surprise that she was killed.
What's pitiful about that?
Hey! Saying it like that...
Don't worry about her, Miku.
Sheena, you were with that bald guy
for the whole morning again.
That's why you're in a bad mood, right?
Hang in there.
Shut up, fucking bitches...
Just die, seriously. Just die.
What's her problem?
Sheena's so weird.
There's never been a doll like her before.
Don't let it bother you.
If you let it bother you, it'll affect your work.
We should always think about
making our clients happy.
That's our Julka!
Yum!
Ah, I can't believe she's my junior.
I'm here.
Thanks for your hard work.
We've got a message from your first client tonight.
Let's see...
Doll
Julka
elected Outfit
Dress
Total
er Comments
I want to enjoy the smell of a real girl.
I would especially like for her genitals to
smell of urine. My tesucles augmented.
Urine...
Get the scent applied in the Medical Room.
Sensei, please make this drinkable.
And how do I quickly accumulate smegma?
Eh? What's that about?
Wow! You're so cute!
Thank you.
Wow! Delicious!
I'm glad. Feel free to help yourself to a refill.
That's why you're #1.
Thinking up such a unique service...
Thank you.
At first I was thinking about a girl named
Sheena, but I'm glad I chose you instead.
Oh, that's curious...
That girl doesn't have many customers.
So you think it was obvious that I'd choose you?
Well, yes.
How confident you are.
Oh, this is it!
The smell of a woman has such a
unique and aromatic fragrance.
Ohh... I want to stay like this forever.
I think you'll find what's inside
to your liking as well.
I already saw it in the sample, but looking at
it here your asshole's really something...
I thought about making it prettier, but
everyone says it's perfect as it is.
It's beautiful.
That feels good!
It's so delicious!
You can't wait, can you?
I'm coming!
You're great at keeping me on the edge.
Put it in your mouth.
Yes!
All of it.
Amazing!
OK, Julka-chan... I want to move.
Your throat feels good.
Sorry, I came hard down your
throat before I knew it.
Yay, I'm glad.
You came so much for me.
Did my throat feel that good?
She's a pro.
I'm really liking this.
Let me fuck your ass.
Shall I clean it?
No need for that.
Hurry up and spread your legs.
You're a sadist, Taki-san.
Julka, you're a masochist, aren't you?
We're a good match.
No, I'm not an M.
Then what are you?
I just like things that feel good.
If I can make my customers happy, I'm happy too.
That feels great!
You're a total masochist!
Despite the looks, it's tight inside.
That's because I've been practicing.
What's this? Looks like you're
losing your composure.
I'm coming!
Why aren't you coming?
It's just late ejaculation.
You liar...
Well...
Julka-chan, technology is so amazing.
You can train and enhance even
the most minor characteristics.
But that also makes me want to break it.
Now that's a nice face!
You're so cute right now, Julka.
No, no!
We're already on our 10th round.
Come!
Where do you want it?
In my pussy...
That's good.
Tighten up just like that.
This is the best!
I wonder how many more times I can come.
I'm gonna cum again.
This asshole is the best!
Julka, nice work.
You too.
Sheena, thanks for your hard work.
It wasn't hard.
Taki-san (New): Long executive, came 12 times.
I could tell from the reservation that he's
a customer with strong preferences,
But he really exceeded expectations.
He made me come so much.
It's not a service if I'm gettin more
pleasure than the client is.
Even if it felt so good I might
have died from pleasure.
I'm exhausted.
Well, he really satisfied me, so we'll say it's all right.
Doing it with Taki-san taught me that there are still
plenty of pleasures in this world that I haven't found yet.
It's not like he did anything that different,
but it was really amazing.
It's been 5 years since my first time.
Maybe I've become a little conceited.
We exist to receive humanity's sexual desire.
My clients' happiness is my happiness.
Tomorrow I'll make an active effort to do my best.
To become the best doll...
Hi, what's up?
Have you seen Taki-kun's post?
It's in the training section.
Not yet, I'll take a look.
What were you doing?
Oh...
I was looking at that year-end post again.
Nice... You know it's good when
it has you coming back.
Yeah, that's right!
Just the thought of it makes me wanna cum.
Good idea!
I'm reserving these girls for tomorrow...
...but it's decision day.
FUCK!
I made a reservation for a threesome.
With those two girls of course. (Executor)
Sounds good. Let's do it.
All right.
OK, take care.
Quit slacking.
'kay!
Nothing out of the ordinary...
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Sheena-chan, your reactions
are so innocent. I love it!
Tomorrow night's client asked
for you two by name.
He requests you wear girls' uniforms
from the late A.D. era,
So he doesn't want to see your
collars for even a second.
We normally decline these requests,
but he's offering quite a price,
so we've specially approved it.
You'll receive a bonus for the work as well.
Wow!
So we'll take care of your collars here
before you go to the waiting room.
When you're done, they will be delivered
to the room, so just wait there.
Understood.
Yes.
Then, that's all.
It's just like heaven.
Now this is something...
Will you be coming?
Yes, I will.
Very well.
Delicious.
I'm gonna come.
Excellent.
That's good.
It tastes so bad. I'm gonna puke.
You really hate semen, don't you.
Sheena-chan, there's a rumor going around.
What rumor?
About a strange doll in The Dollhouse who
doesn't seem synthetically-made at all...
That it's almost like she's a human-born girl.
Sheena-chan, your body's so warm.
You're right. How cute.
How lovely.
Alright, let's enjoy our time as best we can.
There's still an hour left.
Let's give it our best.
I don't think I can...
You came so many times, didn't you.
You're really enjoying this, aren't you?
Just die.
You're so cute. You really have
to stop talking like that.
What?
I'll clean you up.
Hey, Julka...
Have you ever thought about quitting as a doll?
I'd never!
That's no good, Sheena.
Dolls never think about that.
Don't worry, I'm sure you'll be popular soon.
When you're having sex, you're really cute!
From now on, I'll teach you
anything you want, okay?
OK...
All right...
Shall we go a round again?
Go ahead.
Julka... don't stop!
Julka?
I think she's in heaven.
What... What have you done?
I gave her a strong one.
It makes her orgasm nonstop.
It's so tight.
Well then, Sheena-chan.
It's OK. I won't use it on you.
That drug only works on dolls.
I feel bad for your father,
but he did some wonderful work in the end.
Sleeping with his beloved 8-year-old daughter,
having her go underground...
It's like he was handing you to us.
Now I'll be sneaking you out here and
taking you to my friend's place.
It's taken a record number
of people to pull this off.
They're all your big fans. They know everything about you, from
your deflowering day to the number of creases in your asshole.
Hang in there.
Peeing out of excitement?
Well if you're so happy about this,
I'd better hurry up and get you out of here.
Show them your thanks with your body, OK?
I-I'm coming!
That was great!
Shall we go then?
Julka...
What have you done?!
I had to...
You were going to be...
What do we do?
Sheena, are you really...
Wait!
This is...
What?
Message from Josh_id
Non done yet?
Their security system goes back online in 5 minutes.
Chiba-san's already at the lift station.
Message from Josh_id
Hurry up, OK?
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч