You are doing good, young lady.
Make me much stickier.
More, more,
and more...
Hey, don't you wanna taste me?
Oh yes! Please fuck me in the ass!
I want your dirty cock to stir me up in the ass...
Freakin' ay, you make me horny.
Your vagina is telling me that she wants my penis.
Hurry, put it in. I want it now.
Alright, if you insist!
Ahhh! Fuck, this feels great!
Your cock is long and fat, I love it!
Please cum inside me.
You don't need to say that twice.
Cum inside me.
Ohh... ahh... Hey, don't urinate in me.
Yes, that's great, YES!
Oh, ahh, please...
Please Cum inside me, CUM, CUM!!
My soul is being fulfilled. The man's essence is
my life source...
In return of pleasure, sacrifice your soul to me...
The pact of the soul has been achieved.
A new day is always a new start.
What is it this time?
I... I bought this perfume for you yesterday...
It's almost your birthday Ms. Sayoko, so I...
Well, it smells like my mother.
Do you have some sort of complex with your mother,
Junichi?
No, it's nothing like that...
So she is indeed a pest.
Should I kill her?
No. At least, not here.
If any more problems happen, we won't be able to
hold off the cops... Also,
I don't want the chairman to get involved in this.
Let's take care of it on our own, slowly...
I, I also have concert tickets and...
I'm sorry, but I have plans for tonight.
Besides, you should be studying!
You don't want me to tell your mom, do you?
Why, yes. But Miss Sayoko,
My mom is no longer part of this world.
Huh!?
I'm... sorry...
This smells nice...
OK, homeroom time is now over.
I will now introduce all of you to a new classmate.
Nice to meet all of you. My name is Yuka.
Wow!
You mean you failed?
Yes, there was an accident...
That means we have to approach this differently,
I'm sure they are aware of our presence now.
Aiko, something was different about her...
Alright, let's leave this school then, Sayoko.
Huh?
Thanks for being on my side.
Not yet, let me stay at this school for a little longer.
Sayoko...
Ms. Kirika, I, I am about to cum...
Go ahead... cum on face!
Ahh... Ms...
Ms. Kirika...
Go ahead... didn't you want to do it?
I know you have always wanted to fuck me
from behind...
Oh, ahh, c'mon, stick your finger inside my ass...
I never knew you were like this, Ms. Kirika.
I'm a new person now.
I've given my soul to the great Mesphito and
I went to hell for it.
Give it to me harder! Fuck me like how Mesphito
fucks me!
I'm going to cum, ahhh!!
Oh yes!!!
He died.
My part of the plan is going on track.
How about yours?
Yes, I plan to retrieve it tonight.
She is a night dweller.
On a full moon like tonight, she will most likely be
looking for a prey.
You're such a slut. Can't you wait until we get a
room?!
Yes, lick my dirty hole.
Please, violate my ass too.
Violate inside my ass too!
Oh, that's right... caress my tits.
I'm going to piss on you if you do that!
Then piss, bitch!
Oh my...
PPlease look at me piss, look!
This is so great...
Let me make you cum!
I love the smell of penis...
The moon is still shining bright. Stick your penis in
my vagina.
It's so thick! Ah... it's wonderful!
Give it to me in the ass too! Ah... hurry!
Harder...
Yes, that's it.
Give me...
Give it to me inside my pussy!
More, more... Yes!!!
Give me your entire load!
Ah, no, not yet...!
I'm still not satisfied, I want more cum!
Her blood should be overwhelming her today...
And tonight might be the night we can seal her power.
My blood, it's lusting. It' s still lusting for a man...
This is why I hate the full moon.
Looks like you lose your senses when you're
in heat.
I didn't think trapping you would this easy.
Don't bother me when I'm alone.
And what can I do for you, Ms. Kirika?
Oh, nothing. I just want a sample of your blood.
I'm sorry, but blood extraction is not my thing.
You are that bodyguard, argh!
When your blood in lusting, your five senses goes
numb, but don't worry.
I won't kill you someone wants to see you in pain.
And tonight, we're we're just getting ready for it!
You can't die simply from this right?
This trap is not something you can't handle, right?
Only if my blood was lusting...
Hehe, in return of sharing your blood, I will give you a
present.
Oh, this is great!
How is it? Don't you love it...?
Ciao.
Oh, ahh, ahhh, great!
More, more, and more...
I'm cumming!
I wonder what Ms. Sayoko is doing...?!
Ms. Sayoko!! What is wrong!? Sayoko!!
Ms. Sayoko!!
WWhhere is... argh... I feel, hot...
Ms. Sayoko, don't get up yet.
I was surprised when I suddenly saw you naked...
I thought you were involved in some freak accident.
If you were, you're more than welcome to stay here.
Thank you, boy.
What?
I don't know who you are, but you are
such a nice boy.
Let me give you areward.
Ms, Ms. Sayoko, what are you doing?
She's so soft. This smell... It's the perfume
I gave her.
She smells like mom...
I'll make you feel good.
Whhat are you saying Ms Sayoko?!
You don't need to by shy.
You can fuck me in the ass, if you want.
Huh?!
C'mon, I'll make you feel good.
No, this, this is just a dream. It's a dream!
Hehe, you're so cute.
That's the picture of my dead mom.
Mother...
Sayoko, Ms. Sayoko!
I have retrieved it.
Good job. I can not wait for the next full moon.
Ms. Sayoko...
You have such a talent for art, Ms. Ayako.
My, thank you Sonia.
When this doll is completed...
What should I do?
Ms. Sayoka has been asleep ever since that day.
But, who can I talk to about it...
But no matter what, I will protect Ms. Sayoko!
You will protect who?
What did you say about Ms. Sayoko?
Yu, Yuka, nothing, it's nothing!
I haven't seen Ms. Sayoko in a while.
Don't tell me you have imprisoned her?
That's ridiculous!
Besides, who the hell are you?
Why should a new student like you have to worry
about Ms. Sayoko?
Hmm, are you sure you don't know anything about
her?
I, I don't!
If you know, you better tell me where she is!
I don't know anything!
I see...
So, it's complete now.
Yes.
The moon is full.
I, I only live for you to give me pleasure, Sonia.
A good girl like you deserves some.
I will fuck your brains out tonight!
That's right, cum all you want!
Its big, it's so big! Ah...
Almost, almost... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'll cum inside you!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm...!!!
Cumming!!
What's wrong Ms. Sayoko?
No, we must take you to a hospital.
Um... Ssstop...
Ms. Sayoko... knock some senses... Sayoko.
We finally meet.
(chanting...)
Huh... what?!
She should be fine now...
What just happened here?
I don't know...
I saw her naked in the streets and I just helped
her out.
That's it? Did you see anything else?
Nothing...
Ms. Sonia, the school chairman, and Kirka...
Ms. Sonia had a penis and...
You know too much... I can't let you live...
Wait!
Don't hurt him! That young man saved my life...
Ms. Sayoko...
More troubles might happen...
That's ok. I will protect him...
Don't worry, I'm here...
Fine, fine...!!