That's my ass...
That's my ass! Oh...!
My ass... my ass feels great!
Oh yes! More... violate my pussy and ass, please!
Violate me more, more! Give me more...!
I'm cumming!
Me, too!
Hey, give it to me more. More, more! I want more!
Everyone, please be quite.
I will introduce all of you to a new teacher.
My name is Sayoko and I will be here as a
counselor temporarily.
I will be in the office most of the time, so please stop
by when you have the chance.
Hey... isn't that...?
Yeah, it's the girl we fucked...
The one that asked us about the drugs...
...and left while we were asleep.
This is going to be fun.
We are so lucky.
She is so beautiful...
If I follow the source of this drug, I will find them.
It seems like Mikami College has some
connection with the drug.
Sayoko, I order you to investigate the school.
I have already made arrangements for you.
Understood.
Who is it?
Umm, well, uhh, I'm Junichi Yano.
Well, umm, Sayoko...
Oh, may I call you Sayoko?
Aren't you supposed to be in class?
Well, yeah, but...
How did your voyeurism go?
No, I wasn't! I was just filming you!
Filming your beauty, Sayoko.
I want to make a film, about you...
By all honesty...
Ooops!
Oh my.
I, I will do anything for you Sayoko. It's the truth...
Thank you, Junichi.
You’re welcome...
And nice to meet you too!
Ms. Sayoko, let me tell you one thing.
Since you are here temporarily, you will not be staying
for long.
This school has a lot more male students than female.
Please be careful with your actions.
That means, no sex with students.
Um, yes.
Please, I'm not interested in that kind of
behavior.
I am only in my 30's, but because of my
capabilities,
I am appointed the principal of the school.
Ah, what are you doing, Ms. Principal?
If you get me on my good side, I’ll make you feel
heavenly.
Huh? My body... it won't move.
And, feeling horny...
This sweet smell...
Her body odor...
My, my, you have a beautiful body.
Beauty gets more beautiful when it gets violated.
I want to violate you.
Aren't you a bit hairy down here?
Excuse me!
What... is that principal?
Ohh, my body...
I want to masturbate...
There she is!
So you want us to check her outright?
We fucked her last time.
She really loved the drugs you gave us.
Fine, we'll do it, bitch.
Don't overdo it.
So your name is Sayoko?
You two are...?
We were lonely because you suddenly left us
the other night.
Hey, don't you two want to go back to that hotel?
Wow, her pussy smells delicious!
Nooo, you're touching my pussy just right...!
If you continue to keep that pace...!
No, nooo!!!
This bitch... she's just a filthy dick hungry whore!
Why does the principal worry about her so much?
Yo, hope two dicks is enough for you today.
Shit, her tits are so soft!
Yes! Stench my tits with your dirty cock!
Damn man, she’s even more ambitious than last time!
Shoot your load on me!
Crap, I’m going to cum!
Give it to me... give it!
Ohh, the smell of cum!
This time, here...
Give me your huge cock... now.
See, you're still hung like a horse.
Hurry, don't make me wait. You know you want
some of this.
God, I can't wait any longer.
This feels great! Violate my pussy, violate it!
When you gotta cum, cum in my pussy!
Fuck, this is great.
It's a pussy from a different nebula.
It's my turn next!
Teach... I'm already... I'm already hard.
Why not stick it in my ass then.
Fuck me harder, please!
Fuck me!
That's right, keep double penetrating me.
Give me more cum!
It's not over yet, things are just getting started.
I... feel...
Me too... I feel strange.
My pussy and ass is slobbering for more
dirty cocks.
Stick it in me.
And lets go to hell together.
Yes, that's it!
Keep giving me you guys' cum!
Yes!!!
You guys were unlucky...
Two students dead?
Yeah, it's been rumored that they overdosed on
drugs.
Drugs?
They were hoodlums after all.
I've also heard they've been selling the drugs.
Umph!! If it was drugs, I wonder who their
distributor is?
I heard it's from someone with high powers.
I'm not sure of details,
But the principal might have something to do with it.
The two guys who died, frequently had meetings
behind doors with her.
The principal?
...excuse me.
Sayoko... coming Sunday, do you...
Hey, Junichi, do you know anything more about the
principal?
Man, do you like her that much?
Huh? Oh, I just wanted too...
Stop that!
Well, well, Sayoko.
How about a shot together?
Umm... please... stop.
Crap, she is really angry!?
Sayoko.
Looks like we made the right choice by
sneaking you into the school.
Thanks to your investigation, we found out who is
behind all this.
The big head...
Sayoko, here is your new order.
She is Aiko Nogami, kill her.
She is an owner of many restaurants and is also the
chairman of the school.
Aiko Nogami...
Make her perish from this world...
Aiko has just entered the school grounds.
She will be back in Yokohama by tomorrow morning.
It is out of our jurisdiction if she goes back to
Yokohama.
That means... I must kill her tonight...
Use this!
Alright, Mido.
I will kill her!
I wonder where the principal's room is at...
I don't want Sayoko to continue being angry at me.
I have to find out the principal's secret and make
Sayoko happy.
Wow!
Damn!
Isn't that the chairman and Kirika, the school board
leader?
What the fuck...!
Oh yeah, Ms. Chairman, that feels good!
Kirika... you belong to me...
That's right, feel the lust!
Oh, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!!
Ahhh, I'm cumming, ahhhhh!
Again?
Ohh, that's it...
The school principal having sex with her
students...
What is going on with this school?
Oh, yes...
Please continue to lick my sweet hole.
I will now suck your cocks in return.
You slaves have a great penis. Just wonderful!
Come here and let me have a taste of those cocks.
Give it to me up the ass too.
Yes, that feels great. More!
The two dicks are rubbing my g-spot!!
Oh... cum inside! Ahh...
Stick it deep in me and cum inside!!
I’m cumming!!!
Was that exciting for you...?
Shit! She knows!!
Don't move!!
Who, who are you?
Oh crap...
Who are you!
What's going on!
Stop!
Forget about it.
You humans won't be able to chase her.
I like to see strong girls like her cry in pain.
Me too, I’ll take care of her soon...
You bastard! You fucked up my mission.
Why were you there? Do you want to die?
Who would've thought something like that will
happen...
Besides, l wanted to find out about the
principal's secret
So I can make Sayoko happy...
Hey, you dumb ass...!
Don't you never do something like that again.
Crap. I should've been more careful!
That girl, Aiko Nogami...
She is no human being...
What is she?
Hey baby, what are you doing in this alley?
Are you celebrating Halloween already?
Hey, we're fucking horny.
Really... that's great. I’m hungry for a man.
Shit baby, you are amazing!
Ohh, cum!
Please make me more wet!
That's it, fulfill my lust. .
Do you want to stick it in?
I’ll do everything you want!