Just from that, your dick is already
starting to secrete love juices.
Onee-san, stop, or I'll come!
Not only is your dick repeatedly thrusting into me.
I bet you want to ejaculate lots of smelly come!
You annoying and perverted little brat!
If you want to come, go ahead and do it.
If your perverted penis can't withstand being thrusted
like this then there's no other way is there?
Like this...
I- I'm...
Oh, I'm gonna come!
Young boys are great.
Lustful Laughing Nurse
Counseling. 1
Onee-san, please stop.
Aren't you a noisy kid,
even though your dick is so hard.
Eh, looks like something's coming out.
So much white fluid is coming out of it.
O-onee-san!
You noisy kid.
This is a hospital, so be quiet.
It smells.
I'm gonna have to seal that loud mouth of yours.
No matter how much you say you hate it.
Your penis is still this hard.
You...
When you lick my pussy, your penis keeps throbbing.
Aren't you a perverted little boy?
Well, can you see it?
Your horny penis is about to be eaten by Onee-san.
All right, put it in slowly just like that.
My pussy just completely swallowed your dick!
No, Onee-san, let me go.
Your dick is repeatedly plunging into my pussy.
Let me go, I don't want this!
What are you saying at this time.
Your dick has already been swallowed by my pussy.
Mmh, I'm starting to like it.
You should have liked it from the start.
But what a pity.
Your dick is already enjoying my delicious pussy.
Ahh, how incredible.
No, I can't, anymore, stop moving.
Onee-san, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Well, well, you're coming already?
Hold it back a little longer.
No, I can't, I'm coming!
So you came. I bet you really enjoyed it, didn't you?
At first you say you don't want any of this sex,
But it turns out you're just a horny little dick boy, aren't you?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It's that perverted nurse.
She passed us.
Your skin is bare.
I'll bare mine too.
Hot, it's hot.
How's the smell of my sweat?
Can you smell the pheromones?
N-not really.
Hmm... what's this?
That's because you got naked.
Oh, so it's my fault?
You bad boy, now I'll have to punish you.
O-onee-san.
Do we really have to do this everyday?
Even though you say you don't want to, your dick is all hard.
A perverted little boy doesn't have
to hold back or anything, right?
S-Stop it, Onee-san.
Look, it's stained.
Looks good on you, you perverted little boy.
Wow, your dick has become so big,
the stockings are about to rip.
This is my pantyhose.
You better not dirty it with your smelly cock juice.
Feel bad? You perverted little boy.
Soon, all that smelly juice will come out.
N- No, I'm gonna come.
Don't, you can't come on my panties.
If this perverted boy's penis gets any bigger,
it's going to be bad for my panties.
You can't dirty these panties, so don't come.
Oh!
Aww, this perverted little boy dirtied my panties.
Looks like you need more punishing.
Excuse me.
Mi-Misaki-chan.
Yuu-kun, I've come to see you.
Hmm?
Please wait a moment, I'll be with you shortly.
Please.
Yuu-kun. You look a lot better now.
Thanks.
Are you in the middle of an examination?
If I'm being a bother, I'll go back soon.
Not really.
Yuuji-kun was just about to urinate into this container.
Wanna see?
U- Urinate?
It's quick, so I'll be fine.
Umm... hope it'll be quick then.
See you later.
M-Misaki-chan.
Well well, what's wrong with letting that
girl see your perverted dick urinate?
She's cute, I feel like I'm 10 years younger.
This is getting interesting isn't it?
Oh no, I forgot to give him this good luck muffler present.
Oh, you didn't cry at all right?
Was it because she was here?
With all this smelly stuff on my stockings.
I don't want it anymore.
With this much love juice coming out, why
don't you come for that girl to see?
Misaki-chan.
I wonder if he finished urinating...
Should be fine.
Eh?
Onee-san.
If you keep doing that with your tits...
What about it?
I'm gonna come.
Ah, your dick is so hot.
My tits are about to make you come.
Rubbing it like this, doesn't this feel great after all?
I... I'm coming!
Seems like the perverted boy is more suited
to the peeping perverted girl isn't he?
That woman... shall we rape her?
Your dick has become hard.
With such a horny penis, you're
sure to make Misaki-chan come.
Misaki-chan.
W-What, what is this...
Dirty love juice is also coming out from Misaki-chan's pussy.
No... Yuu-kun, don't look.
Y-Yuu-kun, are you alright?
He's not in pain, but in pleasure.
Yuu-kun actually likes doing perverted things.
Y-Yuu-kun is... perverted?
T-that's wrong, Misaki-chan.
Because Yuu-kun is perverted, his dick is all swollen.
He won't be able to put his pants back on like this, right?
Misaki-chan.
Please help cure Yuu-kun's sickness, okay?
Eh? N-No.
You're going to come an ocean inside your
cute girlfriend's pussy, aren't you?
No, Yuu-kun, don't.
Sorry, Misaki-chan.
Well, well, why don't you just come now?
Misaki-chan's gonna cure that perverted
dick of yours, isn't she?
No, don't do this horrible thing please.
Please, Yuu-kun, please stop.
So that you can come inside, I'll open this up for you.
Eh? N... no... Sto~
Eh... you came already, perverted Yuu-kun.
What is this... it smells.
Looks like perverted Yuu-kun hasn't had enough yet.
You'll have to come properly inside her this time.
Well, it went in.
Please come inside her, perverted Yuu-kun.
I-It hurts, please stop.
Misaki-chan's virgin pussy...
Come another ocean and fill it up.
No.
Well, feels good doesn't it?
O-onee-san, please stop, otherwise I'll really come inside her.
That's fine, go ahead and come.
Shoot all your load into her womb.
That's as far as you'll go, nurse.
W-what the hell are you guys~
We should be the ones saying "What the hell".
You dirty, perverted, unashamed bitch!
W-we're in the middle of something
private... so get out of here!
There's no way I can just let this slide.
Misaki-chan.
You perverted nurse. We're gonna punish you now.
No, wait, no.
There's no need to struggle.
No, with dick of this size I'll~
It's gonna go in sooner or later anyway.
N-no...
Oh look, all of it's in.
Oooh.
Start moving and let's see.
Oh, it's tight.
No...
It's moving so much inside.
It's like a gift from God.
What's that? You cant take it already?
This pussy is awesome!
No... take it out, take it out!
Ahh, I can't~
N-Nooo!
You idiot! I didn't do her yet, why
the hell are you coming inside!?
S-sorry, man.
Hazuki-san, your face is flushed.
You have a fever?
I- I'm fine.
R-right...
My penis definitely won't lose to
that inexperienced brats penis!
Here it comes!
It's too big... I'm going to break!
I-I'm feeling it...
Suck on it more!
It's been getting wetter and wetter ever since I first put it in!
It's exactly what I like!
Damn it.
Why do I have to suck on this dick?
What I like... are undefiled young boys.
No, don't look at me like that.
Not at this horribly perverted situation.
Hurry up and come!
Don't look at this dirty perverted woman.
Don't look at me, who's being raped
and sucking someone's dick.
Don't look!
Goddamn, she's so tight I'm almost at my limit! Hoho!
That's it, I can't move anymore!
How many decades has it been since I came inside?
Well? This is the Onee-san who's always
tormented and scared you.
Why don't you rape her too?
Stop it.
No, wait...
Regardless of what I said.
No matter how many times I told you to stop.
Sorry, I won't do it anymore... so.
Onee-san. I was forced against my will just like this.
No!
Onee-san, can you feel it?
You actually feel great having this done to you don't you?
Stop... no, that's not it, not it at all.
Onee-san, you're just as perverted as I am aren't you?
I'm not... perverted... why do you say that...
Oh look. You're moving by yourself, Onee-san.
I'm not!
Well, if you don't mind...
Eh? No, don't, that's my ass...
Me too!
Onee-san, can you feel it?
This torment, can you feel it?
Do this next!
Onee-san, can you feel it? I'm coming!
I'm coming, coming, coming!
I'm coming!
Here, for leaving the hospital.
This...
O-Onee-san.
If I start being unbearable, you can switch it on anytime.
OK. Well, see you later then, Onee-san.
Mm. Bye then.
O-Onee-san.
He showed us, didn't he? Even though he's just a kid.
I'll definitely get Miwako-chan back!
to be continued...