I, Shiratori call upon my blade
Respond to my summon
Respond to my Oath!
My name is Mikoto-san, Shiratori Mikoto
Awaken, Spirit Slaying Sword "Raikou"
Sorry, Mikoto.
I was all too slow.
We could not finish it off and kill it
I hope I can move a bit faster and find the main body.
We first need to detect it.
According to what you said
- Yamato-chan?
- Quick go change your clothes.
There's a pervert here staring at your chest.
Don't you dare peep of I'll kill you, Yamato.
Yeah yeah.
Although I always thought they were too bit in a way...
my heart leapt a little when he saw how big they were.
Disgusting, I'm not a naughty girl.
But, although this is rather embarrassing
I'm actually very happy about it.
Tch, do I also have any self-confidence in myself?
Yamato you idiot.
Yamato
Don't move, stay in this boundary to protect yourself.
Yamato!
Let go, I told you to let me go
Yamato, Mikoto!
Huh? No!
Don't...don't touch...Please stop it!
Don't touch...
Don't touch me...
Stop...this feels good
This feels good, Yamato
No...
Hey you guys...
why didn't you kill us earlier
I'll say it again, why do you keep ignoring me?
I'm not lying, you guys
I turned you into burning coal
Cut you half, then...then...
Please...that's enough...Ah!
Don't that...
Mi-Mikoto, hold on I'll...Ugh!
Yamato!
No, please stop now...
Please, Yamato could die...
Did you retreat while you were looking for me?
You are the demon spirit...
Amazing, such strong magic in the air...
I can't speak too long or the atmosphere will affect me...
His breath alone is making my body's insides burn up already...
If you can feel my breath that
means that you're nothing a lewd human being
I've heard once before
that they can transforms all of ones feelings and sensations into pleasure to make a
nightmare.
Frankly first,
those mildy shameful songs of yours appease me
Who's there...
This is the punishment that those who hurt me shall receive
Stop, he'll die
I was the one who hurt you
Leave him alone
Yamato!
This is part of the punishment for your arrogance.
Speak defiantly again and I'll kill him
Yes, I'm sorry
My breasts...Stop squeezing my breasts...
before I come...
Sorry, don't fondle my nipples...Ah!
I don't want to lose...Ah! Please
Don't make my body feel good anymore
Stop,it feels good...Ah!
My panties are soaked in juice and urine
I'm sorry, that wetness feels good...Ah!
Sorry...
I don't want to do it again
I've already apologized...
Don't. Ah!
Sorry, There...not there again!
No the pain is itching all over me so please stop
Yamato...save me
I'm going to lose...I'm going to lose...
I'm going to lost to depravity...
Don't. Ah!
No not there! Sorry!
Please!
Don't enter me...Don't enter my insides.
Don't...I'm not ready yet...
Please! I can't take it! Ah!
That...can't...no...
Don't Look!
Don't go any deeper...
It's already in enough...
No...no...
My virginity...It can't be...
I don't want to lose it like this!
Please, don't look
I see now
Is this why men enter slowly?
I now understand your desires...
Yamato!
No way...
Too big, shot into my stomach too many times...
Too painful...Ah!
Please...
Isn't that good enough
I don't want to endure more pain again
I'll apologize already.
No don't, please let me go...
It hurts...it hurts already...Ah!
My virginity....give it back...
This is my first...Ah!
Originally I wanted to give it to you...
but it's already been taken...sorry, Yamato
It hurts...to lose face like this...
I wish I was dead...Ah!
Sorry, I'm such a weakling
Other than resisting, there's nothing I can do
Sorry
It does not matter if you resist...
When you see yourself in ecstasy
you're mind will have no choice but to give in...
No no, I don't want to see those things in my mind
What is that that thing doing looking at me
Don't, don't look at me...Ah!
Don't show me those kinds of things
My legs can't take it...being so open like that. Don't...Ah!
No this...Ah!
No! Ah! Stop, no...
Bearing this endless pain and suffering
is the only way to save that boy
Woman...what do you want?
I want it inside me...you're sticky semen...
So ashamed...Ah!
Where? Ah!
My most important...place...
It has a more suitable name
Vagina...I want it in my pussy...
Stop
Let me ruin you and let your body
experience the epitome of feminine pleasure
Don't feel ashamed, keep calling out slowly
and I'll liberate you from your body.
Feels...too good...Ah!
There...there...So full...Ah!
Fill me with happiness
Shoot it into my womb
That...in there...
Can't, the orgasm will be too good...
It's already hot enough inside me
There's so much cum inside already...Ah!, It's too good...Ah!
My mind is already gone...
melted into pleasure...
Going...going to...
I'm going to come!
Stop...Ah! Hot, this can't be...
How can it...why is it burning.
I'm going to faint from the heat
Really, the heat is going to make me faint.
Stop...please
Don't turn it around like that...
Don't do it...it hurts...Ah!
How can this be...
I'm going to come, I need to pee...
Let me pee
Pee...I want to pee...Ah!
Pee...it's coming...it's coming out...
No, stop drinking my urine...
Feels bad...Ah!
There...already...
Can't do it again, I'm already split open...
Begging for mercy? Only when you
climax and only then will I allow you to die.
No! No, I can't do it there again!
I won't ever exterminate demons again!
I swear!
Are you trying to deceive me or are you
just saying things in this disorientated state?
However, you do look truely cute like this.
Don't...
Even so. Don't...
I hate it, I can't take, I can't take it anymore.
What I've done is certainly a mistake.
No
Why?
That...
Only "that" I don't understand.
Not so...Ah!
Incredible...
This can't fit inside...it'd split me open
there and would break me
but...
It won't work, I can't act like that in front of a demon...
No
Please put the hard, hot thing into me!
Put in that hard thing, I can't take it anymore...
It looks so good...
Don't...
Amazing, so much went in.
My viginity snatched away like this...I'm so happy...
Being broken like this as a virgin is the best...
I can't...Ah!
Not wiping clean after urinating isn't good...
What?
How can I see that?
No
- Isn't this how one shows their love for someone's body
- Don't...Ah!
The important place I look after.
You still nothing but a lewd little girl
Don't...
Let me see you look more inviting...
Too shameful...Ah!, My anus..the hair around it...
it's shameful to look at
Letting that boy enjoy too is quite a pity...
That shameful girl with the pink hymen
still has a dissatisfied appearance.
What!
No...you can't...no...Ah!
That is something...
you can only give to someone you like...Ah!
No...Ah！
Sorry, Yamato
Although it's happening like this..
It's amaxing for Yamato to be hard like this...Ah!
Yamato...
So cruel...
Stop
My hymen, is there...
Why?....Ah!
I originally wanted to stay with Yamato
I'm alright like this...Ah!
Yamato and I haven't even lost our virginity yet
But...why can I not resist this?
Don't, don't go inside...
That is where...kids are born from...
Enjoy your ecstasy, you
are now pregnant with a little devil...Ah!
You're womb is begging for my semen
Not there, I can't...
This child's place...to insert and exert such force like this...
It feels so strange now...
This hot feeling, I want more of it...
But if it's not Yamato's child, I don't want it
Although I don't want to get pregnant...
For this huge thing to enter me...
It feels so wonderful. Ah! It's unbearable...
Amazing, so big...Ah!
It's filled me up entirely...amazing...Ah!
Although it is not Yamato, I want to come...
Beacuse...it feels to wonderful...Ah!
Please...don't...Ah!
Please....please
too much...
No, don't look, don't look
This is proof to turn you into my concubine...
You will realize this joyfully
It can't...too full...too full...Ah!
It's too hard, the thrusting...
Come...
I can't,Not so...Ah!
The force, it`s amazing...Ah!
I`m going to die, I can`t bear it
Sorry, Yamato
I want to come inside, it's too good...Ah!
Into my womb
I can't believe it's this good!
It doesn't matter if my insides become soiled...
Don't pull it out, I want your cock inside me...
Inside me
It's so hot inside of me...Ah!
Good, put it all in me
I want all of your semen to flow into my womb.
Although I don't want to become pregnant, I want all of your semen...Ah!
I can't endure it any longer
Sorry, Yamato...
If I become pregnant...I'm sorry...
This evening has finally ended and now we wait till dawn...
but this is only the devil's entrance...
OAV Inyouchu 2
You...Please...Forgive me...