In'youchuu Shoku
Monster Lust Bugs
and the Fallen Women Who Birth Them
Anime Edition
Oh, you're awake.
Good morning, Oka.
Isn't my baby so cute?
I wanted to show you, Oka.
Nee-sama...
It looks like you've had your babies come out alright too.
I'm happy for you.
Oh wait, you haven't started yet.
You're about to give birth, aren't you?
This sound...
I can hear the sound of eggs hatching inside me!
It's squirming, trying to get out!
It's coming out!
You did great, Oka.
Such a good girl.
Nee-sama...
But you're not out of the woods yet.
You still have more to give birth to.
My boobs are on fire.
They're tingling like crazy!
My nipples are so huge, I can tell how much they're leaking.
They're gonna be born!
Hey, girl!
You've been summoned by Meiouki-sama.
What are you waiting for?
My boobs are too heavy, I can't move.
Sure, put all the work on me!
Ow!
Please don't pull me!
I've brought her.
Thank you, you can leave now.
Mikoto-chan? Takeru-chan?
Stop it already!
Stop!
Oh wow, Sui, your boobs have gotten really big.
S-Sui?! No!
Don't look! Don't look!!
You just got a whole lot tighter all of a sudden.
You're gonna make my dick melt!
No! Don't say that!
It's been a while since you three
have been together, hasn't it?
Don't... move!
Th-This is so good! So good, Mikoto!
Takeru! Stop!
Takeru-chan was always so smart and kind...
I know she loved Mikoto-chan, so...
Why is she doing such horrible things to her?
It's because she loves her.
If you force a child's body to mature,
the love felt from that young age just seems to blow up.
I gave her a dick by her own request
and reunited the two of them.
My dick...
Nee-sama...
Well they're even closer now, so isn't that great?
That's not true!
This... This isn't right!
This isn't...
This is great!
Mikoto, your body feels so incredibly good!
Please, stop already!
We're sisters!
Your moans aren't sexy enough, Mikoto.
But squeezing the milk out of you turns me
on so much that it doesn't even matter.
Th-That's not...
You're so cute, Mikoto! Mikoto!!
I love you, nee-san!
I've loved you for so long!
Takeru, I love you too, but not in a romantic way!
Let me... go...
Just let me go, please!
No way!
We're just getting started!
You're going to become mine!
I'll never let you go!
No! Stop!
I'm gonna lose it! My body's gonna go crazy!
Are you getting turned on from watching them?
Then how about I play with you?
No! Don't touch me!
Oh, right.
You're still a virgin, aren't you?
I can't believe you'd still worry about your
virginity, even after getting like this.
Is there a guy you'd give your virginity to?
I wonder what that guy would say after seeing your tits.
That's fine. I promise not to take your virginity.
You'll just keep birthing demons
through your breasts as a virgin.
Let me help you!
Looks like it's time.
Time for them to be born.
Th-They're moving!
Th-The babies are moving inside my boobs!
Th-That felt so... good...
Sui! Sui!!
Keep it together! Sui!
Takeru! You're being too rough!
I'm inside you right now. You can't be looking at other girls.
I'll keep loving you until your head's
filled with nothing but me!
Takeru! Stop!
My stomach's starting to feel weird!
Looks like you're about ready to give birth too, nee-sama!
Actually I've been feeling like I'm about to give birth as well.
Let's give birth together!
Stop! Don't move my body like that!
My womb's gonna break!!
No!
It's coming out!
Something hot is coming out!
The baby is coming out!
They're rubbing against each other! The baby
and your dick are rubbing against each other!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
I love you! I love you so much, nee-san!
Let's cum together!
Let's have our babies together!
I'll make you have my baby next!
I-It's coming!
It's coming!
I'm cumming!
Babies feel so good!
It's coming out!
I did it...
I really gave birth...
These are my... babies?
Why are they so...
Well the slime that impregnated you
had human sperm mixed into it.
Because of that, they're born as
a failure half-breed monster.
The best that they can be is food for the other monsters.
So basically you're just a birthing
machine for monster fodder.
Just wait...
Yamato's going to come and save us!
Yamato...
Save us!
I...
I can't stay here!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч