Yamato, it's headed your way!
You're so helpless...
Takeru would laugh if she saw us right now.
She'd say something like,
"The two of you could only handle one opponent!?"
What about you, Mikoto?
You don't do so well when you have to defend in the darkness.
You're the one that's weak, idiot...
Yamato? Yamato? Yamato??
Yamato... I'm so relieved...
What happened to... Sui!?
Don't get up yet. You need to recover first.
He drained most of my power...
but I'll give it my all to heal you.
It's up to you from here, Yamato.
MeiohSubs Presents
Inyouchuu: Volume 2
QC: EchelonV
Translation: Barbar of Damascus
Mikoto!
I made a deal with him.
He said that he wouldn't hurt you if I didn't resist him.
I'll definitely make an opening for you. You'll know what to do when the chance comes.
Plotting something with your boyfriend over there?
N-no, I wasn't!
I've heard that some humans enjoy seeing their women go with other men.
So I've taken the shape of another man for you benefit.
Whelp.
(whelp = impudent young fellow, referring to Yamato)
Listen to my words carefully.
A woman's womb is her master; it is not possible for you to resist me
with a body like that.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry, but I'm borrowing your shirt.
It kind of smells of sex...
But it feels like you're beside me, Yamato
giving me courage.
No...
Your tongue is...
No!
How does the tongue of a human feel?
So the original really is best after all.
Yamato is enduring it...
I have to endure this too!
You promised that you wouldn't hurt Yamato!
I granted your request because you're an obediant girl, aren't you?
This is no good if I can't protect Yamato, if I get caught again I won't be able to help him.
I-I'm sorry.
Please don't look at me anymore, Yamato!
What a slutty look you have.
No tricks.
I know what you're thinking of doing, but resistance is futile.
No matter where your heart really lies...
your body will remember these things.
What are you thinking of, with an expression like that?
The hunter who once was pure has become so vulgar.
How many times have you been fucked now?
We've done so many different positions.
Stop... it.
Stop it!
You... Lord Nightmare!
Half of your body and mind already belong to me.
What a slutty body you have. This is the best kind of body for being a mother.
In your human speech, it would be "mother", correct?
Behold! This is the way it should be.
Females crave the domination of a male.
That's not true!
Cry out for me louder.
Feed my power.
The women of this school are all caught in my spell.
They're all enjoying themselves, why am I the only one that has to resist?
Watch carefully, whelp.
This woman is showing her true colors. She's enjoying this!
Everyone's feeling good...
Don't have to think about anything when it feels this good, right?
Actually, the cock bumping up against my womb feels wonderful.
It's so good...
I want more. I want it all. Keep going until it's all inside me!
Please! Please!!
Mikoto! Get a grip!
Mikoto!
Yamato, don't worry.
I'm doing fine.
'Fine!?' You're!...
More. I'll let you see more of what she's really like.
Mi...koto...
It's so good... It's all inside and I just can't resist it anymore.
It won't stop, I can feel it all the way inside me...
I'll definitely make an opening for you. You'll know what to do when the chance comes.
What 'chance' will there be if things keep going like this?
Now...
Mi--Mikoto!
The two of us together...
'Together', you say?
Is that what you really want?
This is not enough for me to climax.
You can just stay there and orgasm by yourself.
I'm not going to let you--
Takeru's going to laugh at us if you keep doing things like that.
She'd say something like, "Even with the two of you, you could only handle one opponent?"
It took two of us to handle one.
I'll definitely make an opening for you.
S-Sorry, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!!!
Shit! Shit!
'The two of us together', huh? Guess I'll send you two back.
MIKOTOOOOOOO...
What... just happened?
This is the dorm? I'm back at my room?
Yamato...
That's Sui!
Yamato's scent... turns me on so much...
I shouldn't be doing this, but I just can't stop.
Can't hold back anymore!
Yamato! Yamato! Yamato!!!
If he came back and saw me doing this
he'd definitely think I was a slut.
If he saw me he'd hate me!
Or would he think that I was sexy?
If he wanted to do perverted or degrading things to me...
If he wanted to take me into his possession
I would do it. I would do it at any time.
I've always wanted to be Yamato's girl.
It's almost that time of the month again
Yamato, please come and stop my period from coming.
Please, come soon!
Hurry, Yamato, please stick your hot throbbing cock
into Sui's sopping wet pussy!
I want you to do me
in this embarrassing position! Please! Please!!
Yamato!...
You saw it all, pervert.
You know what I want, right?
You act like you don't know what's going on
but you want to do perverted things.
Yes, oh no. Er-No!
S-S-S-Sui!
You always leave me alone though.
You're so big and hard down here.
I just can't leave it alone.
Su... Sui.
Wake up, Yamato!
What are you doing? Why do you always have to interfere with me??
Sui! What the hell is going on?
We're inside a dream. Sui's dream.
You can see the things that you want here, but you can't have them.
The only person who can is...
The only person who can is me, whelp.
Go ahead and let him know what kind of place this is.
No!
Shall I show the whelp the things I've seen?
Shall I show you what your woman has been doing here in this place?
This is the place for training.
A nightmarish prison where you go through hellish tortures
in front of the person you love.
Your name is 'Mikoto', isn't it?
This woman succumbed within three days, because the one she saw in her dreams was me.
Your wish will be granted very soon.
You look like a bride on a wedding night.
No! No more!
Yamato!
No...
Yamato can see me...
No!
Well, as long as we're on the subject
I might as well show you some other things.
How about I show you how I trained them, whelp?
We'll take it one step at a time.
Don't want it! I don't want it!
No! Please stop!
Don't waste your breath.
Let's let the whelp see some of those memories.
No!
They're going in my head! My head!
Stop!
STOP IT!!!
No more, please no more!
Please stop, no more please.
They keep on raping me.
It doesn't stop even when I sleep.
The sex continues in my dreams.
Please stop, I can't take any more...
So cruel... Mikoto...!
Watch carefully. She's enjoying this.
Take a good look into her memories.
Look at her slutty blushing face.
All of my shameful memories are being watched...!
You're such a little slut. You like having my cock in your womb, don't you?
You-you're wrong.
I only want Yamato's babies...
Only Yamato's!
Come. Now it's your turn.
Let's have a taste of your tongue.
Be sure to swirl it around alot.
This... this is as far as I can go.
I already told you I wouldn't run away!
There's no such thing as day or night here
but my body still needs to carry out its functions.
I'm really regretting that I was born a woman.
I'll definitely remember these embarrassing things.
No! Mikoto, it's coming out!
You devil...
Making us pee in front of each other...
Sui!
It's okay if you have to go...
I'll kill you! Just watch, I'll definitely kill you!
My body... someone...
We couldn't do anything to stop it. Our bodies were completely under his control.
Always... with Sui... together...
No more. I can't take any more!
Don't look! Don't look at me!
Fall into the sensations!
Your bodies are addicted to those sensations.
There is no way for you to go back.
Mikoto!
Enough!
I've seen and heard enough!
Don't do it,
Yamato!
Geez...
Interrupting really makes Lord Nightmare angry, you know.
And I was trying so hard.
Why... Mikoto...?
Sorry about that. I really was trying to make an opening for you at the beginning.
But you never got up,
and it felt really good,
so Sui and I belong to Lord Nightmare now.
I've already cum twice.
Three times for you, right, Sui?
You little slut, you! Heh.
I want a lot of babies...
It is impossible for you to go back now...
I can't even remember what he looked like.
That person is done for, right?