Ouka, get off this island, somehow.
Quickly!
No! I'm begging you, forgive me already!
N-no! Please stop already...
Ouka...
Hurry...
Hurry and...
Ouka...
Sister?!
Big sis, because of me...
No...
Why did it come to this?
Long ago, I lived peacefully in the corner of a small village
with my mother and older sister.
One day, Meioki suddenly appeared there
and began attacking the villagers.
Our mother, who was a powerful maiden,
fought Meioki and attempted to seal him.
However, he used the villagers as hostages
and forced our mother to surrender.
Afterwards he raped and devoured her, and thus stole her powers.
And binding us, her daughters with the curse of immortality,
he disappeared off somewhere.
Chasing him, my older sister and I left the village behind.
To avenge our mother, and to get rid of this disgusting curse.
Finally, we located Meioki's lair.
But...
Ouka, look out!
Sis!
Ouka!
Sis! Sis!
And later, they got me too.
Sis? Sis!
Thank goodness...
Thank goodness... that sis' really alright.
Eh? Sis?
Hold on, Sis!
Break out of that delirium!
Ouka, you too will be coming with us.
No!
It's okay.
You'll surely like it soon enough.
Thus, their assaults on me began.
No...
No, stop...
Don't come in...
No!
No... that thing's impossible.
It won't fit!
S-stop, it's gonna tear me apart!
My body will break.
Sis, sis!
This feels amazing, right?
Ouka, I've always wanted to... with you...
Ah, Master!
It's high time for me to taste your powers.
Ah, how large!...
Master, hurry, hurry and put it in me!
Sis, that's unfair!
Master, give it to me too.
Please put it in me as well.
Very well.
You may taste it to your heart's content!
Ah, here it comes!
Put it in!
It's great.
It feels great!
Give it to me more!
Make my pussy feel even better!
This is great, my pussy... feels amazing!
How's this? Does my penis feel THAT great?
Yes!
It... feels incredible!
Master's penis feels really good!
Ah, it's reaching sho~ deep!
The dick... is stretching everywhere inside!
I'm about to cum.
If you want me to fill you up with cum, beg for it!
I want it, I want it please...
I beg you, Master!
Shoot your hot dick juice in my pussy!
Squeeze out lots of it, loads of it!!
Sis, sis!!
Ouka, together, let's come together!
Sis...
Ouka...
With this, these two are finished.
Well then, it's time for me to collect my food!
Translation: FAKKU
QC: Barbar of Damascus
Inyouchuu Lover: EchelonV