I, Shiratori call upon my blade!
Respond to my summon!
Respond to my oath!
My name is Shiratori, Mikoto.
Awaken, Spirit Slaying Sword Raikou!
Sorry, Mikoto.
I was too slow.
It got away before we could finish it.
I hope I can move a bit faster and find the main body.
MeiohSubs Presents
Inyouchuu: Volume 1
Translation: Unknown
QC: EchelonV
We first need to detect it.
According to what you said...
- Yamato?
- Quick go change your clothes.
There's a pervert here staring at your chest.
Don't you dare peep or I'll kill you, Yamato!
Yeah yeah.
I kind of always thought they were a bit too big...
but my heart jumped a little when he noticed.
Disgusting, I'm not a naughty girl.
But, although this is rather embarrassing
I'm actually very happy about it.
Do I also have any self-confidence in myself?
Yamato you idiot.
Yamato!?
Don't move, stay in this boundary to protect yourself.
Yamato!
Let go, I told you to let me go!
Yamato, Mikoto!
Huh? No!
Don't...don't touch...please stop it!
Don't touch...
Stop it please...
Don't touch me...
Stop...this feels good.
This feels good, Yamato.
No...
Hey you guys
why didn't you kill us earlier?
I'll say it again, why do you keep ignoring me?
I'm not lying, you guys.
I turned you into burning coal!
Cut you in half, then...then...
Please...that's enough!
Don't do that...
Mi-Mikoto, hold on I'll!...
Yamato!
No, please stop now...
Please, Yamato could die...
Did you retreat while you were looking for me?
You're the Demon Lord!
Amazing, such strong magic in the air.
I can't speak too long or the atmosphere will affect me...
His breath alone is making my body burn up inside.
If you can feel my breath that
means that you're nothing but a lewd human being.
I've heard once before
that they can transform all of ones feelings and sensations into pleasure to make a...
Nightmare.
Frankly first,
those mildy shameful songs of yours appease me.
Who's there?...
This is the punishment for those who attempt to hurt me receive.
Stop, he'll die!
I was the one who hurt you.
Leave him alone.
Yamato!
This is part of the punishment for your arrogance.
Speak defiantly again and I'll kill him.
Yes, I'm sorry...
My breasts...stop squeezing my breasts...
before I come...
Sorry, don't fondle my nipples!
I don't want to lose!
Please leave my body alone, it feels too good...
Stop, it feels good...ah!
My panties are soaked.
I'm sorry, this wetness feels good!
Sorry...
I don't want to do it again.
I've already apologized...
Don't. Ah!
Sorry!! Please no...not there again!
No, the pain is itching all over me so please stop.
Yamato...save me...
I'm going to lose...I'm going to lose...
I'm going to lose to depravity...
Don't. Ah!
No not there! Sorry!
Please!
Don't enter me...don't enter my insides.
Don't...I'm not ready yet...
Please! I can't take it!
That can't possibly fit...no way...
Don't look!
Don't go any deeper...
It's already in enough...
No...no...
My virginity...it can't be...
I don't want to lose it like this!
Please, don't look.
I see now...
Is this why men enter slowly?
I now understand your desires.
Yamato!
No way...
So much pumped into my stomach again and again...
Too painful!...
Please...
Isn't that good enough?
I don't want to endure more pain again.
I'll apologize again already.
No don't, please let me go...
It hurts...it hurts already...
My virginity....give it back...
This is my first time!
Originally I wanted to give it to you...
but it's already been taken...forgive me, Yamato.
It hurts to lose face like this...
I wish I was dead!
Sorry, I'm such a weakling
Other than resisting, there's nothing I can do.
Sorry...
It does not matter if you resist...
When you see yourself in ecstasy
your mind will have no choice but to give in.
No please, I don't want to see those things in my mind.
What is that that thing doing looking at me?
Don't, don't look at me...no!
Don't show me those kinds of things...
My legs can't take it...being so open like this. Don't!
No, this...ah!
No! Ah! Stop, no...
Bearing this endless pain and suffering
is the only way to save that boy.
Woman, what do you want?
I want it inside me...you're thick semen...
So ashamed...
Where? Ah!
My most important place...
It has a more suitable name.
Vagina...I want it in my pussy...
Stop...
Let me ruin you and let your body
experience the epitome of pleasure.
Don't feel ashamed, keep calling out slowly
and I'll liberate you from your body.
Feels...too good...
There...there...I feel my stomach filling!
Fill me with happiness!
Shoot it into my womb...
Yes, give me more.
The orgasm will be too good...
It's already hot enough inside me!
There's so much cum inside already! It's too good...
My mind is already gone...
melted into pleasure...
Wait...I'm going to...
I'm going to burst!!!
Stop... It's too hot, this can't be...
How can it...why is this burning?
I'm going to faint from the heat.
Really, the heat is going to make me faint!
Stop...please...
Don't turn it around like that...
Don't do it...that hurts!
How can this be...
I'm going to come, I need to pee...
Let me pee!
Pee...I want to pee...
Pee...it's coming...it's coming out...
No, stop drinking my urine...
Feels good...Ah!
There...enough already...
I can't do it again, I'm already split open...
Begging for mercy? Only when you
climax will I then allow you to die.
No! No, I can't do it again!
I won't ever hunt demons again! I swear!
Are you trying to deceive me or are you
just saying things in this disorientated state?
However, you do look truly beautiful like this.
Don't...
Even so. Don't...
I hate it, I can't take, I can't take it anymore.
What I've done is certainly a mistake. I'm sorry!
No...
Why?
That...
Only "that" I don't understand.
Not so...Ah!
Incredible...
His penis is enormous. This can't possibly fit inside me...
it's too big, it'd break me!
But, maybe...
It won't work, I can't act like that in front of a demon...
No!
Please pound your cock into me!
Please split me open with your huge cock,
I can't take it anymore...I want it...
It's so big...it'll fill my stomach again...
Don't...
Amazing! My belly is overflowing with so much cum. I'm full!
My viginity snatched away like this...I'm so happy...
Being broken like this as a virgin is the best...
I can't!...
Not wiping clean after urinating isn't good...
What the?
How can I see this?
No...
- Isn't this how one shows their love for someone's body?
- Don't...Ah!
The important place I look after.
You're still nothing but a lewd little girl.
Don't...
Let me see you look more inviting.
Too shameful... My anus...the hair around it...
it's shameful to look at.
Letting that boy not enjoy it is quite a pity.
That shameful girl with the pink hymen
still has a dissatisfied appearance.
What!
No...you can't...no!
That is something...
you can only give to someone you love...
Noooo!!!
Sorry, Yamato.
Although it's happening like this..
It's amazing for Yamato to be hard like this!
Yamato...
So cruel...
Stop it...
My hymen, is there...
Why?....Ah!
I originally wanted to save it for Yamato...
I'm alright like this...
Yamato and I haven't even lost our virginity yet.
But...why can I not resist this?
Don't, don't go inside...
That is where...kids are born from...
Enjoy your ecstasy, you're
now pregnant with a little devil.
You're womb is begging to be filled with my semen.
Not there, I can't...
This child's place...to insert and exert such force like this...
It feels so strange now...
This hot feeling, I want more of it...
But if it's not Yamato's child, I don't want it
Although I don't want to get pregnant...
For this huge thing to enter me...
It feels so wonderful. It's unbearable!
Amazing, it's so big!
My womb is stretched out...amazing...
Although it's not Yamato, I still want to come...
Because...this feels so hot and wonderful...
Please...don't...
Please....please...
too much...
No, don't look, don't look...
This is proof to turn you into my concubine.
You will realize this joyfully.
It can't...too full...how does this fit!?
It's too big, such hard thrusting...
I can't do this!
I might come...
Such strong force, it`s amazing!
I`m going to die, I can`t bear this...
Sorry, Yamato.
I want his cum inside me, it's too good!
Into my womb...
I can't believe it's this good!
It doesn't matter if my insides become filled...
Don't pull it out, I want your cock inside me...
Hurry, inside me!
It's so hot inside of me...
Good, put it all the way in...
I want all of your semen to flow into my womb.
I don't want to become pregnant, but I want all of your semen! I can't endure it any longer!!
Sorry, Yamato...
If I become pregnant...I'm sorry...
This evening has finally ended and now we wait till dawn...
...this is only the devil's entrance...
Next: Inyouchuu 2
You...please...forgive me...