I love you so much...
No, you're my...
Hello?
Masaru? I need you to do me a favor.
What is it, Mother?
I forgot something at my sister's place last night.
Can you go get it for me on your way back?
Sure...
Well, I'm counting on you!
Huh? Is it broken?
Oh, she's home.
Aunt...
Aunt!
No... don't do that, Masaru.
No!
Masaru!
Masaru! Not there!
More... more, Masaru!
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming!
Yes!
Wait!
Masaru.
Aunt...
Come.
Umm... l didn't see anything...
Liar.
Look at that...
That's...
it's my fault, right?
No...
As a token of my regret, I'll make you feel good.
Aunt!
I'm sorry, Masaru.
It's okay...
Aunt...
it's mighty fine, Masaru.
If my mother finds out about this...
Don't worry.
She's not even your real mother...
And if she finds out about it...
I'll take full responsibility.
Responsibility?
Aunt!
I'm coming!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Aunt!
It's delicious, Masaru.
Aunt...
But it's still full of energy...
it's good to be young...
Touch me, Masaru...
What?
Are you sure?
Yes... keep squeezing them!
Aunt...
I'll make you feel much better.
Well? Does it feel good?
Yes, very...
it's hot and beating real fast.
That's because...
What?
I think I'm coming again...
No! Not this time...
This time, I'll collect it perfectly.
Were you surprised?
Not really...
I'll make you feel much, much better.
Masaru.
It's amazing, Aunt.
I can't hold it anymore... Aunt!
It's okay... it's okay Masaru...
Go ahead and release plenty of it in my mouth...
Aunt!
Amazing... it's so warm and delicious...