Masaru.
Let's head over to the bed now.
Aunt... I can't do it anymore...
What are you saying?
You're still young...
This one says you're still not done yet...
That's...
it's just not fair you know...
Not fair? Aunt...
Come!
There...
Aunt...
it's okay!
Aunt.
Your thing is getting really hard.
Masaru...
Aunt... it's amazing...
Don't climax too fast this time, Masaru.
But...
Keep going, Aunt.
I like you because you're honest.
What do you want me to do?
More...
More what? Masaru?
Please lick it more.
You mean like this?
Don't climax, okay?
Aunt...
Now, you have to make me climax, Masaru.
What? But...
Lick me.
Come on!
You're really wet, Aunt.
I get so wet just thinking that you're watching my privates.
Masaru!
More... lick me more!
Yes! You're doing good, Masaru.
That's strange...
She picked up earlier but...
Did my sister go out?
I want your thing, Masaru!
Don't climax.
Even Masaru...
Why isn't he picking up?
So full of energy!
I can't believe you already climaxed twice in the living room.
I think I can keep going.
Aunt.
I'm going to take your cock, Masaru.
So hard and hot...
Plus it's twitching...
How do you feel, Masaru?
It feels good...
I'll climax...
No... hold it!
Yes! That's it, Masaru!
My hips keep moving on their own...
if it was going to be like this...
then I should've gone to pick up my stuff.
Aunt, I'm about to...
Why did you stop?
No!
I haven't felt this way in a long time.
Aunt.
Come on...
I want you to stick your hot stuff inside me!
It feels good, Aunt.
Slowly...
Do it slowly in the beginning...
You'll climax if you don't...
Masaru...
Hot... it feels so hot...
Aunt... Aunt...
No Masaru...don't climax!
I'm stopping at way too many traffic lights today.
Right here...
Slowly...
Yes...
it's getting tight...
Do it slowly.
That's it...
Yes... that's it...
Gradually increase speed...
More... much harder!
Much deeper!
Tear me to pieces!
More... more!
Aunt!