Jane! Let me see your dirty hole!
I don't remember allowing an ogre to call me by my name.
Inda no hime kishi Janne (jane)
SubDESU-H Presents
「晒されたボテ腹王女 Exposed Fat Princess.」
Don't order me around...
I'm haven't given up yet.
And I don't intend to.
An enema?
Thinking such a wicked thought just because I'm in this pose...
How nasty...
It's not only your looks which are monstrous!
Hey, Celine, you haven't trained your daughter very well.
I'll show you how to train her.
You haven't given in yet?
It's only a matter of time!
Doing this to a girl who's not even old enough to marry...
You can't train your daughter if you won't train her hard!
Put it all in!
Because of this token which only can be peeled off by the caster who placed it on me that night...
Please forgive my clumsiness... Let me pee...
Our menstrual period was also watched by him...
We were taught the happiness of being able to excrete...
Stop it... They might see us...
They won't recognize you if you make that pose.
It's embarassing, please don't laugh!
Keith...
I'm still peeing...
I've thought so much about wanting to die...
But... We're already in a situation where we're caught.
I don't know what the punishment would be if one of us were to die...
Don't make such a pathetic face!
You pathetic girl.
It's spreading...
No way...
Stop...
Please forgive us, father...
This can only change us for the worse...
How embarrassing, my body is sucking this thing deeper...
The hot stuff is spreading inside my ass,
and it's like it's going to break!
I'm going crazy...
You're feeling it, right, Jane?
N-No, I'm not...
N-No...
No, I'm not...
Don't take it out...
Then be honest with yourself
I can't take this anymore!
Say it, It feels good to take it in the ass...
I... Jane... Ass...
No... It feels so good, I can't think of anything!
I said anal!
I don't care about anything except for cum!
Jane feels good by doing it in the ass!
Good, Jane!
That's my whore...
Ass... My ass...
What about your ass?
Good... Good... My ass feels good...
It's because Jane is a filthy, perverted woman that feels good when she's raped in the ass by an ogre!
I didn't think that a novice knight would say that...
Keith... No... I don't want to be seen by Keith when I'm like this...
I should not be seen!
Don't worry.
I will send you to heaven!
It's coming out...
A lot of sperm inside my ass... I'm no good anymore...
I'm cumming...
Brace yourself, Jane...
Please don't forget that you're a pure girl from the royal family!
Even if you say that... What happened to you, mother...?
Ogre sperm has within it the power to control women.
Taste it well...
Remember the smell, too.
Is it good?
Gidou-sama's sperm tastes delicious...
It's much thicker, stickier and smellier than a human's, and it's so delicious that I'm about to cry...
Good...
Together with your mother, be the slave of my dick!
Before long, came the worst day of all...
Please don't look at me...
Which ones of them are watching me?
I won't forgive you to your gaze
Me? Shamelessness?
No... There's a pressure in their gaze...
No... Don't look at me with your dirty gaze...
Being looked at like that makes me horny...
No... It's not what you think!
The voice is about to come out.
No... The dirty voice is right inside my head!
No... No...
I don't want these men to be concerned about me!
My princess!
May I see the princess for a while?
The people in the castle have noticed that she's always locking up herself in her room...
If she's going to lock herself up in a place like this...
Sometimes, she must ignore the people to stay inside and pray.
That is our duty as women from the royal family, those with the blood of angels in their veins.
I'm jealous that everyone's concerned about Jane...
Please tell the princess this:
We will guard the tower, so take your time and do your duty as best you can.
I'll be counting on you... Chief Knight...
I'm glad that you're all supporting her...
What's with that attitude?
Having fun by herself while her daughter is suffering...
Anyone might do the same thing if she's not forgiven for one whole day...
The ogre has implanted a parasite known as an 'Angel Killer' in my womb.
It not only grows inside, but it devours the sperm and later grows to release sperm on its own.
When it grows...
That means my holy angel's power has been taken,
That means I'll have become an ordinary woman... No I'll have become a lecherous woman who lusts after men...
The feeling of having a dick is great!
To be able to ejaculate feels so good!
I didn't think that my heart would be won by a monster's kiss.
I'm such an immoral woman!
Gidou-sama, I want to pee!
Please free my perverted pussy!
Don't look, Jane!
Mother... Does being able to pee feel good?
Don't ask me that kind of question!
I want to feel good too!
Mother's mouth is so warm!
My dick is cumming...
I always thought that my mother's boobs were the symbol of motherhood, but...
How dirty...
No... I just came... Don't suck it...
I'm cumming again...
Mother... Please stop licking already...
She did that much but it's still erect...
It's hot...
No... I want this to be sucked by a tighter hole...
Mother...
I... I...
No... Stop, Jane!
Mother...
Stop...
Jane... Please... I'm...
I know, mother...
Celine... Your mother's pussy is sucking pervertedly!
Come to your senses, Jane!
But you smell so dirty... Forgive me, mother...
Jane can't hold it anymore...
It's warm... Mother's pussy completely sucks me in...
I just put in the tip... What will it feel like if I put in the whole thing?
Jane... How dirty... How sinful...
Even though we're not blood related... We're still mother and child!
It's so hot... Mother's pussy is so hot and great...
I just touched something... My dick just touched something, mother...
There... No...
That part is what we call the womb... If you open that with your dick, it will suck you more...
The womb... The womb... I'm going to thrust into your womb with my dick...
Good job, Celine.
Your body transformation is complete.
Now you can become pregnant from any species!
Even the insects!
The womb feels good, my dick too!
Mother's pussy is sucking my dick...
No... Stop it... How sinful... How unforgivable...
Mother's womb is really shy...
But even if you hide it... I can touch it...
My dick won't let your womb escape!
Come to your senses, Jane!
Do you understand what that means?
Of course... You'll be pregnant with my child, right?
Jane!
No... So hot...
If it's let out inside... I'll...
Yes... I won't let those dirty ogres take you away!
What are you saying..?
No... Stop... Deeper in my womb...
Stop it... Don't thrust it!
My womb will open...
My womb will open!
Please... Please get pregnant... I want you to bear my child!
Mother... I can't hold it... My dick... My dick... My dick got numb!
No... Stop it!
If I get pregnant, my uterus will...
It opened! The uterus is sucking Jane's dick, and...
No... Stop it... It's my daughter's dick... We're mother and child!
Please forgive us, our angel...
Please forgive us, we sinful mother and child...
It's coming... It's coming... It's coming out... The hot stuff from my dick will come out!
If you let out a lot... My womb will fill with sperm...
She knew that she reached it... She knew that I can get pregnant, that's why...
My dear... Celine... I... My body wanted to get pregnant... I'm sorry
It's our child... I'll make Jane and mother's child in your womb...
Ok... You're saying it as my pussy becomes yours...
Make your mother pregnant in front of your father!
Because your pussy feels so good... My child... Jane's child wants to enter your pussy!
My father... I'm going to take Celine's womb...
I'm going to let her get pregnant with my child...
Jane-sama... Jane-sama, I'm going to give you my womb...
I'm going to suck all your sperm with my pussy!
Get pregnant... Get pregnant, mother!
I'm going to bear it... I'm going to engrave your dick and your heart into my body... Jane-sama...
I can feel the beat... It's your child... Jane-sama...
You became an ordinary woman... Jane...
The holy knight on the battlefield is trembling right now...
There's no one who can come between us!
You womb is already melted by the happiness you gained when you made your mother pregnant!
It's so hot...
I can't stop shaking as my stomach is filled...
Is this the happiness of being a whore?
Great... This is so great!
The male monster is really great!
This is amazing... An ogre's dirty thing... It's so strong...
Even as I take it in... It's still going in deeper...
I can't think!
I don't care about anything anymore!
I think... I think I only need the ogre's dick!
It's big, right?
Yes... It's so big... It's so big, and I'm so dirty!
Are you going to cum? Say 'I'm cumming' when you cum.
I can't say it... A princess can't say something like that!
And while being raped by a monster...
I can't say it...
Let her see your perverted face!
Don't call yourself a princess while being raped!
Please forgive me, mother...
I'm sorry, father...
I'm called the honor of the knights, and even the treasure of the country by Keith...
Jane... I'm such a shameless girl!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry for being a perverted woman!
I'll apologize for having such a shameless pussy!
Please let me cum... Forgive me for cumming!
Cum shamefully!
Cum, and be pregnant with my child!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'll accept the task of destroying the barbaric ogres!
My princess...
Let's pray before going to sleep...
Let's pray for the safety of our father...
Please stop... I have a husband...
The angel of these humans is weak!
They are incomparable to us!
So deep... It's coming in so deep compared to his...
I can let out more sperm!
My dear... My dear!
Don't let it out inside!
Please... Forgive me...
Please...
Stop... She's going be to married soon!
Then I'll congratulate her with my sperm!
What a good night...
The women of this country are all crying.
Jane... It's the celebration of your impregnation!
Don't let your pussy squeeze that one.
You can only squeeze my dick!
Yes... Jane is only your pussy slave...
I... Celine Gulnove... the queen of Milfarl Kingdom,
will abandon my right to be a human and...
I promise that I and my daughter Jane will become the pussy slaves of Gidou-sama, the head of the ogres...
Please... Let me say that too!
I'm going to be a pussy slave, a slave of Gidou-sama's dick!
My princess... my queen...
All of you! Nourish them with our child... with our sperm!
How does it feel to get pregnant with the child of an ogre?
Do you hate me?
No... My pussy exists for Gidou-sama's dick!
Are you happy being able to be a big fat ass?
Yes... I love you... I love you! Thrust your dick deeper in my pussy!
With the dick that made me pregnant... I'm going to suck it and squeeze and using my boobs I'll
comfort it and squeeze it again with my pussy!
What's the matter, Chief Knight?
Celebrate with us too!
I... Celine is cumming... I think I'm going to cum as well!
Jane is also cumming... I'm going to cum, so please give a lot of milk to my child...
My princess...
Keith... Look at me...
Please say that I'm pure...
Jane will become a good mother...
Please tell the story of how I'll bear a child of an ogre...