The scream of a woman surpassed by her own eyes.
Even a knight guard hunts this receding embarrassment.
Those lechers too
set their foot in...
The one I just excreted.
That shameful thing remained wet in my body...
No!
Y...yes...
The soul which is purer
has a greater effect...
Good...
They are so wise...
If with the Queen's noble soul
S...stop...
Your dick...
It's so good.
My pussy is cumming...
My pussy... is cumming...
Damn...
Every time you ask for information...
You're always cumming.
The ones who are called Ogre,
Their appearance is almost the same as that of humans.
They move according to their instincts and love to plunder.
The secret technique of the dark elf is useful sometimes.
Their breeding is abnormally vigorous.
If you're a female,
You'll be pinned down.
Because of the fierce strength they weild
They have been hated by the women.
Because I'm linked with your soul
I was able to come back from hell!
Queen Celine,
You're like a cow!
It's breath and body odor smells like a beast!
It seems he's getting excited...
There's a male ogre in my body...
Ah!! I will be drooped by him with this.
The wing of light,
Jane the Guardian Angel!
I came back to make you pregnant!
I will surely make you bear my child...
Inda no hime kishi Janne (jane)
「孕まされた守護天使 The guardian angel got pregnant.」
SubDESU-H Presents
Why do we need to retreat?
We have taken their chief
and the momentum is in our favor.
We should not be afraid of the ogre!
That's presumptuous of me, my princess.
Being arrogant...
Being arrogant makes the sword blunt!
Right?
I know it.
I'm no longer a kid!
Kees..
(i dunno the spelling of his name lol)
Let's follow the rules of the knight chief...
Do what you want.
Oh... angel-sama...
My body which descended from you.
Being embarrassed by an ogre...
What an unforgivable sin...
Do the noble families eat different things than the commoners?
You grew into a perverted one!
How shameful...
What are you finding?
No you shouldn't...
You shouldn't touch there...
That's unwell...
That's an embarrassing place...
The fingers..  how filthy...
Having evil intentions towards the queen!
He's the one who guided us...
Gor...don..?
Show him that dying wrestling face of yours!
It's crazy...
Placing it in the unwell place...
How dirty...
I want to die.
It's coming in...
The horrifying liquid is going to the stomach from the unwell place...
I think I'll release it if I lose my consciousness...
But the more I bear it, I will surely make a shameful face...
Enema...
Why does this kind of filthy assault exist in this world?
I can't.. hold it...
I've been injected with 500cc of enema liquid
and I bore it this long...
Are the noble woman's embarrassment this huge?
I think it's obvious.
I, who am a queen must not defecate in this kind of place...
But...
A filthy thing is going to rip off my ass...
I can't hold it...
My dear...
Celine wants to be free already...
If I release it in this kind of filthy situation...
Then it's better to get embarrassed!
For God's sake, please stop the enema!
He's watching.
My embarrassing appearance makes the male horny...
There's no male who stops if you're being strong like that.
Please don't inject me anymore!
Please stop it already...
I want to defecate here, now...
I think I'm going to collapse because of my ass...
It's already an embarrassing ass...
The position which must not be shown to men.
I've already failed as a queen...
D.. don't touch it...
It's a momento from my husband...
It's a gift which I received from my husband...
I'll adjust it properly!
My ass.... take it out.
It hurts...
You must keep your precious thing in your precious place...
No...
I want to release it.. I'll goi= crazy if I don't release it...
Your husband's momento tastes different right? Perverted queen...
No...
It's spreading more...
It's not like that my dear.
I...
Please don't get mad at me...
How filthy, to make my mother a hostage!
Please keep this a secret from the knight chief.
Those filthy ogres...
I can take care of them by myself!
You know the post agreement right?
If the imperial government knows this, you'll be doomed!
You're just being reluctant.
Wow... what size...
This is impossible, it's not comparable to a human's!
The male beast's,
Is he going to make me cry myself to sleep with that?
The beast... the male...
Coming inside my body... this is bad...
He's an ogre, he's not human.
What!?
Will Jane and I keep our name in this world if we got pregnant with the child of the ogre?
Filthy mother and daughter!
It's spreading...
The hot thing is coming inside...
My dear.. please protect me...
My dear...
Does the dead King go only this far?
Then... I will be the first one to go beyond that point!
No way...
It went deeper...
It touches the womb even it didn't move...
And it went in deeper...
He's owe.. he's owe..
Don't wash away his mark!
Isn't it lovely, Celine?
This will be yours starting today...
Stop it...
This is the reason why the king died so early.
No...
Making a kind face...
It's so tight!
How brutal...
It's so intense...
This is the ogre... the beast...
A powerful male...
Making an innocent face...
You're squeezing mine...
Don't go so slowly...
I must not think of it...
It's a filthy thing...
It's an excretion organ,
It's not lovely...
What a filthy shape!
You're squeezing it like you know how to work a dick!
Please...
It hurts.... this is abnormally hot...
No... I'm going to melt if my body remembers it...
My womb got numb!
The feeling I forgot a long time ago came back!
No... he's not human...
Your pussy is getting wider...
You're twitching like a green girl...
What!?
Something rubbed me and it tickles.
Something big came right now!!
Don't do it there...
I'll moan with that part...
I will no longer be a queen!
It's great.. it's great...
Scoop your knot more...
I'm going crazy...
Is it going to burst? It feels like it's going to burst...
If you go deeper...
Don't tell me you... .. you must not!
Do you know the meaning of that?
I am a queen!
Dear... My dear... help me...
I'm... I'm going to cum from a beast.. a filthy being...
Protect me...
Please protect my womb...
It's ejaculating...
No!!!
Dear...
He's releasing it...
It won't came out from the womb...
It's hot.. my womb is going to burn!
He's releasing the beast sperm...
Noooo!!
You demon!!
You're living a life like a cockroach!
I will let you bear that cockroach's child!
How filthy!
I am a princess!
I will never let an ogre take my purity!
Mother...
The key to immortality lies within the soul of queen Celine.
We're linked...
The soul and the body...
What have you done to my mother!?
She's going to suffer more, depending on your decision.
Y..you...
Just bear it a little longer... mother...
I will surely...
There's a thing you must do with your impudent mouth, right?
I must bear it for now...
Jane.. you must not...
You must not smell that odor...
It seems this is the excretion organ of the beast...
What an odor...
What a filthy smell of a male...
I feel like losing consciousness just smelling it!
Even Jane who's being called a reborn angel...
What am I doing...
Don't hold back.. smell it more.
It's great, isn't it?
The smell is getting stronger...
I need to let it ejaculate or else I'm going to go crazy...
Pilther effect...
To accept that thing easily...
The ogre makes the woman fall with the secretion liquid...
That size too, that is to make it reach the womb.
The dirty knot...
The stems got that thick too...
The shape that makes women cry and get pregnant easily...
I didn't think that I'd give my first blow job to this filthy thing...
No...
It's getting bigger...
It became more of a dirty shape as it reacted to me...
Release it quickly...
Faster...
Didn't you promise to release my mother?
Before that...
I will join you with your mother.
No...
I will make you "hole-siblings"...
It's hot...
N... no...
Stop it...
If you do that more, don't think that I'll make it easy for you!
No.. don't move Jane!
You're rubbing it...
But mother...
Do you know what you're doing!?
I will never forgive you for that!
O...uch...
I will never forgive you!
It's hot and I'm going to burn!
It's so hard and it's going to rip...
I can't take it... It's so thick...
How is your Hymen feeling with my dick?
Hymen...?
Jane...
I feel it being linked through that beast...
It's squeezing...
The hymen of Jane which is trying to push that thing out...
It's unforgivable to lose it in this situation.
Moreover with that kind of partner...
Angel-sama...
Please protect me...
No...
No... way...
I'm sorry my dear...
I wasn't able to protect our daughter's purity...
And.... with this kind of situation...
Feeling the hymen of my daughter... I...
I can't bear it...
You demon...
Know your shame!
Together with the mother and daughter, they're enjoying my dick!
Are you going to do it again!?
You're the one who must know your shame!
No...
Are you going to thrust that deeper!?
Know the embarrassment of a woman, princess!
I...
What kind of voice am I producing...
But...
This... He's pushing it in deeper...
Wow...
It feels like my dick is going to be ripped...
So this is Jane...
You feel it too right, Celine?
I will squeeze it through your mind...
How rude! Don't call the queen by name!
It's alright.. because it's great...
Your pussy is... so great...
You feel it, right?
The part where the dick is kissing...
That is the womb..
The.. womb..?
The source of this happiness
That's a room to keep your baby...
It's touching the womb!?
The filthy thing of the beast touching my womb...
Wow...
It's hot and good inside Jane's...
The dick is happy too...
It's pumping and happy...
Mother...
It's getting bigger...
You squeeze it so great...
No.... no...
You must not lose Jane.
But...
Why is this so thick...
It's hot, hard and going to burst...
My hymen is being ripped...
Giving my virginity to his kind of filthy beast...
Don't tell me you're going to release it inside!?
I will never forgive that!
I must protect it... even just the womb...
That man's... it's getting bigger like it's going to burst...
Is it going to release? Is it going to be released?
It will reach the womb if it's like this...
The tip won't move from the opening of the womb!
He's going to release it!
Take that filthy thing out right now!
If you release it inside...
I will tear you apart!
Faster... take it out quickly!
It's hot..!!
He released it inside...
And he pushes it and releases it inside the womb...
It's so dirty inside Jane!
It's rolling like it's going to squeeze it out!
It's coming in..
It's coming inside the womb a lot..
Say your goodbyes.
Next time you meet my dick, it  will be the time you get pregnant
Body modification...?
You two are my girls.
You must get pregnant with my child...
Get pregnant?
Ruining one's pure life...
Not with the one I love but...
I'll bear the child of a filthy beast...
A monster which lays it's egg inside the body of a female!
It hatches inside the body
and rules the body which bears it.
It erodes the womb and the ovary
and makes it able to bear another of the same kind of monster..
I thought you were still a child,
but you're such a filthy pervert!
Both holes have been made into one and it's secreting a nice smell.
I will never forgive you for insulting me!
I think you can bear with this through your strong will.
With this thing... I will never...
lose!
Of course...
Celine bears twice as this one.
Y...you!!!
I can't use the front one until the monster is born.
But don't worry,
I will let you cum with your ass so you don't get bored.
Celebrating the health of the queen and let's drink!
Stop!
No... please forgive me...
I will make your body not be satisfied unless there's something being injected!
The thing which is incomparable came!
I'm going to burn.. my ass hurts...
It will come out.... it will come out...
Did my mother bear this...?
It's... impossible... this will come out easily...
God... father.. help me...
Jane can't hold the excretion!
Someone... someone... kees!!
Please help me quickly!
Please... bear it...
My shameful ass.. don't open...
I will cap it if you're going to release it.
It's spreading nicely.
Is it inborn?
This filthy ass!
Wow... what a feeling...
It's my first time... this is my first time...
The knot is rubbing...
Because... I've only used it for defecating.
I haven't release this kind of thing...
Don't struggle and loosen your ass
Who the hell would do that...
Don't move it...
It hurts.. Stop...
If he takes it out now, it will come out...
Don't take it out...
I won't forgive you if you take it out!
That...
What are you talking about?
It will come out...
I'm a princess and this kind of embarrassing thing...
I don't want that to happen!
Your dick...
yes.. that hard and dirty thing...
Give me that deeper...
So great...
The hard and thick thing spreading inside me.
It's stopping my shameful thing...
No.... don't take out your dick...
This is an order...
Ah!... n.. no...
No.. that one right now is...
Then, as you've ordered...
What's this... this is great...
It's so intense and I'm going crazy...
My ass is going to be riped and it's so great...
and it's coming out...
If you release it now, I can't hold it...
I will let you release it too!
Live by apologizing for the lives you've taken from my comarades!
My princess.. it's me Knight Chief Kees.
It's me Knight Chief Kees.
I just came back.
Why did you get tough by yourself?
Did something happen to the castle?
I just got a bit tired.
I wanted to rest immediately.
Only thing is,
My body hurts...
Even Kees is here, I can't hold it...
It feels great when my asshole spreads...
My body learns to be tough so...
My body won't be satisfied if I don't release it.
So you're just resting your self?
Sorry for the rudeness.
Good job.. you can get out now...
My body is getting more crazy...
Kees... please take this tag out...
My womb is about to burst inside...
Sorry for the rudeness I made last night.
I didn't intend to treat you like a child.
My princess, you grew into a excellent princess.
You're the pride of our knight group.
I can't show him this kind of appearance.
It's better to die than to be seen!
But...
If it's like this, I'm really going to be pregnant with an ogre's child...
Oh God...
Protect me...