Kazuki-sama...
Nanase-san, what are you doing?
C-Coming!
Onii-sama?
Doctor Mikage gave a call earlier reminding
you to visit the hospital this week.
Onii-sama, are you listening to me?
I'm simply worried about your...
I know.
But I don't feel like going.
Onii-sama!
Have you finished your meal, sir?
I've brought your medicine.
Thank you, it was very delicious, Nanase-san.
Jeez, what's up with her anyway...
Hey.
Yes?
What's with this tea?
It's so bad I can't even sip it!
That will teach her.
My apologies, ma'am.
Besides, you're always...
Stop it already, Mito.
Onii-sama.
Come to that room later.
Understood?
Yes.
Kazuki-sama!
That could be dangerous, let me help.
Th-This should not be, sir.
Mito-sama will be upset with me if you do such a thing.
Would you please let her off this time?
No, it's all my fault.
You're kind, Nanase-san.
N-Not at all, sir.
Ow...!
Nanase-san...?
I-I'm sorry, I just...!
She's probably calling for me already
so I will have to take my leave, sir.
I've already told you not to get involved too much with Onii-sama.
Seems you still don't get it at all.
I never intended to...!
Silence!
Seducing my brother like that... you bastard pig!
You are mistaken, I just...!
You're not going to get off easy if you try to get close to him again.
Kazuki-sama...
Excuse me.
I've brought tea, sir.
Kazuki-sama?
Kazuki-sama!
What is wrong?
Please get a hold of yourself.
Oh, it's you, Nanase-san.
I-I shall call a doctor immediately.
No, I'm fine.
Can you please keep this a secret from my sister and everyone else?
But...
If the doctors ever find out, they'll surely
lock me up in the hospital this time.
So please...
I never knew.
I never knew that you were that seriously ill...
Yes, an illness that will eventually lead to my death.
When I was a child, the doctors said that I only had one year to live.
Two yeas, then three years went by,
and I was even able to live up to this point.
But it seems I'm at my limit already.
I don't really care anymore, though.
My life has been extended well enough.
It might be a lot easier to just pass away this time.
P-Please don't think like that!
I... love you, Kazuki-sama.
Nanase-san?
I will probably be punished for this,
but I need you, sir.
A-Am I not allowed to think like this?
I'm ready to do anything for you.
I can eat carrots for you even if I hate them,
I will sew even if I'm not good at it,
and I can even clean everything for you.
So please, please don't think of something that sad.
I already decided since the first time I met you.
So you're the rumored crybaby new maid?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kazuki.
You?
I-I'm one of the newly staffed maids here, Sakakibara Nanase.
I hope we can get along.
Kazuki-sama...?
No need to be so uptight, Nanase-san.
But you're my Master, Kazuki-sama.
I've been trained to act as such.
Ever since that day,
I became your slave.
I vowed in my heart that I would do whatever you wanted.
That's why, I can even do this...!
Nanase-san?
What are you...?
Nanase-san...
Please use my body as you see fit.
Because I am your slave.
It feels embarrassing.
It's beautiful.
Ka-Kazuki-sama!
I'm about to...
Oh no!
Is it really okay?
I'm going in.
Ow...
Ka-Kazuki-sama.
Nanase-san...
It feels very good.
Ka-Kazuki-sama...
I wonder what's happening.
Kazuki-sama...
Onii-sama.
That's good, Nanase-san.
Nanase-san!
Me too...
I'm... no...!
Kazuki-sama...
Hurry and get to our hospital already.
Right away, ma'am.
I'll show you what happens if you dare oppose me.
I was a fool.
Just waiting to die even when someone
already deeply cares for me like this...
Kazuki-sama.
Thank you, Nanase-san.
N-No, I thank you, too.
What are these?!
D-Don't worry about it.
It's Mito, right?
Forgive me.
For letting her do something like this to you.
No, it's not your fault.
I'm...
Actually, I have a younger twin brother.
He's currently mentally ill, and has been
in the hospital for more than ten years.
It is possible that my sister also shares the same inclination.
Inclination?
Mito's trying not to let our secret be revealed.
Because if she doesn't...
I cannot be held responsible for this, ma'am.
Onii-sama told me to do so.
I understand then.
Please.
A woman, a woman!
I haven't sniffed this scent in such a long time.
I think I'm about to cum.
Still the same as always, Nii-san.
Huh? Mito, is that you?
I've come for you, Kazuma-niisan.
It's so wonderful to be free again.
Kazuka-sama?
Haven't you gone to the hospital?
I came to change the bedsheets...
Are you Nanase?
Yes.
Seems you have made Mito quite upset.
Did you do something with Kazuki?
That girl's been in love with Kazuki ever since we were kids.
Actually, I have a younger twin brother.
Kazama-sama?
Oh, so you know.
Did you hear that from Kazuki too?
No!
That's right, run.
Then I'm going for the chase.
You brat!
Kazuki-sama!
It's a pleasure to be in your presence, sir.
When did you come back from the hospital?
We could have picked you up on the way if you gave a call.
Where's Nanase?
She hasn't come back yet.
Where could she have hidden?
Alright then.
I'll just warm up with you girls.
Please save me, Kazuki-sama.
Onii-sama...
This sensation feels awesome!
Looks like I won't get tired of this just yet.
I'm going to pleasure you even more.
Come on, come on, come on!
Ooh, it's starting to grip me tighter.
Come on, do it, do it more!
Now, for the main dish.
Mito, what are you...
Awake already?
You're mine, Onii-sama,
and I'm not about to hand you over to anyone.
The medicine seems to be working.
Stop this, Mito...
Mito, don't...
It's okay.
Because we are not really siblings.
Just who told you...
Kazuma-niisan told me when we were still kids.
Kazuma?
Mito, that's not true.
It's the truth.
You're the one who's trying to lie.
He's telling the truth.
Looks like my room down here really is the best.
Everything's as it was.
Na-Nanase-san?
No way, but I...!
As expected of a refined, innocent young lady.
Listening to some brat's silly words.
This can't be...
Why are you here?
Mito, is this your doing?
Because she's in the way.
Stop this, I'm the one who threw you in the
hospital so your vendetta is with me.
Leave her out of this!
Revenge, you see...
is a dish best served when you try harm the
people most important to your target.
But enough about that.
I'm free now.
So I'll just do whatever the hell I want.
Mito, hold him for me.
Hey, wake up. It's show time already.
No!!!
Nanase...!
Kazuki-sama!
Nanase...
Stop!
Yeah, just keep on screaming.
It's making me really excited.
No!
Don't come closer!
No...
Please stop...
I beg of you...
Look,
you're actually quite honest down here.
Don't look.
Oh, so this is the thing that Kazuki got, eh.
No, don't look!
Let me have a taste of it.
Don't, stop!
Nanase...!
Here...
There...!
Stop, just... stop...!
Here, here's some more!
Kazuki-sama, please don't...
This is something great.
Onii-sama!
Have some more!
Kazuki-sama...
What's wrong?
Came already?
We're just getting star... ow!
Who did that?!
You...
Betraying me now, huh.
Stop this, Nii-san. You've had enough.
Looks like we need to punish that one girl who broke her promise.
Ain't that right, Mito?
It hurts!
Stop this!
What are you trying to do, Kazuma-niisan?!
What are you going to do?
I don't want this, let me go!
I still haven't used this.
It's a special item that was commonly used when I was kid.
Stop this, Nii-san.
Please stop this foolishness!
Don't worry, it's just a cleaner.
Thanks to you, our session ended quite abruptly.
You'll have to take responsibility for it.
No, stop!
You've grown really well.
I'm happy for you as your brother.
– There, there!
– S-Stop...
So you are a still a virgin after all.
The gripping sensation is different from earlier.
Here now...
S-Stop this... it will come out...
Looks like you're about to blow.
So am I.
No...
No... why...
Look, this is amazing.
Onii-sama...
Please forgive me...
Alright, sorry for the wait.
Kazuki!
When did you...!
It's the muscle-relaxant that Mito injected me with.
It's over, Kazuma.
Curse you...
An earthquake?
Nanase-san, get a hold of yourself!
Nanase-san!
Ka-Kazuki-sama.
I-I'm...!
It's alright, it's alright now.
But you need to hurry and get out of here.
My sister's injuries may no longer heal.
Are you... trying to escape...?
Damn...
Damn, damn!!
I entrust my sister to you.
Kazuki-sama!
Kazuki-sama, Kazuki-sama, please open the door!
The place will soon crumble to the ground.
Take my sister and escape!
I don't want to!
I can't just leave you here, Kazuki-sama!
Nanase-san...
Thank you for everything.
I'm happy that we met.
As the master of this house... no, as his brother...
I can't just let Kazuma get away.
No, I'll call the cops and then...
That won't do!
The secret of this household ends here.
So just go.
Go!
Kazuki-sama, Kazuki-sama!
Kazuki-sama!!
Kazuki-sama...!
Kazuki-sama...
Shall we continue our walk then?
Let's go, Miss Mito.