As the various ninja clans were
weeded out, some appeared...
...who had secretly mastered the art...
...of manipulating those of the demon world.
The Shikima, perverted denizens of a perverted realm.
At that time, there was a struggle to determine...
...who would control the Shikima.
ln this, the Suzuka clan plotted
to eliminate all opposition.
Desiring mastery of the dark arts,
they attempted to win over...
...the females of the Miroku clan,
current controllers of the Shikima.
But their refusal to join the Suzuka
marked the clan for destruction.
To save their clan, the Miroku bound themselves...
...in an agreement with the Shikima
to oppose the Suzuka forces.
This union was embodied in an enchanted signet case.
Whoever is struck by sunlight
reflected from the case...
...faces the perverted wrath
of the Shikima themselves.
For hundreds of years of unbroken succession...
...the women of the Mido family,
head family of the Miroku clan...
...have passed down the signet case.
And now, in the present, an unusual young woman...
...is born to the Mido family's unique destiny.
Miko Mido. Age 18.
A girl yet to learn of the
hundreds of years of strife...
...between the Suzuka clan
and the forces of the Shikima.
Oh Jeez!
l'm damn late again!
Sis, sorry l overslept!
Breakfast's on the table, Miko.
Why don't you help yourself.
This the script for your new series?
Mm? Yeah, it is.
Same old kind of trendy drama,
just like the last one.
Uh, l mean-- Well, you know...
Sorry l brought up about your getting cancelled.
That's okay. By the way, Miko-chan...
You raided my underwear
drawer again, didn't you?
Uh, well...Yeah, sorta...
Why are you always doing that?
Cause l find silk panties to be
just so comfortable on my skin.
Well, too bad! l hate sloppiness like that!
Okay, l'll put them back if you insist.
But if your fans knew how you felt,
it would shatter your image.
Miko-chan!
Oh no, l did it again...
l've gotta risk it.
But it's still scary as hell!
Oh no! l'm gonna crash!
Got to work on my landings.
Damn, why'd l bother rushing in here?
Shiratori-sensei's out for today.
Bet you and him were really going
at it til morning...Just kidding!
C'mon, get real.
l'm jealous!
You really should go for it you know!
C'mon now, Miko!
He's just one quiet little 30-year-old instructor.
Well, l don't know how to say this,
l'm just...not into men at all.
Oh, so you're a lesbian?
No, no! Of course l'm not!
But l've seen you get pretty horny yourself.
That means you must go to bed stroking
your little friend every night, right!
You don't understand. lt's part of my training.
Fight it, Miko! Don't let yourself come!
When you conquer your inner passions...
...you will master the inner
secrets of the Miroku clan!
But this stuff you put on me...
lt feels so good!
Miko, virgin of 18 years...
ls this your destiny?
l can't stop it anymore! l'm coming!
Noway... l get hot just remembering it.
Hi ho, Miko-chan.
Nin-nin!
Nin-Nin, you can't just wander
around the campus like this!
But the Mistress is calling for you.
Do you mean Grandma?
But training's on Sundays...
She told me to bring you now.
Ok, then we'll go.
Wait here and l'll go get my stuff.
l can smell the girlies in there.
Young ones are always the best!
Oh, l just love it!
Nin-Nin!
Don't you embarrass me again,
the way you always do.
l was just enjoying myself!
Don't be such an idiot!
The guys in my class would sure be surprised if...
...they knew l cut out early for sexcraft training!
You're pretty clumsy.
l guess l'll just go on ahead.
And l get to cut training. Lucky me!
Oh, Grandma.
Ah, Miko.
Say, what's the deal, pulling
me out of class like this?
Don't be angry, dear. l have something
important to tell you today.
The years are catching up with me fast.
As well trained as l am,
l fear l'm not long for this world.
Are you sick, Grandma?
Oh no, nothing too serious.
lt's just a little spasm now and then.
l've got an idea. Why don't you come live
with onee-chan and me in our apartment?
No, that would be absolutely impossible
for me to even consider.
Who would protect the grave
of the Mido family ancestors?
l called you here today
so that, in their presence...
...l could pass something of
vital importance on to you.
Look at this!
A signet case?
What is it for...?
Stay out of its light!
lf anything at all should happen to me,
this signet case belongs to you.
lt's all yours.
For generations, the women of the Mido family...
...the rightful leaders of the Miroku clan...
...have carried on an agreement
with the heretic Shikima.
''Shikima...?''
Against women, using their roots of lust...
...and against men, using their perverted vessels...
...they take advantage of
human nature to gain control.
A dark clan which marks the perverted underworld.
That is the Shikima.
They sound like they're on drugs.
An 18 year old virgin like yourself couldn't
possibly know how incredible it feels.
So the Shikima and this
box are connected somehow?
Exactly, my dear. lnstead of the Shikima
treating us as our enemies...
...we have an agreement that they fight for us.
This box keeps that agreement sealed.
So, you're saying they're really our friends.
You've told me everything, you Miroku crone!
Now the Suzuka clan will claim the box!
This is the life...
Hope Miko-chan's holding up well.
lt's one o'clock... And l'm sure starved!
Miko, you'll never handle them
all yourself! Get out of here!
Grandma...
As well as you fight, your abilities...
...are no match for me, old woman!
Damn you!
My heart... No!
Grandma...
G, Grandma!
Miko Mido! The Suzuka clan now
controls the seal of the Shikima!
From now on, they shall fight
the Miroku clan on our command!
Grandma, are you really dead?
Miko-chan...
The Mistress wanted you to have something.
She really did?
Her diary and fertility statue?
Yes.
Yours by right as the 14th leader of the Miroku clan.
Nin-Nin, you just shut up about all that!
l'm sorry, Nin-Nin.
l... l just don't know what to do!
Well, first of all, you should go
home and have a talk with Miyu-san.
Yeah, you're right.
What the Suzuka clan has dreamt
of for 300 years is realized!
The agreement with the Miroku clan is now active!
Cast the spell to find and destroy
the bearer of this scent.
Her name is Miko Mido!
How do l explain this to Sis?
You've noticed me?
Who's there?!
Are you Miko Mido?
Who in the name of hell are you?!
A Shikima, sent to kill you as per the agreement!
And by my sexcraft, you shall be mine!
Miko-chan!
A Miroku female this easy?
Must be a foolish beginner!
Why you...!
Meddler! Stand aside!
Oh, no. He's too good!
You seem to be in need of
a lot more training, little girl.
And so now you will become
a victim of my roots of lust!
Stop it! Sto, Stop it!
Don't! Stop that!
You call yourself a woman of
the Miroku clan? Just pathetic!
Stop it!
At this rate, l'm screwed. Literally!
Somebody, help me!
Nin-Nin...
What are you doing?
Help me, please!
One chance! lt's embarrassing,
but it's all l've got!
The hair blast spell...
What's that?
Swell my lower half up,
make 'em as hard as steel...
Worked!
Shit! l was going to take it easy on you.
Your body will sucumb to my pleasures!
...your body and mind will
move as l wish them to...
...until l have driven you mad!
Hey, what's going on? Help! l don't
really believe this is happening to me.
This isn't just some penis.
lt is a root of lust!
Nin-Nin... Nin-Nin!
Help me, please!
Nin... Nin-Nin, help! Help me!
Silence, damn you!
Nin-Nin...
Miko-chan!
Oh, my God, no! l'm losing it!
Oh no, Miko-chan!
Miko-chan!
Meddler, you shall die!
l'm sorry!
That'll teach you to be so rough with me!
That was really close.
Miko Mido...
l am not the only Shikima.
Resign yourself to your fate.
l know you're lonely, Grandma.
But be patient a little longer.
Sis and l'll will give you the
funeral you would have wanted.
Grandma's diary...
No way... Sis and l aren't blood related?!
l am uneasy about Miko
living with her as a sister.
But l pray, pray, that this
woman of different blood...
...will raise her to be a
strong woman of the clan.
''Different blood...''
Miko-chan!
You have to dry your panties
after washing them!
What are you babbling about?
What happened?!
l can smell the love juice.
This strange effect...
Oh no, it's on Sis's body now!
What's happening? Why do l
feel like this all of a sudden?
l need someone... l need someone...
lt seems to be working...
The scent of Miko Mido...
Sis...
What's with you, Miyu?! This isn't a porno video!
lt's just supposed to be a simple love story!
Director... Please... Oh, please...
Can't we...?
Director...
Hold on here! What're you...?!
Somebody, get her into the trailer!
Where'd they go?
Director!
Miko-chan!
They just seemed to vanish into thin air!
Sis...
No!
Miko-chan! Look...
These are... Sis's panties
that l wore last week!
Why? Why was she taken instead of me?
Grandma, tell me! What should l do?
Don't cry, Miko.
Grandma? lt can't be.
That was the Mistress!
Nin-nin, did you hear it, too?!
Then it wasn't just my imagination.
When Miyu wore your panties...
...the scent of your love
juices got onto her body.
But, l washed everything out of them!
A normal person couldn't tell,
but a Shikima can.
No matter how much you wash...
...your scent is always detectable
by their incredible sense of smell.
So that means it must be all my fault
that my sister Miyu got captured?!
Dear Grandma, please tell me,
Where have they taken her?
Rub the statue.
Yes, yes...
Grandma!
Miyu is most likely trapped in
the bowels of the Shikima realm.
What?! So how do l get to her?
Around midnight, turn your
womanhood to the north...
...and let your hand satisfy your desires.
What?! Are you saying l should
masturbate?!
But before you do, you must
drink the seed of a virgin man.
And suck off some guy, too?!
Why should l have to do that?
l can't! l can't.
You can't?
No... Oh, but Sis is running out of time!
Then, my dear, l'm afraid that all we
have left to try are the secret female arts.
But that will entail great risk.
So just tell me what to do.
lf it'll save my sister, then...
Kyomara-sama, l have brought Miko Mido to you.
See? Her body is so sexually aroused
that her womanhood...
...flows uncontrollably with the love juice.
Ah, the crack of a skilled
woman is tasty indeed.
Damned female! You will be
taken as you never have before!
Now see...
Oh please, please... Hurry...
Miko-chan, it's ready.
Are you sure about this?
This is supposed to be
a really strong aphrodisiac!
My Grandma taught me
this technique herself.
lf you can't drink a man's sperm,
then this one is the only possible way.
Now, to face north...
Hang on, Sis...lt won't be long now.
You know that l'll save you!
Oh, no!
l'm almost...! l'm cumming!
Wow! This is the Shikima world?
Ow, my backside!
Oh man, l can't believe how
really creepy this place is.
l feel like l just fell into a bad horror movie.
Miko Mido... l, Kyomara-sama, shall personally...
...and thoroughly violate your body!
l've never had such a full wad to blow!
Ow! lt stinks! No!
Liar... You don't really want
someone as big as l am to pull out!
No... Don't look...
Throw off your bashful heart.
You know how much you love it.
Now then show me the full limits of your sexcraft!
No... l'm so ashamed...
Still bitching about that?!
Then have a taste of this!
You just love it, don't you?
No... No!
Oh! That was my sister!
Sis... Nin-Nin, let's go!
Can't go just straight in.
Miko-chan, up there!
l get you. Great idea, Nin-Nin.
Can you believe it? l wish l was Kyomara-sama.
To get that girl, you mean.
Yeah. l'm jealous.
You know we weren't born to get
to have sex with the human girls.
lf l could just get the clearance...
...l'd be in the human world in a second!
Must be talking about my sister...
What was...?
Shit!
Nin-Nin!
Uh... Hi there.
lntruder! Grab him!
Sorry, Nin-Nin. You'll just
have to escape on your own.
Help!!!
Come back here, you little creep!
You're so far into me!
With further still to go.
This little mix of ours is starting to overflow!
l'm so hot... l can't control myself.
More, more, more!
So, you reveal your true nature
at last, you horny little bitch!
Pump it! More! Split me in half!
Once you say that, you're in his trap.
Their power grows stronger when
a woman gives in to her sexual passions.
Sis, l've come here to save you!
Mi...ko...
What?! You're the real Miko Mido?
You've got guts to face me like this!
Say your prayers, monsters!
You're about to get hit with
the power of the Mido family!
With the fires of life itself!
Sis, you must get out of here now!
Mi...ko...
You thought that puny weapon
could defeat the great Kyomara-sama?!
Oh shit. Now what? l don't
have any other weapons on me.
Miko-chan!
Nin-Nin! Where are you?
Here. They caught me.
Oh great! And here l was hoping Nin-Nin would rescue me!
lt only goes to show
how foolish humans are!
Please Kyomara-sama.
Let Miko go and do
what you want with me.
Sorry, but your hole bores me now.
Please...
Sis, don't!
Little female, drawn to the flame...
You too shall fall to my sexcraft!
To think l'd capture both sisters...!
Don't you fucking dare!
Now then, let me squeeze the love
juices from that well-trained part.
Hey, lizard-face! Would you
just give the trash talk a rest?
Great, now what do l do?
You broke your promise!
Fool! You think we'd follow
our promises in our own world?!
Now her muscles are all
loose and flabby down here.
Sis...
Can't help it that Kyomara-sama's built so big!
Maybe that little trick...
Given up?
Got to concentrate. Only one chance at this...
Go!!!
Sis! You've got to run for it!
Her will is broken.
As yours, too, will be soon.
Oh, nice and tight!
See? You're getting nice and wet now.
No...use... l'm going to lose...
What? You want some of this action, too?
Sis, why...? Run!
Miko, the time has come to release your full power.
lt's Maria-sama!
Miko, be strong as you face your true destiny.
Mi...ko... Where are we?
You saved us all, Grandma.
We're okay.
Miko, let's just try to forget all this.
No way!
This could all happen again!
And l'm the only one who can stop them.
Don't worry, Sis. You know l'll protect you.
So Miko-chan, how long until you
put some clothes back on?