Hi! So, we meet again!
We've got another great episode lined up for you.
l'm Miko Mido, usually a pretty ordinary girl.
But seeing how my ancestors
were ninja in the Miroku clan...
...l've been raised to be a ninja warrior girl.
And since l have to fight other ninja with sex...
...and have to do it with gross monsters, too...
Well, being a ninja is no picnic!
But you've got me to help you, Miko-chama!
But Nin-Nin, you're always useless when things get tough.
The hell l'm not!
Lookit, without this, l'd be the one to protect you.
Hold on, just what are you touching there?
l'm just...trying to show off your sex craft.
What're you talking about?!
Get your fingers out of there!
Yow! l can't stop!
Oh, see what you did?
Here come a bunch of Shikima ninja right now!
- Run for your life!
- Whoa! Hold it, Nin-Nin!
Well, Miko Mido, heir to the Miroku
ninja clan, swings into action.
Bring them all on, from wherever they come from!
Or something like that.
Stop it! Stay back!
So, is your body paralyzed with fear?
Your own carelessness is to blame!
What a lovely view.
Now, you'll taste the Miroku clan's
Yokonshin punishment rod!
Take this!
Do you remember Kamiri's own torment?!
Kugutsumen, l've found it! The golden treasure, Zipang!
Kamiri!
You slimy traitor... Give it back!
Miko and Yaku are in pursuit
of the two thieves who have...
...stolen Zipang, the secret
treasure of the Miroku village.
Kamiri, the vengeful Miroku sex
craft master who broke the Law...
...and Kugutsumen, renegade
former member of the Suzuka clan.
The stolen treasure sword is said to be able...
...to take the life of Seikima, the Shikima king.
My dad's life?!
With Zipang, we will take
control of the Shikima world.
And then both the Miroku
and Suzuku clans will know...
...that they are controlled by Kamiri and Kugutsuman.
To do with as we please.
But neither one is aware of the evil power...
...residing within Zipang.
Have you heard? Now it's up to five.
Yeah, looks like we have
a rapist in the village.
And all the victims were
young girl students.
And none of them can remember
anything about who attacked them.
The guy who did this must be really good.
l wish someone would do
that sort of thing to us!
You think they're talking about Kugutsumen?
Kamiri may not be totally healed yet.
Kugutsumen would need an
outlet for his sex craft...
...since he can't screw her.
Nin-Nin!
What's the big idea, leaving me behind?!
So sorry, Nin-Nin.
l don't see anything that looks like a hotel.
We're really out in the sticks.
We'd better look for an inn or something.
Cool!
Doesn't really go with the landscape, does it?
Hey, you good-looking babes!
Are you girls from Tokyo?
l'll bet you girls came out to the
country just to get back to nature.
Why don't you let us be your guides?
They call me Hammer.
They call me Cool J.
We're the Gokufuu Club's Soul Boys!
Can we hang out with you guys for a while?
H-hold on a minute! Miko-chan!
Delicious! Doesn't fresh air make food taste better!
Hey, how about a pizza, too?
Just feel free...
Hey, miss! Let's have a pizza with all the works...
...O.J. and a salad over here!
How much do you got left?
Zero. Nothing.
Man, we find a couple of hot Tokyo girls...
...and now we don't even have
enough money for a motel!
This sucks!
That sure was a serious feast.
So, where you gonna take us next?
Uh, well, that is...
We sorta have to meet some of our buddies now.
But, it was really fun hanging out with you two.
Too bad. l really wanted to party with you some more.
Damn, she's slick!
- Sorry about that.
- See you all around.
Hey, wait a sec.
That's not fair. l paid out twice what he did!
Well then, here's your reward.
So, how do you like Yaku-chan's breasts?
l bet those things feel better than mine do.
They do feel great. City girls sure are something!
Hey, you don't have to hang on all day.
Oh, l'm sorry.
See you, maybe we'll meet agian.
Nice, in a naive sort of way.
Well, at least our stomachs are full now.
Too bad we couldn't swing a
free motel room for the night.
Miko-chan! You're unbelievable!
No sweat. l'd just string them
along until they both fell asleep.
You're a real city girl, all right.
l could never be that convincing myself.
lt's gonna get dark soon.
We'd better find a place to sleep.
Miko Mido...
Don't!
You're really stacked!
They're like a couple of small watermelons.
Don't! You're getting me horny.
What a view! l'm glad l rented
a room to those two young girls.
The wife was pretty well stacked herself, God rest her.
l'd like to get a little suck
on those babies, though!
Miko-chan, wow you're pretty impressive down there.
Ahh! Don't do that...!
l don't recall any of the other
girls in the village...
...having one as well developed as yours, Miko-chan.
You must be really well-trained.
What...!
Oh, relax. We're both ninja, aren't we?
Try and squeeze it.
Look! lt's swelling up!
Oh, my grandmother always made sure
my training was pretty good, you know.
lf you're jumped by Kugutsumen...
...l'll bet you could cut his dick off inside of you.
l hope l don't slip up so badly that l'd have to try.
l'll bet you could fit a whole fist inside there.
No way! Don't play with it!
That felt good!
Too bad Nin-Nin has to be out scouting around...
...but we got to stuff ourselves...
and now l'm really ready for
a good night's sleep, aren't you?
What's...? l think l smell lilies.
l don't smell anything like lilies.
Your nose is just amazing!
l'll just bet you could smell something
no matter how far away it was.
Maybe.
How about an after bath snack
and some fresh parsley juice?
Ah, you bet. Let's eat!
Cheers!
Delicious!
And there's miso on the side, too.
Smells good.
That's natural country cooking for ya.
Huh...? Miko-chan, your face looks strange.
So does yours, Yaku-san...
What's wrong...my body...?
Me...too...
Mister...?
You did well to sniff out
the lilicae in the drink.
lt's colchicine, and it's extracted
from powdered inu saffron.
The alkaloid components in it paralyzes
all of your sensory nerves.
But why...?
Dogwort is a highly poisonous
plant known as chikutokishin.
These two ingredients have
rendered you helpless.
The Man of a Thousand Faces...
Kugutsumen...
That's right. Now, before l cart
the two of you off to see Kamiri...
...l'm going to have a bit of fun with you.
My, all wet so soon?
l'll have fun with that and
your breasts as well.
Yaku-san!
Look well, Miko!
Her heart will never stand reaching an orgasm.
She will surely die at the height of ecstasy!
You perverted traitor...
There, there... The hotter she gets,
the closer she comes to death.
Even weakened, her senses are still keen.
As she approaches her climax,
her heart will explode!
Oh, l see gramps has the
bathhouse cranked up for me.
Does he have some lodgers tonight?
Probably got a couple of newlyweds in there.
Maybe l should just take a little peek.
Gramps?! What the hell...?!
l can't take it!
Oh no... lt's a full moon,
and Yaku-san's body will turn into...
My sense of smell gets a little
haywire when there's a full moon.
A full moon?
People sometimes have embarassing
secrets they want to keep.
She gets sex-crazed during a full moon.
lf l don't do something, her heart...!
Well now, shall l take you up as high as l can?
Yaku-san!
What the hell...?!
You've seen what l didn't
want you to see, Miko-chan.
What l turn into during a full moon.
You...!
lf l can come before it happens,
l can avoid it.
lf the fun lasts too long,
then l'm doomed to this form.
Why, you...!
l won't forget this!
What?
You...
Miko-chan, are you all right?
Yeah. My antidote technique's
started to kick in.
So, now you have seen me at my worst.
l'll understand if you hate me now.
No, not at all.
You know, l'm a blue-blooded half-Shikima.
l'm really very happy that you have
now shared your secret with me.
Thank you. You're the only
person who's ever said that to me.
What a coincidence, running into him!
Who'd have guessed this was that joyrider's home?
Yaku-san!
Well, l have to admit l sorta like his type.
And this is the best way l can think of
to thank him for that banquet today.
No way!
Ah, that feels good... The m-m-m-monster!
You must have been seeing things.
Too many horror videos or something.
The two city girls, eh?
Yes. We meet again!
So the one making me feel so good must be...
...Yaku-chan, the extremely well stacked one.
lt's okay. Do what you want.
l haven't gotten any since l left my village.
No way!
lt's okay? lt's really okay?
Yeah... Yeah. l'm halfway to an orgasm, so...
Lucky me!
Yes!
Now what? l'm getting so horny
watching those two suck each other.
l can't take this!
Yaku-san's really something else.
But... But... l wonder if we should be doing this
while poor little Nin-Nin's out there all alone.
Wow...
Who's there?!
Yikes! She's spotted me!
What?!
Kugutsumen, you knew where Miko and Yaku were
and came slinking back anyway?!
l wasn't expecting Yaku's counterattack.
But now that we have the
bite-sized ninja as a hostage
we can lure Miko here.
Your sex craft is slipping.
You've changed, Kamiri!
Your body and soul were mine
Even after we both vowed to
kill Seikima, the Shikima king
and together take control of the ninja clans.
That vow was not in vain.
Then why hasn't the wound they
gave you in the village healed yet?
How many months has it been
since you let me inside of you?
l've taken to raping those girls
in the village because
l can't get anything from you!
That's why l went after Yaku.
My carelessness is all your fault!
You truly desire me that much?
l do!
l can't take this any more!
You want this?
Kamiri, please!
Let me have it, with its overflowing love juices!
You'll have it after Miko shows us
the way into the Shikima world...
...and Seikima is dead.
Let the anticipation excite you.
They say abstinence makes the
sex much better, Kugutsumen.
l just can't take any more of this!
Those two don't have any limits!
lt's a total rip-off playing with
myself in front of those two.
Nin-Nin?
Miko-chama, l can smell the love honey from here!
Those two are the reason. l feel
like l'm about ready to come, too.
Miko-chama, let me help!
What's that Nin-nin?
lt's a special mechanical dildo l invented...
...for when we find Kamiri and attack her!
How do you like it, Miko-chama?
lt's really great!
lt feels like l'm being screwed with the air!
l don't know why, but it feels incredible.
Nin-Nin! lt's incredible!
l know that voice...
Feel so good.
Fool! Did you really think that
micro-ninja could build this?!
Kugutsumen!
You've fallen into my trap, Miko Mido.
lf you want your ''Nin-Nin'',
he'll be with Kamiri until...
...you tell us how to get
into the Shikima world.
So good... l'm going to come!
Now, will you tell me Miko's
path into the Shikima world?
Don't wanna look! Don't wanna!
So, how do you like my air dildo?
The core draws air into it and
then releases it into your hole.
Much more comfortable than a man's flesh would be.
Are you kidding? l don't know
what a real man even feels like!
Little liar! Then explain why your hole is so active!
lt must have seen hundreds of battles!
Well, l've just done it with lots
of Shikima and monsters so far.
My body's just doing it as a reflex.
l couldn't be so careless as to use something that
you could only snap off inside of you!
No fair!
l'm free to do my worst!
Like this!
And this!
Something just went inside of me!
l hope you felt that. Did you think
l came here just to air fuck you?
What are you...?
My snatch is throbbing on its own.
l'm getting so hot!
l've inserted a small, but
effective, control device in your womb.
lt's in my womb?
The womb is the center of a woman
and the source of all life
and ability for a female ninja.
lf you take control of the womb,
you take control of the woman!
Oh, that was great! Yaku-chan, five times in a row!
Oh, that's nothing. l'm ready for more.
No way! l thought farming
made me tough, but not enough.
You're right. l think l'll go wash
up now, and give this baby a rest.
Oh well. l'll go and get some
sleep in grampa's room.
Alright. See you in the morning.
That was sure great!
Strange... Where did Miko-chan go?
Miko-chan.
l was watching you, and now...
l can't stand it!
l want to have you, too.
Wait a...!
Yes! Feels so good! l'm coming!
l'll make you feel even better.
l'm... l'm coming!
No, you're going... Straight to heaven!
Miko-chan!
Miko, the controller you carry in
your womb has you in its grip.
You are my puppet.
Now kill Yaku! Kill her!
Never let her become a werewolf again!
Miko-chan, what's...?
Yaku-chan, what's wrong?!
No! She's dead!
lt can't be! Miko-chan's...
No! Yaku-chan! She killed Yaku-chan!
So you've come, Miko.
Ka...miri...
Kamiri, Miko has fallen into my little womb control trap.
You did it! Well done, Kugutsumen.
Nin-Nin... Where's Nin-Nin...?
That little ninja?
Before he would talk, he covered himself
with my love juice and then fainted.
Rather pathetic.
You must give me Zipang...
Even though under our control,
you must still remember your mission.
Much as l'd like to respect your willpower
in your condition l'm sure l would rather
have you show me how to get in to...
the Shikima world.
You think you can just order me to do it?
As befitting a Miroku ninja woman. Excellent.
You're stretching it!
l'll use all the secret sexcraft
arts to control you.
Feels so good...
lndeed. But it isn't just that l'm
a master of the Miroku sex craft.
Kugutsumen multiplied the effect
of the womb controller, just in case.
lf you resist, it'll rip your uterus apart!
You're looking at losing the whole honey pot.
Your resistance is futile.
No use... Feels so good!
Kamiri!
The damned controller isn't supposed to come out!
That enough, Kamiri!
That voice!
Your womb's as well trained as the rest, Miko-chan.
That was a close one, though.
- Not you!
- But you are dead!
Sorry to disappoint you.
When l noticed how strange Miko-chan was acting
l also smelled the radio transmitter in her womb
- ...and then figured it all out.
- What?!
So, you see l basically played dead for you.
What's so funny?
The controller may be out, but its
effects will not be wearing off for a while.
Miko is still under our control.
No, it can't be.
You poor little girls are still
no match for me!
Now, let us into the Shikima world!
Miko-chan!
What the...?
Hammer!
Yaku-chan! Miko-chan!
Gokufuu club, to the rescue!
- Assholes!
- Meddlers!
Alright, drive them into the old factory!
Miko-chan, are you okay?
Yeah. But, never mind about me.
We have to get Zipang back.
Right. Absolutely.
Kamiri! What the devil...?!
A monster!
What is this?!
Kamiri has awakened me from my centuries of slumber.
Who are you?!
Zipang. The cursed sword of blood and sex slime.
What?! But you're supposed to
be the Miroku clan's treasure!
No one has known my true nature until now.
You're a demon!
lndeed. 1400 years ago, l was a treasure
of the ruined house of Aobe
in the ancient Korean kingdom of Shillagi.
The daughter of a powerful clan who had stolen me
amused herself by inviting travelers
in at night for carnal pleasures.
Once the affairs were over,
she would slash them to death
using me so as to contain the rumors of her lust.
But she didn't just kill the men.
Her blood lust excited her
and she would slideme across her vessel
reliving the ecstasy of their deaths
and building her orgasms higher and higher.
This feast of sex and blood
seemed to go on for days.
At last, she pushed me
up to her own throat
in a frenzy of orgasmic madness.
And her blood and lust have survived within me.
That's can't be true!
And you're my village's greatest treasure?!
l was passed from generation to generation
sleeping in my role as a holy
relic of the Miroku and the Shikima.
And at last, Kamiri has awakened me from my slumber.
Kamiri... Then it wasn't you who denied me your body.
lt was all your mingling with this thing every night!
She is no longer for any human.
She is now my slave.
Kamiri!!!
Look at Kamiri's body... lt's joining with Zipang!
lt is her destiny, she who
has given herself over to me.
Yaku-chan!
Yaku-san!
l now have control of Kamiri's body.
And with this girl, l will become even more powerful!
Yaku-chan!
Yes! Yes! lt feels like...
lt feels like l'm going to die!
Don't underestimate a Miroku ninja woman!
You fool!
l am a sword at heart! Of what
use are daggers against me?!
Oh damn, it looks like this is it!
Feel the pleasure and go mad!
Let the love juices and your own
lustful hearts drive you
to give me your powers!
Does it feel good? lt does, l'm sure!
Let yourselves be carried away
by this orgasmic madness!
Like hell! Don't expect me to follow
Kamiri's path of defeat!
That was close.
Great work, Nin-Nin! That thing'll
never pull itself back together.
Miko-chan, you're all right!
l created an instantaneous steel
membrane over myself for protection!
Don't think l'll be so easily destroyed!
No way!
So much for you.
Now, shall l rape you to death?
What? l'd sooner become a man
than be forced to have sex with a monster like you!
You lie! Why then do you drip
with the slime of passion?
Why does your vessel throb and your body burn?
Deep down, you know you really desire me!
No! Don't!!
Don't fuck with the Gokufuu club!
A regular human can keep fighting
but a half-demon like me can't do anything.
l'm finished. l'm starting to lose consciousness.
Good-bye, everyone. l couldn't do anything. Sorry.
Grandma...
Mother...
Miko, daughter of both human and Shikima.
How can one who carries the
blue blood of the Shikima
be beaten by this low-born scum?!
Father...
You are a ninja of the Miroku
clan, and nothing can defeat you!
Not with the spirit and knowledge you possess!
l won't lose. l won't!
For Dad's sake, for everyone's sake...
l'll give my ribbon all the
spirit l have left!
l call upon the secret arts of
the Mido of the Miroku clan!
The Blue Whirlwind Attack!
Stop! Stop it!!!
Wow...! Yaku-chan!
Run for it! She's blowing everything away!
She's cutting me apart!
l, who have survived centuries
on blood and lust! How...?!
Miko-chan.
Yaku-san.
You did it.
Yeah. But Zipang has been cut to ribbons, though.
lt's better this way.
The Zipang we saw come to life
was never really a treasure to begin with.
And there was Kamiri and Kugutsumen...
They got what they deserved.
But now that they aren't tools
for Zipang to use any longer
maybe they can pursue their real
love story in the next world.
Maybe...
No one will ever tear us apart.
lt's a miracle we're even still alive.
Hammer-kun!
lt's party time, girls! Party!
And when we finish this time...
Sure, we'll do it till the sun comes up.
Jeez, you can't take those two sex maniacs anywhere.
You can take me wherever you go, Miko-chama!
Nin-Nin.
Well, that part's certainly worth living for!