No! Stop!
Let me go!
Help me!
No!
It was only a dream.
Who would have ever thought
that such a terrible dream
would soon become horribly real.
Angel of darkness 2
The trouble started on a day just
before the end of the spring semester.
My name is Haruka Tachibana,
an ordinary student majoring
in Natural Science.
Hey, Haruka!
Reiko, good morning!
This is Reiko Yoshinaga, my best
friend since we were both kids.
She's a bit of a tomboy,
and is currently a member
of the kendo club.
What's wrong, Haruka?
Your eyes are red.
Yeah, I had a really weird
dream last night,
and I never did get back to sleep.
I'm really going to get tired now.
Professor!
Good morning, Professor Shimazaki.
You're always here so early!
Good morning, Professor Anzai.
Oh! She's on the Akina
volleyball team!
Hey, this one's part of the
Naumi swimming club.
It's tearing me apart!
So, how's about thirty bucks a print?
I'll buy!
Me too!
I'm rich!
What are you doings?
– Haruka!
– Kazuya, what is this?
Well, it's a...
It's a what?
That, I'm sorry to say, is
my boyfriend, Kazuya.
I knew he was in the Photography
club and Mass Communications
but I can't believe he actually
made that his part-time job!
Idiot!
The process of natural selection means
that animals and plants are always
changing themselves in response
to changes in their environment.
These changes can be either
in physical form, structural,
or in a way the organism
functions, behavioral.
Under this theory,
there are occasionally extremely
radical changes called mutations.
Mutants are unlike any other
organisms...
Haruka... Haruka...
Yes, Sir!
Miss Tachibana, didn't you
get any sleep last night?
Yes... I mean...
After my lecture, stay and
clean up the classroom.
Yes, Sir...
That Professor Shimazaki
is really sneaky,
not to mention really weird.
Know what I heard?
Shimazaki's got a secret lab!
A secret lab?
Yeah, you know that one in the
basement of the building?
Really, the one in the basement?
Practically nobody's ever
seen what's in there.
I've heard there are a lot
of weird plants inside,
like nothing no one's ever seen!
Weird plants?
Yeah, there was someone who
saw inside it before
There were a lot of really weird,
freaky insectivorous plants.
He was really freaky too.
Insectivorous plants eat
bugs and stuff, right?
Yeah, the place was full of them.
Man, that is just too gross!
Well, I've got to be going now!
What, you're not going to help
me clean up anymore?
I've got a kendo practice
to go to. See ya!
Reiko...
I hate this.
Being along in the botany
lab is too scary.
Haruka!
Who's there?
Hey, Haruka!
What's wrong?
Hey, pull yourself together,
Haruka! Hey!
Where am I?
Ah, you're awake!
Kazuya?
What happened?
I was with Reiko cleaning the room...
Oh yes, and after she left...
Haruka!
What?
Forget about it.
Don't forget what's really
important, Haruka.
What? Now wait just
one minute!
In here? I don't think so!
No, stop it.
Stop it, someone's going to see.
It's okay, no one will come in here.
Are you starting to feel good, Haruka?
I'm so hot...
Please come...
Don't tease me like this.
Oh, be quiet!
You'll get your food soon.
What?
Was that the wind?
What do you mean, "what"?
Huh? Oh, sorry! Sorry, I thought
someone was watching.
Oh, that's a nice thought.
Now I'm turned off.
I'm sorry!
Sir, I brought the reports
you asked for.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Well... Sir?
Sir?
Cease this pointless resistance.
All you have to do is make
some food for them.
Look at them, the poor little dears.
Normal foods aren't enough anymore.
Just look at how skinny they are.
I've got a lot of work to do!
Don't worry.
All you need to do is relax and
let them take care of the rest.
Well then, if you please...
Wonderful! What a beautiful
flower you are.
Excellent! Make her feel
it deep inside!
Now listen, you will erase everything
you saw from your memory.
Yes.
But you will come immediately
whenever I summon you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You are dismissed.
Yes, excuse me.
How magnificent! What a marvelous
potential for growth!
If it continues growing at this rate...
This is wonderful!
Absolutely wonderful!
Oh, it's budding! My first level of
research has been completed!
What are you doing!
What... What has happening?
Why... Why Professor Shimazaki?
If you watch closely, you'll see the
plant reacts even as I touch it.
As you can see, plants
are very sensitive,
and this sensitivity includes an ability
to feel a person touching it.
Now, let's see how it reacts
to inanimate objects.
First a drop of mineral water.
And now we'll use some water
with ammonia in it.
All right, everyone separate into
groups and write a report
charting the effects of liquids,
solids and living organisms.
Yes, Ma'am!
Haruka!
Haruka, wake up!
What, Reiko?
What do you mean, "what"?
Why are you so spaced?
Well...
Take it easy, Reiko.
I bet Haruka was thinking about what
happened here yesterday!
You jerk! What are you
talking about?!
That was all your fault anyway!
Haruka, what are you doing?
What did you mix in that?
I don't know... Uh oh...
Well, we've got no choice now.
Let's dump it in.
Just what did you mix in this liquid?
I was so out of it that I...
I think I mixed a lot of stuff.
I don't remember, sorry.
Well, don't worry about it.
I'll analyze it later.
Let's just put this away for now.
Professor Shimazaki!
I wanted to see you.
What good timing!
I was just about to head
for your laboratory.
What is it?
I have a flower that withered during
today's lab experiment.
I thought you might know what
happened to it, so...
I understand. This way.
You have a lot of unusual
plants down here.
Step this way, and I'll show you
something even more unusual.
Is this a plant?
You might call it that.
You can't really call it a plant or an
animal. It's quite mysterious.
It's also a very troublesome plant,
especially since its special
food is so hard to get!
Professor Shimazaki, help me!
The special food it needs is you!
Professor Shimazaki has something...
something...
Let me tell you something about it.
It requires your vaginal fluids to live.
It is a very rare plant, or animal
indeed, Ms Anzai!
This one has its own
will and ambition.
This is an entirely new
breed of creature,
created by the miracle of nature!
You too shall become its
slave, Ms Anzai!
You know, I have needs too.
Let me take it from the other side.
Ms. Anzai!
There's something terrible
happening Kazuya!
Kazuya!
Haruka, can't you see I'm working!
Kazuya, I was so scared!
Hey, I'm going to fall!
You must have had a weird
dream or something.
No, it wasn't a dream!
Professor Shimazaki turned into a
monster and ravished Professor Anzai!
Well, I can't say that Professor Anzai
looks particularly ravished.
Professor Anzai!
Hello Haruka what are
you doing here?
Weren't you just in
Professor Shimazaki's lab?
Professor Shimazaki?
No, I was in my own lab.
See you!
See, it's just your mistake.
I have to go.
So, what's up, Haruka?
Please Reiko, you are the only one
who might believe me.
Okay, okay. What do you
want me to do?
Oh, yeah!
No this... I see...
Lucky! A wide-open window!
Awesome! What a view!
What's that?
Shimazaki!
Oh, damn!
Reiko, shouldn't we get out of here?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who wanted to find out
about Shimazaki's true form, right?
Let's go.
But wait...
Come on.
Reiko, what're those sounds?
There's something in there.
What is this?
Surprised, Miss Tachibana?
And Miss Yoshinaga, you too?
Shimazaki!
This thing lives on female fluids.
Now you too shall become plant food!
Run, Haruka!
A waste of energy!
You cannot escape!
I can take you out all by myself!
What the...
Let me go, you monster!
What are you doing?
What a lively catch!
Reiko...
At last, you're awake!
Now, it's your turn to be
bait on the hook!
No!
Your friends are all waiting.
Reiko! Professor Anzai!
Now, go and feel up your friend.
Reiko, what's happened to you?
Reiko, stop...
No!
Stop it!
Let me help you, Miss Tachibani.
Professor, no... stop...
It's just like Haruka said.
Shimazaki is a...
Haruka!
Professor Anzai!
And Reiko!
Shimazaki!
What the hell is that flower monster?!
Flower... Monster... Flower...
That's it!
How naughty...
Let me have a taste too, you two.
So good...
Right there!
Hang in there, Haruka!
And now it's your turn!
I'll do you right!
Haruka!
Kazuya!
Oh, how convenient!
You came to die!
Die!
Take this!
What do you think your doing?
What is this?
Haruka!
Are you all right?
Haruka, are you hurt?
Yeah, I'm okay.
This is all thanks to that solution
that you made.
Ms. Anzai and Reiko ought to recover
from being controlled by Shimazaki.
Everybody's okay.
Reiko!
Reiko, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
asked you to do this.
You made that solution?
Run, Haruka!
Kazuya!
Now, give me your fresh fluid
and heal my body.
Haruka!
Kazuya!
I'm invincible! I won't die
from this! I won't die!
Haruka...
Kazuya...
It was like a nightmare, there
and then gone in a flash!
It's been a few months since then.
The campus is back to normal,
so quiet and peaceful.
Good morning!
Good morning.
But who can say that nightmare
will not return?