Sanshiro, can I come in?
C-Could you wait for a second?
Are you studying?
Y-Yes.
W-What can I do for
you, Miss Momoyo?
Let's go shopping!
But...
It's not healthy to stay
at home on such a nice day.
Come on, let's go!
Yes...
Sanshiro, hurry up.
Please wait, Miss Momoyo.
Let's eat something
delicious before we go home.
Huh?
Y-Yes.
I had a great time today.
W-Well, we should go home soon.
I know.
You're spoiling the mood.
Watch out, Miss Momoyo!
I-I'm sorry.
Do you understand?
Keep your position in mind.
What's that look?
N-Nothing, sir...
I'm terribly sorry.
Excuse me.
I was just wondering where you were.
You went shopping
with that guy again?
You have such a bad taste.
That's a bit rude, Sister.
I didn't realize you were so into him.
N-Not like that.
Your wedding is just around the corner.
You better be careful.
That bruise...
Master did it, didn't he?
You poor thing.
I'll cheer you up.
I'll make you forget about the pain.
I know that you watch...
what Master and I do.
It's big...
I'll treat you just like Master...
Forget about Miss Momoyo.
M-Miss Tamao, please stop it!
You really like Miss Momoyo...
We've been expecting
you, Mr. Furushiba.
Welcome.
Welcome, Yoichiro.
How was England?
It was a great experience.
Welcome back.
It's been a while, Miss Momoyo.
I'm glad you returned safely.
You've gotten even more beautiful.
I didn't see anyone as
beautiful as you in all England.
You flatter very well, Yoichiro.
I'm not flattering.
She's still a kid.
I want you to educate her.
Father...
It's been a while.
Yes, it has.
Actually, Momoyo's bridal
dress was just delivered this morning.
Please, take a look.
Of course, let me look at it.
What do you think?
Well...
I've never seen such pure bright white.
I can't wait to see
Momoyo in this dress.
Momoyo is such a lucky girl to be
marrying a gentleman like you, Yoichiro.
Oh Father, but I bet
you're going to miss her dearly.
He'll be fine.
Because he has this divorced daughter.
Sister...
That's enough.
Put it back.
Yes, sir.
Ouch!
What happened?
A sewing needle was still on the dress.
Let me...
P-Please stop, Mr. Yoichiro.
I just don't want your blood on
the bridal dress, it's very special.
Sanshiro.
What are you doing out here?
Nothing...
Getting some fresh air.
I see...
Miss Momoyo, aren't you
going to get into a trouble?
It's okay.
Father and the others are
talking about something complicated.
So...
What happened to your face?
It's nothing, I'm fine.
Father...
Father scolded you again, didn't he?
I'm sorry...
It swelled up.
The evil aura is getting stronger...
I hope nothing bad will happen...
Miss Momoyo is sacred...
Nobody should stain her.
Yet, that man...
Master...
Oh, Master, no...
I hate that stuck-up
greenhorn from the Furushiba family.
Please Master, don't...
You were flirting
with him too, weren't you?
N-No...
Don't lie!
That bastard, he thinks I'm a fool!
Master...
I'm useless...
I can do nothing but
watch her from a distance.
Harder, Yoichiro.
Yoichiro!
Please forgive me...
I wonder what Momoyo would
think about your naughty hobby.
No, don't tell her.
You want to violate both
me and Momoyo, don't you?
You're such a whore.
You are jealous, aren't you?
I guess I haven't
trained you well enough.
Damn whore!
Yes, I'm a whore.
Filthy blood...
To think that Momoyo
also has such filthy blood in her...
I will train her, nice and slow...
I don't want her to have you.
Please, give it to me.
I want you.
Oh, do you?
You're dripping all over.
Please, give it to me, don't tease me.
Now!
Give it to me now.
Don't tease me.
Yes, yes...
M-My head...
It hurts...
Miss Reiko...
Miss Reiko!
What on earth...
It's like a...
piece of art.
What is that?
"I am who aims at the bride"...
Master, please call the police.
Unnecessary.
What?
She died from an epidemic.
B-But...
That's a good idea.
If you report this to the police, it
will spread through the world and...
it'll be problematic for
marriage between Momoyo and I.
That's right, Yoichiro.
Sister!
I'll never let anybody touch Momoyo.
I'll hire veteran security guards.
How's security?
Perfect.
I suspect everyone who
disagrees with this marriage.
I'll use this gun when I find him.
We can't let our guard down.
I have a good idea.
What's that?
I want to get married to
Momoyo as soon as possible.
Sounds good.
I knew you would agree with me.
What happened that night after I...
I can't remember...
But I remember Mr. Yoichiro was
having a twisted affair with Miss Reiko.
I can't let a man like
that have Miss Momoyo.
Yes?
It's me, Yoichiro.
Come in.
I have good news.
Our wedding date is moved up.
It will be next...
We shouldn't get married.
What are you talking about?
Our marriage must be cursed.
So...
Be strong.
I love you.
He's lying!
So what if somebody's
opposed to the marriage between...
the Count's family and
the Furushiba conglomerate?
My love for you will
overcome any obstacle!
Mr. Yoichiro...
Did I scare you?
I guess I did scare you.
Sanshiro Goda.
H-How do you know my name?
Hey!
What's your name?
Sanshiro Goda.
You may get into
trouble with women, be careful.
Remember me now?
I'm Konago.
K-Konago?
I've been looking out for you...
but it attacked the
woman when I was off guard.
How do you...
Somebody's coming.
Who's that?
He must've killed Miss Reiko.
And next he'll...
He sure looks possessed
by the evil spirits.
T-The evil spirits?
Yes.
I have no time to explain, let's go.
What?
We're going after him.
Hold my hand and close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
W-Who are you?
I've been hunting
evil for two hundred years.
Y-You mean you've been
living for two hundred years?
Don't worry, I'm not a ghost.
Look, it seems we are almost there.
It's here...
Is it you who called me?
Meeting after midnight
brings the smell of death.
I have to settle things with you...
before the freshly
cut flower is disgraced.
Settle?
What are you talking about?
Why would anyone
hold a grudge against me?
I'm not holding a grudge.
I just want to love you.
I want us to love each other
until our bodies and hearts are burnt.
Interesting.
Please, come closer.
Be careful.
There's a demon in there.
A demon?
Oh, please keep enjoying yourself...
Hey, can I see your face now?
P-Please, show me your face.
How is it, Mr. Yoichiro?
Does it feel good?
They're gone!
What's going on?
Not here either!
Damn demon!
M-Miss Momoyo?
No.
She's not Momoyo.
What?
What happened to Momoyo?
Who is the
mysterious sorceress, Konago?
The evil hands of the
demon that haunt Momoyo...
tear up the wedding dress mercilessly.
The Sex Beast...
growls ominously in the mansion.