Got it!
You're so cool, Mr. Kawamura!
One more time...
Please...
Only me...
I...
Love you so much...
Oh, please.
Please tell me...
I've been what you wanted me to be.
What was wrong with me?!
Please...
Please tell me, Sir.
Mr. Kawamura!
I'll do anything for you.
I'll never disobey you!
Please don't look at anyone but me.
Please, black crystal ball.
Please grant my wish.
If you grant me this wish,
I'll sell my body to the powers of darkness forever!
Who are you?
I am Shimazaki!
Angel of Darkness 3
Hey, it's Miss Yamashira!
Hi, Minako!
Good luck on your next tennis match, Minako!
You know we'll all be cheering for you!
You're a shoo-in to win the championship.
Let's celebrate your victory with a great party!
Championship? Winning's just a matter of luck, you know
What's all the fuss, ladies?
Oh, Sir!
Hello, Mr. Kawamura!
I'm so jealous, Minako.
You're always surrounded bysuch beautiful girls.
Whatever you say, Mr Kawamura!
The school's number one playboy walking all alone?
How unusual!
Don't be silly.
Okay, Yamashira!
I'm going to steal away all your fans
by showing them what a great tennis player I am.
Really?
I'm looking forward to it.
Sir...
So, that's the one?
That's right. That's him.
Very well.
But you do remember the conditions, don't you?
Yes, I do.
But I can't...
do that kind of...
Oh, yes you can. It's not hard.
I... I... I...
I see...
You were a virgin.
You're a very good student.
I'll see you around.
Wait, Sir!
Don't go, Sir!
Please wait, Sir!
I... I...
Sir...
Where am I?
Ms. Mamiya?
Then this must be the nurse's office.
Ms. Mamiya? Ma'am?!
Oh, my! How embarrassing!
I fell asleep in front of a patient!
Oh, well I...
Ms. Takabe, how do you feel now?
I'm fine now, thank you.
Really?
I was worried when I found you in the hall unconscious.
You were out cold.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'll get you a glass of warm milk.
Please don't bother. I...
No, its okay. I've also got some nice cake.
Come on, let's eat.
Okay...
Is Ms. Mamiya here?
Excuse me, Ms. Yamashira has twisted her ankle
during an exhibition match.
Sir, I'm fine.
Oh, my!
Please put her in that empty bed over there.
It's okay. You'll be fine now, Minako.
Sir, I...
I'll go get your clothes, you stay here and rest.
No, Sir! Don't go!
Please stay here with me!
Minako...
Please stay with me. Please!
If you leave me, I... I...
Mr. Kawamura, I won't be able to treat her this way.
Oh, sorry! I'll go now.
No!
What's so great about men, anyway?
I'll go get some bandages.
Remember, I've got another patient, so please be quiet.
Oh, well...
Ms. Takabe?
Hey, you!
Aren't you Hiromi Takabe?
We'd just like a little of your time.
We've got some important things to discuss, understand?
Who are you?! Let me go!
I haven't done anything to you.
Please let me go!
You haven't done anything?!
Is that so true down here too?
No! Stop it!
We heard that you gave your virginity to Ms. Kawamura.
That must be why you follow him around all the time.
No, I...
You know, it's foolish,
but many girls think when a man takes their virginity,
it means they'll have him forever.
We're what you might call
Mr. Kawamura's Guardians.
What? What are you...
Always make sure you're well lubricated,
or you might hurt yourself.
Look at her. See how she trembles!
Oh, you like it?!
Then let's try something even better.
Please, don't...
Stop it, please!
What shall we do?
We really don't want to do this, you know, but...
Please, stop!
Pl... Please!
Did you think we would have mercy if you cried?
If you don't want these pictures to be distributed,
don't even look at Mr. Kawamura.
Oh, you can keep the souvenir
even though we could have taken it.
Remember this picture, and feel sorry for yourself.
Why me? Why?
Sir...
No! Not here, Mr. Kawamura!
I knew you were waiting.
See how wet it is.
No, don't...
You needn't be embarrassed.
Before you're a school idol, you're a woman.
And before I'm a teacher,
I'm a man.
You're so manly.
Wonderful!
So good...
Oh, yes, Minako.
That's it...
You're doing great.
Now...
Spread your legs.
Like this?
Oh, beautiful.
Oh! My body feels so hot!
Minako, are you ready?
Sir, I'm scared!
So, you've finally decided?
If you'll grant my wish,
I'll do anything!
Very well, let's start the ceremony.
Come to me.
Good...
Now move your body up and down and pray in your mind.
My wish is to have revenge!
On everyone who's abused me!
Revenge? So sweet to my ears.
What are you doing?!
Hey! What's this?!
Look at our umbrellas!
Who the hell did this?
Oh, my!
I don't mind renting you mine,
Lady Guardians.
Hiromi Takabe!
You did this!
Bitch!
Stop!
She went into the basement, and there's no way out!
You'll pay for this!
There's no escape now!
Fools! I didn't run down here to escape!
I led you in here!
It won't open!
What's the matter, bitch?
What have you done?!
What is this?
Megumi?!
Mayu?!
Help me, Erika!
It's so gross!
Now Hiromi, how would you like your revenge?
Let's see, what should I do?
Please, stop!
Funny, that's what I said.
Do it to them twice as bad as they did to me!
Got it.
Stop it!
I'll give you my extra hard special!
Right here!
Oh, boy! I've got how much left?!
But what can I do?
Is that the time?!
It's going to be an all-nighter.
Stop...
Please...
I'll do anything.
Please forgive me.
Oh, yeah?
But we're not supposed to show mercy, even if they cry.
Right, Erika?
My revenge has only just begun!
Oh, she's still here?!
I'll see about that.
Boy, I really need a cup of coffee!
Ms. Takabe?!
Ma'am!
Ms. Takabe!
What happened, Ms. Takabe?
What's the matter?
I heard weird noises coming from the basement and I went...
And there was a strange man who attacked me!
Poor baby! You are really scared, aren't you?
Everything's okay now, honey.
Ma'am... I...
What am I going to do?
Did anyone see anything?
No...
I see.
Then let's just keep it our little secret, okay?
But...
It's okay.
I'll protect you.
Just forget about everything that happened today.
But that would be impossible!
I know it's hard now, but it's easier as time passes.
Even I could do it.
You were... You too?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't of told you that after telling you to forget.
Ma'am...
Beautiful tears...
Ma'am, let's forget.
Yes, together.
Ma'am, you're wonderful.
Oh, Hiromi, please take me.
Don't leave me alone.
Okay, Ma'am.
Let me soothe your hot body, Ma'am.
There... right there...
More... More...
Ma'am, you seem to be in a lot of pain.
Should I quit now?
No! Please don't stop now!
I understand, Ma'am.
Like this?
Oh, yes! That's it! Don't stop!
Yes! I didn't know it could feel this good!
Hold on just a little more, Ma'am,
and I'll do something even better for you.
You'll become my possession forever with this!
Oh, yes, Miss Erika.
Do you know what this is?
That's right. This is the camera
you used when you did this to me!
Fuck that shit!
That idiot! What has she done?
Pictures aren't enough!
I'm going to hang all of you from the top of the school!
Where were you?!
Sorry about that.
If you admit your faults, then it's okay.
Remember, if not for my rancor,
you wouldn't be alive!
I understand.
Haven't you had enough?
Please let us go!
Shut up!
Who said you could talk, bitch?!
I'm sorry!
Now bring me another quarry, Shimazaki!
Understood!
That's right!
From now on, everything will be my way!
Sir, do you only want me because my family is rich?
How could you ask that?
I love you as a person, not because of your fortune.
Oh, Sir, I'm sorry!
I'm so happy.
You're the only one who sees me as a real woman.
What are you so worried about?
Silly goose!
Sir!
Who... Who are you?!
I am Shimazaki!
I'm sorry to bother you, but...
I'm in a hurry as well.
So, you're finally awake.
Where?
Who are you?
Shut up!
Why does Mr. Kawamura like this slut so much?
Did you seduce him with your filthy body, whore?!
Is THIS how you did it?!
No, that's not right!
What's not right?
You let him do this, and you enjoyed it.
Didn't you, bitch?!
I was just...
You may have protested when you let him in here,
but you enjoyed it, didn't you?!
You filthy pig!
Don't ever come close to my
Mr. Kawamura again!
Is that clear?!
Please... Please don't!
I'll fuck your body up so bad you'll never show it to him!
Shimazaki!
The next thing is to bring
Mr. Kawamura here.
I want him to see this, Shimazaki!
But he's already here.
As you wished, I've already let him see her being raped.
Where is he?!
Don't you know?
He's right in front of you!
Come now.
As you wanted,
I will let the two of you become one in my body!
And when I have absorbed your body, so full of rancor,
I will be able to resurrect completely!
You tricked me!
Help me!
Ms. Takabe?
Where'd she go?
This is Ms. Takabe's.
What are you doing?!
Let me go!
My body will be able to absorb you far more easily
with a little help from your friends.
No! Please don't!
It's about time.
No! Stop!
Please let me go! Stop!
Shall I have it now?!
Ms. Takabe?
Where did she go?
No!
That voice is...
Ms. Takabe!
Ma'am, help me!
Who are you?!
Let her go now!
How humorous!
If you can get her, go ahead.
Help me, Ma'am!
What?! What the hell?!
Ma'am, he tricked me!
Mr. Kawamura, who dumped me,
and the girls who hazed me...
He said I'd have revenge on them!
He said he could get me and
Mr. Kawamura together again!
So I did what he told me, and then...
I was a fool!
I should never have made a wish to that black sphere!
The black crystal sphere..
When I hit it with the camera, he...
Ma'am, that black crystal ball!
It's that black sphere!
Break the black sphere!
The black sphere is his weakness!
What are you doing?!
You want me to break that sphere, nght?!
Stop her!
What's this?!
Hurry up! Move!
Get out of my way!
It's no use, Ma'am!
He's controlling all four of them!
You can't escape!
Here!
I won't let you!
Ma'am...
I'm sorry!
Almost...
Ms. Takabe...
I could've been...
Ms. Takabe!
Ms. Takabe, hang in there!
Ma'am... Ma'am I...
I'm so glad. So glad...
Nurse's Office
Ma'am, I...
Don't say anything.
Ma'am, I love you so much.
I love you too!
I'll never let anybody touch you.
I'll protect you.
I'm so happy.
I'm all yours.
Right, you're all mine.
Forever and ever.
All mine...