What... What the hell?
Man, can you believe all that
rain we had last night?
Keep an eye on your footing today!
What?
Hey, no one's allowed in
the construction area!
What the...
Good morning.
Angel of darkness
Looking back on it, the horror
really began that spring.
I remember, because the cherry
blossoms had just begun to fall.
The old and distinguished boarding
school for young ladies,
nested so serenely among
the protecting trees,
had been replaced by a sparkling
new Women's Academy.
A new chapel had been built as well,
and both were open and waiting
for the new crop of freshmen.
Just what you'd expect of a
distinguished school
for young ladies, all so
sweet and pretty.
Oh, excuse me for not
introducing myself.
My name Is Atsuko Yoshikawa,
I'm a freshman here.
And over there you can see the love
of my life, Sayaka Matsumoto.
Anyone with half an eye can
see how cute she is,
but Sayaka's no slouch in the
brain department either!
Luckily, I was able to scrape by well
enough on the entrance exams
so we could stay together.
And with Sayaka and I bunking
together in the dorm,
I'd figured school life was going
to be pretty sweet.
But can you believe this?
Not only to my older sister now
living in the same dorm,
but she's also going to be
one of our teachers!
What will happen if my uptight
older sister finds out
what's really going on between
Sayaka and me?
Man, I don't even want
to think about it!
It's scary!
Man, was that boring!
Atsuko!
What?
Don't run off and abandon me, Atsuko!
I'm sorry, but I get twitchy when
big sister is watching over us.
Come on...
Aw, let's blow, I'll buy you a cake!
Okay!
Oh, wow! That is so weird!
Take a look at thisl
Oh shoot! And it was a good one too!
You'd better get rid of it!
There's something spooky
about that picture.
Yeah! You ought to toss it!
I agree. I'd better handle it.
Well, okay, I'll get rid of it.
This is the first one from
the freshman class?
Indeed!
We're so pleased to
have you join us!
Now then, suppose we try this?
Very good. And how would
you like one of these?
There!
Oh, what a beautiful welt!
She seems to have fainted.
Well, we should start the experiment.
True enough.
It would seem it prefers the
extract of younger women.
Sooner or later, we'll have to set
our sights on more freshmen.
Miss Yoshikawa!
The commencement ceremonies
will be starting soon!
I'm sorry! I'll be there in a moment.
Hold on a second, will you?
Hey, she's cute!
Oh, she's cute too!
And there's another, and another...
Looks like I won't have to worry about
having too much free time!
You were lusting after other girls,
weren't you?
Remember, if you can have affairs...
No! No I wasn't! I was just
thinking about you!
Atsuko! Miss Sayaka!
Sister Yuko...
Hello, Sayaka.
Atsuko, you're not planning
on being as rowdy
as you were in high school, are you?
Sis...
Still, it's good that you've got
such youthful vitality!
I wish these upper-classmen would
show half the initiative you do.
They've got no sprit at all,
as if some demon had come and
sucked the life out of them.
The fact that this welcome
party has already
developed rigor mortis seems
more than a little ominous.
Hey, Sis! Sis!
– What?
– How about I liven up this party
with one of my usual brilliant
improvisations?!
Your usual improvisations?
You don't mean...
Uh huh!
All right, everybody!
I, Atsuko Yoshikawa, representing
the freshman class,
shall now demonstrate a feat
of strength and skill!
Here we got!
To start: Ten tiles!
Next, ten juices!
Atsuko? Nobody's looking
very impressed.
Sis!
That's wonderful, Sister Yuko!
You little flirt!
What an unpleasant sound!
Such impertinence!
Made it again!
That was wonderful, Atsuko!
What a great snot!
That was terrific!
...and the resurrection
of the Holy God...
Is someone there?
Did it come from the basement?
But how...
Who... Is anyone there?
Sorry for being so late Sayaka.
Atsuko!
The rest of the club wouldn't
let me get away.
But I missed you!
I'm sorry! Let's blow this joint!
I have to take a shower.
I'm soaked!
It was so spooky! There
were strange sounds
and a weird light coming
from the basement.
Sounds intriguing!
We ought to go now.
Don't worry. It's a cinch!
There's no reason for us to be in a
dark chapel in the dead of night,
and especially not in the basement!
But exploring a dark basement
could be fun! Come on!
I'm already scared!
Hey! That's enough!
Let's go home, Atsuko!
Are you kidding? This is just
the beginning! We...
– What was that?
– Be quiet!
Fuck... It was just a cat!
Really?
All right then, let's go!
So, think you could make
it there by yourself?
I'm getting upset with you, Atsuko!
Hey! Looky there!
– Come on!
– Wait up!
It was behind the altar.
Right there!
Hey, you're right!
Hey! That's good enough!
Let's get out of here!
Are you kidding? The exploration's
barely begun!
Let's go down.
I knew you were going to say that.
I'll open it.
– What's that?
– Let's go home!
It's the school director!
Why is the director...
Who's there!
Professor Goda!
Oh damn, let's get out of here!
That's what I've been saying!
Damn!
You won't escape me!
Wait up!
Move your ass, Sayaka!
What are you doing, Atsuko?
They'll kill you! Please run, Atsuko!
Get out of here now!
Make sure my sister and
everyone else knows
that I'm just buying time!
Get goingl Hurry up!
You can't do it by yourself!
Please, come with me!
Go on!
Move it!
All right...
Damn!
Man, what a pain!
What?
It's too high!
Sister Yuko! Something terrible
has happened! Sister!
Atsuko is... Atsuko is...
What's wrong?
Sister...
Sayaka, what's happened?
Did Atsuko do something to you?
No! They got Atsuko!
WHAT?
Where am I?
Why am I here?
What's happened to me?
What's going on?
What...
What is this?
Stop it!
No, stop!
Leave me alone!
No, no, not yet.
How about this?
Please...
Please stop...
Please stop... Stop!
You'll be liking it soon enough!
What in the hell are you doing?
Master Rom!
It has come to my attention
that your tribe has become bound
to the Dark Elemental.
You know how this happened to us!
A human has broken the seal and
freed the Dark Elememal!
Now we are subject to the
power of his desires!
Enough! Get out of here!
What the...
All my cuts...
The cuts are all healed?
It was I who healed you.
Who are you?
The one who cut your bonds
and healed your wounds.
Consider it an apology for the rough
way my associates treated you.
That was quite unacceptable, even
if they were under mind control.
What are they?
Dwarves, the oldest residents
of these woods.
I am a forest elf.
An elf?
You're real!
Please, compose yourself.
Who knows what the consequences will
be if we fail to stop Goda's plans!
Goda?
What's happened to our teacher?
I do not know everything, but in his
final form, the Dark Elemental,
Goda, will become an avatar
for misery and chaos.
Dark Elemental?
An unclean, filthy beast, born
from darkness and decay,
he exists only to satisfy his own
insatiable appetites.
Countless ages have passed
since he last appeared.
These woods were a paradise then,
blessed with the bounty of the sun.
In those tranquil days, the dwarves
danced among the trees.
Streams of pure water fell into
sparkling fountains of crystal,
glistening at the forest's edge.
But then one day...
As if born from that act of destruction,
the Dark Elemental had corne!
At first, my people fell before
his unexpected onslaught,
but united we were able to
challenge and defeat him!
Unfortunately, he could not be killed!
And by absorbing energy,
he was capable of regenerating
himself endlessly!
The source of this energy was human
lust, of which he had an ample supply.
Once again, we found ourselves forced
to fly against the Dark Elemental!
The conflict seemed endless,
But at long last we found
a way to contain him,
binding his essence with
a special seal!
We buried this seed of evil,
with the seal,
deep in the forest, and at last
peace was restored.
However...
Humans began to come,
harvesting the forest.
Our power, and numbers, diminished.
The survivors were forced ever
deeper, further in the woods.
No one foresaw the danger.
We never thought what might happen if
someone like Goda broke the seal!
We never realized our power
had grown so weak that
the seal could be destroyed
by a mere human!
It's not your fault!
Would you say that knowing
that everyone who
dwells within your school has become
Goda's unwilling slave?
Say what? What about my sister
and Sayaka in the dorm?
Feeling better now?
Yes, but you're got to believe
everything I told you is true!
Right, right. I'll try.
What? Yes?
Atsuko...
Who is it? What do you...
Teacher...
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
What do I do now, Atsuko?
What's happening? Sayaka?
Yu... sister Yuko, help! Help me...
Sa... Sayaka!
Teacher...
What's wrong with you?
No! Stop it!
No, please stop, please.
That's it! Tonight I shall at
last finish my work!
So, you're saying you won't do it?
We all have to join together to
defeat the Dark Elemental.
You know that as long as
the humans remain,
the Dark Elemental cannot be killed!
There is some truth in that.
But if we do not all join together
now to attempt to defeat him,
then the future for all of us will
be both grim and horrible.
Let's join with Atsuko
to defeat him now!
But even together our powers
are insufficient
to take on the Dark Elemental.
So be it! I shall not ask you again.
And so, it appears you and I must
handle the Dark Elemental alone.
Fortunately for us, Goda has not yet
achieved his ultimate form.
His ultimate...
Goda is no longer human.
At this point the Dark Elemental
merely controls his body.
At the peak of its development,
the Dark Elemental and Goda will
become one. We must hurry!
Okay, I think I got that.
We've got to stop him before
he reaches that final form!
Look hard, Yuko!
Do you know what you are seeing?
No, what?
An entirely new creature.
Something this world has
never seen before!
This creature's life energy is
nurtured on an extract
obtained from young women.
Like these students, for example.
Welcome to my little laboratory,
Ms. Yuko.
You! You're the school's director!
I find this enlivens the otherwise
dull tedium of faculty life.
In fact, I rather enjoy it.
Tonight, I even have a new play toy!
And now, I would like to show you
something very interesting.
It's Sayaka?!
Oh, but look more closely.
What the...
Those are Atsuko's classmates,
from the dorm!
Correct! Tender young freshmen
whom I've already selected
and trained.
With my special lessons and Goda's
power, it's no big deal.
I'll be training you as well. But first...
Stop! Stop it! Sayaka!
Please, less noise if you would, Yuko.
Soon you will be just
another plaything.
However, before you can do that, we
have a vital task selected for you.
Such a full, ripened, woman's body.
We could not do this one
task with a younger girl.
You must do it!
Oh yes! That's right!
Until then, open you eyes,
wet your thighs
and watch your shameless
students perform.
She looks ready from down here.
Please, take your amusement from her.
Is that so? Well then, let me play.
After I've taken my pleasure, I shall
collect your extract as well.
Then you, young woman, shall
be my slave forever!
You're awake?
You'd be better off worrying
about yourself first.
What a slutty-looking trollop you are.
You ought to be ashamed of yourself!
What do you think of this?
How's this? Feels good, doesn't it?
It gets better and better though.
Now, you shall experience
the other joy!
With time, you'll come to love
this as much as the other.
How's this?
Does it hurt? But soon
this begins
to become
a pleasant feeling!
How do you feel?
Your life force glows brightly,
but how long can you
sustain the flame?
Struggling will grant you
no escape, Yuko!
Director! The time has come.
Okay, let's do it.
I adore the look of fear on your face.
Is it ready?
Don't move and stay calm.
I'll give you something very nice.
Here!
Excellent! It is done!
New creature!
My other self!
That's the place!
That's where they must have taken
my sister and Sayaka.
In the basement!
In there!
I'm sensing something!
Sometning horrible!
What is it?
I don't know,
but the Dark Elemental's power is
expanding somehow, of that I'm sure!
I pray that you're safe, Sayaka, Sister.
This is the final step!
Yuko, I shall now place this inside you.
It will become one with your body,
absorbing you to become
my new creature!
Your body will be integrated into the
very matrix of my new creature!
Damn! It opened last time!
No, I can't do it! The door won't
budge an inch! Oh, hell!
All right then, how about my fist?
Damn! I can't...
You must fuse with me!
– Fuse?
– Yes! Fuse ourselves into
a single body!
A single body?
The process is simple and
takes little time!
But how?
Here I go!
It's finished, Yuko.
In a few short hours you shall
be part of my new creature.
Dearest creature, the time
has come for me to
transform myself into my
own ultimate form!
All I need is a little power from
the new seedling inside you.
And then I will...
I will achieve my ultimate form!
At long last, the time has come
to reveal your ultimate form!
Ultimate form of the Dark Elemental,
reveal yourself to me!
What the...
Who the hell are you?
I've come to get Sayaka and my sister!
What's that?
Sister!
I won't let you go any further!
What?
Director! Can't you see the truth
when you look at Goda?
He's no longer human!
Who the hell cares?
I'll accept anything that expands
my own personal power.
Even make a deal with the devil!
Now, my sweet slaves, grab her!
Damn! You're crazy! Oh well,
now I have to fight!
What? Sayaka?
Stop it, Sayaka!
What's wrong with you?
Her strength's inhuman!
She'll break my neck.
I'm losing it. No...
You guys! You camel
Yes! We could lose what
little we have left
if you humans don't
put up a good fight!
Look at this! She was being
controlled through this seed!
By planting this seed in their body,
any human can be transformed
into a Dark Elemental!
And all that power could be
tapped by the original!
We'll take care of the seeds in the rest
of the girls. You defeat Goda!
Thanks, you perverted dwarf!
Move out!
So sorry! I've got the power of a
Dark Elemental myself!
The odds are 50-50 as to
who's more powerful!
Director! Just hold her back
for a few moments longer,
just a little bit more!
Oh! There it is, the ultimate form
of the Dark Elemental!
Don't take your eyes off me!
Yes! Now!
What? You're not...
I can't do anything!
She carries no seed!
That's right! I'm not under control
of the Dark Elemental.
This sort of thing just comes
to me naturally!
I didn't need e silly seed to
gain my power, either!
I gladly mixed my blood with
that of the Dark Elemental.
You mean, you actually want to
become an Angel of Darkness?
You got it! My pleasures and his
desires mesh rather well I think.
And as long as he can
find filth like you,
the Dark Elemental will
never fear death!
That's human nature!
Shut up you bitch!
This is for what you did
to that poor dwarf!
You just can't see it, can you?
Okay, now it's time to destroy
the other one!
Thank you for waiting.
However, I cannot make new creatures
if you damage that device.
Your persistence concerns me.
Yuko will need more training though.
Son of a bitch! You've achieved
your ultimate form!
Damn! We've got to beat
him somehow!
Beat me? Defeat this perfect body?
Shut your mouth!
I'll kill you myself!
What was that?
What the fuck are you?
You didn't budge an inch!
Desist! Your feeble power
is nothing next to mine!
Don't fuck with me! Next time
I'll break your ugly face!
Sis!
It has begun! And now Yuko
shall be my mate!
What have you done to my sister?
The new creature will be the
true Angel of Darkness,
and she will bear my spawn!
A female?
That's right! Like a queen ant,
producing my offspring forever.
And with this machine I shall create
still more queens from mortal females!
Like hell! I'll never let you succeed!
You are a fool!
All of you combined cannot
hope to defeat me!
And Yuko will bear my descendants
even if I die!
Miss Atsuko?
We brought you this.
Is it not your weapon?
We saw you use it before.
That?
You! What are you doing?
It's my weapon of choice!
Can you catch this?
What?
You little bitch! What?
Here I am!
When did you...
I made it!
Sister?
I'll help you!
Wait! Let me do it!
Rom?
If we leave her, she will become
another elemental!
I must enter her and cut the Dark
Elemental's seed from her womb!
But what about you?
Don't worry! Thank you, for
your kindness.
Thank you, for being what you are.
Rom!
Atsuko, in moments I shall
become a great tree.
You must now blow this
joint immediately!
What?
What the...
Why are you...
Hurry! Go!
Rom!
Atsuko...
Thank you for your help, but this is
the path I was set to follow.
There will be another Goda
if we leave the nucleus of the
Dark Elemental unbound.
I know few humans, but if there
are more like you, Atsuko,
I don't think they will
destroy this world.
Until then, I will watch over
my people from here.
Perhaps I will see you again
when Elf and Human can live
together in harmony.
Goodbye, Atsuko.
Well, today we begin a new semester
and welcome our new director.
Would you please say something?
Good morning, everyone!
I think you'll all find this new
school year quite enjoyable.