Wait a minute, l should brush up on my sex craft?
You should be practicing every day!
lf you keep messing around, Fubuki-chan will steal your title of leader of the Miroku clan!
Hmm, Fubuki-san's methods are sorta strange.
l wonder if l should just surrender my title to her?
What are you saying?
We have a mission in the Shikima realm tomorrow!
Missions are hard when l just have to have sex.
Well, but it's also fun.
Miko Mido, a student of Himenoki Girl's Academy.
Heir to the Miroku clan female ninja.
A half demon who carries the blue blood of Seikima.
The king of the Shikima realm.
Born to the strange destiny of fighting her enemies with sex.
Also known as... La Blue Girl.
Or something like that.
Bring 'em on, where ever they may be!
Who are you?!
Who's there?!
Who?! Who are you?!
Stop it!
l'm comming!
Stop it...
Damn, that dream was so real.
First of all, l've never even seen those Robocop rejects before!
No way...
They're soaked! This is so embarrassing!
l'm glad Fubuki-san wasn't here to see this.
Miko-chan, l'm staying in the Shikima realm for a while to train.
But we've got a big test coming up!
l'm just the phantom transfer student to those teachers.
And my exams down here suit me a lot more.
Miko, you'd best go back to take that exam.
Okay...
Do your best. And l'd like to borrow your little ninja here to be my guide.
Get him in shape for me, okay?
Sure. Leave him to me.
l guess it was good that l came back alone.
But l feel like Fubuki-chan's won over Nin-Nin and the entire Shikima world.
The exam!
This is the only way.
Oh, Jeez! l forgot my underwear again!
- Good morning, Principle!
- You again?
Excuse me!
Er, better get to class.
Okay.
What's with me?
Fantasizing about the students...
That's a one-way ticket to resignation!
Better hit the massage parlor again...
Help!!
Miko-chama?
She's not here, and where are the others?
l'd better hurry or l'll be in big trouble!
They're real! The guys from that wet dream l had this morning.
Miko-chan!
- You're okay!
- What's going on?
Explanations later. Don't let them get away!
Right.
Seiko! Midori!
So, how do you like seeing your friends raped?
l so love the feel of pale, young skin.
And you love the feel of metal, don't you?
Miko-chan!
Help us...!
Let them go! Stop humiliating my friends!
Soon the spectacle will begin!
Miko-chan! Where are you?
Over here, Fubuki-san!
Miko-chan!
You won't get away!
Fubuki-san...
Miko-chama!
Seiko... Midori...
lt's hypnosis gas! Snap out of it!
You're coming around, Miko-chama!
Nin-Nin? What the hell's going on?
Well... There's big trouble in the Shikima realm!
Since you went home, strange things have happened.
The king's fallen into a strange sleep
and he's come down with a strange skin-rotting sickness.
What? Dad?!
Darling, hang on! Just hang on!
And the king's always been like an unshakable mountain of health.
The cause! Do they know the cause?
Maria-sama was looking for it as hard as she could
when these weirdos broke into the realm and took her away!
What?! Mom!
- Maria-sama!
- Damn it, who are you?!
Some of them who attacked were like holograms with no physical form.
And then these super-strong mechanical guys...
...suddenly would appear for real and then they'd start ripping the Shikima apart!
You mean those cyborg guys who grabbed Seiko and Midori?
Uh-huh!
l didn't realize. They even got my mom? But why?
We don't know either.
Fubuki-chan and l were on their trail, but they disappeared.
Disappeared?
The guys who attacked the Shikima realm.
We were sure they'd go after you next.
And you came to school to rescue me.
But that mess happened.
We can't leave Fubuki-san to handle this by herself.
What are we going to do?!
Can't breathe... Miko-chama!
People who can freely be both projections and solid.
Sounds weird, doesn't it?
Their power isn't of this world, l'm sure of it.
Not from this world? Then who?
And l'll bet anything that someone's behind their attack.
Ma'am, where do you think my mother, my friends, and Fubuki-san might be now?
To be brief, there are at least 3000 realms.
The realm of demons, of Shikima, of Buddhas, of ghosts...
lt would be beyond the abilities of any ninja to check them all.
Then what do we do?
Go to a spiritualist l trust.
A spiritualist?
lt is the only way to find your mother, Miko-chan.
l cannot refuse the old woman's request.
- Please!
- Whatever you can do.
Naam mandala daramandaa. Naam mandala daramandaa.
Where are you, you who were taken from the Shikima realm?
Maria, wife of Seikima, mother of this girl.
Life which flows through the 3000 realms...
Tell us where this girl's mother is. Show us the way...
Naam mandala daramandaa. Naam mandala daramandaa.
What's wrong?!
Some incredible power... Telling me to withdraw...
Miko-chama, look!
Nin-Nin!
Ma'am!
- Pervert!
- Miko-chama!
lt was bad luck that you hired this foolish medium who discovered us!
Who are you? My mother's kidnapper, right?!
lt's hurts!
Stop it! Let me go!
Miko Mido... Such a lovely scene.
Where do you come from?!
Amplified by that foolish medium's power...
...the request that warped space and time to call me forth...
...from the lnjo realm was made by you!
lnjo realm...?
Beyond the flow of time and space among the 3000 realms...
...it is the world of defilement and carnal lusts controlled by Lady Taijuten!
Taijuten?
We have become the servants of Taijuten so that...
...we may defeat the Shikima realm and realize our dreams!
Who are you?!
Have you forgotten, Miko Mido?
A survivor of the Suzuka...
From our raid into the Shikima realm that you halted!
Zenzo, of the Suzuka clan!
You?!
What?!
Hey!
Can you guys give me a hand up there?
Come on!
Get off!
Now do you understand our desires?
But why would ninja of this world...
...work for Taijuten of the lnjo realm?
A ninja girl like you cannot comprehend her glory.
Like us, she wishes to bury the Shikima realm.
Bury the Shikima realm...?
With those eyes shall you behold a living hell.
Behold the death of the Shikima king.
Behold the torment of your mother.
Behold the destruction of the Shikima realm. The home to which you will never return.
You will know the pain of loneliness!
Rather than die, you will live on as a humiliated ninja!
We will meet again, Miko!
After the Shikima realm dies with it's king!
Wait! You won't... get away with this!
M, Miko-chama!
lf l let this go, l'll never find her!
Nin-Nin!
Anyway, where the hell...?
lt doesn't look like the Shikima realm.
That's...
That must be the leader of the lnjo realm, Taijuten.
Mom, Fubuki, Midori, and Seiko must be around here somewhere.
Miko-chama!
Mother!
You okay, Nin-Nin?
Extremely okay.
Never mind. Private joke.
Mother!
Miko? ls that you?
Hold on and l'll get you loose.
Wait!
l can't be set free just yet.
Why? l came here to save you.
And to save Fubuki-san and my two friends from school, too.
l see, but Fubuki-san and the others will have to come first.
Mother!
l don't think they've spotted you. Now listen.
Right.
lf l disappear from this spot, the king, your father. He'll lose his only chance to survive.
You mean...
As long as l'm here, Taijuten will be careless.
l thought that was her.
You saw her. And her horrible bodiless existence.
ln the meantime, you have to find the Nyoin flower crystal.
Nyoin flower crystal?
Yes.
The crystallized love juices of 3000 virgins.
A sex flower that only grows in this realm.
To revive your father, the only way is to draw the source of his life out with its scent.
Father...
So, Taijuten's responsible for what's happened to him?
Yes. lf l'd just noticed it sooner...
The king, always so virile, had been tired for three days.
At first l thought it was Fubuki-san. Who with her young charms, had seduced him away from me.
But then l saw it.
Maria... Maria...
The one he called out for in his joy was me, not Fubuki-san.
And what he was having sex with was a bodiless charge of lightning.
Who are you?!
Seikima has fallen into my trap!
That form... You're Taijuten of the lnjo realm!
Taijuten's astral body had been draining the life from him.
Her astral body?
Wake up! Darling, wake up!
But then l was taken captive by Taijuten's mysterious servants.
Those half-machine monsters?
The remnants of the Suzuka clan.
l didn't know who they were.
Mother, l'll find that Nyoin flower crystal for you.
l know it'll be tough, but l will come back to save you.
Go to it, Miko. lf you don't succeed...
...it means the death of your father and all the Shikima realm.
Miko!!!
Get away from me!
Seiko! Midori!
That voice... ls that you, Taijuten?!
An admirable performance, holder of Shikima royal blood.
Miko Mido!
l commend you for penetrating my lnjo realm and staying alive.
You... How can you do this to them...
...when they have nothing to do with the Shikima or the Suzuka?!
The joy of ecstasy is the true source of all life.
So good...
They don't hate me for giving them such joy.
What are you talking about? That isn't even logical!
Not logic. The truth transcends flesh and thought!
What are you babbling about? Give me back my friends!
You still don't understand?
lf l give these bitches repetitive ecstasy...
...they will overcome their karma.
They begin to take pleasure...
...in transcending body and mind to become my servants!
Why?! You're the leader of the lnjo realm with the Suzuka clan...
...your servants. My friends haven't done anything wrong!
Your words reveal wisdom...
Fubuki-san! Where's Fubuki-san?!
You're worried about her?
Of course l am! l wouldn't abandon someone...
...who'd sacrifice themself for the Shikima realm!
Girl who carries the royal blood of the Shikima...
l shall reward your spirit though its frailties are all too clear.
Come with me!
What are you doing?!
lt stinks! Brush your teeth!
Where, where are you taking me?!
Miko!
What are you doing to Fubuki-san?!
lt's perfectly obvious.
We're turning this ninja girl to our purpose.
Fubuki-san? This place...? What is all this?!
l will tell you.
Of how the Suzuka left the Shikima realm in defeat...
...and of how we trained to fight the Shikima again.
And of how we came to serve Lady Taijuten.
We, the defeated remnants of the Suzuka...
...attacked a bio- electronics research lab.
As we began to reconstruct our bodies to fight the Shikima...
...we had to sacrifice many of our group to trial and error.
At last, we possessed the strongest physical forms possible.
A perfect union of metal and flesh.
A victory of biotechnology!
Damn you! Who's there?!
l am Taijuten of the lnjo realm.
Don't play us for fools! Are you a stray ninja?
A woman?
l may appear to be a woman to you...
...but l am a god whose existence is beyond either gender.
The concept of gender is not absolute throughout the cosmos!
Whatever you may babble, once we're done with you...
...you'll be a regular ninja girl whimpering with passion!
Now, let your body taste the feel of our metal!
So, do you feel it?
Taste our metal to the depths of your womb!
Sex craft at this ultimate level l possess, can be one of the forces in the Shikima realm.
Look at her. She drips and drips with passion but still she babbles on!
Kinembo, what's wrong?
My arm's being pulled in!
Kinembo!
Now do you understand?
He passed through my labia into the universe of carnal defilement that is a part of me.
He has gone to the lnjo realm.
l don't believe it.
l am Taijuten of the lnjo realm!
Please! You'll destroy the Suzuka clan this way!
l'll do what you want, just return my men to me!
Do you agree to serve me?
Yes, Lady Taijuten!
Then you may come as well.
l give this place to you.
You are from here on my servants.
lnjo warriors dedicated to destroying the Shikima realm!
My lady Taijuten, Buddha made flesh.
For the destruction of the Shikima realm, we will serve without any complaint.
And you threw away your pride as ninjas!
Silence! We wish only for the destruction of the Shikima realm!
You cannot know how little pride matters to the defeated!
Why... Why are you doing this to Fubuki-san?
So that she will make the Shikima king breathe his last breath!
What?!
He has already fallen into Lady Taijuten's trap.
She's stolen Seikima's vitality so he cannot move.
We're reconstructing this girl so she'll have a stronger vessel.
What?! And then?
When her ninja-trained labia climaxes...
...the reconstructed area will devour Seikima's manhood.
You coward!
Fubuki-san!
M, Miko-chan... All my fault...
Seiko! Midori!
Let them go! They can't handle this like Fubuki-san can!
You wish to save them?
Of course! lt isn't fair for them to get caught in this...
...when they've got nothing to do with the Shikima realm!
You think you're a living Buddha? You're a coward!
Then you agree to take their place to see if your body can survive the raging stream of carnality?
lf l do... Will you let them go if l do?
You're going to rip them apart and kill them!
Taijuten!
- Oh, yes!
- Help us!
lf you can survive the ordeal.
- Guess l have no choice.
- Very well!
Where am l?
And why am l wearing this?!
So, little bitch. You've come.
Huh? Are you talking to me?
You see anyone else here? Everyone's been waiting for you.
''Everyone...?''
Rape her! Rape her!
Do it! Do it!
Oh, shit! This is a sex show!
That must be...
l did it, Miko-chama...
Little bitch!
Kneel at your queen's feet.
What an ill-mannered girl you are.
Now beg for your queen's forgiveness!
No!
Let's see if we can't get your body to answer for us.
l'll give you something you want.
You wouldn't!
- Do it! Do it!
- Let both her holes feel it!
Your body's much more honest than your mind.
Your nipples are so hard.
Now then, how about down here?
Oh, do l feel some piss coming?
No!
Stop it!
Taste your eternal humiliation.
You devil!
Give me a better look. Give us all a better look!
How long does this humiliation last?
Maria-sama, l'm worried about Miko-chama.
She's probably been taken to that shrine.
l just saw Taijuten's light head over there.
Miko-chama...
Maria-sama!
You are now my servant. Take us to that shrine!
Ah, it works.
Let us be off! To the Shikima realm!
To witness the death of King Seikima!
To the Shikima realm!
Maria-sama, where's Miko-chama?
Mi-Ki-Maun-Ken On-ln Kai-Un-Hatta
Where is Miko?
Miko...
Miko-chama!
She's suffering the Trial of Humiliation.
lt feels like she's digging into me!
Well, doesn't it feel good? Speak the truth!
lf it feels good, then cry out loud!
Do you think l've fallen into your trap?!
No matter what my body does... l want Seiko and Midori back!
What?
They all turned to stone.
ls this an illusion? Or is it real?
Where...? l'm back in the lnjo lab.
So, you've returned, Miko.
Mother!
Nin-Nin, Midori, Seiko... You're all right!
All thanks to Nin-Nin.
While you were in Taijuten's hell of humiliation...
...Nin-Nin found the Nyoin flower crystal...
...and freed me from that mountain peak.
Way to go, Nin-Nin!
But if it wasn't for Maria-sama, you wouldn't have gotten back.
Thanks a lot, Mother.
Taijuten's left lnjo unattended. l am a Miroku ninja, after all.
l simply located you and called you back.
ln any case, we have to get back to the Shikima realm.
Now that you mention it, where's Fubuki-san?
And those Suzuka cyborgs?
They took Fubuki-san with them.
Oh, no! They're gonna use Fubuki-san's new, improved love machine...
...to snip off Dad's... The king's thing!
No, Miko! lf that's true, then this realm will be...
...destroyed with the Shikima realm.
What'll we do?
ls there any way to the Shikima realm from here?
This world exists within Taijuten herself.
lf we want to go back home...
...we'll have to use her desire for us to be there to do it!
Tight...
Can't take it... This feeling...!
Now let yourself and the king reach your climax!
When you reach the limits of joy, you will belong to the lnjo realm!
- Taijuten! You coward!
- That voice?!
You're scared! So scared you've locked me in the lnjo realm!
lt seems you escaped my Trial of Humiliation...
...but what you say is ridiculous.
Your ability to project your astral body's a good way to cheat!
You're afraid to face me in a real fight!
Conceited bitch! Come forth!
Darling!
What have they done to Fubuki-chan?
Fubuki-san, stop it!
Useless! She is controlled by my will.
Miko! Maria! Look clearly!
At Seikima's hour of death!
At the destruction of the Shikima realm!
Father!
Miko-chama!
At least... At least let me kiss my father goodbye!
How touching, Miko.
You finally accept that you are helpless before my power?
l don't like it, but l'll accept it.
Then grieve at his side. Go.
A kiss to Seikima, before he finally meets his end.
Your Highness... Father... Goodbye.
What have you done, Miko?!
Damn you!
You'll pay for this!
Taijuten of the lnjo realm?!
Eh, let me go!
Fubuki!
Fubuki-san, wake up! You're a Shikima!
No matter what they've done to you...
...you're still a Shikima, with the same blood flowing...
...through your body. No, through your heart that l have!
Fool! You think you can turn her back to normal with words?
Fubuki-san!
Shikima... Shikima...
Fu, Fubuki-chan!
Shikima! l am a Shikima! A Shikima!
Damn you all! Kill them!
Warriors of the lnjo realm, l command you!
Lady Taijuten!
l'm through with playing nice! Come and get me!
They aren't just holograms like last time.
When she brought us here, she brought everything in lnjo here as well.
Taijuten's power is valid only in lnjo.
Her mistake was to bring it here to the Shikima realm.
Curse you! Take this!
Miko! Miko-chama!
You strike at me when you don't know if you can win?!
Wait!
What are you doing?!
Miko, now! Use your powers!
l call upon the powers of my half-demon blood!
Blue Whirlwind Attack!
What are you doing?!
Taijuten, who claims to be beyond gender?
Don't make me laugh! l'll show you your true female nature!
Taijuten... Beyond gender and ruler of a great realm...
When your desires are captured, your soul degenerates!
You return to your true female nature!
Taijuten's face!
The ugly heart that would rule the whole world is revealed!
Damn you!
Darling.
She was pretty strong, wasn't she?
Yeah, but what about Fubuki-san?
There she is!
Are you all right, Fubuki-san?
Just more valuable training for me!
Man, l really have to admire your drive to improve.