Nurse's Office
In case of fire, notify Ryoko Mamiya
I'm sorry to be such a pain, Ms. Mamiya.
As a coach, it's hard for me to go
long without hurting myself again.
I'm more concerned with something else, Mr. Oota.
I thought you gave up smoking?
Well... It's just that I find it relaxing to flick my lighter.
Well that about takes care of that.
Ms. Mamiya!
No!
Please!
stop!
Ms. Mamiya, I've been waiting for this for a long time.
Come on, let me see.
Let me see how that pretty face
contorts as you struggle in terror.
Well, look at this, Ms. Mamiya.
Ryoko, you're already hot and wet for me, aren't you?
No! I'm not!
What was that?
I couldn't hear you over the slurping
sounds from your hot, wet slit.
You're really quite a whore, aren't you?
It feels so good to be inside you,
Ms. Mamiya.
Come on, put some effort into it.
Wiggle that lovely ass of yours some more.
Faster!
Yeah, that's better.
Now you've got the rhythm!
How do you like it? You'll soon
become addicted to the way I fuck!
You are already my slave!
What's so funny?
Oh, I just find that terribly amusing since...
You are now MY slave!
What?!
So, it would ap pear that you've finally awoken, Oota.
Don't you dare touch me with your filthy hands!
Oota, you have now become my slave.
From now on, you will obey any order that I give you.
Do you understand?
That's a good boy.
And since today's a special day, I'll let you lick my legs.
Come on.
With Oota under my spell,
I will be able to gather your new
friends more quickly than anticipated.
You'll be a good baby until then, won't you?
Angel of Darkness 4
It was over one hundred years ago
when Dmitrii Mendeleev the
famous chemist of Tsarist Russia,
first developed the periodic table of the elements.
Mendeleev also predicted the existence of elements that were,
as of that time, still undiscovered.
It hasn't been long since I received
my temporary teacher's license.
My first position is as a lecturer at
a very famous private university.
It was here that I, Haruka Tachibana,
was to encounter that horrible nightmare once more.
Ms. Tachibana!
Are your classes over already?
Yes, Ms. Mizuki.
Ms. Mizuki, why are you dressed like that?
Oh, this?
The gymnastics studio is just around the corner.
I just slip this on whenever I need to slip out of there.
Ms. Mizuki!
Ms. Mizuki, hurry!
Everyone else is here already.
You're the only one who's not here!
Shame on you ! You shouldn't be
walking around dressed like that!
Sometimes I wonder if these girls
have any sense of moderation at all!
Ms. Tachibana, if you don't have any other plans,
why don't you come by and watch us practice?
Oh really? You don't mind?
That's Mai Akimoto, she's the university's star gymnast.
She really is something, isn't she?
She's in the final stages of preparing
for an upcoming competition.
I just wish she'd allow herself to be more glamorous.
Yes, I wish she'd follow your example, Ms. Tachibana.
What are you talking about,
Ms. Mizuki?
Wow, she's so beautiful.
Oh! So, that must be the new chemistry teacher.
Teacher! Teacher! What should we do, Ms. Mizuki?
Akimoto!
What's happened to her?
Mr. Oota?
It looks like she fainted from anemia.
Why don't we let her rest in the Nurse's Office?
I think she's been practicing a little too hard.
She should come around on her own in just a little bit.
Really? That's good to hear.
Come on, Ms. Mizuki.
Let's let Nurse Mamiya handle
this and get back to our business.
Yes, I agree.
I'll leave her in your hands.
Excuse us.
Mr. Oota, you were so kind to help out.
Don't be silly. I'm always happy to help you out, Ms Mizuki.
Oh, you flirt so well.
At least it ap pears that Ms.
Akimoto's condition wasn't serious!
Yes, but I'm sorry that you had to get involved in all of this.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Well, I've got to be leaving now!
Thank you for everything.
Goodbye, Mr. Oota.
By the way, Ms. Mizuki...
Yes?
There's something I need to discuss with you.
Could you come by the storeroom later?
Whatever for?
How do you feel?
What did I...
There's nothing to worry about.
You just got a little light headed.
Well, the best way to treat anemia
is by warming the victim with your own body, you see.
And just look at the wonderful body you have!
But...
You certainly have a body befitting a star gymnast.
Ms. Mamiya!
Oh, no!
Ms. Mamiya, please stop...
I beg you!
No, I can't...
Ms. Mizuki, what happened to Akimoto?
It's all right. It looks like it was nothing serious.
All right then, everyone, back to your practice.
Yes, Ma'am.
Mr. Oota?
Ah, Mr. Oota.
There you are.
Well, Mr. Oota?
What was this discussion we needed to have?
What? What do you think you're doing?
Someone, hel...
My, my, aren't we making a mess here?
Looks like I'll have to clean it up for you.
Hiromi, take a look at this.
Doesn't she look so delicious?
She's young and full of fresh juices.
I softened her up so it would be easy for you to drink.
Isn't that right, Mai?
There now, go and enjoy yourself, Hiromi.
You're such a mess, Ms Mizuki.
I thought repetitive, grinding motions were you specialty?
Oh, yeah...
You're nice and tight, my little Sayuri.
Oops, looks like you've got more drool on you.
This has worked out well, Oota.
Go on and let yourselves go.
I'll help you myself.
I've got something special for you two.
First, this one is for Ms. Mizuki.
Next, it's you turn, Mai.
Open wide.
That's good, both of you.
Enjoy sucking on these for a while.
Oh, Oota!
Can't you wait any longer, you bad boy?
Very well, come right in.
Oh yes, that's good Oota.
Do that some more!
Nurse's Office
In case of fire, notify Ryoko Mamiya
Good morning!
Did you do your homework?
A seed!
I see that you are nurturing a seed, Hiromi!
Don't worry. I understand.
Now is the time. You know what you have to do.
Yes!
We will now begin to experiment with
the chemical reactions of liquids.
Everyone, please be extra careful
when you're handling hydrochloric acid.
I'll start off with a demonstration.
Ouch!
Ms. Tachibana, are you all right?
I'm all right, really.
Are you sure about that?
Whatiwas doing there was a demonstration of what not to do!
I've got to go to the Nurse's Office
just sit tight until I get back.
Ms. Mamiya?
I guess she's not here.
Oh, well!
There! But I guess my class has left already.
Oh well, that's okay!
I don't believe it!
I thought all of those flowers were gone!
Hey, what say we go out and have
a little fun after practice today?
I've got a craving for a big mouthful of jello!
Say, why is the door to the storeroom open?
Hey, you're right.
I wonder why it's open?
Yuka, what's up?
Yuka!
What's wrong, you two?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Ms. Mizuki!
She's right, you two.
It isn't scary at all.
Actually, it feels wonderful!
Bye-bye! Let's go!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Mai, please stop!
What? Isn't it much bigger than your boyfriend?
No, stop!
Come on, shake that ass of yours some more!
Oh, it's such fun to have lots of friends to play with.
Looks like you're having quite a party here!
Well Hiromi, why don't we join in the fun as well?
Let me see...
Way back then...
I think it was this medicine...
You have to remember, Haruka!
I was able to kill Shimazaki back then.
I have to replicate that special liquid again.
I did it!
Get out of the way, Oota.
Be a good boy and keep an eye out for trouble.
Where?
Where is it?!
Where?!
I can't find it!
And what might you be looking for?
Ms. Mamiya!
Hello, Ms. Tachibana. What's wrong?
Actually, I need to know about the
flower that was in this room...
Flower? What are you talking about?
Would you be referring, by chance, to my dear Hiromi?
What? What happened?
Why are my clothes over there?
It would seem that you know something about the flower.
I know all about it.
That flower the lives off people,
off their hidden carnal desires!
That flower doesn't belong in our world.
That maybe how you feel about this flower.
But for me, it is the most precious thing on the planet.
What do you mean?
Do you want to know?
This flower is my lover.
Yes, the lover who meant everything to me.
The name of my lover was Hiromi Takabe.
She was a female student at this university.
We loved each other very deeply.
But it didn't last for long.
I was devastated by the loss of Hiromi.
That's when it happened.
Hiromi's shadow-self made itself known.
I planted that seed and nurtured it.
This flower is Hiromi.
No, that flower is...!
I see that you've just noticed.
That's...
Ms. Mizuki!
Ms. Akimoto!
Mr. Oota?
I'm going to breed more of Hiromi's shadow with these girls.
The plant grows by drinking girl's
juices. You know that, don't you?
Oh, my God...
Ms. Tachibana, you will help us as well.
You look delicious!
Let's all become good friends, shall we?
No!
All right everyone.
Let the fun begin!
Come in to me too.
Come in.
This is fun!
No!
No! Get off of me!
Oota, get out of the way.
Shut up!
Stop bothering me!
What was that?
I won't let you get away with this!
Hiromi...
Oota, you'll pay for what you did!
How dare you hurt my dear Hiromi?!
I'm going to kill you!
They all belong to me!
You're the one who's going to die.
No!
Why don't we get to know each other more intimatey?
I need to get that...
Ms. Akimoto!
Ms. Akimoto...
Push that flask to me.
Looks like that's that.
Ms. Akimoto, try harder!
Yes, you did it!
Oh, no!
Ms. Mizuki!
Yes, we did it!
What?!
Hi... Hiromi.
This is so much fun!
At last, it was all over.
Now the nightmare could finally end.
Hey, give me a hand! I need to
push the piano to where it belongs.
It's always the freshmen who get bossed around.
Heave-ho!
All done!
I wonder what this is?
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
Let's go home.
Okay!