Darn it, Nin-Nin!
l thought l felt you scoping out my ass!
No point trying to stop me.
l can't really help it when you're dressed like that!
l didn't put on fresh panties when
l threw the others in the wash!
That's why you're such a generous girl to work for!
Anyway, did you finish editing that tape?
Of course l did!
This is a tape of your sex craft in action.
All part of my duty to record your exploits...
...so you can study your sex craft later on.
Okay, let's start!
Oh, man, this is total porn!
You're too busy taping this stuff to ever help me!
But Miko-chama, the mistress said l'm supposed to back off...
...until you really need me, so you can develop your skills.
Oh, really?
And l suppose you don't enjoy doing it, right?
Oh, well... l know pursuing pleasure is fun and all...
But these are the hidden arts of the Miroku ninja women!
Now be quiet and watch this!
Jeez, you never answer me straight, do you?!
Oh, shit!
l was so wrapped up watching this, l forgot it's time for school!
Guess l'll have to get fancy today...
Miko-chama! N, No panties!
Well, it's more hygienic!
Miko Mido, a student at Himenoki Girl's Academy.
Heir to the Miroku clan female ninja.
A half demon who carries the blue blood of Seikima, king of the Shikima realm.
Born to the strange destiny of fighting her enemies with sex.
Also known as... La Blue Girl.
Morning, Principle!
Did l see...?
No, none of our girls would do that!
Heir to the Miroku ninja women, Miko Mido...
Quiet down, everyone.
l'd like to introduce a transfer student.
This is Kai Fubuki-san.
l'm Kai. How do you do?
l believe there's a space next to Mido-san.
She'll answer any questions you might have, right?
Of course!
Pleased to meet you.
The pleasure's all mine.
Uh, something wrong?
Oh no. Not at all.
What was that look all about?
Damn, she's fast! l have all that ninja training and she just stole the ball! Who is she?!
Not bad, Kai-san.
Oh, it was nothing.
Were you an athlete at your last school?
Not really.
Oh no?
Your height would indicate you wouldn't be very good but you have excellent moves.
Thank you.
But can you get past my defenses?
Who knows?
Shall we?
Sure.
Aoba-sensei's taking this seriously.
Can't keep up with her! l used to be a pro, but...!
lt'll never go in!
That was great!
Lucky shot. A pro couldn't have made it from that far.
Of course.
Looks like we're out of time. Thanks for the game, Sensei.
Aoba-sensei's majorly pissed.
Oh please, just for once let nothing weird be going on!
- You were so cool!
- You really blasted her!
That was great, seeing that stuck-up Aoba-sensei get hers!
Popular, aren't you?
Why that look again?
What did l do to make Kai-san hate me so much?
That smell!
We ninjas use it... The potion to rob someone of their will!
Oh no!
Who...?
You're a fine ninja to have detected my potion.
But this battle goes to me.
Your will is now mine.
And now to implant a key phrase that will lead to humiliation.
You will sleep and remember it well.
The key phrase is ''What time is it?''
When you hear those words, you'll become incredibly horny.
This pleasure l give, you will desire unconsciously.
ls that clear? The key phrase is ''What time is it?''
''Faculty Room''
Strange...
How could Fubuki have run rings around me like that?
l went to check if she was a sports star at her last school, but there're no records at all
No records of her transfer to this school.
Like she's a phantom student or something.
Maybe there was some dirty dealing, getting her in here...
"Aoba"
Kai-san?!
Yeah, a gym teacher would be in as good shape as you.
The door was locked! Where did you...?!
That was nothing for me to get through.
And what are you doing here, looking like that?!
Thought l'd give the man-hungry teacher a good time.
Who are you?!
Once l'm through with you, you won't go checking up on me again.
Are you insane?! Do you realize what you're doing?!
Yes, perfectly.
You're about to become my servant.
Stop it! Stop it please!
My little clitty's special, you know.
Just stroke it a bit...
Kai-san!
Well? Now you'll want nothing more than to help me.
But l... l'm a teacher!
Teachers are women, too.
And l know what women like. Don't l, Sensei?
l'm comming!!
You're mine, Sensei.
No more!
Man, it's a holiday but l have to go shopping by myself.
l want a steady boyfriend for a change!
Did you call, Miko-chama?!
l told you never to go out
in public dressed like that!
lt's okay! They think l'm a street performer.
Then perform or something! Sheesh!
Oh Miko-chama, you've got me all wrong...
You're cute.
Miko-chama!
Miko-chama!!
All he does is embarrass me.
Miss?
Miss, what time is it?
Huh? Now? Uh, it's...
What time is it?
What time is it? What time is it? What time is it?
- l feel...strange...
- You're strange all right.
l feel so horny!
That's awesome!
Would you look at her?
Ugh! Playing with herself out here!
Hurry, hurry somebody do me!
Do me! Do me!
What's going on?
Miko-chama?!
Right there on the street in front of everyone, you say?
Ma'am, this isn't anything to laugh about!
She's never done this before!
Somebody programmed her vessel to do this.
Programmed it? How?
A simple application of hypnosis.
The one who did it got the opportunity to light the fuse to her body's desires.
But Miko-chama's a ninja!
She wouldn't let someone get control of her like that!
The enemy is cautious.
Miko was careless.
Probably used a ninja potion to knock her out and program her.
But who's the enemy?
Another ninja girl. But not one of the Miroku clan.
Ma'am! That would be her ultimate enemy!
ln any case, this old woman will be here to mix you the antidotes you need.
Miko-chama, snap out of it.
Oh, my head still feels weird.
l'm glad the old woman's antidote cured me
but even after a good night's sleep, l still have a headache.
Miko!
You're in trouble!
No way!
Who could've... Who did this?!
Mido-san.
Okay everyone, get to class.
Come with me, Mido-san.
The school's never had such a scandal before.
They're going to want a nice, tidy explanation for all this.
The school's chairman would likely demand that you drop out.
But the principle has agreed to let me handle this.
Women to women, l want to know what really happened.
Sensei...
lt was a trap!
l'd never act like a sex-crazed maniac like that!
Then explain it to me.
You see, l'm the heir to a centuries old ninja clan.
This was all a trap set for me by an enemy ninja.
A ninja? Do you think l'm some sort of idiot?!
lt's the truth! Believe me!
l'm the heir to the ninja of the Miroku clan!
l suppose you can prove this somehow?
Like perhaps a scroll that shows your family line?
l have one. l'm not supposed to show it to anyone...
But if it'll prove l'm innocent. lf it'll make you believe me.
All right. l'll come to your place tonight.
lf you show me the scroll, l'll believe you.
lf you're telling the truth, then perhaps l can protect you.
Thank you, Sensei!
Well done, Sensei.
Kai-san
And here's your reward, as promised.
My, you certainly get turned on quick
when you haven't had a man for a while.
Miko Mido can also pull off a Nyoninboh attack.
But l won't be beaten!
We'll see who really is the greatest of the ninja women!
l'll show you the scroll, like l promised.
But my being a ninja is supposed to be a secret!
Please don't tell anyone.
All right, but who'd believe ninja still exist even today?
Who are you?!
Give back that scroll!
You've served your purpose, Sensei.
Sensei! You mean you...?!
Wait Sensei!
Fight back! Where's all that ninja skill of yours?
What clan are you from?
l can't say. l've surpassed every school of Ninjitsu!
What the hell?! Something's happening up there!
Now is the time the Miroku blood line comes to an end.
Very sloppy, Miko Mido!
Miko-chama!
Nin-Nin!
Kai-san! You?!
lf he hadn't interfered...!
But why? Why attack me?!
Because l can't stand the monopoly of the ninja arts based on family bloodline!
Someone with real talent has to take their place at the top!
And l've gotten this far on my talent alone!
Kai-san!
Miko Mido! We'll finish this yet!
Wait, the scroll! Give me back that scroll!
lf we don't get that thing back...
At last, l possess the secrets of the Miroku clan!
Their alliance with the Shikima has made them invincible.
lf l had the Shikimas' power...
...l could master any sex craft or spell craft l wanted to!
lf l can gain control of them...
...l will have reached the heights of power in the ninja world.
To enter the Shikima realm...
...l have to drink the sperm of a young virgin, eh?
Oh, l can't take it!
Hi!
Who are you?
Just shut up and l'll make you come.
Or would you like me to stop?
Oh no. Be my guest.
Oh, yes! This is great!
Now turn to the north and let my fingers satisfy my desires.
And chant the name of the Shikima as l do it...
Shikima! Shikima! Shikima! Shikima! Shikima!
l'm comming!
This is the path to the Shikima world!
l've done it! l've done it!
Hey doll, are you a human? How'd you get in here?
l have come to take control of you all!
Watch what you say!
Baby, are you nuts?
Underestimate me at your own risk, pal.
l smell a human girl!
Wha-hah! A girl!
A girl!
A human girl!
Wha-huh?
Oh, one of them hard-boiled gals, huh?
Well, right back at you, doll!
Wha-hah! You'll be feeling fine in a second, baby!
What are you doing?!
There's no record of her.
She's certainly covered her trail well.
Just snuck into the school out of nowhere.
Yeah, l realized that.
Considering how she got control of Aoba-sensei, too.
l dunno. How do we get the scroll back...
...without even an address to start looking at?
Oh, grandma would be so ashamed of me!
Stop... not any more...
What happened to all that spirit?
Well, you're certainly pumping out the love juice!
Did you come? l guess you humans...
...really can't take us Shikima after all.
lf you think l'm a regular human, you'll get burned.
What?
You think l'd sneak into the Shikima realm without a plan?
What?! l'm burning up!
When l came, l released a powerful acid from my uterus.
My dick!
Glad l went in anal style.
Of course! That's what l would do!
Why didn't l figure something so simple out before?
She wants to be the greatest ninja of all time.
Whatever she does, she'll have to challenge the Shikima world.
Here Miko-chama, your special potion's ready.
Thanks.
l just can't drink some virgin guy's stuff.
Fubuki must have followed the scroll's instructions...
...and drunk the sperm of a virgin and then masturbated.
You know, if you need essence of virgin, l'm always here for you.
Don't be stupid! Get ready, Nin-Nin!
Right!
Man, my heart's really racing.
My crotch knows how you feel.
The secret to control of the ninja, of the entire world...
lt lies somewhere here in the Shikima realm.
The secret that binds the Miroku and the Shikima.
When l discover it, l'll take Miko Mido's place.
l will be the leader of all ninja!
Maria!!
Wonderful!
Darling, you're wonderful!
Holy shit!
She can fit that huge thing inside of her?
That must be the Shikima king and his queen.
Lets rest for now.
Oh no. l'm still ready for more.
You'll be that much better tomorrow if we save it.
Maria, please.
Tomorrow. l need a little rest for now. Good night.
Little tease...
You're a human girl.
Why did you gain passage into the Shikima realm?
To be with you, Your Majesty!
What?
Your queen looks like she's human.
l may only be a human girl, but there's nothing l can't do.
Wow! lt got that big so fast!
l've trained myself pretty well, but still...
You may be a human like Maria, but she's different.
You think you can be my bed partner, eh?
Either l can or l can't.
But if l can do it, will you hear my wishes?
Gotta relax my body. Can't overdo it now.
So tight!
lt's in! l got it all in!
This girl... Where did she get such a well developed vessel?
Your Majesty! Let me be your lover!
Call me... Call me Fubuki!
Feels like it's going into my insides...
But it feels wonderful!
This girl... She's special.
l didn't think a normal human girl could accept me into her.
Who is she?!
l'm going to come!
That voice!
That's the king, isn't it, Miko-chama?
But what about that woman's voice? Mother?
No... l think that was...!
No way! Kai-san?!
You were quite impressive. Are you tired?
l'm young, Your Majesty.
Unlike the queen, l can do it as many times as you like.
My, my... Confident, aren't we?
Kai-san, return that scroll you stole from me!
Miko?
Your Majesty, this girl stole my family's scroll...
...and used it to sneak in here!
lf you want it back, then you'll have to fight me in front of the king!
Say what?! Just how arrogant can someone be?
We'll have a one-on-one battle and let the king decide who the best ninja really is!
l see. You're challenging Miko?
Ever since l was little, l've wanted to be a ninja.
l read every book and manuscript l could find...
...and learned of the world of sex craft.
And then l learned of the leading ninja clan, the Miroku!
And of Miko Mido!
And so l trained myself so l wouldn't lose.
You are no match for me now!
Nice speech. Now shut up.
Come and get me, you... Ninjitsu fan-girl!
Miko-chama, you're so cool!
You've fallen for my traps at every turn.
Don't talk like that just because the king is here!
Miko-chama!
What's wrong? Can't defend yourself?!
l never was very good at hand-to-hand fighting!
l'll finish you off!
All right! Blinded her with a Milk Strike!
Two can play at that!
Seems we have a stalemate.
My victory is quite close.
Damn her, she disguised herself!
Once l've got you from behind, you can't escape my Nyoninboh!
You can do it too?!
Don't be so conceited! Did you think it was your private little secret?
Oh man, l've never seen a double Nyoninboh duel before!
Now you'll taste the Mido family secret arts!
What?
What's with the hair?
l make it harder than steel...
...then use it to pierce your hidden pleasure points!
My body's...burning up...!
My body is burning all over.
l'm piercing the hidden erotic...
...pleasure points in your body's depths.
Condemning you to the 4000-year-old Chinese Hell of Womens' Pain.
lf l make one mistake, pleasure can turn to nerve destroying pain and send you to hell.
Here come some more!
The final point is 2mm above the clitoris.
The most sensitive point on any woman!
Stop it!
Now, if we pluck them, your pleasure points resonate.
Writhe in the agony of ecstasy!
No!!
Looks like you came.
l underestimated you. Miko Mido... l lost.
My skills were no match.
Mother!
Well done, Miko.
l haven't seen a good ninja battle in a long time.
And although you did lose, you fought well, Kai-san.
You've mastered everything to the limits of conventional ninjitsu.
You may even be at my level, soon.
Uh, are you saying Miko's...?
She carries my own blue blood as well as that of the Miroku clan.
She appears human, but is in fact half-demon.
l really doubted you could beat her.
What! She's your daughter?!
- You didn't know?!
- No, not really...
For crying out loud! You were just some reckless idiot?!
Exactly.
l regret she is a mere human.
Dear?
Why don't l give you what you desire most of all?
The blood of the Shikima.
You mean it?!
The ceremony of blue blood!
We shall make you a creature of the Shikima realm.
A Shikima, with powers beyond those of mere humans!
She looks stronger than any other Shikima!
Kai-san... Wow!
Can l turn myself back to normal?
Of course. Breathe out from just below your naval and concentrate.
l did it! l've got Shikima blood now!
Man, she's weird.
Most people would feel creepy about it!
Gotta hand it to her, getting this far.
Miko-chan, l think you and l should be closer now.
l mean, we're practically relatives!
Does it mean that?
Let's be friends from now on.
After putting me down all the time?
You change personalities a little too easily!
So?
Well... Yeah, l'd like to be your friend.
All right!
Yeah!
l saw all the way inside!
Nin-Nin, would you cool it?!
Miko-chama, forgive me! l didn't look inside you!
Can't breathe!