Oh, my dear... Oh, honey.
I'm coming!
Explosion!
Oh, my God!
Look, shooting stars, two of them!
We see them all the time.
No. You have to make a wish.
In Europe they say they're bad omens.
Besides, what would you wish for?
I'd wish for a girl.
Are you serious?
Just kidding.
Bad joke!
You need to be punished!
No! Not here!
No.
Of course I was surprised.
It's on the news there, too?
I never imagined
one would hit so close to home.
You called me because you were worried?
That's so nice of you.
It'd be even nicer if you'd come over.
No. Don't worry about that.
It's been a month.
I miss you so much.
I don't even go out with other guys...
...'cause I'm thinking about you.
Listen, I think about you
and my heart throbs.
And I'm so wet down there.
Are you getting excited?
Are you getting hard?
Give it to me. Hurry!
Police Science Laboratory
A life form?
Did you say you found a life form
from that meteorite?
bother you, Mr. Sugo.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have dared
They recently discovered
organic elements in Martian rocks...
Are there more obvious traces of life?
Traces? It's alive!
It's alive?
Multiplying, to be exact.
At a tremendous speed.
It's a single-cell organism, like an amoeba.
Would it have any effect on us?
Like a new virus?
I wouldn't like to rush to a conclusion.
No need to worry about
contagious disease.
But what?
Call it a scientist's intuition...
beyond our comprehension.
...this one may be
I feel we need to act quickly.
I see. I'll talk to the Prime Minister
and put together a response team.
Ms. Tsukuba, this is a top secret.
I want a gag order within the Police Lab.
Yes, sir.
Shibuya Center Promenade
Not even acid can kilt it.
Too late.
- What's going on?
- What happened?
Freeze this sample
and the tentacle immediately!
Yes, sir
A gruesome murder
in a Shibuya alleyway...
...around 7:00 pm tonight.
What gives? No action tonight.
Watch out!
Quit fucking around.
You can't fall asleep like that.
We'll take care of you.
We're so lucky.
As Mr. Sugo's report mentioned...
is moving south...
...this gruesome murder spree
Utsunomiya, Tokyo, Yokohama...
...first in Hokkaido, then Sendai,
...as if it had a will of its own.
First, an autopsy report on Ms. Tsukuba...
...who died while...
...studying the meteor at the Police Lab.
head of Tokyo P.D. Forensics.
My name is Suzuka,
With assistance from the Hokkaido police
we've concluded...
...that the meteor,
the recent murder spree...
...and Ms. Tsukuba 's murder...
...are all connected.
- Impossible.
What?
Each murder victim...
...including Ms. Tsukuba was raped.
We found what appears to be semen
in the victims' uteruses...
...and to our surprise...
...the tests show that the samples
share the same DNA structure.
You mean there's just one perp?
That is impossible, if you consider...
Mrs. Tsukuba and the others...
...when and where
...were murdered.
It would seem impossible. And yet...
What?
The DNA of the perp's semen...
...doesn't match anything known to Man.
What?
It's unbelievable, but...
...the semen found in the victims
does not exist on Earth.
All the tests:
The organism from the meteorite...
and Ms. Tsukuba's data...
...the DNA in the murder victims,
...all show the same results!
It's a single-cell organism, like an amoeba.
It can't be!
Contact with outer space!
It must be "beyond our comprehension,"
as Ms. Tsukuba said.
- Chief!
Yes, sir!
Bring in Tokyo P.D.'s finest men...
...and increase security where
you might expect more murders.
Yes, sir.
A new discovery.
chronological order of the murders...
We examined the evidence in
...and found that
the DNA was mutating itself.
and multiplies rapidly.
This thing assimilates other organisms
It has an explosive life force.
Due to this...
are still...
...the victims' reproductive organs
...alive!
What do you say?
of the semen keeps them alive.
The explosive life force
I can't believe it.
My guess is...
it's seeking surrogates.
Surrogates?
It can't reproduce on its own, so...
for gestation.
...it plants its eggs in other species
This is urgent.
the murder spree is spreading south...
From Hokkaido,
...even to the Police Lab.
You say it was a fatal mistake
to bring the meteor to Tokyo?
Even worse, the meteor is alive.
The source of the semen is alive.
The meteor is an alien life form.
It metamorphoses,
and absorbs female life force to grow.
The alien offspring resides
inside the women's womb.
It's a horrific invasion.
What if all the women in Japan,
in the world are raped by it...
What would happen?
women will be impregnated.
Men will be killed and
Say they hatch in a year...
...there would be two billion of them.
In the world?
No, in Japan alone.
The murders are centered in big cities.
This thing seems to respond to something
only women have.
Can it do that?
It's different from us humans.
These days we even have machines...
...that can identify people's gender
from their footsteps and body temperature.
If this thing can sense pheromones...
...no wonder it goes to large cities.
Call the National Guard chiefs of staff.
And call the Prime Minister.
I had no idea you were such a slut.
You're a real slut!
A slut?
Yes. I like this very much.
Really.
When we picked you up,
I thought you were fucked up.
Give me more.
You, too. Give it to me.
In here.
Hurry. Give me your hard one.
She wants it double.
Incredible!
Give me more! More!
Stick it in me all the way.
Give it to me.
I can't.
Come in my mouth.
Let's not waste.
I'll squeeze out the last drop.
What a nympho.
You're such a slut. Do you play around?
I've never had anyone this tight.
You've really got a tight ass.
What would you do with a loose ass?
You idiot.
Sluts are usually so loose...
...but your ass is top-notch.
We've been doing nothing but the nasty.
Where are you from?
Why don't you tell us?
There.
The air is too polluted here.
But way past that red star...
All right. You must have your reasons.
Stay with us as long as you want.
Worse comes to worst, we can sell her.
We'll be rich.
Hey, hey. It's too soon.
This isn't like porn.
Sure it is.
You've still got more.
Give me more and more.
I'll squeeze out the last of you.
The very last of you.
I got it.
As the Prime Minister, I authorize
the deployment of the National Guard.
Prior to the commencement
of the Operation...
...the Interior Secretary shall organize
civilian evacuation within a 20-mile radius.
The F.C.C. Shall notify the media
that no news coverage is allowed.
Yes. But...
an unprecedented event in human history...
This may be
to the entire world?
...how can I disclose such an operation
Thank you for joining our young elite team.
Don't let us down.
Yes, sir.
But is it really okay?
I don't know.
It's his idea.
Don't worry.
We have pheromones, it will come.
We have pheromones.
It will.
Repeat.
As of noon today...
of the National Guard.
the Cabinet announced deployment
The mission's objective
has not been disclosed, but...
of the freeways have been ordered...
...civilians living within six miles
...to evacuate Tokyo, Kanagawa, Gunma.
Opposition parties have lodged
protests against...
...the National Guard's deployment.
Panic is spreading among the populace...
Mr. Mogi, why the media blackout?
It's the first time National Guard
has been deployed.
This is media control.
Because it's the first time. And...
And what?
It's something you just can't show.
I got it on the radar.
at 15 mph.
The subject is moving underground
Looks like it's going to come up
in Gotenba
It's here.
Mr. Suzuka, stand by.
They should be leaving Atsugi Base
about now.
This is  Man P Spot.
Hello, Iwahata.
and you're still playing around?
The world is going crazy,
You never get tired.
What? No girls around?
That's right. I came for research, but...
...massage parlors, brothels...
...there are no girls anywhere.
Maybe a police raid?
No way. I thought about that, too, but...
Shinjuku, Ikebukuro, Gotanda.
No girls anywhere at all.
So I asked around and...
...I heard the Government bought them.
What?
The Police and National Guard bought up
all the sex industry ladies.
Hey. It can't be.
Police, maybe.
But why the National Guard?
I don't know.
But it smells like a conspiracy.
My source was terrified...
...and tried to talk me out of looking into it.
I see. I have contacts in that field.
I'll look into it.
Thanks, Boss.
Be careful with your research.
This may be connected to
the National Guard deployment.
Public Relations, please.
Hello? National Guard
safe keeper of national security.
This is the National Guard,
We regret to inform you that our
telephone service is closed for the night.
Any questions about
the Guard and the Constitution...
civilian traffic on...
The National Guard has banned
...Chu-Oh Freeway,
Tomei-Odawara-Atsugi Freeway...
the Saisho Bypass
and all other public roads.
We have no details since the media
are not allowed access to the area.
is considering legal action.
The National Broadcaster Association
It smells.
We sprayed artificial pheromone
but it has no taste or smell.
Perfume?
It's the perfume.
and it smells like feces.
You mix different natural perfumes,
Artificial ones don't smell like this.
They make money with their bodies.
They invest in them handsomely.
But this is unbearable.
You can't say that. If things go wrong...
this operation's sacrificiai lambs.
...these girls will be
But you don't mean...
We should be able to see the effect now.
What's wrong?
Pheromones were originally
used by males to attract females.
A little known fact is that
females of certain species...
...release substances to arouse their males.
We can call it anti-pheromone.
Turns out we humans do as well.
That's all.
That's all?
We will attract the monster
but it turns out..
it comes with a side effect.
This is side effect? No way!
I said sacrificial lambs.
These girls need to work hard
or the whole operation will be a bust.
You are...
You may think I'm cruel,
but there's no other way to stop it.
And you, Mr. Okayama.
In your present condition...
...nothing you say will sway me.
These are the Empire of Japan's Warriors?
This is so sad.
What an archaic thing/ to say.
It'd be healthier
if you were honest to yourself.
Maybe, but how come you're not affected?
I am no good.
Nothing works for me.
I'm sorry.
Chief, come on.
Ms. Takahashi! You, too?
No reading on the subject.
What's wrong? It's here?
No, not yet, sir.
You're so good.
What's good?
the direction of Northeast 2:00!
Life form reading,
Northeast 2:00? How far?
How far?
How far? Right there!
Right over there! I'm coming!
Poor girls.
Mr. Suzuka, is this really okay?
Yes, fine.
Its aim is to pump semen into
as many female bodies are possible.
In Nature, animals ejaculate and die.
The answer is simple.
When it's spent, we win!
It's virile
It shows no sign of going soft.
It can't be
Its body mass is 13,000 times ours.
Human ejaculate is 3 cc a pop.
It should go soft after 39 liters.
Did you forget it's growing daily?
It absorbs life force and grows.
It does not go soft after this little sex.
My shortcoming
My, ljfe as a scientists is undone
by 32 years of virginity...
... at this crucial moment.
Don't be philosophical!
No! No civilians allowed.
You, Seedian of the Fourth Planet.
It is illegal to visit Earth
Heaven may forgive you...
but I from the Joint Galaxy Vice Patrol
will notl
I was not expecting you
on such a remote planet.
But females of this planet...
...already carry my seed.
You came too late.
I don't know about that.
You may not be aware, but...
...your DNA
is fatally different from humans'.
What?
Your sperm and an earthling egg
may unite, but...
...at a certain point in the cell division,
a red eruption will develop.
It will survive only three minutes on Earth!
That's stupid!
You're stupid!
Even so...
...I will keep planting my seed until I die.
I have nothing to lose.
I will defeat you before that!
This is like a monster movie.
Spare me.
It sounds nasty.
This sounds great.
This feels good, doesn't it?
Not so hard.
Finish!
Come on, come for me.
I'm coming.
I can't help it.
- I'm coming!
- Ecstasy!
I came.
Sorry about the trouble.
Thanks for your help
So long.
She was not bad.
Why didn't you have a go at her?
Spare me.
There must be more monsters out there.
We have to build up a defense
against space invasion.
Any actual plans?
First, the National Capital Defense Weapon
Mega - Sex-Roid!
My, my...
I already have a name for it: Super Sex.
It will retaliate against
any aggression 10 000 fold...
Hey!
Wait for me. Don't leave me behind.