Oh, here l go! Hi, everyone!
How are things going?
l'm Miko Mido, usually just a...
...normal student at Himenoki Girls College.
But since l was born into the Miroku ninja clan...
...l've been raised as a ninja
girl and have had to fight...
...all these really weird monsters.
And considering how we fight
other ninja with sex...
...it's been nothing but
trouble for my sister and me.
And ol' Nin-Nin's usually no help at all!
But Miko-chama, that's not true!
Oh, you're here?
We get into some really dangerous situations!
But justice somehow triumphs in the end.
But the guys we're facing
this time are REALLY tough.
l'm worried.
Well, as full ninja, we'll have to do our best.
Let's go, Nin-Nin!
Coming! Time to follow Miko-chama, folks!
So, bring 'em all on, from
wherever they may come from!
Or something like that.
Regular girls get spring break off.
'Cept the ol' ninja girl here...
l have to just keep doing this...
...to stay in shape.
Wow! Way to go, Miko-chama!
l think that's a new record
for holding off her orgasm.
Nin-Nin, are you peeping again?!
Jeez, and l was just about to come...
Grandma, as l promised
my father, the Shikima king...
...and my mother, l'll go out
and be a traveling warrior.
Please watch over me from the other side.
But l don't know which way to go.
You once talked about going
to the secret Miroku clan village...
What's the deal?!
There's no wind or anything.
You aren't getting the mistress' signal, Miko-chan.
lt fell in the same direction twice.
Hey, you're right!
South by southwest, l'd say.
Meaning it's probably that way on an old map.
There's nothing that way on a newer map.
There must be some kind of secret village, surely.
l just don't like how only she gets to ride!
Are you a ninja or not? Don't be such a slacker!
Hold up, Nin-Nin. Rest here.
l notice you have a strange scent about you.
- Eep!
- Yow!!
l'd say your blood isn't the usual type, is it?
Er, umm, how...?
Then you could only be a demon half-breed,
with the blue blood of the Shikima.
Who the hell are you anyway?!
Yaku, though l go by other
names in the outside world.
You wouldn't by any chance be...
A ninja woman of the Miroku clan, just like you.
Of all the unbelievable luck...
You see, my nose is especially
sensitive to blood and sweat.
So, l'll bet you were masturbating
this morning, weren't you?
Oh no! This is so embarrassing!
l'm on my way to the supermarket in town.
Why don't you go on to the village ahead of me?
How... How did you know where l was headed?
An old woman had a vision yesterday that said...
...a ninja girl of our clan would come and visit.
l wonder if my grandma sent
a message from the other side?
Maybe. But would you like me to tell
you exactly how to get to the village?
Thanks.
No problem.
So, do you like completely undressing me
with your eyes, little ninja?
Who? Me?
l can smell the Bertholin glands in your little dick.
See ya.
Sure. My name's Miko Mido. Nice to meet you!
She's kinda fun. l think l'll like her a lot.
Didn't have to call me ''little ninja''...
Miko-chama, wait up!
Hello in there?
Um, is there anybody in there?
Miko-chama!
What the... Why...?
Miko-chama, what the hell...
Are you just gonna feel me up all day?!
You... Mido's granddaughter...
Hang on!
Hang in there!
You are the woman that Yaku-san said had the vision, aren't you?
Yes. From the Mido vessel came a premonition...
So it was Grandma, wasn't it?
But, what the hell could she have been...?!
God help us...
Kamiri... Wicked Kamiri.
She has stolen our village's...
...most valued treasure.
A prized sword that is called Zipang!
Kamiri? Zipang?
You must get it back!
The Miroku clan's prized treasure...
Join powers with Yaku's and get it back!
No, you can't die! You must hang on!
The wicked Kamiri has joined forces
with the renegade ninja Kugutsumen...
...to take revenge on the Miroku clan.
Hey! Hang on! You must hang on!
Miko-chama, do you think Yaku-chan's all right?
That's right!
l remember she said she was
going to go to the supermarket...
...but what if she went somewhere else instead?
Miko-chan! That's Yaku-chan's minibike!
Yaku-san! l'm glad we caught up with you!
Since l came into town to shop,
l figured l'd get my stuff...
...from my boarding house and take it back to the village.
School's now out, after all.
Something horrible has just happened in the village!
l'll never forgive her! Kamiri!
Kamiri, and Zipang, and Kugutsumen...
l heard so much of that stuff
that l just don't know what's what.
But lucky for you. lf you hadn't gone shopping...
Pure revenge. You see Kamiri came back
to take revenge on the entire Miroku clan.
Revenge...?
Listen now. lt was last winter...
...when the village was hit by a surprise
huge storm and buried in deep snow.
Yaku! What are you supposed to do
when your vessel closes from the cold?
A Miroku ninja who cannot warm up her own love juices...
...certainly cannot call her training complete!
Yes, ma'am!
As sex craft instructor for the village...
...Kamiri enjoyed unrivaled power.
A Suzuka spy! Grab him!
That night we heard that a Suzuka
spy had hidden himself among us.
That was Kugutsumen, right?
Right. Even we have heard of
''The Man of a Thousand Faces.''
He'd fully infiltrated the Miroku clan.
But Kamiri, being the great sex craft instructor...
...brought him to a climax and defeated him.
But while we all thought Kamiri had won...
...a drop of his sperm had made it inside of her...
...and he was actually controlling her.
She had become Kugutsumen's puppet.
Kamiri, l can't live without you.
Or l you.
l'll tell you the truth. l'm a renegade, driven out...
...by the Suzuka for crimes against them.
Go renegade with me, and we'll
take control of the ninja clans!
Take control?
Yes. You see, if we steal the treasure,
held by the village.
l know that the sword conceals great magical power.
lf we do that...
Together we'll be unstoppable.
Kugutsumen!
Kamiri!
You'll do no such thing!
Traitor Kamiri. Did you really think that...
...we couldn't see right through your heart's schemes?
Kamiri was punished, according to the Law.
That is the ninja's compassion.
Your evil schemes are punished,
but we will allow you to live.
The wound your vessel carries
will perhaps heal some day.
Now begone with you!
l kinda feel sort of sorry for her.
But we cannot forgive all the
blood she has spilled in revenge.
You're right! And do you have any idea...
...what kind of amazing power Zipang holds, Miko-chan?
The sword Zipang holds enough
magical power that Kamiri could...
...end the life of the Shikima king!
My dad's life?!
No way!
lf they kill him, they'll take
control of the Shikima world.
With that kind of power, they'd
rule the ninja clans as well.
What'll we do? We can't let them do it!
Don't worry. They may have Zipang...
...but they don't have the secret
to entering the Shikima world.
Do you understand?
Then...what...
They'll probably figure out that somehow you have...
...that particular power, Miko-chan.
But then, you have to figure, maybe they already have.
Miko-chan, this is major!
lf they're coming, then let 'em come!
That is the only way we will be
able to stop them before...
...anything can happen to the king. To my dad!
You're so inspiring, Miko-chan!
l will join you and together
we'll avenge the village elders!
And l'll do it to protect my father!
We are the Miroku ninja, after all!
We'll combine our strength and then beat Kamiri!
Hey, don't forget about me.
Of course, with Nin-Nin's help.
You betcha! "Little ninja".
What's wrong?
l wasn't undressing you with my eyes again!
A strong scent. Someone's there!
All l see is a dog.
Maybe it was my imagination...
My sense of smell gets a little haywire
when there's a full moon out.
A full moon you say?
People sometimes have embarassing
secrets they want to keep.
Damn that Yaku... Better not be careless.
What?!
Are you saying Miko Mido is sheltering Yaku?
lf we can get her to cooperate...
...then we can get access to the Shikima world.
But the other half of the problem is spilling the blood...
...of the Shikima king, Seikima.
And his power isn't to be trifled with.
You've yet to recover from the wounds of your punishment.
You better leave this one to me.
Don't slip up.
Yaku can be a tough opponent during a full moon.
Perhaps if you were to separate them...
Kamiri.
You've been talking even more
arrogantly since we got Zipang.
lt's as though l were her servant!
Perhaps she's being affected
by the power within Zipang...
And the panic which started last winter continues.
Yet another female student has been kidnapped.
The latest missing girl, Reiko Mikogami...
...left to visit some friends two nights ago, when--
What?! Oh, not Reiko?
- Friend of yours?
- Yes. A classmate.
According to elderly locals, the foothills in the area...
...have long been rumored to be a sort of...
...refuge for monstrous creatures.
Concern for the missing girls' safety remains high.
Jeez, it's hard to believe that in this day and age...
...that anyone could believe in the monster refuge.
lt really is an embarassment for the locals.
Yaku-san, this refuge of theirs...?
lt's about 20 km west of our village.
l have heard some say that a few fugitive warriors...
...discovered it a long time ago.
But later, the priests and
shamans started saying that...
...wounded monsters would revive there at midnight...
...so everyone stays away from it.
Anyone who thinks that you can blame these...
...disappearances on monsters is fooling themselves...
Don't you think so?
Yeah, but...
Well, l've actually met Shikima and demons and stuff.
They're not nonsense, believe me!
l see...
Yaku-san! Yaku-san, what's wrong?!
They're so big!
Twice as big as yours, Miko-chama! Just like l imagined!
Ooh, drippy, sloppy!
Yaku-san, what is it?
l told you, this happens when there's a full moon.
Make me come, please!
lf you don't then my body... My body...!
Yaku-chan's... Transforming!
Like this?
Yes! Yes!
l'm going to come!
Yaku-san!
Thanks, you saved me.
l think l need a shower.
Now l'll never be satisfied doing it alone.
That was indescribable!
Yes?
lt's Nishikie.
Uh, hold on just a second.
Nishikie-sensei?
Yes.
Have you heard of the missing Mikogami girl?
We think she was last seen in this area.
Tell me, did she visit you at all, by any chance?
No, and truthfully, l've been
so very worried about her...
ever since l heard about it on the news.
l see... She didn't come here.
l'd be more than happy to help look for Reiko.
Although l'm not really dressed for it at the moment.
Oh, l see. Well, l'll try someone else, then.
Sensei!
You're not Nishikie-sensei!
Kugutsumen!
l was so busy concealing my true scent...
...that l couldn't help but reveal my face to you!
Miko Mido! You will now show me
how to get into the Shikima world!
Who do you think you are, ordering me around!
Oh no!
Gotta concentrate... The lron Pube Blast...
Fight fare!
Like hell. Yaku's used up her sex power for the night.
Let her go, you dirty bastard!
She is my sex toy.
And she'll remain mine until you
give us access to the Shikima world!
Yaku-san...
Miko-chama, did l just miss something?
We'll search for that hideout, Nin-Nin.
l dunno. Monsters can be a real pain to fight.
What are you scared of?
They only come out at night.
And we have all day long to search.
But how do we know Yaku-chan's
in this monster refuge?
Nin-Nin, you've really gotta
learn to use your head.
Oh, now you're saying l'm stupid?
Let's not just get into that.
The thing is, Kamiri stole
Zipang but hasn't been seen yet...
...that's left Kugutsumen doing all the legwork.
l figure a woman who's had her
most important body part hurt...
...would go to this refuge place
to give it time to heal.
You're really smart, Miko-chama.
Just don't be so easily impressed.
However, with his beloved Kamiri's snatch still wounded...
...Kugutsumen can't have sex with
her whenever he wants it.
So what do you think a guy
who's starved for sex craft will do?
Well, uh... Try to get some young girls to use as an outlet?
You're right. That's why all those young students...
from the local town are missing.
You mean Kugutsumen's doing all that?!
Well that's what l think.
So if we find this refuge...
...we'll find Yaku-san and her classmates and rescue them.
-Just what l was thinking, too.
- Liar.
Miko-chama!
lt's somebody's panties!
lt isn't superstition or nonsense.
l'm sure that the monster refuge
is hiding something pretty big.
Let's find it before it gets dark.
Yeah.
We've searched and searched, and now it's dark.
Maybe l jumped to conclusions?
No sign of any monsters or of Yaku-san
and her friends around here.
Um, who are you?
l was raped in town, coming home from work.
Ahh...
l heard this place was good for healing wounds.
l was scared because of all the monster rumors...
...but l came anyway.
Oh, l see.
l heard you talking and l didn't want to come out.
l hope you two aren't monsters, are you?
Of course not.
That's not totally true, seeing
how l'm half demon and all...
But what about that strange little man?
Oh, him? He's only my little friend. Don't worry.
You're really Kamiri, aren't you?!
Yes, and l've trapped you in the spring of shame...
...with my water tentacle technique, Miko Mido!
Miko-chama!
You meddling little ninja fool!
But what happened to Yaku-san? Tell me!
Where have you taken her?
Don't worry, she's our special gift
for tonight's mystery guest.
And exactly what do you mean by ''a gift''?!
Yaku-san!
Calling to her is useless.
Your juicy friend Yaku is already
under our complete control.
You raped her, didn't you!
The only one who gets to
do that is our guest tonight.
You know how hard it is to have this
body in front of you and not do it?!
Kugutsumen's a bit horny from...
...not being able to have me for the last few months.
Liar! You've been snatching Yaku-san's classmates one by one...
...to try and satisfy your filthy desires!
You fool! lt has been the monsters all along...
..who have been responsible for taking
the girls out from their homes!
But why?!
For the purpose of summoning their elder chief.
Even now, you can smell the sex
that's been set loose in this pool.
lt calls to him.
Will you be consumed by the monsters' chief, like your poor Yaku?
Or will you take us to the Shikima world, you bitch?!
Never! l lose either way!
l came here to get the sword Zipang back!
You mean this?!
Zipang!
The secret to controlling the Shikima world!
The Miroku clan will never possess it again!
You filthy traitor!
Save your insults!
That's... Reiko Mikogami, the girl from the news.
Poor thing. She's been raped so
much she can barely think anymore.
Hey, check out the new girl.
A tasty-looker...
Give her to me!
Mine! Mine!
No! Keep away from me!
- Hurts...
- Stop it!
Can't breathe...
Well, Miko? Do what l ask, or
shall l let the monsters rape you?
No way! Who wants to get fucked
by a creepy monster?
- The boss!
- The boss is coming!
Miko, if you wish to experience the summit of terror...
...then keep on defying me.
But look at what you now face!
Yaku-san!
Fool! You think you've got a chance against us?!
Bay with pleasure! Weep! Cry out!
You there, girl! Look well!
When she reaches climax, l'll absorb her into me!
Absorb her?
Once that's done, she will
become part of my body!
My body will gain in strength.
Once l've absorbed the life from
her, her soul will be destroyed.
No way!
Look then, and see my joy!
The absorption begins! Her entire
body becomes like nectar.
lf l don't do something, Yaku-san's a goner!
Now then, it's your turn.
- What a scene this is!
- Don't look at me!
That twitching little rosebud
of yours is prime quality!
Now, we can either make this an exercise in terror...
...or you can be a good girl
who makes this good for me!
Hey, what the hell is happening?!
Kamiri!
The water l control with my sexual energy...
...is now drawing itself into
the monster's crucible of joy.
So, l guess it sort of looks like
you're trying to save me...
...but why don't l buy that?
Now you'll listen to me?
What's that?!
Kugutsumen is controlling the monster's body from within.
Kugutsumen?
This isn't like Yaku's being sucked in.
The monster's own body has been absorbed.
What now, Miko Mido?
Kugutsumen!
l now control the monster.
All so that l may absorb you!
And once he has accomplished that,
then your mind will be ours to control.
You will gladly take us to the Shikima world...
...so we can make our dreams come true.
Can you withstand such pain?
Now you may suffer on the boundaries
of agony and ecstasy!
There, let yourself feel it to your heart's content.
Once you've climaxed, the absorption begins.
Can't come... lf l lose...
Yaku-san will end up like her friends...
...and the Miroku ninja clan will die here.
You slimy piece of shit!
l don't want to waste my cum
on a stupid water demon like you!
Little punk ninja!
Trying to get me drunk with whiskey?!
Little shit!
Nin-Nin!
Miko-chama, the Alcoholic Shower technique!
Are you kidding?! l really hate that one!
No time to argue!
l guess if l have to and it'll save Yaku-san...
What are you jabbering about?
What the...? Her body's heating up.
Heating up?
She's trying to ignite the alcohol?!
She's striking sparks from her own mouth!
Damn, Miko.
She actually heated her body up
to the ignition point of alcohol.
As l thought. A tough opponent.
We haven't lost yet, though.
Not as long as we still hold on to Zipang!
Yaku-san!
Mi... Miko-chan...
You saved me. Thank you.
Of course. You're an irreplaceable partner now.
- Kamiri and Kugutsumen got away.
- l see...
Let's go together and see if we can find them!
Right. But don't forget, we must get Zipang back!
Guess it's true that water
demons can't take heat so well.
That was great work, Nin-Nin!
Aw heck, even l can use my head once in a while.
Here's your reward.
Miko and Nin-Nin's do-or-die combination came together...
...and Yaku was saved.
However, the goal of these three Miroku ninja is clear.
The recovery of the treasure sword, Zipang.
But what further sexual traps lie
in wait for them on their quest?
Nice view, here.
Nin-Nin! What do you think you're looking at?!