It was the late Taisho era.
Sanshiro Goda, who's been
struggling to enroll an art school in Ueno...
secretly fell in love with
Momoyo, the daughter of the household...
where he stayed as a servant.
However...
she had been engaged to Yoichiro,
the heir of the Furushiba conglomerate.
One day, Sanshiro
witnessed the secret love affair...
between Yoichiro
and Reiko, Momoyo's sister.
The next day, Reiko
was found murdered.
A message was left saying "I am
"the one who aims at the bride."
Will Momoyo be next?
As Sanshiro worried...
a mysterious
woman, Konago appeared.
She suspected that Yoichiro
was possessed by something...
and followed him with Sanshiro.
There they witnessed...
T-That's Miss Momoyo.
It's not a demon.
Miss Momoyo!
Don't be fooled.
Demons disguise themselves
as acquaintances to fool men.
What a strong evil aura!
Show me your true self!
It's strong...
That's not your true self either.
Stay right here.
Wait!
It feels good.
Now is the time for us to settle it.
What?
S-Sanshiro!
A-Are you alright?
K-Konago!
Sanshiro, what happened...
S-Stop it!
C-Cut it out, Sanshiro.
What's wrong with you?
Have you gone mad?
L-Let go of me!
Stop it!
What have I...
You awake?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
S-Sanshiro...
You did this for me?
You okay?
Yeah...
I failed to defeat it last night.
It was stronger than I imagined.
So wasn't it really Miss Momoyo?
No.
How about Mr. Yoichiro?
He might not be alive anymore.
What?
If you're worried about Momoyo...
you can go home.
But...
Thank you for your help.
Why...
this confusion?
Sanshiro, where have you been?
Miss Tamao!
Something terrible happened!
Mr. Yoichiro is dead.
He fell from the 12th
floor of the brothel.
From the 12th floor?
Yes.
The police officer came by earlier.
But strangely, they didn't
find a single drop of blood.
Just like Miss Reiko...
He died mysteriously...
How is Miss Momoyo?
She looks as if she's lost her soul.
She shut herself up in her room...
I see.
Was she in the
mansion all day yesterday?
Yes.
I see.
After that incident...
I just tried to focus on the painting...
with everything I had.
I wonder what happened the other day.
I felt as if I became
the beetle in the jar...
What are you doing?
W-What are you doing?
Thank you again for the other day.
Now that I'm here, I
want to see how you live.
Hey wait!
This is...
Miss Momoyo in a bridal dress.
Did you paint this?
Yes.
I feel something ghastly...
What's wrong, are you okay?
The wound from the other
day still hurts, but I'll be okay.
The demon's waiting for a chance.
He may try to kill you
and Momoyo this time.
Be careful.
Miss Momoyo, too?
I need some air.
I have to go, but be very careful.
Konago, why do you care about me?
Something from a previous life.
I cannot attack the demon
until he leaves the body...
he has possessed.
The question is when...
We've got a problem.
We can't find Miss Momoyo anywhere.
Have you seen her?
What?
N-No, I haven't.
It must be Master.
He's been drinking since the incident.
It's all over for this family.
Hey Sanshiro...
Why don't we just leave
this mansion together?
I can't leave Miss Momoyo.
You really love her.
Miss Momoyo...
I have to...
go to Manchu.
M-Manchu?
Sanshiro!
I don't want to go to Manchu.
But, I have to
follow my father's orders...
Nobody can oppose...
my father.
I had hoped that Mr. Yoichiro might...
Sanshiro, please...
Please help me.
I see.
Let's leave this mansion!
Really?
I heard that.
Tamao!
Don't worry.
I will help you guys.
Miss Tamao!
Thank you.
Wait, Sanshiro.
You almost forgot this.
I forgot something?
It's your dream, isn't it?
The wedding dress.
Thank you.
Well...
Let's go.
Yes.
Maybe I am too nice...
The prostitute at the brothel...
looked just like Miss Momoyo.
I don't care if she's a monster.
I don't care if I get killed!
What?
Huh?
Nothing...
Um...
Do you have any regrets?
No, I don't.
Because...
I have Sanshiro.
Really?
You bitch, you helped
Sanshiro escape, didn't you?
Taking advantage of my kindness...
Damn!
I will catch Sanshiro, I'll
use the army if I have to!
No, you won't.
You're too old fashioned.
Stop, what do you think you're...
I won't give Miss Momoyo to anybody.
I want her to be mine.
If I could...
I would trap her in a jar like the beetle.
Again...
I'll wait at the end of the tunnel.
Wait, the train isn't coming out!
Where did it go?
Miss Momoyo, you're so beautiful.
Sanshiro...
step up to this altar.
This is our wedding.
O-Our wedding?
Please, come forth.
Hurry up, now.
I'm not afraid anymore.
Even if I have to descend into hell.
You're such a pathetic man.
So pathetic that you
can't even tell her you love her...
You've created these twisted desires...
You were possessed, and you've
given your bride to the Sex Beast.
Sex Beast?
M-Mr. Yoichiro, it can't be!
I won't forgive Reiko
for insulting Momoyo...
or Yoichiro for taking
Momoyo away from me.
Momoyo is mine.
All mine.
W-What the...
Yes, I've been waiting for
this moment for a long time.
Miss Momoyo...
I wanted you because
you were out of my reach.
W-What are you talking about?
Someday, I will have you to
myself like the beetle in a jar.
And I'll fuck her.
That's a lie!
I will take the virginity of your bride.
Sanshiro...
if you really want me...
Stop it!
That's not me!
Miss Momoyo, run!
Sanshiro!
No!
Please, stop it...
Please...
Finally, you left your host
and showed your true self!
K-Konago, what the hell is this?
Your desires called
the beast to this world.
Set the seal!
What the...
I will confine you for sure this time!
The demon won't bother you anymore.
Did my desires really call that monster?
In truth, that was the demon
I failed to catch a long time ago.
He waited for centuries
to take revenge on me.
Sanshiro, you're my
distant relative, so he took...
advantage of your
desires and possessed you.
W-What?
I've fulfilled my duty.
But, there're still demons trying to
take advantage of human weaknesses...
so be careful.
Konago...