The overweight obscene teacher: Yamada Takashi. He is a middle aged teacher who is treated as a way of stress relief and is looked down on by everyone. But he doesn't let that get to him as he enjoys his days happily fucking a high school girl. The rapidly rising member of the parliament: Kashiwagi Yutaro. He's made Hatsune his lover and has quickly risen to the top as a new member of the parliament. Now she supports him as his wife with various services and secretarial duties. Even though they're busy, he still spares time to dote on Hatsune and teach her various things...
The cheeky model high school girl: Takai Shizuka. As the girl who took the modeling world by storm, she was a person to admire... but, she gained an incredibly persistent stalker who quickly exposed her frugal private life... But she has a strong mental fortitude and aimed to quickly get back on her feet. She's a very active and admirable, but cheeky high school girl.
The good luck charm, rich high school girl: Kashiwagi (Aoyama) Hatsune. She was married off for political reasons to her husband, Yutaro. But maybe it was destiny, because she had a knack for helping him and as a result, he shot up to the top. After that, she became his admirable number one partner despite being a rich girl, high schooler.
The two love birds, Yutaro and Hatsune-chan are on vacation, cruising around the seas. Wearing nothing but a micro bikini, Yutaro fucks Hatsune-chan all over the deck's pool. They were all alone... except for the secretary who sat in the boat, the light reflecting off her glasses... Hatsune-chan was already delighted to be his wife, but he had another piece of good news for her. He enrolled her in school so that she could resume her education. Hatsune-chan was overjoyed by the chance to make friends her age... Seeing her happy made him a little aggravated...
To relieve the stress of her every day life, the cheeky model, Hatsuka-chan, would have lots of sex... She released her stress by voicing her complaints to her manager while sticking his thing in her... One day: the daughter of a parliament member, Hatsune-chan appeared before Shizuka-chan... Sensing this meeting as destiny, Hatsuka-chan let her ambions get the better of her and set her sights like on him like a predator... She because friends with Hatsune-chan and was able to meet her father... But she was actually plotting to get some dirt on him... however...
Obscene Teacher 4 feat The Dirty Parliament Member
This is really embarrassing.
Why'd you make me wear this?
I hate you, Yutaro-san.
You look beautiful.
Hmph, you're incorrigible.
This is the last day you can take it easy.
You're starting school tomorrow, Hatsune.
I'm happy that I'll be able to make some friends my age.
Thank you very much, dear.
Whoa, it's peeking out.
W-We mustn't, Yutaro-san!
It's just us here.
What about your secretary?
No, we really shouldn't!
That's... Sensei!
You've gotta say my name.
Sorry. But calling you sensei is more...
This is so good.
No... Sensei's fingers are...
They're pinching my clitoris!
That's...
Your dick is on my pussy out in the open! We can't!
Your dick is inside my pussy!
Your big thing is...
It's so amazing! It's making me lose my mind!
No... Sensei, if this keeps going, I'm going to...
We're just getting started.
Your dick is too amazing!
It's even bigger than usual!
It's because you're too good, Hatsune.
I'm so happy that I make you feel that way, sensei!
I'll make you feel good with everything I have!
Sensei, your cum... it's so wonderful!
Sensei!
Thanks.
It's so manly, but also so cute.
I love your dick, sensei!
Sensei!
You have too much stamina!
You've had sex with me so much!
And from now on, you're going to be a dirty high school girl.
What? You're the dirty one, sensei.
You're an obscene teacher!
For god's sake... knock it off already!
You're the one who wanted this.
I didn't at all!
You really piss me off!
That was embarrassing, wasn't it?
Shut your mouth, you creep!
I was just experiencing how normal people live!
Do something about it, will you?!
Knowing when to give up is important.
Also, we're apparently getting a new transfer student.
What?! Why are you changing the subject?!
You fat obscene teacher!
So? Who's coming?
O-Oh, yeah, looks like some rich girl.
Pampered all her life, I'm sure.
She needs to know the harshness of lif...
You idiot! If anything happens to her, it'll be a huge scandal!
So, look after her, will you, Shizuka?
Huh?! Why should I... Don't call me by my first name!
Also, she's going to be in my class?!
Yeah. It'll be reassuring to have
the most popular student by her side.
W-Well, yeah, I guess she'd be lucky
to have me show her the ropes.
You're such a simpleton.
Huh?!
Come on! Hurry up and cum already!
I have a photo shoot after this!
You really just go at your own pace, huh?
Well, you're no better!
You just cum in my pussy whenever you want!
Your dick's too good, fatty!
The angle it's hitting my pussy at is amazing!
Oh god! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I bet the new girl's really pretty.
What are you fantasizing about?
Reality won't be so kind.
You know how much a person can change with makeup?
I bet she's nothing without it.
You don't have any dreams or ambitions, do you?
High school girls shouldn't have them,
you dirty, obscene, kiddie-fiddling teacher.
Obscene Teacher 4 feat The Dirty Parliament Member
Shizuka & Hatsune - The Cheeky Model and The Rich Girl
A pleasure to meet you.
My name is Kashiwagi Hatsune.
I will be in your care.
Y-You serious?
She looks like she's straight out of a painting.
She sure is beautiful.
I bet she's a virgin.
Good grief, you creep.
I'm Takai Shizuka. Nice to meet ya.
Call me Shizuka if you want.
Thank you very much, Shizuka-san.
I will be in your care.
This is the music room and here's the art room.
And you can have your lunch here in the cafeteria.
You really act differently in public, don't you?
What was that, fatty?
Keep your weird comments to yourself!
See? Like that.
Shut it. Look, you're scaring Kashiwagi-san.
I think it's wonderful how well you two get along.
But actually, he and I have a pretty deep
relation that goes past teacher and student.
"Deep relation?" Really?
Oh, it's not what you think!
I'm a model and he's my manager.
O-Oh, I see.
I made an assumption. My apologies.
I heard you were a rich girl.
I really expected you to be more arrogant.
Rich girl? My father's a member of the parliament, that's it.
Oh, you don't say...
I'd love to meet him.
It'd be great to meet the father of my friend.
I would love to introduce my friend to him as well.
If all goes well, my popularity's gonna skyrocket!
What?
Would it be better for me to
call you Papa in front of everyone?
Hey, don't tease me.
Your guests have arrived.
Hello. I'm Takai Shizuka.
Thank you for having me over today.
She has a much more spirited
feel to her compared to Hatsune.
Y-Yutaro-san, just where exactly
do you think you're looking?
Goodness gracious. That's my friend.
He's really staring.
Charming an old guy or two's no challenge for me at all.
Wow, this is fantastic!
This office and your father, I mean!
I thought all the members of
the parliament were more like geezers.
I'm so jealous that you have a wonderful
father like this, Hatsune-san!
You're Hatsune's friend.
You can come over any time you'd like.
Thanks so much!
Thanks for showing me around!
I'll be back again!
Yutaro-san, you were fawning over my friend
right in front of me. It was difficult to watch.
Oh, I've never seen you like this, Hatsune.
I knew sending you to school was a good idea.
You kept giving her dirty looks.
You're the only girl for me, Hatsune.
I don't believe you.
You're cute even when you pout.
Yutaro... Geez, Papa.
Your dick is even harder than usual!
The reason it's this hard is because of Shizuka-san, isn't it?
You're the only one for me, Hatsune.
You just keep trying to sweet talk me...
I'm going to make sure I thoroughly milk your dick.
Yutaro-san...
You came a lot...
Goodness. It's because of Shizuka-san, isn't it...
Yutaro-san?!
You just came, but you're still hard!
My pussy's totally filled by your dick!
Yutaro-san's cum is flooding the insides of my pussy!
Yutaro-san, I love you!
I never expected a big-shot like him to be like that!
Hey, stand there.
Hey...
Shh!
Good... oh my god!
I'm... in an elevator...
Your dick's in me!
I love it so much!
It's too good!
I'll keep it a secret!
Did you really go through with it?
Next time I go over, I'll make sure I sneak it back with me.
Poking around in people's private affairs is cute, isn't it?
Open up, Takai Shizuka.
I know you're in there!
Huh?
Huh? What? Huh?!
Hey!
Takai Shizuka, we're arresting you for treason!
Arrest Warrant
Takai Shizuka
And here I thought I'd made a good friend.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
There goes my easy life.
She committed a crime. We can't go easy on her.
I understand that, but...
This has everything to do with her punishment.
She's waiting, so... Listen!
Yutaro-san!
We can't go any further!
This is...
I hate you, Yutaro-san!
Sensei!
Then why are you so wet?
I'm not wet because of you! I'm...
Hey, stop! What are you... This isn't the place!
Hey! They can see my body!
No! Seriously! Stop!
What's wrong with you?!
They can see us!
But you like being watched, don't you?
I like the sound of Hatsune-san's voice.
Why are you getting turned on by her voice?! You creep!
Why are you getting even harder from
hearing Shizuka-san's voice, Yutaro-san?
I hate you!
You pervert! You're doing my pussy so intensely!
Your dick is...
The scandal that has rocked the political world!
Rumors of obscene acts tarnish reputation
Cries for action to be taken throw the Parliament into disarray
Yes, please do.
Sensei isn't like that at all.
Thanks to you, my life is ruined!