Female Locker Room.
Hey, what are we going to do on Sunday?
Sunday?
Let's go there!
I'm leaving now.
Good night!
Yes, good night!
Sorry...
Sorry I'm late, Lena...
Good job, Ayaka.
You're dumb as always.
Your boobs look really pretty...
Show me more.
No, Lena...
You're so sensitive, Ayaka.
You're feeling good already.
Lena...
You're so cute, Ayaka.
You want me to stick it in here, right?
No, Lena...
Don't you want something bigger?
I don't want a man's thing...
it's scary...
That's why I want you...
Oh, stop it, Ayaka.
But you like Masaru, don't you?
What?
Masaru...
I don't care about Masaru...
You're so mean, Lena.
Then I'll just be mean.
Manager!
What are you two doing here so late?
There's no sex allowed between employees.
I want you to come with me.
Manager, people are going to see us.
That's the best part!
Don't worry, you'll get extra pay.
Then it's okay!
Manager.
Lena...
Yeah. This is the kind of relationship we have...
What? But you said there's no sex in the store...
Employee rule 4.
No matter what the situation is, don't ever talk back to the manager!
In other words, employees can't have sex with one another...
but the store manager can have sex with an employee.
What? That's just messed up.
Lena, I don't mind you doing naughty things...
but you did break the rule.
Manager.
Either way, I'm going to have to punish you both somehow.
Punish?
Now, let's begin.
Listen up! Rule 1.
Let's start with the way you greet customers!
Now do it!
Welcome...
Drop your head very low...
Make sure they can get a good view of your cleavage.
Welcome.
Welcome...
No! You're doing it wrong!
Again!
We provide service to our customers!
You need to smile more!
Lena, it tastes a bit weak!
Yes, Manager...
This is just...
You have to do what the customer wants.
Then you can be a great employee!
Come on!
You need to treat your customers nicely!
We're able to thrive if we can make the customers happy!
So you should serve with gratitude!
That's it, Lena!
That's how you do it!
Ayaka, learn from Lena!
Yes...
I gave you great service.
You should take me somewhere nice!
We can't just close the store...
No, I want Odaiba.
I wanna go to Odaiba!
Jeez...
Well, let's try to wrap this up!
I'll stick it in order!
No... please no...
I don't want this...
No? What do you mean no?
It's not your first time is it?
I'm sure she stuck some things in there...
but it's probably the first time having a cock inside.
You don't want to do this?
Or you don't want to do it here?
I don't want to do this here or anywhere else!
I see, you don't want to do either one.
Well, that's too bad.
I guess it's time for you to practice.
There we go!
It's really tight...
Somehow...
it hurts!
It hurts!
Stop it!
Manager! I want some too!
You really like this, don't you?
Meanie!
Yes! More... more!
That's it, Manager! More... more!
It's amazing, Manager!
Masaru!