Thank you very much!
That will be 450 yen!
Thank you for waiting!
Next person please step forward!
Welcome!
Please place your order!
Thank you very much!
Umm...
Will that be all?
King burger and a large coke and...
Thank you very much!
We have pumpkin pies on the dessert menu for sale today.
I guess I'll take that as well...
Sure. Thank you very much!
Add a pumpkin pie to that order!
Hey, Saito.
A new employee will be coming in tomorrow.
Yes, Manager.
Thank you for waiting!
Thank you very much!
Please come again!
Manager, I'll be right with you...
Thank you very much!
Make yourself at home!
Well, I'm taking a break!
Okay!
No, Manager...
it's not like you hate it right?
You can just add in two hours of overtime...
You're so persistent, Manager...
it's going to be three hours of overtime from today!
You're shrewd.
Aren't you dying for a screw?
We can't do it in here!
Cleaning
okay!
You're getting used to anal...
Well? Does it feel good?
Sort of.
I don't have to worry about getting pregnant...
There! You like this, don't you?
No...
Yes, it feels good.
No... I'll make the bathroom really dirty.
So what? We'll just make the new employee clean it...
Ayaka?
Not her...
Are you kidding?
I hired her because you begged me to!
She said she doesn't get that much allowance so...
Female Locker Room
Lena!
Ayaka!
More... do me much harder, Manager!
Manager, more... more!
I'm just shocked by this coed girl...
What if your classmates see you like this?
It doesn't matter...
Guys in my class don't have any money.
I'm not interested in them...
Stop talking and do what you have to do!
Masaru...
I'm coming. Ready?
Cleaning