Manager!
We're going to practice making fries.
It's hot!
No!
Listen.
Stay still so that the product doesn't fall.
It's hot... it's hot!
I told you. It'll fall if you move.
What should I do?
Well, since Lena is your senior...
We have to try something harder.
If you do anything painful...
you're going to pay me extra!
Don't worry.
I won't do anything that'll leave a scar.
Everybody likes our fries because of the quantity.
I think we have to stuff some more.
Stop it!
It's going to expand!
No?
I think it's going to be really popular.
We can't serve fries like this!
Can't help it.
No! The fries are going inside!
They're being dipped in your special sauce.
Maybe we'll sell it to the customers next time.
No!
Isn't it nice to do it with a guy?
Well, Ayaka? Don't you agree?
No... Ayaka hates men...
Are you serious?
Is that why she was doing it with you?
We can't use her!
Hot!
But it's strange...
Somehow, she likes Masaru...
Masaru, eh?
You mean Masaru from the soccer team?
Then that means he's my junior.
I believe I got him a job last summer.
Lena...
Hello? It's me.
Yo. What are you doing now?
Can you come over right now?
You know my store, right?
I'll be waiting for you on the roof.
No! Who did you call?
Just wait.
Sir?
What is it?
Well, I'm in the middle of giving them a lesson...
but I need some help.
So I thought you could help me out.
I see...
Now, here's your new customer!
Welcome.
Welcome...
Manager, l...
You don't pick and choose your customers!
Come on!
Yes...
Sir...
how does it taste?
It's good... it's really good.
Thank you very much...
Looks like you've learned a lot.
No matter who the customer is...
you have to service them with sincerity!
That's what you need to do in this business!
What?
Now, let's give Ayaka a prize for doing a good job!
Ayaka?
Masaru!
Ayaka.
Masaru...
Ready?
I'm going to stick it in, Ayaka.
Okay, Masaru...
Ayaka, it's amazing...
I love... l love... l love you...
Masaru!
It feels good!
It's so tight, Ayaka!
Ayaka looks like a slut...
Are you jealous?
Not really.
Masaru!
Manager!
You'll have to buy me an expensive bag for yesterday's services!
Plus you're doing this to me now!
I can't buy you a bag.
Too expensive.
Then what are you gonna get me?
I'll buy you some ramen.
What? That's not fair!
By the way, how's Masaru and Ayaka?
They're madly in love!
Even when they're in a cold place!
Like this?
Yes, harder!
You're doing good, Masaru!
Ayaka!
This is all because of you, sir...
I love sex!
Yes! Manager!
More! Do me more!