Obese and Lecherous Teacher: Yamada Takashi
He is a middle-aged man who works as an attendant,
a homeroom teacher and a stress-relieving vibe
who's being treated impudently like he has no dignity.
He never really minded that though as long as he is able to do it
with a highschool girl and enjoyed the days to their fullest.
A Legislator who Lunged Himself
to Hatsune: Kashiwagi Yuutarou
He is a newly elected legislator who quickly made
his way to the top. He keeps Hatsune by his side as his lover.
Nowadays, he is being fully supported by his now official wife Hatsune.
He is accomplished enough now although he hasn't been intimate with her
lately for being busy. He's been considering his future plans for it.
Cheeky Magazine Model
Highschool Girl: Takai Shizuka
She dominated in popularity on current generation
as a reader model, being an object of admiration for girls.
However, she was being troubled by a stalker who targeted her.
After finding out about her private life, the said stalker
lost interest and left her alone in disappointment.
Even so, she is making an effort nowadays,
aiming to make herself become a better person
with a newfound strength within herself,
a strong-willed cheeky highschool girl.
Lady Luck Highschool Girl: Kashiwagi
(formerly Aoyama) Hatsune
She offered herself to Yuutarou
as a wife in a political marriage.
It was almost like fate meant it to be,
as she is a girl of good virtue
who lent him her support.
After that, Yuutarou rose to the top
of his career in a blink of an eye.
Since then, she became his best partner,
a confidant and companion,
a formidable highschool lady.
Hatsune-chan became classmates
with the cheeky reader model Shizuka-chan.
After knowing that Hatsune-chan's father is a legislator,
ambition and arrogance led Shizuka-chan into paying them an
opportunistic visit. This alone shouldn't be a problem in itself...
However, Shizuka-chan found herself getting arrested by Hatsune-chan
on suspicion of high treason while having their usual stress-relief sex
in a restroom before going home. Still dumbfounded by the turn of events,
she was taken into custody in an investigation room.
Shizuka-chan's scheme to eavesdrop in their private lives and
dig up some dirt from her classmate's legislator father fell apart.
In the end, the confounded cheeky reader model
has nothing to say but apologies.
But as expected from a prim and earnest lady, Hatsune-chan
couldn't bear witness on what was happening in front of her.
She goes next room where Yuutarou is watching
the investigation room through a magic mirror.
He uttered with a stern voice how a prank as it might
have been, it must be death with utmost strictness.
"D-Do I even have to dress like this in the first place?"
Hatsune-chan asked bashfully while still wearing the cosplay uniform.
"Of course." Yuutarou said as his rough hands pulled her uniform apart.
He pushed her well-endowed breasts upwards as he squeezed them with much force that they misshapen and overflow through his fingers.
Inkou Kyoushi
feat.
Ero
Giin-sensei
Original Animation
(Lecherous Teacher 4 feat. Erotic Legislator)
L
La
Las
Last
Last T
Last Ti
Last Tim
Last Time
Last Time O
Last Time On
Last Time On In
Last Time On Inko
Last Time On Inkou
Last Time On Inkou K
Last Time On Inkou Kyou
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 fe
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 feat
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 feat. E
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 feat. Ero
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 feat. Ero Gi
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 feat. Ero Giin-sen
Last Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 feat. Ero Giin-sensei
Today's the last day we can take it easy.
You're going to school starting tomorrow.
You shouldn't! That part is...
...sensei!
Your cock is going inside me!
Your sturdy thing is—!
Your cock is amazing, it's shoving into me!
That's mean! You're lewd as well, sensei!
You're a lecherous teacher!
I said that's enough of you!
Just let it be and the issue will eventually die out.
Oh yeah, someone's transferring to this school.
Why are you changing the topic?!
You fat-ass lecherous teacher!
So, who is that girl supposed to be?
Seems like some high-class lady.
Yuutarou-san.
Your nostrils are flaring up while looking
at my friend, it's so unsightly!
It's the first time I see you like that.
I'm right about enrolling you there.
You're also cute when you're sulking.
Jeez, Yuutarou... Papa...
Your cock is filling my pussy deep inside!
Hey...
I'm just snooping a little for
some secret. Isn't that cute?
Open the door, Takai Shizuka-san!
We know that you're in there!
Wait... huh, what?
Hey!
Takai Shizuka, You are under
arrest for high treason!
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
And here I thought that we'll be good friends...
Inkou Kyoushi
feat.
Ero
Giin-sensei
(Lecherous Teacher 4 feat. Erotic Legislator)
Original Animation
Shizuka & Hatsune: Immoral Investigation Through The Glass
Everything is over now one way or another for me...
You know why you ended up here, right?
I-I'm sorry!
You're going to be charged with high treason.
It should have been a rose-colored life...
It's your fault that my life became a mess!
No, I'm sorry!
Wait, you're mistaken!
You assaulted me in the first place just like now!
Sh-Shut up! It's your fault!
No—!
I will be violated all night long...
I'll become a plaything and everyone
gets a turn one after the other...
It seems to be no more than a personal interest.
She's so lost in thought that
she didn't even notice me.
Well, we're only checking just in case.
We don't want something like
before happening again.
B-By the way, d-do I really have to wear these?
Of course. Even if she never
meant any serious harm,
it's a crime. We can't be lenient on this.
No... I understand that part,
but I don't see my outfit
having anything to do with it.
It has a lot to do about the situation.
We can't do this, Yuutarou-san!
We're making Miss Shizuka wait, you see?
I said that we can't!
Yuutarou-san, we can't go any further!
Jeez... Now we're doing the same thing as them.
You have to make do with this, please!
It's brimming with energy!
Your cock is in my pussy!
She heard us! Shizuka-san noticed
the thump and is coming towards us!
Look in front of you.
I-I know that... But somehow, I'm...
Did you get aroused? So you have
exhibitionist tendencies.
Th-That's not true...
I'm sorry for coming in late—
Sensei! Umm... This is...
You see... It's...
I'm sorry, but you should understand
since you're a man yourself.
She's in the next room.
P-Please pardon my intrusion!
Jeez! I hate you, Yuutarou-san!
Telling that to sensei...
You say that though you're dripping wet.
Y-You're wrong! I don't feel
aroused from being watched...
I'm so sorry!
I should have listened!
You can't pass that off as
a mere joke! You should stop.
This much won't hurt, It's just a prank!
What would become of me now?
No matter what happens, it's all over for me now!
It's alright, don't worry about it!
I already talked to them and
you're clear from any charges.
Really?
Thank you, sensei!
You hands... Come on, wait... hey!
W-Wait, hey! You can't do this here!
Weren't you nervous? You're sloppy down here.
Stop messing around in this place!
If someone happens to come in...
Idiot, lowlife!
We can be seen behind that though.
No way, is that a magic mirror?!
Wait, won't they see my body?!
Hey, I said no... Stop this...
Give up already.
Idiot! You actually pushed your cock inside!
You lowlife... No way!
Filthy fat-ass!
You... You're fooling around too much!
You know that we're being watched...
Don't you love that?
I love being looked at, but not in this way!
No way... Sensei and Shizuka-san
have that kind of relationship!
Looks like Shizuka-kun loves being watched
as well. She's just like you, Hatsune.
I'm not like that, jeez!
Please give me that!
No!
Your cock is being too intense...
In my pussy...
Huh, Hatsune-san is doing it with his father?
Huh?!
This can't be! They can see us!
Yuutarou-san, the switch...
You're so intense!
Hatsune-san's voice sounds good!
H-Hey, what's with you?
You're getting bigger from hearing
Hatsune-san's voice, you lowlife!
That's right, Yuutarou-san! You're getting harder
while hearing Shizuka-san's voice... I hate you!
No... No, don't!
Your cock is being too intense in my pussy!
Hatsune-san is so bold!
But so am I, my pussy is sopping wet!
Why are you getting competitive now?
Dammit! Having a lowlife like you talking
back at me makes me feel pathetic!
Yuutarou-san, you're watching
Shizuka-san while doing me...
I hate you!
I'm faithful to you, Hatsune.
Where do you think you're looking?
I don't care about you anymore! Hmmph!
I definitely won't forgive you!
I won't let you do me anymore after this!
N-No!
I'm breaking up with you, Yuutarou-san!
I will be going back to my parents' house!
No... I'm gonna come while
being watched by Hatsune-san!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
No... It's the same for me... In such a situation...
No!
No... Together with Hatsune-san...
...at the same time!
I look indecent in front of Shizuka-san!
So he's not your father. That was shocking...
I'm sorry...
But are you and sensei, umm... lovers?
No, not at all!
But he's kind of my stress-reliever.
You shouldn't do something like that anymore.
Yes, I'm truly sorry for what I did.
Huh? Umm, what's this?
This is what you left behind, right?
No, it's way smaller.
It was a bugging device, not a camera.
Japanese Diet Representative scandal,
in a situation that shaken the political world!
Meeting to find out the culprit in disarray!!
...face on dropped lascivious suspicions...
Yes, please do so.
What's written about him isn't true at all.
Sensei, you have a call. It's... from that person.
Yes?
Being in power means walking
on a precarious path, Kashiwagi.
After all this, you dare say that...
It not gonna end with only that much!
Your wicked schemes are futile, villain!
False Information Leaked As Black Propaganda! Demand For Resignation Backfired To Another Resignation!!
Legislator Kashiwagi, Innocent! Political Diversion Tactic Uncovered!
As expected from a person in power...
And Hatsune-san too, isn't she a wonderful wife?
...shaken...
...whether it's the end...
...the influence of Kashiwagi's camp remains strong...
...information
...since the rise of the groups in the gravure world...
...holding ground! The past modeling industry gets visited one after another...
...up until now, the balance of power has shifted...
...influence! In the middle of all that, reader models...
...the famous Takai Shizuka-san wears foreign branded...
...exclusive modeling contract! The model industry...
I'm also in the spotlight, so you can
become my official manager now.
I'll pass.
Whoa, how cocky!
I'd rather not be dragged around
more than you already do.
What the hell, you're enjoying this as well!
This lowlife fat-ass! You're a scum!
You see, I also go and party a lot with my co-models.
Alright, I'm your manager starting today.
You're getting too cocky!
But I really am grateful to Hatsune-san!
Isn't she a good girl. She's honest, beautiful
and feminine. She's a model highschool girl.
Jeez, and to whom are you comparing her with?
Scum! You're ticking me off!
What, are you gonna lay your hands on her as well?
You'll end up with a death penalty for sure!
You're right. I guess I'll just make do with you, then.
What—
Who do you think you are?
Damn, quit joking around!
It's me who's putting up with you!
You're the one who assaulted me
because you thought I'm cute!
Quit playing dumb!
Well, that's when Hatsune-kun wasn't here yet...
Damn you...
Just make me come already!
That's great! Use your cock more!
Yes, right there! My pussy is coming!
Wow, your semen is gushing into my womb!
Jeez...
This fat-ass scum's cock...
It's pouring too much semen inside!
They're doing it so intensely in a place like this...
Shizuka-san is so lewd!
Yuutarou-san!
Jeez, you can't do something like that here!
How about you, Hatsune. You were looking
for your friend but now you're peeping on her.
That's not true at all!
Jeez, father!
Father, that feels great!
You're more intense than usual!
Jeez, father!
I can't hold myself back when you talk that way.
I'm glad to hear that you liked it.
I'm so happy that you allowed me to get
admitted to this school and that I made a friend!
Father, your cock is incredible!
It's a tight fit in my pussy!
You always had to drag me
around with you ever since.
Hatsune, about my resignation...
I'm glad that you're worried about me,
but that will just make me feel bad.
I don't want to give you even more troubles.
You don't have to protect me all the time.
I want to help you as well!
I'm not letting you retire yet.
Sensei, you'll climb back at the top once again.
You got me all fired up now, Hatsune.
That's my beloved husband!
Sensei, father, husband...
My loved one can do anything!
You can call me whatever you want, Hatsune.
Yes, my pussy squeezes with delight!
I am very happy!
Father, give me lots of your semen deep inside!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization