Obese and Lecherous Teacher : Yamada Takashi
He is a middle-aged man who works as an attendant,
a homeroom teacher and a stress-relieving vibe,
who's being treated impudently like he has no dignity.
He never really minded that though as long as he is able to do it
with a highschool girl, and enjoyed the days to their fullest.
Public Representative who Lunged Himself
to Hatsune : Kashiwagi Yuutarou
He is a newly elected public representative who quickly made
his way to the top. He keeps Hatsune by his side as his lover.
Nowadays, he is being fully supported by his now official wife Hatsune.
He is accomplished enough now although lately he haven't been intimate
with her for being busy. He's been considering about his future plans for it.
Cheeky Magazine Model Highschool Girl : Takai Shizuka
She dominated in popularity on current generation
as a reader model, being an object of admiration for girls.
However, she was being troubled by a stalker who targeted her.
After finding out about her private life, the said stalker
lost interest and left her alone in disappointment.
Even so, she is making an effort nowadays,
aiming to make herself become a better person
with a newfound strength within herself,
a strong-willed cheeky highschool girl.
Lady Luck Highschool Girl : Kashiwagi
(formerly Aoyama) Hatsune
She offered herself to Yuutarou
as a wife in a political marriage.
It was almost like fate meant it to be,
as she is a girl of good virtue
who lent him her support.
After that, Yuutarou rose to the top
of his career in a blink of an eye.
Since then, she became his best partner,
a confidant and companion,
a formidable highschool lady.
Hatsune-chan and Yuutarou spends their vacation by going on a cruise.
He made her wear a micro bikini and they made love at the on-board pool.
The secretary assured them of their privacy with a twinkle from her glasses.
Hatsune-chan  received some good news. She will now become his official wife,
and she also got admitted into a new school to continue her neglected studies.
Hatsune-chan smiled innocently on him, looking forward
on being able to spend her days with girls of the same age group.
Seeing her like that makes his shaft become more in heat...
Shizuka-chan, the cheeky reader model,
needs sex to rid herself of stress from daily lessons.
With her manager's stress-relief vibe, her so-called "Yamada Stick",
she throws all of her grievances out on him while getting herself humped on.
What appears in front of Shizuka-chan later on is the supposedly daughter of a public representative, Hatsune-chan.
With this fateful encounter, Shizuka-chan's cheeky eyes overflows with desire, getting sharper just like a beast.
If everything works out well, Shizuka-chan will be able to arrange
an appointment and get herself together with this "politician papa".
And while behind that is something more from her getting ever hotter burning ambitions, the day of their acquaintance comes... however...
Inkou Kyoushi
feat.
Ero
Giin-sensei
Original Animation
(Lecherous Teacher 4 feat. Erotic Public Representative)
Th-This is embarrassing!
Jeez, making me wear something like this...
I hate you, Yuutarou-san!
You look beautiful.
Jeez... you're so naughty.
Today's the last day we can take it easy.
You're going to school starting tomorrow.
I'm happy now that I'll be able
to make friends about my age.
Thank you, my-dar-ling!
Oh! You grew big down there and it's poking out...
You can't just do that, Yuutarou-san!
There's no one else around, right?
Y-You're secretary is...
You shouldn't! That part is...
...sensei!
You're not calling me by my name...
Sorry... But sensei, your hands are...
You got something wonderful down here!
No... sensei, your finger...
is pinching my clitoris... Right there!
You can't just put your cock...
inside my pussy while at such a place!
Your cock is going inside me!
Your sturdy thing is—!
Your cock is amazing, it's shoving into me!
This is bad! Sensei, if this keeps up, I'm...
We've only just begun.
Your cock is so amazing!
It's more sturdy today than usual!
That's because you're so good.
I'm glad that you're like it, sensei!
I'll give my all to make you feel good!
Your sperm...
It's fantastic, sensei!
This is...
Sorry...
It's so sturdy yet so lovely...
I love your cock, sensei!
Sensei, you're so energetic!
You're doing a lot of lewd things to me!
From now on you'll be
a lewd highschool student.
That's mean! You're lewd as well, sensei!
You're a lecherous teacher!
I said that's enough of you!
Aren't you the one who led me on?
Like hell I'd ever do that! I hate this!
Celebrity Off-duty News Compilation
The currently active highschool idol and top runner Miss Takai Shizuka acts so much like a commoner! She has a lifestyle that's surprisingly way off her public image!
Among many idols, what first comes to mind when talking about Takai Shizuka is "celeb". But in reality, there's an extremely wide gap between her image and her private life. This time I got some candid snapshots of her overly plebeian lifestyle.
1. She doesn't have to act so fired up!
Getting a heap of red ginger in a major beef bowl food restaurant chain
2. Surprisingly buying a 50% discounted boxed lunch at evening!?
Making that hostile face even against an old lady (TAT)
3. Where did that supposed fashion leader personality go...
She's looting western-style clothing from a garbage dump.
Celebrity Off-duty News Compilation
The currently active highschool idol and top runner Miss Takai Shizuka acts so much like a commoner! She has a lifestyle that's surprisingly way off her public image!
Among many idols, what first comes to mind when talking about Takai Shizuka is "celeb". But in reality, there's an extremely wide gap between her image and her private life. This time I got some candid snapshots of her overly plebeian lifestyle.
1. She doesn't have to act so fired up!
Getting a heap of red ginger in a major beef bowl food restaurant chain
2. Surprisingly buying a 50% discounted boxed lunch at evening!?
Making that hostile face even against an old lady (TAT)
3. Where did that supposed fashion leader personality go...
She's looting western-style clothing from a garbage dump.
Celebrity Off-duty News Compilation
The currently active highschool idol and top runner Miss Takai Shizuka acts so much like a commoner! She has a lifestyle that's surprisingly way off her public image!
Among many idols, what first comes to mind when talking about Takai Shizuka is "celeb". But in reality, there's an extremely wide gap between her image and her private life. This time I got some candid snapshots of her overly plebeian lifestyle.
1. She doesn't have to act so fired up!
Getting a heap of red ginger in a major beef bowl food restaurant chain
2. Surprisingly buying a 50% discounted boxed lunch at evening!?
Making that hostile face even against an old lady (TAT)
3. Where did that supposed fashion leader personality go...
She's looting western-style clothing from a garbage dump.
Celebrity Off-duty News Compilation
The currently active highschool idol and top runner Miss Takai Shizuka acts so much like a commoner! She has a lifestyle that's surprisingly way off her public image!
Among many idols, what first comes to mind when talking about Takai Shizuka is "celeb". But in reality, there's an extremely wide gap between her image and her private life. This time I got some candid snapshots of her overly plebeian lifestyle.
1. She doesn't have to act so fired up!
Getting a heap of red ginger in a major beef bowl food restaurant chain
2. Surprisingly buying a 50% discounted boxed lunch at evening!?
Making that hostile face even against an old lady (TAT)
3. Where did that supposed fashion leader personality go...
She's looting western-style clothing from a garbage dump.
Isn't that embarrassing?
You're the lowest of scum!
Isn't that just me being streetwise!
Do something about it!
Just let it be and the issue will eventually die out.
Oh yeah, someone's transferring to this school.
Why are you changing the topic?!
You fatass lecherous teacher!
So, who is that girl supposed to be?
Seems like some high-class lady.
She grow up being pampered, right?
Teach her about how harsh the world can be!
Idiot, if that happens it will be a big trouble!
So you should get together with her.
Huh?! What... Wait, what did you just call me?
Wait, she's going to be my classmate?
Yeah. They'll be at ease knowing that
the most popular girl in school helps her.
W-Well yeah... She'll be lucky
to have me guiding her.
You're so naive.
Come on, make me come already!
I still have a photoshoot after this.
I'm really just a convenience for you.
And how about you? You always come
inside my pussy as you please!
Your obese cock feels good!
Right there, just like that inside my pussy!
Good!
I'm coming... I'm coming, I'm coming!
A lady, huh? I bet she's gorgeous!
What are you fantasizing about?
Reality can be harsh, you know?
Even models have to make effort for their image.
They're like someone else when
you see them without makeup!
This girl won't even let me have dreams and hopes.
For even having those in the first place,
you're a lolicon pervert lecherous teacher!
Inkou Kyoushi
feat.
Ero
Giin-sensei
(Lecherous Teacher 4 feat. Erotic Public Representative)
Original Animation
Shizuka & Hatsune: A Cheeky Magazine Model
and A Lady's Chance Encounter
Pleased to meet you. My name
is Kashiwagi Hatsune.
I hope to get along with both of you.
S-Seriously? A lady who looks like someone who came out from a painting exists...
She's beautiful... She's a virgin, right?
Jeez, you scum!
I'm Takai Shizuka, nice to meet you!
You can just call me Shizuka.
Thank you, Shizuka-san. Pleased to meet you!
This is the music room, and this one's the art room.
This the cafeteria for lunch...
That facade of yours really haven't changed.
What, fatass? Stop saying weird stuffs!
Look, your cards are showing.
You're annoying! Look, you made
Kashiwagi-san feel awkward.
You look like having fun with sensei. That's lovely.
We have a relationship way deeper
than just a student and teacher.
Deeper relationship? You...
That's not it! It's not what you think.
I'm working as a magazine
model, and he's my manager.
Of course you are. I quickly jumped on a conclusion.
Please forgive me.
When I heard that a lady is transferring here,
I thought that she might be pompous.
I'm not really some lady... My father just
happened to be a public representative.
So he's a public representative...
I'd love to meet him some other time.
I mean, he's my friend's father.
Me too, I'd love to introduce my friend to him.
If it all works out, I'm going to quit modeling!
What's your problem?
Can I call you papa in front of everyone?
Hey, stop making fun of me!
The guest has just arrived.
Hello, I'm Takai Shizuka.
Thank you for inviting me here today.
She's more lively unlike Hatsune...
Y-Yuutarou-san, just where are you looking at?
Jeez, that's my friend...
He's looking, alright.
Getting a middle-aged man or two
is a piece of cake for me.
Wow, your father and his office are both amazing!
I always thought that public reps are all old geezers.
But your father looks gorgeous, I envy you.
Hatsune's friend like you are always welcome here.
Thank you!
Thank you for teaching me various stuffs!
I'll drop by some other time.
Yuutarou-san.
Your nostrils are flaring up while looking
at my friend, it's so unsightly!
It's the first time I see you like that.
I'm right about enrolling you there.
You were giving her an indecent look!
You're the only one for me, Hatsune.
I don't believe you!
You're also cute when you're sulking.
Jeez, Yuutarou.... Papa...
Your cock is harder than usual.
It's all Shizuka-san's fault that
you're this aroused, right?
You're the only one for me.
You always know the words to please me.
I'm going to make your cock squirt a lot!
Yuutarou-san!
A lot came out.
Jeez... it's because of Shizuka-san too, right?
Yuutarou-san?
Even though you just came...
Your cock is incredible!
Your cock is filling my pussy deep inside!
The semen from your cock
is filling me up inside!
I love you, Yuutarou-san!
Amazing! I never thought that he's
such a prestigious man, it's amazing!
Hey, come here for a second.
Hey...
Good... This feels great!
In such a place... I'm...
Your cock went inside!
This really feels good!
Jeez, this will be great!
I'll definitely find out some secret!
Did you really do it?
I'll be going back there again.
I just have to pick it up by then, right?
I'm just snooping a little for
some secret. Isn't that cute?
Open the door, Takai Shizuka-san!
We know that you're in there!
Wait... huh, what?
Hey!
Takai Shizuka, You are under arrest for high treason!
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
Arrest Warrant
Suspect
Full Name
Takai                     Shizuka
Address
Tokyo Metropolitan Area, Nagairie City, Ayumitsuyu
Nature of Crime
High Treason
Summary of Facts for Suspicion
Included in Attachments
And here I thought that we'll be good friends...
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time On Inkou Kyoushi 4 feat. Ero Giin-sensei
It should have been a rose-colored life...
It's a crime. We can't be lenient on this.
Yes... I understand that but...
There's a considerable relation!
I'm going to relieve you, okay?
Yuutarou-san! You can't do any further!
This is it!
Jeez... I hate you, Yuutarou-san! Sensei...
You say that when you're overflowing down here.
T-That's not true! I'm not that...
Wait, hey! You can't do it in this place!
Wait, my body will be seen!
Hey, I said you can't! Stop—
Fatass!
You... You're fooling around too much!
Even when we'll be seen in this place!
Do you like being watched?
Hatsune-san's voice sounds good!
H-Hey, what's with you?
You're getting bigger from hearing
Hatsune-san's voice, scum!
That's right, Yuutarou-san! You're getting harder
after hearing Shizuka-san's voice... I hate you!
No... You can't!
You're cock is being too rough on my pussy!
Japanese Diet Representative scandal,
in a situation that shaken the political world!
Meeting to find out the culprit in disarray!!
...face on dropped lascivious suspicions...
Yes, please do so.
What's written about him isn't true at all.
It's your fault that my life became a mess!