Okizari Fansubs presents
【Return of the Beast】
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine...
and Anne's...
brief summary of the story!
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
Aine  &            Anne's
Brief Summary of
the Story
We're going to help you remember what happened up till now.
First, we have our vampire idol, Mina Shijyon, a main character in this story.
She can transform, and she's scary when she gets mad.
This is us.
We also can transform.
We're two beautiful girls who lost our home along with Mina and came to Earth.
We support Mina and are very reliable.
You guys...
This is one of the despicable beasts who took over our home.
We don't know why they're here on Earth now.
They pop up out of nowhere to attack and kill girls.
They're enemies of all women!
Until they're all dead, there can be no peace on Earth.
This is the president of the Kannaduki Group, Kannaduki Kozaburo.
We haven't met him yet,
but I can sense he's bad news.
We have to keep our eyes on this guy.
This is Megumi, one of our classmates.
And then...
That's it?!
All we know about you is that you're a perverted high school student.
Oh, and you're Tatsuo's girlfriend too, right?
You know what? I'm actually a very important character in this story!
Never mind.
We'll find out what happens anyway as we watch the story.
Hey! What about me?
Oh, it's that pervert boy, Tatsuo.
You suddenly turned into a beast after having sex with Megumi.
What was that all about?
Hey, can you tell me what's going to happen to me in the story?
I doubt this explanation was very helpful to the viewers.
Be quiet!
"Beast City Part 3" is going to start now.
Here we go!
Tatsuo...
Is that really you, Tatsuo?
For confidentiality reasons,
you're allowed to kill people who were witnesses!
Help me.
Damn, you have a beast with you?
We can't kill beasts with these.
Let's just kill the woman.
Yeah.
Nuclear bombs?
Are you saying you're going to nuke our own country?
Once other countries find out,
they'll take action sooner or later.
If that happens, the whole country could be annihilated!
That's a great idea. An excellent idea!
We just want to be graceful losers.
"Sweep the problem under the rug,"
huh, Prime Minister?
You don't have to say that.
Watch what you say, Saotome.
Okay, okay.
You're going to abandon the nation, huh.
We told people not to look outside,
because it can be dangerous if foreign countries attack.
That plan sounds almost like a joke.
Our real society was destroyed by beasts that are like...
monsters out of a grade-B anime.
Which sounds more like a joke now, huh?
I get it.
So when is it going to happen?
Tomorrow at 4 AM, sir.
In six hours, huh.
This is insane!
I don't... I will not accept it!
Do you think this is acceptable somehow?
You selfish crackpot!
Tatsuo, wake up.
Mina...
Help me, Mina!
Tatsuo, stop what you're doing.
Shit, what's going on?
I'm out of control.
I didn't expect there'd be anyone still alive.
Get her!
Who...
Kill her!
Who are you?
Kill them.
Kill all the people!
Who the hell are you?
Are you the one controlling me?
You are me.
What are you talking about?
Run, Mina!
T-Tatsuo...
Mina!
Kill! Kill her!
Shut up. Why would I...
Kill everyone!
Shut up!
Kill.
Kill, kill, kill.
Cut it out!
Kill her!
Kill, kill!
Mina!
No! Stop it!
Kill!
Kill, kill, kill!
Mina!
I feel the energy.
I sense the increased power.
This must be the power of the King of Beasts.
I'm going to suck the fresh endorphins from your brains after enjoying your bodies.
Wh-Who's there?
Dr. Aisha.
You fool.
You won't get any positive feelings from taking endorphins in orally.
What?
You're producing endorphins in your body from the joy of killing people.
That makes you a sexual psychopath who loves killing.
You... bitch.
What a hopeless beast.
Read this book for once,
and educate yourself first.
All About the Brain
What are you, exactly?
I'm a human.
Don't underestimate humans.
Brains get better as you use them.
That was holy water. Beasts hate it.
It doesn't have anything to do with God, though.
Instead, it's made with all of my knowledge.
It's pretty effective, isn't it?
It acts like a pesticide for beasts.
Once you're hit with the water,
your body cells die off rapidly.
You must be in great pain by now.
It's a lesson for you about learning the wisdom of human beings.
You guys are all going to be killed soon...
by a woman with a "powerless" job as scientist.
I can't wait until that happens.
Dr. Aisha...
Hm?
The beast is...
Dead already?
I had more to tell him, though.
Now, let's go, Ririka.
Y-Yes.
How are you feeling, Ririka?
I feel better now, thanks to you.
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Good.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
Okay.
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Special
1Medical
11Emergency
111Hospital
Oh, Doctor!
Please help her.
Is she going to die?
This is a red emergency alert.
We're under attack.
Make sure to close your doors, and don't look outside.
I repeat...
Sir, we apologize that we let some enemies through, resulting in all this.
That's okay.
But...
the beast destroyed a third of our buildings.
And he's going to wreak far more damage.
I said it's okay.
Huh?
The company was created for this day.
We should be celebrating.
I don't care about losing a building or two.
I-I'm sorry, sir, but the beast is clearly targeting this building.
He's been here for a long time.
The king wants to be with the queen.
What?
I have to thank the girl who gave me this great gift.
I'm sorry, Tatsuo.
I... I...
This is very interesting.
She's immortal, huh.
So?
You're not surprised to see us?
I am.
I'm Aisha, the doctor in this hospital.
This book will tell you more about me.
I'm Ririka, an assistant to Dr. Aisha.
Oh, so you don't have to be physically fit to be a nurse, huh?
Are you saying you heard us despite the condition you're in?
Um, I just wanted to make myself useful to the world.
And I'm not really a nurse.
And I can tell from the smell that you just killed a beast.
Wow, you can really smell that?
That was a joke, but this whole room reeks of beasts.
Wh-What are you doing?
Then that makes it easy.
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
People think this hospital is for people who've been attacked by beasts.
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
Special
Medical
Emergency
Hospital
But actually, this place is a hideout for research about the beasts.
D-Doctor!
Don't worry. I've never seen a beast like that.
Now it's my turn to ask you a question.
Tell me...
why you were fighting the beast?
What made you fight that huge King of Beasts all by yourself?
So you saw me?
I saw you flying.
A past King of Beasts ruined our planet.
Are you an alien?
And...
I know the guy.
You know him?
Okay.
Then the queen must be around here.
And you might recognize the queen as well.
Do you want to save him?
There is a way to save him, if we get the chance.
R-Really?
Yes, but you might have to go through some difficulties.
Hey, did you hear that?
We can save Tatsuo!
I'll do anything to save him!
Has the advance party left yet?
Yes, that was our best team.
I really hope they will settle the matter.
Most likely. Bit of a boring operation.
How can you be so certain?
And what did you tell the people this time?
I told them that a poisonous rain is going to fall.
Hey, hey. Give me a break.
Like Saotome said, that sounds like some sort of joke.
It's not a lie, though.
Poisonous rain is going to fall sooner or later.
You look like you're having fun.
I'm getting worried now.
You're worried about Kannaduki's property, right?
Our country has been heavily damaged since the beasts showed up.
It would fail without his financing now.
You're saying you can't even afford one nuclear bombing?
Rumor has it that he owns more property than this country's total savings,
and that's not actually wrong.
So I should at least call him.
You can't do that.
He won't accept a proposal like that.
You should be aware that if he talks, the country will really be finished.
It's me.
This is an emergency.
Just put me through him quickly.
You fool!
Hey, it's me.
I have a situation on my hands.
Hi, Prime Minister.
That's good news.
No, I'm in a shelter now.
I was starting to think that this country has abandoned me.
Okay, then I'll come see you and bring some money soon.
As an innocent company, we weren't sure how to deal with something like that.
Yes, I look forward to your continued cooperation.
I guess I don't even need to go there.
I'm sorry, Tatsuo.
I've been looking for you, girl.
Thanks for the great show.
I'm impressed by the way you awakened him and by your love for each other.
Oh my, aren't you a tomboy?
Wh-Who are you?
You'd better stay quiet.
I built a great company just for this day.
My father, who used to run this company, died when I was young,
and I found this book when I was organizing his belongings.
The book taught me how to contact you...
Investigation
on Beasts
and how to deal with beasts properly.
I was very lucky to have a chance to read it.
We didn't know anything about beasts back then.
Our company has grown at the hands of you beasts ever since.
And now here we are.
It's all thanks to you beasts.
I want to thank you,
as the Queen of Beasts.
So you're the one who used us?
I didn't "use" you.
Instead, you could say I'm the only one who understands you.
Tatsuo...
It's started.
I mean the army here just started to fight that huge beast.
Please stop!
I didn't do anything!
I didn't even realize it when I turned into this.
Please, someone help me!
Damn that beast!
I killed someone again!
I'm immortal!
Poor guy.
He must be scared.
Tatsuo...
He doesn't understand his power or how to use it.
He's just scared.
The King of Beasts can't even resist the attack of powerless humans.
Megumi...
Tatsuo!
Help me, Megumi!
I don't want to die!
Tatsuo!
Do you want to help him?
Is there a way?
Mina!
There's much more of this!
We have  A, O, B, and AB, RH+ or RH-.
I didn't know they could store blood like this nowadays.
You can gain energy from all of it.
It's time for a checkup.
Did you guys drink all of them?
What the hell...
They were tasty.
Why don't you try some, Ririka?
I'm okay.
I'm fully recovered, thanks to these.
Oh yeah?
First of all, even if you partook the blood through your mouth...
Oh boy.
Because you recovered before I even properly closed the wound,
I feel like all my scientific research has been meaningless.
Doctor...
It's good that he's following the queen.
Tatsuo...
Tatsuo!
So what's your plan?
Oh, you don't know?
This is the plan.
Megumi!
How's it going, Ririka?
You seem to be doing well.
Okay, I'm going to come back in two hours.
Megumi... Megumi...
It's not me. It's not!
Believe me!
Someone is controlling my body.
I'm sorry, Megumi!
Tatsuo...
Megumi?
Tatsuo... please don't cry.
You're still alive, Megumi?!
Tatsuo...
Thank God.
Megumi! Megumi...
I was scared!
Someone orders me to do things,
like to kill Mina or humans,
so I...
You still don't remember?
Remember... what?
Tatsuo, we are the King and Queen of Beasts.
No way.
I know that we're both perverted,
but the King and Queen of Beasts? No.
Megumi?
What you were hearing were commands from your genes.
The genes you inherited from your ancestors, who were Kings of Beasts.
All creatures follow the commands of their genes.
Humans or beasts...
But because of that, I put you through all this.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to forgive me.
I don't deserve to be your girlfriend.
Megumi... you're a fool.
What are you apologizing for?
I should apologize.
Tatsuo!
Megumi...
I'm glad.
Tatsuo is a reincarnation of the King of Beasts?
Reincarnation is not a scientific concept.
Instead, genetic information gets passed from parents to children.
So we're just talking about the possibility of a king and queen.
They're probably ordinary people.
Now here's the thing.
When they grow up, the King and Queen of Beasts combine and form a cocoon.
Then their babies are born,
and those kids eventually have babies with humans all over the world.
The children that received the most powerful genetic inheritance will grow up
looking just like humans and be candidates for king and queen.
That means...
Yeah, we have to see if they combine and form a cocoon.
Tatsuo!
I feel you going inside me.
I'm connected with you, the King of Beasts.
Tatsuo...
I didn't realize sex with Megumi was this good.
I'm getting sleepy now.
The problem is that we don't know when or even if they'll form a cocoon.
It's very hard to know because we can't get ahold of them.
Aine, Anne, you have some work to do now.
What do you mean?
Go to the Kannaduki Building and see how Tatsuo is doing.
Roger!
Here I go!
Hurry up, okay?
Okay!
Hurry up, hurry up.
You look stressed out.
I'll help you release that stress.
Hey, check this out.
Hm? Let's see.
Watch me carefully, okay?
Here it goes.
Wow, that was cool.
How did you do that?
Well, this is how it works.
How dare you play with girls in this situation?
K-Kannaduki?
I don't need you anymore.
I'm going to replace you as Prime Minister.
Wh-What?
You betrayed me!
Don't worry. I won't let them press the button on the nuclear bomb.
Not against this country, anyway.
What are you planning to do?!
It's about time to say goodbye.
Oh, there it is!
Mina, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
Tatsuo's in trouble.
What do you mean?
He keeps getting attacked.
What? Is he dead?
No, but he looks like cotton candy.
Cotton candy?
You mean a cocoon?
Yeah, something like that.
That's good news!
Cool.
It's finally the time I can help you.
Yeah.
You're also a candidate to be queen.
Right.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
I've always wanted to be useful to you.
And my brother wants this too.
Aren't we the worst?
No, I respect you and my brother.
Are you ready?
Yes, any time.
Please... cum inside me.
I wonder if this ritual went well.
Ritual?
Sex is an important ritual to take over the history of the past
and to pass down valuable memories to the future.
You even have sex in your head, huh?
That's right.
I feel everything in my head,
and the signal goes all over my body from there.
I receive the signals in my head.
Then I give them back to the other person.
There. My brain is sending you a lot of signals now.
Yeah, I do feel that.
Hey, I should be ovulating about now.
I wonder if we'll have a baby.
That's very unscientific.
Oh, it was scientifically proved a long time ago that women are unscientific.
That's news to me.
Sorry, Saotome. I couldn't have a baby at that time.
But our dream to live in a world with no beasts is going to come true soon.
Our will is going to be passed down.
You scared?
No.
Doctor Aisha...
Hm?
Actually, I am scared.
Kiss me.
Are you able to walk now?
Yeah, as you see.
You saved me.
I'm running out of time.
We have to act on our ideas right now.
Why are you in such a hurry?
A nuclear bomb is going to be dropped on the beasts' city at the crack of dawn.
Oh yeah?
We have about an hour until that happens.
The person I trust the most told me right before he died.
All right.
Here, take this.
What's this?
This is Ririka's hope.
Ririka's hope...
It's a huge charm.
I'm going to explain this briefly.
The King and Queen of Beasts are deeply in love and have formed a cocoon together.
All you have to do is to split them in two.
That's it?
I could say more, but that wouldn't change things.
You just stab the cocoon with it.
That sounds easy.
It's easy to say and also to do.
But it's not as fun a job as you might be imagining.
We don't have much time.
Can you do that for me?
Of course.
I'm going now.
Make sure to stab it in the forehead.
Roger!
She's a little angel.
Was that a devil?
M-Mina?
You're alive!
Are you here to save me?
This is it.
Wait for me, Tatsuo, Megumi.
You two looked good together,
even though you argued all the time.
I'm going to save you now.
You guys should go on a better date than this.
Wh-Why...
It's not as fun a job as you might be imagining.
Good. She found Megumi.
I can't wait to get out of here.
This is harsh.
She looks like a human.
How...
How can I do that?
I'm sorry.
Megumi?
I don't have enough power to keep myself under control anymore.
So please hurry up.
But you're just a human.
You're Megumi, the girl I know, right?
I'm a beast.
Even so...
Hurry up! Or Tatsuo...
Otherwise Tatsuo is going to die!
Please.
Are you really okay with this?
Goodbye, Tatsuo.
I had a good time with you.
Wh-What are you doing?!
Megumi!
What's this?
They disappeared.
The beasts are all disappearing!
You're good.
Megumi, Megumi!
I'm sorry... I...
No, I was watching.
It's not your fault.
I know that you did what Megumi asked you to do.
I wish we'd all been born as ordinary humans.
Yeah.
Then we could have...
Mina!
Is everyone okay?
Megumi! Are you okay?
No! Don't die! No!
Are you dead, Megumi?
Megumi's dead!
Aine...
Megumi!
Is she alive?
No, she's becoming invisible.
Megumi!
This is not the end.
I still need your help.
Someone controls the beasts.
Until we kill him, the beasts won't disappear completely.
Please, I need your help.
Aine, Anne, take care of Tatsuo and Megumi.
Thank you.
Is he really in here?
I'm sure he wouldn't miss the chance.
The chance?
You'll see.
Who are they?
Humans.
Most of the beasts started celebrating when they saw the king come back to life.
The rest still have enough power to keep up their human appearances.
You wait there.
Hold on.
Here it is.
It's closed, though.
I'll show you.
I've been waiting for you.
Bingo!
That's your way of saying
"I've been waiting for you"?
Excuse me.
You are...
As a fan,
I wanted to obtain their strength and power.
And I had to actually use them before selling them out.
Selling them out?
You mean the beasts?
They can be very useful because they can survive without eating,
as long as they have women from the enemy lines.
You were going to use them in the military?
Theft and rape are very common on the battlefield.
They're very human that way.
That's true.
But I didn't expect you to do what you just did.
Because of that, I had to change my plan significantly.
Was that your plan?
You even killed one of the queen candidates you knew.
This is Ririka's hope.
Aisha...
I see. You're one as well.
Yeah, one of the candidates to be queen.
What?
I'm sorry, Mina.
This is interesting.
No way.
Stop, Aisha!
Such an obvious ploy.
You think so?
What?
I'm going to die with him.
Sorry, but can you clean up the mess after this?
Wh-What are you...
Wh-Why?
Did you think a low-grade beast like you could stay away from the body of a queen?
You should have chosen a better possibility to try out.
Damn!
Mina, hurry up and blow me up with him.
No!
I couldn't!
I don't want to kill anyone anymore!
Get off of her!
Damn!
Move apart!
Mina... please.
No! I don't want to kill anyone!
Shit! I have no choice.
Don't, Aisha.
Aisha...
The evacuation order is no longer in effect.
Recovery work is underway.
We need volunteers, so please come help with the recovery effort.
I will repeat the announcement...
The electricity, gas, and water are back on now.
The schools I called just now will open again today.
Boys and girls, have a nice day at school!
We are not responsible for any fire damage, so please...
Thank you.
Mina!
Megumi?
This is the ego of a beast king.
Wow, aren't you horny this morning?
Shut up!
Megumi is the only one for me, okay?
Don't lie.
What did you say?
Damn you!
This is all good.
Is it?
What should I do now?
You can do whatever you like.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You should enjoy your life more, Mina.
My life, huh.
Sounds good.
Because it is!