If you want something, go get it.
Even if...
it ends with something unreasonable.
Raise your arms higher!
You won't win the upcoming race
if you swim like that!
Ms. Hinakawa is so cool.
An alumna of our swimming team.
Selected for the next Olympics,
Izumi Hinakawa.
A beauty with a capital B.
So perfect,
I can't even begin to bo envious.
I wouldn't mind living in the water...
with her forever
Feast of victims
Inmu
Aki...
She too will be soiled by a man someday.
The third night:
In the water
Aki...
Aki, I love you.
Aki.
I can't...
Aki...
I'm coming.
Aki, you're still here?
Ms. Hinakawa.
What's wrong?
Get going. They've already started.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I slipped, Ms. Hinakawa.
Watch out. It can bo dangerous.
I will.
Really.
You're so careless.
Maybe you dropped it somewhere?
No way.
Ms. Hinakawa.
What is it?
Someone's stealing my underwear.
Stealing your underwear?
I've had my underwear
stolen several times.
You left them somewhere, didn't you?
You and Yuka say the same thing.
I'll keep an eye out.
Please.
Aki, you promised him about this Sunday,
didn't you?
Aki's finally losing her virginity.
I'm still young.
But it's about time I give it to him.
You're a late bloomer. You're so old.
Am I?
Of course!
I'm still young, but it's about time.
That girl, too.
Nothing surprising there.
No! Not Aki.
Some guy taking Aki...
I don't even want to imagine.
Hey you.
Unreasonable, unbelievable things happen.
If you want something, go get it.
Even if it ends
with something unreasonable.
Have you ever stared at your own back?
What was that?
Maybe I had too much to drink.
Aki.
I'm so much in love with you.
So good.
Why is it so good?
Aki!
Ms. Hinakawa, where are you?
Ms. Hinakawa, already in the water?
Please don't scare me.
Come on in, Aki.
But I have to warm up first.
Don't worry. The water is warm
You can do it with me in the water.
Okay. But a special training session
at this hour?
Ms. Hinakawa?
You don't want to?
No, it's not that!
A private lesson with you. I'm so happy.
I won't permit it.
What are you doing?
I don't want to lose someone I love
to a man.
Ms. Hinakawa!
You can't do this.
No!
Not like this!
See? You like it.
No! Not that!
No.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you want it?
I want it.
I can't hear you.
All right. Good girl.
Turn around.
I'm so embarrassed.
Ms. Hinakawa!
You're so beautiful, Aki.
I feel really funny.
Aki. You do me, too.
I don't know what to do.
Not like that.
Aki, please.
Okay.
You're ao hot down there.
Harder.
Yes.
It's good! It feels so good.
It's great. Miss, it feels so good.
I'm going crazy.
My darling Aki. I love you, darling.
What is this?
What's wrong? I love you.
No use running from me.
I'm not giving you up.
Please forgive me.
I won't let you get away, Aki.
No!
Help! I want to go home!
Stop playing around or you'll get hurt.
Aki, like you always say.
Let's stay in the water together.
Forever. Forever.
You, fallen angels who cannot become
the Virgin Mary...
stay in your daydream...
and wander into the Pleasure Garden.
Again?
How many times do we have to do this?
No more.
Stop!
How long have I been here?
The Four Night:
Box
The party starts at 07:00 in Shubuya.
Let's hang out before that.
Let's go to that place
we saw in the magazine.
Sounds good!
See you later.
Are you leaving?
Aoi, you never hang out with us lately.
Sorry. I don't feel like it today.
Again? We're just trying to be nice.
Did the get a boyfriend or something?
She'll never be able to get one.
Don't you know
that hoys love quiet girls like her?
No, I meant that Aoi doesn't like people.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm here for you.
Hello? I want to ask you something.
Excuse me?
Welcome.
Welcome to Nightmare.
I've been waiting for you.
So? Anything you like?
Anything touched your heart?
That one in the box in the window.
Would you sell it?
The one in the box?
I don't think so. You want the other one.
No, that one in the box.
That one in the window.
You really want the one behind it.
You can't hide. I can tell.
You want the other one.
You've been here everyday to stare at it.
What is this one? No.
I want the one in the box.
Have you ever stared at your own back?
Finally you are mine.
So pretty.
We'll be together forever.
It looks so cozy in the box.
Maybe I should do the tame.
Just wait, I'll be joining you soon.
You're not coming again?
I never said I was.
But so many guys want you around.
Sorry, but I'm not interested.
You don't hang out with us,
we're not inviting you.
I don't feel like it. Bye.
I'm home. Have you been good?
Really? Good girl.
My darling.
I will do anything for you.
Happy?
You made me like this.
It smells funny.
I'm just like you now.
Night, already? I did it again.
Time flies when I'm with you.
That's it for the day.
Later.
So soon?
Don't stare at me.
I don't like to be stared at.
What is this? It spoke to me?
What's wrong?
You want to join me here, don't you?
All right. Let's switch.
So let's have fun.
No!
Stop!
Stop, no.
Give me a thicker one.
How long will I stay here?
I'm tired and sleepy.
Such a cute doll.
Really. What is this one for?
Doesn't this doll remind you of...
It reminds me of...