Shadow is the other face of Light.
The Moon repeats full of new.
Careful not to be devoured
by the Shadow.
INMU
Fruit Flesh Feast of Shame
Let me, now.
Hold on a sec... Not yet.
Not there.
Not that hard. No.
Please, let's not do it today.
What're you talking about?
You promised you'd give me
your virginity on my birthday, Youri.
I believed you, and I've been
waiting for a half a year!
I know that, but...
But I'm still scared.
I'm scared.
No.
Please, not today.
It's too late to say that now.
Episode 1: "Illusion"
Not there...
No, no!
I can't anymore...
Oops.
-Youri.
-I'm sorry.
Oh, well. I can go to the
massage parlor to get off.
Youri!
How are you getting along
with your boyfriend these days?
What? Why would you
ask me that?
Because rumor has it your
boyfriend is frequenting a massage parlor!
You let him do it, right?
I know it's a private thing
between you two.
I guess I shouldn't be too
nosy about it.
But, Youri.
You're not doing
anything shady, are you?
Huh?
There's a rumor going around that
you're working at the massage parlor.
I asked around, and it sounds like
there's someone who looks just like you.
Maybe your boyfriend
is seeing her.
Someone who looks just like me?
You...
You look like you're interested in
massage parlors...
but some things in life,
you're better off not knowing.
Please, mind me your own business!
Why would you say something
like that?
If you must know...
You...
Have you ever stared
at your own back?
Mister, you've visited me
every day this week.
I'll give it to you good today,
so come all you want for me.
Thank you, Youri. No, Yuri.
She's a dead ringer for me.
Mister, you're getting so big.
I'm sure you'll come a lot.
Yes. Please.
I'll let you come in my mouth,
just this once.
Please, do it quick, now.
I'm sorry, it's agains the house rules
to give you "full service."
Yuri.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Mister, did you enjoy that?
You're the best.
Really, it feels so good.
I should be feeling betrayed,
but why...
Why is my body...
hot?
No...
Was that a dream?
If you mean to go ahead...
you'd better remember
what i told you.
Me?
No way...
This can't be true.
It can't be real.
So good!
Yes. I've wanted to do this.
Be bold and honest with myself.
Just like she is.
Be careful when you meet someone
just like yourself.
She could be your other half.
Your other desire.
Your other shadow.
And the premonition of your
death and demise.
Your doppelganger.
She knows what I would like to
have done to me.
Yes, I want you to do it to me.
I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Huh? Where's Youri gone?
Huh? What're you talking about?
The girl who joined us. My girlfriend.
The door is locked. How could
anyone have come in?
But I'm sure I was fucking her
a few minutes ago.
Weird. I wasn't just imagining it.
No way.
Maybe she just vanished.
That's ridiculous.
Youri! Youri!
Weird. Was I
dreaming or something?
Tsk.
What?
Your desire can create an illusion
with no substance.
Doppelganger.
If you have an vision of yourself,
you are destined to vanish.
Vanish, too, will the shadow,
now that it has no body.
Humans, the creature that dreams.
Your neglected heart will seize you.
That is the world called Inmu:
Lust Dreams.
Episode 2:
"Excessive Love"
Do it, do it now!
I've always hated you.
Always looking down on me,
like I'm a sleaze ball.
You're really slow and clumsy.
I get irritated just watching you.
Oh, I hate it.
Just to think I'm breathing the
same air as you do...
I get nauseated, and I'm sick of
putting up with that!
What are you staring at?
Yes! That's it!
Bitches like that need to be punished.
Now the next scene is our
Senior Manager performing...
various fetish plays,
for your pleasure.
What a laugh.
The more self-important ones
tend to be like this.
Oops, she's already coming home.
My dear lovely Megumi.
A nurse, I hear.
Please, nurse me one day.
In return, I'll do something
nice for you.
No.
You sound so cute,
like you're begging for me to eat you.
Now it's my turn to pump
my seasoning inside you.
I want to see her.
What a perfect body.
I'm the only one who can defile you.
What was that dream last night?
It was strangely vivid.
What a delicate smell.
Wait for me to defile you.
My heart...
I can't breathe...
Please take this patient.
I Room 13? But...
We don't have enough beds.
It's his heart, so he can't
share a room with other patients.
I'm asking other hospitals
too, but...
It'll take a few days.
I understand.
Just for a few days.
Mr. Satomi?
Mr. Kousuke Satomi?
Let me check your temperature.
Don't worry.
Here it is.
If you need me,
press the call button.
Mr. Satomi, time to
turn off your lights.
How are you feeling?
You're not in pain, are you?
What is this?!
Finally, you're here for me.
My cute little flower.
You're awake, finally.
You can make noise, but it's no use.
This room is very far away
from other rooms.
And the another nurses are all asleep.
Ah, this one.
The undies you kept in your drawer.
You wore it for our maiden night
together, didn't you?
What's wrong? I see this is
a bit hard for you.
Who the hell are you?
When did you sneak
into my room?
What's this photo?
Don't be shrill like that.
I know everything about you.
I know your favorite underwear...
...I know you have
a cute mole under your boob...
I know your period was just last
week, and...
Stop, you pervert!
What're you talking about?
My dear Megumi, you shouldn't use
such vulgar language.
Stop fucking around!
I might have to shut your
loud mouth up.
I can't breathe...
Now, you're quiet.
Now, take my swollen member
in your mouth.
No!
No, don't be so unreasonable.
Go ahead. Use your tender tongue
to lick me softly.
Come on, now.
No! I really don't want to!
You're being so unreasonable.
Please don't cause me
any more trouble.
That's right, roll it around
in your mouth.
Take me deeper.
I'm coming.
Why aren't you swallowing it for me?
If you don't do as I say...
I'll do this.
Now, you lick it clean.
Good, good, that's good.
You're so beautiful, my dear Megumi.
You'll never get away with this.
Scum like you, I'll report you
to the police.
And, this photo!
That's the evidence!
The police won't ignore this.
Scum like you deserves
to go away.
Thanks for the insults.
Can't blame you, though.
Now that I'm here, I'll show you
how to rape a bitch.
What about it?
Didn't you enjoy yourself?
Didn't you have enough?
Lie down.
Now do it!
Don't use the wrong hole!
You're so cute, my dear Megumi.
So why don't you just shut up,
and let me rape you!
A woman.
I'm inside her. I'm getting inside her.
How wonderful it feels.
You're sucking me down there
as if your pussy has a will of its own.
This is heaven.
Yes, that's the way to do it!
More! More!
It's cold!
The energy of desire,
lost and wandering.
Guess who opens the door?
It could be you.