A dream.
A borderline of reality...
is a dangerous and fragile abyss
of darkness.
Be careful not to be consumed by a dream.
No. A pervert?
You got to be kidding.
Feast of victims
Inmu
Last stop.
Anything wrong?
No, I'm fine.
The first night:
I am being watched!
Damn.
Starting tomorrow
I have to take a different train.
Just my imagination. Right?
A kitty.
No. Someone was following me.
I'm sure someone is watching me.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm sorry.
Spying on you?
Yeah.
It feels like someone is watching me
all the time.
Aren't you a little paranoid?
You think so?
It's one thing when you're outside...
but in a classroom, under your skirt?
You watch too many weird videos?
I am serious.
Are you upset?
I'm going to bathroom.
Paranoia?
Who's there? Don't look!
Don't loot at me!
What is this?
Counseling?
It's close to the school.
Is this it?
That one? I never noticed it before.
Excuse me. Hello?
Come this my, please.
Yes.
I see.
You feel like someone is
always watching you.
Yes. Not always, but when I look around.
Some kind of phobia, I think,
fear of being watched, maybe.
No.
You feel people's eyes on you...
whether they're there or not.
How do you know?
What can I do?
Don't worry. I will let you have a dream.
In that dream...
you will discover all that you desire.
In that dream,
you will be free to be yourself.
When you awake, you'll be yourself again.
All I desire?
Have you ever stared at your own back?
What?
The truth is where you cannot see.
Just as you cannot see your own back.
Enjoy it all.
Your lusty dream.
A dream?
It was so real.
Was that the real me?
What is this?
No!
Don't!
Help!
No! Don t!
Not like this...
It feels good.
More. More.
I'm coming. Coming!
Now you know the real you.
I have been watching you.
I have been watching myself?
Your outside is the reverse of your inside.
What you desire is...
what you abhor.
The second night:
Things detested
How many years
have you been doing this job?
What is this?
Your stitches are all over the place.
I'm s-s-sorry.
Yamasawa! Do you want to ruin
the Mikthara Brand?
No, of course not.
Mr. Yamasawa again?
Yayoi gets tense before the show.
Yamasawa is her stress reduction.
Given his character.
It was a sudden design change, so...
Your job is to deal with
minor design changes.
What a useless man!
You're lower than a dog.
You dare look at me like that?
Don't bother to come tomorrow. Or ever.
No, Ms. Yayoi.
Be a dog, then.
I'll raise you
from lower than a dog to a dog.
Ms. Yayoi...
Mr. Taguchi?
Yes?
You handle number 12.
But...
Do it.
Bow.
Bow wow.
Are you stupid? What a show.
Okay, everybody. Work, work!
We don't have time.
Yes, ma'am.
Yamasawa, no more.
Don't bother me, go home.
But, ma'am, you promised...
From lower than a dog to a dog?
I'm not so low to hire a dog.
I shouldn't have hired a man like you!
A fortune teller? Here?
You're flipped inside out.
What are you talking about?
Your outside is the reverse of your inside.
What you desire is what you abhor.
You want to catch my attention
and take my money?
Unfortunately, I hate fortune tellers.
Have you ever stared at your back?
What was that?
Yamasawa?
Where am I?
This is great!
Back off, back off.
Clear the way.
Did you check the outfit?
One needs size adjustment,
the rest is all good.
All right.
I'll do the final check at the studio.
Hey, over there.
Too much color, it'll kill the lighting.
Paint again.
But tomorrow's the show.
You'll work overnight. I'm the director.
Okay, okay.
Oh, no. What am I thinking?
Yamasawa!
Yamasawa! Come out!
I want that man!
What's going on?
Yamasawa.
Ms. Yayoi, it's show time.
Do you think you can get away with this?
Who cares?
What are you doing?
No. Don't.
Stop. Please. Help.
What are you staring at?
Someone help me!
Stop it, Yamasawa.
Yamasawa?
What're you forgetting?
Mr. Yamasawa.
A hog like you has no business
saying my name!
That was close. I almost chopped it off.
Ms. Yayei of the Mikihara Brand is
peeing on herself.
How dare you talk to me like that.
It's wet. You'll catch cold.
No, not that one.
This side, too.
No! Don't look.
You know what to do, don't you?
I have no idea!
You just don't get it, do you?
You suck if.
Or the scissors will do their work
on your pretty face.
Not bad. Keep it up.
Good. More. Faster!
Now, a reward.
Please. Forgive me.
What are you saying?
We've only just begun.
You're drenched, ma'am.
Don't say that.
Feels good, doesn't it?
You get tormented, humiliated,
and you get wet.
No way.
Well, if it doesn't feel good...
No. Stop!
It's getting good.
You've been using it a lot.
I haven't.
See, ma'am, you're like this down there.
No more.
I can't stand it. Please.
Please what? Say it.
Give it to me.
What do you want?
I want your...
My what?
I want your hard one.
I see. You want it that much?
Then I'll give it to you.
It's good. I feel it.
You're driving me crazy.
I'm coming. I'm coming again.
More. Give me more.
It's so good, Yamasawa.
I underestimated you.
Yamasawa...