Joy of the Beast Mourning Wife.
I never would have expected it.
Even my husband hides this kind of DVD like other men.
I overheard through the sliding glass door,
the sobbing of the people mourning my husband's funeral.
I was stripped naked and...
had a hard dick in my uterus that was like a burning nail.
I begged him to stop because it was my ovulation day,
but he slapped my face and then continued to fuck my pussy.
This is the worst.
Or rather, this doesn't even seem real.
I want to promise to be his wife forever.
I'll devote my whole life to my husband.
Yes, your dick is so much sturdier than my ex-boyfriend's.
Please keep fucking me and give me your cum.
I swear in front of God, please take away my virginity.
I'll make you make me pregnant.
I'll get pregnant and I'll be yours.
I'll give my virginity for you.
I want to be real woman and wife for you.
No way, what am I thinking?
Today is the day... where if someone cums in me,
I'll get pregnant.
That's why I had that dirty dream.
My name is Saeki Nozomi.
I work as a nurse at Mizuno Hospital Pediatrics Department. I am 24 years old.
I am a newlywed and young wife.
Although we barely had our honeymoon,
I'm already worried about our marriage.
What's wrong with me?
Mizuno Hospital
Good morning!
W
Chart 1:
「When My Darling Cousin Gets Pregnant, The New Wife, Nozomi (B-93)」
These two are cousins who were raised like brother and sister.
The boy was hospitalized at my hospital yesterday.
Nozomi Nee-san!
Good Morning, Hiroto-kun!
Oh, she's still here.
I told her this visit was just for a physical examination.
Don't complain. Such a beautiful woman loves you,
consider yourself a lucky one.
But maybe my upper classmates will...
I don't think it's good to stay with Yumi...
Because it might seem like she's taking care of you,
but actually she's depending on you.
You really don't understand a woman's feelings at all.
A woman needs to lean on somebody.
Otherwise, she won't be happy.
They always want to be held tight.
Nee-san, I think maybe...
Is it bad for me to be here?
You're not going to leave without me, right, Onii-chan?
No problem, he's not going to go anywhere.
I'll be watching him.
Then, I'll be leaving for school.
How are you today, Hiroto-kun?
E-Excuse me.
Was Yumi-kun crying?
No way, I am not a heart breaker like you.
You don't have to say something like that, Hiroto-kun.
It's amazing that Hiroto's friend is an honors medical university graduate and heir to this hospital.
Why don't you take your time to recover here,
so you can enjoy your life better out there rather than staying in here.
It's like the moon and the turtle.
Although I'll cheering for turtle-kun.
The streets are scary at night ～ (T_T)
I don't like walking alone late at night...
-Nozomi
-Okay I understand (^^;;
Because he takes care of me every night.
I was really happy because of that.
You are really like a child, sleeping so quickly after eating.
Stop it!
What are you doing!?
Be quiet.
You know, the nurse has to protect the patient.
N-No...
No!
I said be quiet!
Oh, Hiroto-kun!
No! I can't take this.
Not so rough...
You'll leave marks...
The real thrill of rape is when I put my signature on a woman's body.
No!
Hiroto-kun...
Don't...
No-
No, don't!
No!
No...
Not bad, I like a woman who fights back.
I have something that will calm you down.
What's this? S-So hot-
No way, such a big dick!
Don't...
Don't go that deep.
You're going to break my stomach.
Stop!
That place going to break apart...
It's too big! You're opening my pussy, it's impossible.
No!
I can't let him fuck me!
Oh no! this feels like my uterus is being sucked out.
No, it's deep...
It's coming in deep inside of me.
No one, not even my husband,
has gone this deep into me!
Is this the first time a dick has touched your uterus?
Like this! like this-
I can't believe it...
This is the first time I've felt all of my pleasure points being stimulated.
I am full... but his dick is getting bigger.
Stop moving your dick like that...
Don't make my body feel good like this.
His dick is getting bigger.
He's gonna cum!
Don't cum! No!
Don't!
This is my first time with a man other than my husband.
I'm sorry I called you while you're at work.
No, I just wanted to tell you something.
I just want to talk with you sometimes.
I cannot explain this over the phone.
At least the rapist didn't cum inside of me.
That was the first time my pussy and uterus trembled so much afterwards.
And then...
I cannot keep this to myself, because that dick went so deep and reached my uterus.
Something like that...
After I ate that day, I fell asleep and...
I don't remember anything after that.
Why isn't my husband here at a time like this?
Why do I lean on you, Hiroto-kun?
Am I okay just talking to any man?
Remember?
You told me a woman needs to lean on a man.
Now I am the man who's close to you.
No, you are just like my little brother, Hiroto-kun.
I am a man.
I always saw you as my little brother.
Hiroto-kun...
We shouldn't...
Don't!
A married woman has to be clean,
and be just for her husband.
I don't care.
Right now, I'm the only man by Nee-san's side.
No!
Another man's dick is going to come into me again.
Don't be so tight, I'll cum.
Even though I said we shouldn't...
Since I didn't really finish last time...
No.
So my body is hungry for this, it won't stop.
That's good.
Keep doing that.
It's making my pussy shiver.
I'm cumming.
No.
I shouldn't cum like this. No!
Y-Your cum...!
Your cum...!
Give my uterus your cum.
That hot and sticky manly stuff, filled up my pussy to clean that ugly rapist off of me.
Every time his young, strong, innocent dick filled me up,
it was as if all my worries melted away.
Where is the clean, chaste wife now?
You're a big tease...
Is that story true?
Yes, I hear they call that thing a "special nurse service".
The pay is better than what the other nurses get.
I heard about it from Dr Mizuno.
That's not what I meant.
I don't want to be a burden on my brother anymore.
But you're taking nursing school during the day and at night you have this job...
I know I'm going to be busier, but there's still someone else who can take care of him.
I will.
She might have found out.
I did a very bad thing.
I'm a very bad woman.
Then your dream came true right?
No, I...
I see. You came inside her right?
Hiroto-kun, in the case of courtship behavior of the animals, who wins?
It's the animal who gets the female pregnant first.
You mean, to make a woman pregnant means winning?
What I mean is, if you want her to open her heart,
you should get ready to make her pregnant.
Ozaki Hiroto
Hiroto-kun... is serious about me.
I should stop him from getting seriously into me.
If I actually get pregnant, that will cause a lot of trouble.
But I wonder if he'd say "yes, you can have my child".
Why am I thinking about this bad stuff?
I am sorry, dear.
Did you love him until he left his bedsheets?
Dr Nimura?!
A nurse sleeping with a patient,
that is a serious morale problem.
N-No, I was just feeling dizzy and wanted to rest.
Really?
I still have to patrol the patient's beds, excuse me.
Take some time here, would you?
He is not going to return for a while.
What... I can't move...
You're a professional nurse, right?
Don't forget the nurse's basic training:
don't be shy in front of an examiner.
Why won't my body move?
Look at your pussy, it must be your ovulation day.
Stop it!
You just got infected with the indecent lust syndrome.
And the infection is spreading.
What?
Then I am going to give you an examination.
No, I can't move.
No way! It stinks!
Very stinky!
No, he's so big.
I used too much muscle relaxants.
It smells like fresh soap.
Well I guess you wanted him to take off your panties,
that's why you got new ones, isn't it?
No! No! Stop it! Please!
Your vagina got pretty loose.
Guess I can skip the foreplay.
Big!
It's Big!
It's like the dick from that day...
That's right...
This is...
I knew it, it's going into that place...
I-It's reaching my...
I... It's ripping apart-
I don't want this hard dick! No!