Mizuno Hospital
Onii-chan, don't... somebody might come here.
No!
Stop!
You'll make me scream, Onii-chan.
Not so...
No, Onii-chan!
No... I'm almost...
No way, what am I thinking?
Nozomi
It's because I saw that earlier...
I can't be by Onii-chan's side anymore.
Nozomi
I want to be with Onii-chan.
I'll turn my eyes away from it and stay with him, at least for now.
Waiting Room
She may be your sister, but she is also a woman.
No way, stop saying that.
But I think Saeki-kun doesn't understand that you guys are brother and sister.
That can't be...
W
Chart 2:
「When my beloved sister gets naughty. Virgin Saeki (small-size)」
I-It's so tight... It's rubbing inside of me...
No!
No! I'm losing... my power...
If this keeps up...
It's going deep inside!
No...
Help me, Hiroto-kun.
No, I don't want to feel it.
But my body is getting hot.
No, stop...
My voice...
Holding back is not good for your body.
Good... good... no...
Hiroto-kun...
Amazing, the dick is so deep inside of my pussy.
I can't hold it anymore...
Hiroto-kun!
The dick is rubbing inside of my uterus.
I'm about to cum... and he's still so deep inside...
I'll give it to you even deeper.
No! Don't cum inside of my uterus!
This is Hiroto-kun's pussy, don't!
Don't!
Stop!
No way, his dick is completely touching my uterus.
His sperm is filling up my uterus.
Yumi...
I think this is a good time to stay away from your sister.
Onii-chan?
Oh, sorry.
H-Hey...
You know, if I go away somewhere...
No!
Why, Onii-chan?
You told me you would never leave me.
Onii-chan...
No I don't mean that, I'm just saying...
I would like to be with you forever, Onii-chan.
Eh? W-Well, that is...
Changing room
Nozomi
Hiroto-kun, what should I do?
N-No!
No.
Coming in deep...
It's deep inside my pussy.
Not inside...
Not this.
Great..
It's great...
My body is shaking and... full!
Don't!
No!
Stop!
S-Stop!
I'll cum deep inside of you.
I can't
I really can't.
It's coming straight in again! Cumming!
I compared him to Hiroto-kun, I'm the worst!
Special nurse training room
Starting today if you study and train hard, you can be a special nurse.
First of all, nursing your brother.
Hang in there, okay?
Yes...
Nee-san.
Yes, good, please push more.
Nee-san, I'm about to cum.
Hiroto-kun, please, no more.
Please, deeper... deeper...
Nee-san.
I will never leave you.
I will always be by your side.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Oh that's right, will you come with your brother tomorrow, please?
With my brother?
Tomorrow is practice, and you need a partner.
Someone you know is easier for you, right?
Oh... yes.
Doctor said someone you know is better for practice.
Oh... sure!
I will pick you up later on.
Special nurse training room
Well, the practice is very hard, but I know you would do well.
Yes, I will!
Ok!
So, Ozaki-kun, you need to sit here, please.
Oh... okay.
Nozomi
Why would I do that?
The interesting part is about to start.
No way!
I sucked that big of a dick.
Onii-chan, your dick is wonderful!
You imagined your brother's dick,
are you a pervert, Yumi-kun?
So I think I will show Yumi's perverted actions tonight!
And then about Yumi's special nursing course.
It'll be much better than the others.
Special nurse?
Of course, special nurse service is at night.
For the libido, that is.
But there is one part of her training that is still not complete, right here.
No.
Yumi!
You may feel a little pain,
but just hang in there, Yumi-kun.
No, doctor.
Stop it, please!
I don't like those kind of things.
Stop it!
Onii-chan!
Yumi, run away!
Onii-chan, I am sorry about this. I am sorry.
Yumi, please run away, don't mind me.
No!
You can become a real woman on top of your beloved brother's chest.
That is good, isn't it?
Onii-chan.
I am....
No... Onii-chan...
It hurts!
Stop!
Onii-chan!
No!
Stop!
Too tight!
Onii-chan!
Please enjoy your first man, get a good taste of it.
Something is deep inside.
Onii-chan!
It hurts!
Yumi...
It will feel good soon enough.
Stop it!
Onii-chan.
No!
So tight...
It's breaking apart...
My body is starting to feel strange.
Onii-chan...
My insides are...
Ozaki-kun, did your dick get hard?
Because you actually want your sister.
You siblings were an indecent family.
No, you're wrong, we're not...
Onii-chan...
My body....
I will cum and fill you up deep inside.
What?
No.
Onii-chan.
It's going inside...
Onii-chan...
Yumi...
No!
Stop it!
You've gotten used to it, huh?
You were a virgin, but you'll get used to it pretty quickly.
No...
Please stop this! You can't...
You're saying that, but your body is grabbing my body.
No, don't go...
... so deep like that.
Please stop it!
I think you're excited because your brother is watching you, right?
No!
Onii-chan.
Be honest, if you don't I will punish you.
No, please don't punish me.
It's deep inside me now.
Stop!
It looks like you're feeling good.
No!
It feels like my body is breaking apart.
Get pregnant, okay!
No, I'll get pregnant.
His dick is so deep...
It's amazing... Onii-chan...
Yumi-chan?
N-Nee-san.
Oh, Saeki-kun, is something wrong?
No way!
Yumi-chan.
Why?
Nee-san...
It's Yumi-kun's turn this time.
N-No...
Your dick is bigger than Hiroto-kun's.
It fills up my pussy perfectly.
D-Doctor, your dick belongs only to me!
Onee-chan...
I love your pussy.
Yumi-chan, do you feel good?
Onii-chan, do you feel good?
Amazing, your dick is so hard!
Onee-chan...
It's okay, Yumi-chan.
I don't mind handing him over,
because Hiroto-kun's dick cannot satisfy me.
It's sliding right into my pussy.
Doctor's dick was too big for me,
but Hiroto's dick is easy for my pussy.
But, maybe it's not quite big enough...
But I can't live without it because I love my brother.
I also love Hiroto-kun...
but doctor is no.1 right now.
I think Hiroto-kun is about to cum.
You're right.
Please give me a lot of cum Onii-chan!
A lot of cum... for Yumi's pussy!
Onii-chan!