Well, l'll see you later.
OK, see you later.
l've married my husband 3 years-ago through a service.
l have no regrets.
He's nice and honest.
Honestly, l think he could've gotten a better girl than me.
ln his warm arms...
He shows me love.
He's been showing it ever since we've met.
Natsumi...Natsumi!
Honey!
However, l was not a loyal wife.
Hey, you alone?
You're...a slut.
l never had tits like these!
Delicious cock...
Deeper...give it to me deeper.
Yes, l want more!
My wild single life.
Words can not explain what l did...
l never thought you would really let me fuck you!
Are you a nympho?
More, l want more!
Great, oh cuming!
What's that, take this and this!
l was not able resist sex.
Please give me cock, now...
l don't know what to do about your penis addiction, Natsumi.
Don't be mean by holding it off...
More!
You want this right, Natsumi?
Yes, l like that warm, pulsing cock!
More, more!
Let me suck it, don't be mean!
You filthy slut...
Lets see how many times we can cum until morning.
l'm about to bust.
Here!
Cum, cum all over my body!
More, l want more cum!
More!
l know it's not right, but l cannot resist the lust.
The days l slept with many men.
l tried to get away from it by marrying my husband.
However, lately l've been thinking about it.
l thought l've gotten over it.
More, l want more.
But my body wants it.
That one lustful sensation.
alright?
OK, bye.
My husband doesn't have many friends.
But he called saying he's bringing one over.
A friend that share's the same thoughts, a friend of 10 years.
To be honest, l was surprised my husband had such a friend.
Coming!
lnsatiable Volume 1 Reawakening Lust
Man, just relax alright?
l will.
lt's very rare to see him this happy.
Natsumi, stop cooking and come drink with us.
O, OK.
Natsumi can drink pretty heavily.
Stop it, Honey.
Wow, amazing.
By the way, you found a good wife.
Yeah, l'm surprised myself.
Like always.
No way waking him now.
But what's more surprising.
S...stop it!
Hey, you don't need to treat me like that Ma'am.
Or should l call you Natsumi like before?
l never thought you were my friend's wife.
Are you satisfied?
Sex with him, that is.
W...why should l tell you.
Hey, l'm just worried about you.
That's why l'm asking.
l know everything about your body.
M...Megumi...
What position do you like...
where are you're sensitive?
Stop, Megumi.
l'm not like that anymore.
l don't think so.
After all, you're not resisting one bit.
The fetishes you like.
Please, please stop.
Are you sure, a girl like you?
l don't think you could be satisfied by just one "man".
His chest touching me, my butt touching him.
l haven't been this close to another man since l married.
l....
Hey...
Stop it!
And?
Then what?
Please...
N...no!
Those skinny, cold fingers.
lronically, those very fingers made my body heat up.
Megumi's touch l haven't felt in a long time.
l know it's not right, but l dare not to stop him.
What if Shunji wakes up!?
He just might.
So please...Megumi.
Please...
Lets see...
He asked me to please him using my mouth and hands.
lf l do, he'll keep my past a secret.
Just this one time.
As l think about it.
What's wrong?
Don't like?
Then you can.
His cock was harder than l could remember.
A very strong male smell.
Warm and hard.
Different smell than of my husband's.
ln my mind l tell myself don't.
But the taste and smell of it makes me ignore that thought.
Suddenly...
Yes, l was wet.
My husband is just right there too.
Yet, l go on.
The guilt...
Awakens the lust that l stopped craving long ago.
His wishes began to escalate, but...
l had no reason to reject them.
l told myself that it's not right, but
there's nothing that can be done...
No, l was probably waiting for this moment to come.
No...n, n, not that...
Don't make me wait...
No! No, no, no!
l know you like it.
Cuming by your ass, l bet Shunji doesn't do it.
lf you don't be quiet, he'll wake up.
You want that?
N...no!
His continuos, non-stop fingering made me cum many many times.
On top of that, even after l came he did not let me rest.
A man who's not my husband gave me endless orgasms...
The only thing l could think of was his cock.
Please, stick in inside, hurry!
lf you want it, beg for it.
What does slutty Natsumi want?
Please, l want your dick Megumi.
Please stir me inside with your dick.
Please...
Promise me one thing Natsumi.
Please, don't make me wait...
lf you want me to continue, obey everything l say.
Obey them no matter what.
l'll do anything, so hurry...
Stick it in!
A penis from a man that's not my husband made me very excited.
The thought of being caught was no longer in my head.
More, more. Deeper, deeper...
were the only things in my head.
No...cuming, no!
No, l'm cuming, cuming!
Thank you for the nice time.
Well, sorry to sleep on you like that.
You always do.
When did he take these pictures?
(Phone: Come to the Crown Hill Hotel at 1pm)
He also asked me to dress like before.
The dress l wore when l was single.
lt doesn't fit my current image.
lt was very embarrassing.
But...
Something in me wanted more.
l can experience "pleasure" again if l go to the hotel.
Part of me says don't, but another says hurry...
(Phone: Come to Room 1701 )
Megumi, who is he!?
He's a...very close friend of mine.
B...but!
l...l can't do that...
But you have to.
l already invited him.
Come.
No!
B...but!
You don't need to hold it in today.
No!
Natsumi, look at your syrup pouring.
Wait...we need to have him join or else there was no point of inviting him.
S...suddenly!?
No!
lt hurts, be more gentle!
The man with the mask was so rough that it hurt.
But that pain also made me relaxed.
You like it?
You're just a slut like before.
Natsumi, suck on this.
l'll cum inside your mouth today.
Cuming! More, more!
Are you sure?
Natsumi, lets make you a sandwich.
B...but!
l...l'm going to lose it!
How is it Natsumi?
The feeling of being fucked at both ends!
Long time, right!?
Great, it's great!!!
Cocks rubbing the inside...cuming!
Cuming!
M...m...more!
More.
Being treated rudely by a man l don't know.
But...
But l was satisfied mentally and physically.