You're finally here, Natsumi.
l love you, Natsumi.
Dear!
Having sex with my husband gives me comfort and happiness.
But...
Ever since...
My husband is there.
Yeah, he might wake up.
So please...stop Hayama.
Please.
l'll do anything, so hurry...fuck me!
Not only did l have sex with a man that's not my husband, l loved it.
Natsumi, look at your syrup.
Don't!
So Natsumi, how do you like being fucked in both holes at once?
lt's Been a while, right?
l haven't even gave my husband a blowjob.
Always Sex in a dark room too.
Only if...you had given me more.
l'm sorry, Dear.
Let me introduce you.
This is my lover, Eriko.
Your girlfriend?
No, someone else's wife.
ln other words, cheating.
Nice to meet you, Natsumi.
l heard a lot about you from him.
These guys work for me, Mikitani and Yoshida.
l am Mikitani, lt's nice to be on this trip with a beautiful woman like you.
Let's have fun together.
OK, same to you.
l don't think he needs an introduction.
Well shall we get ready and sail out?
This is my dad's boat, feel free to use anything you want.
Lets go!
l have a husband, yet l wear this skimpy bikini to get their attention.
No, more could happen...why did l come here?
You sure have a nice ass.
Eriko!?
l'm a girl and l like it.
D, don't do that.
You are Hayama's sex friend, right?
Uh, um, but...
Don't worry, l don't mind at all.
What's wrong, you worried?
Yes.
Don't worry, l heard we're just sailing today... or would you rather have some other fun?
But...
But?
They told me to wear this.
lt sure reveals a lot, but think of yourself as eye candy.
l mean it is a vacation after all.
The guys need something to look at.
A waste of beauty if you don't use it.
By the way, how close are you to that masked man?
l don't know him...
So you won't be mad if l have him.
l'm going to have fun.
Cheers.
We're friends as of today, OK?
Sure.
The breeze is great, the sea was the perfect choice.
H, hey, Eriko.
Oh, what's the matter?
l, it feels good.
W, was l always this sensitive?
Flip over.
But my chest is...
Don't worry, my hands will cover it.
Still!
See, now you aren't alone.
No need to be shy.
Eriko, want me to do it?
Nope, l'm doing it.
You better hurry or those four will really do it.
Hurry, Natsumi.
Here, move your hands.
How else am l going to get this on?
Good, right?
Our nipples rubbing against each other while oiling...
E, Eriko, l'm fine now.
The oil is on me.
We need to cover more.
l want you now.
No, Eriko!
Come on, we can tease them a little.
N, no, l'm getting wet!?
Can't hold it!
Yoshida, Mikitani...come over here!
Hurry.
Take off my bathing suit and apply oil on me.
Eriko, you're always such a slut.
Your lover's watching.
lnside too.
So good.
Eriko, would you please.
Fine.
No, not yet.
Get me in the mood.
Natsumi, l'm sorry.
Looks like l like taking more than giving.
Right there...more...
N, no, give me more.
Why...why am l enjoying this?
More, rub my clit!
Eriko.
Oh, you want some too?
Uh, of course not!
Hmm, you saying you don't like this?
Well, we won't force you.
Hey, you're wet.
No, cuming, more...more!
Cuming...cuming, cuming, cuming!
No, more...
Cuming!
Cuming, cuming, my ass!
lt feels so good up my ass!
Was it that good?
My body is so sensitive.
Someone, please...l want...l want it here too.
Someone, please!
Wait up, Natsumi.
Let go!
Don't say that, l heard you in the shower...don't you want it?
Be honest, you want us real bad.
That's not...
We could hear you moaning from outhear.
That's right.
No, stop...
l said stop!
No, don't!
You're soaking wet.
You want it?
l...
Come on, lets cum together.
You give good head...cuming soon.
Same...here.
Look at her coating herself with our cum.
What a slut.
What would Omoi think if he saw this?
No! Don't say such things!
Alright, if you make me hard again.
OK.
You give head to Omoi?
He doesn't know that l'm a slut.
So, we get the better treatment?
and you're playing innocent with him.
No...but...
Hey, why did you stop?
Please, make this our last encounter.
That's!
Don't you love it when l rub your clit like this, Natsumi?
S, stop Yoshida! Don't call me Natsumi!
Please!
Don't listen to her.
Why?
l'm guessing Yoshida's voice reminds her of her husband.
Especially when he calls her Natsumi.
l see now.
Natsumi, didn't know you're such a slut...Natsumi.
Please, stop!
Natsumi, thrust your hips and moan louder.
No, please forgive me...feels good!
Natsumi, l'm going to fuck your ass alright?
Please darling...l love it up my ass!
l'm cuming Natsumi, cuming.
Cum!
Natsumi, can you do the same for me?
Can you fuck my pussy? lt really needs attention.
Amazing!
No, don't, making me cum!
So good!
Good!
lt's so good that it's driving me wild!
Wow, and l thought l was a slut.
Yeah, l've never seen anyone as horny as her.
She's definitely one-of-a-kind.
More, right there...deeper, deeper.
Can l cum inside?
Yes, please!
Natsumi, l feel bad for your husband.
No, don't say that Eriko!
Face the facts, you're a fucking slut.
No, don't say that anymore!
Don't!
l'm sorry Dear.
But...
Forgive me, Dear...
Please.
l believe l can't....no matter how much l liked it or regret it...
Forgive me, Dear.
What's wrong? You look sad.
Huh, that voice!?
Natsumi.
Darling!?
Natsumi, Hayama told me about your past.
l also know that you two had a thing before.
What!?
This trip, l asked Hayama to plan this out.
The hotel incident too.
Why...why did you do it?
l was shocked when l heard about your past.
But l realized that the more l hear about your past, the more excited l get.
l am happy, Natsumi.
Happy that you're a girl who loves sex.
Very happy.
And excited.
Watching you mess around with other men....look, see what it did to me?
Darling.
Why should we pretend to be something we're not?
l want to love the real you and gladly accept your past.
You don't need to pretend anymore, Natsumi.
l believe today is Sasaki.
Boy, l can't wait until l see him fucking you.
Darling...wonder if l can wait that long?
l can't wait.
Darling, it's amazing! lt's so big and hard!
Oh god!
Your fingers are making my ass feel good!
Sir, your wife is great!
Of course, but you gotta try her ass.
Try it out.
P, please!
l, it's so tight, l love it!
Great!
Darling!
C, cuming...Cuming!
Natsumi, you're the best wife.