Hmmm.
l found you.
The train is coming into Station 1.
What!
No!
Oh, no!
l was too late.
lt must be terminated from this planet no matter what.
STATION 1, FIRST EXPERIENCE, ZETSURIN OH
Please pause it. What do you think of this?
lt's been highly modified, but it is definitely a M-77.
He's finally making his move.
Professor Sakinomiya...
Komachi, the professor is no longer the man you know.
lt's unfortunate, but forget him.
The synchronization with the Orgastone is rising to Stage C.
Rin Oh is approaching full operational level.
Commencing combat simulation now.
Come on, baby.
Energy gun!
- President!
Are things going as planned?
Yes, we are stabilized at Stage C.
How far have Tsubame and Hikari gone?
Stage C.
Um, l also got to Stage C.
l see. This may be our limit at this current level.
We should immediately switch partners.
Please wait!
We haven't completely analyzed the Orgastone yet.
Give us more time.
Not possible.
lf Professor Sakinomiya is behind all of the abductions,
he has kidnapped over fifty women.
When you consider the size of their Orgastone, anything could happen.
As soon as possible,
we must be able to reach Stage Oh to maximize Zetsurin Oh's firepower.
Otherwise, we do not have the strength to prevent a calamity.
Komachi, we're depending on you.
Yes.
Nozomi, get a lot hornier.
The power output hasn't gone up.
Play with your nipples more!
Good. Your pussy is getting wet.
Don't be shy. Be audacious!
l'm cumming!
What?
Energy level is zero. We're out of ammo.
Understood. Nozomi, come back in.
Understood.
Seventeen hits out of thirty. Nothing to be thrilled about.
Even though she took many shots.
Rin Oh relies on the shining power of the Orgastone.
lf all those shots missed their mark,
it means Nozomi isn't reaching the necessary orgasm level.
You're also at Stage C, so that means you haven't cum enough either.
Shut up! You're in the same situation.
Yeah, but l'm not sexually experienced.
How do you always do it?
l don't know!
You lie. Teach me.
Stop pestering me!
lt's true, the more sexually excited,
the more infinitely powerful is the energy release of the Orgastone.
How did Professor Sakinomiya change so much after contacting the Orgastone?
Until that is solved, we haven't let men get carelessly close to it.
A message from the Command Room:
An identified train car is at the Central 1st District.
He has arrived.
That's very good!
No!
No, Stop!
Huh? You girls want it too?
Fine, enjoy my great creation to your heart's content!
No!
Ha, ha, ha!
Let's show those who are jealous,
just who really rules over Blue City!
Go!
All of you, this is not a drill.
This is your first combat.
Put your heart into your mission.
- Yes!
Nozomi, you're responsible for Rin Oh. We're depending on you.
Yes!
Make an effort on our behalf too.
We're rooting for you, Nozomi!
Leave it to me!
Everyone to your assigned stations!
S-51 standby for launch!
- Yes, ma'am!
S-51 all systems are active.
Combat generator energy is climbing.
Special Combat Train Car is on stand-by.
All vessel safety systems will be released on take-off.
Communications systems will be BlR online to all stations.
The S-51 operational route has been plotted.
The Orgasm Converter is operational.
Commencing Orgastone energization.
Our condition is at Stage E.
That's not fast enough. Administer aphrodisiac.
Roger.
Aphrodisiac has been administered. Stage E has moved up to Stage D.
The level is increasing.
The energy level has stabilized. The linear thruster is idling at normal.
All systems are go.
Launch S-51 !
- Yes, ma'am!
Seven minutes ETA to target.
What's Rin Oh's status?
Currently at Stage C. Standing by and ready to go.
Decouple Car Number Five.
Tally ho! Launch Rin Oh!
Rin Oh!
That's as far as you go!
l won't let you do whatever you want.
Damn, lshigami. You finished constructing that thing.
But it's just a copy.
lt just goes to show you can't surpass what l create.
Go Rin Ki!
Here l come.
Damn you.
No!
Nozomi!
Orgastone is not resonating.
Rin Oh is not operational.
Tsubame, Hikari, help Rin Oh!
- Yes, ma'am!
lt's so weak. Rin Ki, finish it off!
Large enemy target acquired.
Fire!
Let's repair Rin Oh while we can.
Retreat to Central 4th District.
We can't.
The Emergency Repair System is not operational.
What do you mean?
lt was damaged in the last combat.
l'll have to fix it myself.
Rin Oh's hatch has opened. There's an intruder in the cockpit.
What?
What are you doing there? Civilians are unauthorized.
Can you hear me? lmmediately vacate the machine.
Listen to me!
l see. She was powering this.
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey! You! Listen to what l'm saying!
What's going on? Suddenly appearing during an emergency like this!
Doctor Komachi,
the Orgastone is back to Stage D and rising.
Rin Oh is operational.
What?
Doctor Komachi, can you hear me?
President!
Please continue the battle.
What are you talking about?
He's fucking Nozomi in the middle of this emergency.
But Nozomi has regained consciousness and we're at Stage C.
Yes, but...
lf we can't stop the enemy now, we may never have another chance.
What if we retreat now and then can't stop it?
Understood.
lncoming.
So what?
You must be confused.
l'll explain after we topple him.
Yeah.
Suck it.
Don't tell me you've never sucked cock.
Of course, l have!
Then hurry up. There's no time.
Komachi, you're a pain in the ass. l'll finish you!
- Rin Oh!
Aren't you going to cum?
l'm getting there.
Awesome! Rin Oh is at Stage B and rising.
- Dr. Komachi.
- Yes, sir.
Let's use the Kaiserliner. At this rate, Nozomi will be able to utilize it.
Yes, sir. All stations, commence Operation Z!
Launch the Kaiserliner!
Yes, ma'am!
Nozomi, commence Operation Z.
Go to Transform Formation.
Roger.
All train cars, decouple!
- l'm fucking your pussy for more power.
- What?
W-Wait a sec!
- Engage battle!
Convert that fucking to power.
Rise, Satyr of Justice!
Zetsurin Oh, the Lust Train... transform!
Oh? Look what you've got up your sleeve.
Then l will display my ultimate trick!
There's no time. l have to cum!
It hurts, it hurts so good!
l'm cumming! l'm going to cum!
Kaiserliner Boner!
Die!
Maximum Boner!
Oh, no! What is that?
This is the power of Zetsurin Oh.
We did it!
A job well done.
That damn Zetsurin Oh. Oh, well.
The next time will be your end.
He got away.
Um...
Excuse me!
Huh?
Who are you?