I'm back.
Come in, Aoi, don't be shy.
Sorry for intruding.
Come on, have a seat.
Thanks.
Can I offer you a drink?
I think I'll hate some wine.
Alright, coming right up.
Here you go.
Thanks.
ОК, cheers!
Cheers!
Whatever, those guys from earlier were really boring.
Tell me about it, they were jerks.
Hello! Nice to meet you.
I am a colleague of Yui, Aoi Fukunaga.
You know...
You're pretty cute.
What about your homework?
What?
Were too noisy and it's bothering you?
Little dick. Do you know who pays the rent?
Exactly.
And if I'm bothering you, you can go home first thing tomorrow!
Good boy.
Then you don't have an objection to our chatter, right?
By the way, I need a massage.
Come give  me one...
If you give me a relaxing massage, i will probably fall asleep sooner.
Then you can continue you homework in peace.
Then if you please.
Ah, it feels good.
You can massage my shoulders too.
Can I get in on this too?
Of course.
You're okay with her too, right?
Really?
In that case...
Oh my!
My breasts are weighing my shoulder muscles down, making them sore.
So, can I entrust them to you, little bro?
Come on, don't just stand there, come over here.
That's good, keep going.
Don't be afraid, you can massage me harder.
Yeah, like that.
Use your palms effectively, press harder when you caress me.
Hey!
Yui, do you want to do it too?
You've got big breasts, so it uncomfortable, right?
Yeah, bearably...
So? It feels good, doesn't it?
Нey! Little bro...
Yui, your brother's penis is hard as a rock.
Huh?
Look at this!
I see that, but I'm still your sister!
He can't help it, boys are like that at his age. They all have dirty thoughts, right?
Hurry up and continue with the massage, you nasty pervert.
I'll take off your skirt before it gets wrinkled.
You really seem to enjoy it when she touches you.
How can you be like this in front of somebody?
To start with, you are a virgin.
Don't tell me you masturbate while I'm sleeping.
It's useless to lie.
You masturbate while thinking of your sister, don't you?
If you aren't honest, I'll stop.
Pervert!
Aoi, rub him harder.
Allright.
Hey you, who told you to stop?
It seems like he's about ready to cum.
As expected of a young boy, his sperm is delicious.
It's my turn this time to massage you.
You just came and you still have a hard-on.
Horny asshole!
Come on Yui, help me.
We have to thank him for the massage.
I guess I don't have a choice than.
So?
Does it feel good?
We'll make you feel even better.
I'm feeling nipples on mine.
It's so great!
Are you ready? You can cum whenever.
Ejaculate on your sister's boobs!
Shoot it out, you pervert!
It's my turn!
This is the second time you've cum there's still so much.
You really are the worst pervert.
It's your turn to make me feel good.
It's amazing how fast you're recovering.
It's good.
Oh yeah, it's good.
Come on, caress my breasts, massage them.
Yeah, just like that.
It feels great, your cock's getting bigger and bigger.
More, push it in deeper!
Keep going, deeper and deeper!
Harder, do it harder!
Right there, keep going like that.
Yeah, just like that.
Do it faster.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's good, so good!
Yui, don't play by yourself, come over here and join us.
But i can't, he's my brother.
You aren't blood related.
Genetically speaking, you are strangers.
Besides, it's obvious you are attracted to each other.
You should strengthen your relationship.
Look, Yui's your pussy has been waiting for your penis.
Are you scared?
Don't worry, your sister's really wet.
See? I can put two fingers in if I want.
Do you hear these dirty sounds? And this smell..?
Aoi...
Yui, you seem to be enjoying this.
Not my ears!
Нey, my fingers alone aren't enough, right?
I...
Where do you want him to stick his thing?
My pussy...
Ask your brother clearly.
Put your dick in me...
I beg you, I beg you!
Do you understand, little bro?
It's amazing...
Your cock is hot and it feels so good!
Yui, will you cum?
Yes!
I'll cum, I'll cum!
Yiu, i want you to cum.
Yeah, I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
I will come with my brother's penis!
I can't hold it anymore!
It's coming, I'm cumming!
This isn't the end yet.
Me or Yui, choose the pussy you want.
It's good!
Like this, it's good!
Come on, give it to me, too!
Yui, it seems you're already addicted to your brother's cock.
But it's so good!
Please, cum inside me.
Oh yeah, from behind!
No, it's too good, good, good, you're in my womb, I'm going to cum!
Lick my pussy, it's already so wet.
It's alright, okay gimme more.
It feels good everywhere on my body!
So, it's good?
I'll help make you feel even better.
No, I can't take much more, it feels so good!
I can't believe it feels even better now!
It seems you can't restrain yourself anymore.
You can do it, shoot all your cum inside your sister.
I'll cum..!
I'm cumming, cumming.
Together, cum with me.
I'll cumming.
It's shooting out, I feel so much of it!
Aoi, we should stop for tonight.
You're right, that's probably the best thing to do.
Good night.
I'll sleep with you.
Oh, I almost forgot!
Once again, make love together!
I hope you enjoyed this and found the translation Okay-ish
Thanks to Zèro fansub for the original french translation :)