I'm sorry for calling you like this.
There's something intriguing me.
Um.., for now why don't you take off your clothes?
No~, please don't put on a strange face like that.
I'm an infirmary doctor, right?
Don't worry, there's only the two of us in here.
Come on, quicky..quickly...
Issho ni Ecchi
W
It's okay, especially if I'm gonna do it for you
Right..right, you can leave your pants just like that.
Is is possible that your penis is getting big?
It's okay, you don't have to worry. It's proof that you're a healthy boy.
Then, It's my fault too that you're feeling that way.
Right now, I'll do it especially for you.
Maybe it's embarrassing if only you show it to me,
then I'll have to show it to you, right?
Don't be nervous like that.
Just leave it to me.
Here, It feels soft and feels good doesn't it?
Is it your first time doing it like this with breasts?
Your penis is getting hot.
It's beating around.
Did you know that my nipples are getting hard as well?
My nipples are starting to feel good...
From the top of your penis it's letting out some pervert juice.
It's getting sodden in here.
Eh, you're gonna come?
It's okay, whenever you want to come out, just let it out on me.
On my face or my breasts, just let it out as you like!
You're cumming a lot...
My stomach is getting full too.
After this, let me feel good too alright?
Do I have to spread my legs and show it?
Don't look at it so closely, okay.
It's embarrassing...
That's right, It's letting out a perverted sound from it.
It's drenched.
After doing it with your penis, It's turning me on.
It's tapping around..It's tapping around in there...
It's rubbing around!
That's right, inside of me, it feels warm doesn't it?
Just move it around as you like.
No way, you're doing it too good!
The feeling of your finger is...
It's feeling roughly around inside...
Look, I'm squeezing my own breast.
'Cause It's feels so good and I can't hold it!
I'm sorry, for being perverted like this!
You can't, you can't infiltrate so deep with your finger!
It's making pervert juice leak out.
I can endure it~!
Please, be more rough with me!
Please mess with my pussy inside!
It feels good...
In there...
If you're teasing  my clitoris-
I'm gonna get crazy inside myself~!!
It's cum..It's gonna cum...
Can I.. can I cum?
It's great! It's great!!
It's great to cum!
My pussy is..chewy..chewing around...
Cumming..I'm gonna cum, okay?
I'm cumming..It's because you're so good...
No, I'm not peeing with it...
It always looks that way when I'm cumming with myself.
Is it strange?
Um..I can't..hold it anymore.
It's the same for you too, right?
Then, let's do it together for the last time.
There, It's okay. Just put your hot penis inside of my pussy.
Hey, just do it quickly!
It's embarrassing when posing like this,
It's inside..your penis is inside the deepest part of my pussy.
It's okay..move it-
No way, suddenly you're getting rough...
I can't...
You can't hold it anymore?
It's okay, I'm happy for you to do something like this.
It's tapping around..your penis is tapping around inside of my pussy.
It's hot-
It feels good..It feels good-
More..I want it more...
It's amazing!
It's touches inside, the perverted sound is-
My ass is also hitting around...
I'm..inside of me...
For being pervert..like this...
It's not like that.
It's not usually like me.
It's true.
Today is special...
Your penis is getting big...
You're gonna cum again, right?
It's fine, today you can do it...
With this way..inside of...
Please~! Inside of my pervert pussy..on my ero-pussy....
sperm..semen..let it spread on me~!!
I can't hold it...
I'm..I'm..I can't!
No!!
No..you can't-
Hey, I didn't think that you were rough with something like this.
I don't dislike you about that.
It feels so good.
Ah, I'd already forgot the reason I called you...
The truth is..my little sister has a crush on you.
Did it startle you?
It's because you're one of my students from here,
I'm intrigued by how you look...
But, my little sister isn't a honest person.
So a big sister like me, should help her a little.
If you like, please come into the infirmary again after school tomorrow.
My little sister would be there at that time.
W
Issho ni Ecchi
Would you like..to do it..with me?
No, we can't do something like this in the infirmary-
Even if you say that, I can't...
I can't hold it anymore...
No way, my pervert juice is flowing out...
It's too rough, It can be bad habit.
Someone's gonna see me doing something like this.
My breasts and even my downside is showing like this,with a pervert view of it.
No, I said something like that, It's turning me on more.
I feel..like my body is getting hot...
Please, look at it...
Look at all of my embarrassing things...
My nipples are getting hard like this!
My special thing is drenched like that.
I think it can fit three fingers inside of it.
No, It can't hold it...
Feels good..It's really feels good...
It feels good...
Good...
Cumming..I'm gonna cum~!
Why is someone like you in here?!
Is it possible..that you were watching it all along?
What's with your strange face?
You must think that I'm some kind of pervert, right?
It's okay, It's fine for you to laugh at me!
It turns you on?
How foolish!
That's because..you're watching it...
That's expected of course..It can make you feel excited...
Is it true? Watching the pervert side of me is making your penis getting big?
Then, why don't you take off your clothes?
It's embarrassing if only me is in this situation.
Just quickly!
No way, you've already this big?
Feet? You want me to do it with my feet?
Isn't gonna be hurt?
No..It's really hot...
More strongly?
Like this?
I didn't even know that rubbing penis with feet can make a penis feel excited.
It's getting big again.
It's not like that I'm talking about myself, but you're the same kind of pervert as I am.
You're looking at my breasts as we speak now.
It's really lewd, isn't?
I'm sure that you're always think about doing something like this, right?
You're thinking that my feet would rub and keep teasing your penis.
No way, something is coming out...coming out from your penis.
Isn't this what you first called cum?
Of course I know something like that!
I'm just startled by looking at it.
It's drenched in there, my socks are getting wet as well.
It's lewdness...
I have to punish you for making my socks dirty, right?
There, you're feeling it when my feet is rubbing on your penis, right?
Just when I'm rubbing at the tip of your penis, It feels like your juice is coming out.
If your penis is beating like this,
If you're getting excited with this, I'm gonna be crazy with myself.
It's okay, just keep your cum from the tip of your penis flowing out like that.
It's gonna feel good that way.
Here, you want to let it out don't you?
Do you want to make my white feet dirty like this?
You want to make a stain on my socks, right?
No way, hmph...!
Let me know if you're gonna cum!
With a lot like this, I don't even wanna know how much you hold it up.
Wait a minute, you're still big as before?
You want to cum more?
I have somthing to ask you.
Do you..want to do it..with me?
I just can't hold it anymore!
Eh, um...
There's something I want to tell you.
I'm..honestly..this is the first time for me.
That's why..please be gentle with me.
What is it? It's not something shocked like that?
I don't have a choice, okay. I've always been doing it with myself...
I don't even try it with any boys around me.
You..you're gonna put it inside, right?
Slowly, okay..? Slowly, right..?
Please, do it more slowly...
It's going inside! It hurts!!
It's not possible to let my power go just like that!
It hurts, you know?!
Your penis is infiltrating my pussy-
I'm having sex..I'm having sex in here with you.
I'm feeling strange, my body feels hot and fluffy inside.
It's fine, If you want to move it more inside...
Move it as you like...
Amazing, in there..my pussy feels like it's gonna cum already!
No..even if it's my first time,
my pussy..my pussy gonna cumming!
With this..I'm gonna be seen as lewd girl.
It gonna feels good...
It's your fault!
Take responsibility until the end of it!
Amazing...
Your penis feels hot and hard,
No-
It feels different when I'm doing it with myself.
It feels good..It feels good...
More..I want more of it...
I'm gonna cum..cum too...
Great..It's great!!
I'm..I'm..I can't hold it!!
It's really it, isn't it? Having sex with boys like you.
I really didn't expect something like this would happen.
Onee-chan...
Why?!
Hm..Isn't it that I reminded you to called me Sensei when we're at school?
That's not the point right now!
The truth is, I've always know that you were masturbating in the infirmary.
I wanted to punish you by sending him to look after you.
It looks like there's so much love overflowing in here...
Hey, why don't you come at our house next Saturday?
Why's that?
You know, I also feel intrigued with him.
Next time, let's have fun with the three of us.
W
Issho ni Ecchi
We're gonna show all of our perverted
side for you
W
Onee-chan, do you really want us to take a bath with this guy?
You can't say something like "this guy", okay?
Aren't you forgetting that before you had sex with him, right?
Wait-
Hey, please look at us.
We'll show you all of our perverted side to you.
No way, It's embarrassing doing something like this...
Maron-chan, aren't your breasts getting big?
And your body is also silky & smooth.
Don't say something strange like that...
Onee-chan's body is more-
No, we can't do something like this as both woman...
Even if you said it like that, but I'm sure you want it isn't?
Not..in there..you can't!
As I thought, your drenched in here.
It's a lie..something..like that...
It's fine to be honest with yourself.
It's okay to be more lewd.
Here, why don't you touch my pussy as well.
Amazing, Onee-chan's pussy is hot...
It's my first time doing it with other girls.
Maron-chan's finger is really gentle...
Hey..let's feels good together?
Onee-chan...
It's coming out again...
I'm doing something perverted with Onee-chan.
I feel like I'm being infiltrated with a penis...
Maron-chan, your body is getting hot-
If you move your finger that roughly, then I'm gonna feel it too.
Onee-chan..I'm..I'm gonna cum..cumming soon...
It's okay, I'll let you cum with me...
Maron-chan, you're so cute.
It's coming out...
There, as you can see, he's already that big, It seems he can't hold it anymore.
No way..hmph...
The next time, we'll make you feel good.
Looks like you've come already.
Did the pressure get too high?
Onee-chan, was the first cum from his penis really good?
It's really delicious.
Can I..lick it too?
It's fine, let's do some fellatio together.
You should be grateful with that!
For cute sisters like us doing something like this for you.
Maron-chan, you're doing good on licking penis.
I'm not sure if this your first time...
It's my first time-
Licking something like this, It's embarrassing to me.
Even though I'm just licking at a penis like this, my body is feeling hot as well.
I feel something strange as well...
Even though, It's where the pee comes from...
But I'm licking all around it...
Licking at something hot like this...
I can't hold it anymore...
I'll squeeze my breast too.
Sorry..Onee-chan..but I'm already like this...
I'm even touching my pussy too...
Maron-chan, If you say something like that...
This penis can't hold it anymore.
It's true, It's still getting big as well.
We're gonna be covered with the cum,
and it's gonna be sticky around...
It's okay, you can spread it on our face or even in our mouth too.
Spread all your sperm..semen on us!!
Amazing, It's sticky and smells of something lewd inside it.
But Onee-chan, this penis is still as hard as before.
That's true, It's still gonna cum a lot.
Maron-chan had already came out, then I'll be the next one.
It's little embarrasing to be seen with Ma..Maron-chan when I'm doing something like this.
But..I can't..I can't hold it anymore...
Hey, please make me feel good as well.
Please lick at my perverted thing...
Right..please be more deep with it.
You can..drink all of my pervert juice...
No way, It's amazing even though it just came a while ago.
It's hitting on the deep-
It's tapping around the inside of my womb.
Please, can you move it too?
Move around inside of my pussy...
Tha..That's really feels good!
No..I'm being seen with Maron-chan at doing perverted thing like this.
No~!!
Onee-chan, It's really turning me on...
Hey, do you think Onee-chan's better than me?
You can do it with me.
Whether it's my pussy or ass as well, you can do it!
My ass..my ass is teasing with you~!
No way, It's tapping..tapping around inside of it.
It's something new for me...
Look..my breast is swinging around like balloons.
You really want..want to see something perverted of me, right?
It's okay, you can look at our breasts, pussy or even ass too...
Even if It's an embarrassing thing or perverted thing too, we're gonna show it all to you.
Cumming..aren't you..you're gonna cum, right?
It's fine, you can do it inside..inside of my pussy!
You can do it to me as well-
Let it out inside!
Cumming..cumming..alot of it!
My juice is flowing on your face...
Sorry..I'm so..sorry...
No~!!!
Then, the next one...
The next would be me.
I'm gonna put it in, okay.
The next is me, right.
Hey, what's wrong? It isn't over this way, you know?
That's right we're gonna be doing it from morning 'till dusk.
Issho ni Ecchi.