~Miyazawa Akina Chapter~
New Gene 00 H-Subs
Ha? You're just looking at me with bothersome's face, right?
I can see it clearly in my eyes.
E, what's my business in here?
A~, right..right.
Tonight was our champion's celebration in Inter High,
so we're just finished gathering around.
And then....
I don't have any place to go,
then I realize that your place is around here....
I know it's bothering you,
even for a day please let me stay at your place.
Please....
Ah~, I really grateful to you.
If you're not around here, I just can't think where I have to go.
A, can I borrow that shirt?
I don't bring any change right now.
Thank you.
When I change, I'll use toilet, right.
A, don't ever try to take a peep.
Hm..you're living here around, right.
Look, it's fit on me.
What's wrong with you? You're face is red.
Is it possible you're shy, because it's been a while not seeing me?
Look..look....
I understand right now, I'm disturbing you a moment ago.
Hey, let me see when your doing with yourself.
Don't say something formal like that.
Is it from me, that I want to see it myself, right?
A, that's right....
Look at it, does you feel something stimulate already?
Hey..let me see yourself doing it.
Did I'm not stimulated you enough?
Well, as apology because disturbing you,
I'll help you doing it then.
This is..men's thing?
Is it like this, doing it?
It's great, getting hard already.
Something wet is going out from it.
Is it, what you called feeling good?
I see....
Eh, with my breast?
It's not a matter though....
What..what is it? You're not likely happy,
when look at my breast, right.
Then, I'll do it.
You're feeling good with this?
Wait, not like this.
It's embarrassing.
No..no....
No..don't do it....
No..don't bullying me like that....
If you're moving like that....
No....
My breast gonna be break out....
It's great..my breast feeling your thing already.
Doing it with my mouth?
You're just cruel,
I had to drink it all, you know.
Hey, want to continue it?
If it's with you....
It's fine.
But over there, I just had sweat from my match.
That's why..that place....
It's dirty..but, you lick on it....
Eh, I don't say something like that.
No, don't....
Don't..if you're doing like that,
I just want your thing to be inside of me.
Hm..the way you're doing it,
make me can't hold myself again.
Here..is it okay in here?
I make myself doing something dirty, right.
With you..I want to make it good.
It's fine, I just startled at it.
You can't hold it off? You want insert it....
It's fine, just hurt a little.
No, it's not like that.
I crying happy, because I'm doing it for the first time with you.
It's fine, just moving it as before.
How is it, does it feel's good?
It's great, I'm moving it into myself.
It's too good, no..don't....
I'm completely strange right now..even in my head....
Coming out..It's coming out..I'm gonna coming out....
You're coming inside of me....
Sorry, just let me rest a bit.
Don't do it, we're just coming out already.
I can't hold it....
Don't....
Please don't bullying me.
No, It's not like that.
I'm not that indecent....
No..don't, I'm gonna coming out.
I'm gonna coming out from there.
Coming..it's coming out....
Gezz, idiot.
Because of you, I just look like an indecent girl.
That's why..you're..bullying me....
Did I told you to make an H's thing more with me?
Idiot.
It's great, your thing scrapings in the deepest part of me.
Right..more,,more like that.
No..is it like this?
You're..you're okay with this?
Don't..because of me we're doing something like this.
No..it's coming out....
No, you're doing it..from behind....
It..it feel's good.
No, over there is feeling good already.
It's out..it's coming out....
Don't..my head gonna be strange.
Don't, don't stop it.
Yes, doing it more slowly....
Let me feel your thing.
You're really like breast, right.
More slowly....
Don't, I'm gonna die..it's gonna coming out.
I'm gonna be strange!
My breast..I'm licking at my own breast....
Great, it feel's great....
No..it's feeling good already.
I like it..I really like it.
It's deep..it's hit my deepest thing....
Doing it hard like this,
I really like it....
More..I want more....
No, it's not that indecent..I'm fall in love with you.
Let us come toghether.
No, I can't hold it.
Come, let's coming out together.
Inside, let it come inside of me.
Let it all come inside of me.
It's great, your thing is scrapings inside all of my thing.
Let it out, let it out inside of me!
You're not satisfied already?
Come out..come out....
With a looked like this, it's embarrassing.
It's coming out again, let it all coming out!
Next time..I want you to show me,
how you're doing it yourself, right.
Gezz, you're stingy.
But, if it's your lover..you're gonna let it, right.
What I want to say, if I'm your lover..
you're gonna let me see, when you're doing it with yourself right?
Did I'm not good enough?
You're not gonna let me see it?
I'm happy!
That time, I'll let you see when I'm doing it with myself.
Let's feeling good together, right.