My name is Natsukawa Hina.
I’m on my way to visit my grandmother, who just fell ill.
I moved to the city and it’s been years since I’ve been back to my hometown.
My grandmother’s illness is apparently nothing big, so it’s just a friendly visit.
But THIS is my real problem.
Back in my life after a long absence.
He has this silly dream of becoming a farmer.
But, ah well. Guess I’d better do my best to help out!
And so,
SubDESU
-H
Presents
Isshoni H Shiyo!
Natsukawa Hina's arc, folks.
So, what do you do on your days off?
I'm learning how to be a fortune teller!
How’s that?
It’s lots of fun.
Hey, you, during all the time I haven’t seen you, you seem to have become quite the lazy-ass.
Natsukawa Plan, part 1:
If ya don’t work, ya don’t eat.
You should know that expression.
Come on. Eating food don’t come as easy as ya think!
Come on, let’s go to the field!
It’s all round and smooth - growing mighty nice.
All right! Let’s pick ‘em all!
Let’s work real hard, okay?
What the hell’re ya doing? You sure are being half-assed.
Natsukawa Plan, part 4:
Men should be strong.
With such a weak lower back like that, you’ll never find yourself a wife.
What’s wrong? Ya look kind of glum.
Come on, let’s gather ‘em up!
Ah, yeah, my clothes got dirty. Wanna take a swim?
What’s with that scared look?
Natsukawa Plan, part 7:
Those with dirty bodies aren't fit to enter a house.
With that mud on your body, I won’t let’cha go home.
Aw, please. It’s fine.
It’s hot today so our clothes will dry quickly.
And let’s wash the daikon while we’re at it!
Umph...
Whee!
What’s wrong?
Take your clothes off and get in fast.
Aw, please. Why’re you being so shy?
We used to bathe together all the time when we were kids!
Come on. Just take it off.
You... Could it be... You’re excited from seeing me naked?
Look, look!
I used to be so tiny and now I’m big, ain’t I?
Take a good look.
Y-You don’t need to apologize.
I thought it wasn’t a big deal, but I guess what I’m doing is kind of extreme.
Hope I didn’t startle you.
Did I scare you?
Wait a minute.
Natsukawa Plan, part 8:
Once you start something, see it through to the end.
You can touch me more.
Uh, er, sorry about that.
Your... thing... It’s so big and hard.
It used to be so tiny and cute, but now it’s so manly.
It's got so hard and thick.
You want me to suck it?
Don’t be silly!
That’s just too...
What?
'Remember Natsukawa Plan, part 12'?
Natsukawa Plan, part 12: Try anything that comes your way.
Right?
Eh? You mean THIS?
Fine, I get it.
I’ll do it.
Um... Just don’t stare at me, okay?
Um...
Does this feel good?
Can it really?
In that case, how does this feel?
Something’s coming out!
I couldn’t drink it all.
My glasses are all sticky.
How was that?
How was your cousin’s technique? Felt good?
Then I guess we should get going.
What?
You still haven’t pleasured me yet?
Oh, don’t worry about me.
Wh-What are you doing?
No...
Don’t...
Not so sudden...
Don’t stare at it.
You’re embarrassing me.
Wait...
Don’t lick such a nasty place.
All the way inside... It’s touching...
A cucumber?
What are you... You’re not...!
Stupid! Stop!
Don’t put it in so deep!
Inside of me... there’s a cucumber...
A cucumber penis is scraping inside me!
It feels... so good!
Stop... or I’ll really...
Not so rough...
I’ll cum...
Something’s coming...
Wait... Wait, please!
This’s embarrassing.
It feels like I’m gonna pee.
Stop moving your hand...
You idiot. You didn’t stop, so I pissed myself.
But you came so much just then.
You’re hard again?
It’s okay.
We’ve gone this far already.
We might as well finish it.
It’s a bit embarrassing when I'm so old, so I didn’t tell you...
But I’ve never had sex before.
Be gentle, okay?
Put it in gently, okay?
Put it in slowly.
Ow...
D-Don’t stop
I’ll be okay.
It’s inside.
My insides feel so full.
You’re so thick.
It’s okay. Go ahead and move.
Wait, slower!
It’s okay.
This feel good?
Does it feel good to you?
I’m glad.
I think I’m used to it now.
You can move more now.
Natsukawa Plan, part 9:
'Carry out all activities with full force.'
So please.
Harder, fuck me harder!
So rough!
This is my first time, but it feels so good!
This is the first time I’ve felt this great!
All the way in my pussy, there’s a cock hitting so deep!
That’s good. Very good.
Stay inside and...
So hot... It’s so hot!
My insides... are so hot!
Natsukawa Plan, part 15:
Men and women should be treated equally.
You were the one to move last time.
So this time it’s my turn.
You’re harder than before.
Right about here?
D-Don’t do that!
It’s my turn now!
But I said!
This time, I’m supposed to move.
Yes. You just stay lying there.
Let’s see... like this...
It feels different... Hitting a different place from before.
How is it?
Feels good?
It feels good for me!
Oh yes!
Let’s move together!
So rough!
Oh...
Wh-What?
My insides are also moving?
Oh no! I’m scared!
Y-You idiot.
Stop staring at me like that.
It’s gotten pretty late, huh.
Come on, let’s go back fast.
Ow, it still stings.
Men sure are cruel.
Natsukawa Plan, part 13:
Men should take responsibility for their actions.
So you need to look after me to the end.
So, let’s have sex again soon!