~Takai Haruka Chapter~
New Gene 00 H-Subs
Go..good morning, senior.
This is a souvenir.
Yes, excuse me.
There's a cooler, that's why it's refreshing.
As I thought of you, senior.
Senior?
Why don't we eat the souvenir,
I bought delicious cream cake.
So..sorry!
I'm making dirty at senior's room.
Let me borrow some swab-cloth or something?
Gezz, senior is too kind with me.
Senior, you don't eat it?
E, you want this?
But, I had eat this with my mouth....
Do you really want this thing?
Well, there's nothing I can do.
Right, here it is.
A, the cream....
Senior.
Please don't touch my nipple,
don't bullying me like this.
My nipple is getting hard.
Please don't say something like that.
No, please don't bullying me like that.
Please don't lick it like that.
I'm get the feeling alreday....
I'm loosing my strenght.
If you're licking more than this....
Please don't eat it.
Senior....
If you're crumpling like this, I'm....
Yes, I want to feeling good more than this.
It's embarrassing.
Your finger..inside my..
Yes, it's feeling good.
Se..Senior....
Yes, that's feel's good.
Coming out....
Coming out..I can't hold it.
Coming out..it's coming out!
This is Senior's thing....
It's really hot and it's getting hard.
It's my first time though,
but i'll try my best.
Do you feel's good?
Yes?
With my breast?
Is..is it like this?
Yes, I'll start moving it.
Does it feel's good, Senior?
Yes, is it like this?
Did you feel's good?
I'm kind of embarrassing.
My ears....
Wait..wait, don't.
I'm feeling too good.
Please stop doing like that.
My breast feeling good.
Senior, I'm embarrassed with a looked like this.
Senior's finger, it's feeling good.
Yes, if compared when doing with myself it's feeling more good.
Just can't be a compared thing.
That's..if you're licking at that place....
It's dirty.
My butt's hole feeling good.
It's feeling to good.
I'm going to be strange already!
Senior, let me lick your thing too.
Does your butt feel's good?
Senior's butt hole,
let me more play with it.
I'll make you feeling more good.
My waist is moving itself.
This indecent feeling won't stop!
Senior, I can't hold it anymore.
Yes, inside my wet's thing,
let Senior's thing inside of it.
It's fine,
but it's my first time.
Please do it little slower.
It's going in....
It's fine,
Senior's thing already inside of it.
I can feel you inside of me.
I'm feeling happy.
Please moving slower.
It feel's good.
It's my first time, but I'd already feel's it.
Get in slower, right.
It's in..it's inside....
It's against my deepest thing.
It's really great.
Inside..inside of....
My thing's getting soaked as your thing's moving inside it.
My waist is moving by itself.
Senior, I don't even know myself right now.
Break out..it's gonna break out.
Senior's thing is going inside the deepest part of it.
It feel's good, just can't stop it.
My indecent's place is in sight like this.
No, I'm feeling it already.
Senior, I love you..really love you.
Yes, let it come out a lot of it.
Let it out inside my thing.
Se..Senior, I can't....
Coming out..Senior..it's gonna coming out.
Senior, let's coming out together.
It's coming out..inside my thing,
a lot of Senior's sperm is coming out.
Because of Senior's sperm my stomach is full.
I'm happy, because Senior is love me that much.
From today let's having H together a lot, right.