Dispatch working girls, cleaning house, washing, & it can do anything.
World Maid Association
If you call right now, it's free for a week.
World Maid Association is,
waiting for you to call to be our master.
Leave your room to us to make it more brighter.
Not only cleaning it.
All of our master cloth's laundy will be clean & feel refreshed.
Of course for cooking too, leave it to us.
You can enjoy food which filled with our love.
Then for this campaign program
You can try it for a week with free.
Master, we're at World Maid Association will be wait for your call.
That's why, let's having H together.
~Tsuji Suzuran Chapter~
New Gene 00 H-Subs
Pleased to meet you.
From today, I'll live with master for taking care all of your needed.
Your personal maid, Tsuji Suzuran.
Whatever anything you need, please let me to know.
It look's like you don't clean up your room for a long time.
But from the time I come, you can rest assure.
Master.
Please leave it to Tsuzuran!
Cleaning, washing, & cooking is a must.
If it's your wish, I could prepare you some packed lunch too.
What's wrong, Master?
Right, now let me start working on my my job.
Ha~, please stop!
I'm gonna be the laundry!
Why it's always end like this?
Even though I'm working hard for master,
but all I do is make it worse than before.
I'm just gonna be Master's burden too.
Master....
Thank you so much.
I just want to be some help for Master.
No, I'll definitely could make you satisfied.
I, I'm doing it again!
Is there, is there anything for clean it?
Right, handkerchief that I receive for a moment ago.
Surely around here....
Huh~, it's strange....
I'm sure it's flying around here....
Mister handkerchief, where are you?
Ah, it's dropped in here.
Then, Master.
Could you put down your pants?
Don't refrain yourself, leave everything to Tsuzuran!
It's hurts....
Ma, Master!
My bad!
I beg your pardon,
for doing something like this twice....
For the time being, could you put down your underwear?
Master's precious thing is getting hot for sure.
Would you let me cooled it down  with my mouth?
I'm really are useless maid after all.
Eh? Right, thank you very much.
Then please excuse me.
Is my mouth is feeling good?
Master....
If that's what master want....
Go ahead, Master.
If you're okay with my breast, please enjoy yourself.
Master~
Suddenly, doing like this....
Right, since I was little only my breast were big....
No, doing something like that with my nipple....
Eh? Doing it with my breast to Master's thing?
Is it like this?
Is it something new for me.
With doing like this, did Master feeling good?
Right, this time make it stand & rubbing it?
Is it like this? Did Master feeling good with this?
I feel my breast feeling paralyzed & having strange feeling around it.
It's hot.
It posses intensive scent, it's bitter.
Master, suddenly I'm getting strange.
I'm getting muddy.
Right!
Err, did you satisfied already?
Well....
What I should do then?
Doing it with myself?
Once I'm doing it, but....
Don't stare it that hard, okay.
It's embarrassing.
Master, what're you doing?
That's because for a short time ago with Master's thing....
It's embarrassing~
Stare at something like this....
It's embarrassing, but I'm getting stare of it.
That's impossible, Master.
I understand, if it's for Master Tsuzuran will do anything.
Master, the banana....
It's going into my deepest thing.
No, not like that!
Master, no..no....
It's coming, coming out!
Master, if you're bullying me when I clean up it's....
No..No, don't do that.
No, It's dirty.
With a looked like this....
Please wait....
Not like this, it's all of a sudden....
It's wonderful....
Master's thing it's big..big....
It's great..Master..Master....
It's, It's feel good.
Feel's good, It's good.
Master's big thing, feel's good.
Master....
No..coming out..it's gonna coming out.
It's my limit....
I'm already at my limit..Master....
Please allowed me to come out.
It's coming out....
It's already coming out.
No, it's gonna break out.
Master..Master....
Tsuzuran gonna break out..it's gonna break out....
Please, get it a little slower.
A little slower, so I can feel Master's thing too.
It's feel good.
Master, I can't take it anymore.
More than this, I'm gonna die soon.
No, you can't thrust in it!
No, It's coming out.
Coming out!
Gonna coming out, I'm gonna die!
It's coming out!
It's a lot..a lot of....
Master's sprem, it's coming a lot of them.
Err, Master....
Please forgive me amoment ago.
If Master not satisfied already,
please use & play with my body untill you're satisfied.
This time for sure, I'll make Master satisfied.
What it's feel, Master? Did Tsuzuran's thing feel's good?
Please let coming it out.
Did you see it, Master?
My thing..dirty sound coming out from it.
It's feel dood.
It's alright, don't hesitate.
Inside my thing..Master's thing it's thumping up.
Please let it coming a lot.
Master?
No, don't do that.
Right now please let me Master's feel....
No, you're bullying me.
I'm coming out..Master, you're bullying me.
No, it's coming out, no.
Master's banana thing,
please let Tsuzuran....
Let Tsuzuran make Master feel's good instead....
Master....
I'll do my best.
How is it feel?
My thing is thumping at it.
Master's thing it's been swallowed by it.
Then like this....
No, not only inside my thing....
All of my skin too....
It can't wait at all.
Let it out, please let it out.
Inside my thing, please let thumping it hard.
Please let my thing swallow your sperm.
No, I can't hold it on. Please let it out.
Let it come together, Master.
Please let it out inside Tsuzuran's thing, so you can satisfied.
It's coming out..it's gonna coming out.
Together, a lot of....
Coming out, let it out, Master.
It's coming out!
Master, did satisfied already?
Thank you so much.
Then once again,
from today 'till next week. Pleased to meet you.
Then~, let this room get cleaned first....
Is it possibly this night too....