My name is Futaba Yuuki!
I'm about to go meet Onii-chan! But...
It's been five years since he left home, so I'm a bit nervous.
Although I call him "Onii-chan,"
we're both children from our parents' previous marriages,
so we're not blood related.
Although while he was still at home, we were always together.
So we're supposed to be close siblings, but...
For some reason, he doesn't return home anymore!
He's even stopped contacting us!
Mom and Dad are getting worried,
and they say things like: "a wicked woman must be tricking him",
or, that he's joined a criminal organization!
That's why I'm visiting him to check up on how he's doing!
So, let's: "Isshono H Shiyo! Futaba Yuuki's Arc
SubDESU
-H
Presents
Long time no see.
Are you surprised?
What's with that expression?
Did you forget that I was coming?
That's good.
It wouldn't have been nice if you'd forgotten
that I was coming from afar to visit my recluse brother, would it?
Well, nevermind that. Can I come in?
Sorry to intrude!
This is Onii-chan's room?
No sign of him cooking for himself...
No sign of a woman, either!
No sign of anything criminal, either!
Right!
Here you go.
Note: Since we haven't heard from you, we've sent Yuuki as an investigator on how you're doing. You two have a nice time.
So, I'm going to be staying over for a while.
I didn't know that rooms were so small and dirty in the city!
Oh, right. It's dirty because of Onii-chan, isn't it?
It can't be helped, I've gotta do something since I'm staying for free.
Whew, finally done!
Oh, Onii-chan. The bath is ready, so please go ahead!
I'll make something for dinner!
Onii-chan!
You should come home sometimes!
Everyone is really worried about you.
Hey, are you listening to Yuuki?
Onii-chan! I'll wash your back!
I'm coming in!
Hey Onii-chan, hurry up and get out! I'll wash your back.
What's wrong?
C'mon! Get out!
We used to take baths together like this, didn't we?
I'm going to do the front now.
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
It's been five years, so my breasts have gotten larger!
Like I said, you haven't been home in five years, right?
So, Onii-chan...
W-What?!
I'm getting wet!
Geez, Onii-chan! You meanie!
I'm soaking wet!
Oh well. I'll just join you in the bath, then.
Here, please wash my back too!
Onii-chan?
Huh? Pants?
R-Right, I should take them off, too.
Huh? Eh?! You'll take them off for me?!
I-It's okay, Yuuki can do it by herself!
You really want to take them off?
O-Okay, if you want to do it that much...
Is that okay?
Then please wash me, Onii-chan.
That felt great!
Thanks, Onii-chan!
Eh?!
F-From the front as well?
I-I'm fine!
I can do the front myself!
B-But I don't want to cause anymore inconvenience for you...
Geez! Fine then, if you insist...
It's a bit embarrassing...
You're going to wash me with that?
That would work better? I see...
Then please begin with my hands...
Onii-chan...!
Onii-chan-! That feels strange!
I-I'll do that myself!
W-What are you doing?!
Onii-chan-! Don't put your fingers inside me or Yuuki will lose it!
It'll feel too good!
No-! Don't do that! You can't-!
No! Onii-chan, s-something is coming! Onii-chan!
No! D-Don't do that!
No! Yuuki will lose it! She really will-!
Onii-chan, Onii-chan!
That felt amazing, Onii-chan...
Did I cum? Is that what cumming is?
Onii-chan?
Sure, it's Yuuki's turn to wash you.
But what am I supposed to do?
L-Like this?
A-Are you okay?!
H-How is it? Am I doing it properly?
Onii-chan, does this feel good?
Eh? With my mouth?!
O-Okay, I'll try...
How is it?
Eh?
Okay then...
I-I'm sorry! Did it hurt?
A-Are you okay, Onii-chan? I-I'm sorry I bit-!
Onii-chan...?
What should Yuuki do?
Y-Yes! I'll do anything! Just say it!
Is this okay? Then I'll move them...
Does it feel good? It doesn't hurt, right?
I'm glad, please feel better.
My nipples are getting paralyzed, it feels strange...
What-?
Like this?
What's this?! It feels incredible-!
Does it feel good for you, Onii-chan?
P-Please get more aroused Onii-chan!
How is it? Is Yuuki doing it right?
Onii-chan's cock just twitched! It must have felt good!
Then I'll do it some more.
Onii-chan's cock is so hard-!
It's making my breasts hot!
My nipples feel good from the rubbing sensation!
Yuuki is losing her mind!
Something is coming again, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!!
Is this Onii-chan's semen?
It's bitter-! It's not exactly tasty...
But it may get addictive...
I'll clean you up.
Eh? Onii-chan?
W-What are you doing, Onii-chan?!
Onii-chan, you can't-!
What's this?!
Onii-chan's cock is rubbing against me down there!
Onii-chan's cock is so hot-!
Onii-chan, that feels so good! Please, please do it harder!
It feels so good-! Onii-chan's cock feels so good-!
S-Something's coming! Something's coming, Onii-chan!
It's scary, I'm scared!
Onii-chan, hug me tight! Hug me with all of your strength!
O-Onii-chan-!
Onii-chan! Tighter! Hug Yuuki more!
Onii-chan-!
Onii-chan!!
Hey, Onii-chan... I won't be satisfied if we finish now...
Let's do it until the end, okay?
Onii-chan...
I'm borrowing this, since Yuuki's clothes are still in the wash.
I'm serious...
If it's you, Onii-chan... It's okay if you take Yuuki's first...
I love you, Onii-chan!
Not there-!
Don't show me that!
Eh?
It feels so good-!
Even though we're siblings, even if it isn't right, but...!
I'm so happy that Onii-chan is the one doing it to me!
Yuuki feels so good!
Not that-! I said that you can't-!
I'm at my limit! It's throbbing down there!
It's longing for Onii-chan's cock!
Please, Onii-chan!
I-I guess I can't report to Mom and Dad that we're doing this...
Eh?
No! Don't say that you're going to stop!
Onii-chan's cock has gotten so much harder and bigger than before...
I-It's in-!
We've finally become one, didn't we?
I-I'm okay. It hurts a bit, though...
But Yuuki's happy that she became one with you, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, it's difficult to stay like that, isn't it?
You can move, Yuuki will be fine...
Sorry Onii-chan, but can you go a bit slower?
How is it, Onii-chan? Does it feel good inside Yuuki?
What are you doing, Onii-chan?
No-! What-?
Eh?
N-No way! Even if you say "move as you like..."
Onii-chan's cock is getting hot inside of me!
This feels good!
T-This is strange. Yuuki feels good, even though it's her first time!
So good-! It's coming, something's coming, Onii-chan!
Please-! Hold my hand!
Onii-chan-! I'm gonna cum! Yuuki is gonna cum!
Onii-chan! I'm gonna cum, even though this is my first time!
N-No! I'm at my limit-! I can't hold back-!
Sorry... I got too excited and came before you...
You haven't cum yet, have you?
Let's cum together this time, okay?
O-Onii-chan, does it feel good?
Yuuki feels good too, even though it's her first time, it's amazing!
Onii-chan, do what you want!
Do what you want to Yuuki-!
Onii-chan-! T-That feels so good!
No more-! Yuuki can't hold it in anymore! It's not stopping!
I'm gonna lose it!
It's so embarrassing, but I'm gonna cum again! Something big is coming!
I don't want to cum alone again-!
I want to cum with you, Onii-chan! Please, I want to be facing you when we cum!
So good-! Your cock feels incredible!
Onii-chan, do you feel good?
Does it feel good inside of Yuuki?
I'm so happy!
Hey Onii-chan, please kiss me.
I know this isn't allowed, I know that siblings shouldn't be doing this, but-!
But, I can't hold back anymore!
I love you, Onii-chan. I love you so much, so make me your lover...
I'm so happy...
Onii-chan! Give me more, thrust more-!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Onii-chan, are you gonna cum too? Yuuki is about to-!
Let's cum at the same time, Onii-chan! At the same time!
Your cock is twitching-!
It's twitching inside of Yuuki!
O-Onii-chan, you can't cum inside!
Please cum outside-!
Onii-chan-! I'm gonna cum-!
I'm cumming-!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!!
Onii-chan's semen is so hot...
It's bitter, isn't it?
I can drink it because it's yours, Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, did it feel good?
Yuuki felt good too...
Onii-chan, um...
Um, can you kiss me again?
Onii-chan, I love you so much!
You idiot, Onii-chan!
Doing such things to your little sister... It's horrible!
Just kidding!
Will you come back home occasionally?
Okay!
Then let's have sex again, Onii-chan!