All right guys, let's do this!
It's been so long! You're a human! A real human!
Huh? My face is too close?
You're so mean.
I didn't mean to... I was just so excited to see you.
I'm Hinako. Nice to meet you!
Umm... you look like you're pretty confused.
Let's see... how should I put it...
From your perspective, I'm just an anime character, right?
Well, I'm not really sure how it happened, but I'm actually a human who was turned into an anime character...
I was watching this really awesome anime one night and, without thinking, I shouted, "I wanna be there with them!"
...and then I appeared here.
Since then, I've been an inhabitant of the anime world.
I'm actually even in the anime I was watching before, too.
You're not very surprised...
You should have some sort of reaction, you know?
Okay, how about we do some cultural exchange? Between the anime world and the real world!
What should we do, though?
How about rock-paper-scissors?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Huh? You're not enjoying this very much, are you...
I guess rock-paper-scissors wasn't the best choice, after all...
I know! Let's train together! Why training, you ask?
Well, just between you and me... I've put on a little weight.
Please don't look!
Notice!
Hinako-dono,
If you don't lose 5 kg
in 3 months, you will
be removed from the anime.
Notice!
Hinako-dono,
If you don't lose 5 kg
in 3 months, you will
be removed from the anime.
So... let's train together!
T-r-a-i-n!
We'll just be doing push-ups, sit-ups, and squats, so it shouldn't be a problem.
Keeping at it is the important part!
Hmm? Now that I look at you more closely, aren't you pretty pudgy too?
Very well, then!
Come on, hurry up and get ready! Let's train!
Training
Like I just said before, we'll just be doing some of the usual push-ups, sit-ups and squats.
We'll do 12 reps for each.
Let's begin with the push-ups.
Remember not to raise or lower your hips!
Let's try doing it once, 'kay?
Like this.
One.
How's that? Got it?
Now, you had better do this with me! I'll be watching you!
All right, let's start with the push-ups!
Push-ups
There! All done!
Mm, I haven't worked out in a while, so it's kinda hard, huh?
But this is only the beginning!
Next are sit-ups!
Bend your knees and clasp your hands behind your head to get the proper form.
Like this!
There!
Got it?
Don't try and cheat by just lifting your neck up, and remember to breathe!
Sit-ups! Let's begin!
Sit-
ups
All done!
Are you doing okay? Can you keep up with me?
Next up is the final exercise, so please give it your all!
Last is the squats!
You do them like this!
Woo!
Got it?
Let's do this!
Squats
There!
Okay, we're done!
Ooh, I'm burning up after all that exertion...
We weren't actually at it for too long, but it feels like we got a lot accomplished, huh?
Working out isn't particularly flashy, but you'll definitely see results if you keep it up.
I said it before, but it's been a while since I've worked out like this.
It brings back memories of my old club...
Oh, darn! It's this late already? I have to be on stage by 12!
I'm only playing a supporting role in the anime I'm in, but I'm giving it all I've got.
So I have to get in shape!
Will you come see me again tomorrow?
All right!
It's a promise, then! If you don't come see me, I'm going to get you!
If you break your promise, you'll have to swallow a thousand needles!
Thanks so much for today! See you tomorrow!
Training with Hinako!
Hold on!
You startled me, appearing out of nowhere like that!
But... you came to see me again today. I'm glad you kept your promise.
So let's do our best again today!
We're starting with push-ups! Let's go!
Push-ups
Next are the sit-ups!
Sit-
ups
Finally, the squats!
Squats
That's it for today!
You can still do more? Wow...
But please don't push yourself.
Thanks for training with me all the time. You're the sweetest.
We're just working out, but... every day is fun when we spend it together.
Ah! What am I saying!?
Shoot, it's this late already. Sorry, but I have to get ready for my performance now.
Bye!
*smooooch*
Bye-bye.
Training with Hinako!
I'm so hungry!
But I can't eat! It's too dangerous to eat at night!
I'm toughing it out, so you can too, right?
Tuck in your tummy.