Winner of 2nd Annual
Vanilla Original Story Contest
Original Story by Manmaru
This is bad!
I'm never gonna finish
this by noon tomorrow!
If this essay doesn't get me
the scholarship this time...
That's not even funny at all.
I'm hungry and...
I'm about to pass out...
I can't believe I wasted time like this.
Where am I?
Am I dead?
I can't believe I died worrying
about starving to death...
This is just hilarious!
Hey! My descendant!
A flying dwarf!
Damn you!
You don't look surprised at all.
The Erotic Adventures of Tom Thumb
Part 1
Well, I'm sure there are lots
of strange things in the afterlife.
You and your negative thoughts.
He's got one serious case.
You're poor, and you don't
even have a girlfriend.
That's none of your business.
Well, you're right but...
You rude bastard!
When I was your age, I made
a name for myself in the city...
...and had all sorts of
delicacies for my meals.
I had lots of money as well.
It wasn't just about material things.
Rumors went around
about me with a beauty...
...and when I wrote songs,
they ended up in a songbook.
I was enjoying the
extremes of luxury but...
Lightning struck!
So what does a great
ancestor like you possibly want...
...with a descendant who's
barely getting by with his life?
Are you dissatisfied?
No, it's nothing.
Well, anyway...
I wanted to help my descendant
who's living miserably like a grub...
...by providing some good luck.
I have a bad feeling about this...
What the...
What's going on?
It's no use.
I don't know what happened...
Is it an earthquake?
Hey, Tomo!
Are you awake?
Oh no! It's Masumi!
No! No... This is bad!
Hey, Tomo!
He's not here?
If she sees me like this...
Stretch, stretch!
I can't!
I stepped on you.
Take this!
He's not here...
I feel stupid for being nervous.
He's probably low on cash...
...and writing his essay...
...on an empty stomach...
He shouldn't attempt
to do things he can't do.
Hey, wait a minute.
Smells like Tomo...
You're so stupid Tomo...
Maybe he's got a girlfriend...
...and he's doing it with her...
No way.
You know I don't have a girl.
Hey, Masumi!
Stop! What are you
planning to do on my futon?
I'm wet...
I'm getting wet from Tomo's scent...
Hey, stop it!
That's my only futon you know!
If I don't have my futon at
this time, I'll freeze to death!
When I'm wrapped
up in Tomo's futon...
It's like he's really doing it with me.
It feels much better than usual...
Tomo!
I want you to touch me more!
L-I'll let you do me!
Tomo? Tomo?
I'm sorry my boobs are so small.
No, no, no!
Tomo! Don't play with
my nipples that much!
My nipples are hard,
but it's not like that.
It's not like that!
It's not like I want you
to play with them!
These panties are getting in the way!
This...
No... Makes me want to shout...
This is great!
Tomo... This is great, Tomo!
My fingers are going inside!
My juices are pouring out,
and it's going in smoothly!
I...
I'm going to climax with your thing!
I kind of like Tomo to be sadistic...
I can do it so many
times with this idea.
What should I do with this?
Oh well.
If I say that I'll wash this for him...
...then maybe Tomo
might get all sentimental...
I don't think so!
Look what you did to my futon!
Wha... Wha...
What?
I can't believe this happened...
I'm not dreaming am I?
I feel that this is the strangest
thing that's ever happened...
No, I just thought I was
masturbating too much...
...and saw an illusion or something...
Nevermind what I just said!
You're right.
You were like "Tomo,
Tomo, I'm going to climax!"
What?
You were naked from
the waist down too.
That means...
That was...
Well, this might sound weird
after you saw me like that, but...
Me... I mean I...
I always thought you...
This is bad...
I can't complete my essay like this...
Do you want me to write it for you?
Thanks, Masumi.
I don't know
if I'll return to normal, but...
Now I can keep attending college...
Well, this means you
owe me another favor!
Shut up.
Now, now. Don't be sullen.
I'll be gentle with you...
Oh no!
You better hide, Tomo!
That was close!
It might not be safe for
you to be seen like this...
...so maybe you can...
...hide in my bosom.
Hey, Masumi...
Walk a little slower, will you?
It's very unstable, so it's
hard to balance myself...
Man, look at the time!
I'm counting on you, Masumi!
Ok, then I'm going to hurry.
It'll be a bit shaky, but hang in there.
Okay!
Wait a minute, Tomo...
Tomo, don't...
...grab on to that part!
But if I don't, I'm going to fall!
I... I... I...
You're making me get all excited!
T-Tomo!
Not my belly button!
I can't help it!
But if I stop running,
you'll be expelled.
Masumi, I didn't know you
cared about me that much...
Why?
Laboratory
We're almost there...
Almost there...
Tomo, Tomo, Tomo...
Don't...
Don't play with my private area!
But it's all dark in here
and I can't see a thing.
Wait! I found
something I can hang on to.
No, no, no, no...
If you keep doing that, I'II...
I... I...
I won't pee, but I'll
release that happy juice...
I'll release it all over the place!
Not there...
No!
It's coming out!
My happy juice is coming out!
It's really coming out!
You're so bad, Tomo.
I don't think I can live
without you, Tomo...
Who's the one making
all those loud noises?
Who's that?
Issunbashi's essay?
It's a little too late to
submit the essay...
...but since she really rushed to
make it on time and fainted...
...I'll make an exception.
Professor, what's wrong?
No, it's just that Issunbashi's
girlfriend delivered his essay...
Wow! Love is a miracle!
Professor?
No, it's nothing.
It's nothing...
It's nothing for me too...
I thought I was going to drown...
But it might be satisfying for
a guy to drown in love juice...
Um...
It's so cute!
It's mine now!
So cute!
This is mine.
Professor, it's not fair!
This time, I'll suffocate...
This is bad...
Definitely bad...
Bad, bad, bad...
It's really bad...
What the hell.
I feel like I'm doing the right thing,
but they certainly don't think so...
Maybe I did bad things
in my previous life.
Hey, Issunbashi!
I thought you were a bit cute!
Did you know that?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
Ouch...
Hey!
Issunbashi doll turned
into the real Issunbashi.
This is probably a dream...
My body was getting real hot...
You let that cute girlfriend of
yours bring your essay instead...
Issunbashi...
I always liked you...
I always played with myself like
this while thinking about you...
So you see...
I'm so happy it turned out like this...
You're so cute, Professor...
Idiot...
You don't have to do whatever I want...
...just because I'm dreaming.
Issunbashi...
I want your cock...
I want you to make
me feel good too.
Professor...
Don't look at me like that...
Not now.
Okay?
No...
I just love you so much...
I just want to start moving...
No!
I'm supposed to be
the one to violate you!
No, no...
If you move that much, I'II...
I'll go crazy.
Is your cock moving?
It's moving!
Keep moving...
Your boobs are really nice...
Boobs...
My boobs... do you understand?
I want you to keep shoving them.
Shove them, okay?
Okay?
I can feel your cock
rubbing inside me.
It's grinding inside!
Issunbashi... Issunbashi...
Make love to me like a lover...
I want you to make love
to me as if I'm your lover!
No, don't pull your cock out.
Issunbashi...
I... I...
You...
I like you... I really like you!
Your cock juice...
It's flowing out...
Come to think of it...
If the professor wakes
up seeing me like this...
...it would be very bad...
I'm sure she thinks
it was only a dream.
But she was so cute...
Issun?
Oh, Issun!
What? What? What?
Liz.
Issun!
You have such a cute girlfriend...
...but you're fooling
around with the professor?
You're such scum, scum, scum!
You... You...
Japanese playboy!
Wait a minute Liz...
It's not what it looks like...
There's a reason for all this...
I don't want to hear it!
Liz?
Could you stop?
Issun?
Wha... Wha... Wha...
What?