If I think about it, it was actually a horrible encounter.
The first person to ever write me a love letter,
was a cute girl from the other class.
Dear Kanzaki-kun, Please come to the PE storage room after school.
Setagaya Mari
And in my full-bloom adolescence,
if you said that I had unrealistic expectations
of what was going to happen,
you’d be right.
But...
It's not like it's realistic that I’d get
kicked the moment I see her!
Alright.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
I'll Have Your Semen!
Dinner for Vampire
You! You stupid bitch!
What the fuck was that!?
Huh? They usually all go down with one kick...
You're tough, huh?
Don't give me that.
Why would you kick a person you just met!?
Uhh...pl...
Please calm down, Kanzaki-kun!
I'm sorry.
I... uh, I just need some blood...
Huh? Need blood?
You sure it’s not some brains you need?
No, no, it's blood!
When looking at how lively and energetic you are,
I just get so hungry...
I'm sor...
This girl... really bit me...
Hey.
I'm, I'm sorry... I...
I'm not used to the raw taste...
So?
I mean, I'm a vampire, but I can't handle blood very well.
Well even if it's not blood we are still able to obtain
nutrients as long as it's in the form of life energy...
Hey.
so up until now I've been taking
energy from sweat and spit!
Hey.
But of course blood is still the most efficient way!
Hey listen already, you psychotic rascal!
Geez! I'm not a rascal!
Shut up! Like I'd deal with your stupid fantasies!
Fantasies?
Oh, so you don't exactly believe me?
Well then...
I you see this, you'll believe me...
...Are those real?
Um, can I get you to believe me now?
I, um, I'm just really hungry...
Could you please spare me some sweat or something?
Just a little is alright! Pretty please!
It's fine as long as it's some kind of secretion?
Eh? So you'll help me?
Oh, of course. However...
Not sweat, but if you want semen I’ll let you have some.
Semen...
I see, it's a little embarrassing,
but it seems very nutritious.
Alright, I'll do it.
Then, let's squeeze some out!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Huh? It won't come out.
Are you stupid? It's not done like that!
It's not like milking a cow.
You gotta lick it and suck it and make it feel good!
Licking...
and sucking...
I see...
What should I say... she's... really bad.
Can he really feel good from something like this?
It's not just licking just the tip, but more
of taking it in deeper and sucking on it.
Understood.
Huh? Hey...
What? I haven't said anything,
but she's suddenly a lot better.
Well I guess it's alright...
She doesn't seem to be smart, but she might
just be very intuitive about some things.
If only her boobs were larger, I'd be
able to get some good titty fuck...
Tasty..
Never mind, as a virgin I shouldn't
have too high of expectations.
Huh? My chest is suddenly getting heavier?
What?
Kanzaki-kun, what's happening?
Like I'd know!
But it's good! It's great!
Oh. It's good?
I'll borrow these for a sec.
Use these like this...
No...
I always wanted to do this!
Wait...
Ah, sorry, did that hurt?
That's not it...
It'll feel good, so...
These are so soft!
You can hear it, right? The erotic sounds.
My boobs are wet...
This is amazing! It's way too good!
Hurry and give it to me.
Let me drink lots of Kanzaki-kun's semen!
I can't, I'm...
It's here! Semen came!
It's so thick!
Your life energy is soaking into me!
I see.
Looks like you've been saving up lots.
Could it be that's this is your first time?
None of your business!
It's great, really.
Well then, this time I’ll take your
virgin dick with this mouth!
Hey!
I'll move, so Kanzaki-kun can just stay still...
What is this? It's really tight...
So this is the inside of a girl!
Kanzaki-kun's is so big... and hard...
It's good!
My insides are being ground!
How does your personality change so fast!?
But...
you like this kind of girl, don't you?
I can read Kanzaki-kun like a book!
See? You like it when I shake my hips around like this...
and push my boobs against your face, right?
This girl... even the way she talks is changing.
Is this some power of the vampires?
If anything...
Don't get too full of yourself, being so stupid!
No! Don't!
Huh? What? Your wings are your spot?
Well then...
I've gotta touch them more!
Don't... you can't...
What's up? Your pussy is squeezing
even more than earlier!
That's not true!
My... my pus- pussy... isn't...
No... it feels so good I can't...
What? Are you cumming? You want to cum?
I'm going to cum!
Your penis is swelling inside me!
Hurry and let it out!
Let my pussy know the taste of your semen!
Hot stuff is coming!
My pussy is twitching...
You know, I lost my virginity a couple of days ago!
Kanzaki-Kun!
Thank you for that time!
I have something to tell you!
Her personality went back...
Her chest, too.
My mom just told me recently...
But it turns out I'm a half-blood hybrid
of a vampire and a succubus!
She's been hiding it until I get sexual education, she said.
Aww?
Turns out I've awaken from fitting
so well with Kanzaki-kun!
My chest gets bigger happens because of that, too.
I see.
In conclusion, from now on as my food,
please give me lots of seme-
If you fix that broken brain of yours!
Full-course dinner for Vampire
Kanzaki-kun! It's lunch break!
It's time for food! I’m starving!
Kanzaki-kun... Kanzaki-kun...
It's those guys again.
Hey wait, don't rush!
They're so loud. Every day, too!
Hey don’t rub on me!
Hey! Let go!
C'mon, let's go.
Is it lunch? Lunch?
Music Room
Hey, please stop the things like clinging
onto me or kissing me in the classroom.
Eh? But I was hungry...
Is that all you can think of?
Calling herself a hybrid of vampire and succubus,
this girl feeds on the life energy of humans.
And apparently she's fallen in love of my semen,
so she comes at noon and after school to eat.
So, she doesn't have any feelings of love for me...
No, it's not like I'm upset about that.
But still...
We've been doing it every day, yet she's still horrible at it.
C'mon, be more erotic!
Also, do something about those tiny tits.
Oh, enlarging my boobs again?
You really love these, you pervert.
But, why does her personality change, too?
Is this also changed to my liking?
For Kanzaki-kun who's from Planet Boobs,
shall I caress your penis like this?
Her boobs are so soft and elastic!
It's twitching... so cute!
She's secretes a lot of saliva, so it feels
really warm and wet inside her mouth!
She sucks really well.
It’s a bit soon, but I'm cumming already!
Woah, other people are...
And of all people, these guys!
Oh, it's Kanzaki.
I've been wondering, where you disappear off
to at lunch. So you've been doing it here.
Why are you getting so full of yourself
despite being so uncool?
You'll disrupt the morale around here, please stop!
What's wrong, Kanzaki-kun?
Let's keep going!
How can you say that under these circumstances!?
You, too. Why would you prefer someone like that?
He's no good at studying or sports or anything.
And he's got zero presence in the room.
Ours are definitely much better.
Huh? What are you talking about?
There's no way you guys could replace Kanzaki-kun.
I don't even want to talk about that
feeble energy you guys can give!
Never mind comparing it to the
thick semen of Kanzaki-kun!
Hey, just leave it there...
You're disturbing my meal, so please leave.
What do you mean...
Ouch, ouch!
...feeble, you slut!
What are you doing? Stop trying to interrupt my meal!
Stop it! Let go of Setagaya!
Calm down, It's got nothing to do with you.
Hey, let go!
What is this?
Shut up and watch from over there.
Damn!
Kanzaki-kun!
Huh? They seemed larger earlier...
Was that just me?
Hey! I said stop!
So who’s the feeble one here?
I wanted at least a D!
Her body isn't changing...
she's not using her power?
So you're used to fellatio, right? From
doing it every day with Kanzaki.
Try comparing that with ours.
No! After knowing Kanzaki-kun's,
I don't want your thin semen...
Like you'd know!
What? She's got no technique at all!
You'd better teach her well, Kanzaki-kun!
Stop it! Can't you see she doesn't want it?
C'mon, rub mine with your hands, too!
What are you doing? You're letting
them boss you around...
Where's your usual stubbornness?
Don't make that sad face!
You'll just make them happier with that!
What? What happened?
You failure! You bit me!
I meant to do that, you see.
But don't worry, I'll take care of it till the end.
What?
Or, I’ll make sure you cum properly, to be exact.
What is this woman talking about?
So, for example, you seem to be quite the masochist.
You like the pain along with pleasure
all at once, don't you?
And then you,
would like this part to be teased, right?
How is she... so suddenly...
C'mon, you guys need to catch up!
I can't... I’m gonna...
Me too... cumming...
Are you cumming already?
You masochist dicks!
Well then, let’s have a taste...
Oh? It's not as bad as I thought.
Just now... did my thoughts reach her?
Even though she doesn't react to what those guys say...
Your penis, it's standing, Kanzaki-kun.
Hey, heyi
But after ah, Kanzaki-kun's is the best!
Stop it! I don't have any intentions
to do it in front of others!
Oh, right! I forgot!
Kanzaki-kun is only willing if I have big boobs!
No! That's not the point here!
What's with those wings!?
You're some monster?
Hmm, I don't like the way you put that.
I'm a succubus, plus vampire.
Remember that.
Wait!
The only one that can satisfy me...
The only one that can feed me...
is Kanzaki-kun!
Don't say silly stuff like that!
For now, at least free my arms!
No way! This is so exciting!
If anything, Kanzaki-kun got turned
on watching me being raped, right?
Shut up...
Kanzaki-kun is so cute...
I see you are swallowing your spit in excitement.
Like, like hell I was!
I see... although I'd be glad to love you
with this side if you were honest.
Woah... what, what!? Don't give me that look!
Alright, this time I'll make you moan for sure!
Wait, no way!
This... it's tight...
Wow... you can feel the movement from this side...
It's actually pretty good...
No... no... don’t move...
Huh?
Is she kind of different...
Ha! Where'd all your spirits go?
Hey, could it be that you...
Even though it’s the first time in my butt...
Don't bite off more than you can chew!
But... my pussy can only be fore
that one person I decide on!
Huh?
Don't forget that I'm here, too.
If anything, it'll be bad if this goes on.
If there's some way she can get better...
What? Her asshole is squeezing suddenly!
This feels way too good!
I'll go crazy... something amazing is coming!
Even I just came... I'm gonna...
Me, too... gonna...
Cumming, I'm cumming!
It's here!
Oh... it's true that getting too greedy
is bad for your stomach...
I won't be taking anything other
than Kanzaki-kun's anymore.
I see.
I came...
I came from this weird woman, twice...
Oh by the way, if you can change your body,
why didn't you react to their thoughts?
Oh!
That's a good point you make!
It’s because I'm not a full succubus, you see.
My body won't take anyone other than Kanzaki-kun!
Yes?
I've realized it today!
I like you, Kanzaki-kun!
Please go out with me!
You... Do you mean it?
You sure you're not just trying to keep
me as a permanent source of food?
Geez, I really mean it!
I love you!
This casualness seems fishy...
The Next Day
Kanzaki-kun! It's lunch time!
It's time for food! I'm starving!
Like I thought, you just think of me as your meal!
Dolce for Vampire
After I started dating Setagaya Mari,
there was something I just couldn't stop suspecting.
Which was, her sense of virtue as a succubus.
So she's really doing it with other men as well!?
You're amazing!
How can you still go after cumming five times already...
It feels good!
You're dick is even larger than Kanzaki-kun's,
you'll stretch my pussy!
Yes!
Your penis is reaching the deepest parts!
If you do me with this amazing thing every day,
I'll get addicted!
If you give me semen this thick... I won't be
satisfied with only Kanzaki-kun’s anymore...
anymore... more...
It's gonna end up like something like that!
...kun!
Geez, Kanzaki-kun!
What's wrong? Everyone else has left already.
Hey, Setagaya, I don't I can keep dating you!
Although we're seeing each other... in reality I'm just
your food... it's not like I'm good looking or...
So in short you are going to break up with me!?!
No, that's not it!
That's so mean, Kanzaki-kun.
Well, it's true that I’m weak as a succubus...
Um, listen to what I say.
and my boobs are small so it disappoints
you all the time...
Oh, you were worried about that?
But that's not a reason to just give up and dump me!
I've always changed it to your liking!
See, like this...
Wait, what are you doing??
Wait! Whit I'm trying to say is...
So that's what you mean...
So you're already tired of my body!
You have no intention to listen to what I say, have you...
Then...
I can also make you hard with a plump, soft body!
Woah, so soft!
See? You're starting to get hard.
Well yeah, because it feels good...
wait, that's not the point!
Hmm, even this isn't enough?
Well then! How about this?
You can ravage this cat-girl's pussy as much as you want!
That... could be dangerous...
My pussy in heat is being filled up!
If Kanzaki-kun wishes, I can be a cat,
or a rabbit, or even another girl!
Like I said that's not the point!
It's you...
Are you fine with... someone like me...
Of course I’m good!
The person I fall in love with...
the person I have sex with...
It has to be Kanzaki-kun!
Ma... Mari!
Cumming... I’m going to cum!
I'm cumming, too!
It's overflowing...
I love you. I really love you, Kanzaki-kun...
Hey, wanna go to my house after this?
Huh? Really?
Yeah! I want to introduce Kanzaki-kun to my mom!
Err... Your mom is a succubus, right?
Yep.
Will I be alright?
Don't worry! It's not like she's gonna
go for her daughters boyfriend.
...Probably.
Probably... huh...
Ah! You're thinking about perverted things, aren't you!
As if you have the right to judge!