Dolce for Vampire
After I started dating Setagaya Mari,
there was something I just couldn't stop suspecting.
Which was, her sense of virtue as a succubus.
So she's really doing it with other men as well!?
You're amazing!
How can you still go after cumming five times already...
It feels good!
You're dick is even larger than Kanzaki-kun's,
you'll stretch my pussy!
Yes!
Your penis is reaching the deepest parts!
If you do me with this amazing thing every day,
I'll get addicted!
If you give me semen this thick... I won't be
satisfied with only Kanzaki-kun’s anymore...
anymore... more...
It's gonna end up like something like that!
...kun!
Geez, Kanzaki-kun!
What's wrong? Everyone else has left already.
Hey, Setagaya, I don't I can keep dating you!
Although we're seeing each other... in reality I'm just
your food... it's not like I'm good looking or...
So in short you are going to break up with me!?!
No, that's not it!
That's so mean, Kanzaki-kun.
Well, it's true that I’m weak as a succubus...
Um, listen to what I say.
and my boobs are small so it disappoints
you all the time...
Oh, you were worried about that?
But that's not a reason to just give up and dump me!
I've always changed it to your liking!
See, like this...
Wait, what are you doing??
Wait! Whit I'm trying to say is...
So that's what you mean...
So you're already tired of my body!
You have no intention to listen to what I say, have you...
Then...
I can also make you hard with a plump, soft body!
Woah, so soft!
See? You're starting to get hard.
Well yeah, because it feels good...
wait, that's not the point!
Hmm, even this isn't enough?
Well then! How about this?
You can ravage this cat-girl's pussy as much as you want!
That... could be dangerous...
My pussy in heat is being filled up!
If Kanzaki-kun wishes, I can be a cat,
or a rabbit, or even another girl!
Like I said that's not the point!
It's you...
Are you fine with... someone like me...
Of course I’m good!
The person I fall in love with...
the person I have sex with...
It has to be Kanzaki-kun!
Ma... Mari!
Cumming... I’m going to cum!
I'm cumming, too!
It's overflowing...
I love you. I really love you, Kanzaki-kun...
Hey, wanna go to my house after this?
Huh? Really?
Yeah! I want to introduce Kanzaki-kun to my mom!
Err... Your mom is a succubus, right?
Yep.
Will I be alright?
Don't worry! It's not like she's gonna
go for her daughters boyfriend.
...Probably.
Probably... huh...
Ah! You're thinking about perverted things, aren't you!
As if you have the right to judge!