You got into another fight, Hikaru?
Why...
Why don't I have a mommy or daddy?
You have a mother and father.
Then why?!
Why can't I ever see Mom or Dad?!
Your mother is simply waiting for you.
She's in another land, waiting for you to grow up.
That's why you have to be strong.
And become a good man.
HEroAP Presents
Crimson Martyrdom
K-Kaede-san...
More, Hikaru-sama. I want more.
H-Hikaru-sama!
Are you alright, Kaede-san?
Y-Yes. I need you to make me
more and more aroused.
Then, I'll get to have your essence inside of me.
Hikaru-sama!
Our destinies are now entwined, my master.
It wasn't... a dream.
Ayaka-san...
Nanami-chan...
Nagisa...
Staring at your sleeping female companions?
W-Who are you?!
Odd, you sure don't look like siblings...
Who the hell are you?
At the very least, you have an unwavering heart.
But, seems like that's all you have.
Oh, don't worry. For now, you don't
have any major challenges ahead.
But, I am amazed that you managed to get Kaede.
Kaede?
My name is Susanoo.
None of you will make it out of this forest.
Farewell, Hikaru Touma.
Susanoo...
That was a good night's sleep.
Just what are you doing, Hikaru?
What kind of person touches himself
like that in the morning. Pervert!
Nagisa-san? What's perverted?
Hikaru was...
*mumble mumble*
H-He was...?
N...No!! This is out of context!!
Well, Hikaru-chan... aren't you the young one?
Touka, I've shown myself to the
visitors from the other land.
Mission accomplished.
Yes, so I heard.
What about you, Great Lord Susanoo?
Unfortunately, I cannot harm those visitors just yet.
Leave it to me then.
Hey...
Just how long do we have to keep walking?
It's weird... It didn't seem like this
big of a forest from out there.
I'm hungry! I'm thirsty! And I want to take a shower!
Will you just shut up?!
Um...
Haven't we walked down this way before?
No way!
I got that feeling too.
We're oin in circles?
That cant be. The school's getting.
smaller as we're walking.
That's true, but still...
What's wrong?
I could've sworn that wasn't behind Hikaru before.
How can that -
H-How?
There was a path right there just a minute ago!
W-What's going on here?
l-lt's like things change as soon as
we look away from it, doesn't it?
But there's no way that can
actually happen... sensei?
Master!
Stay alert. An enemy's coming!
Enemy?
There's something in the forest that feels
the same as when you and I met.
What is that?
We just can't get a break, can we?
Careful everyone, here it comes!
Damn this monster...
Going for the girls first!
He did it!
That thing wasn't tough at all.
Not yet!
Touka hasn't been beaten yet!
Hikaru!
Hikaru-san!
Hikaru-chan!
It's up to us, Nanami.
You know how to use your weapon, right?
You have to use it.
Right.
Ayaka-sensei, we'll keep it busy
while you tend to Hikaru.
All right.
But be careful!
Over here you monster!
Hikaru-chan!
Oh dear, he lost consciousness.
But he looks fine otherwise...
I know!
Thank goodness, you're awake.
What the hell is that stuff?
It was supposed to be part of your exam.
I'm glad I held on to some chemicals...
If you didn't wake up, I might have
had to spill some on you.
The stuff really burns.
T-That sounds really dangerous...
Burn?
That's it!
This thing just won't go down!
Nagisa-san. I'm all out of arrows!
Hikaru-san!
Ayaka-san!
He did it!
What's happening?
What is that?!
It... disappeared.
What happened to it?
Hey, I hear water in that direction.
Water?
Maybe it's a river.
It may lead to a way out.
Let's go!
Do you see anything, Nagisa?
Like a town or...
Uh, what is... all this?
This looks like... where my house should be.
You there! Don't move!
Drop your weapons, and surrender!
What's with the weird cosplaying?
Don't you guys have anything better to do?
Wh-What is this?
I'll say it one more time...
Drop your weapons, and surrender!
It's almost like...
One of those places you see
in ancient Japanese times.
It looks like stuff from the Yayoi period.
But, a little bit different too.
Maybe it's part of a theme
park we don't know about.
With some overzealous and annoying
employees to boot.
Seriously...
The great Amaterasu-sama will now speak with you!
Wait there.
Amaterasu-sama! We've brought
the outsiders to you.
Amaterasu?
What a ridiculous name...
It must really be an important person.
This girl...
The one from my dream!
It's her!
Hikaru?
Amaterasu-sama, these are
the intruders to our land.
How would you like them dealt with?
Kami-sama...
Thank the heavenly plains...
At last... My prayers have finally been answered!
Kyuuseishu-sama!
Kyuuseishu?
Me?
This feels wonderful...
A meal and a bath...
We sure made out.
Nagisa-san, this isn't an inn...
I feel alive again.
Ayaka-sensei...
Your body is a lot better than ours.
Is it really?
That's because she's a full adult.
We have parts that still need to mature and fill out.
But then again...
There are guys that like a long and slender body.
So you may be good as you are.
But if you really want a bigger bust, then
I can certainly help you along...
Huh?! What?! No - Please, leave me be!
Speaking of which, about what happened earlier...
What do you two think about it?
Now that you mention it...
It was a lot to take in.
This world seems to be a replacement
world from the one all of you live in.
It is a world far from the one you call Ashihara.
We call this world Nenokuni.
Nenokuni (land of roots) is a land not quite in
Yomi (underworld) but also not our world.
The same one from Japanese history.
It's written in Japanese history that Nenokuni
could be known as our modern Ashihara.
Ashihara is referred to as the world between Takamagahara (heavenly plane)
and Yoml (underworld). In modem terms, it means our world while in an
archaic sense, it meant the land of Japan between those two worlds.
That’s exactly the case.
But the fundamental difference is, from
this world, Ashihara does not exist.
You cannot exist in both worlds, so
therefore you ended up in this one.
W-Wait a minute, so does that technically mean
that we died and this is the place we end up?
That isn't the case.
Out of the two worlds, it is only your
souls that were exchanged.
But I fear that you have come at a
time where you might as well be.
Ten years ago, evil beings overtook this land.
All of us fought for our lives.
But their power was overwhelming.
And we are now close to completely dying out.
This affects all of the people from Ashihara as well.
The evil beings spawn from Yomotsu Okami, and
then start to overrun the beings in Nenokuni.
Izanami-sama will not simply stop
with both worlds in existence.
Once the evil beings are done here,
they will surely spread to Ashihara.
If that happens, both our worlds will end.
I and the other shrine maidens have
conducted countless ceremonies for
a kyuuseishu to descend upon us.
And the great one has answered us.
That white place appeared...
And all of you have showed up here.
There is a legend that says four beings shall
descend, and that they would be kyuuseishu-sama.
Even if she claims that we're kyuuseishu...
T-That's right.
True, even if we are the kyuuseishu
that Amaterasu thinks we are...
The four of us aren't enough to change all of this.
Kyuuseishu-sama?
Is there something wrong?
You must be tired from what
you've been through today.
There's something I really have to tell you.
We aren't the kyuuseishu that you say we are.
It is true that we're from a different
world than this one.
And I do believe that horrible
things have happened here.
T-Then...
But...
We're just... regular people with no special powers.
We don't have the power to
save the world or anything.
We've just had weird things happen to us.
And... Anyway, I'm concerned if there's
a way to get back to our world.
There isn't...
There isn't a way... for you to go back...
Excuse me, kyuuseishu-sama...
So what are we going to do...?
Nenokuni, or Ashihara-no-kuni...
I can't make sense of either.
And besides...
There isn't...
Any way for you to go back....
I'm sure Miyuki and grandpa are worried too...
Qnii-chan, I forgot something. I'm going back...
Miyuki...
Would you like me to wash your back?
Uh, is that usually done here?
I'm perfectly fine doing it myself...
So don't feel like you have to.
Oh no, I'm not a part of this village.
The original legend of the Okamutsumi (seed of kami) pertains to a
peach seed that had powers to ward away evil spirits and beings.
I am the Okamutsumi, the tree spirit named Touka.
Though I'm sure you wouldn't
really know about all that.
Um, actually, I'm the monster that you
defeated while you were in the forest.
W-What the hell do want from me, monster?!
Were you just waiting here to ambush me?!
Just what are you after?!
I didn't expect you to change your impression of me.
I am simply here to offer an exchange of
vows so that I may grant you my power.
Huh?
I also want to be taken under your skillful hand.
W... Wait a minute!
Just what do you mean by "also"...
Oh...
So if you would, Hikaru-sama...
N... Now wait a minute!
Are you refusing me?
Well, no, it's just that I can't take this all in.
And... the two of us only just met.
And now you want to...
Don't try to patronize me.
You've already made a pretty
intense vow with Kaede...
Only because she didn't leave
me with much of a choice...
H-Hey...
Pretty please...?
Hikaru-sama...
T-Touka-san...
I don't mind.
Do whatever you please with me.
I think it would be better not to give it to him.
It doesn't look like he wants to go out with anyone...
I think it would be best if you simply stay
the childhood friends that you are.
Childhood friends...?
I need to clear my head...
Hikaru-sama...
This is... too good.
Why am I... losing it?
The smell of the flowers must be it...
H-Hikaru-sama, that's my...
N-No!
N-No... not...
It's too... No...
Don't... I can't handle it.
I-I can't take this.
P-Please don't tease me like this, Hikaru-sama.
Hikaru-sama!
I'm really going to...
let's... Let's...
Touka-san.
Our destinies... are now entwined...
Hikaru-sama...
That's...
Is it?
Seriously... What was that about?
Nanami-chan!
Hikaru-san!
What are you doing all the way
out here, Nanami-chan?
Uh, yeah... I thought I'd clear my head out here.
Clear your head?
Well, because...
We're in such a weird place... so
I don't really know what to do.
You're right...
Being tossed into a place like this. No normal
person would be able to sleep well.
But, I wouldn't worry, Nanami-chan.
I'm sure that we'll get back and see everyone again.
Hikaru-san...
I said awhile ago that I couldn't
sleep for three days, right?
Yeah.
The real reason... that I...
I really...
Nanami-chan, it's just a fish jumping out.
You'll be fine.
Nanami-chan...
Hikaru-san...
I really do...
Nanami-chan?