Nanami-chan...
I-I'm sorry.
Nanami-chan!
HEroAP Presents
Amber Reminiscence
I love you, Hikaru-san.
I'm sorry, I know this isn't the right time.
But, we're in this weird place...
And we may be stuck here... So...
Nanami-chan...
But, to hug you like that out of nowhere...
You really didn't need that.
I'm very sorry.
"I didn't need that...?"
Hikaru-san...
Nanami-chan...
Hikaru-san?
How are you and Miyuki-chan related?
She's my younger sister...
Why?
Do you really mean that?
Do you only see her as your sister?
Nanami-chan?
I-I'm sorry...
Don't worry.
I'll be gentle with you.
T-That's not what I meant...
This is my... first kiss.
Nanami-chan, you're already...
Please don't say that, this is embarrassing enough.
H-Hikaru-san, don't... do that.
It feels... weird.
Hikaru-san...
Please go easy on me.
I know.
Ouch!!
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine...
Nanami-chan...
It's all the way in.
Just tell me if it hurts.
OK.
Am I hurting you?
No worries.
Nanami-chan.
Hikaru-san...
This position's really embarrassing.
Nanami-chan...
I'm going to come.
OK.
Hikaru-san.
Nanami-chan.
That looks like...
Something from a dream.
I never thought that I'd be with you like this.
Do you... regret doing it?
Of course not!
I... do love you, Hikaru-san. But I also don't
think I should have you to myself.
For you to be my first... That
alone makes me very happy.
I really mean that... so...
Nanami-chan...
Hikaru-san?
Maybe... we should go back home.
Amaterasu told me that we can't.
That doesn't matter...
As long as we're all here, we'll be fine.
No matter what's happened, or what
painful experiences I have...
Your warmth has always been there to comfort me.
Do you really have to leave us?
Yeah... We can't intrude on your goodwill,
and we're already indebted to you.
Hikaru-sama...
If you really are Izanami's kyuseishuu
that was sent to us...
I'm sorry. I'm simply a normal
person with a normal lineage.
You must be exceptional. I feel that you are.
Sorry.
We'll have to find a way back
to our world on our own.
You say that now. but do you have an actual plan?
F-For now, we'll just head back to the academy.
And then?
Then... that...
"That" What?
Nagisa-san, it'll be fine. Things will work out!
You seem pretty optimistic, Nanami-chan.
Nanami-chan, did something good happen to you?
Huh?
N-N-Nothing in particular.
No matter what I say, you're really going to leave?
There are people in our world that we have to see.
Family and friends that we can't leave.
In that case. I will show you the
way back to Ashihara-no-kuni.
But you said there wasn't a way...
I deeply apologize...
It was a lie.
In Nenokuni, there are eight divine
guardians in existence.
Seiryuu...
Genbu...
Byakko...
Suzaku...
The other four have been captured by the
evil beings and must be turned back...
And under them, an inversed spell must be chanted.
When the spell is used your
souls can lapse through...
And then it will be possible to return
from Nenokuhi to Ashihara.
God of the Sea...
God of Fire...
Blade of Attack...
Spirit of Reverence...
Spirit of Sufficiency...
Spirit of the Inexplicable...
Spirit of Assurance...
Appendage of crustacean...
Appendage of insect...
Appendage of offering...
Trembling waves swaying and parting...
These guardians can sure pick
the creepiest places to live.
Amaterasu said that this place has been
occupied by evil spirits for many years.
I just feel that we'll run into tons
of problems down there.
This is so we can go back to our world.
Let's go.
Well, when an evil spirit or whatever should
come out, just let me take care of it.
Amaterasu!
Amaterasu-san!
I'm going with you.
I won't have you risk yourself.
We just want to go back to our world.
The spell requires a connection with Nenokuni.
And to be frank, I have resolved
in my very soul to help you.
I truly believe that you are the kyuuseishu.
So please allow me to go with you.
Hikaru, let's bring her along.
We don't know what's out there in this world.
I don't think she's leaving either way.
Yes, we should take her with us.
Ayaka-san...
It's just like in the legend...
Four people and their leader.
Hey, I never said that I was involved
with Hikaru in any way!
What is it!?
Oh, just some water.
Nagisa, don't yell out like that!
I couldn't help it!
That scared me...
You can never keep your mouth shut.
What was that?
That hurts, damn it!
Quiet.
I sense an evil presence.
Nanami-chan, Ayaka-san, get behind me!
OK.
I know you're there!
Show yourself!
Can't breathe...!
So that's what you look like.
You sneak...
Nagisa.
Kill... Kill... I'll kill you.
Nanami-chan?
I'll kill you...
Kill you all!
Impossible...
What's wrong, Nanami-chan?
You're...
Nanami-san, what's wrong?
Chinatsu-chan?
Is that you, Chinatsu-chan?
Why are you here of all places?
Chinatsu-chan!
It's Nanami!
We were friends back...
Look out!
Chinatsu-chan!
Hikaru-san! Don't!
No, no...
Chinatsu-chan. what happened to you?
Did you forget about me?
This thing is a vengeful ghost from Yomi.
Vengeful ghost?
She died in her past life.
I feel great resentment from her.
Chinatsu-chan...
It's coming, stand aside.
It's building power.
My blade will tear it down!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill them all!
Die!
Stop!!
What are you doing!?
Please, don't hurt Chinatsu-chan!
You must be joking!
Chinatsu-chan isn't a vengeful ghost!
She's not a fake!
Let go of me!
I have to put her to rest!
She's my friend!!
Please, she's my friend?
Hikaru-sama! Nagisa-san!
It disappeared...
Nanami-chan!
I'm sorry, Nanami-san...
She isn't alive anymore.
Once an evil being, humans cannot be turned back.
No...
That monster was your friend?
What do you mean?
Nanami-chan...
Do you mean Chinatsu-chan from back then...?
Chinatsu-chan was...
...my best friend.
I didn't know...
...that she was suffering so much.
She didn't have anyone, and was all alone.
I never noticed...
That Chinatsu-chan was...
...picked on so much.
This way should lead us to Seiryuu's sacred alter.
What's this?
This is Chinatsu-chan's... diary?
Why would that be here?
Nanami-chan, I really don't
think you should read that.
Yeah, Nanami-chan...
Here, let me have it.
Nanami-chan...
Nanami-san...
June 10th
My textbook was painted black
I won't be able to study.
June 10th...
My textbooks were painted black
Now I won't be able to study.
June 29th
Someone put mud in my lunch.
I haven't eaten anything.
June 29th...
Someone put mud in my lunch.
I haven't been able to eat anything.
N-No...
Stay away!
What's wrong?
July 2nd...
When I was in the bathroom
I got water sprayed over me.
As I tried to dry off, I could
hear those girls laughing.
July 4th...
I have a high fever.
Nanami-chan made me feel a little better.
I thought I would be over it by now.
I got a call that night.
It was from the people that surrounded me.
She has a pretty damn good body.
Her tits are even getting hard.
July 10th...
I wanted to tell Nanami-chan about
all this, but decided not to.
All I want is for this to end.
Anything, just make it stop.
No? Stop it!
Holy shit, she's wet!
July 18 th...
While taking a break after Wednesday's class...
The girls put semen in my desk.
And of all things, I found it
was from someone I like.
NO!!
Here it comes...
No... No more...
I'm trying, but...
I can't...
No more...
I want to die...
Chinatsu-chan...
This time, I will kill it.
But, Amaterasu-san...
if we don't kill her, we can't get through.
Is It alright with you if you can't go home?
She does have a point.
Let's go!
Wait!
Hikaru-sama?
If she can get through to her...
There is no way.
It's only a vengeful ghost.
Chinatsu-chan...
It's me, Nanami...
Nanami-san! Get away!
Nanami...
That's right.
You know who I am.
Nanami...
That's right.
Chinatsu-chan...
Everyone... Everyone's...
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Chinatsu-chan!
You aren't the only one in pain!
Do you have any idea how much Nanami-chan's
been crying and suffering?
You.. You... You...
You're still alive...
Alive, alive, alive!
Hikaru-sama!
Hikaru!
Hikaru-chan!
Wait...
Nanami-chan!?
Chinatsu-chan!
It's too late!
Why... Why does everyone have to torment me!?
It's not working...
Nanami-chan!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Chinatsu-chan.
Chinatsu-chan... let's go.
Anywhere. I'll go with you wherever you want.
I know you were sad...
I know you were alone.
You went through so many unbelievable things....
Everyone took advantage of you...
You fought it for so long.
Nanami-chan...
I'll always be here for you.
I'll never let go of your hand.
Really?
Yes, because... we're best friends.
Nanami-chan...
Chinatsu-chan...
Thank you.
To think a vengeful ghost could
pass on as a heavenly spirit...
Your servant failed, Tsukuyomi.
You sent Satori?
If that's really the best you can do...
Then maybe you do belong in the gutter.
If I may...
What is it?
I have another way to defeat our enemies.
If you give me another chance, I'll definitely...!
Definitely lose, you mean.
Very well, Satori.
Just don't you dare lose again.
Tsukuyomi-sama... Thank you
for this second chance.
It will be the last one I need.
Just be prepared for the consequences...
Yes. None of them will leave.