To those who have the courage to
struggle against the evil beings...
I am pleased that you have made it this far.
You have my thanks.
Oh, y-you're welcome.
Then I shall await the proper time.
Yes, Seiryuu-sama...
Hikaru-sama, everyone, let us proceed.
Oh, right.
Hikaru-san, your nose is bleeding.
Aren't you the young one, Hikaru-chan?
Honestly, if you get so many nosebleeds,
then drink some fluids or something.
I don't want advice from you.
What's that supposed to mean?
That hurts, damn it!
Hikaru-san, not there!
Wait, don't move or...
Hikaru-san, you're making it worse!
Stop that!!
Wait, wait, use the handkerchief.
That shrine maiden...
Isn't just any normal one, is she?
HEroAP Presents
JADE TEMPTATION
Hey, is that enough for us to for back to our world?
No...
The inversing spell requires all
of the Four Great Sage Beasts.
Of course...
The Four Great Sage Beasts... or powerful animals.
But then, Seiryuu-san seemed more like
a goddess than a beast, didn't she?
Can't say the same for everyone though.
Nagisa, in your case, you could only cause
a nosebleed because you're violent.
How about I give you one right now?
Just three left...
Genbu, Byakko, Suzaku...
Amaterasu-san, what's wrong?
I fee a strong energy...
We'd best be moving on.
What happened?
What's going on?
Hikaru!
Hikaru-san!
Everyone! Where are you?
Was that a spell, Tsukuyomi?
I've separated them...
I see.
That should make things easier for Satori.
Then there's no reason for me to watch over this.
I'm going back.
Very well. Rest assured that we're
ready for what happens.
By the way...
You seem to like that girl of yours.
What's your point?
She Isn't from Nenokuni, for one.
So you're suspicious too.
You infer quite a lot.
Just be mindful about your feelings.
What?
You have to, for your dear mother's sake.
Tsukuyomi, are you trying to piss me off?
Such a scary face...
It looks like a demon's.
And to show it to a poor woman like me.
Manipulative wretch...
Such is the heart of a juvenile...
Tengu! Are you there, Tengu?!
Hikaru-chan...?
Everyone?
Where is this?
Who's there!?
Who are you!?
You've forgotten me?
Have you forgotten about me, Ayaka?
I don't... I don't know you!
Don't lie like that.
You remember all right.
There's no way that you could forget about me.
I don't! I don't know who you are!
That body of yours could never
allow you to forget me.
No...
NO!!
Stay away...
Stay away!!
You remember me.
Your young, supple body...
That sweet smell, and that loud, gratifying scream.
No, please...
You've tried to forget...
What I've done for you.
And what you've done to me.
What's wrong? You've done this everyday before.
Come on!
Yes, just like I taught you to do.
That's it...
Yes, very good.
You're getting good, Ayaka.
Good. Don't let up.
Keep up the pace.
You still want more, Father?
Of course. I haven't gotten my fill from you yet.
Such a perverted daughter.
You only gave me a blowjob and you're this wet.
Don't say that, Father.
Yeah, Ayaka...
Ayaka...
You belong to me.
I know that.
You'd be nothing without me.
Father.
Please, don't come inside me!
It'll be fine.
You and I are only related by name only.
So who cares if you have a baby?
Ayaka onee-chan...
What is it, Hikaru-chan?
What's wrong?
You don't seem like yourself today.
It's nothing at all.
Really?
Really.
But you look... scared.
Why? Don't I look the same as usual?
No, you look scared, and sad.
There's nothing wrong, really.
Why are you crying?
It's nothing. It's nothing at all.
Onee-chan!
Ayaka onee-chan...
Where am I?
Amaterasu!
Hikaru-sama...
Are you alright?
Y-Yes...
And everyone else?
I don't know.
This is Suzaku's forest...
Suzaku? You mean...?
Yes, we can find Suzaku of the Four Great
Sage Beasts somewhere here.
It's said to be the most beautiful place in Nenokuni.
The evil beings don't seem to have broken in yet.
But are they here too?
No, l can't feel any of their presence.
All right, then first let's go and find the others.
Right. Then let's meet up here later.
Yeah.
Your body hasn't changed at all, has it Ayaka?
Don't say those things
No matter what you say. you're always
going to be my piece of meat.
You're getting the tatami all sopping wet.
You dirty slut.
I'd be ashamed of you if I were your real father.
I'm back!
I'm home!
The others...
Hikaru...
Damn it, how could I let this happen.
Where did everyone go to?
Hikaru-sama! Hikaru-sama!
Touka?
I feel an evil presence.
Someone may have been captured by it.
It's coming from underneath us.
Got it.
Damn...
Kaede, I need your power!
Ayaka-san?
Ayaka-san!
No! Don't look at me, Hikaru-chan!
Don't look!
Ayaka-san!
You're such a bad daughter...
Murdering your surrogate father like that...
I-I'm sorry...
Now for your punishment!
I'm sorry!
Ayaka-san!
No! Stop!
Please, don't put those in me!
No! Don't look!
What am I supposed to do?
I have nowhere else to go...
Hikaru-chan...
Ayaka-san!
Ayaka-san...
I can't let you... see me like this.
I don't want him... to watch this.
Who's... that kid?
This will be your home from now on.
From now on! you'll be our daughter.
We'll be your mom and dad from now on.
From todays...?
What do you mean, from today?
Hey, fath...
Didn't I say that from the start?
Nagisa and our dead child aren't the same thing.
She'll never be able to replace him.
But, I don't know if I can bring myself to do this...
Hey, what are you taking about?
What kid?
Becoming parents again may make things better.
My parents?
Aren't I a part of this family?
Wasn't I born here?
I'm sorry. I suppose time with
eventually heal everything.
Akiha...
No way...
Then where did I come from?
Who am I?
No... No, I can't accept that!
Well...?
How does it feel to watch your friend's true nature?
This girl tried to kill her surrogate father
after making the effort to take her in.
No, I didn't!
And now, shamelessly enjoying herself
while a monster fills her every orifice.
No... Stop. Hikaru-chan...
Don't look!
Just look, she's completely into it.
I don't know what I should do with her.
Don't waste your time.
No human can break my spells.
Hikaru-chan...
Ayaka-san!
What!?
Impossible, no human can break that!
Ayaka-san...
Hikaru-chan...
Quite the shock, Isn't it?
That I'm... such a... murderer.
You're not a murderer, Ayaka-san...
As far as I know, that guy deserved to die.
That doesn't matter! I was planning to kill him.
I'm sorry, Ayaka-san...
Why are you apologizing, Hikaru?
I was only a kid at the time.
I didn't even realize... nor could I do anything...
Ayaka-san?
I'm sorry... Just when you were
setting such a good mood...
I'm...
You can't control it, can you?
Hikaru-chan...
Ayaka-san...
Wow...
Sorry, it's hards not to get aroused...
Go ahead then.
It's sliding around... inside me.
Ayaka-san!
I'm going to come!
Hikaru-chan!
Ayaka-san... Why is it that you
came back to us of all places?
That's my little secret.
A-Amaterasu-san...
Why...?
Amaterasu...
How I hate that name.
Hikaru-san...
I'm sorry...
Why can't you do this, Nagisa?
I'm sorry!
Isn't it embarrassing enough that you're an
adopted daughter in the Kurashima family?
I'm sorry, Mother!
Akiha could do these problems when he was three.
Akiha?
I-It's nothing.
Now do them again!
You don't get your snack until you do!
Ok...
Isn't this Nagisa's house?
I'll look here!
Ayaka-san, you go and find Nanami-chan!
All right!
Nagisa!
Nagisa!!
What's with you, Nagisa?
What do you mean, "what's with me"?
Why do always want to pick a fight?
I'm not trying to pick a fights...
And anyway, from here out, you are
to address me by my proper title.
You're to treat me more like the princess that I am.
The best all around at any sport.
The one intelligent beyond her years.
You're open!
Nagisa!
Hey, Nagisa!
Come back here!
You're the one who never backs down!
Don't you always brag like that to people!?
What do you know?
So I'm not really in the same family
that I said I was. What's it to you!?
l do know one thing...
You'll always be Nagisa Kurashima!
Well duh, of course I am!
I'm... Nagisa Kurashima...
You're open!
Hey! Nagisa!
That's right...
Even when I doubted my own self,
Hikaru was there for me...
Nagisa! Are you with me?
Hikaru...
Thank goodness...Thank goodness.
Let's do it, Hikaru...
W-What?
I want you to take me.
But...
Just shut up and take me.
Nagisa...
Damn you two!
You couldn't be... all of you couldn't be...!
Hikaru!
Nagisa!