Shrine maiden...
All is...
Useless...
Be silent, yomotsu okami!
yomotsu okami can be translated to "ancient, great deity"
Be silent...
Why?! Why am I the only one who has to suffer?!
Why... Must I endure this pain alone?!
Why?! Why only me?!
Because you have been abandoned, yomotsu okami.
It is only because you have betrayed yourself.
Preposterous!
The great one did not complete me.
Just look at that damned land.
There's nowhere for you to go in that world of yours!
Why do it? Why is it that you protect this place?
This unfair world that was created?!
Even so, I...
I'm sorry, Izanami.
I caused great pain to your soul.
It was a disdainful wish that scarred your heart.
Ever since then, I have had unpleasant
feelings toward myself.
I'm sure you must bear great hatred toward me.
That would be... untrue.
For everything as with me.
That is why you fought so boldly.
I... believed that you would create something grand.
Izanami.
And I am disappointed as well...
Izanagi... sama.
Think of me not as a lowly
maiden, but as a woman...
Izanagi-sama...
Izanami...
I propose this to you.
Within my body I have a place of masculinity.
Within your body you have a place of femininity.
I wish to join my place of masculinity
with yours of femininity within us.
In which we will create the lands.
I do. I accept.
Izanami! Izanami!
Izanagi-sama. Inzanagi-sama.
Izanagi-sama.
I feel it...
Your energy...
Warm...
Life...
HEroAP Presents
Indigo Magatama
Miyuki Touma (18 yrs.)
Hikaru Touma (19 yrs.)
Ouch...
Don't worry, onii-chan.
Hmph, I don't do well in the morning.
But then, jii-chan's always tough like that.
How long do I have to practice this?
Rokusuke Touma
For 2025 years.
Most people would just say 2000
years when they joke.
More like, it didn't seem like a joke at all.
Hikaru, Miyuki, if you really feel like always
saying such things, I'll cut you off.
It would be better for you to pay
your own way through school.
Fine, then you can cook for
yourself starting tomorrow.
It takes a lot of effort to make food every morning.
It would be better to cook for yourself.
All right, all right.
Then I'll only cut off Hikaru.
Hey!!
Nanami Minase (18 yrs.)
Hikaru-senpai.
Miyuki-chan.
They look like... they're a couple.
Nanami-chan!
Morning, Nanami-chan.
Morning, Miyuki-chan.
Nanami-chan, about this thing...
I guess I can't bring myself to give it to him.
Why not?
Some girls have confessed to him too,
but I heard they were all rejected.
I don't think onii-chan wants to
go out with anyone right now.
I see.
I think for now you should just continue to
be good friends with him, Nanami-chan.
Maybe you're right. Thanks, Miyuki-chan.
Hey!
Morning, Nanami-chan.
Ah, good morning, Hikaru-senpai.
You're sure working hard this morning...
Are you over your insomnia?
Huh?
Didn't you say that you literally
couldn't sleep for three days?
Oh, I'm perfectly fine.
And it looks like you wrote a love letter there.
N-No, it isn't.
Hmm... I wonder what kind
of guy Nanami-chan likes.
I'm getting jealous.
Hey, I told you it's not a love letter, senpai!
Onii-chan. didn't you have an English
test or something today?
Huh? There is?!
I reminded you over and over last night, didn't I?
Cra - I didn't have a clue!
Catch you later!
Took you long enough, Hikaru!
Nagisa Kurashima (19 yrs.)
I thought you were avoiding me...
My astounding swordsmanship versus
your old, decrepit swordsmanship.
Which is better... We're settling it all today!
W-Wait a minute, Nagisa!
I don't have time to deal with that this morning!
I have an English test today!
T-E-S-T!
Do you understand me?
Of course I understand.
Let's do this!
W-Wait a second!
Touma's in the fight now!
Then I put five on Hikaru!
I'm all for Kurashima to win.
I'm rooting for Nagisa!
This one's all Kurashima!
Could you not struggle?
What if I want to struggle?!
Just give it up!
Didn't you just say you weren't up to it?
Well I'm not just going to let you win!
Hikaru-senpai?
Onii-chan...
My win, Hikaru.
Your underwear's in plain sight, Nagisa...
You peeping... bastard!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan! Wake up! Onii-chan!
Nagisa-san, you're horrible! Hitting him so hard!
H-Hey, you always smack him around too.
I-It's different since we're siblings!
If you say so...
Um, more importantly, shouldn't we
be getting him to the nurse's office?
Y-Yeah, we should.
Hey, Kanaka, help me out here!
Great one, please help our people.
A noble kyuuseishu...
To save us in our time of need.
Who are you?
Ayaka Tachibana
You're awake, Hikaru-chan.
A-Ayaka-san...
Don't worry, you just had a shock to the system.
Uh, Ayaka-san...
No, no, at school you have to
call me Tachibana-sensei.
That's not the problem...
What's with this questionable setup?
Because...
It's been forever since I've been with you...
Ayaka-san...
Hmm? What's wrong?
You're turning red.
Sure you don't have a fever?
Oh, you're just being shy.
O-Of course I am!
What's wrong, Hikaru-chan? You're acting weird.
We’ve been in the bath together.
Y-You mean when I was just a little kid, right?
And Miyuki was with us too!
Hikaru was so cute back then...
She's not even listening.
"Hey, hey, why does your chest stick
out like that? Can I touch it?"
Remember you said that?
You were pretty bold back then, Hikaru-chan...
Well?
Do you want to try touching them again?
Excuse us!
Are you alright, onii-chan?
Oh good, senpai's already awake.
See? He's alive all right.
Come on in.
Nanami-chan told me...
...that she was jealous of me.
Why would she say that?
I don't know what she could ever
be jealous of about you.
You're horrible! What's that supposed to mean?!
She said that she was jealous that
I had such a good older brother.
Oh, did she now?
In that case, just tell her that I'm available
to be her brother whenever she wants.
No!
What's... with the angry tone?
198!
199!
200!
That wasn't any ordinary dream, was it?
Sorry... Nanami-chan...
It's just...
I'm kind of...
With onii-chan...
Onii-chan! You pervert!
We finally meet...
The word "kyuuseishu" can partially be translated with words like savior or messiah.
Kyuuseishu-sama...
Kyuuseishu?
Yes.
The person who I am destined for.
Izumo Academy?
This classroom...
She's gone.
That dream again.
Hey. jii-chan...
Is there some girl who wants me at school?
Onii-chan, where did that come from?!
I'm being serious.
I was wondering since I had a weird dream.
A dream?
Yeah, it had a girl dressed as a shrine maiden...
Dressed as... a shrine maiden?
What, ojii-chan? Do you know what it is?
No, but... Izumo Academy has a
lot of tremors going around it.
I'll be sure to talk to the board chairman
about any spiritual-related things.
Uhm, say...
l-ls there someone...
...that you like?
What do you think about Nanami-chan?
Nanam-chan?
What about Nagisa-san?
Or Ayaka-san?
Hey...
Or even that shrine maiden you saw in your dream.
Hey!
And me...
What do you think... of me?
W-What... about you?
Of course you can't answer.
After all. I'm just your sister, aren't I?
That's right. Don't ask me such weird questions.
Onii-chan?
I forgot something. I'm going back for it.
OK, be sure to catch up.
Yeah!
It's here. No doubt about it.
One, two - !!
What are you doing?
N-Nagisa! What are you doing out here?
The place I study is in this direction,
and this way's shorter.
And what might you be doing?
Swinging your bokutou wildly like that.
Oh. I'm just...
Hey. Nagisa. Do you believe in ghosts or spirits?
Huh?
What's with this classroom?
Why isn't there anything in here?
What a weird room.
Hikaru?
Is there something under there?
W-What's that?
A stone doorway?
What's that doing under the school?
N-Now what?
An earthquake?
H-Hikaru!
What is that thing?
Looks like an alter, or something.
A mirror?
You made it upset!
Another earthquake?
Crap! Run for it, Nagisa!
Nagisa...
You alright?
Why the hell are you groping me, pervert!
This looks like the place we came in...
It think so too, but, what is all this?
Someone! Please help me!
Hikaru-senpai!
Nagisa-san! Help me down from here!
Nanami-chan!
What happened to you?
I was on my way to my club, then
there was this earthquake...
Then everything turned white around me.
and when I woke up I was up here.
Hikaru?
Senpai?
Yeah...
Don't you have any tact?
It's hurting me!
Nanami-chan!
Something's got my legs!
Let go!
Nagisa!
Whoa! What is that thing?
What is that monster?
Hikaru!
Senpai!
Get away!
Damn monster.
Hold it!
I'm over here...
Come and get me!
Thank you very much, senpai.
Oops...
No one's here.
What happened?
Are we the only ones that didn't make it out?
And then that alter...
No good. I can't get anything on my cell phone.
I see...
What's wrong?
Oh, I thought I heard something.
A-Ayaka sensei?
She's asleep.
All the way through that earthquake.
Nanami-chan, don't worry about it.
It doesn't matter if you've gained a little weight...
S-Sensei!!
No good, everything around us has changed.
Let's try to find another town.
I'm sure we'll run into something past that forest.
I forgot something. I'll catch up later.
Miyuki, please be all right.
Who's there?!
My name is Kaede...
I was the jyorogumo that you fought.
"Jyorogumo" Is the Japanese word for Nephila clavata. a species
of golden orb-web spider that is quite common in Japan.
I was the jyorogumo that you fought.
Jyorogumo?
Yes,and now I’m at quite a loss.
Don't go to sleep!
What I mean is, I'll like for you
to take me as my new master.
Huh?
Um, I have no clue what you're talking about...
H-Hey!
Don't worry.
This is a dream. Only a dream, Hikaru-san.
Hikaru-sama...
Here I go.
It's so good, Hikaru-sama!
Kaede-san.
Please, I need you to spread your essence inside me.
There it is...
Your energy's inside me.
Our destinies are now entwined, my master.
I A dream?