Onii-chan.
Miyuki.
I'll never leave you again.
You belong only to me!
Miyuki...
Miyuki!
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan... I love you.
I love you very much!
Volume 5
Red Encounter
Onii-chan...
You're so pretty.
No, I'm embarrassed.
I feel good. Your hand is so... warm.
Your body is also warm.
No, Onii-ch-
I'm feeling a bit weird.
Miyuki, you're already very...
I'm sorry.
The idea itself, of you and me having...
Silly girl. Why are you apologizing?
Because...
Are you happy, Miyuki?
Very.
Are you all right?
Please come in, Onii-chan.
Miyuki.
Onii-chan...
Here.
You must eat. Otherwise, you won't make it through.
If you don't eat...
Thank you.
Delicious!
The last one must be in there!
Hikaru-sama, I detect an evil energy in that temple.
Please be careful.
Got it!
Hey! You!
So you're still alive.
Amaterasu.
Hey, you! Don't scare me like that!
Genbu and Byakko have been freed.
Yes.
We only have to free Suzaku here, right?
Then you can return to Ashihara.
Let's take care of this quickly!
But if Suzaku can't be freed,
then everything will have been in vain.
What does that mean, Amaterasu-san?
It means...
Nagisa!
Amaterasu! What are you doing?!
Don't be afraid.
You will die painlessly...
just like that girl.
That girl?!
Nanami. That was her name, from what I remember.
What?
You will see her again soon.
What did you do to Nanami-chan?!
Nanami-chan.
I can't believe it!
Nanami-chan!
That's... Hikaru-chan's...
My name is Touka.
Please hold me close to her wound!
Huh?
Quickly!
If her spirit leaves her body completely, it will be too late!
Ayaka...
Sensei?
It's a miracle! Nanami-chan!
You were attacked by an evil spirit.
Hikaru-san!
Hikaru-san's in danger!
What's happened to you, Amaterasu?!
You're completely different.
You can't do anything against this girl, can you?
My name's Tsukuyomi.
I belong to Yomotsu Okami-sama.
The ruler of dead souls!
Hikaru!
Even the two of you together don't stand a chance.
Hikaru-san!
Hikaru-chan!
How in God's name...
Amaterasu?
Two of them?
I was careless.
Someone who looks like me took control of my body.
So that was why...
What kind of powerful soul is that?
I...
was expelled.
Be gone, evil spirit!
That's not a very nice thing to say about your sister.
Sure, I'm an evil spirit,
but that's because you've made me one.
You're talking nonsense. I don't have a sister!
You should know, Amaterasu.
Every member of our family has the power to control dreams.
We'll meet again...
my little sister.
I'm an idiot.
Yoo-hoo!
Congratulations! You've succeeded in freeing them all!
Y-You're the last one, Suzaku.
That's not a very nice thing...
to say about your sister.
Miyuki,
Grandfather...
I will return to you soon.
Um...
I love you, Hikaru-san.
Ever since I...
first met you on the lake.
I wish...
just for this one time, to have...
Give me...
a memory that will stay with me forever.
I feel very good.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Hikaru-san, please don't ever forget me.
A strong will can make things come true.
Such is the power that weaves dreams.
Your home...
Someone who's important to you...
Grandfather...
Miyuki...
Miyuki!
You stupid people!
The King of Kings, Sanou, has arrived!
Susanoo?!
Amaterasu!
Grandfather?
I...
Is this... a real sword?!
Please, save...
your mother, Izanami!
And your inheritance!
What are you talking about, Grandfather?
Go with your four servants.
They're from Nenoku.
They don't have any family and were raised here in Ashiharanoku.
Destiny has brought them to you.
Miyuki is also one of them.
She's not your little sister.
I have waited for this day.
No one knew when this day would come.
Grandfather, then I am...
Go to Yomotsuhirasakai,
I'm relying on you, Hikaru.
Forgive me.
I didn't know.
Everyone, follow me!
Okay!
I wanted the tears of Ikkikun.
I've longed for the love of a mother.
I envied you.
I only wanted to play... with my little sister.
Onee-san...
From now on, we'll always be together.
Susanoo!
Brave of you to return.
Why are you attacking those people?
It's all because of Yomotsu Okami,
and a wish from my mother!
What?!
If you don't like it, then come here!
Child of Izanami, born in Nenokuni and raised in Ashiharanokuni!
Child of Izanami?
Die at last!
No!
Sanou-kun, stop it!
Miyuki?
This can't be...
Sanou-kun!
Miyuki?
Why?
Why do you brothers want to kill each other?
Susanoo is your little brother, Onii-chan.
It was he who saved me.
My brother?
Hikaru-chan's...
Sanou is your...
Yomotsu Okami...
and your mother Izanami...
were originally one.
Yomotsu Okami-sama was born out of Izanami's evil spirit.
They are opposites of one another:
a god of destruction and a god of protection.
Then our enemy, the King of evil spirits Yomotsu Okami is...
Yes.
For a long time, you people have been chasing...
my mother Yomotsu Okami.
In reality, she is part of your treasured Izanami.
That can't be.
I am the child of Yomotsu Okami, Sanou!
I protected my mother and killed all enemies
who opposed her!
Sanou-kun!
It's all right. He's not heavily injured.
I've learned the true reason why he was following me.
Hikaru...
Hikaru-san...
Let's go, to Yomotsuhirasakai!
This place belongs to Yomotsu Okami.
Izanami-sama's power to create dreams has built this.
Please be at peace, Yomotsu Okami!
We are...
back again.
Now, everyone, let's go home.
Onii-chan!
I've just apoligized to Nanami-chan about the letter.
I see.
But aren't you mad about it?
H-Hey, Miyuki!
This time...
it's my turn.
Are you feeling good?
Yes, great, Miyuki!
I'm going in.
I'm inside.
D-Did I hurt you?
No.
Maybe a little, but...
I'm happy that I'm now connected with you.
Miyuki...
Please, Onii-chan.
Go on. I'm fine.
I'll start, but gently.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Can you endure it for a bit more?
YES! YES!
Miyuki...
Miyuki!
Onii-chan!
Hikaru, my son.
Not of human origins, prodigy born out of my dreams,
I gave all my love to Izanagi-sama.
You are the result of that love.
Hikaru, I thank you!
Original translation
Anime Crystal Fansubs
English translation
M74
Editing
Collectr
In this old place,
there is a phantom
that is calling to me.
Through the mirror, I can see the other side.
The maze has started to distort space-time.
You stand in front of me,
but are you real or unreal?
My legs tremble, and I fall deeply.
That proves to me
it's a fake.
Despite the many bitter memories that have hurt us,
we must fight on and achieve something.
Be brave,
don't let go of my hand.
Let's cross the bridge of hope together,
which I previously...