Yes, I understand.
I can't make it tomorrow,
but I can probably visit sometime around the 3rd.
I'll talk about it when I get back.
Okay.
I won't be able to stay overnight.
I already have work at that time.
Your Dad must be on the grea...
Absolutely not!
All right.
I'm hanging up now.
See you then.
Yeah, Happy New Year.
Okay!
Toshikoshi soba coming right up!
Ohh, thanks.
What did your mom say?
She says she's looking forward to it.
That's all?
She also said she wants to see her grandchildren soon.
Well, she's at her usual.
So this movie's about to premiere soon.
You know this movie?
It seems to be all the rage in America.
There's lots of commercials for it recently.
I see.
Oh, you don't watch much TV.
Not really.
Hey, can we watch this together sometime?
Hey, you can't sleep just yet!
We're going to watch the New Year sunrise together, you know!
I'm good. I just need to nap for a bit.
You say that,
but you always sleep until morning.
Then, please wake me up when it's midnight.
It'll be way too late at that point!
I'm good. I'm totally good, really.
What are you... doing?
You get perked up with this, right?
Wait, just give me a break.
Hey...!
It'll be bad...
if you do it all the way...
Hey!
I'm about to cum.
Sachi...
Well?
Did that wake you up?
Yeah, all thanks to you.
Wow.
What are you going to do with this?
Well then,
I was thinking that it's about time.
Time for what?
To have a baby... I guess?
Don't you agree?
Well, I do, but...
Right?
Shall we head to bed, then?
'Kay.
What's wrong?
Well, I'm kinda nervous.
Isn't it strange?
Feeling that way at this point...
Sou-kun?
Have you manged to calm down?
Yeah.
I'm fine now.
Raise your hips.
It's wet already.
See? It's overflowing from the inside.
That's...
because I want you...
Sou-kun... Sou-kun...!
I'll do it this time.
You did it earlier, though.
I want to do it properly, okay?
I'll leave it to you, then.
Okay.
Whats wrong?
You're so cute.
Hey now.
Sachi, I'm good now.
About to cum?
Yeah.
All right then.
Sou-kun, come.
Sachi.
Don't you feel cold?
No, I'm fine.
You're making me warm.
You feel warm, too.
Sou-kun,
cum lots inside of me, okay?
Okay.
Let's make lots of babies.
You and I are going to make lots of babies!
I can't hold it in any longer.
Sou-kun...!
Sou-kun!
Sachi!
Hey, why do you want to have many kids?
You said it earlier,
that we should make lots of babies.
Oh,
that's because,
a larger family is best, right?
Which reminds me,
you were an only child, right?
Well, yeah.
You're such a lonesome boy.
That's not what I meant.
Honestly,
I want a boy as our first child.
Someone who'll get to be as cool as you.
I think I'll be happier if our child will be like you.
Even if our baby is a boy?
That's right.
Weirdo.