Yeah, I know.
We can't go tomorrow, but we'll be there
sometime around the third of the month.
Okay, let's talk about it again when we go there.
Yeah.
You shouldn't worry about it.
Nah... I'm am busy with work.
Okay, okay.
I'm hanging up. Alright then.
Yeah, the year is almost over.
Here it is!
Here's the new year buckwheat noodles.
Oh, thank you.
What did mom say?
She says she's looking forward on our visit.
Just that?
Also to hurry and let her see her grandchild's face.
Well, it's the same as always.
Ahh...
They're already showing this movie.
Are you familiar with it?
It seemed that this movie became a big hit in America.
They made good commercials of it.
I see...
You haven't been watching on TV lately, Sou-kun.
Yeah...
Hey... Do you want to see this movie together?
Hey, I told you not to fall asleep!
Aren't we going to see the first sunrise of the year?
It's alright, I'm just taking a little nap.
You say that but you always
end up sleeping til morning.
Then, just wake me up when morning comes.
We'll already be late by then!
Alright... It's alright...
Jeez...
What are you doing?
This will keep you awake, right?
Wait... Give me a break...
Hey...
If you do it that much...
It's gonna be bad, hey!
I'm gonna come!
Sachi...
How was it?
Did that wake you up?
Yeah... Thanks to you.
Wow... Amazing!
What should we do about this now?
W-Well then...
Hmm?
I thought that it's about time already...
For what?
H-Having a baby, I mean...
You don't want one?
W-Well... I want one too.
Right?
Then, should we go in our bedroom?
Okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing... I just started feeling nervous.
Am I not weird, feeling like this now?
S-Sou-kun?
Did you calm down?
Yes... I'm alright now.
Raise your hips up.
You're already wet.
Look, it's steadily dripping out so much from the inside.
That's because...
I already want your thing...
S-Sou-kun... Sou-kun!
I'll do it next...
You already did it before.
I want to do it properly...
Well then, go ahead.
Okay.
Hmm? What the matter?
You're cute down here.
Oh, you...
Sachi, that's enough.
Are you about to come?
Yeah...
Okay.
Come here, Sou-kun!
Sachi...
Sachi, are you feeling cold?
No... I'm fine.
You're giving me warmth!
You're warm as well!
Sou-kun...
Come a lot inside me tonight!
Yeah... Let's make a bunch of kids, okay?
I will bear lots and lots
of children for us!
I can't take it anymore...
Sou-kun...
Sou-kun!
Sachi!
Hey, Sou-kun...
Why do you want plenty of children?
Didn't you say it earlier?
That we should make a bunch of kids.
Yeah... Isn't it merrier to have a larger family?
Now that I remember, you're an only child.
That's right.
You were lonely, right?
It's not really like that.
I want to have a boy first.
I want him to be as handsome as you.
I'd prefer one that resembles you.
Even if it's a boy?
Even if it's a boy.
You're weird.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Happy New Year!