Yeah, I know.
Tomorrow's not good for me.
I'll visit around the beginning of the new year.
Yeah, let's talk about that when I come.
Right.
Children? Don't think so.
Well, we've got work...
My old man's really stingy.
You take too much!
Yeah, I know. I need to go.
I'll talk to you later.
Yeah.
Happy new year.
Hey, here's the New Years Soba.
Wow, thank you.
What'd your mom say?
She said she can't wait.
That's it?
She said she wants to see a grandchild soon.
Well, you know, the usual.
Ah...
Jewelry
This movie's already out?
You've heard of it?
Apparently it was a huge hit in America.
Wow.
There are commercials for it all the time.
Really?
Oh, right, you don't really watch TV, do you, Sou-kun?
Yeah...
Hey, how about we go see it together some time?
Hey, don't fall asleep!
We're gonna watch the sunrise together aren't we?
I'm okay. Just taking a little nap.
You know, you always say that,
but then you just sleep until morning anyway!
Then wake me up in the morning.
That's too late!
It's okay. It'll be okay.
Geez.
What are you... doing?
Now you're not sleepy, right?
Hey come on, give me a break.
Hey!
If you keep that up...
I'm gonna cum.
Hey!
I'm gonna cum!
Sachi...
So?
Are you awake now?
Yeah, thanks to you.
Wow.
What are we gonna do about this?
Then how about we...
I've been thinking that maybe it's about time for us to...
To do what?
T-To make a baby, you know... something like that?
You don't want one?
N-No, I...
I do.
Right?!
Okay then.
Let's go to the bedroom.
Yeah.
What's the matter?
I'm just so nervous all of a sudden.
Isn't that strange?
Getting cold feet now...
S-Sou-kun?
Calmed down?
Yeah.
I'm okay now.
Lift your waist up.
Okay.
You're already wet.
Yeah...
It just keeps flowing out from inside.
I-It just wants you so bad...
S-Sou-kun? Sou-kun!
Let me help you now.
You just did, remember?
I want to do it right.
Okay then, thanks.
Sure.
What's up?
Your dick's so cute.
Oh, you.
Sachi, I should be good now.
Are you about to cum?
Yeah.
Okay.
Sou-kun, come here.
Sachi...
Sachi, are you warm enough?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You're warming me up.
You're warming me up too!
Sou-kun!
Make sure you cum lots inside me today, okay?
Yeah, let's make tons of kids together!
We're going to have babies together!
We're going to have so many!
I'm almost there...
Sou-kun...
Sou-kun!
Sachi!
So why do you want so many children, Sou-kun?
Huh?
You said you wanted a lot of children, didn't you?
Yeah. The bigger the family, the better, don't you think?
Now that I think about it, you
were an only child, weren't you?
Yeah, I was.
So you're lonely then?
No, that's not true...
You know, I hope our first child is a boy.
I want a little boy who's as amazing as you.
I'd rather a kid more like you.
Even if it's a boy?
Yeah, even if it's a boy.
That's weird of you.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч