Yeah, I know.
Tomorrow's not good for me.
I'll visit around the start of the new year.
Yeah, we'll talk about that when I visit.
Right.
Children? I don't think so.
Well, we've got work to do...
My old man's so cheap...
Shut up!
Yeah, I know. I gotta go...
Talk to you later.
Yeah.
Happy new year.
Here's the new year's soba.
Oh, thank you.
What did your mom say?
She said she can't wait.
That's all?
She said she wants to see a grandchild soon.
You know, the usual.
Ah...
This movie's already out?
You've heard of it?
Supposedly, it was a big hit in America.
Ah...
There're commercials for it all the time.
Really?
That's right, you don't really
watch TV, do you Sou-kun?
Yeah...
Hey, how about we go see it together some time?
Hey, don't fall asleep!
Weren't we going to watch the sunrise together?
I'm okay. Just taking a short nap.
You always say that but
then you sleep till morning anyway.
Then wake me up in the morning.
That'll be too late!
It's okay... it'll be okay...
Geez...
What are you... doing?
You're not sleepy now, right?
Hey, come on, give me a break.
Hey...
If you keep that up...
I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna cum!
Sachi...
So?
Are you awake now?
Yeah, thanks to you.
Wow.
What are we gonna do about this?
Then how about we...
I've been thinking, maybe it's time for us to...
To do what?
To make a baby, you know... something like that.
Don't you want one?
N-No, I...
I do.
Alright?
Okay then.
Let's go to the bedroom.
Yes.
What's the matter?
I'm suddenly all nervous.
Isn't that weird?
Getting cold feet now...
S-Sou-kun?
Calmed down?
Yeah.
I'm okay now.
Lift yourself up.
Okay.
You're already wet.
Yeah.
It just keeps... flowing out.
It just wants you so bad.
S-Sou-kun?
Let me help you now.
You just did, remember?
I wanna do it right.
Okay then, thanks.
Sure.
What's up?
Your dick's so cute.
Oh, you.
Sachi, I should be good now.
Are you about to cum?
Yeah.
Okay.
Sou-kun, come here.
Sachi...
Sachi, are you warm enough?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You're warming me up.
You're warming me up too.
Sou-kun!
Make sure you cum ant inside me today, okay?
Okay, let's make tons of kids together!
We're going to have babies together!
We're gonna have so many!
I'm almost there!
Sou-kun...
Sou-kun!
Sachi!
So why do you want so many children, Sou-kun?
Huh?
You said you wanted a ton of children, didn't you?
The bigger the family the better, don't you think?
Now that I think about it,
you were an only child, right?
Yeah, I was.
So you must have been lonely?
No, that's not true.
You know, I hope our first child is a boy.
A little boy who's as amazing as you.
I'd rather have a kid more like you.
Even if it's a boy?
Yeah, even if it's a boy.
You're weird.