My name is Kareki Tsunetaka.
I've been our home's security officer for
twenty years. I'm a veteran so to speak.
Equipped with my decked out computer,
I can surveil and monitor all activity in this house.
And now I have a mission I need to complete.
This woman has recently married my father and is
without a doubt targeting our, no, my fortune.
It doesn't make sense otherwise why she'd
marry a boring nobody tike my dad
and willingly live under the same roof as me.
I need to protect this house from this bitch.
That's my mission.
My dad is rarely home because of work.
That means that this bitch is illegally
trespassing on my property.
What's worse is that there are three of these bitches,
I'm at an overwhelming disadvantage.
One day they'll move out.
Until that happens,
I'm going to have to make sure that they never want
to try to get near me or this house ever again.
I've already completed my work on step sister A.
That means there are two left.
And the next target is...
Original Work Beelzebub
Original Animation Disk
Home Security Officer
2nd Mission
The Cheeky Second Daughter - Yuki Arc
Hey, mind moving? You're in my way.
And this is the second daughter of that whore, Yuki.
What's your problem?
What're you staring at me for? It's creepy.
Out of the way. Quit just standing there.
Do you even have a brain? Jeez.
And that's how that bitch always acts towards me.
She gives me a condescending look like
she's looking at garbage or something.
Seriously what's wrong with the values
of the people in this family?
They both go to a rich girl school, but apparently
she's smarter than her older sister.
But all she does at home is watch tv and play videogames.
I don't get it.
Ew, don't tell me you're going to eat with me.
Yuck! That's so nasty!
She's always very curt with me and then verbally abuses me.
She's the complete opposite when she's around her mother,
but in the end, she's still that whore's daughter.
I need to stop this cancer from spreading!
With these, I'll bring all of Yuki's secrets out into the light.
I've got videos, digital cameras, and wiretaps.
I'll plant them all around where these bitches frequent.
I wonder how I can become as big as onee-chan...
I massage them every day, but maybe that
doesn't really have too much of an effect.
Oh? Yuki wants bigger breasts?
She could just ask me to massage
them. I'd show them a great time.
With the bugs I planted I can capture all
of these bitch's embarrassing moments.
And little by little, I'll begin to grasp their weaknesses.
I'll instill a fear strong enough to traumatize them for life!
Ah god, I'm so pissed. Why do I have
to be nice to that creepy guy?
Yeah, no problem. Twelve o'clock then, okay?
Yeah should be out by then probably.
Nothing's coming.
I'm so tired of this.
I guess even with a face like that, she
can't hide her true sexual desire,
I hit the jackpot.
This is going perfectly!
But this still isn't enough for blackmail.
Hm? I see her come here every now and
then... is this one of Yuki's classmates?
I was so lonely.
It's okay, right?
We can't, Narumi! My Mom might be home soon.
Doing this at home might not be the best idea.
But I guess it has been a while, so...
No...
It's okay, Nanumi.
No! No!
So good... This is so good, Narumi!
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum.
Do it. It's okay to cum, Narumi. You should cum too, Narumi!
And with this Yuki's mine.
You're trying to blackmail me when you're a good for nothing
creep? And you even asked me to be in my school uniform?
If you're trying to call your friends, that's not happening.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I see through all of the words that you sluts spit!
What are you doing?!
Are you sure that's the tone you wanna take
with me? If those pictures of you leak...
Screw you! If that happens, you'll be
caught by the police in no time!
Hey, that's not the only picture that would go out though.
You might come out okay, but what about your friend?
You coward!
Say "Please have sex with me, onii-chan."
I-I couldn't say...
Alright theft I could just upload all
those pictures now if you want.
No! I can't make myself say it!
Don't look!
Reeks of piss...
Shut up! I make sure I wash myself!
I can't believe you're this creepy.
Hey, don't touch me, pervert!
Jerk! Stop! Stop!
What are you doing?
Isn't that enough?
What was that voice you just let out right now? Feel good?
It hurts, that's it.
Maybe you just suck at this.
Then I'll have to make sure that you feel lots of pleasure!
Oh? Looks like you know how this one works, don't you?
It's vibrating so deep inside.
Why does it... I don't want this at all, but...
Looks like you're enjoying this a lot.
Maybe you have a talent for this?
You're an idiot. This doesn't... it doesn't...
It doesn't feel good at...
It feels good...
That's not what I meant!
I was lying!
Lying...
Weak – Strong
Stop already!
You're really hanging in there.
Then how's this?!
Weak – Strong
No, stop that!
If you keep doing that, I'm gonna...
This isn't good. So bad!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! No! No!
That was quite the show.
I expected nothing less from a girl who loves to masturbate.
Shut up.
I'll need you to make me feel good too though.
How about you give me a blowjob?
Stop. Don't show me that thing.
It's disgusting.
That's not nice. You just had something
similar to this between your legs.
What does that matter?
Oh well then. Both you and your friend
can just fall into despair together.
You creep.
It stinks.
This feels so disgusting.
You're usually so strong willed and now you're
sucking my dick. This is a scene and a half.
Shut up!
Just finish this already.
I bet it tastes good and you're just bad at it.
Are you still a virgin?
I guess you're a late bloomer.
Shut your mouth! What's it matter to you?
With that lousy technique, you're gonna make me go limp.
Let me give you a hand.
I'm gonna die!
I thought you were trying to finish this quickly.
Then you can just cum already!
As expected of the smart one. You learn quick.
Your throat's wrapping around me nicely.
Hurry up and cum already!
It's coming out! Hot stuff is flooding into my mouth...
Careful. Don't spit any of it out.
I feel sick.
If you can't drink at least that much,
you'll never make any guys happy.
I don't care about guys!
There aren't any good guys except Dad!
I'm gonna put my dick inside you now.
No, this is so disgusting.
I don't want to see.
If you're honest with me, I'll be gentle.
I don't want the likes of you to be nice to me.
How long can you keep that act up, huh?
Stop. Don't put it in.
Please, no sex.
You can't!
Ow! It hurts!
Take it out! Take it out!
That was just the tip.
Loosen up.
I can't believe that a guy like this is my first time!
Jerk!
And now, you're a full-fledged woman.
Shut up! Are you done now?
Hurry up and take it out.
Stop!
Aren't you done now?
You really think I would be?
How could I stop now?!
How's it feel to have sex with a man?
Stop! I hate men! I hate them!
You say that, but you've gotten really wet.
What does it feel good?
Like hell it does!
Why is my first time turning out like this?!
It doesn't even feel good!
Your thing rubbing against me doesn't feel good at all.
That's not how I see it.
No, stop!
Stop! This is really really bad!
What's the matter? I thought you hated sex!
I hate it! This makes me... I feel bad for you.
It doesn't feel good! It doesn't feel good at all!
It feels too good... It's gonna make me lose my mind!
How's it feel? I bet you wanted somebody to do this to you!
I bet you wanted that girl to grow a dick and fuck you hard!
I don't know!
I don't know! Just do it! Give it to me! Make me feel good!
Please, onii-chan!
Oh my god, so good!
Now cum!
– Cum from being fucked by your onii-chan!
– It feels good! So good!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!!
There's so much hot stuff covering me!
I'm cumming already but I'm gonna cum again!
I love it. I love sex.
I love you onii-chan.
Looks like it felt really good for you.
Shut up. Keep your mouth shut.
Even after you talked down to me so much, you called
me onii-chan and begged me to make you feel good.
This is the worst.
Looks like there's still so much more fun to be had.
What?! That's not what you promised!
Who said that this would be a one-time thing?
This is what you wanted from the start, isn't it?
You coward!
Whatever you say, that was your true nature.
Two down off my extermination list.
The last one is the mother whore.
The next target is this bitch.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч