My name is Kareki Tsunetaka.
hanime.tv
Presents
I have 20 years of experience
as a home security officer.
I'm in charge of this house's
security and surveillance.
And now I have a mission.
Scheming behind the scenes is this bitch.
She's the one my father remarked, and she's
got her eyes on the family fortune.
I must protect this house from this bitch!
There are three of these bitches!
Even though I'm completely outnumbered
I've already taken care of daughters A and B.
They plan to move in and make this
their new home in 5 days.
I have until then to make them never want
to come near me or this house ever again.
The final target is…
Home Security officer
3rd Mission:
The Sex-Starved, Big-Breasted Wife - Shouko Arc
Oh, Tsunetaka-san. Good afternoon.
This is the boss of evil,
Sayaka and Yuki's mother, Shouko.
Tsunetaka san, to you, I should
say good morning instead.
Sorry.
Shouko is the final target.
I'll find this bitch's weakness and coerce her.
We're having dinner around 6,
so please feel free to join us if you'd like.
Every time I see that body of hers,
I can't believe she's had kids.
I can't believe she's older than I am.
She's sometimes a bit reserved,
but she's really motherly.
She gets along with the neighbors.
She always smiles,
and she treats me nicely.
She takes care of things when
her husband is away.
She's the very definition of a
perfect wife and mother".
But don't be fooled.
She plans to take over this house.
This is the face of evil!
To prevent that,
I'll record their most embarrassing
moments and blackmail them.
I'll have them completely at my mercy!
Shouko always has her guard up, so it won't
be easy to get a shot of her privates.
Let's go over the places in this house
where she mainly spends time.
This is the house's entrance.
Passing through this area,
the bitches go to and from school.
They go shopping and come back here.
The bitches don't stay in this area long.
This area is priority C for surveillance.
I'll install a camera.
This is the living room.
It's where the bitches relax,
so they may let down their guard.
This area is priority B for surveillance.
I'll install a camera.
This is the dining room.
The bitches eat here.
When all three bitches are in there,
it's a difficult place for me to be in.
This is the dressing room.
The bitches disrobe and get naked.
No holds barred in my surveillance.
This point is rank A.
This is where the bitches urinate and defecate.
If I can record them in the act,
that should take the bitches down a peg.
Rank S: The master bedroom,
Shouko's room.
It's a very private space, so the bitch's
genitals should be on display here.
And this is the control room.
It's my castle.
With my computer, I can manage
all the information I collect.
I'll bring your secrets to light, Shouko.
Camcorders, cameras, listening devices… They're
installed wherever the bitches go.
This might be a little too showy.
But he should get some time off soon…
Those tits are monstrous!
I can't wait to suck 'em!
With my surveillance devices, I can record
the bitch's most embarrassing moments.
Narumi-chan… for some reason, she
keeps looking at my breasts.
I'd understand if a guy was looking…
What a strange girl!
The bathtub and toilet are always clean.
Did my daughters clean this?
How responsible!
Come to think of it,
I haven't cleaned down there recently.
I should shave it.
She's too good at this!
Despite my extensive surveillance techniques
she hasn't completed exposed her tits even once!
I'm running out of time.
Time for my ace in the hole.
2 Days Remaining
1 Day Remaining
Really, I'm fine.
I've got a bit of a headache.
Housework has probably made you tired.
Why not take some rest?
All right, I'll do just that.
I'll put some barley tea on.
Thank you.
She's really hanging in there.
She hasn't even started to masturbate.
She doesn't have a man to fill her sexual needs.
How long will this mature woman's body last?
The Final Day
You'll catch a cold. Take it off.
You can go as soon as they're dry.
We did get some heavy rain.
I thought she was only going
to a neighborhood meeting.
This kid's from the neighborhood.
I'll let your parents know you're here, so-
That looks uncomfortable. Isn't it?
Shall I make it feel better.
Don't worry.
This isn't something to be scared of.
It'll be over soon.
This taste!
Cum!
Let me drink it!
This feels amazing.
I'm sorry! I can't help it!
Sorry!
I'm sorry!
It feels so good!
It's been so long!
I've been waiting for this!
Rub it more!
Rub inside my pussy with your young, hard cock!
Your young cock gave me
such an amazing orgasm!
Now Shouko's mine!
Please
Let's stop doing this.
We're family.
Family? You're the only one who thinks that.
That!s not true!
Yuki's at a difficult age,
but I'm sure she understands!
I'd do anything for this family!
Then that makes this simple.
You've got a really lewd body, don't you?
You can't-
You've got such unbelievable
breasts and an ass to match.
It's your fault that I've gotten like this!
No! You can't!
I'll do anything else!
Anything but that!
Do you want me to show that
footage to your daughters?
You brought a guy home like that…
You've got such a pleasant face,
but you're such a bitch!
I wonder what your husband would think.
Something was wrong with me!
Why did I do that?!
Please
I'm begging you.
Don t tell my husband!
It's inside!
It's not my husband's-
What have I done?
I'm so sorry, darling!
For someone who's birthed two children,
your pussy's nice and tight!
Just how many guys have been in here?
It hurts! It's so big!
Don't compare me to that runt from before!
Who's better, me or your husband?
No! I can t say something like that!
Your tits are obviously great,
but your ass is amazing too!
You don't need a husband who
neglects a body like this!
Why are you doing this? I just
wanted us to get along.
Then there's no better way than this!
Are you still trying to have his kids?
The last time someone came inside you
wasn't before you had Yuki, was it?
Y-You wouldn't!
P-Please, don't cum inside me!
I- I-
Today's an unsafe day!
You're cumming! Your semen's flowing inside me!
Please forgive me, darling.
This is for the sake of my daughters!
Now give me a tittyfuck with
those massive breasts.
Please, no more. I have a husband.
Well then it can't be helped.
There are other women in this house…
Please, don't lay a hand on my daughters!
It's like your tits were made for this!
No!
I-I haven't even done this for my husband yet!
It's so hot!
My breasts are making you cum!
Wh-What just happened?!
I've been so lonely.
I've changed my name, but all he does is work.
Tsunetaka-san, you're like that too, aren't you?
Let me comfort you.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
My breasts-
W-Wait! That's plenty!
This smell, this feeling of skin against skin…
I might just be a debauched woman.
Sometimes these impulses well up from inside me.
And I truly do my best not to give into them.
But that's why I need my husband!
H-Hey, listen!
I don t want to lose someone I love ever again!
My husband, my daughters…
and you, Tsunetaka-san. You're all important
to me, and I love you all as family!
So, as long as it's with my body,
I'll do anything you want me to!
Please erase your recordings.
I'm here for your anytime.
That's fine, I guess.
Anyway! With that, I've solved all our problems!
Nothing is impossible for this veteran
home security officer!
But my battle has only just begun…
We re off!
My next targets are these two.
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
Encoding: Dorans
QA: Dorans
Софтсаб: TFloater