Coming! I'm coming, I'm coming!
H-How is it?
What's with that dream?
That was so crazy.
Hmm?
Tsunetaka-san, dinner is ready.
How about eating with us?
O-Okay, I'll have mine later.
P-Please have dinner without me.
Is that so?
Let's have a meal together tomorrow, alright?
We're family, after all.
What family are you saying? Bullshit!
Home       Guard
Jitaku                 Keibiin
Target : Yuki
Sexual Guidance! Punish That Cheeky Girl
My name is Kareki Tsunetaka.
I'm a veteran home guard for twenty long years now.
This house is my outpost,
an area of strategic importance that
I should defend as a home guard.
Those people infiltrated this place.
Katsuragi Shouko...
She married my father,
and is an enemy who candidly invaded this house.
She obviously married aiming for our fortune.
No need to investigate it further.
Katsuragi Sayaka...
She's the older one of the daughters
that Shouko brought here.
She's an enemy who moved in here with her mother.
She appears to be well-behaved,
but there's no saying what
wicked stuff is going in her mind.
Katsuragi Yuki...
She's the younger one of the daughters
that Shouko brought here.
Her attitude truly is impertinent
even for a foreign invader.
Saying things like "gross" or "don't go
near me" whenever she sees me,
she lacks even a bit of respect.
She's such a cheeky brat with an underdeveloped body.
Of course, she's an enemy of mine.
Like I'll take it sitting down as these
bitches lay waste on my sanctuary!
They will be moving out in due time,
and I need to make them hate being
in this house for that to happen.
Right...
Whatever it takes...
I'll devise a countermeasure for these bitches.
I am a home guard.
I can't let anything within this house escape my eyes.
I will record their shameful moments
and then I'll use those as bait.
It is a simple yet effective strategy.
Yuki has always been treating me harshly.
However, she's very kind to everyone else.
Or rather, she acts in a friendly manner.
Aside from that, I catch her childish
moments when she's alone.
I'd say that she's surprisingly ditzy...
Oh, her breasts are childish as well.
However...
That face she makes from time
to time piques my interest a bit.
She stares at Sayaka and Shouko at these times.
What does this mean?
Both onee-chan's and mom's are that huge,
so why is it that only mine's are small?
I hate this!
People say that they get bigger when massaged.
I only heard about it so I'm not sure...
It only makes me feel good and nothing unusual.
Oh, I get it now!
She's worried about her breasts being small.
Can I use this?
I don't have enough material for blackmail, though.
Is there no material that's more effective
for driving her out of this sanctuary of mine?
Hmm?
Hey, hey... Has she been using
such a suspicious site as that?
[Recommended] Breast Enlargement Drug
Amazing results! Instantly...
Is this a breast enlargement drug?
You can tell it's dubious with just a look.
Oh-hoh... Let's see this...
I wonder how she masturbates.
It's perfectly caught on camera.
Well then... Show me the way you masturbate.
Wh-Why?
My body suddenly started
throbbing and it won't stop!
I-Is this that drug's effect, after all?
Could that drug be...
Does it mean she drank that breast enlargement drug,
and now her sex drive won't subside?
She got duped by something this suspicious online.
What a gullible girl. Epic fail.
Th-This thing should do the job
and make me feel good...
...right?
Huh?!
This is milk, isn't it?
How did this happen?
It went in!
No, the throbbing won't go away!
My finger is sopping wet... I can't stop!
This is a great material for luring her in!
That's quite an intense masturbation
despite having such an immature body.
No... This feels so good that it's driving me crazy!
N-No... This is bad!
I'm coming...
Coming!
Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming!
Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
I'm coming—!
I could get hooked to this...
This is it!
Just as you see,
I had your masturbation scene perfectly recorded.
It's the upright honor student plunging a rotor
inside her with a face warped in ecstasy.
Everybody does something like that.
That's just a little embarrassing clip of me.
Besides, aren't you in a worse
situation for getting that footage?
Hey, hey... I just thought that I should tell you
about the side effect of that drug.
Huh?! S-Side effect?
That drug has a horrible side-effect, you see...
Drinking even a little of it
will make you start lactating.
It'll eventually lead to you
being unable to get pregnant.
Unable to get pregnant? You're lying, aren't you?
It's true.
That's the reason why nobody is using it now.
There have been people who died from its side effect.
No way... I never knew about that...
I know someone who has
a countermeasure drug for it.
R-Really?
Yeah, it's true.
There's only a limited amount of it at the moment,
so there's no telling when it'll be available.
I'll request for one to be delivered immediately.
And in exchange...
You'll do everything that I say.
You're the lowest of all sleazeball!
Hey, hey... Are you not afraid of the side effect?
It'll be a lifelong one.
I get it... I'll do as you say.
Alright then, show it to me.
Hurry up and spread it open.
Sh-Shut up...
H-Here...
Shouldn't this be enough?
Huh?! Who's gonna be satisfied
just with your panties?
When I said to spread it open,
you should be showing your pussy instead.
Huh?!
O-Of course I can't do that! No way, no way!
I'll never ever—
Shut up and strip!
Are you fine with being unable to bear children?
If you don't want to ruin your life for good,
then listen to what I'm saying.
Spread your pussy open by yourself and show me.
Yes, yes!
Go on and masturbate like that next.
Aren't you feeling good despite
doing it against your will?
What an awfully promiscuous girl you are.
I-I'm not promiscuous!
You don't sound convincing
while you're like that.
You're a masturbation freak.
I'm gonna come!
Yeah, I'll be watching that face of yours in orgasm.
No way... No...
What's up with that?
That's a stiff facial expression after feeling good.
Come on, give me a smile.
Wh-What? Isn't it over already?
There's no way it is. We're just
about to do the real deal.
Huh?!
No way, it can't be...
Hey, don't raise your voice.
You'll get hurt if you try to resist.
It's tight! You're squeezing me hard.
Are you getting aroused?
It hurts!
Why... Why is this happening to me?
You're asking why?
I should be asking that!
You suddenly moved into my house,
say that you're my family,
and then make a fool of me!
I absolutely won't let this important
place be taken away from me!
No way! I'm gonna come again...
I'm coming!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
Coming!
Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming! Coming—!
No—!
Hey, hey... Keep it up.
This won't end otherwise.
What should I do?
First of all, squeeze your pussy tighter.
You're not just some kind of onahole, you know.
L-Like this?
Oh, good job!
Here!
Here! Here!
Here! Here! Here!
Here! Here! Here! Here!
Here! Here! Here! Here! Here!
Your breast discharge has stopped.
Should we get this over with for today?
I-It'll finally be over...
Hey...
I'll end this by filling you up with plenty of semen.
Huh?
Here you go! Take it all in, Yuki!
No...
Yes, I did it.
Oh, I perfectly captured
your first experience in film.
H-Have you been recording
this from the beginning?
Hey, let's make more records
of us together. Alright?
Why... Why did things turn out like this?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization