My name is Kareki Tsunetaka.
I've been our home's security officer for
twenty years. I'm a veteran so to speak.
Equipped with my decked out computer,
I can surveil and monitor all activity in this house.
And now I have a mission I need to complete.
This woman has recently married my father and is
without a doubt targeting our, no, my fortune.
It doesn't make sense otherwise why she'd
marry a boring nobody like my dad
and willingly live under the same roof as me.
I need to protect this house from this bitch.
That's my mission.
My dad is rarely home because of work.
That means that this bitch is illegally
trespassing on my property.
What's worse is that there are three of these bitches,
I'm at an overwhelming disadvantage.
One day, they'll move out.
Until that happens,
I'm going to have to make sure that they never want
to try to get near me or this house ever again.
Original Works Beelzebub
Original Animation Disk
Home Security Officer
1st Mission
The Compliant Big Breasted Eldest Daughter – Sayaka Arc
I'm home.
This is that bitch's eldest daughter, Sayaka.
U-Uncle...
I'm not nearly old enough to be an uncle!
S-Sorry, Tsunetaka-san.
My first target is this girl, Sayaka.
First I'll need to figure out her weakness
and then blackmail her with it.
Okay, w-well, I'm going to go change.
This bitch is just as unsociable as ever,
It seems that she goes to a fairly high class all girls school,
but she's a very shy girl.
She's apparently the captain of the school swim team,
but do her huge tits really stay underwater?
Who knows?
She understands that her mother has just remarried,
but she shows me little to no respect.
So just in case,
I'll have to record embarrassing scenes of
them and then use them as blackmail.
After I get my hands on that, I'll be free
to do whatever I want with them.
I'm gonna get my hands on Sayaka's secret!
My camera is at the ready.
I'll be able to get a clear look at their privacy!
I think they got bigger again.
Oh, god.
Yuki-chan can't seem to take her eyes off of them
and they get in the way when I'm swimming too.
Maybe I need to lose some weight.
You got a point. The more I look at them, the
more I see just how amazing your tits are.
I wanna hurry up and get to rubbing them all day!
With my security cameras, I'm able to film
these bitches' embarrassing figures.
I need to take my time to get a hold of their weaknesses.
I need to be able to inflict trauma so great
that they'll never want to mess with me!
I'm so sleepy.
I need to hurry or I'll be late for morning practice!
I need to warm myself up.
Practice was pretty rough today.
That feels good. I almost peed myself.
Yuki-chan, sorry, could you bring me some toilet paper?
Seriously, sorry!
I'll be more careful next time!
Please!
This is going great!
But this still isn't good enough to use as blackmail material.
This...
Sorry I took today off too.
I really wasn't feeling well.
Now that I think of it, she has been absent
from school for a few days recently.
So that guy's the swimming club's adviser, huh?
Wait,
this guy's...
No, stop! Sensei!
No! Sto...
Stop!
That's hot... Stop!
No, please stop! Please!
It hurts!
You're hurting me!
Stop!
P-Please sto...
Please, sensei, stop!
And now, you're mine.
B-Blackmail? What do you want from me?
You even asked me to be in my uniform.
No! Stay away from me!
Hey come on now, don't be so cold.
If you hadn't done anything, I wouldn't
be standing here right now.
But... But I haven't done anything!
But guys see that a bit differently.
Your body is just a huge temptation to every guy out there!
No! That hurts!
Please stop!
I'm gonna scream!
Just try. What's gonna happen to your club's
adviser when that video gets released?
Your club is gonna disappear, for one.
I wonder if you'll still be able to go
to school like you do normally.
Th-That's low! Th-that's not fair!
How many times have you done it with him?
W-We haven't done anything!
He came to our house out of the blue that day.
I couldn't participate in the club the entire week...
that day I was feeling especially bad.
Please, he may be strict, but he's a really nice
person. Everyone in the club loves him!
And... he's a normal guy, so, um, maybe I led him on...
If anything happened to him or the dub, I...
Then you're gonna have to listen to everything I say, okay?
No, you're gonna have to beg me for that.
Please... do dirty things to me.
Onii-san...
Damn, they're huge.
What did you eat to get this big?
This is why I hate them...
Guys just look at my breasts all the time.
Alright then, try giving me a tit fuck.
Tit fuck?
Shit, just stick it in between your tits.
With my breasts?
No, I don't want to!
You know what'll happen if you don't, right?
Fine, I'll do it.
This is gross.
This is it, right?
Move your tits, you dumb bitch!
I... I can't!
Do it already!
When did they start growing?
Middle school? Don't tell me from Elementary School.
I'm not telling you.
Hmph. Looking at you, I bet you were ridiculed
by your male classmates a lot.
Why do I have to do something this dirty?
It's to make me feel good. Isn't that obvious?
O-Ow! Don't touch it!
They're so big but surprisingly sensitive.
But shit I can't get off with your crappy tit fuck.
Of course. I-I've never done this before!
Then use your mouth too!
I-I can't!
I don't ever want to put this thing anywhere near my mouth!
You have no right to refuse! Here!
No, stop!
That's the ticket.
If you don't get a move on, it's gonna
be daytime before you know it.
That's good! That's amazing!
Use your tongue more!
This is so embarrassing, I'm rubbing a guy's dick with my boobs.
Oh, that's good!
At this rate...
There's so much... Hurry up and end already!
I'm almost done. Where do you want it?
Nowhere! Don't...
There's so much of it and it's all sticky and disgusting.
You don't really think we're done already, do you?
Now spread your legs.
N-No!
Looks like you're off your period.
Don't say that...
This is such a great view.
Please stop!
I don't want this!
One day you'll do it with a guy you like.
I'm sure you'll do it one day whether it's with
just a guy you like or your future husband.
What are you getting at?
Do you even have a brain, woman?
When you do it with that guy, you'll definitely remember...
You'll remember your first guy!
My first... No!
That... Anything but that!
S-Stop!
Please, anything but that!
I'll do anything else, so please!
Please, don't!
No!!
It hurts!
It hurts so much!
Take it out!
Please take it out!
No!!
It's pretty tight in here.
Come on, your parents are gonna hear you.
A guy's thing is really inside of me right now.
Ow! Ow!!
Stop moving, it hurts!
So tight! You really are a virgin!
It's coming into my stomach and thrusting so deep inside me!
It feels so disgusting!
No! No! Stop!
Shit, you're such an annoying bitch.
You let two guys into your room so easily.
You really don't understand the difference
between a man and a woman.
This is what that adviser of yours wanted to do.
He was obviously gunning for those
huge tits of yours the entire time!
He wanted to rub them, suck them, and fuck the
shit out of them and cover them with his cum!
The instincts he'd been holding back for so long just exploded.
There's no guy in this world who'd be able to
keep his sanity around those tits of yours!
No, but I didn't do anything!
Why? Why is it my fault?!
Ow!
My boobs hurt!
Stop!
Stop doing this to me!
Stop! I don't want this!
Don't worry, I'm ending soon.
You don't mean...
No!!
Anything... Please, anything but that!
No! You can't!
What can't I do?
If you cum inside me, I...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm gonna get pregnant!
It's inside me... This can't be...
No!!
It's coming out.
It's coming out from inside me.
How's it feel to be a woman?
You might even be a mother now.
What should I do?
What happens if I get pregnant?
Please... I did as you said, so please delete that data!
Did I ever say that you only had to listen to me once?
Th-That's...
No! Why?!
Why is this...
That's one down.
Another great job done by me, a veteran home security officer.
But I can't let my guard down.
There are still two bitches left who are
trying to destroy my peaceful life.
Onee-chan? You're gonna be late!
Okay, I'll be back later!
The next target is her.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hibrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub:торрент иваниваныч