This guy's name is Kareki Tsunetaka.
He's the pervert who lives at the
house of the man mom married.
My mom's name is Katsuragi Shouko.
She got married to our new father,
but I honestly don't accept it.
We've been doing well even without a father.
My older sister's name is Katsuragi Sayaka.
She's a beautiful, clever,
and kind sister that I'm proud of!
I really envy her for having those huge tits!
I'd love it if she'll share some to me as well!
I'm Katsuragi Yuki, who has
the two of them in my family.
I'm an honor student with good
grades and who's adept at sports.
Those are the cherished talents
that I inherited from my parents.
Our family of three should be good enough,
but we have to get along well
with such a creepy shut-in.
This really is the worst!
We'll eventually be moving into a new house,
so I have to hold on until then.
...or that's what I thought.
I reprimanded Katsuragi Sayaka,
the cheeky second daughter
who always scorns me.
As a home guard who's
constantly defending this house,
I hammered my might directly into her childish body.
That brat Yuki... She bawled
like a dog at the beginning,
but she behaved in no time
after I raised my voice a little.
However, she still acts with that
very bossy attitude of hers.
If this goes on, then I'll have to thoroughly
keep raping her until she feels sorry for her actions.
Home       Guard
Jitaku                 Keibiin
Target : Yuki
Bitch Training! Milk That Beautiful-breasted Tsundere Dry
Yuki won't let go of her cheekiness as usual,
but there have been some changes in her.
As soon as I show her my meat rod,
she starts to behave like a good girl.
No matter how much her
well-spoken mouth speaks,
she's nothing but a mere bitch in the end.
And when that happens, even I
won't be unable to hold myself back.
She eventually stopped caring
when I rape her anywhere in our house.
She accepted things on her own.
It seems that she'll resist at first, but no longer do.
It looks like she got addicted to sex.
Now that I remember...
Her own previous worries about comparing
her breasts to her mother and older sister
seems not to bug her anymore now.
Are you not worried about your breasts anymore?
Huh? Yeah...
That's not really the case,
but I've already forgotten about
it since you kept raping me.
Size doesn't really matter.
Even I ended up getting attacked
by a pervert like you.
It also won't matter anymore if I ended up
infertile as a side effect of that drug.
Huh? Oh, that was a lie.
After I checked it out,
what's in that breast enlargement
drug are just vitamin pills.
Huh?! Eh?
What the hell was that? You pervert!
Your personality is unpleasant as always.
You still need more discipline.
Hey, why are you going in like it's nothing?
Yeah, yeah. There's no point on
getting embarrassed now.
We already did this a few times.
I'm not embarrassed!
I feel creeped out as one normally would.
Don't say that.
I'll make you come until you faint again.
I don't want that too...
W-Wait, wait!
I get it already, so don't be rough on me!
Don't you like it when you're being roughed up?
That's not true.
D-Don't suddenly shove it in!
Looks like you're enjoying this.
You're squeezing hard.
I-I can't help it, can I?
When your dick goes inside me,
my body is merely reacting on its own.
Aren't you completely trained now?
Just like a dog wagging its tail on its owner, right?
Who's the dog you're talking about?
Your dick doesn't make me feel good at all!
I'm certain that I found your weak spot.
Your master is capable enough.
L-Like hell that's true!
Here, this is a reward from your master!
Make sure to accept it!
No! Ah!
No! Don't...
Don't—!
Oh yeah, you had that breast
enlargement drug in the end.
Is this the limit of your breast growth?
W-We don't know about that yet.
I keep on drinking that just in case.
It'll be great if you'll bear a child, huh?
But we're able to do lactation play
thanks to that drug's side effect.
I think that your milk is thicker than before.
Could it be that you're pregnant?
I-It can't be, no way!
You say that you don't want it,
but aren't you feeling good?
Don't you actually want to give birth?
No, no way.
I don't want to give birth to
a child of a perverted voyeur!
Hey, hey. If you tighten your pussy that much,
I'll end up giving you a creampie.
Don't!
Don't... Don't shoot it inside me!
Yuki, you're shaking your hips on your own.
Huh... Huh?
You're already captivated in sex.
Stop caring about anything anymore
and only think about getting
pleasure and having an orgasm!
Don't, no more...
Don't!
I can't take it anymore!
The female invaders who took over this house
have all been successfully driven out with no problems
thanks to my efforts as a home guard.
My endlessly peaceful days
are finally back.
But several months after that,
Yuki came back alone to have a look in this house.
Just by seeing her,
I was totally taken aback.
The reason for that is actually...
Huh?!
Y-You... That's...
Yeah, I got pregnant!
W-Well, is that mine?
That was my first time back then.
I never did it with anyone besides you.
Well, after each passing day
of fucking me bareback with
no regard of place and time,
I'll obviously get knocked up.
Even I figured out that much.
Don't tell me that you never
thought anything about it.
Th-That's...
In case you can't fully believe it,
how about we have it
checked up at the hospital?
You'll know for sure that way.
No, that's...
You're the one who was telling me to bear a child.
As far as I remember, you kept
plunging your dick into me.
You pounded me just like a beast.
And when you made me come from
a creampie, I stopped caring anymore.
I thought that I should just bear your child.
But that's not how it really is, right?
You were telling me that I wanted to bear a child,
but weren't you the one who really wanted that?
I was so hooked on sex at that time.
That's because it felt so much
better than masturbating!
There's no way I could stop.
But even more than that,
you're the one addicted on this body of mine.
You've been saying things about my breasts,
but I wonder which one of us got so hooked
on their first sexual experience?
You virgin.
I
I-I
I-I-I
I-I-I-I
I-I-I-I-I'mma notcha virgin!
Wasn't that great? You finally
graduated at such a nice age.
Th-That's right, my plan was supposed to be
making her a much more obedient female slave.
But I started longing for her before I knew it.
Could it be that she pretended as a
tsundere to lure me into her trap?
Don't tell me that you thought this'll
be over after impregnating me.
You did as much as that to someone.
Of course, you'll take
responsibility. Am I right?
Y-Yeah...
I knew it, you're so hard!
It feels like it'll push my foot back
if I'll relax from stepping on it!
Th-This is bad, I'm about to come against my will.
but I can't do anything at this state!
Don't hold back, you can shoot it out.
You won't be using that on anyone else
but me anyway, so shoot it out already.
Come on, come on, come on!
Hi-yah!
Alright, then. I'll have you lick me next.
Wh-What are you doing?
I'll be licking yours too, so lick mine.
Let's lick each other.
Good! That feels good!
Th-This is bad! I can't breathe this way!
Her pussy is blocking my nose and mouth!
I get it!
I'll make you feel good as well!
Wh-When did you get that good at this?
I've been practicing hard since we last met.
P-Practice, you mean...
It was just with a dildo.
Oh, did you just sigh?
So you felt jealous thinking about
me having sex with other men.
I-I'm not jealous at all!
I don't care about other men!
People who say things like that should be punished.
S-So cramped! Are you really a nympho?!
Of course, it's cramped since
I haven't given birth yet!
Here we go, I'll start moving!
Come on! One-two, one-two...
Hey! If you do it that hard, the baby will...
It's gonna be alright.
It won't die that easily, and besides...
We can just make another one when it does!
Taking that aside,
let's feel even more pleasure!
I-I can't take it, I'm coming already!
Yes, it's okay! Come a lot!
Drown the baby in my belly with your semen!
W-Wait!
I can't come anymore! I'm at my limit!
Huh? Is that real?
Wanna try?
Your semen came out!
More, I want more!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization