My name is Kareki Tsunetaka.
I've been our home's security officer for twenty years - a veteran, so to speak.
Equipped with my decked out computer and surveillance equipment,
I can surveil and monitor all activity within this house.
One day, a mission I have to accomplish suddenly appeared.
This woman has recently married my father and
is without a doubt targeting our, no, my fortune.
It wouldn't make sense otherwise for her to marry a boring nobody like my dad
and live under the same roof as me.
I need to protect this house from this bitch.
That's my mission.
My dad is rarely home because of work.
That means that this bitch is illegally trespassing on my property.
What's worse is that there are three of these bitches,
I'm at an overwhelming disadvantage.
In 5 days, these bitches will move out to the new house,
I have to make sure they never want to get
near me or this house ever again by then.
My conquest of daughter A has already been completed.
One down, two to go.
My next target is...
2hd Mission
The Contemptuous Beautiful Breasted Younger Daughter - Yuki Arc.
Hey, you're in my way.
This is Shoko's daughter B, the little sister: Yuki.
What do you want? Stop staring at me like that, you're gross!
Stop standing there and get out of my way.
What are you, stupid?
This is how this bitch always acts towards me.
She looks down on me as I were some garbage.
How was she raised to end up like this?
Both sisters go to a pretty high-class school,
but she's apparently smarter than her sister.
I don't know how she does it, when all she
does at home is play games and watch TV.
Ugh, you're eating with me!?
You're disgusting.
She doesn't hide her animosity towards me, and always scorns me.
She's against her mother remarrying, but she's that woman's daughter.
I have to prevent them from taking over this house at all costs.
I'll unveil Yuki's secrets with this.
Video, digital camera, wiretaps: I've set them
up where these bitches regularly appear.
How can I get my breasts to be big like my sister's?
I'm massaging them everyday,
but it's still not producing results?
Oh? Yuki wants bigger breasts, huh?
If she just asked me I could massage them all day for her, hehe.
By setting up surveillance, I can record the bitches' embarrassing moments.
Slowly but surely, I have to gain blackmail material on them
so that I can ingrain a trauma so deep into them that they'll never mess with me!
Ugh, so annoying!
How can she be friendly towards a gross guy like him?
Yeah, that works. See you at 12.
Yeah, I think she'll be gone.
It's not coming out...
Oho, what is this?
I guess she's honest to her desires even when she seems all uptight.
What a nice catch.
Things are moving along as planned.
I still don't have enough to blackmail her properly...
That's a face I see every once in a while.
Is she Yuki's friend?
I was so lonely.
Hey, it's okay, right?
You can't, Narumi! My mom might come home at any moment.
We shouldn't do this at my house.
It has been a while, but...
N-no, not there!
That's so good, Narumi.
Oh no oh no!
A-again,
I'm about to cum!
N-Narumi, can I cum?
I'm gonna cum, cum with me!
With this, Yuki is mine.
A gross moron like you, blackmailing me?
Even telling me to be in my uniform.
Trying to get more allies won't do you any good.
Huh? What the hell are you talking about?
I've already seen through your conspiracy!
What was that for!?
You sure you want to talk to me like that?
If that footage somehow leaks, you...
Don't mess with me! I'll have the police arrest you in the blink of an eye!
Did you forget there's someone else in that footage as well?
Even if you're fine with it, is your friend going to be okay with it too?
Bastard...
Say, "Please do perverted things to me, onii-chan."
Th-that's so...
Should I just upload the footage right now?
No, I can't say it.
D-Don't look.
Hehe, smells like piss.
Stop lying! I wash it properly.
I didn't think you were this disgusting.
Don't touch me, pervert.
N-no, stop it!
What are you?
You should be satisfied, right?
What's with that voice? You're getting turned on?
It just hurts.
You're probably just bad at this.
Oh yeah? I'll make you feel so good it'll drive you crazy.
Looks like you know how this is going to be used!
It's vibrating all the way inside. Why does it feel so.
Even though I hate it.
You're feeling it an awful lot, you might be cut out for this kind of stuff.
Shut up, idiot!
This doesn't feel
it doesn't... feel good at all.
I-It feels so good.
That was a mistake! I was lying!
A lie.
Please, no more!
Doing her best to hold out, huh?
Then... How do you like THIS?
N-no, that's too much!
If you do that to me.
Oh no, this is bad.
Stop it stop it stop it, nonono!
That was quite the orgasm, as expected of a serial masturbator like you.
Sh-shut up.
I have to have you make me feel good too.
I guess I'll have you suck me off.
Stop, don't show me that gross thing.
It's dirty!
That's cruel, the guys who you'll open your legs for in
the future are going to have one as well you know?
Like I care about that.
Fine by me, your friend will just have to be miserable along with you.
You're disgusting.
It smells disgusting... I feel sick.
Seeing you, who's always deriding me, suck me off is a sight to see!
Shut up, I'm just trying to finish this as quick as possible.
You're popular but you suck at this.
Are you still a virgin?
I guess you're surprisingly innocent on that side of things.
I told you to shut up, what does it matter to you?
With a shitty fellatio like this, my rock-hard penis is about to go limp.
Here, I'll give you a hand.
I thought I was going to die.
You wanted to finish this quickly, right?
You should just hurry up and cum already!
As expected, you're a quick learner.
Ugh, her throat is tightening around my cock.
Hurry up and cum!
The inside of my mouth... It's so hot.
Woah there, don't spit it out.
I feel sick.
You can't please a man unless you're able to drink at least that much.
I don't care about guys!
They're probably all sleazy scumbags like you!
This is about to be inside you.
Gross, I don't want to see it.
I'll be gentle if you're honest about it.
Why would I want to be gently done by you of all people?
Let's see how long you can keep up the act.
Stop, don't... Don't put it in.
Please...
It hurts! It hurts!
Take it out!
It's still just the tip.
Relax and loosen up.
I can't believe my first time is with a guy like this.
Congratulations, you're a woman now!
Shut up. You're satisfied, right? Let me go.
W-wait, aren't you done?
Of course not, who the fuck could stop here?
How is it, having sex with a man?
I hate it, I hate sex and I hate men!
You seem awfully wet for someone who hates it.
You're getting turned on, aren't you?
There's no way I'm feeling good after you
ruined my first time like this. There's no way!
No matter how much you shove your thing into me, it doesn't feel good at all.
Doesn't look that way to me.
N-no!
That's not good! Nononono!
What happened? I thought you hated sex?
I-I hate it.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
It doesn't feel good... You're not making me feel good...
I love feeling good... This isn't anything!
Then how about doing it like this?
That time, you wanted to be fucked like this by somebody, right?
You wish that girl had a penis and banged you with it!
I don't knowww.
I don't care anymore, please make me feel good!
Please, onii-chan!
That's so good.
– Cum! You're going to cum from being fucked by onii-chan!
– It feels so goooood!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Your hot stuff's getting all over me! I'm cumming again while cumming!
I love sex... I love you onii-chan...
You seemed to be enjoying it a lot.
Shut up, I don't want to hear it.
From treating me like shit to calling me onii-chan
and begging me to make you cum, huh?
This is the worst.
Looks like I can enjoy this for a while.
Wait, that's not what you promised!
Who said I'd let you go after just one time?
That must've been your plan from the start, you wretch!
You can say whatever you want, but we saw your true colors today.
That's two down.
All that's left is their bitch of a mother.
You're the next target...
Translator: Shameless Persimmon
Timer: Shameless Persimmon
QA: Dorans, Fogil
softsub: торрент иваниваныч