My name is Kareki Tsunetaka.
I've been our home's security officer for
twenty years. I'm a veteran so to speak.
I've conducted various secretive operations in this house.
And now I have a mission I need to complete.
This is the bitch behind it all.
This woman has recently married my father and is
without a doubt targeting our, no, my fortune.
I need to protect this house from this bitch.
What's worse is that there are three of these bitches,
I'm at an overwhelming disadvantage.
But I've already completed my work on step-sister A and B.
In three days, they'll move into their new home.
Until that happens,
I'm going to have to make sure that they never want
to try to get near me or this house ever again.
And now, the last target is...
Home Security Officer
3rd Mission
Lustful Big Titty Wife - Shouko Arc
Oh, good afternoon, Tsunetaka-san.
And this is the evil mom.
She's Shouko, the mother of Sayaka and Yuki.
Oh, I guess this is more of a "good
morning" for you, Tsunetaka-san.
Pardon me.
My final target is this woman, Shouko.
I'm gonna get my hands on her weakness and then blackmail her.
Dinner will be ready by six thirty, so come
down and eat if you feel like it.
She doesn't have a body of a woman who has given birth at all.
Somehow she's actually older than I am.
She seems very reserved but can really play the part of a mother.
She's well liked in the neighborhood and even smiles
when she sees me. She's a very considerate person.
She's a good wife that cleans and keeps
the peace when Dad's not around, but...
I can't let myself be fooled.
She's nothing but a spawn of lust and
temptation who's after this house!
As long as I get some embarrassing photos or
videos of this bitch and blackmail her with it,
I'll be able to do anything I want to her!
Shouko keeps her guard up so I'm
sure she won't slip up too easily.
So I'll have to go to a place that she goes to a lot in this house.
This is the front door of this house.
This is where those girls go to school and come home from.
This is where that woman goes shopping and comes home from.
The time that they actually spend in this house is minimal,
so this becomes an important surveillance point. Rank C.
I guess I'll set this up here.
And this is the living room.
This is where they come to relax and
where their guard is lowest.
The importance of this surveillance point is Rank B.
I'll put a camera here too.
And this is the dining room.
This is where those bitches eat.
But since they're all grouped together, it'd
be difficult to really get a good shot.
And this is the changing room. This is where those
bitches undress and get completely naked.
This is without doubt a Rank A surveillance spot.
And this is where they get rid of their waste.
Showing them and footage or pictures from here
will be enough to make them fall apart.
And this is another Rank A... the master bedroom
or in other words, Shouko's room.
It's her private space and I'm sure she'll
show her true colors in here.
And this is the control room.
You could call it my fortress.
From my computer, I can observe everything.
And like this, I'm gonna drag out her secrets.
I have cameras, video cameras, and microphones set
up all around where this bitch hangs around.
These may be a little too bold.
But then again, he'll be home again soon now
that work is starting to wind down for him.
Shit, those tits are like monsters.
I wanna suck those so bad.
With these cameras, I can capture
all of her embarrassing moments.
Narumi-chan keeps looking at my boobs.
If she was a guy, I'd understand, but... she's kind of strange, huh?
The toilet and bath are always so clean.
I wonder if they're cleaning them.
What good girls.
Now that I think about it, I haven't shaved in a while.
I shouldn't put it off so much.
How the hell is this possible?
I've been surveying her this entire time and
I can't even get one decent shot of her tits?!
I'm running out of time.
Aphrodisiac
4 Customer Reviews
Buy now with 1-Click
I'll have to use my trump card.
2 Day Left
1 Day Left
Oh no, it's nothing.
I'm just feeling really lightheaded all of a sudden.
I'm sure you're just tired from all the housework.
Why not take a break?
You're probably right.
Then I'll do just that.
I'll give you some barley tea.
Oh, thank you very much.
She's really holding it in.
She hasn't even tried to masturbate.
But how long will that whore body of yours
last without a man to satisfy you?
Final Day
You're gonna catch a cold.
Take those clothes off.
I'll drive you home after you dry off.
Oh yeah, there was a pretty bad storm, wasn't there?
I think she went out to go to a neighborhood
association meeting or something.
And this is a kid from the neighborhood...
If we end up heading out too late, I'll call your parents for you.
You look like you're struggling.
Would you like me to help?
Don't worry, this isn't anything scary.
It'll be over soon.
It's so tasty.
Let it out.
Let me drink it from your dick!
Wow...
I'm sorry, I...
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I-It feels so good!
It's been so long!
I've wanted this for so long!
More! Rub me more!
Rub me harder with your young, hard dick!
I-I'm cumming!
I just came so hard from your uncircumcised dick.
And now Shouko's all mine.
Please, don't do this.
We're family.
Family, huh?
You're the only one who thinks that.
That's not true!
Yuki's at a difficult age, but I'm sure she understands.
I'll do anything you want me to!
Then this makes things faster.
You have quite the dirty body, don't you?
Y-You don't mean...
My dick's only this hard because your huge
tits and ass have been seducing me!
No! Don't!
I'll do anything else!
But not that! Please! Anything but that!
What, you want me to show that video to your kids?
You lure guys in with that dignified face of yours
even though you're actually a complete slut.
I wonder what your husband would think of all this?
There was something wrong with me then.
I don't know why I did that!
Please not that!
Please don't tell him!
I-It's coming in!
A dick that's not my husbands is...
What have I done?
I'm so sorry, my love.
You're pretty tight for a woman that's given birth twice.
How many guys have been in here?
It's so thick and big!
Yeah, mine's in a different league than some uncircumcised dick.
So what feels better?
I... I can't say that.
Your tits are one thing, but your ass is just as amazing.
How could anyone leave this body alone?!
No! That hurts!
Why are you doing this?
All I wanted to do was get along with you!
Then doing this is probably the best way.
You still trying to get a baby with him?
I'm guessing you haven't been cummed in since
you gave birth to your last daughter.
Wait, you're not going to...
Please, please don't cum inside.
I... I...
Today's not my safe day.
It's coming out! There's so much cum coming out inside me!
Please forgive my lewd self, my love.
This is for my daughters.
Now how about you give me a tit fuck
with those great tits of yours?
I can't do any more than this. I have a husband.
Oh, well if that's the case, fine. There are
other women in this house anyway.
Please, don't go after my daughters.
Those tits look like they were made to give tit fucks.
Please. I haven't even done this with him.
It's so hot.
You came inside my boobs.
What the hell was that?
I've been so lonely.
We're married now, but he's always busy with work.
You're the same too, aren't you, Tsunetaka-san?
I'll cheer you up.
S-So how does it feel?
Does it feel good?
Do my boobs fee...
W-Wait!
That's enough.
This smell...
this sensation...
It's been so long.
I might be a dirty woman.
It's true that I've been desperately trying to hold back my
carnal desires that well up inside me every now and then.
But that's exactly why I need him.
Listen to me! Hey!
I don't want to lose the people I love.
Not the man I love or my daughters.
Even you, Tsunetaka-san.
You're all my precious family.
That's why, if you're okay with using
my body, I'll let you do anything.
Please delete that video.
I'll play with you whenever you want.
O-Okay...
Yeah, that works.
In any case, I've completed my mission.
Nothing is impossible for a hardened veteran such as myself!
But my battle has only just begun.
See you later.
These are my next targets.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч