"Ahem, my name is Kareki Tsunetaka."
"I've been our home's security guard
for twenty years... a veteran."
"My mission is to bring down the hammer of justice on
the dirty bitches who have infiltrated this house."
"Yes, and this is the bitch behind it all."
"This woman has recently married my father and is without
a doubt targeting his fortune as well as mine."
"My father is mostly at work and hardly ever returns home."
"So basically, this bitch is knowingly
illegally trespassing in this house."
"And what's worse is that there are three of these bitches."
"I'm at an overwhelming disadvantage."
"The mother's name is Shouko."
"And her daughters are Sayaka and Yuki."
"I've completed my work on all of them."
"They should now be unwilling to even step a foot in this house."
"Kukuku..."
"Or at least that's how it was supposed to be,"
"but an unexpected result occurred."
"Even though they were supposed to have moved out by now,"
"they're still here in this house."
"I don't understand..."
Home Security Officer
4th Mission
Lewd Life With the Perverted Mother and Daughters Arc
I'm home...
This is that bitch, Shouko's first spawn
A, the older sister, Sayaka.
O-Oji...
I'm not old enough for you to be calling me that!
S-Sorry.
Tsunetaka-san...
Okay, well, I'm going to change...
Strip.
What's wrong? Didn't hear me?
Okay...
Onii-san...
It's hitting me!
Your tip's hitting me so deep inside!
Please! Don't do anything to Yuki or Mom!
You can do whatever you want to me!
Okay, we have a deal.
You'll spread your legs for me whenever, wherever I tell you to.
It feels so good.
Your dick's so good, onii-san.
I can't hear you.
Your dick...
Your dick feels really good!
More! Please thrust it in me more!
Give me more of your dick, onii-san!
You're such an unskilled slut.
Hey, you're in the way.
This is that bitch, Shouko's second
spawn B, the younger sister, Yuki.
What? Why are you staring at me?
It's grossing me out.
Move out of the way already!
Why are you just standing there? Are you an idiot?
Suck it.
Okay.
Onii-chan...
There's so much pre-cum!
You can do whatever you want to me.
But please don't do anything to onee-chan or Mom!
I gave her my conditions.
No matter where or when, she'll suck my dick if I tell her to.
It's so tasty! Your dick's so tasty, onii-chan!
You've gotten too good at this.
You really like it that much?
I love it! I love it so much!
Cum! Shoot all your cum out!
There's so much!
Hey, come on, put your dick inside me.
Maybe next time.
Oh, Tsunetaka-san, good afternoon.
And this is the evil ringleader.
She's Sayaka and Yuki's mom, Shouko.
Oh, maybe this is more like "good
morning" for you, Tsunetaka-san?
My apologies.
Dinner will be around six thirty, so
please come down if you'd like.
Tit fuck.
Okay...
Tsunetaka-san...
It's so hard and hot.
I feel like my boobs are going to get burnt!
I'll take their place, so please don't lay a finger on Sayaka or Yuki!
Please, I beg you!
So I gave her my conditions.
No matter where or when, she'll give me a tit fuck if I tell her to.
Cum whenever you'd like.
Cum whenever and wherever you'd like, Tsunetaka-san.
You came so much.
Did my boobs feel good?
I'm glad!
You're being so rough out of the blue!
Your dick feels so good, Tsunetaka-san!
And just like that I was able to fuck any of these
three whenever and wherever I wanted.
And the evildoers followed my bidding without
any complaints. They became obedient bitches.
I never expected for all of them to stay in this house, but...
Either way this doesn't affect my work
as this house's security guard.
Let's go and take a look at the usual spots.
This is this house's entrance.
The place from where the bitches go
to and from school or food shipping.
Of course, I, being the house's security
guard, have never used this door.
The amount of time that these bitches spend here is short.
The level of importance that this spot deserves is a C.
Let's set up a camera here.
This is the living room.
This place of rest is where those bitches
come to relax. They've taken over it.
This is the place where their guard is lowest.
The importance of this surveillance point is Rank B.
I'll put a camera here too.
And this is the dining room.
This is where those bitches eat.
Now that there are three bitches sitting and
eating here, it's impossible to stay here.
And this is the changing room.
This is where those bitches undress and get completely naked.
They have nowhere to hide here.
This is without doubt a Rank A surveillance spot.
And this should be obvious, but this is where
those bitches get rid of their waste.
Showing them and footage or pictures from here
will be enough to make them fall apart.
And this is another Rank A... the master bedroom
or in other words, Shouko's room.
It's her private space and I'm sure she'll
show her true colors in here.
But there's a limit to how much footage I can get out of here.
I just need to make sure that I get the timing
right to start filming her at a good point.
And this is the control room.
You could call it my fortress.
From my computer, I can observe everything.
I have cameras, video cameras, and microphones
set up all around where these bitches hang out.
I think they got even bigger.
Oh, geez.
Yuki just stares at them and it's hard to swim with them this big.
I wonder if I just need to lose weight.
And as usual, Sayaka is worried about the size of her breasts.
Those are tits that I'd love to rub all day!
What do I need to do to become as big as onee-chan?
I massage them every day, but nothing's happened yet.
And as usual, Yuki wants her boobs to become bigger?
If she'd just tell me, I'd massage them like there's no tomorrow.
It sounds like he'll be back from work after all this time,
so maybe I should put in a little effort.
I'm so excited.
But actually you want to be fucked by me, don't you?
I can't believe you're saying that even
though you know I'm watching you.
Like this I can take videos of all these bitches
in their most embarrassing moments.
There is no rest for a house security guard.
Any evil that tries to disturb the peace in this house...
Will not be overlooked by me.
Man, these bitches just don't learn, do they?
We can't, Narumi.
My mom might be home soon.
We can't do this here.
I mean, it's been a while, so maybe...
Hey how about you let me do it today?
It's so pretty, Narumi.
You're getting so wet.
Does it feel good, Narumi?
Does it? Does it feel good?
I'm cumming!!
It feels so good! No, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum!
Sorry, onii-chan found out!
But don't worry, I bet you'll feel even better, Narumi.
Feel like I do with onii-chan's dick.
You're so cute, Narumi.
See? Doesn't it feel good?
Dicks are the best, right?
For a veteran security guard like myself,
no amount of trespassers can stop me.
I'm the best.
And once again, I've protected the peace of this house.
U-Um, I have a favor to ask.
Please rape me today, onii-san.
I put in a little effort today.
You're going to rape me, right?
Right, onii-chan?
I thought you were going to rape me every day,
but you're definitely going to do it today, right, Tsunetaka-san?
It seems as if the three of them knew
about all this for quite a while.
They knew that their mother and both
of them were all getting raped by me.
And then they pretended as if they didn't
know anything and followed my orders...
You only did me twice yesterday.
After that I felt kind of unsatisfied...
So I tried masturbating...
Please do me more today.
That's not fair!
Before that you got him for four times, onee-chan!
I just learned a new fellatio technique.
I need to make him pour his cum inside here.
Sayaka, you're close to your period and Yuki,
you just did it with Narumi, didn't you?
Just leave today to your mom and get some rest.
I was so surprised.
Mom said that she'd be okay if the two
of us moved out and she'd stay.
But I can't leave mom to be the only
one taking care of onii-sans dick.
I figured it out.
I knew that this kind of thing was happening.
Onee-chan said that at the very least I should leave, but...
I'd be the only one without his dick then.
Isn't that just unfair?
I'm the one who canceled our move.
Of course my husband was surprised, but...
This dick...
I mean, when I said that I wanted to live here with
Tsunetaka-san and everyone, he actually became very happy.
And just like that, I protected this house's safety today as well.
But I can't rest just yet.
Please make your dick stop twitching.
I'm licking the glans right now.
I'm licking here! Why can't you just be happy with the base of it?!
Mom's gonna make him cum immediately.
Just watch.
That's not fair mom!
I'm going to do it.
No, it's going to be me!
I protect this house from threats that can
appear at any time or from any place.
That's me, the house security guard.
I'm home.
Onii-san.
Onii-chan.
Tsunetaka-san.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч