What's with that dream?
That was vivid like crazy.
Hmm?
Ts-Tsunetaka-san...
Hey there, Sayaka-san.
You're home already, huh?
Y-Yes...
I usually am around 4 PM.
Oh...
Anyway, that dress is lovely.
It suits you well.
Huh? U-Umm...
Thank you...
Umm... I-I have to help make dinner.
Hmph, damn invader!
I'll get my hands on your weaknesses
and chase you all out of this house.
Home       Guard
Jitaku                 Keibiin
Target : Sayaka
Revelation of One's True Nature!
Strip The Busty Honor Student's Disguise off Her
I will record these women's shameful moments
and then I'll use those as bait.
After I have some dirt on them,
I'll be able to do as I please.
Sayaka is as docile as she looks,
so it looks like I can easily coerce her.
However, I'm having a hard time
to get anything to use against her...
She behaves like a good honor student,
may it be at home
or even in her room.
She doesn't do anything strange in particular.
Well, her body is erotic
so I managed to get enough fap material.
Huh...
Huh?!
Gosh, it got tight again...
I'll have to buy a new one.
If they keep growing big,
I might not be able to find
my size in a typical store.
Men are always staring at them...
They're a heavy burden to carry around.
I hate this...
Gah! To hate having such a sexy body...
What a waste!
It also feels tight on my butt...
I'm not losing weight despite
pushing myself in club activities.
It really might be the fault
of mom's genes, after all...
I wonder how mom looked like back then?
These are nothing but voyeur videos.
These won't be good enough for blackmail.
However, she is but another human being.
Aphrodisiac
4 Customer Reviews
Buy now with 1-Click®
Upon experiencing an uncontainable lust,
She'll most likely show her immodest self.
Oh, my... Is that coming from my room?
I didn't set an alarm for this time, though.
Yes... Alright...
After drinking this aphrodisiac,
even a withered granny will end up soaking wet.
I'll have you show me your true nature, Sayaka.
Why... Why?
What happened to me?
No, this isn't enough...
This won't be good enough for me!
I need more...
I need more of it directly!
No!
Wow!
This feels amazing!
Th-This is weird!
The itchy feeling is spreading deep in my body
and it won't stop!
I'm feeling hotter and hotter...
I can't get enough of this!
My breasts too... They're feeling so good!
I feel like getting zapped when I tease my nipples!
I never felt this sensation before!
No...
No! No! No!
Th-This still isn't enough!
I never had enough yet!
More... More... More...
I want to mush it up even more!
Here... I want it harder right here!
I want more and more of this!
No, this isn't enough!
Please...
I want to feel even better!
What should I do now? I turned strange!
If this itchy feeling won't settle down,
I'll have to rub myself like this all the time!
Here it goes again!
I can't take this anymore!
Wh-What should I do about this?
This feels amazing...
I won't be able to stop...
This is it!
I'm coming... I'm coming! It feels good!
Just as you can see,
I fully caught your masturbation on camera.
That was surprising. I never thought that someone
as diligent as you masturbate in such a lewd way?
Th-That's not true! That was...
My body just started
throbbing for some reason...
Doesn't that mean that you're
actually a slut deep inside?
You've been hiding it all this time,
but this is your true nature.
S-Saying that I'm a slut would be...
Why are you acting all innocent?
You're jiggling those huge tits around,
so there's no way that you're still a virgin!
Wh-What are you doing? Stop!
Can't I at least have a little touch?
I'll bet that you let other guys fondle them as well.
N-No, I don't!
I haven't done it with anyone yet...
Oh? I see...
I'm gonna have your first time.
A-Anything but that!
I'll do anything else...
I don't mind it if you'll say no.
It's either all men in the world will see that video,
or you'll get raped by me alone.
Choose your poison.
I-I understand...
I'll do as you say.
That's a huge and supple ass you have there.
When a man sees this,
you can't blame them for wanting to have a touch.
E-Even if you tell me something like that...
P-Please stop doing that!
Jeez, are you not being suspicious at men at all?
Stop!
Do you have any idea how those
around give you a dirty look?
O-Ouch!
If that's the case, then don't be surprised
if every man you come across ends up doing this.
You don't even consider how
your own body titillates men!
To hell with prejudice against men!
No way! E-Even I...
...never wished to have this kind of body!
Hmph! Talking back, are we?
This calls for harsh punishment.
Huh?
Wh-What are you planning to do?
You already know, don't you?
I am about to have your hymen
torn open by my cock.
W-Wait!
Please wait for a moment!
I-It hurts!
So this really is your first time.
Good job on avoiding getting raped
until now with such a body.
It's cramped and tightening.
Here you go! This is how a cock feels like.
Make sure to savor the sensation.
Wait! It still hurts!
What are you saying?
We've only just begun!
Ouch, it hurts!
Stop! Stop...
Shut up! Just bear with it.
The neighbors will hear us if you're that loud!
Whoa! Isn't this quite a nice
thing you have down here?
What an amazing onahole!
O-Onahole?
It's a tool for rubbing cocks!
Your body is well-adapted for pleasing men!
That's cruel!
Hey, hey... That's a compliment!
Both of your body and personality are erotic.
You're the ultimate cum dumpster.
I-I don't want that!
Well then, it's about time for me to dump
my semen into this cum dumpster.
Huh?
I-I feel a yearning agony deep in my belly!
I-It's hitting me!
No! No, you can't!
You can't!
Here, take it all in!
It's pouring into me!
It feels hot inside me!
Oh, they're soft!
I always wanted to do this
from the moment I saw them.
Stop this already...
There's no way I'll stop now.
I'm still far from satisfied.
Here you go! Aren't you having a hard time
with these dangling breasts?
I'll be carrying them for you from now on.
No!
Don't do that!
Don't mess my tits up!
Oh... So you feel good from
having your breasts teased.
Like this, huh?
Don't do that!
I-I'll start becoming weird!
Huh? Like I care!
You're feeling good by yourself.
I'll make myself feel good too!
N-No... Don't!
I'm getting pounded by your thing
down there! You can't!
What can't I do? Tell me.
Say it!
Y-Your cock is pounding me...
You're making a mushy mess of my insides...
I'm starting to feel good!
I-I can't think about anything else anymore!
I'm feeling it... It feels good!
You really are the ultimate cum dumpster!
You are being raped right now.
You've been peeped at, blackmailed...
...then you had your virginity stolen!
And yet, what's up with you
feeling good from this?
You're hilarious.
Come on, I'll give you my semen again!
Be sure that your pussy swallows it all!
No—!
It got all dirty...
It's all your fault,
so you have to clean it up.
Y-Yes...
Oh! Coming... I'm coming!
Hey, Sayaka! Do you know what this thing is?
Huh? What is it?
I got the whole thing caught
on camera up until now!
It will be a huge trouble if anyone sees this.
Look at your face here.
I wonder if this face of yours in ecstasy
will be recognized by people who know you?
No! Stop!
Well, I'll blur your face if I ever
decided to share this online.
It'll be a huge scandal if your
personal information gets exposed.
Student ID
Katsuragi Sayaka
Let's keep getting along from now on, Sayaka.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji