Usually I just give you a blow job and that's it,
but now that were actually having sex,
I can't imagine doing anything else!
You're drilling me so hard with your rock hard cock!
You called me out here, but it ended up being for this?
Yariko-senpai just couldn't stop talking
about how good sex with you was.
But I never thought that it'd be this good!
Hey, keep your voice down!
Hurry up and fill me up with your cum!
You don't have to tell me twice!
I'm gonna knock you up!
I'm seriously gonna cum! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
It's coming out. There's so much semen coming out!
There was so much, I was sure
it was gonna come out of my mouth.
Listen, I'll stop having sex with other guys,
so keep my pussy full with your cum, okay?
Hey, isn't it a little too early?
You never wanna go out at night anymore, Yariko.
Yeah, that's 'cuz there's a guy I'm interested in now.
JK Bitch Station
This is messed up. This isn't like you, Yariko!
Why don't you bring him over some time?
Tap Here
No can do.
He's mine and mine only.
I Wanna Be Jacked Off By A High School Slut
#2 Slutty Girlfriend
Time to go to the bathroom.
What the... who the hell are you?
Wait, aren't you...
DARK
We went to the same middle school, didn't we?
Yeah, now that you mention it, I think we did.
That's fucking hilarious.
No matter, you came at a good time.
I hear you have quite an amazing cock.
You've gotten pretty famous around here.
O-Oh, thanks.
Because of you, I couldn't cum.
You'll take responsibility, won't you?
What?
Just hurry up and take your cock out!
A-All right!
Oh wow, it has a pretty good shape to it.
Come on, stroke it already.
Like this?
Wait, what the hell is this?
I've never seen anything like this before!
I'm already getting turned on just
by looking at it! I wanna shove this in me.
What's with that thing? It's so erotic.
If you shove that long thing inside me, I'll...
Good! Just watch! Just watch me as I cum
as I pretend we're having sex! Watch me!
I'm cumming!
Oh my god, you came on me.
I think I came even harder than I usually do.
I can't go to school if I'm covered in cum.
You're gonna take responsibility for this, okay?
Please, I'm begging you... I'll do anything!
Just let me have sex with that long cock of yours!
Fine, I'll do it!
Welcome!
It's forcing its way into my pussy! It's so thick!
Sorry, but I can't stop moving!
If you shove your whole cock inside of me like that,
I'm gonna... How big is your cock anyway?!
My pussy's so happy! Your cock just keeps
diving to the deep end of my pussy!
I'm gonna cum inside you and
make your pussy even happier!
Your cock's gonna make me go crazy! It's gonna make
me cum! It's gonna make me into a one cock woman!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
In my womb...
My womb's filled with your semen!
Anyone who has sex with that cock
would become addicted to it.
Dark
This is my username. Message me sometime, 'kay?
Doors closing.
Is she for real?
LOOSE
This is my kouhai. Her nickname is Yuruko.
She's just as loose as she looks,
but rumor has it that her pussy isn't.
How has no one done anything
to her with her looking like this?
I can't eat anymore of your dick, senpai. I'm full!
She's not waking up...
This girl never gets upset no matter what I do.
She's such a slob. Her mouth is just wide open.
Keep it open like that and I'll stuff my dick in there.
This cock! This cock!
Oh crap!
That wasn't supposed to happen.
Hm? What are you doing here, senpai?
Oh, so it wasn't a dream after all.
I turned you on, right?
I'm pretty confident when it comes to my pussy.
Wanna give it a shot with your big cock?
This is definitely gonna be amazing!
This... is... Your cock is too big!
Sorry, but I can't stop moving!
No!
You're gonna pull out my insides!
I love your cock, senpai!
What is this cock? It's so amazing!
I still can't believe that I'm having sex
with him right after I woke up!
I can't think about anything but this amazing cock!
This cock's so amazing! This cock's so amazing!
This cock's so fucking amazing!
It's gonna pull everything out!
It's gonna pull everything out from inside of me!
My pussy's gonna become the shape of your dick, senpai!
Your cock's size puts every other cock I've had to shame!
Mark my pussy all over with your cum!
I want you to cum!
Yeah, you got it! Take this!
Your big cock is ramming inside of me! Cum inside me!
I'm cumming!
Your cock is so divine, senpai. I just can't anymore...
Wait!
Hamburgers
Cheeseburgers
I'm getting tired of the same menu over and over again.
I think it'd be great if you changed it up a little.
Don't you think?
Senpai, you're too defenseless!
Are you even listening?
O-Of course!
You're never around, so I get pretty bored.
Your face is so hilarious!
Oh, that's my phone.
'Sup?
Yeah, I'm good. I'm just about to get it on.
Yeah, right now I'm giving him a handjob.
What? No way. Don't you have a boyfriend already?
Also, if you ever experience this guy's cock,
you'll never be able to go back.
What? Well, I guess I'll try asking the little doggy.
Hey, do you wanna have sex with my friend?
She's one of my model friends,
so she's pretty good looking. What do you say?
Your model friend?
That's tempting, but I wanna keep
having sex with you until I die, senpai!
Oh? So that's what you want, huh?
Hey, so, sorry, but looks like
this guy only has eyes for my pussy.
Yeah, right now he's already creaming in my hand.
Though I'm pretty sure if I go at it little harder, he'll cum.
Senpai, I'm cumming!
He says he's cumming.
He's cumming!
Wow that's so much!
I'm so covered in it that I just reek of it right now.
Senpai, that turned you on?
Hey, wait! Don't get ahead of yourself!
Hey, stop! Stop rubbing my clit!
Senpai, right now you want my dick, don't you?
Girl A
Mute
Speaker
End
Come on, tell your friend,
otherwise I'm not gonna put my dick inside you.
F-Fine! I'll tell her, okay?! God damn it!
I... I can't live without your cock!
So hurry up and put your cock inside me!
I've been so turned on ever since you came on me!
Come on, overpower all the semen inside me with yours!
Yeah!
All of your cock is inside me!
You already came,
but your cock is spreading my pussy so wide!
No, not my boobs! You're gonna make me go crazy!
What's going on?
My pussy is going completely weak from his cock!
He's fucking my consciousness away!
This is my pussy now!
Yeah, it's all yours. This pussy is all yours!
I'll never let another cock inside,
so take responsibility and always keep it full with yours!
Your cock is making me feel like I'm flying off to heaven!
I want you to fill up my pussy with
a hundred people's worth of semen!
Yeah! I'll give you everything inside my balls!
Give it to me! Fill my pussy up with your semen!
I'll cum with you!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Oh my god!
Your semen is filling up my pussy!
Oh, my phone...
You got way too full of yourself.
As punishment, we're going to spend the night
draining your balls until they're empty, darling.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч