Hey!
Sorry, looks like I'm broke again.
Mind lending me 1000 yen for lunch?
Slut
This girl is known around school as Slut.
She'll fuck anyone if it means money.
Come on, I'll suck you off like I did last time. Please?
Not again... I don't even have
that much money this month...
You can do whatever you want with my boobs, so...
Please? Let me suck your cock.
See? You totally want me to.
I'll suck you off, so let's go over there, okay?
No matter how many times I suck your big,
thick cock, I never get tired of it!
It's going so deep down my throat!
How many times have I had this in my mouth?
My body is already used to it.
It's actually turning my throat into its shape!
My pussy already wants your cum,
so hurry! Give me your cum!
Hey, don't suck so hard, I'll...
Sorry I couldn't drink it all.
I'll make it up to you. I'll suck you off one more time.
I Wanna Be Jacked Off By A High School Slut ♥
#1 High School Whore
Hey, you.
I was wondering if you could help me out with something.
This girls name is Shank-senpai.
She's really popular with the guys,
and apparently works as a model, too.
Skank
You a virgin?
Y-Yeah.
I've always secretly had a crush on her.
You see, I'm trying to have sex with one hundred virgins.
O-Okay...
I was hoping you would help me out.
Everyone says that my mouth and pussy
are amazing, so, how about it?
Wow, it's already so big!
That's because you're the one doing it, Skank-senpai.
Then, I turn you on? That makes me happy.
This is the first time I've seen something like this!
I'm gonna have sex with a cock this big? I'm so excited!
Well then, let's start.
Oh god, the smell of your cock
and the hardness is so amazing!
I'm gonna make you cum in an instant. Get ready.
Wow, it's going all the way down my throat!
Your cock's so big!
I'm in heaven!
I can already taste his pre-cum... Is he going to cum soon?
I can't wait! His balls seem full, so maybe it'll overflow?
Senpai, you're sucking so well, I'm gonna cum!
Do it. Cum whenever you want.
Just shoot it out! Come on, I'll do it harder.
I'm cumming!
Your cum is so tasty!
Well then! It's time for you to lose your virginity.
What? Are you nervous?
No, I was just stunned by your beauty.
Come here.
It feels good just by rubbing our tongues
against each other, right?
You know, I don't kiss guys that I don't like.
I'm really horny but we don't have much time,
so let's hurry and have sex already.
Come over here.
You're gonna take that huge cock
of yours, and shove it in here.
Aim right here, okay?
I really want your cock right now.
Okay then, here I go.
Is this really gonna go inside me?
Yeah, right there, come in!
Oh my god! It's so big!
Senpai, your pussy's so warm!
Congratulations, you're not a virgin anymore!
My pussy's so tight, it feels like I'm a virgin again!
Your huge, stiff cock is so amazing!
I love taking a guy's virginity.
Come on, aren't you gonna fuck me?
Senpai!
Y-You're being so rough! My pussy is convulsing!
I can't believe I'm getting this turned on
from a virgin's cock. He'll make me crazy!
Senpai, you're so cute!
Don't say that, you dummy!
Why is this making me happy?
His cock is making me go crazy!
Sorry, I think I'm gonna cum!
Do it! Just pump all of your cum into my pussy!
I want your raw cum in my pussy!
Come on, pour it into my womb!
Fill me up with your cum!
It's cumming!
It's flowing into me!
There's so much I might even get pregnant!
Thank you. I'll treasure this memory for as long as I live.
What are you saying?
Huh?
I'm not letting you off the hook after just one time!
Skank-senpai!
Move it more!
Let's cum together!
Thrust it in me like you're trying to break my womb!
I only wanted to take his virginity,
but now I can't stop thinking about his dick!
Shit!
I'm not gonna lose to a virgin!
I want more! Fuck me harder with that sly cock of yours!
Of course! I'll mess you up, senpai!
I want your cock! Cock!
I'm gonna cum inside again!
Me too! I want your cum!
I wanna cum together! Spray your cum inside of me!
It's shooting out inside of me! Your cum's filling me up!
Thank you very much.
Oh, crap, what time is it?
Hey, why don't you come over to my place?
Forget about the hundred virgins,
I just wanna fuck you a hundred times instead.
Senpai!
I'm really bored. You wanna come to karaoke with me?
Yay! Don't you wanna sing?
This is my kouhai, and her nickname is "idiot".
Idiot
She's famous for being cute,
while tacking in the brains department.
Hm?
Why'd you just strip? You don't think
about anything other than sex, do you.
You say that, but aren't you thinking you
want me to play with your microphone?
Come on, why don't you take your cock out already, senpai?
Fine!
Oh, wow, it's senpai's cock!
How does it feel, senpai?
Does it feel good, Mr. Cock?
Squeeze squeeze. Rub rub.
Oh my god, your hands are so dirty.
Doing this makes it feel like I'm raping
you with my boobs. It's turning me on.
I think I'm gonna cum!
Oh no, if you're that rough, you're gonna rip off my nippies!
I'm gonna...
You're going to cum from my boobs?
Shoot, shoot, shoot it out!
You're cumming so much!
This is so great!
Looks like you can keep going, senpai.
Good, your cocks hitting my pussy.
They're rubbing against each other!
It's just like the rumors about your cock said!
It's so hard!
Don't move now, senpai. Just stay still.
It feels like I'm raping you. It's really turning me on!
Does it feel good? Your cock is so hard,
but you're so soft, it's cute!
Hey! Don't get carried away!
No, don't do that! My pussy...
Your cock's digging into my pussy!
It feels like I'm floating!
You're making my pussy go crazy!
I'm gonna cum inside. You don't mind, do you?
Cum! Cum inside my pussy, it's just for you!
I'm cumming!
Oh my god, senpai! That feels so good! I love this!
It's my first time having sex this amazing!
Next time, let's have sex on top of a roller coaster, okay?
Are you an idiot?
Come on, shoot your semen out already!
You've become pretty popular.
You used your cock to make me fall for you, after all.
You're the one who started those rumors about me?
Why wouldn't I? Don't let it get to your head,
just because you lost your virginity!
This is it! This hugeness! My pussy can't be
satisfied with anything but his cock now!
That's because, I really like...
Before that, let's have more sex, first!
Then we can talk about that!
With that being said, pump me full of your cum!
I'm cumming!
This guy's the best!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
encoder: bakaproxy
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч