Last time on JK and the Convenience Store Manager
Cleaning in progress
Thank you for your continued patronage.
Please come again.
Thank you. I'll come again.
Oh, great. Thank you...
This perverted geezer's just going at it out in the open!
Just watch, I'll get you back!
Cleaning in progress
This is so embarrassing...
That's right! I think I've said this before, but be careful, Yui.
He might sneak a peek at your
panties. Don't let your guard down.
Geez, Shii-chan, your image of him is so warped.
Did something happen?
Huh?
Oh, no. I just get that feeling, you know?
Geez, Shii-chan.
She's even going so far as to lie.
I can't forgive you, oji-san.
Wh-What is it?
Y-You're committing a crime! You're molesting her!
You're a pervert!
You're a mongrel!
You're fat!
Where's all this coming from?
That's pretty rude. Can't deny being fat though...
Don't try and play dumb when I know you've
been doing horrible things to Shii-chan!
Are you blackmailing her even during work?!
Did she see us?
No way!
What would you even know about the two of us...
I know everything about her!
That face...
Do you really know her?
Wha... What are you doing? Stay away from me!
I know her better than you do!
Did you know that she has a mole next to her pussy?
Huh?
Puss... Mole? Huh?
Did you know that when Shioni sucks
dick, she goes at it from the left side?
Wh-What are you saying?
What's even up with that? Pervert!
Why you...
No! I'm sorry, Daddy!
I'm sorry!
A perverted daughter like you needs
to be punished inside her body too!
No, Daddy, what are you going to do?
No, don't! Daddy!
No! What is this?!
Daddy! Stop! It hurts!
Daddy's inside me!
It hurts!
No! No!!
Daddy! It hurts!
It hurts!
It's so painful! Daddy, forgive me! Please!
Please let me go!
It doesn't feel good no matter how many times you do it!
Your sister was a pretty good learner.
I'm sure your body will learn to like it after
I pour enough into you until morning too.
No, I don't want that!
Daddy, please let me go!
I promise to be a good girl!
JK and the Convenience Store Manager
Get some dirt on the part time bitches and then it's all you can fuck!
Perverted but Cute JK Shiory & Yui ~Backed Into a Naughty Corner~
No, stop! Listen! This...
Daddy, stop!
No, please!
I can't take anymore!
You're a perverted girl who
masturbates while watching her friend.
I can tell your body wants more.
No...
I'm really at my limit!
No! No more!
I really can't take anymore!
No! This...
No!!
No way! No!!
It's coming out! It's inside me!
No... I peed myself!
I told you to stop!
Why?! You're so mean!
I can't believe you made me do that!
I-Is this all I have to do?
This torment never ends.
That's it.
It's better than me telling everyone
about your embarrassing moment.
Stop! If you do any more than this,
I really won't be able to go home.
No way! You came so much but you're this hard again already?!
No! Why?!
It's still so ready to go!
Please finish already!
Your dick is... It's coming inside!
It's rubbing against my insides!
This... It's digging into my insides!
It just keeps rubbing against me! It's so intense!
If this goes any longer, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum!
As long as we're in here, you can cum all you want.
But I don't want to! Put me down already!
I told you already, didn't I? We're going all night.
You can't be...
No! I... I don't want this, but...
But if this keeps going on, I'm going to break!
No! No more! I can't...
Calm down. You're mine forever.
That's...
I don't want to be yours forever!
No, I don't... I don't want that!
No, this...
No, this is bad!
It's coming again!
It's coming!
This...
I'm cumming!
I'm peeing myself again!
I can't stop it!
No!!
So, I'm your slave forever, huh?
I'm your plaything now, huh?
I wouldn't say slave, so much as... uh...
Just someone who looks after me.
Does that mean that you'll do something
for me for doing dirty things with you?
Oh, yeah, that's about right.
I'm not trying to force you to do anything, Yui.
That's only if you listen to what I tell you to do, okay?
Is that right?
I understand.
Huh? What are you doing here?!
School let out early, so I thought I'd come over and hang out.
Hm?
I guess single guys really are hopeless when it comes to cleaning.
You need to hurry up and get a g-girlfriend you know?
Nobody asked for your opinion.
Go home already.
Huh? What? Is there something you don't want me to see?
Well, I guess you are living alone at your age.
Of course you'd have weird...
What? Were you taking a shower?
That'd be great if you were.
Go ahead. I'll wait here.
No, I...
What?
Is a girl using your shower right now or something?
As if that'd ever happen.
You're a fucking idiot, you fat piece of shit!
Well, I...
What's going on here?!
What am I? The girl who walks on the
girl her man's cheating on her with?!
You lied to me! You sleaze!
God, I told you, didn't I?!
I told you she was a girl who'd sell her own panties!
What? You told him that much, Shii-chan?
You're so mean!
What's up with that act? You charlatan!
You're sounding more like your age now with that word, granny.
Yui, you idiot! Peeper!
Are you talking about yourself?
It's okay to fantasize about high school girls, but an
old, single fatty piece of shit like you is just a sucker!
He said he'd take care of me for the rest of my life.
Now I don't have to worry about any of my expenses.
Wait, are you actually gonna...
So what would you do if he pushes you
to the ground and says "you're mine"?
What the heck? Your imagination is crazy, Yui.
Are you really okay with having your
first time just taken away like that?
As long as it's someone I like, I don't mind what they do to me.
I don't understand you at all.
I'd rather a more romantic time cuddling in bed.
That's weird, Shii-chan. You need to get with the times.
No, you're just too crazy.
Well see, if it happens my way, we'd do
it so much that he'd feel indebted to me.
What's with that reasoning?! You'd
break if it went on for that long.
Is that your real plan?!
Yep.
Welcome.
Okay then, go more to the right.
Yeah, yeah.
A little higher.
Maybe a bit more to the right.
Yeah, a little bit higher.
Just a little more, okay?
Okay, Daddy?
Shii-chan, you peeper.
It's your turn to manage the register. It's not good to slack off.
I-I'm not!
I just came to tell you to keep it down
because people can hear you from outside!
His tongue is just so amazing... I'll try to keep it down.
What?
Do you want in on this, Shii-chan?
What are you saying?!
Hurry up and finish so you can clean the store!
I just cleaned though.
So good! Your tongue is poking around in my pussy!
So good! Your dick is so amazing!
I need to get back to work.
So please hurry...
I can't believe your dick feels so good!
What do you do by yourself with
the footage you get from the store?
Sheesh, oji-san, you're so silly.
I'll take care of your dick for the rest of your life.
Look at you pouting. You're so cute.
I want more, but we need to stop soon.
If you don't want to work as the manager
right now, then focus on making me feel good.
Just like that! Rougher!
It's coming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!
So much of your cum is shooting out inside me!
Geez, Yui. She always steals away the things I like!
Give me more of your dick, oji-san.
My insides are filled with your dick!
Your tongue is spinning around inside me!
So good!
It's so amazing!
Focus more here!
I want it rougher!
Come on!
Just focus on me!
You're going to look after me for the rest of my life, right?
So focus on me, not her.
I'll take better care of you!
So just leave her for later!
What are you talking about?
What? Aren't you going to take care of me forever?
Yui, move somewhere else!
Give me your tongue, oji-san!
Mess me up more than Shii-chan!
Your dick is inside me!
Yes!
This is so intense!
This is too good! It's so deep!
That's not fair!
I haven't even cummed yet!
Hey, don't touch ther...
Harder!
For someone who's being allowed to fuck
hot girls, you're not doing a very good job.
Yes, that's it!
Harder!
This! Yes!
You're going to make me go crazy!
Yeah, that... that feels amazing!
I-If you keep doing it like that,
you're going to turn me on for real!
She's lying to you again.
Shut up Shii-chan.
I'm really enjoying his dick!
Don't get in our way!
So deep!
Just keep coming deeper like that!
Yes! I'm gonna cum again!
I'm cumming!!
This is so amazing! Cum just keeps
pouring out of your dick into me!
If you put that much inside me, I might get pregnant!
I'm sharing some with you, Shii-chan.
Oh right, Shii-chan, congrats!
You got your scholarship, right?
Oh, thanks.
And in that time you domesticated that guy.
That kinda pisses me off.
Don't be like that. I'll share him with you.
Why are you acting like you'd be doing me a favor?!
I was the first one to do it with him!
But I was the one he chose to take care of for the rest of his life.
I hate you, Yui!
If we don't get you home soon, nee-san is gonna worry.
What do you think you've done to us?
Geez, Shii-chan, play nice.
He's my slave after all.
Slave?! Yui, you...
Mom.                                                            Mom.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality check: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч