Thank you!
What are you lookin' at, old man?
The customer as they were leaving.
What an obvious lie.
Geez!
You're such a creep.
Look, I totaled everything up for the day.
Oh, great. Good job.
She's such a brat,
but I can't say anything since I slack off.
What's the matter, Shi-chan?
Hey, Yui! I told you not to call me that!
I've always called you that, though.
You're Shi-chan to me.
Sheesh, Yui, you idiot.
Huh? Why am I an idiot?
You're done, right? Let's go home.
We're being eye-raped by that disgusting old man.
Shi-chan!
Sorry about that, sir.
Wait, I forgot to restock the toilet supplies.
I'll be right back, Shi-chan.
You're gross.
You doing well in school?
What does that have to do with anything?
What are you, a stalker?
Do you work here just to creep on
and stare at high school girls all day?
Gross! You're disgusting, what's the matter with you?!
With your age, belly, and face,
I think you're getting in over your head.
Th-This fucking kid...
That wasn't my intention at all.
I was asked to work here, too.
Yeah, by my classmate.
Sir, I found this in the bathroom! This is a camera!
In the public bathroom?
This is a crime. We should give this to the police.
Wait, if I remember right, the manager
said something about preventing shoplifts.
So you think maybe...
But if it was in the restroom, then...
If the owner put it there,
wouldn't there be a live feed in the office?
U-Uh, I'm not sure about that.
I mean, you know the owner just does whatever, right?
I don't trust him at all.
Maybe we should contact the owner.
I'll confirm this with him in the report later.
All right, then.
JK and the Convenience Store Manager
Ero
Get som dirt on the part time bitches and thenit's all you can fuck!
Cheeky Wanton JK: Shiori Sucking Scheme Fucking her to Shreds.
God damn, that fat ass beating around
the bush pissed me off so much.
He used to be pretty cool.
I don't care. Let's just get back home and study.
You need to do well on the next test
to keep your scholarship, right?
Yeah, I need to step my game up.
You can ask me for help, you know?
I've done enough of that. I'll return the favor soon.
You don't need to.
Oh, but if you come over to my house,
you can't call your boyfriend.
Owwie!
Geez, you know that neither of us have one.
Oh, come on, Shi-chan, stop it.
I keep telling you not to call me that!
Oh, wait. I forgot the bento from work.
Yeah, me too.
Now that I think about it, we've just been
going to work and then back home every day.
Oh crap, I messed up, now I have no dinner!
Same!
You can go home first.
My aunt should be back by now.
God, Yui. Stop, you pervert.
You touched me first, didn't you?
Just as I expected, huh?
I forgot something. I'll be out of here soon.
Aren't those from the store?
What? These are the ones you gave us.
Like, the ones you were going to throw away.
That's not the one I gave you.
How senile are you? Geez.
Tonkatsu bento
Why'd you call me out here?
What are you doing?
You're not even friendly while working,
and now you're stealing?
I'm not stealing! Just let me explain!
You're lucky I convinced the owner not to call the police.
I'm sorry, but I really wasn't!
If we reported this, you could
be suspended, or even expelled.
That wouldn't work out well for
the sister you're so indebted to...
S-Suspended?
I'm already indebted to my aunt,
but now I might lose my scholarship? No!
If you still insist that you weren't stealing,
then we'll really have to make the report...
Please don't do that! I'll do anything!
I'll even work for free!
You'll really do anything? Really?
Yeah, I will, so please!
Then, lift up your skirt and show me your panties.
What the hell? Screw that, you piece of shit!
That's sexual harassment... a crime!
Wait, you didn't...
I don't care what you think.
If you refuse, I'll just go to the police...
I'd rather throw my life away than do that for you.
Yui would be reported as an accomplice, you know?
That would be really bad
for someone you owe so much to.
All because of your pride.
W-Wait!
I'll do it... I'll do it, okay?
"I'll do it...? I'll do it, okay?"
I understand. I-I will do it.
Th-That's enough, isn't it?!
No, not yet.
You fucking dirty lecher.
You're fucking scum.
You're so stiff. This shouldn't be new for you.
You've sold yourself for sex, haven't you?
What? Like hell I have!
I don't know what you've been fantasizing about,
but keep that shit to yourself, you scumbag!
Okay then, suck this.
Wh-Wh-Wha...
Is this your first time seeing one?
Do it already!
No!
Don't make me touch it! Hey!
Everything depends on your attitude.
Screw you! Stop it! Please!
Not happening.
Hey!
Should I take your cousin to the police too?
It stinks! How did I get into this?!
I'll never forgive you for this!
I'm the one doing the forgiving.
Fucking geezer. Stop messing around, you lowlife.
You still have a foul mouth, even in a situation like this?
You...
Why am I being forced to do this? I don't understand!
I can't breathe!
I really can't breathe!
Looks like it.
Fuck, your teeth made it hurt.
I won't forgive you like this.
Hey, what are you doing?!
You're not gonna... You're kidding, right?!
No! Don't do it!
Wai...
Why are you cumming inside me?! Wait, stop!
If I can't cum in your mouth, then I'll do it here.
No, you can't! You can't!
It's coming in! You can't go in any further than that!
Ow! It hurts! It really hurts!
Looks like my dick made you a woman.
No!
It hurts! Stop!
It'll start feeling good soon.
Like hell it will!
I won't feel good doing it with
someone like you, you animal! Scumbag!
You blackmailed me into doing this!
You're fucking scum!
I'm gonna call the police on you!
Rich, coming from a thief.
I didn't steal anything!
You pervert! You dog! You piece of shit!
You went through with this though,
which means you admit to stealing, right?
I didn't do it, you piece of shit!
Your pussy is a lot smoother now.
Has the pain changed to pleasure?
What are you saying, you... Stop this already!
What's going on?
It hurt up until now, but now my body is...
You're letting out a nice voice now too.
Screw you! Just hurry up and finish already!
Don't be in such a rush.
I'll finish by cumming inside you.
No, you're kidding, right? Don't do that!
No, stop, please! Please don't! I beg you!
You think you can get anything
by just begging? You're too naive!
No! No! Please, no!
Don't! No!
No!
No way, he really came inside me!
His semen is inside of me!
Keep up the good work.
Die.
That fucker...
This is a cleaning fellatio. Don't bite.
Welcome!
Yesterday was great as usual.
It's been a while since I've been this motivated.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning...
Oh. Let's work hard today as usual.
Yep, I'll do my best.
Happy to hear it. Let's do our best today, Shiori-chan.
Yeah, looking forward to it...
White today, huh?
That suits Yui since she's so pure.
Shiori's pretty docile today.
Is she being cautious?
Yui, can you take over the register?
We have a lot of inventory to do,
so Shiori and I will take care of that.
Hurry up and do inventory.
Knock it off! You already did whatever
you wanted yesterday, didn't you?
Stop! I'll scream!
You think you're in a position to do that?
Scum... You animal...
Pervert!
Cute panties you have on.
You giving me the silent treatment? Fine. That's fine.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie