Cleaning in Progress
As always, thank you for coming!
Please visit us again soon!
Thank you! I'll be back!
Oh, great! Thank yo...
This perverted geezer doesn't even care
where we are, he just does it in the open!
Just watch. I'll get you back!
Cleaning in Progress
This is so embarrassing...
Seriously, if somebody finds us,
we won't be able to come up with an excuse.
You perverted geezer.
You got so hard while we were at the register, you trash.
I have really important exams tomorrow, you know?
You'll be fine, Shiori.
I'm not worried at all.
Hmph. From you, that doesn't mean anything.
If you lay your hands on Yui when I'm gone,
I'm gonna kill you, okay?
Jealous?
Not at all, you dumbass.
I'll come and give you a hand even on my days off.
That was too much!
Their shifts aren't even over yet.
Is he forcing her to do it as part of her work?
So deep!
Your dick is too rough!
You're getting too turned on from a high schooler,
you perverted geezer! You trash!
There! Deep!
Keep thrusting!
No! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
No!
It's coming inside me!
Your dirty semen is pumping into my pussy!
It's still flowing inside me!
Tomorrow's finally the day, huh? I've gotta give it my all!
It'd be great if you get that scholarship.
Yeah.
Sorry about skipping work.
But, with this I can finally be independent!
Financially independent!
Oh, right, I should probably warn you to be careful.
Like, being careful of not showing your panties, and stuff.
Geez, Shi-chan, I don't think oji-san's the type to do that.
Did something happen?
Huh?
U-Uh, no! But, you know, you can never be too careful.
Geez, you're such a worrywart.
Shi-chari's lying to me.
I can't forgive you, oji-san!
Good morning.
Good morning. Shiori's not here, so it's gonna be...
I know! It'll be fine.
Now that Shiori's not around, this is my chance, but...
O-Oji-san, I need to talk to you about something.
Wh-What is it?
Y-You're committing a crime! You're molesting her!
You're being a pervert!
You're a mongrel!
You're fat!
Where's all this coming from?
That's rude.
Can't really deny being fat, though...
Don't play dumb! I know you've been
doing horrible things to Shi-chan!
Are you blackmailing her to do
things like that, even at work?!
Did she see us?
No way!
I'm going to file a complaint
with my mother, and the police!
I never thought you were such a horrible person!
You're falsely accusing me.
You don't even have any proof...
I have proof!
I copied it off of there.
When I saw you looking at Shi-chan with
perverted eyes, I thought I was just tired,
but I guess I wasn't, was I?
– I always wanted to believe that it was nothing
more than that, but I was wrong...
– Should I just do it now?
– She'd fight back, though.
I'm against violence!
I can't believe that you'd try to get rough with me!
This is just a misunderstanding.
I didn't force her into anything.
Shiori came on to me.
That's a lie!
What would you know about the two of us...
I know everything about her!
That face...
Do you really know her that well?
Wha...
What are you doing? Stay away from me!
I know her better than you do!
Did you know that she has a mole next to her pussy?
Huh?
Puss... Mole? Huh?
Did you know that when Shiori sucks dick,
she goes at it from the left side?
Wh-What are you saying?
What's up with that? Pervert!
You're the one saying you know everything about her.
How can you say that without
really knowing everything, huh?
Th-That's...
Aren't you embarrassed?!
S-Stop it...
I'm not done talking to you yet!
You damn liar!
I'm not lying. When it comes to Shi-chan, I know...
People who lie so blatantly deserve to be punished.
Stick your ass out.
No! Pervert!
What are you even saying?
I know more about her than you do!
Still lying, huh?
Hmph, you must've been spoiled as a kid.
I'm not going to be so soft on you.
In place of your father I'll punish you!
That hurts!
No, oji-san! Stop!
Stop! It hurts!
Call me Daddy.
You're making your dad sad. This isn't how I raised you.
No, stop. Why is this...
Ow!
Please stop already, oji... Daddy!
No, please, Daddy!
Please, not there!
What's this? You got wet after Daddy hit you?
That turned you on?
No, it didn't!
There's no way! Sto...
Then why are you so wet?
Are you lying to me again?!
No! I'm sorry, Daddy!
I'm sorry!
A perverted daughter like you needs
to be punished inside her body as well.
No, Daddy, what are you doing?!
No, don't! Daddy!
No! What is this?!
Daddy! Stop! It hurts!
Daddy's inside me!
It hurts!
No!
Daddy! It hurts!
No! It hurts!
It's so painful! Please, Daddy, forgive me!
Please!
No! This can't be happening!
Daddy, please!
Please forgive me!
Daddy's punishing me on his lap! No!
Please, stop already!
Forgive me, Daddy!
If you promise not to lie anymore, I'll forgive you.
I won't! I won't lie anymore!
Daddy, I'm sorry!
Daddy's glad that you've come around.
Daddy, this is amazing! So intense!
Daddy!
This... What is this?
Something is going inside me.
Daddy, I'm sorry!
I was a bad girl.
Daddy.
I'm sorry.
Come on, wake up, Yui.
Daddy?
Huh?
That was great Daddy is so happy.
Y-You're horrible.
"Daddy?" What the hell are you even saying?
You mongrel! Trash! You perverted fatty!
You look really cute on film, Yui.
No way.
You don't mean...
Did you do this to Shi-chan too?
I told you, didn't I? She came onto me.
That's not... That can't be...
All right then, see you tomorrow.
This can't be. My first...
Oji-san did those things to me...
I liked him, but now that I know he's that kind of person, I...
What the hell is this?!
Even Shiori didn't do this.
That being said...
I have a backup.
I'll keep it hidden at my base.
Huh?
Is this...
I need to thank the owner for this.
Calling
Yui
Good... morning.
What do you want, pervert?! Don't come near me!
Wow, you really hate me.
That's your own fault!
I'll never forgive you!
I could say the same thing.
I could say that you attacked me.
The owner installed some cameras over here too, you see.
I think I've made my point.
I don't need to say anything else, right?
Stop!
Not there!
No!
You're... You're being too rough, Daddy!
Please!
Forgive me! I can't take any more of this!
Your body seems to like it, though.
That's not true at all!
No! I'm serious, please stop!
Not in this position!
It's rubbing so deep inside me!
No!
Please, let me go!
No matter how many times you do it, it won't feel good!
Your sister is busy with her studies.
It'll feel good by morning, after I pour more in.
No, I don't want that!
Daddy, please let me go!
I promise to be a good girl!
Deep...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч