No! Stop!
No!
I don't want this, but my body is acting weird!
Every time his dick goes inside me, I...
No! Not agai...
If this keeps up...
If I keep quiet, then...
Here, this is for you. If we continue like this,
everyone will be happy. It's up to you.
Shii-chan? Are you okay?
Yeah.
They have such dirty bodies.
If this goes well, then...
Wait, what happened to all of the drinks from here?!
You're going to stock them right now.
Hey!
Better get started, or someone might see.
Really? Here?! You're such a pervert!
Oh, you're wet.
Does that mean you want it?
No! I don't wan...
It slid right in. Were you waiting for it?
No, I wasn...
It's inside me! His dick is inside me!
Just because there's nobody here,
doesn't mean that he can put it in me!
Just stop already!
Put your hands to work, not your mouth.
You're such a...
It's getting easier to thrust it inside you.
Looks like you've gotten used to me.
That's not true at all!
There's no way I'd get used to a piece of shit like you!
There's no way I'm getting turned on from doing it with him!
No!
Don't!
If you keep going, I'm gonna...
Wait!
Wait, no, stop! Stop!
Here, of all places?!
No!
No, wait! Stop! No!
Please, no!
Don't look!
No!
Hey, Yui's coming!
What should we do?!
What?!
I heard something break. Is everything okay?
Oh...
I dropped the bottle.
The old man went to get some cleaning tools.
Oh, okay. Are you all right?
Grape juice?
Yeah. Some of it got on me,
so I'm going to change after I clean up.
I got this. You can go back to the register.
Okay, got it.
On top of peeing in the store,
you broke merchandise. You need to be punished.
I'm sorry! I won't do it again!
No, stop!
Please, stop!
If Yui sees me like this...
She's a good girl, so she's still at the register.
She sold her panties once.
What?
She was broke, and heard about selling them.
She posted pictures without showing her face.
Yui did? No way.
Geez!
What are you spacing out for?!
If you really want panties, you can have mine!
Seriously. Even if she took pictures of her panties,
those weren't the ones she actually sold.
Oh, really? That's a relief.
Seriously, how dumb are you?
You're just a shitty old man!
My pussy's getting so wet and it's throbbing so much!
I can feel your dick twitching.
You're gonna cum inside me soon.
Do it!
Give it to me!
Give me all of it!
It's coming!
Pour your semen into me!
Your semen's pumping into me! There's so much!
This...
My mind's blank.
His dick is making my body feel so amazing!
Shii-chan?
Mister? This can't be real!
There's no way customers won't find out.
Thank you for your patronage!
Hey, Yui's gonna be here soon.
Yeah, I know. Hurry up and cum already.
Excuse me?
Yes?
Is the blonde girl on her day off?
O-Oh, you mean her.
She's coming later, do you need something?
Oh, no, nothing.
I see, so she's coming in later.
Thank you.
What was that all about?
She's coming later.
We'll have to come back later.
Yeah.
For crying out loud. Fucking kids.
Good morning.
Um, is Shii-chan here already?
Uh... yeah, she is.
Yeah, she's definitely in me.
In you?
I mean... Uh, she's out on an errand for me right now.
Oh, I see.
Um, Mister, listen.
Um, so, do you, uh... With Shii-chan, um...
Hm? What's this about?
No, it's nothing. I'm going to go get changed.
What was that about? Did something happen?
There's too much. You're gonna make me choke.
Yui's in now, so let me go on break.
Geez...
You're too hard!
You really think it's a good idea to do this in a public area?
This is what you want though, isn't it, Shiori?
Don't get the wrong idea! Before, I was...
Hm? What's that?
I'm saying that I had never had sex
with anyone before you.
I'm going to have sex with Yui.
You're crazy if you think you can
have sex with someone as pure as Yui.
Don't I let you do everything you want to me anyway?
Let's see if that's true.
Just like this.
Yui won't let you do any of this stuff to her.
It's here! Your cum!
It's shooting up to my womb!
It's still pouring into me!
You're gonna make me pregnant!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
encoder: bakaproxy
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч