Manager of the Reisai Convenience Store: Shimoda Yoshihiru.
Overweight, middle age, and single.
He relies on his job as the manager of the convenience store that the owner,
his friend gave him. His secret entertainment comes from taking secret videos
and pictures of the two high school girls that he hired.
One being his niece Yui, and the other being her cousin, Shiori.
High School Niece: Nakaizumi Yui.
A serious girl who always follows the rules. She's a hard worked and very positive.
Yui is a twintailed natural klutz who always tries her hardest, but has
a tendency to be very clueless. She works part time to help her mother
a little since she pays for both their daily lives as well as her school fees.
She's a lovable and diligent dirty, but cute high school girl. ♥
The Wanton High School Cousin: Fuyuzuki Shiori
Both her appearance and speech pattern show that she is a cheeky and arrogant, modern high school girl. Her parents have passed away and her aunt, Yui's mom, took her in.
They have recently begun to live together. Shlori didn't want to be taken care of
without being able to give anything back, so she decided to take up a part time job
to pay her back She's trying to get a scholarship for school and even though she might
look and sound like a floozy, she's a very serious and hard working high school girl. ♥
The Mom who doesn't look like a mother, Yui's Mom: Nakaizumi Mao.
She's so cute, it's hard to imagine that she's a mother.
She works as a saleswoman for life insurance plans and is an upstanding worker.
She's very doting on her little brother, Yoshihiro. ♥ Even though she let Yui work
a part time job, she's a cute mom who always makes sure to ask about Yoshihiro
She's very frightening when she's mad... or so Yui says.
On the one hand, Yui doesn't want her mother finding out about what's going on, so she comes up with a plan: "Let's have mom assaulted." Using the dumbfounded Shiori as a part of her plan and getting Yukihiro to cooperate by having sex with him, she came up with a plan to deal with Mao. Unknowing of the plan, Mao receives a worring call from Yukihiro and rushes to the convenience store office to help him... Yui and Shiori sit in the back office watching the scene unfold on the computer through the hidden cameras...
JK's and the Perverted Convenience Store Manager
Get some dirt on the part time bitches and then it's all you can fuck!
Last time on JK's and the Perverted CSM ♥
No! I'm not lying!
No! No more!
I really can't take anymore!
No! This...
No!
No! Stop!
It's coming out! It's inside me!
I-Is this all I have to do?
This torment never ends.
That's it.
It's better than me telling everyone
about your embarrassing moment, right?
Stop! If you do any more than this,
I really won't be able to go home!
Your dick is still so hard!
Please finish already.
Your dick! It's coming inside!
It's rubbing against my insides!
I'm gonna cum!
No! No more! I can't!
Calm down. You're mine forever.
That's... I don't want to be yours forever!
No, I don't... I don't want that!
No, this!
So, I'm your slave forever?
I'm your plaything now...
I wouldn't say slave, so much as, uh...
Just someone who takes care of me?
Does that mean that you'll reward
me for doing dirty things with you?
Y-Yeah, that sounds about right.
I'm not trying to force you to do anything, Yui.
At least, as long as you do what I say.
Is that right?
I understand.
No, go more to the right.
Right there.
A little higher.
Yeah... a little bit higher.
Your tongue's so great! I'll try to keep my voice down.
What?
Do you want in on this, Shi-chan?
What are you saying?!
I just want you to hurry up and
finish so you can clean the store!
You said that I feel better than her, didn't you?!
You're going to look after me for the rest
of my life, right? So focus on me, not her.
I'll take better care of you!
So just leave her for later!
What are you saying?
I'll take care of your needs for the rest of your life.
You...
Hey, don't touch there!
Do it harder!
For someone who's being allowed to fuck hot girls,
you're not doing a very good job.
Yes, that's it!
Harder!
This! Yes!
You're going to make me go crazy!
Geez, Shii-chan, don't be mean.
He's my slave after all.
Slave?! Yui, you...
Mom?
JK's and the Perverted Convenience Store Manager
Get some dirt on the part time bitches and then it's all you can fuck!
The cute but sexy Mother/Older Sister:
Mao ~Dirty Pictures and the JK Friends that He's Fallen For ♥~
What should we do?
What's the matter?
You can go home ahead of me.
This might take a while.
Yeah, okay.
Don't come back too late, Mom.
I doubt she's going to be talking about us, but...
She's done so much for me. She's helping
me go to school and makes food for me...
How am I supposed to explain these illicit relations...
Are you okay?
Illicit relations? Shi-chan, you...
No one says that anymore!
Shut up!
I hate you, Yui!
Sorry, Shii-chan!
Stop it!
I give up! I give up!
I hate you, Yui!
Yui?
Should we kill her?
Hm?
I told you, I'm worried about you.
Look how big your stomach has gotten.
I don't like pigs, you know?
You're worrying too much, nee-san.
I just don't know what to do
when it comes to you, Yoshihiro.
Mornin'.
Morning.
What's with that? Way to set a mood.
Adults like me have a lot going on.
More importantly...
Hey, stay away from me!
I want you to work the register today.
Welcome!
That'll be two hundred yen.
I'll get that.
I-I'm sorry about that. Here's your receipt.
Welcome!
I knew he'd be up to something! This bastard!
I'm definitely gonna kill this asshole.
U-Um... Excuse me?
I, uh...
Y-Yes?
Um...
Oh, you're...
I'm not wearing panties...
So? What's going on here?
Huh? Ah...
This young lad's into you, apparently.
H-Huh?
But you know, this girl is an irredeemable slut.
You sure you're still interested?
Hey! I am not a slut!
Stop saying these weir...
You get it now? She's an exhibitionist.
If you're okay with that,
then I've no reason to stop you.
U-Uh, I, um, I, uh...
Sorry to have bothered you!
Good morning!
Huh?
Yui! That pig, he...
He made me...
What'd he do? Take off your panties and
show your bare ass to some random guy?
That must've been scary.
Yui!
That guy's been creeping on us, so I told
boss to do that to you to get rid of him.
Huh?
Y-Yui?!
Anyway, I brought something cool!
Check it out!
Is my butt really that unimportant?
Oji-san, right there!
It's okay. I'm just gonna copy it right here.
I didn't expect to get this many pictures.
But it should be good enough to get her with.
Yui?! That's horrible!
What's wrong with you?!
Geez, Shii-chan, we're having a serious discussion here.
Don't butt in.
You're having a serious conversation in that position?
Are you an idiot?!
She was yelling at you, wasn't she?
You need to prove that you're a man by getting back at her.
I don't think it's as simple as that.
And now you're sucking him off when
we're having a serious conversation?!
Shut up.
You started it Yui. I'm just continuing it.
I'll do it like this.
Your tongue's too intense!
What's gotten into you, oji-san?
All of a sudden, you're...
Shii-chan, what are you doing?!
I was gonna do that!
Yeah, well I got here first.
Looks like it feels good.
That's not fair!
It's twitching so much! Your dick's so amazing!
It's starting to bulge!
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Oh, wow.
It's coming out!
There's a flood of cum coming out!
There's so much cum.
So it felt good then, right?
Your dick's so amazing considering your age.
This computer's so slow!
Get one with better specs!
Just credit it as an expense.
Geez.
Your dick is...
It's coming inside of me...
I'm making it come inside of me!
It's all your fault, Yui, that I've become this dirty!
This is so good! I'm making it hit all my soft spots!
It's not my fault. You were this dirty all along, Shii-chan!
Geez, you're too loud.
It's because you always kept teasing me.
This is payback!
So good!
This old guy dick is so good!
My boobs are feeling more turned on than usual!
No... I can't stop... I...
No! Stop...
Stop! Stop!
I did it again...
Looks like that felt good.
Look at you pee yourself, Shii-chan.
Oji-san, you're being so intense!
Does that mean we have an agreement?
If you do it just like you do me,
then you'll have it done in no time!
Yeah I'll get on top of it just like how
I'm getting on top of you right now.
Your dick... It's so amazing!
It's so rough, and it's going so deep!
This is enough for you to tease her with, right?
Can you really call it teasing at this point?
C'mon, don't wimp out on me now!
Do your best for me, Yoshihiro-san.
So deep!
Right there! More!
More, Yoshihiro-san!
Do it like a man, okay?
Let's do it behind the shelves.
Even if we're hiding behind here, it's still pretty easy to tell.
If someone comes here, they'll see us!
That feels good!
Right there! Thrust it in more!
A customer might see us!
No! This...
This feels too good!
No! Don't!
So good!
There's so much coming out!
The customers will see all of my embarrassing places.
Okay then, oji-san, Shii-chan.
Don't hold back.
Oh, Yui?
Is he in the office?
Yeah, he's there.
What's the matter?
Well, he said there was something
he needed to talk about in person.
It's got me a bit worried.
She always gets so worried when it comes to him.
Have a good time.
It's finally time.
What kind of daughter looks forward
to her mom getting assaulted?
Look!
So what did you want to talk about?
Did something happen?
Yoshihiro, you can tell me anything.
Nee-san, you were doing these
things in our shop's bathroom?
This isn't good.
I know you're lonely, but how can you
scold me when you do things like this?
Are you sexually frustrated?
I-I'm not!
What is this?!
What were you thinking, taking these pictures?!
I can't believe you!
I was thinking, maybe bean help
you with your sexual frustration.
W-We're siblings!
You're kidding, right?!
Stop messing around! I'm starting to get mad!
Riding your dildo in my store...
Was riding my ass not enough for you?
Huh? No way... Yoshihiro?
Was I really that overbearing?
It's your own fault, nee-san!
You always treat me like a child!
Stop, Yoshihiro!
This isn't right! We have to stop!
We're siblings, for god's sake!
Please, stop it, Yoshihiro!
With a body like this, you can get any man you please.
Are you faithful to your husband?
No, stop...
Getting turned on by your little brother? Fucking slut.
Keep struggling, and I'll post those images online.
You might even lose your job.
Yoshihiro, what's gotten into you?
Why are you doing this?
I don't want to hear anything from a whore like you.
Were you waiting for this, nee-san?
Not that I care.
You're incredibly wet.
Do you get wetter after giving birth?
I'll never forgive you!
I'll hate you for the rest of my life!
That's fine.
In exchange, I'm gonna have my fill of fun with you!
Get a good look.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Don't...
Yoshihiro, if you go any farther...
It's too late!
Oh no! I came just from him putting it inside me.
Stop! This isn't...
We can't do this!
Stop!
Please!
It's not too late to stop.
You think I'm gonna stop now?
You can cum, but not inside, okay?
I'm being serious!
You're gonna get me pregnant! Today's not safe!
Please, Yoshihiro!
I bet Yui'd love a little sister.
Please, stop, Yoshihiro!
Stop! No! Stop!
Don't!
Stop! No!
You're cumming inside me...
Deep inside me...
You're really...
I'll never forgive you!
I'm never going to forgive you!
Wow, that was really something...
Shii-chan? Yeah?
Shii-chan...
Yui...
We can't...
Tell me, Yoshi-kun...
Did you not hear me say "stop"?
Boys who can't listen to their older
sister's orders need to be punished.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: hctah
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Next time on JK's and the Perverted CSM ♥
Then I'll help you remember.
Yoshi-kun, lick.
Really, while holding it?
Yoshi-kun, you fainted? I didn't know.
But this is just for today, okay?
You can't do this with anyone but me, okay?
So just for right now...
Give me lots of cum, Yoshi-kun!
Nee-san!
You cheeky brat!
Fine, I'll lick something! But I'm licking down here!
You dirtbag! Where do you think you're licking?!
Stop it! You idiot! No!
That's my asshole...
Stop! It's not clean!
You trash! I'm sorry, you shitty old man!
I hate you!
Are you apologizing or complaining? I can't tell!
It feels good, right?
Like I'd feel good from your trashy hands!
Just knock it off already, you...
Hey! I don't need your pity!
If you really feel bad then take your dick out!
It'll be easier to move around after I cum in it once.
It's going in! Your huge dick is
really going inside my asshole!
I heard you put my photo in...
Well, you've helped me out a lot, Yui.
I'll do something special.