Manager of the Reisai Convenience Store: Shimoda Yoshihiro
Overweight, middle age, and single.
He relies on his job as the manager of the convenience store that the owner, his friend gave him. His secret entertainment comes from taking secret videos and pictures of the two high school girls that he hired. One being his niece Yui, and the other being her cousin, Shiori.
High School Niece: Nakaizumi Yui
A serious girl who always follows the rules. She's hard worked and very positive.
Yui is a twintailed natural klutz who always tries her hardest, but has a tendency to be very clueless. She works part time to help her mother a little since she pays for both their daily lives as well as her school fees. She's a lovable and diligent dirty, but cute high school girl.
The Wanton High School Cousin: Fuyuzuki Shiori
Both her appearance and speech pattern show that she is a cheeky and arrogant, modern high school girl. Her parents have passed away and her aunt, Yui's mom, took her in.
They have recently begun to live together. Shiori didn't want to be taken care of without being abie to give anything back, so she decided to take up a part time job to pay her back. She's trying to get a scholarship for school and even though she might look and sound like a floozy, she's a very serious and hard working high school girl.
The Mom who doesn't look like a mother, Yui's Mom: Nakaizumi Mao
She's so cute, it's hard to imagine that she's a mother.
She works as a saleswoman for life insurance plans and is an upstanding worker. She's very doting on her little brother, Yoshihiro. Even though she let Yui work a part time job, she's a cute mom who always makes sure to ask about Yoshihiro. She's very frightening when she's mad... or so Yui says.
"I'll assault my sister." Yoshiro was encouraged by Yui to assault her cute but sexy mother, Mao. Yui and Shiori watched from the back room as this all unfolded, but began to get excited themselves. But suddenly the steamy situation that they were watching on the screen in front of them quickly turned into Yoshihiro prostrating himself in front of Mao. In conrtact, Mao was leisurely smoking a cigarette on the chair in front of him. While her lips curled into a sadistic smile she barked out that she'd "make him remember" and the she stuck out her leg and ordered him to "lick". Unable to say no, Yoshihiro began to lick her foot and suddenly from the deepest part of his memories, he remembered a trauma from when he was still a student.
"I want to become one with you, Yoshi-kun." The stunning revelation in front of Yui and Shiori. "It's okay, because now we're even. Also, Yui's behind this, isn't she?" Mao caught the culprit with ease and surprised Yui and Shiori who were still watching them... "She's so cool! She's so amazing! I think I'm in love!" "I didn't expect her to find me out..." Shiori quickly fell to the woman's charm and wit. As a way of getting back at Yoshihiro, Shiori tried sticking out her foot and saying "Yoshihiro. Lick" but she was only poking the bear with a stick...
JK and the Perverted Convenience Store Manager
Get some dirt on the part time bitches and then it's all you can fuck!
Last time on JKs and the Perverted CSM
Stop, Shii-chan!
I give up! I give up!
I hate you, Yui!
Yui?
Should we take out Mom?
You get it now? She's an exhibitionist.
If you're okay with that, then I've no reason to stop you.
U-Uh, I, um, I, uh...
Sorry to have bothered you!
Mom was yelling at you, wasn't she?
You need to prove that you're a man by getting back at her.
I don't think you really have to go
as far as assaulting her though.
And now you're sucking him off when
we're having a serious conversation?!
Shut up.
You started it, Yui. I'm just continuing it.
This computer's so slow!
Get one with better specs!
Just credit it as an expense.
It's all your fault, Yui, that I've become this dirty!
This is so good! I'm making it hit all my soft spots!
It's not my fault. You were this dirty all along, Shii-chan!
Geez, you're too loud.
It's because you always kept teasing me.
This is payback!
So good!
This old guy dick is so good!
My boobs are feeling more turned on than usual!
If you do it just like you do me,
then you'll have it done in no time!
Yeah I'll get on top of it, just like how
I'm getting on top of you right now.
Your dick... It's so amazing!
It's so rough and it's going so deep!
This is enough for you to tease her back with, right?
Wouldn't really call what she did as
teasing, maybe more over protective?
C'mon, don't wimp out on me now!
Do your best for me, Yoshihiro-san.
So deep!
I was thinking, maybe I can help
you with your sexual frustration.
W-We're siblings!
You're kidding, right?!
Stop messing around! I'm starting to get mad!
Riding your dildo in my store... Was
riding my ass not enough for you?
Are you faithful to your husband?
No, stop...
Getting turned on by your little
brother? You're such a pervert, nee-san.
Keep struggling, and I'll post those images online.
If those pictures get out, you're gonna lose your job.
I'll never forgive you!
I'll hate you for the rest of my life!
That's fine.
In exchange, I'm gonna have my fill of fun with you!
Stop!
Please!
It's not too late to stop.
You think I'm gonna stop now?
Stop! You can cum, but not inside, okay?
I'm being serious!
You're gonna get me pregnant! Today's not safe!
Please, Yoshihiro!
I bet Yui would love a little sister.
Tell me, Yoshi-kun...
Did you not hear me say "stop"?
Boys who can't listen to their older
sister's orders need to be punished.
JK and the Perverted Convenience Store Manager
Get some dirt on the part time bitches and then it's all you can fuck!
The Cute Relatives: Mother. Daughter, Niece~ Punishment by Anal~
So what do you say now?
I-I'm sorry, nee-san.
That's good. Apologize when you've done something wrong.
That's what I taught you.
But what did you do wrong?
I-I raped you...
Yes, that was definitely wrong, but...
That doesn't bother me too much.
Now we're even.
Huh?
– Huh?!                                                                           – Huh?!
I see the shock of it all is blocking the memory.
Then I'll help you remember.
Yoshi-kun?
Lick.
Good boy.
Slowly but thoroughly, okay?
I'm talking about the time we were at
Grandma's house over summer vacation.
Wow, it's getting all slimy.
Onee-chan, this is enough, isn't it?
No, we're only getting started.
Anyway, Yoshi-kun. Aren't you getting hard?
N-No I'm not!
There's no way...
I told you that I don't like liars, didn't I, Yoshi-kun?
I-I'm not lying! I'm just...
See? Look how hard you are.
Onee-chan, I can't breathe...
You're twitching so much. You're
already about to cum, aren't you?
Can you see? My private parts are getting soaked.
Oh god, this feels so good.
I'd like for us both to have our first times here today.
Ow...
But now we're connected, Yoshi-kun.
The view from up here is so nostalgic.
It was my first time back then.
I was so into it.
I didn't even know you passed out.
When you woke up, you forgot everything that happened.
So I just kept it a secret.
I'm starting to remember...
It was a secret I was keeping to myself, but...
Bu now that we're doing it again, I...
But this is just for today, okay?
You can't do this with anyone else but me, okay?
So just for now...
Do me hard, Yoshi-kun!
Nee-san!
Your dick feels so good!
Even though you're my little brother, it feels so good!
I-I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
There's so much cum gushing into my pussy!
Shii-chan...
Yui...
Yui?
Shiori-chan?
Yui's the one who came up with this, right?
– Of all the places to choode, why a convenience store?
– She saw right through everything.
So your plan was to rape me and blackmail me?
But what about after that?
I bet you didn't think that far.
You've even been taking pictures
of yours and Shiori's panties.
But it looks like Shiori's were more popular.
I took them down immediately though.
Oh, right. There are old pictures of
Yoshi-kun that I took in Yui's bag.
Don't play around too much.
I'm happy you're letting them work
here, but let's leave it at that, okay?
Wow, she's so cool!
Did you see that?!
She's so cool! I'm in love!
Yeah, yeah, I'm impressed by her too.
I need to be more careful around her.
Wait, she said something about
you taking pictures of our panties...
H-Hey!
It's fine if you're impressed by her, but
don't bite off more than you can chew.
Good morning!
Yeah, morning.
What's wrong with you?
Is this all because of what she said yesterday?
You're hopeless.
Shut up.
You don't know anything, kid.
Get to work.
Hey, hey, over here. Come on, did man.
What do you...
Yoshihiro. Lick.
Hey, sto...
You cheeky brat!
I'll lick all right.
But it's gonna be down here!
Gross! Where are you licking?!
Stop it!
Dolt! Stop it you idiot!
That's my asshole!
Stop! It's dirty!
Trash! Fatty! Animal!
Pervert! Sleaze! Idiot!
Stop! I'm sorry!
I'm apologizing!
Can't you hear me? I'm sorry you skeevy geezer!
Stupid!
Are you apologizing or complaining? For fuck's sake.
You like it, don't you?
As if, you fat sleazeball!
Stop it already, you...
Wait, your finger...
Stop... It's coming inside!
Stop! Seriously, stop!
Hey, come on, please! Please, you old man!
If you didn't pull that stunt in the first place...
That was Yui's idea! That wasn't my fault!
You're so pathetic for trying to
blame everything on high schoolers!
No!!
Fine, I get it. Let's all calm down!
Let's take it slow, okay?
I'm not mad or anything, okay, Yoshi-kun?
Stop! Why are you going even harder now you sleazeball?!
Most people would be more gentle now!
You stupid stupid stupid!
This is for you teasing me.
No way! No way! No way!
That's not going to fit!
You're going to rip me apart!
You're going to make me bleed! It's going to be a bloodbath!
No way! It's coming inside!
This is bigger than your usual shits, right?
Wait, fatty. Don't tell me you've
been watching me when I poop too?!
You filthy pervert!
No, that was just a guess...
I'm sorry to hear that.
I-I don't need your sympathy!
If you feel bad for me then take out your dick!
If I cum inside you, it'll make good lube for your poop.
Oh my god, your fat dick is really going inside me!
No! Stop! I'm gonna...
Why'd you put it in there?
No! It feels so weird!
It feels so disgusting! I don't like it!
I'll keep moving until it feels good.
Hold back a little!
Wh-What is this?
You shitty fatty! Die!
Please! Th-This is enough, isn't it?
No!
You've gotten so dirty.
Who has, dumbass?!
I'm not gonna let this slide! I'm gonna tell Auntie on you!
I'm not scared of my sister at all.
If she comes back here, I'll just rape her again.
You fat fuck!
You perverted, shitty dick idiot!
You should at least have second
thoughts about these things, you creep!
I could say the same about you too, Shiori.
Damn... You stupid fatty!
What is this!? It feels bad, so why am I...
Just cum with your asshole, you dirty high school girl!
No! I don't like this, but I...
I'm...
No! No!!
Cum's pouring into my ass!
It's coming all the way inside me!
You piece of shit!
You didn't even hold your cum back a little!
Haven't learned your lesson yet?
Good morning, Yoshi-kun.
N-Nee-san, I can explain...
Wow, you really are the worst.
Oh, you were having fun with Shii-chan?
Then I'll just be over there doing work.
You're joking, right, Yui?
Wh-What do you mean? You're
the one misreading the situation.
I have nothing to do with this.
You have pictures of me?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I haven't the slightest idea.
I'd prefer if you didn't randomly accuse me of anything.
Well, I do owe you one, Yui.
Let me pay you back.
Welcome!
Thank you very... much!
I'm never going to forgive you for making me do this!
I'm going to tell Mom on you!
Both you and Shiori think that I actually care!
Playing...
[MOVdata]no title_008
I'm not scared of my sister at all.
If she comes back here, I'll just rape her again.
You fat fuck!
You perverted, shitty dick idiot!
I'll play along this time, but this
is the last time, okay, mister?
W-Wait! Yui?!
You were watching the entire time?!
If your mom finds out...
Mom doesn't seem to know that he's laid his hands on us,
so with this...
Yui, you scare me.
There's that whole panties
incident that I had no clue about.
U-Um, excuse me.
I was a little surprised at the time, but I have
no intention of judging what you're into.
I-I'm not into that!
Something like that's way too early for me.
U-Um...
She's not into guys.
She only likes girls.
She's a total pervert!
Um, I...
I'm sorry to have bothered you!
Shii-chan...
This feels even better with something inside me.
Hey! Yui!!
What's the problem? No one's here and we're
not getting any customers now anyway.
And our manger's already doing it.
Listen, you idiot. Then don't
pretend like you're being serious.
Shii-chan, th-this is...
It feels so good!
This chair...
You call everyone else a pervert,
but you're the biggest pervert here.
Mister, this feels so good!
This fat chair is so good!
Now that I think about it...
Mom was pretty into the idea of getting you onto a diet.
What?
If you got thinner, I'd be pretty
happy too. Why don't you try it out?
Yeah, all this fat is just a ticking time bomb of disease.
You should really consider a diet.
If you succeed with your diet, you can have
sex whenever and wherever you want...
With Shii-chan.
Hey, Yui! Don't make weird promises!
This feels so good!
Do your best for me!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Oh no! It's the owner and Mom!
Huh? Aren't they supposed to be open?
Huh? What's the matter?
Why are you closed?!
It's just temporary.
Do you two need something?
I was just thinking about coming over and
suddenly I got a call from Takahiro-kun.
So he gave me a lift.
It was really nothing. Don't worry about it.
What's going on? Is she going out with him?
Huh? Given what happened the other day, I doubt it.
If I had to say...
This must be pretty transparent if even you,
the densest person on the planet can get it.
H-Hey, Yui?! Sheesh, you never miss
an opportunity to put me down!
The owner, huh? I just might have a great idea.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч