www.SubDESU-H.net
Sensei!
It's so deep.
Too rough.
Sensei, your dick is so amazing—
Oh no.
I can see my naughty reflection now.
I’m so... embarrassed...
Sensei.
We mustn’t.
I am acting so dirty...
Slutty Hatsune is the best!
Sensei, if you say things like that to me...
I’ll lose my mind!
So stuffed.
I feel it deep inside.
Yes, this feels great.
It’s feeling... so... tingly...
Oh the sex... is making me go crazy...
Then go crazy!
So thick... and your dick is so big...
Amazing...
My big, thick dick rubbing around inside feels great, right?
Yes.
I like it.
My pussy feels great!
Hatsune, it’s you that makes it this great for me.
Sensei... so having sex with me, turns you on so much?
I am so happy.
Your hard, turned-on dick is rubbing me inside.
I can’t take anymore.
It feels too good.
I’m going to melt.
Hatsune!
Give it to me.
Fill me full inside with your hot stuff, Sensei.
Sensei... so much...
It’s throbbing around inside of me.
Sensei.
For flooding me with this much quantity, thank you very much.
It’s leaving...
Sensei, your semen...
Sensei’s precious dick.
Allow me to clean it.
You’re cleaning it for me?
Hatsune, thank you.
Sensei, it’s your precious thing.
Sensei.
Do you like this?
Yes. I fell like I am in paradise.
Sensei... I’ll... ’ll make it even cleaner for you.
Oh, Sensei... you’ve fallen asleep on me.
W
Erotic JK and the Public Representative
~He takes JK as his lover and has his way with her~
With wet black stockings, Hatsune’s gracefully distorted erotic tits
Original ERO Animation
Do you remember?
The day you got my father’s petition.
I could not forget your kindness towards me, when I was terrified to go through with it.
Please pardon the intrusion.
I humbly apologize for making you wait.
I am Hatsune, the third eldest daughter of the Aoyama family.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Ah... I’m glad you came.
Um, are these clothes not to your taste?
The limo was late, so I had no time to change.
No, no... oops!
My humblest apologies!
It was my fault – I shouldn’t have talked to you at a strange time.
I will take care of this.
This is no big deal.
And besides...
Um, is this... umm...
I deeply apologize!
I was thinking of changing clothes soon.
And besides, that uniform suits you.
Hearing that makes me relieved.
Yes, I will gladly drink with you.
Do you usually do this sort of thing?
Usually my older sisters do it, but they’re busy tonight so I came here in their place.
It’s just that... um... this is my first time.
So I might not be very skilled at it.
But I will try my best all night, so please ask whatever you wish of me.
I see.
Then let’s get to it.
Um, yes, but may I ask a favor?
This is my first time, so will you please be gentle?
Please don’t stare. It’s embarrassing.
Don’t worry and leave everything to me.
Oh no... it’s too rough!
Your tongue... it’s rubbing...
It’s too amazing... I can’t breathe...
My boobs. Your hands are... touching my boobs!
My boobs... if you rub them so hard, I feel ticklish all over.
That means you’re turned on.
Sensei, your hands are directly on them now...
That’s...
It feels good, right?
I’m not sure.
I...
My body is... getting hotter...
Oh don't... my n-nipples...
Looks like you’re a slut at heart.
Oh no.
I’m losing my mind!
No!
Sensei, don’t!
You came just from your tits, didn't you?
Don’t look there... it’s embarrassing...
Sensei... You’re looking at my precious place.
Hatsune.
Everything about you is perfect.
Especially down here.
Is that so?
I don’t know how to reply, but I am happy that you are pleased.
Licking there... it’s dirty...
Not there... no don’t.
Sensei...
I’ll make it even better for you.
No.
If you suck so hard... I’ll...!
It’s a flood.
Are you about ready?
Yes, Sensei.
A man’s... um... thing... I had no idea it was so big.
I’m a bit bigger than average. Does the size scare you?
No. My body already belongs to you, Sensei.
I will not complain even if you destroy it.
That’s quite the determination.
It will only hurt at first.
Soon I’ll take you to heaven.
Yes.
Please, put it in.
What’s wrong?
Does it hurt, Hatsune?
Yes... but I’m fine.
I’ll move slowly. Just endure for a bit.
Yes, Sensei, please have your way with me.
It’s completely in.
Must be intense for a virgin like you.
I’m fine.
I am happy to be able to take in all of your precious part, Sensei.
Hatsune.
It’s amazing... so thick...
You’re so tight. I like it, Hatsune.
Sensei.... more... please, taste me more.
Right there... Sensei!
So is this your good spot, Hatsune?
Sensei, this feels strange... I...
I’m feeling... strange...
Sensei... I... I’ve become more slutty...
Sensei...
Sensei... I’m sorry.
I’m almost...
Oh no!
Sensei!
Sensei...
Giving my first time...
I felt like a country bumpkin changing into a princess.
I’m the lucky one here.
Oh was that so? I felt the same, Hatsune.
Sensei.
My apologies. Are you okay, sir?
Yes, I’m okay. Please be more careful.
I’m sorry, sir.
Sensei’s hand...
Is this... hitting my cheek... Sensei’s...?
Sensei, we mustn’t!
Not in a place like this.
Hatsune, whenever you are around, I just can’t hold back.
But still...
Sensei, this is embarrassing.
Don’t worry. There is a partition so he can’t hear us.
Sensei, are you sure?
Must I do this here no matter what?
Just being near you makes me like this, Hatsune.
Sensei... Just being with me makes him so hard...
So hard.
Sensei’s dick, it’s throbbing.
I’m starting to fall in love with this dick.
Sensei...
Sensei’s dick is getting bigger again.
Sensei, we’re almost there.
O-Okay.
Are you okay, Sensei?
Yes, don’t worry.
Hurry, I must finish this quickly.
Sensei... I can’t breathe...
Sensei, we’ve arrived.
Ah, thanks.
Sensei, I get the feeling you enjoy it when I protest.
Well, yes, um, maybe...
You meanie.
H-Here, this is where I work.
Mountains of papers.
Assembly men have so many things to do.
I understand. I will do whatever I can to help you.
I’d like to repay you in anyway that I can.
Oh, really?
But doing so will hinder your studies.
I know! I am well aware of that.
But I have confidence that I'll manage this without compromising my studies.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Thank you.
That’s a big help, Hatsune.
Then let’s get to it.
Wait, right now?
I can’t let this go, now that I see how much work needs to be done.
When the room is clean, it feels great doesn't it?
I’ll be finished soon.
Sensei?
Um... I’ve not finished cleaning...
Yes, that’s true.
I’ll wait for you until you’re done.
Sensei...
Um... if you could soothe that mighty rod of yours... I’d...
I see... you want it soothed, Hatsune?
So sudden... Sensei...
Oh, what have we here?
Please don’t... tease me with your... fingers...
You’re turned on, aren’t you, Hatsune?
You’re going to soothe me.
Sensei, do you like it when I’m slutty?
Of course. A straight-A student by day, and an erotic slut goddess when around me – that’s my precious Hatsune.
I’m so glad.
Being told that by you, Sensei, it turns me on even more.
Hatsune.
Oh, I don’t want to be abandoned by you for being perverted and slutty, Sensei.
You don’t need to worry about such a thing.
Sensei, it's okay for me to be such a naughty slut, right?
You’ll still love me?
Sensei...
My insides are spreading and it’s coming all the way deep inside.
Having my boobs squeezed... rammed by your cock... it makes me so happy.
That's good. Let yourself go crazy.
Okay.
Sensei, your dick... is rubbing my pussy...
So deep... your dick is throbbing deep in my pussy.
It feels so good.
Sensei, your dick is beautiful.
My insides is stuffed with it.
I’m going to go crazy from this sex.
I’m turning into more of a slut.
Everyone changes from sex.
I’m also becoming more of a pervert.
What is this?
My body is feeling... deeper, even crazier and fuller....
Your dick is so good... that I’m...
I’m cumming!
Cumming... I’m going to cum!
It’s coming inside...
Your hot stuff, Sensei...
Sensei...
That was an amazingly beautiful sex.
Even a slut like me... can I stay with you?
I want you with me forever, Hatsune.
Sensei...
Sensei, your precious dick, allow me to clean it for you.
Like always, thanks.
Whenever you’re with me, I get the sensation I can do anything.
That pleases me, Sensei.
Shit!
The mob boss demanding so much money!
Sensei...
Please stop this!
Sensei, your fist... your precious hand...
Your hand is the hand that will improve this country.
Umm... this might sound weird but...
Please, allow me to soothe you for a bit, Sensei.
Sensei, will you close your eyes for a while?
I saw this on the internet when I was looking for ways to please a gentleman... so allow me to...
It’s called “titty fucking” apparently.
Yes...
Does it not feel good?
No, no it's feels quite good.
What a relief.
I wanted to become more erotic for your sake Sensei.
Hatsune...
Sensei, your dick... it’s getting harder.
Amazing, sensei’s dick has regained its life.
Thank you Hatsune, you brought determination back into me.
I’m so pleased.
That I could be useful to you, even slightly.
Hatsune, you’re always helping me out.
Sensei... praising me with such kind words...
Hatsune, could you start using your mouth as well?
As you wish!
Sensei, your dick is getting so hard and big.
So big...
I’m so pleased.
That my mouth could help you release so much.
Your dick is amazing, Sensei.
Still hard, even after cumming so much.
Yes, being around you fills it with energy, Hatsune.
Oh no.
Sensei, you’re going to see my slutty-self again.
Sensei, it's embarrassing. Please don’t stare at me so much.
No. I’m going to stare at you always.
Slutty Hatsune belongs to me and only me.
Sensei...
So sudden... all the way inside...
Sensei... so hot... so manly... you make me feel so good.
Rubbing around inside my pussy...
I’m going crazy again.
So aggressive...
It feels great!
Hatsune, I’ve decided!
Sensei, your dick fits perfectly into my pussy. It’s amazing.
I’ve decided!
Yes, Sensei?
Praise me more.
I won’t follow those scumbags anymore!
Sensei... yes...
I’m... almost...
I’m going to walk my own path, come what may!
Yes...
And I’m about to cum too... by your dick...
I’m cumming! Cumming my own way!
I’m going to cum as well... by your dick, Sensei,
I’m going to cum!
Sensei... your hot semen...
It’s going so deep within me.
Just you watch, Hatsune, I am the man who has this country on my shoulders.
Yes. With your power, Sensei, I’m sure you can bring prosperity to this country.
www.SubDESU-H.net