Thrusting all he wants...
You...
This thing is really a monster!?
What were they called... right, an orc.
Geez, fantasy in real life, really!?
Let me go already!
That bitch said that they are attracted
to special characteristics...
Stop it!
What, what is this? This, my body is...
This isn't right!
Damn, did they drug me or something?
No way!
There's no way, I...
There's no way I'm feeling good!
What is this! Even though you're just a disgusting pig!
Why am I heating up?
Really? From the dick juice of this thing?
Did that happen to everyone?
Damn! Even so... like I'd ever... just accept that!
You... Don't get too full of yourself!
You're just a stupid pig! You can't even fly or anything!
Damn, it's not from your dick, you know! This is...
This is just the body’s natural reaction!
It's definitely... nothing else!
Don't misunderstand!
There's no way I’m... feeling it!
It’s not you... that made me cum!
Don't joke around!
Like I'd ever... feel good from you...
Hey, that's enough already! You just came!
Let me rest already...
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net [ #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
JK and the Orc Corps
~ The Assault on Seijo Academy by Evil Demon Pigs ~
At the same time
Um...
Wh...
What...
What are you going to... stop...
No, stop!
Don't lick... my pee!
What is this... being licked is making my body... strange!
No, don't, not there...
It's dirty!
You can't!
Don’t...
No way, his tongue is inside...
Not that... no there.
Why is his tongue getting hard...
It hurts! Stop!
I can't take it in anymore!
His tongue is trying to go deep inside me...
No...
Why is Mr. Pig's tongue... taking my first time...
It hurts...
Why I am... No! No!
Don't move anymore! No! Help!
Why... I don't want it it's gross, but..
I... No way!
I can't! No way! This is...
What?
What? It's moving inside... deep inside...
My insides are being licked... what is this!?
Stop... this is strange!
I'll go crazy! I...
This is just strange!
No way... not something so thick!
Don't... too big! No...
I'm kissing... with Mr.Pig...
His tongue... is inside me...
What do I do...
Horrible things are happening to me, but my body...
What?
No... don't... stop!
That's... not inside me...
No! No!
No... please, I beg you!
Don't’... not that... no way...
He'll come... Mr. Pig's semen is coming!
I... I...
It's flowing deep inside... I...
I'll get a baby of Mr. Pig...
Why is this happening... Nee-chan...
Twelve Minutes Ago
I can't even reach my manager!
What on earth is happening, geez!
You can't see outside because of the fog,
the phones don't work,
and an earthquake goes off when I try pee!
This is terrible!
But I guess homework is even worse...
What do I do?
Well, it is my fault for being too busy with my work
as an idol and skipped all the work before...
But there's just too much...
My savior Kotoko had just left me, too...
Help!
I have to go meet my fans at an event today! Please!
You'll make it if you finish that,
right? Just get started on it.
There's just too much! I don't
even want to think about it...
There aren't any male teachers, either...
Well, we are a girls school after all.
The families worry, too. What if a
male teacher does something...
That's it!
If that "something" does happen,
I could solve all of this...
Why?
With a special service from a high school girl idol!
Eh, um, um... What? The sleeping business?
Oh, so the serious Kotoko is interested in this stuff, too!
But it's different from the sleeping business.
It's not like I...
Um, I just want to know about
It, from intellectual curiosity...
are you doing that Kind of stuff?
A lot of rumors fly around but...
For me, it’s just with hands and mouth.
I get it easier, being an active JK idol.
The first time is for my boyfriend, right?
It's embarrassing if people ask, but...
Yeah, I guess.
You should give your first time to your boyfriend...
I know right!?
I'm just like Kotoko, a high school
girl who's bad with studying!
So, please help me with homework!
Why does it end like that?
Because I'm a dummy!
You know, it's pointless if you
don't figure them out yourself.
A normal student would rely on herself!
Kanon is also an active highschool student, right?
You're mean despite being perverted, aren't you.
It's completely unrelated to being perverted or not!
Geez...
Hey, wait, who are you!?
This is too much even for a prank!
What is this? Silicon?
Who in the world would make something like...
What is this? A doll?
Um, what is happening?
Someone explain! Kanon is just a dummy!
Hey cut it off...
Huh?
What, this is real? No way!
What is this... it's not a doll or costume...
What's going on?
Is it something from the mountains?
I've never seen anything like this!
I have to hurry and make him cum, then escape!
It's good right?
A blowjob from an active JK idol!
Hurry and cum!
All at once... my technique is really good, you know!
What's with this amount?
It's too much! I can't drink it all!
It came so much, but it's still hard?
Wait, no way, don’t!
Not that far, I...
No... an active idol's virginity is...
No, I have to run!
Like I'd give my virginity to...
I did it!
I've got to run and hide somewhere!
It hurts...
Hey, hey... wait up!
That’s enough already! I gave you
a blowjob from a highschool idol!
My virginity isn't cheap!
Ouch!
What's with you!? Don't just hit an idol's
face with something like that!
Not even my parents have hit me on the cheeks!
I said no!
I'm an idol! Everyone looks up to me!
Stop!
Don't lick my pussy, it's gross!
No!
It's coming...
My pussy...
Why won't you understand!?
No!
This pain... was supposed to be for someone I love!
Why is it taken by something so gross!?
You can understand?
It's just the tip at the moment, so I can still forgive...
Something gross... is inside my pussy!
It hurts!
Something random is sticking inside
my pussy! I'm being dirtied!
Even though I’m an idol...
Even though I have to be a virgin... because
everyone is believing in me!
It's in again...
So much dick is inside...
My pussy and my mouth are both sticky and wet...
They're so dirty from the stains!
No...it's coming...
A creampie is coming!
Are you trying to impregnate an idol!?
Don’t cum inside! I don't want gross stuff!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for betraying everyone... and servicing them!
I'm sorry for losing my virginity!
No way... gross stuff is flowing inside...
Tell me this isn't happening... this is just a prank, right?
It's overflowing... I'm being suffocated by a pig's cum...
They came... they took my virginity...
No way... this can't be happening...
No way!
What is with this line up!
I've never even had so many at an event!
So I’m still alive...
Ow...
They really did whatever they wanted...
Geez, it's all messed up...
Is the same as normal people's?
Why didn't they take me away...
To be honest, I was even more afraid
of that than of being raped.
These monsters, you see.
Seems like they are attracted to people
with special characteristics.
Your amber coloured, beautiful eye.
They'll fall for you for sure.
Damn, she fooled me.
No! Stop it!
Take out your dirty thing at once!
Stop!
I'm telling you to stop!
Listen already!
My Papa is a member of Parliament, you know!
All of you will be taken...
What is this...
Don't you understand?
What are you doing?
Just when I thought I could escape!
Wait, where are you putting it? Stop!
No! That's not somewhere to put it!
You are so vulgar an improper!
Embarrassing me like this... I'll make you pay for this later!
I'll kill you!
I'll definitely, definitely kill you!
No! Stop!
My pussy and my butt feel strange!
Don't rub your things inside! No!
It's sick!
What?
Yukino? Yukino!
Help me, please!
I'm sorry for earlier, I don't know what I was thinking!
I was wrong!
If you save me, I'll do anything for you!
Please! We're friends, right?
So you'll do anything?
As long as I'm able to do it, anything!
I'll treat to to dinner; I'll buy you something!
Please, help me. Quickly!
Right now!
I see... I get it. We are friends, after all.
Then...
Just continue being raped like that.
Why is it me!?
Papa, I’m getting pregnant!
Even though I wanted to be adored by Papa!
Yukino! Remember this! I'll kill you, too!
Wow, how scary.
Onee-chan...
Mr. Pig... I feel much better than that girl, right?
To save me, Onee-chan, she...
Onee-chan was already protecting me...
Billy: Hey, how come you have two? It's unfair to keep them alt to yourself.
No, you can't!
Alejandro: Shut up, Billy, I want to enjoy them in turns.
Billy: What do you mean "shut up"? Alejandro, I was just trying to be nice.
Alejandro: Well thanks for that. But I've tasted that one already, you know.
Billy: You're getting too full of yourself.
Alejandro: That's my line! You already took my favourite one!
Billy: You're pissing me off. You'd better kneel down and beg for forgiveness!
Alejandro: Well the rules say finders keepers.
You know, I think hospitality is important. Everyone should be equal.
Alejandro: Whatever.
Alejandro: Billy you've got a knife stuck on your head!
Billy: Who did that? It ruined my set and my handsomeness goes to waste!
Alejandro: More importantly the signal. It could be the elves.
Billy: Realty? If we're late we aren't allowed to make creampies, let's hurry.
What's happening?
Onee-chan, are you alright?
More importantly are you alright?
I wonder why the pigs left...
They could come back. Let's hurry and leave, Onee-chan.
You're right Let's go.
Dick is gross!
I just have to bear through this, right?
But I don't want to be taken away!
Yukino, help me! We're friends, right?
I just don't know... what friends are...
What is this place?
Geez, a drifting classroom now?
So with the earthquake, the fog is now gone?
Did they leave?
They seemed to be in a hurry.
It'll start rotting soon; I should look for
a place where the stinks won't reach.
what...
Really?