It's all thanks to you, Hatsune.
I'm almost there. I'll get that top position for your sake.
You might only be a part-timer, but you're part of our family.
Do your best, Sensei.
Thank you! Thank you!
I'm voting for you.
I'm your fan.
Please do your best.
This is my cellphone number.
He sure is having fun.
I'm counting on you.
Kashiwagi!
Sensei!
Waku-subs Credits: Naoya/Fomite http://waku.blog.com
You saved my life there, Hatsune.
No, I've been learning Aikido in order to protect myself as a precaution.
I see. But you shouldn't do something like this again.
Sensei...
What I fear most is losing you, Hatsune.
I understand, Sensei.
What's wrong, Sensei?
Are you all right, Sensei?
I'm sorry, I need to go to the rest room.
It's dangerous, let me accompany you.
Um, I...
It's still dangerous, you should rest for now.
Sensei, no! Please close the door! I'm in such an embarrassing state...
Don't look, Sensei.
Because you were in a suit, that's why I didn't realize someone so sexy was in front of me.
Sensei, the secretary is going to be back anytime.
It's fine, I told her to go have lunch. I even said I'm gonna eat with you.
Even so, at a place like this...
Let's do it here.
Please wait, Sensei.
Geez, you're too rough.
It's so sudden!
That place is...
It's huge, inside my pussy… grinding me.
This is amazing, it feels fantastic.
Sensei, your penis is huge and big. It's wrecking havoc inside my pussy.
Sensei, you're so rough today.
Come, Sensei. Please thoroughly enjoy my body.
Please be more forceful with my pussy.
It's incredible. It's so hot all the way to my tummy.
Sensei, please pour into me. Pour everything inside of me.
Please empty everything deep inside of me.
It's amazing, inside.
Sensei, Sensei! I'm...
Sensei!
Sensei... I'm cuming! I'm cuming!
Sensei.
What's wrong, Sensei?
Sensei, please wait. Why are you always so rough...
You only just came, yet you're already so hard.
No, don't be so violent.
Thankfully I'm still alive! I'm fucking Hatsune now!
It's amazing, your penis is so hot.
It's great, Sensei.
Hatsune.
Please cum. Sensei, give me all your semen.
I'm cuming, I'm cuming! Again, I'm cuming!
No way. If this carries on, I...
You came a lot... inside of me.
My bad, Hatsune.
It's fine, Sensei. Are you more relaxed now?
As long as I'm of any use to you.
I'll be glad to share a part of your stress.
I bought your favorite.
Oh no! Hatsune isn't here.
I thought she was waiting for me?
That should be the case, but she isn't here...
I'll take a look.
Just now, she was so....
It's so cosy. So this is where you work, Sensei.
So you're always working here, it's so cool, you're awesome.
You can't Sensei! Everyone is still around at this time.
It's all right, I already locked the door.
Sensei, don't go down there.
I really don't think it's a good idea. Someone may just enter.
But you're not objecting down there.
Sensei, no way... Don't tease me like that.
Your dick is penetrating the depths of my pussy.
You're coming in. Throbbing inside me.
My breasts are exposed. It's so embarrassing!
So this an office, yet we're doing lewd stuff like this.
It's so intense, I can't hold it anymore...
Sensei, your penis is hitting the sides of my uterus.
If it's so intense, and feels so good, I'm going to cum in no time.
It's awesome! Please cum, Sensei. Inside of me.
Sensei, I'm coming! I'm gonna cum! I'm such a whore.
There's so much of it, it's warm. Amazing...
Hatsune, I haven't had enough.
No way... Sensei, please wait.
It's gotten big again. You only just came, yet it's starting to become bigger.
Good. It's good! I feel good all over.
S-Sensei!
Who'd it be? Well, I locked the door anyway.
Are you in, Sensei?
Shit, she also has the key.
Excuse me, did something happen?
In a bid to healthy, I'm doing squads.
I see?
Did you say something?
What?
The start of this afternoon is the meeting.
He wanted you to grace the event.
I see. It's finally gonna start?
Yes, as we lost some backing. It's a crucial race to win from now on.
I see. I'm gonna need to count on you more from here on.
I've made up my mind. I'm willing to stake my life to support you, Sensei.
You've been different recently compared to before.
You're really reliable with confidence.
Thanks.
The you now, everyone will surely follow you to the end with ease.
I see.
Now's the only chance to rise once more.
I'm sure you can do it.
Ouch!
Sensei, you're really pumped up!
I'll drop by to pick you up later.
Must be nice, with so much pep talk.
What's wrong, Hatsune?
You still have the secretary without me around to support you.
Without your support, I won't have this much confidence.
You're special to me.
Sensei.
It's now come down to this, you've to help me.
Sorry, Sensei. For your sake, I...
I'm gonna climax to meet Jesus.
Sensei, your penis is throbbing so much inside me.
It's wiggling everywhere inside.
Sensei, please release all your semen inside.
No matter how many times, please just cum inside of me.
Sensei, I...
My insides are filled to the brim with your semen.
I'm sure you'll be fine, if it's you.
Well then, I'm setting off.
Good luck, Sensei! I'll await your return.
It might be for the job. But it's like an amulet to me, since you're the one who gave it to me.
There's no way she'd suddenly disappear like that.
Hello.
It must be a tough day. It all comes down on you whether she makes it back safely.
I understand.
Promise me you won't lay a hand on Kashiwagi-sensei if I become yours.
Of course. But to think that imbecile would have such a great woman like you.
But that's only until today.
Darn! I didn't think he'd set his sights on Hatsune. I'm careless!
That guy has plenty of influence. Did he also send that hoodlum to stab me back then?
You're getting rid of Sensei because you wanted me?
A fellow who doesn't know his rightful place should just die.
I'm just too soft.
Hatsune!
Sensei!
You bastard! Why are you here?
Someone, grab a hold of him!
Your men sold you off.
My fellow congressman is also reaching soon.
Why did you say!
You underestimate her just because she's a JK.
She part of my alliance.
I already had a countermeasure in place to track her location using GPS.
In the process, I had it record your conversation, too.
I hope you'll completely retire from this world.
This world is no better because of people like you.
You dare lecture me, you piece of shit!
She knows Aikido for self protection. Thats-
He's out cold...
I'm so sorry! I didn't control my strength and hurt an elderly.
S-Sensei.
A jerk like him, just tie him up.
But Sensei, now is...
Sensei, it's so sudden at a place like this!
You say that but you're already wet, Hatsune.
Please don't say things like that.
Sensei, your penis is so violent. My cunt is all warm.
Fantastica! It's form and structure.
Sensei, your penis is unmatched. My pussy is on cloud 9.
The fuck's this?
Amazing! It's so wet, I'm feeling weak all over.
Your dick is great!
What do you think! This is the strength, power and spirit of controlling the era!
Sensei, you're so rough. It's so hot!
Sensei, I'm in heaven! My waist can't take it anymore.
Feeling horny from being watched, Hatsune?
That's impossible. Because Sensei, yours is so amazing, I'm about to...
It's so good, I can't! I'm so slutty, I...
Coming! I'm gonna cum!
My womb is so filled.
Thanks for cuming inside, Sensei.
The fall of the world's Don. Constant reformation
Leader of a new era.
Um, Sensei.
I owe it to you, Hatsune, that I'm able to climb to the top of the country.
I didn't do anything... It's all because of your abilities.
No, it's really because of you.
That's not true.
Calling it a form of thanks is not really appropriate… But I should let you have a feel of this environment.
I'll pass.
Why?
You can't do something like that here!
You're my lucky star. That's why I'm fortunate enough to be the position I'm in now.
Stop saying that so many times. I'll be embarrassed.
Geez, Sensei. You're so prim and proper in front of others.
I won't in front of you. Besides, stop calling me Sensei.
I'm still not used to it... Um, Yuutaro-san.
You should get used to it. You're the first lady, afterall.
Enemies are plenty too. But with you around, there's nothing I can't solve.
I already said no, Yuutaro-san!
You're so aggressive as always.
It's nice to be like this once in a while.
I'll only allow once in a while.
Well, you'd hit me if I'm to violent.
Seriously, Sensei...
Incredbile, it's throbbing.
Delicious.
I'm having fun doing such a thing at a place like this.
Your dick is radiating heat.
Please be more rough with me.
Sensei.
It's coming in, Sensei's...
Your penis is coming inside of me.
Sensei... Over there, you can't... It's too sensitive.
Your dick is reaching deep inside, Sensei.
Your penis is awesome, it's stuffing my pussy.
I'm such a whore.
These are slutty, too.
My breasts, if you knead it so hard...
Anyway, your fingers feels too good. I can't...
It's so intense, my tits feel great as well. I can't hold it anymore, it's too good.
My pussy is tightening without me knowing.
It's fantastic, Sensei!
It's so intense, if you're so rough...
Yuutaro-san, please cum. I want your semen to fill every inch of my womb.
I'm coming! I'm coming!
So stuffy.
Your penis is vibrating inside me.
The feeling was exceptional. You've grown quite a bit from before.
It's all because we've been fucking too much.
Yuutaro-san! You're even bigger than before.
Hatsune!
Yuutaro-san, wait! This is...
Fantastic! Amazing! Your dick is so deep inside me.
Do me more, Yuutaro-san!
It's great. My pussy is starting to feel strange.
Yuutaro-san, you're big and thick. Awesome.
Your penis is the best.
Yuutaro-san, I like you. I adore you! I love you!
Hatsune!
Yuutaro-san, I'm cuming! I'm about to climax. I'm cuming!
Your hot semen is transferring deep into me.
Yuutaro-san, you're the best.
You've to have more self-respect, Congressman.
I'll always be by your side forever. I'll stick onto you even if you don't want it.