It's not connecting..
It's such a rare chance to be able to eat with the upperclassmen...
Oh, Yukino, what's wrong?
Nothing, really.
Really? Weren't you eavesdropping?
Come on, be honest, aren't we friends?
Who is?
Ah yeah, I overheard you, so?
Oh my, you did?
Such a bad hobby.
You know...
Well that makes it easy.
Yukino, lend me your phone.
Huh?
What is it?
If you're worried about your minutes, I'll pay you back,
Such a petty girl.
No, I don't have a phone.
Besides, isn't there a pay phone on the first floor?
Why don't you use that one?
Oh yeah...
I can't believe you don't have a phone in this day and age.
Well, you probably won't be able to make many friends with those small boob, guess it can't be helped.
Huh?
What do boobs have to do with anything?
Anyways, hurry up and go!
right, right, thanks Yukino.
You're welcome.
Um, no..
I'm in the "go home right after school" club.
Even if you say that, I don't really understand.
And I have to go to my friends place, so...
It's so foggy...
W-who are you?
I-I'm called Mao.
You shouldn't be flaunting that around..
It stinks.
No!
It hurts.
What is it...
Why is his penis in my mouth?
It feels so gross!
It's so bitter...
It hurts!
So cruel!
No...
Please stop...
My insides are being stirred around...
It hurts...
Is this really hapenning?
No... No!
What's that?
What is that?
It hurts!
Help me...
What is this thing? It's like a manga.
Damn it
Amazing!
Many dicks!
It feels so good!
This is so amazing!
I feel so good, front and back.
It's painful, but it feels good!
What's wrong with me?
The dicks are hurting me, but it feels so good!
The dicks feel that good..
There's so much..
I'm wallowing in sperm!
It feels good to be drowning in cum.
Damn, that fog...
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan, get a hold of yourself!
Hey, Onee-chan...
Hey.
H Ni Juu
hentai-ni-juu.blogspot.com
JK
Erobeat Translations
and the
Orc Corps
~The Assault on Seijo Academy by Evil Demon Pigs~
The Cool Odd-Eyed Yukino ~ The Rape of Betrayal and the Large Pig Dicks ♥
Um.. I'm Sae Miura , I'm a freshman,
and that's my Onee-chan, Kotoko.
Thanks for saving us.
I'm Yukino.
I haven't saved you yet.
For now, we've only managed to hide from them.
Still, I couldn't do anything myself.
My sister protected me.
Infirmary
Sae, why did you leave PE class?
I'm sorry, Onee-chan.
I was so shocked when they told me you fainted...
You're different from the other kids, you know.
But, I'm tired of being treated different.
I want to be like everyone else.
And it's fine to faint and be a burden to everyone?
Don't you think that's being a bit selfish?
I'm sorry, I'll go get your bag.
Let's go home together when you feel better.
What's wrong?
Shh, Be quiet.
There's some weird things in the hallway.
Onee-chan?
Hide, and be quiet!
What about Onee-chan?
I'll be fine, but you can't come out, no matter what happens.
No matter what happens.
Understand?
Okay. I understand.
What is that? No...
Don't come, don't come, don't come...
This way!
If only I kept quiet, Onee-chan...
Please stay like this, please!
This way!
Where are you looking Mr. Pig?
I'm not going to be caught by an oaf like you!
Come on, this way!
Wh-What?
I'm sorry, I wasn't looking and bumped into you...
No!
What is this? It went inside me.
It hurts, this dick...
This dick is filling up my insides!
No way! I'm being violated, but why..
Why...?
What is this?
I'm being messed up!
No... No!
Something is coming inside!
No, don't come out!
It's flowing from my insides...
What's he going to do?
It hurts!
It stinks!
Take it out, please!
No, I don't want this!
Something like this.. I can't..
Why is his penis in my...
Why?
Onee-chan...
Infirmary
Cock! Cock feels so good!
My pussy is being filled by cock!
Please give lots of cock to my pussy!
Mess me all up!
Violate me!
This is... Onee-chan?
Yes!
Mess me up deep inside with semen..
My pussy... Make me pregnant!
No...
Yes!
When cock stir around, my pussy is so happy!
Onee-chan, Onee-chan...
Where are you?
No!
Onee-chan, Onee-chan, get a hold of yourself!
Hey, Onee-chan... Onee-chan!
It may seem like a manga or fiction, but...
This is reality.
But...
Well, if we can hide until that fog is over...
Let's leave here after she wakes up.
They say people can say anything when they're about to die,
guess it's not a joke, huh.
I'm the third year Natsume Reika!
How do you do!
Open up!
Is anyone there?
We should probably open the door... if there is then answer me!
Jeez, hurry and open up!
Hey, come on.
Hey, are you listening?
I heard you.
Oh, it was you Yukino.
So what if it's me?
Did I disappoint you?
Of course not,
I'm just happy to see my friend safe and sound.
I have no intention of being your friend.
How heartless.
Are you Yukino's friends?
There's no way,
with those sad boobs.
Huh? Boobs have nothing to do with this.
You're so annoying.
I guess, no matter how small your boobs are, it's still a part of you.
Why are you like this?
That's right, Yukino and I are complete opposites.
We're not alike at all, she doesn't hold back at all.
I thought, "How rude can she be?"
I only thought of her as a troublesome classmate,
and never as a real person.
I didn't know what to do with a girl who had such small boobs.
Boobs have nothing to do this with, right?
Can we change the topic?
Come on, this is the way I am.
Even though you may think I'm rude,
I'm actually having fun.
It's fun?
Making fun of my boobs...
Isn't that kind of rude?
Oh, now that you mention it...
Anyways, I want to be friends with you, Yukino.
I don't understand what it means to be friends.
How does one make friends?
Friends are basically people you have fun and hang out with.
Isn't that a friend?
Can someone..
have fun with someone like me?
What are you scared of?
My, that's pretty.
How's it pretty?
I just have different coloured eyes, and people look at me strangely.
They make fun of me.
I hate it.
Let's be friends.
It's how you associate your name with things.
If I say it's pretty then it'll be loved by everyone.
How very Reika-like.
What does that mean?
Even though I'm complementing you.
Ah, um, sorry.
They're pretty, Yukino.
Thanks.
No way, they already have found us?
How?
They have good noses.
Their pig faces aren't just for show.
It'll be okay,
It's because you're here
For that reason, I'm okay.
Leave this to me,
and stay here Yukino.
I'll figure something out.
What are you.. Reika! Wait!
I told you, didn't I?
Just trust me, Yukino.
Okay.
EH? Reika?
If you open that...
Reika!
Sorry, Yukino!
But there's no way I'll let myself be raped by these creatures.
Reika, why?
Understand your position,
Who do you think I am?
Being friends with you?
You're dreaming if you think I'll ever be friends with people who've crossed me!
Reika...
You know, these monsters have a special pheromone.
It's specially targeted at humans.
Yukino has something even more beautiful, right?
Those different coloured, beautiful eyes...
Those creatures will happily take you!
Now that I think about it, I've always hated her.
How'd I fall for that?
I...
Be gentle.
so suddenly!
It hurts!
No! It hurts!
Stop! Don't put it in! Take it out!
It stopped.
What? Don't look, don't look!
It hurts!
Don't move!
I said it hurts!
Hurry up and take it out!
No! Don't look!
You're just a monster!
You're just some lowly creature!
It's so painful!
You've had enough, haven't you?
Hurry up and take it out!
You stupid idiot, Don't pinch!
That's enough!