www.SubDESU-H.net
It's not going through.
And it's even such a rare opportunity to have a lunch meeting with visiting students.
Yukino, what's wrong?
It's nothing.
Really.
Weren't you eavesdropping earlier?
Tell me the truth already.
We're friends, right?
And just how are we friends?
Okay I admit it, I was listening earlier.
And what about it?
So you were eavesdropping.
You've got some bad manners there.
Hey now...
Then there's no need to for further explanation, right Yukino?
Can I borrow your phone?
What?
If you're bothered about call costs, I'll be covering them.
What a cheapskate.
Well, I don't have a phone.
Besides, there's a public phone on the first floor.
Why don't you use that?
That's also another option I guess.
Though I never would have thought you didn't own a phone.
Well, it probably can't be helped since you can't make friends with those small breast of yours.
Huh? Breasts don't have anything to do with that.
Just go already.
Okay, okay.
Thanks a lot, Yukino.
You're welcome.
Eh, no I go straight home after class.
So even if you ask me that I wouldn't know anything about it.
And I really need to go to my friend's place now.
So...
The fog sure is heavy.
W-Who are you?
I'm Mao.
You can't just expose that.
It stinks.
No...
It hurts...
Why is he forcing his cock into my mouth?
It feels gross.
And it tastes bitter.
It hurts...
Ouch!
It hurts...!
Please... stop!
My insides are being stirred up.
It hurts...
Is this even real?
What is that?
What in the world was that?
Ouch...
Save me...
What is this? Some kind of scene from a manga?
Damn.
Wow!
This cock feels really good.
This is amazing.
These cocks are great.
The pain feels good.
Huh? What's happening to me?
Their cocks hurt,
but it feels good.
So cocks can feel this good.
Semen is overflowing inside me.
I'm going to drown in semen.
It feels good when it leaks out too...
Damn that fog.
Onee-chan!
Hang in there!
Please!
Onee-chan!
Excuse me.
W
Original Animation
and the Orc Army
~The orc corrupted holy school~
The cool girl with strange eyes Yukino ~ Rape, Betrayal and Swine stomps n' cocks
Umm... I'm Miura Sae.
I'm a first year.
And that is my sister, Kotoko.
Thank you for saving us.
I'm Yukino.
We're not safe just yet.
I just found a temporary place for us to hide.
Even so, I won't be able to do anything alone.
I've always been protected by Onee-chan.
Sae, why did you leave the gym?
I'm sorry Onee-chan.
I was shocked when I heard that you collapsed.
You're not the same as the others, you know?
But I'm sick of being treated so differently.
I want to do the things that everyone else does.
At the cost of causing trouble for everyone in case you fall ill?
Isn't that called selfishness?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to get my bag.
We'll go home together once you feel better.
What's wrong?
Shh. Be quiet.
There's something strange in the hallway.
Onee-chan?
Hide here and stay quiet.
What are you going to do?
I'll be fine.
Just don't leave this spot no matter what.
Regardless of what happens.
Understood?
Okay.
What is that?!
Oh no.
Please don't come.
Over here!
If only I'd kept completely quiet back then, Onee-chan wouldn't have...
I hope it just leaves immediately.
Please...
Over here!
Where are you looking at you pig?
I'm not going to be captured by some dumb pig.
Come and get me!
What is that?
I'm sorry, I wasn't looking ahead properly...
No.
No!
What is this?
It's entering inside me.
It hurts...
This is a cock...
My insides are being filled up by this cock.
No way...
I'm being violated like this, and yet...
What's this?
My insides feel tingly.
No... no...
Something's flowing into me.
Please, don't cum in me.
It's going to flow through me.
What does it want to do?
It hurts...
This cock... stinks...
Let me go.
Please, let me go.
It really stinks...
Oh no...!
Why does this cock have to violate me?
Why?!
www.SubDESU-H.net
Onee-chan?
This cock...
This cock is great!
My pussy... It's completely filled by your cock.
Please thrust your cock into me more!
Make love to me more!
Violate me more!
This is...
Onee-chan...?
Yes!
Let your semen overflow inside of me!
Make my pussy burst!
This can't be...
Yes...
Whenever it rubs inside me, my pussy feels happy.
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan?
Onee-chan, where are you?
Oh no!
Onee-chan! Onee-chan!
Hang in there!
Please, Onee-chan!
Onee-chan!
It may look like some scene from a novel or manga.
But this is reality.
Although...
If we could just escape as the fog clears...
As soon as she wakes up we'll leave...
I can usually overcome any situation using only words...
But this is just really over the top!
I'm Natsume Reika, a third year student!
I'm not one of them!
Open up!
Someone's here, right?
Maybe we should open it for her.
Geez!
Open up already!
Hey!
Can anyone hear me?
I can hear you.
Oh, so it's you Yukino.
So what if it's me?
Something wrong with that?
That's not it.
I'm just glad that my friend is safe.
I don't intend to act as your friend.
What a killjoy.
Are they your friends?
Of course not.
Not with those pitiful breasts of yours.
What did you say?
My breasts aren't the least bit related to this!
Just shut up!
Well you're right.
Those small breasts are still being held by a living person.
What's with that?
That's right.
Yukino is cold towards me.
Doesn't try to get along.
And always lets her mouth run.
I thought that she was quite a rude girl.
She treats me as a troublesome classmate.
Just simply as one of the normal people around her.
I didn't know how to approach that small breasted girl before.
That isn't related to this at all.
And keep off the topic of my breasts already.
Well you see, I can only talk like this.
Even if I do think of it as rude, it has become quite fun to me.
Fun to you?
The rude thing here is the way you always tease me about the size of my breasts.
Oh, I see that.
So in other words, Yukino,
I want to be your friend.
I don't really understand what it means to be a friend.
What should be done to be considered as one?
A friend is someone with whom you can share fun moments with.
Isn't it that simple?
Will I be fun to be with?
What are you afraid of?
My, how beautiful.
Absolutely not!
People see me differently just because its color is different.
They laugh at me.
I hate it...
Can we be friends?
Anyone that is close to me is respected.
So anything that I consider cute should indeed be adored by all.
That's just like you.
What?
I'm trying to compliment a friend here.
Y-Yeah, sorry.
It's beautiful, Yukino.
Thank you.
No way.
They found us already?
How?
They have a good sense of smell.
Seems they don't just look like pigs.
It's okay.
You're here with me.
That's why I'm alright.
Leave it to me.
Just stay here.
I'll do something about it.
Hey, Reika!
Wait!
I already told you, didn't I?
That we're saved.
Believe in me Yukino.
I understand.
Huh?
What?
Reika?
If you open that...
Reika!
I'm so sorry, Yukino.
I really can't stand the idea of being raped by these beasts.
Reika...
Why...?
Why?
Learn to know your place here.
Who do you think I am?
To be friends with someone like you?
Someone who always treated me so rudely?
Who are you kidding?
Reika...!
These creatures you see,
seem to be more interested in people with special or peculiar characteristics.
My voluptuous breasts may be special.
But you have something even prettier, don't you?
It's none other than that wonderful amber-colored eye.
You're now that monster's captive.
I forgot, I actually hated her.
What was I getting happy for?
Be gentle with me.
That's too abrupt!
Ouch!
I said it hurts!
Let me go!
Stop this!
Don't you dare insert that in me!
Pull it out!
It stopped.
What?
Stop staring at me!
I said stop staring!
It's painful.
Stop moving.
I said it's painful...!
Take it out already!
Damn, stop looking at me!
You're just a beast!
A monster with no intellect!
It hurts.
That's enough already, isn't it?
So pull it out now!
You, stupid thing!
Stop holding it.
Quit fooling around with me!
www.SubDESU-H.net