I'm cumming.
I'm really cumming.
I feel it in my clit and pussy!
It's all tingly...!
Please, fill me, fill my mouth with it.
Violate my mouth pussy with it.
Do you really want this?
Does it taste good?
You are mine.
Your pussy.
Your ass.
Your mouth.
Every single part of you!
Even your assets,
your sisters,
and this entire island are mine!
The Female Household III
Secret ~ Carnal Fluids
Can't you even get this right, idiot?
Please forgive me, Sir Itami.
I'll not be back till the end of the week.
You'll have to watch over them.
Hashizume-san.
I'm sorry if Itami-san was rude earlier.
Please don't be, Mistress Towa.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Oh, Mistress Saeko seems to be able to eat breakfast properly now.
W-Well, yes, she indeed is.
And most of all...
It's happening again...
Hashizume-san, why don't you try this?
It's a new medicine developed by our pharmaceutical department.
Crush it in your mouth.
Huh? My headache is gone.
It's still in development, so I hasn't sure
if I could really give it to you or not.
Here, in case it breaks out again.
Thank you very much, Mistress Towa.
What are you snickering for, Onii-chan?
Kirara-sama, Anri-sama.
Onii-chan, you're thinking about weird
things while looking at her, right?
You beast!
That hurts.
It's nothing like that.
Hashizume-san, I can tell what your current
state of mind is just by looking at you.
It seems your brain's workings are simpler than it seems.
Anri-sama, you have a tendency of saying such hurtful words.
Look who's making a fuss here.
Anri, Kirara, I suggest you refrain from
exchanging words with this man.
Shie-neesan, Mariko-san.
Shie...
I don't really know how to tell Itami, you know.
Jeez, I feel like my day is already ruined
seeing your face early in the morning.
Stop that, Shie, you're being rude.
Rude?
You're one to talk, Towa-neesama, after
bringing Itami to our household.
That's not true.
He was already one of the candidates as
the successor to our father's company.
So what?
He already left the company once,
then he just nonchalantly comes back, taking everything with him.
What a Joke.
Good grief.
Our mother must have gone crazy.
She locked herself up in her room, and
only interacts with Towa-neesama.
Oh, oh yeah, Onii-chan!
You're going to help me out with my homework this time!
Eh? Homework, you say?
What's with that totally lazy tone?
You promised me, right?!
You're going to be the model for my rough sketch!
Um, well, I'm... actually busy with a lot of things today, so...
Mother...
Oh no, Anri-neechan's consciousness is fading again!
Mariko.
I'll prepare the room right away.
She always loses her consciousness whenever
she tries to remember the past.
Poor thing.
Anri-sama and Kirara-sama's mother was a model,
and was also the late Kiichiro-sama's former...
That's right.
His lover.
When Anri was still a child, someone had...
The shock from that incident affected her memories.
It's gone!
No good, I can't find it.
If anyone in this house were to see that...
I have to hurry.
Yes?
Onii-chan.
Hey, when are you really going to help me with my homework?
Onii-chan, are you okay?
You're not responding.
Onii-chan, please clean this shirt too.
Onii-chan, you just saw my breasts, right?
Can't be helped, in this case...
I'll just have to start the game!
My, I think this is fate!
Your timing is really perfect, Kirara-sama.
What?
What's wrong with you, Onii-chan?
Onii-chan, what's the meaning of this?
This? You already know what this is.
What a great view.
Makes me really excited.
This is...
No, you can't!
You can't do this!
What are you saying, my lady?
You're the one who invited me, Miss.
No way, I didn't want you to do this!
What's wrong with you, Onii-chan?
You're acting weird today.
This is the real Onii-chan.
I'm more of a beast than you ever imagined.
No!
Please, just stay put like the lady you are.
If you don't...
Ouch, it hurts!
Onii-chan, let me go!
Please, stop this.
Oh, you're quite sensitive.
Then, how about here?
No, don't, not there!
No...!
No, I'm scared...
Maybe you really want this after all?
This thing I mean.
I don't want it!
I don't want that thing!
Don't be shy now.
Here.
T-This is terrible.
Stop, not a single person has ever seen me like this!
So, this is your virgin pussy.
Now I'm really looking forward to this.
No, please don't!
Save me, Anri-neesan!
Just give it up already.
Now then, I'll be taking this.
Well?
How does it feel to be toyed with by a beast?
This wrapping sensation indeed proves that you're a virgin.
I'm cumming!
Hashizume-san, are you there?
Have you seen Kirara?
I thought I heard voices coming from here.
That's strange.
Is he not here?
There it is again.
Mariko, more.
Fondle me more.
Shie-sama really wants it strong, eh?
Mariko, oh yes.
My Mariko...
I don't need men if I have you!
Seems I've stumbled upon something really interesting.
Hashizume!
What were you doing there?
Get out at once!
Acting high and mighty as always,
even though you're just a maid.
What are you doing?
You're in the way.
I smell something lewd coming from this direction, Lady Shie.
You can still leave now, if you want me to forget about all of this.
My, how kind of you.
But, I can't just forget this.
Oh, seems the smell really is coming from here.
Your lewd, slutty smell...
What are you doing, you pervert!
Don't touch me with your soiled hands!
Stop this already!
It's not going to end well for you if you keep this up.
Big words, but your body isn't even resisting.
You really wanted to be violated, right?
A-Are you out of your mind?
Unlike you, I was raised properly.
I don't need to put out.
Then, it seems you are about to regret how they raised you.
Miss Shie, you love being fondled like this, right?
W-Who are you kidding?
It doesn't feel a single bit pleasurable with you!
Okay then, then I'll just have to help
myself to these wonderful boobs.
Miss Shie, are you getting horny already?
T-That's not true...
How about this then?
Don't pull them!
How do you like this?
Hey, what are you doing with my breasts!
Their shape feels very nice.
Can you suck it for me please?
Who would...
Come on, don't say that.
Stop.
It's not good to be picky about what you suck.
I'm cumming!
W-What is this stinky thing?
T-This humiliation, I'll kill you if I have the chance.
Big words again, and the humiliation is just about to start.
Your pussy's sensitivity is good.
Don't touch it with your dirty fingers!
Okay, time to see your secret spot.
For me, to be in a position like this...
I'll never forgive you!
Do you really hate it?
Your pussy's already dripping wet, you know.
No, that's just a mere sexual response.
It's just getting wet because of your stimulation.
Oh, how about this?
No...!
That spot is...
It doesn't feel good at all...
You're just a...
It feels hot.
Oh no...
No, don't, any more and I'll...!
W-What? What's wrong?
What are you trying to do?
If you keep on licking it like that...
I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum...
I'm about to cum...!
Eh? You stopped?
What, again?
No more please.
I can't take it anymore.
Shall I stop again then, Miss Shie?
No, keep it up, keep it up...!
I'm cumming!
Well? How's the sensation of a dirty man's tongue, Miss Shie?
Don't get too cocky.
Anyone will cum if their clitoris is stimulated so much.
So even dogs can do it.
That's harsh.
So I'm just a dog now?
Then, why don't we make a bet?
A bet?
I'll position myself below, and just press
the tip of my cock to your vagina.
If you don't cum, then I lose.
If you cum, then I win.
If you win, then I'll leave this household right this instant.
So, I'll just let both touch each other, and not put it in, right?
I won't move an inch.
Well?
Okay then.
I accept your challenge.
Why don't you stop squatting like that?
If I do that, your trashy dick will enter me.
Oh yeah, are you still a virgin?
Of course.
I hate men.
I don't think I can do this.
N-No...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
But your legs are shaking.
Shut up.
Oh no...!
It's inside.
Your dirty dick is inside me!
What's wrong, Miss Shie?
I was supposed to pull it out.
It's pushing in.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
Could I just have hit your pussy's sweet spot?
No! And don't say sweet spot...
Hey wait, why are you pushing your dick?
Because you're also moving yourself.
It just can't help but react.
It's going in, his dick is really inside.
Why?
I can't resist the sensation.
Your dick feels good.
Please stop... oh, but it feels good...
Oh yes...!
I knew you'd feel like this, Miss Shie.
It's my first time being fucked, and yet...
I already feel all tingly...
Oh no, I'm going to cum...
I'm cumming!
You just lost the bet, Miss Shie.
What are you saying?
I didn't lose.
I didn't cum, you know.
You just said you were cumming, didn't you?
You're... just hearing things...
In that case, I'll just have to...
Hey, you said you weren't going to move!
It's going deeper inside.
Shall I stop?
I'll kill you if you stop!
Push it all the way in.
More...!
More... push it in more...
This soiled and dirty dick just took my virginity away.
It feels so good!
Fuck me more, soil me more!
I'm cumming.
Okay then, let it all out inside and impregnate me!
Oh yes... oh yes...
Your dick feels great.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Oh no, it's pouring all inside.
I'm peeing while I cum!
I'm cumming...
Your dick...
Dick...
Oh yes...
Now then,
next one is...
Bad luck for you, Mariko-san.
I don't really have anything against you,
but I'm all worked up right now.
Fucking one just isn't enough.
Stop!
You mustn't do this!
Stop ordering me.
Here now.
Stop.
I'm the one in charge here.
Stop...
Nope.
Don't, anything but that!
My Dad, who was his employee,
commited suicide after being accused of mismanagement.
Now, my mother too is...
He completely wrecked my family
I'll never forgive him.
This is a battle that puts all of Karasawa's assets on the line.
I cannot lose.
I shall definitely...
Hashizume-san.
Miss Anri?
I can't find Kirara anywhere.
I searched the entire island already.
All, except one place.
Your room.
Hashizume-san, you know where Kirara is... am I mistaken?