Queen and Slave
So how's that? You want more?
Yes...
What was that? lf you want more,
then tell me, or l won't do it anymore!
l want it! Please, hurt me more.
Why didn't you say that in the first place?
Forgive me!
You pig!
As you all can see,
I'm doing well as a dominatrix.
This is my calling. Nothing gives me
more pleasure than torturing men.
That's because those lowlife scum
known as men are my enemies....
ls your girl alright?
She'll probably play by herself at the park.
Now shut up, you're ruining the fun.
Look how wet your cunt is...
Yeah! Oh yeah!
Yeah, that's it!
lt feels good! Fuck me! Fuck me!
l feel so hot!
lt feels...so good! So good!
Your cock is all the way up there...
lt feels so good!
Yes! Oh yes!
More! More! Fuck me more! Please!
Oh yeah! Fuck me more!
Yes! lt feels so good!
l can't...l'm gonna cum...
Yes...
l'm gonna cum!
Go ahead! Cum!
Suck it!
That was great...
lt's getting dark.
Shouldn't you go pick up your daughter?
Nah. She'll be back
when we finish round two.
Nodera Central Hospital
How are you feeling?
Fine, thank you.
Let's shift your position a little.
lt's good that the injury wasn't serious.
Since you're a college student,
you don't need to worry about attendance,
plus you can focus on studying more,
so it actually might help.
Yeah...
Okay then, if you need anything,
please use the Nurse Call.
Terada....
Terada...Terada...ah-hah!
Terada, Yoshimi
Time Card
Yoshimi Terada.
Yoshimi....
Cram School
So you see this problem....
Yoshimi....
l love you, Hiroyuki.
So do l.
You're already wet...you horny slut.
Hiroyuki, no.
Are you really against it?
That feels real good.
The extra years help.
Don't talk about my age.
Sorry.
Your dick...it's so good.
lt big and hard...and delicious.
l'm gonna cum!
Hold it in.
lf you're going to cum, do it inside me.
OK...
Yes! Oh yes! Yes! Yes!
That feels good! Hiroyuki, more!
Yeah!
l can't...! l'm cumming!
Let's cum together!
l'm cumming! l'm cumming!
So much cum.
Nodera Central Hospital
Employees Only
What the hell am I doing?
Should I talk to her?
I would've done that by now if I could.
Good morning!
Project SUN...?
Well, duh. Of course she'd have
a boyfriend with those looks.
Let's see who he is.
-What are you looking at?
-Nothing.
What's your relationship with that girl?
This, you see? You can have that...
SM Service Anywhere
Project Sun
She's with an SM club...?
Yes.
-Hello.
-Hi.
First-timer? You know our rules?
No.
You pay in advance. The price is
the same as you heard on the phone.
Okay.
Thank you.
Two hours go by before you know it,
so hurry up and get ready.
What's wrong? Take it off.
Well....
Do you remember me?
You're not a first-timer?
No, from the hospital.
l'm Hiroyuki Ando. l fell down the stairs
and broke my leg. Do you remember me?
l wanted to talk to you all this time...
...but l couldn't do it in public,
so, well...you see, like this...
You shouldn't come here.
l'm not the type of girl that
a sweet guy like you should hang out with.
No, it's okay. l'll pay what's due.
But l'm not here for any SM shit.
l'm here to spend time with you,
Hiromi Tereda!
Don't call me by that name!
Right now l'm Yumi. l'm not a nurse.
l'm not here to chatter with men!
l'm here to hurt men.
So what's it gonna be? You in or out?
No, l'm....
Listen, nurses are supposed
to be nice to their patients.
Don't think l was being
especially nice to you!
You a virgin?
Then you should go to
a normal prostitute or something.
Just tell them and they'll teach you gently.
That's not what l....
What does a man want in a girl!?
What other thing is there besides sex!?
No matter which way you put it,
that's what it is in the end.
Take this and go home.
l'll tell the office that
the customer never showed up.
Can we meet again later...?
Please, Yumi!
Oh, l'm sorry. Don't get the wrong idea.
l have absolutely no intention
of seeing you again.
Quite frankly, you're disrupting my work.
lt's annoying, so don't do it again.
What's wrong?
Dammit, dammit!
Make fun of me will you...!
She was laughing at me! l'll get her....
l won't stop till
she apologizes to me in tears!
She's pretty hot.
Hey, you sure about this?
Not only do we get to fuck this hottie,
but we also get paid for it?
Yeah.
What an easy job!
Alright, Your Highness!
Those are some sexy black panties.
Please....
-Stop it or l'll scream!
-Go ahead, be my guest.
We're not the ones who'll be butt-naked
when someone comes running by.
Check this out! Real SM shit!
Why do l have to go through with this?
Shut up, Your Highness!
That mouth of yours gets this.
That feels good.
Please don't bite me, okay?
That feels good. This is great!
Oh shit!
l always wanted a chick
to swallow my cum.
Can you do that, Your Highness?
Looks like it was too tasty
for her to waste.
Of course, it's my cum.
Today's cum was
especially rich and creamy.
Alright...l think l'll take her pussy.
lt looks good.
Nice and tight. She's a sadist,
and yet she's all wet getting raped.
How's that? Not bad, eh?
Look at that, her pussy's all wet.
Maybe she fits being
a slave rather than a queen.
That can't be!
I love inflicting pain on men.
I'm a sadist, not a masochist!
Holy shit...
l've never seen anything like this.
Let's see how it is inside.
This is some shit.
Not only is it all wet inside,
it clings right on you!
Stop fingering me!
l can't think straight anymore!
Who could stop, with a pussy like this?
At this rate you think
that we could fit a fist in?
l don't wanna go that far.
What if she starts bleeding?
That turns me off.
Hey, l'm starting to get hard.
All l wanna do is torture her.
Can l use this?
Do whatever you want.
How's that! How does that feel?
lt feels good! Hurt me more!
You dirty whore!
More, more!
That's a strange queen.
She's what they call a ''switch hitter.''
Maybe I really wanted someone
to love me in this fashion.
She say something?
Master...l will accept all of
your desires with this body.
This pain...please comfort this pain.
So that means it's okay
to cum inside, right?
Then l'm first!
You just went a minute ago! l'm first!
lt's so big! lt feels good!
This is the shit!
Fuck me, fuck me more. Oh, yeah.
This time, let me see how it is in here.
I've never felt so filled with ecstasy!
It's like every hole in my body
is overtlowing with cum!
Punish me more, rape me more!
More, more...
Why don't you join in?
lt'd be a waste if you didn't.
l'm almost done here!
This spot's gonna be open in a second.
You can pick wherever you want.
l'm cumming! l'm cumming!
Punish me...Punish me more.
The Queen's begging for more. Go ahead.
Dammit!
Oh yeah!
Oh god! lt's all the way in there! Fuck me more!
You were great.
How's that? Give up!
Cry out, ''Please forgive me!''
Please, forgive me!
Hiroyuki!
You're going home?
A lot of things happened.
l don't have the time to study.
What's the point of taking tests
l know l'm gonna fail?
Hey, wait.
Thanks to you
l was able to learn my true self.
l appreciate it. So...
Don't you give up on your dream so easily.
You should think it over.
Please, for me?
-Well....
-What?
Fin