I'm the advisor of the beach volleyball club,
and have been in a relationship with
two of my students for a month.
Kiryuu Saori,
and her younger sister, Kiryuu Sawa.
Now that they're a big part of my normal life,
my mind is starting to become filled with doubts and worries.
And what were they talking about earlier?!
They looked so cheerful.
Maybe they have someone they like among those boys?!
No, that can't be!
I really want to know!
Okay, let's do it one more time!
Saori, come with me to the gym storage room.
Huh?
Beach Volleyball Club Chapter
H-How rare,
for you to invite me to do it during club practice.
W-Well, that's how it goes.
Don't you like it?
Of course I do.
It makes me feel very nervous, though.
It's not that I don't like it.
We're probably becoming more compatible with each other.
Hey, I just happened to notice earlier...
Yes?
You were talking with some boys over
by the courtyard earlier, right?
You seem to be getting along with them pretty well lately.
Sensei, are you getting jealous?
I-Idiot, don't get the wrong idea!
I-I was just worried you were talking about
our relationship with other people.
I didn't!
I only told the other club members!
So you did tell!
Umm... sensei.
We've finished warming up.
Oh, it's alright.
I already heard about your relationship from her.
See? I already told them.
Oh...
Then you don't mind being exposed like this, eh?
I'm going to put on a show then.
Just wait, sensei, no...
Ishida, we'll be finished soon,
so just wait there.
No way, being seen having sex like this...
This is embarrassing.
Wow, they're really doing it in front of me.
That big thing can really fit inside.
Saori, your pussy is trying to suck me in.
Are you getting aroused?
That's not true.
I'm not getting aroused!
That's not just nervousness, you might actually be an exhibitionist!
No, don't say that!
Oh no, when I think we're being watched
my body starts to get all tingly.
My pussy is getting really wet.
That's good.
You're being more honest about it now.
Sensei, it feels good.
I can really feel your dick.
Why is she just yelling out those really embarrassing words?
Oh no, I'm starting to feel weird now because of their show.
Now, let's get back to our earlier conversation.
What were you talking about with those boys earlier?
Th-That's... it's a secret!
I can't say it.
Then I'll make you cum right in front of her.
Se-Sensei, no, no...!
If you do it that intensely I'll cum!
I'll really cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
No way, he came inside?
And she also came from that?
It's pouring in...
Somebody just watched me cum as you came inside.
Oh crap, I never actually did find out what happened earlier.
So, I'm now the one being called out, huh?
I really wonder...
You two are hiding something from me, right?
Is it something you two can't say to me?
Alright then, sensei.
If you can make me cum first, I'll tell you.
Challenge accepted!
You're already very wet here.
This is supposed to be a challenge, but you
actually can't hold back anymore, right?
Maybe you're about to cum already?
Look who's talking, your dick is already getting bigger and hotter.
You're also getting aroused while playing with my pussy!
You... when did you...?!
Damn, I won't lose!
No, not there!
Don't suck on my clit!
Her blowjob is getting better.
Is she practicing with other people?
My clit is getting a hard on, and it feels all tingly!
Sensei already knows all my sensitive spots.
Oh no, I'm going to cum if this continues.
Wh-What should I do?
I've been practicing with a vibrator,
but I can't hold back any longer.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Damn.
Even if it's just by a second, it's still my win, sensei.
Damn, I really can't stop thinking about it.
I never imagined those two would make
me feel this way at such an age.
Huh? It's open.
I did give them a spare key, but...
Are they here?
Welcome home, Master.
My wet pussy's been waiting for so long.
Please fuck our lewd pussies with your dick!
Wh-What are they doing?
Huh? Sensei looks kind of shocked, Onee-chan.
That's strange.
I even researched a lot and went so far as to ask those boys.
Researched?
I asked them what costumes would arouse guys the most.
70% told me it was maid costumes.
Maybe older men have different opinions
about it as opposed to younger men?
Older men, eh?
How about something related to office work?
Yes, if you're willing to go into an agreement,
then you're free to use my breasts and pussy however you want.
Let me refresh your aroused dick with my body.
I see.
So these two were worried too,
just like me.
Sensei?
You bitches, do you really want me to fuck you two?
Yes. We want it.
We want your dick, sensei.
Push it deep inside our pussies,
and stir it hard.
If you can service me well, then I shall think about it.
Sensei, can I show off the results of my training?
Training?
Here, how is it?
With your breasts size, I don't think a tit fuck is possible.
Oh, just leave it alone!
Even if my breasts are just a wee bit tinier,
I can still give one by using my nipples!
They're really rubbing on it.
Hey, you're hogging him, no fair!
Sensei, how is it?
Our sister tit fuck.
Does it feel good, sensei?
Yeah.
You two are good.
I give it a pass.
Sensed your dick feels hot.
And it's twitching.
Sawa, Saori, I'm about to cum.
It's okay, we'll take it all.
Just squirt all your cum onto our breasts and faces.
No, sensei, if you keep on doing that...
My pussy will become completely wet.
Onee-chan is really aroused.
I want my pussy to be fondled like that too.
I want it...
Sorry for being so harsh with you two at school earlier today.
When I saw you two talking with those boys,
I felt really jealous.
You might laugh at this old man for still acting like this,
but I really love you two.
Sensei...
Being madly in love with two of my students...
I really am a failure as a teacher, right?
Se-Sensei, why are you saying that?
Oh no, it feels too good, I can't think straight...
Sensei...
Stop, I'm cumming, I'm cumming...!
There are probably other ways to leave our worries behind.
But, a failure of a teacher like myself...
The only thing I can think of is sex.
I wonder...
If my feelings actually reach them.
Oh wow, it's really going deep inside.
Your thick dick is reaching my womb, sensei.
It's really stirring me inside.
Sensei, please cum inside me.
Okay, here I go.
Oh yes, I'm about to cum too!
Your dick is getting big again.
Your dick is really great!
Oh no, my hips won't stop.
My pussy is being sucked on right now,
and my love juices are being licked.
Sensei, I love you.
I love you, sensei!
I'm going to cum again.
I'm going to cum again if that licking continues.
I'm at my limit already.
I just keep getting hornier and hornier.
My pussy is going to cum.
My pussy is about to cum.
My pussy, my pussy is about to lose it...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Your dick is twitching a lot inside of me.
Sensei, I'm about to cum!
Let's, let's all cum...
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
M-Me too!
Sensei, good morning!
Good morning.
Oh no, now I'm love with them even more than yesterday.
I'm having a hard time accepting this.
I here aren't any classes today,
so we can do it all day.
Hey, sensei,
let's have sex together again!