I'm Aikawa Sousuke.
A freeter fresh out of high school,
and I'm currently living in this dilapidated apartment complex.
Man, I'm tired.
Good morning, Aikawa-kun.
Just got home!
Were you on a night shift, again?
Yup.
You're such a hard worker.
This is Shimizu Yuki-san.
Every moment I spend with this young, and beautiful landlady,
is a blessing away from my exhausting part-time job.
Man, I can survive this day again.
Jeez, it sure is noisy up there.
This is Aikawa from the room below.
Those noises are becoming a nuisance, you know.
This apartment complex is already creaking, for crying out loud!
I'm... I'm sorry.
Was it noisy?
Wh-What a babe!
What exactly were those noises?
I was practicing.
I'm currently aiming to be an actress.
I don't have any experience yet, so...
Oh, so that explains it.
I'll be more careful next time.
Oh well, I guess nothing can be done.
Pa-Pa-Pa...!
Panties are awesome!
Don't look!
Save me!
Eh? Oh, uh...
'Kay, 'kay, 'kay.
Wait, don't move like that!
So soft.
My mouth is moving on its own!
Come on, I said don't...!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's... in.
Wait, oh crap.
It went in? All the way in?
I... I... can't restrain myself!
So tender!
My nipples...!
This feels amazing!
Hey, stop it already—
Oh yes...
This chick is incredible.
She's moving in sync with me!
I can't...!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I'm coming in, Aikawa-kun.
Oh.
Episode 01: The hole, that connected her to me.