Rock, paper, scissors!
I win!
Oh, darn.
Hey, not so close you two!
Episode 8: Two in the Same Hole
No need to worry.
They're not brazen enough to do something so scandalous out in the open.
Says the woman who gave a handy in a theater.
Wow, we're really snug together.
Wait...
Geez, you're such a horndog.
Hey, there's kids here.
You can always cover them up with your mouth.
What are you saying—
Ooh, such passion!
I don't wanna get into that sort of relationship with you.
Wanna just be friends?
Obviously.
Yeah, right! You just wanna have a good time!
I feel the same way... I wanna feel good with you.
Sorry, but I just can't.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
I actually have morals, you know!
Your heart may be moral,
but your dick certainly isn't.
Physical reaction!
I feel so tingly inside...
Do something about it.
Screw it, I'm checking them out.
Oh, no! Water is seeping in.
You're so forceful!
Cum already.
N-Not yet! I want more!
Wow, you're so hard!
Physical reaction.
Hey, stop clinging together!
Make some distance!
Falling Girls
!
~A Girl Comes... Falling from the Second Floor?!~
So this is where you went off to.
Hey... You were getting it on with Yuzu, weren't you?
Or trying to.
What are you getting at?
I'm not losing you to that cunt!
Are you jealous?
Of course I fucking am.
I'm in love with you.
That's pretty cute.
Y-You've never called me cute before!
Don't start now.
You're adorable, Sunshine.
Y-You can't just call me that!
I mean, we're not even dating!
You're so cute when you're mad, Sunshine.
Seriously, stop that!
Just be my girlfriend for the next ten minutes then.
You can't just decide that at your convenience!
You're cute.
She's like a little kitten when she relaxes like that.
Salty!
It's from the sea water.
Hey, not there—
Dude, nice.
I can feel your lady boner through your bikini.
Y-You're gonna have to touch it directly...
Aikawa!
Not so rough...
You're so hard... Guess we'll have to do it.
Let's make it a quickie.
Sure.
It's like I'm back in the ocean.
Don't tease me! Hurry up before someone comes!
Only one cumming is you!
Then I guess it's safe to raise my voice.
Huh?
Whatever, let's get fucking.
I've been waiting for this!
Oh, god!
Wait, you're being too loud!
Aw, shit! I can't stop now!
Oh, god, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Aw, I was hungry for a creampie...
God, I'm so tired now.
Hey, Aikawa... Can you do me a favor?
Could you keep calling me "Sunshine"?
Hmm?
Does calling her that really make her happy?
Sometimes, I don't get women at all.
Sure, why not?
Great!
Sh-Shimizu!
It was starting to get late, so...
All the swimming tired us out, so we were resting.
Why is it always her?
Just kidding.
Let's shower, and then head home.