During lunch yesterday,
I just happened to hear it...
Futami,
is it okay for you not to tell your classmates about it?
Yes.
I don't feel like making a big fuss over my transfer.
I see.
Then I'll keep quiet about it too.
Fu-Futami-senpai is...
moving?
Photography Club
Futami-senpai is my senior in the Photography Club.
He's usually lying on the sofa gazing at some porn magazine.
It's not much different from when I joined the dub.
Now, knowing that he's actually going to move away...
I just couldn't hold back my tears.
I was sad, even frustrated, that he never told me about it.
This pose sure is erotic.
Ubukata,
why donlt you become a model?
Okay then.
Huh? You said okay?
Why are you surprised?
You asked me to do it, right?
But, you...
You usually say no, so...
You don't want to take photos of me?
That's not true, but...
Are you really serious about doing it?
I'm going to ask for lots of erotic poses, you know?
It's alright.
In exchange, I want the photoshoot to be done at your place.
O-Okay...
If parting with him is inevitable,
then I at least have to tell him...
Photography Club Chapter
Umm... senpai.
I'm done changing.
Okay, I'm done preparing too.
Umm...
Well? It looks quite mature, don't you think?
It doesn't feel all that different from your uniform though...
Come on now.
So? What kind of poses should I make?
Let's see...
Try sitting on the bed first.
Roger!
So, let's get started.
How is it?
Hmm... something's not quite right.
Is that so?
Oh well then.
Then...
How about this?
Ooh! There, that's it!
Okay, next...
Tada!
Wow, now this is another style to see!
They're all mature outfits.
There, there! That's perfect!
Now this is good alternative.
It really is cute.
Senpai.
Oh, I see.
You chose that next.
It's a bit small,
but it looked cute so I wanted to try it on.
Would a swimsuit be better?
Nope, that's perfectly fine.
I've been snapping away with my camera
passionately already anyway.
Try tilting your head a bit more.
Sure!
There, that's it.
I can feel my body getting hot as he gazes at me through the lens.
This position...
It's embarrassing because my butt is exposed, but...
...but I feel really good.
Ubukata's really into it.
Well, can you take off your skirt?
O-Okay.
Here,
like this...?
Alright, just hold that pose!
Senpai...
You're too close.
I didn't wear a pad, so it might be seen through.
Huh, Ubukata, it's... wet?
A-Ah, it's just sweat.
Yeah, you're right.
The lamp's making the room hot.
Oh, then let's take off your shirt too!
Eh? B-But...
If you really don't like it, you can just cover them with your hands.
No good, huh?
I-If you say so...
I-Is this okay?
Oooh! That is the best!
My breasts are totally exposed,
and he's taking pictures.
But, he's happy about it.
I can't just hide them anymore.
Ubukata, your nipples look really stiff.
N-No, this isn't what you think.
I'm actually nervous, so...
Umm, so...
Hey, we've already gone this far.
So can you take off the bottom as well?
T-The bottom?
You mean I'm going nude?
Of course I won't show the photos to anyone.
I'll snap some really good shots.
Okay?
I understand.
I'll take it off.
I'll go nude.
I'm now completely naked.
Maybe he thinks I'm a slut,
but, I've already decided.
He said he wouldn't show them to anyone,
but what is he going to do with those pictures?
W-Would he... use them to masturbate?
Oh no, what should I do?
My hands are...!
I can't stop them!
My body is getting hotter and hotter!
That expression...
It looks very erotic, very nice.
Just keep doing it.
He must have noticed it by now.
That I'm actually masturbating.
Oh no... it's really getting wet down there.
No!
N-No good... I can't stop it anymore.
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum!
S-Senpai... Senpai look at me more.
Look at how I cum!
Senpai?
We're doing blowjob shots next.
Is it embarrassing to look at the real thing?
Q-Quite.
Then, put this blindfold on for the next shots.
S-So this is a dick...?
Senpai's...
It's big and it feels hot.
Ubukata...!
His dick is starting to get bigger.
Wow, my mouth is getting really full.
Ubukata, stop, stop!
Senpai?
What's wrong?
Well, it's nothing really...
Oh crap, I was about to cum.
Oh, I get it.
I'm going to do a tit fuck next, right?
H-Hey...
You're...!
Where did you learn this?
It's all in the magazines you leave in the clubroom.
Senpai, how are my boobs?
W-Well... they feel hot and it's amazing...
Senpai, let it all out.
I'm going to take it all.
I-I'm cumming!
A-Amazing, you already came a lot but it's still big.
I never thought you were this erotic.
We're not finished yet.
U-Ubukata?
Senpai, I... I want you.
H-Hey, wait...
I'm putting it in.
Ubukata...
It's all the way in.
Senpai, has your opinion of me changed?
Because I'm such a lewd woman.
For someone who gave her first time to me in tears?
Not one bit.
Rather, are you okay with me?
I'm just a camera-loving pervert.
Your breasts are really sensitive.
Yes, you are... you are the one for me.
Please do it more.
If you say that, I w-won't be able to hold back anymore.
S-Senpai...
I love you.
E-Ever since I joined the club!
Ubukata, I...!
S-Senpai...!
I finally... I finally said it to him.
S-Senpai, that's amazing...
It's your first time and we're already
doing something this intense...
But I just can't stop.
It's okay.
My pussy's really wet already anyway,
and it feels good!
It actually still hurts a bit,
but I lied anyway.
I don't want him to be too worried about it.
M-My breasts also feel very horny.
More, please do it more!
Ubukata, I think I'm about to cum again.
Y-Yes, it's okay.
I'm safe today.
Just cum wherever you want.
I really am not safe,
I lied.
I thought that it'd be okay if it's him...
We had sex many times after that.
Your dick, oh wow...
Your dick is...!
I was still a virgin earlier and yet I already feel this horny.
Senpai, please...
My pussy... Make a mess of my horny pussy!
I deliberately said erotic things.
I wanted him to be completely aroused.
Your dick is pulsating inside.
It's okay, release lots of your hot cum inside me!
I may have troubled him with my sudden confession,
but it's a lot better than not even saying goodbye!
Ubukata, I'm cumming!
I'm also about to cum.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
He came again.
He's cumming inside me a lot.
Ubukata, there somewhere I'd like to take you next week.
Can you come?
Y-Yes, I will.
Senpai, where is this?
My new home.
My old man came up with the idea and just built the entire thing.
I just finished moving in yesterday.
S-So you were actually moving from that room to this house?
Yeah, why?
Well, he did say transfer, but he didn't
actually say transferring schools.
Did i totality misunderstand?
So, why don't you come in for a bit?
It was actually my dream,
to invite someone that I like home before any of my friends.
But, I'm still glad that I confessed.
Next club activity .  .  .
It's bouncy, it's bouncy!
Pinching my nipples like that feels good!
Fondle my boobs more and more!
Billiards Club