I drank as much as I ate.
Looks like Unyuu's passed out.
Aikawa...
Let's drink some more!
Falling Girls
!
~A Girl Comes... Falling from the Second Floor?!~
Look at how sweaty we've gotten.
Should we take a dip?
I-Is she suggesting we ditch Unyuu and get it on together?
Wait, what are you...
Hey!
You just sneaked a peak!
Perv!
This is, uh, pretty cozy.
Hmm?
Your bust just busted out!
L-Let me get that for you.
That tickles.
My, this is so embarrassing.
Don't back out on me now.
Put your hips in the air and shake 'em like you just don't care.
Like this? This really is embarrassing...
You have to go faster, or it might slip in.
You can't do that!
Who'd've thunk Yuki would get this assertive when drunk!
Shimizu?
What's the ruckus?
Sunny! Aikawa came onto me and—
I-It's just a misunderstanding!
Oh, yeah!
Weren't the three of us gonna do something "special" together?
Right...
We were talking about going to the festival together.
Huh? Did Shimizu wander off?
Seems so.
So what were you two chatting about in the open air bath?
Eavesdropping?
I was just saying how it's more fun if the three of us travel together.
But that was a lie.
A big ol' lie.
There's no way having a third wheel would be fun.
Because I'm in love with you, Aikawa!
I really wanted it to just be us!
What's brought this on?
I mean, I took your virginity, right?
Don't go assuming stuff!
And you always splooge inside me!
My b! It just feels so freaking good, and I can't help it!
You can't help it?
I wrote off your fooling around with Shimizu as you being scum.
And I was fine with our vague relationship.
But not anymore.
Did you have fun in the bath with her?
You were awake?
Why aren't you wearing underwear?
Can't you take a hint?
I'm scum just like you.
Or am I not good enough for you?
How far did you go with Shimizu?
I'm not at liberty to say...
Judging from your position,
you didn't go all the way, did you?
I'm not like that with her.
I just like being around her soothing presence.
Really? Well, I want you to be like that with me.
I want to be the only one to satisfy you.
So...
You can cum in me as much as you'd like.
Goddamn, you're so fucking cute!
You're already going in deep!
This is how you like it, right?
Oh, god!
I can feel a big one coming!
No! I can't hold it back any longer!
Let it out!
The pleasure of being cummed inside...
Oops, I did it again...
We should head back.
Don't worry.
I won't make you choose between me and Shimizu.
Episode 6: Two Sides of the Same Hole