I'm Aikawa Sousuke, a bum who'd rather work part-time than go to college.
I'm poor as fuck, so I can only afford this run-down apartment.
God damn, I'm tired.
Good morning, Aikawa.
Oh, hey!
Are you back from a night shift?
Yeah.
You've earned a good rest.
Shimizu Yuki.
My brief exchanges with this young, beautiful landlady
are a wellspring of nourishment for my weary soul after a hard day's work.
Now I can keep going for another day!
Jesus Christ, they're making a racket today as well.
I'm Aikawa from the bottom floor.
All that thumping around is getting on my nerves!
This place ain't that solidly built, y'know?!
O-Oh, I'm so sorry.
Was I being too loud?
H-Hot damn!
Wh-What are you doing to make all that noise?
Oh, I was rehearsing. I want to be an actress.
But I'm still not very good.
Ah, that explains it.
I'll try to be more quiet.
Who cares, she's fucking hot!
P-P-P-P-P-P-Panties?! Holy crap!
D-Don't look at them!
Help me!
I got you!
S-Stop that!
Don't move around so much!
So fucking soft!
My mouth is moving on its own!
I told you to stop!
Falling Girls
!
~A Girl Comes... Falling from the Second Floor?!~
It's inside me...
Oh, fuck!
I penetrated her! All the way to the hilt!
I can't hold myself back!
So supple!
My nipples? So forceful...
This feels fucking awesome!
No means...
...yes!
Holy shit, this chick rocks!
Our motions are perfectly in sync!
Oh, God, I'm nutting!
Shoot your goo, my dude!
Is everything all right, Aikawa?
Episode 1: The Hole That Connects Me to That Girl