Hey,Yuuichi.
I think it's okay, as a token of our friendship and as classmates.
Why don't you all join the billiards club?
You just don't know when to quit.
I've already said no many times, you know.
And what's with those outfits?
They're custom-made.
Do they suit us?
Though we actually borrowed these from the drama club.
Kojima, you’re not wearing a bra?
Not telling.
Guess there are people that would try to push
something like that no matter what.
It's not really that bad, is it?
Won't you please consider it?
We can't form the club officially if we
don't have at least seven members.
Okay, I'm joining, but only if you let me fondle those boobs.
It's bouncing, it's bouncing!
It feels great to have my nipples pinched.
Fondle my breasts more and more!
Something like that.
I was a fool for trying to ask you to join this.
Well, I'm fine if it's just that.
What, are you serious, Kana-chan?
If that's the fastest way to gather all the members we need.
We've got nothing to lose anyway.
And the deadline for the club's registration is tomorrow.
These bitches...!
Hey, are you serious?
Do you have any other ideas?
I get it already.
Bring it on then!
I'll just have to accept this challenge!
Billiard Club Formation
Kana-chan, your boobs feel tender.
Your nipples are having a hard on.
No, no...
Please don't say that.
I'm really glad to be alive!
Hey, be more gentle.
What Kojima? Is impossible you're actually craving for it?
Well, that's half the reason I guess.
But if we don't increase the pace, those two will never progress.
It's embarrassing, but this is for the
billiards club, so it can't be helped.
I never thought she'd really do it.
Hey, don't just stare at them, fondle them already.
Or maybe this isn't enough for you?
I was already planning on doing so!
Maybe you're not used to this kind of thing?
Virgin-kun.
Shut up.
Ohh, that was cute.
Oh, so that's it, eh?
I see, it's your first time.
Okay, okay, I'm joining already!
Hey, you're not even touching it yet.
Wha....!
Well? How does it feel?
Your boobs look really beautiful, Satsuki.
Are you trying to compare it to someone
else's? You don't even have a girlfriend!
Just leave that issue alone.
Thank goodness, he's not dating someone else yet.
Hey, I didn't say that you could suck it!
Jeez, he's sucking it like a baby.
Senpai, it feels really good.
Please, fondle me below... on my pussy as well.
But we just agreed on fondling breasts, is that okay with you?
It's my first time doing such lewd things
with a lot of people like this?
It made me really horny...
Please, do it more!
Stir up my wet pussy!
Are you ready? I'm about to expose your horny self to everyone.
Yes, it feels embarrassing,
but I'm starting to feel excited as I think
about being exposed to all of you.
Kojima, suck mine too.
Sucking two clicks at the same time...
Feels like I'm in a porn video.
I think I'm at my limit already.
It's alright, I'll take everything, so just let out your cum.
Oh my, amazing, so you two had this much built up inside, eh?
But, you two still aren't done yet, right?
Make me feel good this time.
My nipple feels good,
my mind's going blank...
Yuu's dick is getting bigger.
It's getting aroused by my body.
I'm happy.
Yuu...
Shall we pleasure ourselves some more?
So this is his dick.
It's very hard and stiff.
Would this fit inside my pussy?
Yuu... I already feel very embarrassed being licked like that...
Your pussy is very wet, and has a very erotic smell.
Shut up, your thing is also getting really big here, you know?
His dick, inside my wet pussy...
His dick, oh no...
Just thinking about it is making me feel horny.
I think I'm going to cum.
Not there...!
I can't suck this well if you stir me up like that!
Your pussy is getting wetter, and it's trying to suck my finger in.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I-I'm sorry...
This position completely exposes me, it's embarrassing.
Please put it inside me already.
Kana-chan, your pussy is wrapping around me really tightly.
Your dick is also very big, it feels great inside.
I get to do this every day if I join the billiards club, right?
Every day? But we also have to play billiards...
Kana-chan, instead of shooting billiard balls, seems
like you're the one who likes getting pierced.
That's not true, please don't say weird things!
Kojima, your pussy is the best.
No, not my balls...!
We're the billiards club, so we also need to practice handling balls.
I can't get enough of this.
I want to put it inside already.
Okay then. Do you want to put it in my other hole?
Can you see it? It's my asshole.
I'm so horny that it's pulsating.
Is it really okay?
It's a special service, but only if you decide to enter the club.
I'm in, I'm in!
Oh crap, it's gripping me very tightly!
Oh wow, both dicks are rubbing inside me really hard.
Please... push it in deeper!
I'm going to put it in then.
Hey, are you really okay with me?
What are you saying? Are you chickening out now, Virgin-kun?
It's not that.
Even I'm a bit scared, you know...
This is...
A girl's insides are more than I expected...!
I-It hurts...!
Satsuki, I'm going to move.
Wait, don't!
Satsuki, could this be your first time too?
Something wrong with that?
Nothing really, but...
It doesn't have to be me.
It doesn't have to be someone you don't have feelings for.
Idiot!
If that's what you think, then why don’t you
just do your best to make me enjoy it!
Idiot.
Idiot, idiot!
You're a huge idiot!
I wouldn't just give away my virginity
to someone that easily, you know!
My lips, my breasts...
Even my pussy...
I gave it all, because it's you...
Satsuki, I can't hold back any longer.
It's okay.
I'm fine now.
Just move however you want.
Make me feel good.
This position...
It makes your dick go deep inside my pussy.
No! If you play with my nipples as well I...
Kana-chan, I'm about to cum...
Me too, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
Senpai, let's cum together!
Okay.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
It feels great, it feels really great!
Both my pussy and asshole are being aroused to the core.
I think I'm going crazy...!
Kojima, I'm going to cum.
Okay, go ahead.
I'm safe today so just cum inside.
Me too, I'm at my limit already!
Your dicks are twitching inside me!
I'm going to be cummed on by both of you!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Sex...
Sex with Yuuichi... feels great.
My feelings may be a bit fuzzy,
but I've always been interested in Yuuichi.
I enjoyed our light conversations together.
I really wanted to be with him more, that's
why I invited him to join the billiards club.
I feel embarrassed to want him like this,
but I'm sure I'm in love.
I-I'm about to...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Me too, is it alright if I cum inside?
It's okay, just cum.
Pour lots into my pussy.
Satsuki...!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Thanks to Yuu and the others,
the billiards club was successfully established, but...
Senpai, let's practice properly sometime...
Kana-chan, I think you want to practice more like this.
My clitoris!
Don't play with it!
Now then, I'll put this inside your 'pocket'.
Hey, just wait, what are you trying to do?
Amazing, your pussy is getting even tighter!
No way...
No, no...
Don't play with my body like that...!
Instead of hitting balls,
it's more often that we ourselves are the ones being "hit" by dicks.
Satsuki, it's okay to cum inside, right?
Again? How many times do you intend to cum inside me?
You too, you were cumming the entire time earlier.
If you keep up that intensity, I'll...!
I'll cum, I'll cum!
I'll cum!