The Enma drama club at our school
often holds huge exhibitionist practice sessions.
It might appear to be a giant orgy to the untrained eye,
but it's an important practice for bringing out a woman's inner charm.
President Azumi, you sure are sexy!
Looks like you're going to make me cum again.
Not yet! Hang in there a little longer.
I want to cum along with you, got it?
President Azungu, your insides are gradually getting hotter.
I'm going to cum. President Azumi, I'm so close!
Its alright, go ahead.
Fill me up with your cum!
This is also part of the acting so,
so I have to take it all in.
Cum...! Cum! Cum!
Cum deep inside me!
Miya, have your boobs gotten bigger again?
Not bad.
Stu-Stupid, don't say that!
I-Its because everyone massages them so much!
My boobs are becoming rather lewd.
I know you get off on me talking dirty to you.
I guess it's also the result of acting.
Y-yeah... It's really embarrassing to hear dirty talk,
but it makes me all hot and bothered.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming!
I was skeptical at first
but we all do enjoy having sex, so.
It feels so good!
More! Fuck my pussy some more!
Pussy... Pussy, pussy!
I know, I know, President Azumi.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming again.
I'm cumming!
Oh wow! So many dicks.
All of them rock hard too.
Dicks, dicks, dicks!
Big dicks!
Everyone is like this because of Miya you know.
What should I do?
They're all hot and twitching.
I'm being violated so much by everyone's dicks!
I'm going to get covered in semen!
Wow! It feels so good I can't stand it!
My hips won't stop at all!
Its alright. Everyone is waiting to see you cum, President Azumi.
Oh no, everyone is watching!
Everyone is going to see me cum from a dick, how embarrassing!
They can see everything!
My pussy is on fire!
Please! Fuck me harder!
Wreck my tits and pussy!
Just make me cum a ton!
We won't be able to stop if you go and say that to us.
Its fine, spray it where ever you want!
I'm going to cum too.
I will do my best and cum together with you all!
Cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming!!
Hot... It's so damn hot.
There is so much semen...
I'm losing my mind.
Wh-What an amazingly lewd smell.
Oh no, I am getting excited again!
I am going turn into a perv!
Everyone keeps up with this
until they are all out of sperm.
Who would have thought that it could end
up like this all for the sake of acting class.
Azumi, I brought the scenario.
Megu! Thanks.
Sorry it took so long.
Arabian Night
Megu, from the Literature club, usually writes for the Drama club.
That remains the case for this year's Cultural Festival as well.
Is the scenario ready? What kind of story is it?
You two are playing the main characters this time.
Really?!
Not only that, but I went in a different direction
from the usual slapstick comedy routine.
I'm talking about a true love scenario!
WHAT?!
The stage will be Arabian.
Two maidens, who even put flowers to
shame, become the slaves of a merchant.
But after a certain incident, a love triangle springs up!
Wai... huh?
What's up with the two of you?
Oh!
Nothing.
True love, she says.
Maidens, who put flowers to shame, she says.
Ahh dicks, more dicks!
Give me lots more!
I just love sex!
Cum inside me! Cum! Cum!
We already go naked in our acting practice!
My shyness disappeared a long time ago!
Putting flowers to shame?
Just how shy do you want me to act?!
I must apologize in advance, since this will turn
into an extremely boring act.
I am sorry!
You are so quick to give up!
If it's like that, then we'll bring back
our shyness before the Cultural Festival.
It's special training!
How?
What if we try doing something a little different?
We could try doing it with a single boy.
Try binding or doing it outside.
That's right isn't it?
It might be better than doing nothing at all.
Okay! Lets go grab Amida as our
partner and start our practice!
Why Amida?
Maidens who put flowers to shame don't
really mean you have to act shy, y'know?
We'll, whatever.
U-Umm, so what exactly should I do?
We decided on Amida as our partner
for the special training.
Feel proud to be able to partner up with us!
Listen okay?
This is the setup.
Suzuki-kun is the merchant who bought us.
And we are the two slave girls who can put flowers to shame.
That's why you can do whatever you want to us.
Eh?!
But be sure to let us know if you don't
sense any shyness from our end, okay?
O-okay...
I can't feel any coming from them now.
It's totally cool, alright?
You can give us as many perverted commands as you want!
Come at us with everything you've got!
W-Well then, please let me t-titty fuck you.
No... give me a titty fuck!
Yes, Master!
Wow, impressive!
Master, whose boobs do you want to do it with?
Azumi's boobs are soft, y'know.
Miya's boobs are bigger than Azumi's, y'know.
U-Uhh, w-well then I'll go with president Azumi-sempai.
Yes, Master.
Can't help it if that's the case.
Are you sure you're okay with this?
Yes, my boobs belong to you, Master.
Please use it to your heart's content!
They are seriously soft.
Your penis is already rock hard, Master.
This is the first time I've gotten such a close look at others doing it.
During the acting practice, there were always so
many boys around that I never had time for this.
Azumi-sempai, tightly squeeze your boobs together.
Like this?
Azumi-sempai...
Suzuki-kun's penis is so hot, it's twitching!
Is he gonna cum? Is he gonna cum from my mouth and boobs?
Oh no! I'm getting all hot and bothered watching this.
My nipples are so hard they could cut glass!
D-Does your penis feel good?
Do my boobs make you feel good?
Your boob-pussy is the best, Azumi-sempai!
Master!
Feel free to cum whenever you're good and ready.
Shoot it all on me, your slave!
So much is coming out!
What a lewd smell!
H-Hey! You two are having fun all by yourselves.
It's so unfair!
Let me join in the fun!
M-Miya-serhpai!
Bring it on, Master.
Stick it in my pussy, please!
See? My pussy is all hot and wet.
I-I can't hold it anymore.
You're such a hopelessly perverted slave aren't you, Miya-sempai?
Yes! I'm a detestable slave!
Master, please give me lots of punishment!
Miya, you are so intense!
Did you really want a dick that bad?
N-No! Don't say that!
It's my first time being teased by a single boy after all.
For some reason, that's making me real excited!
I...
M-Miya-sempai.
If you grip me so tightly then I...
Your dick feels out of this world!
Dick... Dick!!
Amazing! This dick is just so good!
Now it's starting to get interesting.
It makes me want to try all sorts of things.
What?
I-I wanted to try anal at least once.
Wa-Wait a second!
Not my butt, I haven't done it with that hole yet!
Holy! It's gripping me so hard!
Don't! Don't move!!
The insides of my stomach are getting all twisted!
W-What a strange feeling.
I am going crazy!
Stop it!!
Slaves listen to everything their master says... right Miya-sempai?
I-I beg of you master!
My butt! Please not my butt!
Please forgive me!
So Miya had yet to do anal huh.
It feels good right?
A-Azumi? What are you doing?!
N-No! No way! Don't do that right now!
Please stop!
I haven't done it yet either.
Let's feel good together.
I-It's so amazingly tight!
My pussy also feels the dick inside!
T-This is bad!
It's suffocating.
D-Don't! T-Two of them inside...
I feel they're rubbing each other in there!
Saying something like that.
You are actually feeling good right?
Bu-But! Doing it with a girl.
D-Doing it with both my pussy and my butt.
No more... I'm starting to go insane!
Wow, your nipples are real hard.
Your pussy is also twitching.
Your dick is amazing, Azumi!
Its drilling through me, reaching the very end!
I'm done for! My butt and my pussy feel so good, I'm going to go nuts!
President Azumi, I am about to cum!
More! Please do it harder!
Yes, Master!
I will do it! Let me stir up that filthy pussy of yours!
Shoot a lot of semen on us slaves!
Me too... I am going to cum as well!
I'm gonna cum from being butt fucked!
Ma-master!
I-I'm cumming, it's gonna flow from my pussy!
Pussy! Pussy!!
I'm cummins!!
I'm cumming!!
Translator: Maq-kun
Timer: MrMew
Editor: punk4real
Huh?
L-Like I said.
The maiden, who can can put flowers to shame, means a beautiful woman.
Didn't you know that?
W-We didn't know.
Guess there was no point in practicing shyness.
Y-You were trying to be shy there?
Hey, the new club member should probably
stop with the cheeky lines!
Guess we'll have you tag along with
us for the "beautiful women" training.
I haven't put a dick inside even once today.
Wa-Wait a moment, President Azumi.
As I thought, a raw dick feels good!
Dick... Dick.
Raw dick is the best!
I-I just came two times before.
If you ride me so hard.
No! I won't let you quit!
Because I don't look good when I'm acting shy.
T-That was just, you know.
I left all my shame behind when I got
fucked in my ass and pussy!
I will have to have Master take responsibility for it.
M-Miya-sempai!
Your dick is getting even bigger!
Are you getting excited by licking Miya's pussy?
A-as if!
Ah! Not just the pussy.
My ass too... lick my ass as well!
I am starting to like this a little.
Master, we are lewd slaves so.
Punish our slave pussies with your dick!
As it turns out, the training seems to have worked.
And the performance for the Cultural
Festival turned out to be a great success!
And all lived happily ever after!