The day ended with me still being awkward around her.
I can't stand this.
I can't believe I was kicked out of that haven.
I need to restrain myself from doing dirty stuff.
Episode 03: Down the hole, panties flutter.
Whoa!
What the hell are you doing?!
Aikawa-san, you're awake, right?
I can't forget about it.
How we had sex... yesterday.
Sneaking into my apartment in the middle of the night?
Seriously?
I told myself that I'm going to hold back on all that dirty stuff earlier!
I need to pretend I'm sleeping.
In any case, I lose once I react.
Man, she smells like she just got out of the bath!
Hey, let's do it.
Why are you removing my blanket?
And don't raise my shirt!
What's this sensation?
There's like, two hard, protruding things in the middle of this soft, squishy stuff.
Come on.
She's crossing the line!
We can't?
Don't look at me like that.
No, don't!
I already pledged not to.
She's so horny right now.
I don't think I can end this quickly this way.
Okay already,
We'll have a quickie.
All right!
Oh crap.
She's gotten really wet.
It's getting steamy in here.
We're both drenched, and it's making me horny!
I'm going in.
'Kay.
Go ahead.
Wait, if you keep pushing hard like that,
I'm going to moan!
She's not awake... right?
I forgot about her bad sleeping positions
Hey, don't stop.
Please.
Right there. It feels great when you go deep!
I can't stop at this point!
I'm going to cum.
I'm sorry, Yuki-san.
Just this once, okay?
Umm...
Can I come here again?
That expression is cheating!
I can't say no to that.
I'll... think about it.
I'll be sure to lock up before we do, okay?
Morning, already?
I can't believe you'd do that while I'm asleep!
What?
What the heck was that?
You're the one who drowsily visited me.
So, you and Unyuu-san aren't dating?
We-We're not!
Is that so?
Aikawa-kun, wanna eat breakfast?
Huh? Is it okay?
Of course it is.
Let's fold up our futon.
Her mood improved?
She doesn't seem to know about what we did,
I think I can patch things up with her.
Aikawa-kun.
Yes?
May I ask what this is?
They're panties... right?
I know that!
I'm wearing them now.
I'm asking who they belong to.
Unyuu-san, why in the world would you forget your panties?!
Are you all right, Shimizu-sa—
Excuse me.
Is he not around?
I thought I heard someone inside, though.
Ah well, I'll just jump down from the hole.
This isn't good... I think.