Our school's drama club has some sort of unique
tradition since it was first established,
which is supposedly known as the "charm performance."
From an outsider's perspective,
this may seem like nothing more than some weird orgy,
But this is actually an important ceremony that helps
female members improve their overall appeal.
Prez Azumi, you're really erotic!
I'm about to cum again.
Y-You can't.
Just hold on a little longer.
I'm... I'm about to cum too, okay?
Prez, your insides are starting to feel hotter and hotter.
I'm cumming, I'm really cumming now, Prez!
It's okay, just cum.
Just cum lots inside me.
This is also part of our 'performance'.
I'm going to take it all.
Just cum.
Cum, cum!
Cum deep inside me!
Mia, aren't your boobs starting to get bigger again?
They're shaking so wildly.
I-Idiot.
Please don't say that.
Th-That's because everyone just keeps on fondling them.
My breasts have become even more lewd now.
But it feels even more pleasurable when
you say it aloud like that, right?
Is this the result of your "charm performance"?
Y-Yeah.
It really feels embarrassing hearing those words, and yet,
my pussy is starting to twitch all over.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum again!
I'm cumming!
I've been wondering if everything is really okay as it is.
True, both of us love sex, but...
Oh yes.
Please, violate my pussy more.
Pussy...
Pussy, pussy!
I know it already, Prez Azumi.
It's coming.
I'm about to cum again.
I'm cumming!
Oh wow, this is amazing.
There's lots of dicks.
And every single one is hard and stiff.
Dicks, dicks, dicks and big dicks!
That's because everyone just wants to fuck you.
What should I do?
They're hot, and they're twitching.
I'm just so fucked with all of these dicks.
I'm going be drenched in cum in a short while.
Oh no,
I feel so horny I can no longer hold back.
My hips just won't stop.
It's alright.
We're all closely watching you cum, Prez.
No, I'm about to be seen while doing it.
How I cum...
They're about to watch every single embarrassing moment.
And my pussy is getting excited all over it.
More, please, do it harder, please!
It's okay to make a complete mess of my breasts and pussy.
So please just cum lots!
Now, we can't just stop with those words.
It's okay, just cum wherever you like.
I'm about to cum as well.
I'm trying hard to cum with you guys!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming,
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
So hot, it just feels so hot.
There's lots of cum.
I've just become something to jerk off to.
Th-This smell is just too erotic.
Oh no, I think I'm starting to get aroused again.
I'm starting to become a slut.
And with this,
the charm performance continued till
the last drop of cum was spilled.
But, we never thought things would
turn out that way because of this.
Azumi!
I'm done with the script!
Megu, thanks a lot!
Sorry if it's quite late.
Megu is the one I'm charge of writing scripts for the drama club.
Of course, she was also the one who wrote the
piece for our play in this year's school festival.
Is the script finished?
What is it all about?
You two are the stars this time.
Really?
Also, we're deviating quite a bit from our usual random comedies.
I tried my hand at a pure-love story.
Wha-
The setting is in Arabia.
The two meek and pure maidens are suddenly
taken in by a boy to become his servants.
But with a certain turn of events, the three
will eventually become love slaves.
Eh, huh?
What's wrong with you two?
Well...
Nothing really.
A pure-love story she said.
Meek and pure maidens she said.
Wow, all these dicks, give me more of these dicks!
I really love sex!
Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me!
Our charm performance now turned completely against us.
Pure? I abandoned my purity a long time ago!
Meek? Wait, just how bashful are we in this story?
I'm going to apologize first.
This is so going to be in monotone.
I'm sorry!
You apologized way too fast.
Then we'll just have to get this 'meekness'
back before the school festival comes.
It's special training time!
How?
How about doing something different from usual?
Like servicing just one guy.
Then we can start tying him up, and start
doing all sorts of sneaky things.
Let's see...
It's probably better than doing nothing.
Let's decide by lots who's going first
and start working on it right away!
Lots, you say?
'Meekness' doesn't necessarily, mean being bashful though.
Oh well.
U-Umm... so what is it that I should do?
We decided through lots who's going to
get his turn first in our special training.
You should be grateful to be able to do it with us, okay?
Listen carefully.
This is how it goes.
You, Suzuki, have just bought us two as your slaves.
And we will play as the part of the meek and pure slave girls.
So, you can do whatever you want with us.
Eh?!
However, you should be aware that we must
maintain our 'meekness' at all times.
O-Okay.
I can't really feel it at all though.
Doing a perverted order is completely fine!
Just go ahead and say it!
Th-Then, let me experience a tit fuc...
Oh wait, I demand a tit fuck!
Okay, master.
Wow, those look really bombastic.
Master, which breasts are you going to use?
My breasts are quite tender, you know.
My breasts are actually bigger than hers.
W-Well...
I'll take the prez's breasts then, Azumi-senpai.
Alright, master.
I guess I can't do anything about it.
I-It's really okay, right?
Yes, my breasts are already yours, master.
Just use them to your heart's content.
They really feel soft!
Master, your dick also feels really hard.
This is actually the first time I'm going
to see someone else do it up close.
I'm usually surrounded by the boys during charm
performances so I didn't really notice.
Azumi-senpai, push it in between.
Like this?
Azumi-senpai.
Suzuki-kun's dick feels really hot, and it's starting to twitch a lot.
Is he about to cum?
Is he going to cum with my breasts and mouth?
Oh no, I feel really horny as I watch it.
My nipples are already very hard.
Does your dick feel good?
Can you properly feel my breasts?
Azumi-senpai, your breast pussy is the best!
Oh, master...!
It's okay, just cum on your slave whenever you feel like it.
Let all of your cum out.
It's really coming out.
It's all sticky, and has a really lewd smell.
H-Hey, it's not fair that you two are the only ones having fun.
Let me join in too.
M-Mia-sehpai...
Come in, master.
Please put it inside my pussy.
Here, look, my pussy is already very wet and itching to do it.
I-I just can't resist!
Jeez, Mia-senpai, you really are a helpless perverted slave.
I am indeed a perverted slave.
Master, punish me more.
That sure is intense, Mia.
Did you really want a dick that badly?
N-No, please don't say that.
It's my first time being fucked by only one guy.
I feel so aroused that I...
M-Mia-senpai, if you keep on gripping me tightly like that, I'll...!
Dicks feel great!
Dicks, dicks!
This dick is really good!
Things are getting quite interesting here.
Now I want to test a few things of my own.
Huh, what?
I really want to try anal sex at least once.
J-Just wait!
Not my ass!
I haven't done anal sex yet!
Oh wow, this is amazing!
It's squeezing me really tightly.
N-No, not there! My insides are getting stirred really hard.
It feels weird, and I'm about to go crazy.
Please stop!
Slaves are supposed to answer to all requests
made by their masters, right, Mia-senpai?
I-I beg of you, Master.
Not my ass, please, not my ass!
Please let me be!
So Mia still hasn't done anal sex yet.
Feels good, right?
A-Azumi?
What are you doing?
No way, that can't be.
Don't you dare do that.
Stop!
I haven't cum yet, you know.
Let's pleasure ourselves together, okay?
It really feels tight.
I can also feel the sensation of a dick right inside my pussy.
This is really bad.
It's being squeezed even tighter.
No, not two at the same time...
Both of them are rubbing me inside.
You say that,
but it actually feels great for you, right?
B-But...
Doing it with another girl,
and being fucked both in my pussy and ass at the same time...
Oh no, this is it.
I feel really horny!
Look, your nipples have become this hard already.
Your pussy is also twitching hard.
Azumi, your dick feels amazing.
It's going really deep.
The sensation from both dicks is so great
that my mind's about to get torn apart!
Prez Azumi, I'm about to cum.
Please, fuck her harder!
I understand, master.
I'm going to fuck her lots in the pussy.
Please squirt all your cum over us, your slaves.
Me too, I'm about to cum as well.
I'm going to cum with my ass.
Master!
I'm cumming!
My pussy is going to cum.
Pussy, pussy...!
I'm cumming!
Huh?
L-Like I said, the "meek and pure maiden" phrase,
simply refers to a beautiful woman.
Didn't you know?
I didn't...
Then our 'meekness' project was a failure...
Wait, you call what we did earlier 'meek'?
Hey, our newbie member over there
is saying something really cheeky.
Let's see, why don't you join us in our special
training for a 'beautiful woman' this time?
I haven't been fucked directly yet, you know.
J-Just wait, Prez Azumi!
A raw dick feels much better after all.
Dick, dick...
Raw dicks are the best!
I-I just came twice earlier.
But if you keep pushing hard like that...
Oh no you won't.
I'm not going to let you stop this.
Because I was never really compatible with 'meekness'.
Th-That earlier was...
Me too, I was also violated in both my pussy and ass earlier,
that I already forgot all about this 'meekness'.
You need to take responsibility for this, master.
Mia-senpai...
His dick is starting to get bigger again.
Did you get more aroused after licking Mia-senpai's pussy?
No, it's not!
Not just my pussy.
Lick my ass, lick my butt pussy as well!
I think I'm about to love this even more.
Master, the two of us are actually slutty slaves.
So please, use your dick on our slave pussies,
to properly discipline us.
In the end, because of this special training,
we then proceeded to successfully present
the play at the school festival.
All's well that ends well.