Our relationship is so fucking awkward now.
I can't bear to lose that healing smile!
Maybe I should stop thinking with my dick all the time.
Episode 3: Descending Through the Hole, Panties Flutter Freely
What the hell is she doing?!
I know you're awake, Aikawa.
I can't stop thinking about it...
How we banged yesterday...
A booty call?! For real?
But I just swore to stop thinking with my dick...
Better pretend I'm sleeping.
If I react, I lose.
Holy shit! I can smell her Dove™ soap!
Hey, let's fuck.
Why's she pulling off my sheets?
My shirt too!
Goddamn, what's this heavenly sensation?
There are two hard peaks nestled within the mountains of softness!
C'mon, let's fuck.
You can't just tempt me like that!
So we're not gonna?
Please don't give me that look!
No means no! I swore to myself!
God, she's like an animal in heat.
I don't think I'm getting out of this one.
My brain says no, but my dick says yes!
Thank you, Mr. Dick!
Mother of God!
She's wetter than an otter's pocket!
It's getting hot in here,
so take off all your clothes!
Good gracious, that ass is bodacious!
I'll put it in nice and slow.
Yeah, go ahead.
S-Slow down! This is too intense!
I'm gonna scream and cream!
She's not awake, right?
I forgot how much she rolled in her sleep!
Please don't get dickstracted...
Yes! Deeper!
Don't stop me now! I'm having such a good time!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Sorry, Yuki... It's hard not to think with your dick when it has an IQ of 200.
So...
Would it be okay for me to drop in on you again?
Like hell I could turn down that face and ass!
Yeah, probably.
Great! Thanks for the sex, homie!
Morning already?
I can't believe you even grope me in your sleep!
C'mon, how is that my fault?!
Once again, you rolled into me.
So you really aren't going out with Unyuu?
Nope! Definitely not!
I see.
Hey, would you like some breakfast?
Really? You sure?
Of course!
Let's roll up the sleeping bags.
Is she not mad anymore?
I guess she didn't notice.
I may be able to patch up things now!
Aikawa.
Yes?
What are these?
Panties, I think...
Obviously!
I'm wearing mine right now,
so just who do these belong to?
Goddammit, Unyuu! How could you forget your knickers?!
Are you okay, Shimizu?
Excuse me!
Are they out?
I thought I heard voices...
Guess I'll drop down the hole.
Falling Girls
!
~A Girl Comes... Falling from the Second Floor?!~
I'm fucked.