Hey, won't you take me in?
I'm Canary, the legendary songstress.
I'm sure I'll bring in more customers than anyone else.
Come here, Alexis.
She's stunning...
A love scene right off the bat?
Falling Girls
!
~A Girl Comes... Falling from the Second Floor?!~
God, I can hardly even tell that's Unyuu.
Because I'm in love with you, Aikawa!
I won't make you choose between me and Shimizu.
That's quite enough, for we do not share the same fate!
She really is dazzling.
I'm scum compared to her.
And that's how I got the lead role as the heroine.
Anyway, you'll come see it, right?
Of course!
You're incredible, Sunny!
Ah, but now I've set you up on a date...
A date, huh?
Ah! Give me more, Alexis!
You're on edge.
I'm sure you can't endure it any longer, either.
Huh?
Caress me.
Hold up, this isn't the time nor place!
Don't pussy out on this pussy.
If you insist.
So good...
We really shouldn't.
You can't just cut the engine after getting it running.
Shimizu's so assertive today.
What is she—
Please stop, Alexis! This is as far as I can go with you.
I've never been able to chase my dreams.
I had to sacrifice everything for the sake of the apartment my late parents left behind.
That's why I'm so jealous of people like Sunny,
who can earnestly fulfill their dreams.
But more than anything, I want to be the only one for Aikawa.
I'm so sorry. I can't see you anymore.
Don't look away from me!
Give me your full attention!
Aikawa, Aikawa, Aikawa!
Shimizu's inexperience is showing,
but I still love me a sloppy handy!
We'll never see each other again.
Focus solely on me!
Hey, guys!
Was I good or what?
You were breathtaking, Sunny!
Yeah, you really brought the part to life.
I saw everything.
I know I told you to come,
but I didn't mean it like that.
Well, I'd better get going.
God, I'm such a douche.
I keep fucking them one after the other without thinking about their feelings.
I guess I should make a decision.
Sousuke!
Yuzu?!
And you are?
Hanazono Yuzu!
Sousuke's girlfriend!
Pleased to meetcha!
Great, now they both hate me.
She's just a childhood friend!
Are you two listening?!
You really are a dipshit. Un-fucking-believable.
This room is already at capacity.
You can have the one next to shitface's.
A shitfaced dipshit...
Was that hole always there?
Yuzu?!
Right when she's changing, just like a porno!
Damn, did she always have that much meat on her?
You peeping Tom!
I knew it! You're super in love with me!
I am not! Now get off me and put something on!
Why are you getting so flustered?
We used to bathe together as kids.
We also promised to get married.
At least this fella is honest.
It's just a physical reaction!
Where did she learn to give head this good?
Pretty good, right?
Wanna fuck?
I wanna become one with you.
Let's do it.
I knew he was fucking around!
W-Were you so horny you had to put a hole in the wall?
I've got it! Let's go to the beach!
We'll all wear swimsuits and get Aikawa to decide once and for all who he likes best!
That sounds like so much fun!
Aw, hell no!
Episode 7: A Peephole in the Wall
Big titty girls in swimsuits fighting over my dick...
I'm gonna fucking die!
DUMBASS