Finale: Don't Fill the Hole
Shimizu! This is the ladies' shower room!
Please don't act like you're against this sort of behavior.
Well, uh...
You're always trying to shift the blame.
That's...
If I'm upfront about it, you'll do naughty things with me, right?
We returned the tubes.
Looks like we're the only ones here.
So what did Sou want to talk to you about, Yuki?
S-Sou? You have a pet name for him?
Yep. Don't worry about it.
What, jealous?
N-Not at all! I absolutely despise that man!
All he does is stagger around and break walls.
...And hearts.
There's not a single decent thing about—
Hey!
You said you wanted to do naughty things.
Wait, not now!
I thought you were serious about me?
You say that, but you're in love with him.
You all right? You suddenly got quiet.
I-It's nothing. Can we stop talking about Aikawa, please?
Good idea. I don't want to get into another fight.
Oh? Do you actually like me?
No...
Well, whaddya know?
Don't play with them!
You're always getting ahead of yourself.
That's what I hate about you!
Oh, no!
I can't stifle my moans.
Face the wall.
You want me to turn around?
Yep.
I'm gonna penetrate you.
Just like you wanted.
You said you wanted me to teach you about carnal pleasure.
R-Right...
But what do I?
Leave it to me.
Stick your ass out.
This is embarrassing.
It took nine episodes, but I'm finally gonna do it!
We in there, boys!
Aikawa's gonna enter me...
It's a bit scary, but I'm happy.
Relax.
It hurts!
So tight! What a squeeze!
Stay like that for a bit.
You ready? Make sure you remember my shape.
Okay...
Okay, I'm heading out.
Sure...
I've had a thing for you ever since I moved in.
I've always dreamed of this.
Your smile was the only thing keeping me going.
Really?
Wait, do you actually hate me?
O-Of course!
Understandable. In that case, resist me!
Huh?
I'm taking you by force!
This is way too much!
C'mon, resist! Don't you hate me?
I can't!
I mean, for the longest time I...
Please, call me "Yuki"!
Can I really?
Yes!
Yuki...
I've caught up to Sunny.
Let's change positions.
Why?
I wanna see your face.
No way! That's too embarrassing!
You're so deep inside!
Don't like it? I can stop.
N-No!
I want to stay connected to you like this forever!
Yuki, I'm so unbelievably happy.
I'm getting out now!
O-Okay!
Are you okay?
Your breathing's kinda ragged.
I'm... just... dandy...
I'll get out soon...
Getting out? More like getting off!
I'll make your whole body melt with pleasure!
Don't thrust so deeply!
Oh god, oh god!
I'm cumming!
In the end, I never chose which girl looked best in a swimsuit.
This slapstick farce that all started with a hole in the ceiling...
If I were to describe it now,
I'd say it's a story still in progress.
A story of a guy living in a sixteen square-foot apartment with three girls.
Everything escalated so quickly
It all began with that hole
What came falling down was more than your body
But also your loving heart
And like how you fell through that hole, I fell for you
I'll make you face me
I won't ever give up
Look only at me
Don't look at her
My feelings are overflowing
I'll never ever lose to her
I want us to become one
Is that too much to ask?
I want to keep all of your warmth to myself
Falling Girls!
Falling Girls
!
~A Girl Comes... Falling from the Second Floor?!~
One of these days, I'll make a decision once and for all.