Hey Yuuichi, since we had friendship as classmates,
Manga enthusiast association
join our billiards club!
You're insistent, I refused many times right?
And what's up with those clothes?
It's a Hustler. Does it suit us?
We borrowed it from the drama club.
Kojima, you're not wearing bra?
Yup!
There are those guys who start with the outfit first.
That doesn't matter, just think about joining our club,
we need 7 members to make a club application.
We'll join if you allow us to touch your boobs.
And if that happens...
Ahh! It's shaking... It's shaking!
Ahh! Touching around my nipples feels so good!
Ahh! Rub boobs more!
What do you think?
It was a fool of me to ask you...
I'm fine with just that...
Kana-chan... what?
That's the fastest way to gather enough club members.
It's not a big deal and tomorrow's the deadline of submission...
These bitches...
Hey are you serious?
Do you have any other ideas?
I got it!
Just do it!
I'll allow them to use us!
Kana-chan's tits are so soft...
Your nipple are erect...
No! Please don't say such things...
I'm happy I'm live!
Do it gently!
What's with you Kojima, of are you dissatisfied?
It's kinda like that, but that's not the point.
Look at those two, they seemed not to progressing nicely.
This is so embarrassing, but for the sake of billiards club!
I didn't expect her do this...
Hey, what are you thinking about? Just touch it now.
Or are you not satisfied with my boobs?
I'm about to touch them now!
Perhaps you don't have experience with this...
Mr. Virgin?
Shut up...
Wow he's cute...
Ohh so that's it, it's your first time!
Fine... I’ll be going home!
Hey, you haven't touched them...
How does it feel?
Satsuki's breast are so beautiful!
To whom are you comparing it? You don't even have a girlfriend.
Shut up...
I'm glad, he doesn't have girlfriend.
Wait, I didn't say you lick it...
He seem like a baby while sucking...
Senpai, this feels so good...
Please tease me down there on my pussy...
We only agreed on touching boobs. Are you really fine with that?
Since everyone's doing it with each other for the first time...
It kinda makes me aroused...
More... do it more!
Do me more, do my sloppy pussy more!
Ok, we'll let them see your slutty parts...
Though It embarrassing to be seen by everyone
I allow you to do it...
Kojima, me too...
I'm about to...
It's fine, you can cum all the way my face...
This is great, this amount...
But It's not finished with this yet!
This time you'll pleasure mine!
My nipples feels so good!
I'm getting wet...
Yuu's dick is getting big...
He's getting aroused with my body...
I'm glad...
Yuu we should make ourselves feel more good...
So this is Yuu's dick...
It's big and hard...
Can this get inside my pussy?
Geez Yuu... it's embarrassing if you lick me there...
Your pussy is so sloppy and has really slutty smell...
Shut up, even you had a hard-on...
His dick on my pussy, his dick on on my slutty smelling pussy...
Oh no, I'm getting aroused just thinking
about. I feel like I'm about to come.
No!
If you do me like that, I'll can't help myself...
Your pussy seems to be twitching and tightening...
I'm cumming! Cumming!
Cumming!
Sorry...
This position is embarrassing, you can see everything...
Insert it now, faster...
Kana-chan, your pussy is really tight!
Your dick is so big and so good!
If I join your club we can do this everyday?
Everyday? We should also practice billiards.
Kana-chan, you like being fucked right?
No, it's no like that... don't say wierd thing...
Kojima, your pussy is the best!
If you do that...
Since I'm billiards club, I'm good in handling balls!
I can't stop it!
I want to get inside too...
Fine, you can use my other hole.
A look, my asshole is aroused it's twitching...
Are you serious?
Since you'll be joining our billiards club
I'll give you this special service.
Its inside... inside!
Oh no, her pussy is tightening!
Wow! The dick is rubbing me inside!
Please do me more, stick it in!
So I'll be putting it...
Hey, are you really fine with?
What's with you? Are you nervous Mr.Virgin?
I'm not nervous.
I... I'm little scared...
Oh what... inside a pussy feels really good...
It hurts... It hurts!
Satsuki, I'll be moving...
Wait, you can't start moving!
Satsuki, could it be that it's also your first time?
Is it bad thing?
No, but...
Is it really fine with you, doing it with someone you don't like?
If you really think like that than just make me fall with you!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
There's no way I'd give me virginity to someone I don't like!
My tits, my lips, my pussy, I gave my everything since It was for you!
Satsuki, I can't stop myself anymore.
Its fine it doesn't hurt anymore...
You can now do whatever you want...
Make me feel good...
His dick id hitting more deeper in this position!
Oh no... If play with my nipples while doing it...
Kana-chan, I'm about to cum...
Me too... I'm cumming! I'm about to cum...
Senpai please let's cum together!
Got it!
I'm about to cum...
I'm cumming!
It's good... so good!
My ass and pussy feels so good, It's making me crazy...
Kojima, I feel like I'm cumming again!
Fine, you can shoot it inside me since today's a safe day...
Me too... I'm about to...
Ok, then come!
Your penis is twitching!
You two come in me simultaneously!
I'm cumming! Cumming!
Sex, sex, having sex with Yuuichi feels so good...
It wasn't clear that I like him, but...
he's always on mind...
It was fun to have conversations with him...
I invited him to join the club since I like to be with him more!
It was embarrassing admit it but I'm really in love with him!
Me too, I'm about to cum... I'm cumming, cumming!
Can I cum inside you?
Yes, come a lot inside my pussy...
Satsuki...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
billiards club
And so, thanks to Yuu and his friends
our billiards club is now safe but...
Senpai, we need to at least practice from time to time...
Kana-chan, you like it more having practiced on that part right?
No, not on my clitoris...
Ok this time it will enter your pocket!
Wait, stop it! What are you doing?
Wow, your pussy tightening!
Such thing... No... No...
Don't treat my body as a toy!
Rather than striking cue stick and balls
we are being striked with dicks...
Satsuki, it's fine if I'll came inside right?
How many times plan to come, stupid...
And what about you, you came over and over again earlier...
No, if you’re that intense...
I'm cumming! Cumming! Cumming!