I'm Aikawa Sousuke.
A freeter fresh out of high school.
But, I'm currently in a bit of a bind.
So basically,
the floor of Unyuu-san's room collapsed,
and you two just happened to end up that way when she fell?
I find it incredibly hard to believe.
But that's what happened!
Please believe us!
Is that so, Unyuu-san?
Yes, kinda.
With the broken old floor requiring repairs...
I got it!
We'll do it this way.
Eh?
I shall take responsibility as the landlord.
What?!
I can understand Yuki-san offering her room to Unyuu-san,
but is it okay for her to, like, live in my room like this?
Wait, wait, wait.
Maybe, if all goes well...
Good night, then.
Good night.
I can't sleep.
What kind of penalty game is this, anyway?
It's so dark, I can't see well.
Is it hot?
Forget that.
Her sleeping position sure is risky.
I can see it!
I can see through it!
Very clearly!
So sexy.
Oh crap, oh crap!
She's too close!
This is heaven!
Such a soft and tender sensation.
Just a tiny, tiny bit... okay?
I'm in hell.
I'm being devoured halfway.
I can't restrain myself anymore!
They're so soft, and yet firm.
Fondling them feels so awesome!
This is bad.
It'll be bad if she wakes up.
Yet, it's so lewd, I can't stop myself!
Aikawa-kun, what are you doing?
Oh crap!
You're... you're the worst.
Sorry, I'm so sorry!
I won't do it again!
Please forgive me!
Is it checkmate for me?
Episode 2: Above, a hole. To the side, is you.
I'm definitely getting kicked out.
What are you doing?
I'm drawing the line.
A line?
You're not allowed to cross this line, okay?
What?
But, I think she's doing this partly because she didn't wake up after I fondled her.
Well, I am to blame, after all.
I-I'm heading off to work then.
Though,
it doesn't seem like she hated me for it.