Lacrosse Club
Hey! You girls...
To think that our adviser
will peep on us changing...
Are you prepared for the consequences,
Kuroda-sensei?
Wait... I told you that it wasn't intentional!
We're not listening to such a childish excuse!
Gag him, Yuri-chan!
Momoi-san, even you...
Heave-ho!
Whoa...
Y-You won't think he carries something
this incredible when you look at his face.
Did we make you horny that
you got hard? What a pervert!
Oh! He got a boner!
Whoa, they're looking at me...
I haven't taken a bath yesterday!
How does it feel, getting this pretty
and pale finger slimy, Kou-chin?
A man's thing is bent backwards so much...
Oh, Yuri-chan! You'll end up
kissing it if you move any closer!
Huh? They touched! You just
touched it with your lips!
It got even bigger again. How mysterious.
It smells stronger than before.
Wh-What's with that thing?
No way, it's grotesque!
And what's up with that smell? Gosh...
Kumi—!
Why are you prowling around back there?
You're the angriest one here for having
your sexy tits seen. Go make him pay!
Hey! I'm fine here, idiot!
The prim lady faces the dick!
Have a good look at it!
K-Kumiko?
Sh-She's too close!
H-Her breath is tickling me!
If she does that at the tip that
got sensitive from getting teased...
I'm at my limit!
Whoa!
Is that... No way...
Whoa... He actually ejaculated!
Seriously? That's terrible!
Oh...
Hmm?
Ahh... It stinks...
K-Kumiko-chan?
Kumi?
Whoa!
Kumiko-chan!
Captain?
My name is Kuroda Koutarou.
For some reason, I got appointed as the adviser
of Felias Girls Academy's lacrosse club...
One, two...
Joshi Luck!
Akagi
Aya
Akagi Aya. She holds an attacker position.
She's the ace of our club. She's well-known
on other schools for her skills.
However, her personality is kind of rough.
Aoyama
Kumiko
Aoyama Kumiko. She is a middie.
She gives off an aura of a dependable older sister.
She's doing a great job of holding
the team together as a captain.
Shirogane
Sakura
Shirogane Sakura. She's the goalie.
She's a peculiar girl who's kind of a ditz.
For example, she believes that
babies are made by kissing.
Momoi
Yuri
Momoi Yuri. She's a long stick middie.
She has a calm and composed personality,
and she spaces out from time to time...
...while making an alluring face.
Kise
Matori
Kise Matori. She holds a defender position.
She's a light-footed and cheerful girl.
She is a known troublemaker.
Kou-chin!
What!?
What are you looking at?
Huh?
Will I be able to carry out my job
as a coach of these eccentric team members?
Lacrosse Club
Not here... It's not here!
I looked at various places.
But it should be here, right?
My pants got torn off earlier today.
Today's particularly worse than usual, though.
They played with my dick.
And in the end, I lost my house key...
In any case, I have to find it...
Who knows what they will say if they see me here?
Who knew that you're sneaking in the clubroom?
You're a perverted and lecherous teacher!
Jeez... You should clean this room a little.
Aren't you women? This is disillusioning.
Huh?
I-Is this a sexy lingerie?
Isn't it too skimpy? Who owns this?
Akagi-san's would be some dull sports underwear.
Shirogane-san would own
something plainer, won't she?
I can imagine Aoyama-san
wearing something prudish.
Kise-san should be wearing something childish.
Then that means that this is Momoi-san's...
This should look great on her nice body!
Kuroda Koutarou, the new teacher
will be caught by a club member
looking at that underwear in the clubroom!
K-Kise-san!
I saw that! Will this mean a disciplinary dismissal?
Or worse, you might end up behind bars!
M-My life is over...
But aren't you lucky, Kou-chin?
I'm the one who caught you.
Huh?
Your dick is all mine!
I didn't get a good look of this earlier,
so I'll take my time now!
Uhh... Why is this happening?
It's so stiff!
It's throbbing and its veins are popping out!
How lewd!
Oh, it's oozing with slimy stuff!
The tip feels like a rubber ball!
Kou-chin, are you washing this properly?
It stinks so much! That's a no-no!
No, I haven't taken a bath yet...
Jeez... I'm gonna make your body
squirm just like your mouth!
Well, my spats might stink as well.
Whoa... It has a stuffy smell...
I-It reeks of a bittersweet odor!
Oh! I'll help myself with this!
I got the first blowjob!
It's supple!
She's narrowing her tiny mouth
and she's wobbling her tongue!
Kise-san, that's not a good idea!
If you keep doing that, I'll come in no time!
Don't move!
I'll shut my mouth with this.
If it was Aya-chan or Kumi-chan,
your life will be over!
I'm in a good mood today!
Anyway, you sure like this kind of underwear.
If you love it that much, why not take
it home and use it as a fap material?
No way, I can't just take Momoi-san's
underwear home without permission...
Huh? So that's how it was...
You thought that it belonged to Yuri-chan!
I see!
Huh?
Then, was this yours?
This skimpy underwear? Huh!?
Uhh... I think my reason for having
a good mood just went away...
You see, I hate being treated like a child the most!
Now I'm pissed off!
How dare you treat me like
a child when you're a virgin!
I'll torment you inside with
all my might, so prepare yourself!
K-Kise-san!?
I'm going to squash your
virgin dick into a gooey mush!
Whoa... It's narrow! It's pushing me out so hard!
But it's slippery inside and
I'm wriggling my way in!
I'll captivate you with my adult feminine charm!
Th-This feels way different from masturbating!
This is bad! This will make me burst in no time!
Kise-san?
Hey...
Don't move!
What do you think of an adult woman's
well-developed vaginal wall?
Aren't you about to come?
Aren't you engrossed in it?
A-Are you alright?
What are you worrying about?
This is a piece of cake!
But your face is beet red...
Huh!?
Enough of that, shut up!
Incompetent and perverted teacher!
You're uncharismatic and
a failure as a club adviser!
Bitch! You're saying anything you want!
Kou-chin, you idiot... Didn't I tell you not to move?
She's pretending to be an adult,
but isn't she already at her wit's end?
Alright... If that's the case...
Hey! I-I'm gonna do the moving!
Haven't I already told you
not to move!? Stupid Kou-chin!
Come on, hurry up and captivate me
with your adult techniques!
Y-You don't have to remind me!
I'll be moving hard when I'm all ready!
This is the problem with virgins!
You're a baby yourself!
I can reach the far end of
your kiddy pussy with ease!
D-Don't push it deep inside without permission!
I'm pressing your baby room upwards!
Does it feel awful?
N-No, it doesn't!
No...
No!
You're such a baby that only
your tits grew up audaciously!
Your areolae got this puffed up!
Isn't it about time to be honest, Matori-chan?
Say that sensei's dick is making you feel good!
D-Don't make fun of an adult woman!
There's no way for such a virgin
dick to make me feel good!
Really?
Even though your pussy walls are like saying
"don't go away" while squeezing hard?
Y-You're wrong!
Don't be stubborn.
Kids are cute when they're being honest!
Ah!
Idiot! Stop spanking me!
For doing something this humiliating on me,
I'll mash your virgin dick into a melty mess!
I'll make you move this time, Kise-san!
Hey!
Kise-san, you're like a pocket pussy!
D-Don't rock me around!
Y-You're not getting away from this!
So you still feel good even from
getting treated as a child in sex!
I-It doesn't feel good! Gosh!
Though if you'll be honest and say it feels good,
I'd pamper you like a child!
I-I'm not a kid at all!
I get it... It feels good,
so hold me right!
I'm feeling miserable, Kou-chin!
Wasn't it Kuroda-sensei?
Y-Yes...
Kuroda-sensei, I'm sorry for
talking with disrespect!
I really was a bad girl.
Please hug me the right way!
It can't be helped! I'll forgive you for today!
Your dick went in!
Your dick is going in me properly!
It's sliding in while you're hugging me tight!
It feels good!
Don't make fun of me from now on, okay?
Okay!
Put your heart in training
starting tomorrow, okay?
Okay!
Alright, good girl!
It's already time for kids to sleep.
Sensei will make you drink some hot milk.
You'll go straight to bed afterwards, alright?
S-Sensei...
Kiss! I want a kiss!
Hey, kiss me!
You're such a spoiled child.
Sensei, make me drink your creampie milk!
It's coming! The milk is here!
I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
My womb is already bulging!
Huh!?
Sh-Shit!
I got carried away and did something terrible!
Kou-chin!
K-Kise-san?
Give me more milk!
Hey, Kise-san!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji