It's okay.
Right there!
Does it feel good?
Don't stop! Do it like that...
Okay.
Go up more, lick my clitoris!
Good, right there!
M-More... on my clit!
I-I'm coming!
Now it's my turn.
Okay.
Oh my...
It's huge! Just like how I want it.
Not yet.
Here we go.
I knew it was just a dream.
Another wet dream.
Shit! I wanna have sex!
Shizue-san...
What a nice pair of tits!
I can see her nipples.
Mature Woman Desire
Bondage
It's been a week already...
Nice to meet you...
I'm from the next door.
We're the Mizukami family.
Thank you. You even bothered greeting us yourself.
Just tell us whenever something bothers you.
Hey Masaru, come greet our guest!
O-Okay...
I'm Masaru. Nice to meet you.
What should I do with this kid.
You see, this kid hasn't been enrolled for two years.
He's self-studying at home
instead of going to a prep school.
Cut it out.
When do you plan to get in college?
Well then, I'll be on my way.
Masaru-kun.
Y-yes?
Let's get along with each other.
Wow, I think she's around F-cup.
I fell for her breasts since the first time we met.
I want to dive on those breasts!
Well then, I'll be on my way.
She also has a nice ass!
From that day...
We frequently end up bumping into each other.
And she will always give
a gentle smile back on me.
I wanna do it!
Masaru, breakfast is ready!
Ahh, I'm tired!
I shouldn't do something like this...
Ahh, I want to take a peek!
S-Shizue-san?!
W-What a nice pair of tits!
Does being tied up feel good?
Your nipples got hard already.
That isn't true.
I wonder about that... How about here?
Whose dick did you have in here?
I-I didn't do such a thing!
I just received a package earlier.
Did you do something?
I-I didn't do anything!
T-That's...
You haven't used a vibe, right?
I'll punish you with this.
No!
Now, open your mouth. I'll let
you have a taste of it first.
This thick thing will be going in your pussy.
Lubricate it well.
Okay, it should be okay now.
Please, anything but that!
You're only saying that now,
but soon you'll be feeling good.
Despite what you say, it slid in easily.
How is it? I'm gonna make you feel even better.
I-It's hitting me deep inside!
D-Don't push it deep inside!
What are you saying? You're starting to get drenched.
There, there. How about there?
No! P-please don't do that!
H-How cruel...
Does it feel that great?
Deep, deep, we push it in.
And something good will come out.
Please stop saying it. It's embarrassing.
Well then...
Keep it inside you.
I can't...
Please take it off.
Lick it.
Here, lick it and make it hard.
I don't want to.
Just do it.
Here, lick it well and make it hard.
Do it!
Shizue-san...
After you're done licking
the shaft, lick the tip next.
That's it, groom it using your tongue.
You're doing great. Now suck the whole thing.
Suck it up to your throat.
It might choke you 'til you get
used to it, but bear with it.
There, just like that.
Here, let me have a good look before I put it in.
No...
Stop staring on it.
I'll be putting it in.
How is it? Does it feel good?
Stop! Please pull it out!
You're body says the opposite.
Just tell the truth, you whore!
That isn't true! I am not a whore!
Don't lie on me!
Okay, let's get to the next round.
N-No!
Please stop!
You'll see everything!
Please stop, it's embarrassing.
No.
This is my favorite view.
I won't let anyone else have it.
Your pussy is dripping wet already.
No!
Does it feel good?
Now, raise your butt up.
Don't do it behind!
I can see your asshole well.
No! Don't look!
It's embarrassing!
I'll be putting it in.
Don't!
There!
Nooo!
How is it? How is it?
There! There!
Good...
More...
Deeper...
Okay, okay...
Okay, Shizue...
There... right there!
Good... Feels good!
I'm gonna come soon, Shizue!
Let's come together!
I'm coming too!
C-Coming!
That was great, darling.
I love you, Shizue.
I love you too.
Who's there!
It's just a cat...
Thank heavens...
Let's hit the sack.
Okay.
Masaru, I already made you
breakfast. Don't forget to eat it.
I heard you! Just go already.
Take care, darling.
I wonder what's with that last night...
I can't understand women.
I wanna have sex already!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project