Ahhhh...
That's good.
Yes! Right there!
Does it feel good?
Don't stop!
Keep going, just like that.
Okay.
More! Lick my clitoris more!
Right there!
That's good! More!
I'm cumming!
Okay then, it's my turn now.
Okay.
Oh my.
It's so big.
Just the kind I like.
Not yet.
Alright then, here I go.
Of course that was a dream...
I came again...
Shit, I wanna have sex already!
Shizue-san...
Her tits are amazing!
I can even see her nipples!
Desire for a Mature Woman
KINBAKU BONDAGE
It's already been a week, huh?
Nice to meet you.
My name is Mizukami. I just moved in next door.
Thank you for coming all the way here to greet us.
If you need anything, please let us know!
Masaru, come and say hello!
Oh...
I'm Masaru. Nice to meet you.
What am I going to do with you?
He's still trying to get into college.
He doesn't even go to prep schools
and just stays home to study.
Get off my back.
When are you going to get into college?
Well then, you must excuse me.
Masaru-kun?
Yes?!
It was nice meeting you.
W-Wow, she might even be an F-cup.
I fell in love with those tits from the first time I saw them.
I wanted to drown myself in them!
Alright, goodbye.
Her ass is amazing too!
And then we started seeing a
lot of each other around town.
And she would always return my
smile with a kind one of her own.
I wanna have sex so bad!
Masaru! Food's ready!
I'm beat.
Should I really be doing this?
I'm so curious!
Ah, whatever!
Shizue-san?!
Her bust is amazing!
Does it feel good to be tied up?
Your nipples are getting rock hard.
That's not... true...
Really now?
What about down here? Who was the
last person to put their thing in here?
Nobody! There was just a delivery, that's all.
No, something happened.
N-Nothing happened!
Th-That's...
This is your first time with this, huh?
I'm going to punish you with this.
No!
Okay, open your mouth.
I'm gonna have you taste it first.
This thick thing is gonna go inside your pussy.
Make it wet.
Alright it should be good to go.
Please, anything but that!
Resist all you want right now.
You're gonna feel good soon.
It went in pretty easily considering you didn't want it to.
I'm gonna make you feel even better.
It's hitting me so deep!
Please don't put it so deep inside me!
What are you saying? The juices just keep pouring out.
Come on. What about here?
No!!
P-Please...
Please forgive me!
This is horrible.
G-Good...
Oh? It really feels that good, huh?
It keeps taking it deeper and deeper. It's very impressive.
It's embarrassing. Please don't say that.
Now then...
Don't take it out, got it?
I can't do that! Please take it out!
Lick it.
Lick it and get it up.
No.
Just do it!
Now lick it and make it big.
Do it!
Shizue-san!
Lick around the glans and then lick the tip.
That's good. Get all of that right
there with your tongue too.
Excellent. Now swallow it.
Take it in, all the way to your throat!
It'll hurt until you're used to it, but just bear with it.
Good, just like that.
Now, before I put it in, show me.
Don't look at it.
Okay, time to put it in.
How is it? Good?
Stop! Please take it out!
That's not what your body's saying!
Spit it out, you fucking prostitute!
No! I'm not a prostitute!
Don't lie to me!
Alright, straddle me.
No...
Please stop!
You can see everything!
It's so embarrassing. Please stop!
Nope.
This is my favorite view.
I won't give it up to anyone.
You're very wet down there too.
No!
Feels good, huh?
Now stick your ass out!
Not from behind!
I can even see your asshole perfectly.
No! Don't look!
It's so embarrassing.
Okay, I'm putting it in.
N-No!
Here!
Feel good? Does it feel good?!
Here! Take this!
G-Good...
More... deeper...
Good girl.
That's good, Shizue.
There... Right there!
It feels good! So good!
I'm about to cum, Shizue!
L-Let's...
Let's cum together!
I'm about to cum too!
I-I'm cumming!
Thank goodness, Dear.
I love you, Shizue.
I love you too.
Who's there?!
What? A cat?
That was close.
Alright, let's sleep.
Right.
Masaru!
I made food. Make sure you eat it, okay?!
Yeah, I know already!
Just go already!
Have a good day, Dear.
What was that yesterday?
I don't get women.
I wanna have sex already!!
translation: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4c4t
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч