Huh? A boyfriend?
Yeah.
I could get one at any time if I wanted to.
But I don't think there's any need to be in a hurry.
Until I find someone I like.
Yeah.
Right?
That's what I say, but I have a secret.
PURE-HEARTED GIRL ET CETERA
Presented by Erobeat | http7/www:erobeat.net | #erobeat@ irc.rizon.net
Translation: May | Timing: vltouch | Typeset &<Encode: ShocWave
VQfflfiffl®  $é 1Ø0Ô  GfflHt3^fflfflefflSIIU<3
Please Master, put your penis inside my dirty butt.
You're asking for anal sex? What a pervert.
Master's penis is going so deep into my butt.
Amazing, Rumi. Your butt hole is so tight.
Thank you. I'm your meat toilet.
My butt, breasts, and pussy...
Please use them however you want.
You're talking dirty to make yourself excited, right?
Y-Yes...
i'm excited, even though this is my
first time taking it in from behind.
Come on, you want more, right?
Beg me!
Please Master, I want more... In my ass-pussy!
Go wild!
Oh boy, you're such dirty girl.
Your nipples are so excited from anal sex!
I'm sorry... I'm a pervert.
My nipples are so hard, and my pussy is so dripping wet.
It can't be helped. I'll ravage all your naughty holes.
I'm so happy, Master.
That's it, you're doing well.
You want more of my cock, right?
Make it excited, alright?
Oh no, I get excited just by sucking his penis.
Just by thinking that this will go inside of me...
Just thinking about it gets me so wet!
Yes! That feels good...
This position makes it go even deeper towards my womb.
It's feels so good...
Don't just have fun yourself but make sure
your pussy squeezes my penis, okay?
Yes, I will...
I'll make sure to squeeze hard,
so please rough up my pussy.
Oh, no. Why do I get so excited by being treated roughly?
Maybe I really am a pervert.
No... No... Master, I'm sorry.
My pussy is so excited... I'm going to cum!
All right, where do you want me to splatter my cum?
Anywhere is fine to me.
Please cum anywhere you like.
All right, then I'm going to splatter it all over your body.
Thank you very much.
Please cover my naked body with your sperm!
Cum lots!
All over mel
How do you like it, Rumi?
Having my sperm all over your body?
It's amazing. Your cum milk is so hot and thick...
So much of it came out.
How many times did I cum?
don't think I can live without this any more.
Baibu = Vibrator I Onahole = Masturbation Hole
This is called Trance BO.
It stands for Trance Baibu and Trance Onahole.
You just meet others on the Internet
and masturbate together.
That was good, Rumi-chan.
Let's do it again sometime.
Yeah, when I'm free.
All right, talk to you later.
I can take on different personalities since
we don't see each other's face.
With Eizi, we play master and naughty sex slave.
With Borocky...
Oh boy, your penis is so hard.
You must be really excited, Borocky.
When I imagine Ane-san is touching me, I...
Hey, you can see my cunt clearly from there, right?
Oh, I can't hold back... I want to lick and touch it
Okay, I'll let you lick it today.
Let's lick each other.
So this is what Rumi-neesan's blowjob feels like.
Oh, crap. If you do it so erotically, I'm gonna cum.
You can't. You haven't made my pussy feel good yet.
Here, I'll swing my hip for you.
Make your penis harder!
My penis throbbing. I'm going crazy!
Go ahead and go crazy.
Imagine a girl putting your penis between
her breasts and shaking them around.
How naughty is that?
Ane-san, my hips are moving on their own.
That's fine, I can't control mine either.
You can thrust harder if you want. Come on, harder!
Wow, it feels so intense..
Your penis is going wild inside me.
Your pussy is hot and tight.
Almost like my penis is going to get taken away.
My dirty pussy is so gushingly wet.
I can t get away from your penis.
I can't hold it in! I'm going to cum!
Wait! I'm going to cum too!
Please cum inside mel
I've reached my limit.
Sheesh, how undisciplined.
I am not completely satisfied yet.
I'm sorry, Ane-san...
Today, I am having fun cybering as usual.
Actually, the Trance BO has been discontinued.
So I am using a social networking site.
Oh, Daiku san!
Hello Rumi-san, is now okay?
Yes, sure.
Honestly, I'm tired, but I can't turn him down.
Because he was the first man I did this with.
Actually, we were both new to the website.
It was fate, wasn't it?
If it weren't for him, I wouldn't have been doing this.
Have you started already, Daiku-san?
Yeah, sorry...
Actually, I've taken off both my bra and underwear, too.
You know, I am rubbing my wet
pussy with the BO right now.
I am switching my personality from wild to lovely.
Then, I'm going to put it in now.
Okay, put it in.
I love your penis, Daiku.
Daiku-san, you're starting off so wild!
I cant help it after hearing your naughty voice.
The good thing about this vibrator is that
cant fully control its movements.
It synchronizes the guy's movement, so it makes
you feel like you're actually having sex.
I can only do things like this on my
days off, so I'm extra excited.
The person I am talking to wants my body badly.
Okay, my pussy is excited too.
Lets feel good together.
This switch is not for me.
This switch activates the vibrator on his onahole.
Rumi-san, your pussy is clenching against my penis.
Yeah, we're connected.
Daiku-san, please do it harder!
While in the heat, I'm completely
immersed in the virtual world.
Do you understand?
My penis is deep inside of you.
No, Daiku... Not that...
No! I'm going crazy!
What are you saying, Rumi? Didn't you want this?
When were excited, we drop honorifics
and call each other by name.
He really likes this virtual world, too.
My body becomes hot and I feel naughty
when he gets into the mood.
Daiku, I'm holding your penis between my breasts.
You like this, right?
I wouldn't be able to say something
like that if I was with him in real life.
Oh, no. Am I using this too much?
It's got warmer.
Just like the real thing.
Do you feel it, Daiku?
Does my titty-fuck make you feel good?
It's amazing. Almost as if my penis were
to be taken away by your breasts.
Huh? What are you saying?
In return, I will touch your breasts from behind.
The truth is, you're cumming soon, aren't you?
Or did you cum already?
Yeah, I came many times already.
I'm happy to hear that.
All right My pussy is all yours, Daiku.
You can be rough with itl
Well then, I'm going to do just that.
Its a little embarrassing, but I talk dirty on purpose.
Even though we cant see each other,
want him to get really excited.
Your cunt is hot and getting tighter again.
You must be really feeling it.
Yeah. I'm sorry, my nipples and clitoris are so excitedl
It feels so good!
I'm reaching my limit I'm going to cum again.
That's okay, Daiku.
My pussy is hot and excited.
Let's... Let's cum together!
Where do you want to finish?
Inside. I want to cum inside of you.
All right, go ahead.
Cum inside my pussy... In my womb...
Splatter your cum inside!
Make me pregnant!
Rumi, I'm cummingi
Me too...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I came, I came again with all I had.
I heard some surprising news.
Huh? Daiku-san, you're actually a student?
I'm sorry, I told you I was a doctor,
but I didn't want to lie to you any more, Rumi-san.
A student?
So he s just like me.
Rumi-san?
Then how did you get your hands on the BO?
They've been discontinued for some time.
My brother moved out, so I use his old room now.
Then I found it among the stuff he left.
That's exactly what happened to me.
Can this be fate?
don't remember what happened
afterwards, since I was so happy.
I wonder which school he attends.
Could it be this one?
Oh, no. I can't wipe the smile off my face.
Maybe I'll tell him more about myself next time.