Um...
Why me?
That again?
But... I'm plain, and not very cute either...
Haven't I told you honestly over and over again?
I like beauties senior to me...
ones that look more mature.
Do I look that much like an adult?
It's touching me...
No way, are penises this hot?
Or could it be... that I'm weird?
No, but...
There's never been anything good that
happened because I look like an adult...
So, it would've been better if
I didn't fall in love with you?
No, I'm happy about that.
Are you alright?
It's fine if you move...
Then, I'll start slow...
Amazing, it's like my insides are being stirred around.
I'm really having sex right now...
Does it still hurt?
I... I don't know...
It's tingling down there, and my
body somehow feels hot...
You're insides are getting drenched...
You're feeling it.
Liar! There's no way that's...
No! St-stop!
No, there are lewd sounds coming from down there...
It's my first time, but I'm getting
more and more perverted!
Amazing, it's really tight!
I think I might be cumming soon...
His penis is twitching..
Yuuto-kun is feeling good inside me...
Konomi!
Please! You can let it out like this...
So please... Let's cum together!
I'm... going to...
Translation, Snake | Timing, Typeset, Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | httpy/www.erobeat.net| #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
I'm Kuramochi Konomi.
My hobbies are... handicraft and reading.
And... I like cooking, too.
I'm not an amazing person, but...
Nice to meet you and please treat me well.
At first glance, she was quite plain.
Perhaps she was worried about being too tall.
She stood a little stooped over and bent forward.
But it rang a bell for me.
They say that these kinds of girls
become really sexy adults.
What is it?
Sorry for staring.
Kuramochi-san, right?
I'm...
Jounouchi Yuuto-kun.
I heard it during the self-introduction earlier.
I see.
Well, seine we sit next to each other let's get along.
Nice to meet you.
Konomi-chan.
Yes! Nice to meet you, too!
She's really a pure-hearted girl.
Looks like she'll be a tough catch.
Although with that said, that's all we've ever talked.
It'd help if there was some kind
of event to help us get closer..
Th-This must be...
A God-given opportunity!
Konomi-chan!
Yes?
This is sudden, but will you go out with me!?
Yes.
Really!?
You're talking about eating lunch, right?
In Japanese, to go out with someone and to keep someone company is said the same way.
No, not that... I mean, be my girlfriend.
So we started going out, and after several dates...
We began our intimate relationship.
Hey, can you lift your hair up for me to see?
Is this all right?
Wow, it's really good!
Like a beautiful secretary.
Geez, do you like it this much?
Konomi likes this too, right?
Not there...
See, your body says you like it.
No, don't say it in such a lewd way...
Well, should I stop then?
Don't, you meanie...
I'll do anything.
If Yuuto-kun wants it I'll do it, so please...
Is that so...
Konomi..
Try saying, "Please lick my perverted pussy."
That's a little...
You said you'd do anything, right?
C'mon, hurry, hurry!
Please lick... my perverted pussy...
Konomi...
No! It's dirty down there...
That's not true at all. It's really tasty.
No, it's embarrassing...
Yuuto-kun likes things like this?
Yeah, I might like this.
I'm bein licked...
A girl's most embarrassing place
is being looked at so closely...
Please...
My perverted anus... Please tease it lots!
Yes, yes, that's right.
No, don't!
Don't tease my but thole so much...
m, don't be like that.
I just did what you said earlier.
I'm... a pervert who gets off...
from my butthole being violated!
Please tease Konomi's butt., my butt-pussy...
Please tease it lots!
W-Why?
Doing such things Is so embarrassing but...
I'm tingling so much down there!
It's about time. You want it here as well, right?
No, don't...
Not both at the same time...
Don't! No!
I'll go crazy!
Go on and cum like this!
Cumming... I'm going to cum!
Cumming... cumming... cumming...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Are we really going to do it here?
C'mon, hurry, hurry!
I'm... naked outdoors and masturbating...
But that feels good, right?
I'm sorry... I can't stop anymore.
My pussy is soaked...
And my nipples are this hard...
For the pure Konomi to become such a pervert...
But... but... It's Yuuto-kun's fault.
Making me do lewd things all the time...
can't take it anymore!
Please... Yuuto-kun, together...
Sure. But in exchange, beg me lots again.
More! Please do me more!
With Yooto-kun's  thick cock
Please mess up my dripping pussy as much as you want.
Please mess me up!
Amazing! It's squeezing really tight!
What do I do? I've never done this before.
I get nervous when I think that we
might be seen by someone...
It's so exciting!
If you let your voice out too much, we'll really be noticed!
No... No...
If that happens, I'll be raped by everyone!
My boobs, my butt and my pussy... all of them...
I don't want that to happen!
Then, I'm going to let it out soon!
Konomi!
Please, please end it quickly!
You can let it out inside...
You can spurt it all in my pussy!
It's coming... It's coming!
I had arrived at an ecstasy.
I wanted so see more and more of the slutty
her, and thought of nothing but sex.
However...
No way...
That's..
Of course, I didn't notice this at all...
Huh?
Like I said, um...
We should give each other some space
and think about some things.
Why?
I'm sorry!
The week following that, I hardly got to talk to Konomi...
One Week Later
Ko-Konomi!?
my perverted game from now?
Yuuto-kun, will you follow along in
G-Game?
Right now I'm going to give your rotten dick a reward.
If you can resist ejaculation, I grant you a wish.
But if you cum, you have to grant one of my wishes.
How's that?
K-Konomi...
But it might be hard for Yuuto-kun who thinks
of nothing except perverted things.
Usually she'd never suck on it unless I ask her...
What happened?
That's right, Konomi is trying to convey something to me.
Come on, think!
You're holding back quite well. Then how about this?
A foot job. This is your first time right?
Yuuto-kun likes new things, right?
It's true...
Are you feeling it from your penis being stepped on?
Mr. Pervert.
But... But, it's that Konomi who's giving me a foot job!
I'd be excited it even if didn't want to!
It's fine. You can cum whenever you want.
Let out all your sticky semen!
This clumsiness...
This is bad... it actually ends up feeling really good...
See? Your penis is twitching badly.
You wanted to see me doing perverted
things like this, right?
I won't cum!
I'll win this game and... we'll once again...
Why aren't you cumming...
Yuuto-kun... We haven't done it in a week...
I want you so badly... I can't control myself!
Konomi?
Mr. Pervert, good job holding back.
As a reward... I'll let you use my pussy.
Konomi is actually pushing herself and acting...
Today's a safe day, so go ahead and let it out inside me.
K-Konomi...
Why... Why are you doing such things!?
But, you say you like mature girls..
Because you like making me say... perverted things.
So, it's embarrassing... But I...
I can't take this anymore!
After seeing such a cute you, there's
no way I can hold back anymore!
What are you saying...
I finally realized.
Though I had so much sex with you because
I wanted to see your lewd face.
I like the cute you right now the most.
No... You can't...
Today... I have to make Yuuto-kun cum!
I... won't just have sex... like an idiot anymore!
I'll go out with you properly!
Going to see movies, or going for a walk in the park...
That means..
I... want to start over with you!
Yuuto-kun...
Amazing... I really like Yuuto-kun after all..
If it's Yuuto-kun then no matter what
kind of embarrassing things...
This is bad... I'm almost at my limit!
It's fine. Let it out lots!
Inside me... Inside Konomi's pussy...
Let it all out!
So, how did it turn out like this?
But... I saw...
Last week...
Yuuto-kun was at the shopping districts.
Last week?
When my Sis came back?
Sis? You mean your sister?
Could it be that you misunderstood something?
I'm sorry!
I just...
Wanted to win the game and say that I
wanted to be with Yuuto-kun forever!
Oh well, I did lose the game.
Plus, I'm weak since I'm in love with you.
I'll grant your wish.
Yuuto-kun...