Wow, as expected the kebab sandwiches
at Akihabara have a trustable quality!
Is it that different?
Well in general if it's sold in a proper store it tastes good,
but you can still compare them through
price and how well done it is.
I see...
Aren't you hungry by the way?
You haven't eaten anything.
If I skip lunch, I'll be able to buy another book.
Okay, have some of mine.
Eh?
If I'm the only one eating, it's kind of like
I'm inconsiderate or something, right?
Wow, we've found some good stuff today.
Telephone card with new drawing that
only comes with the first release!
Where am I supposed to use this nowadays!?
An Earnest Girl... or so I Thought?
But then, your goods are quite amazing, too...
It's like the whole collection of Fetish Erotic
Manga and Erotic Games on the market.
I'm glad I managed to get this banned one today... the
reviews weren't too good, but I really like the artist.
Oh, I played the sequel of that one, it was pretty good.
But hey, I'm amazed you can buy something
tagged humiliation in front of a girl.
Well, I wouldn't have lived for the past six
years if I didn't have that kind of sense.
What?
Well then, there's one more place I wanna drop by.
So hang around for just a bit more.
Wow, as expected from the largest store
in Japan. They have everything...!
Tanaka... you're buying something?
How does Ebikawa think of something like this? Not bad?
I don't know... Just buy what you want...
Oh my, so you're not very comfortable
with shops like these?
Um, how do I put this... um... sexy lingerie isn't
really my thing... well bondage is alright.
Yeah... you really do like bondage . almost all
of the manga you bought today had that...
Huh?
Th-Then... how about stuff like this?
Ta-Tanaka... You were wearing this... all day?
Yeah... I was wearing it.
The fabric doesn't exactly breathe well so it's kinda...
Did you buy this at this store?
No... I bought it online...
It's hard to buy these at an actual store...
Um, this... the upper part is...
Sorry, I got a little too excited.
Woahah! Tissue, tissue!
Dude, what are you trying to do? Badger's Game?
Bad-ger-game?
Err, it's a type of fraud using beauty or sex to rob money.
What would rob from person who even
saves his lunch money for manga?
I guess you're right...
Uh... so ... I mean... um... that...
I... want to... to... to... to have sex. Yeah.
Ever since summer vacation, the girls in my class
have been chatting about doing it or not doing it,
that it hurts or it doesn't,
or that it feels good or it doesn't,
all that endless girly girl talk.
I'm at my limit I can't resist anymore.
I want to accomplish and attain that pleasure, too!
I'm okay with the copulating part but,
though I might not want to say this,
there's plenty of men out there...
Because it seemed like you'd do it.
Huh?
I really like genres with housewives, you see...
Well, you talk about erotic stuff in class
with a straight face and stuff...
I really like genres with housewives, you see...
Besides, you're probably a virgin, right?
I thought if I did some erotic stuff even
someone like me could get you to...
I guess... that's true...
Well, I was planning to negotiate a bit more smartly so...
So um, let me redo it...
Please have sex with me.
Um, a question about your b-boobs...
What?
Are the nipples usually this hard?
Usually they're not...
I was being more conscious of them... because of
the clothing..and they rubbed when I walked...
So... they're a little...
Um, does it feel good?
Being touched is... how should
I put it... um, not... bad...
Woah, it's getting hard.
Of course it's gonna get hard...
Woah... amazing... it's hot... and hard!
I think... the tip is getting wet...
So guys get wet, too...
Huh? Oh, it really does.
Over here, too...
Something like this?
Ah, it still hurts when you tease it directly.
So um, squeeze? Try using the labia majora...
Like this?
Yeah, something like that...
Woah... this could be bad...
No... inside...
No... this is... bad...
Coming... something's...
Just now... was that "cumming"?
Okay, let's try doing the actual take.
But... before that...
Just one more thing...
Done! Well then...
The cowgirl position already!?
I read some kind of "How to" article that
said that this is a good way to do it.
You don't realize how large it is until you try to put it in...
Is this normal?
Dunno... never really compared
sizes of erect penises before...
Here... here I go.
Ow... owww...
What's with this, it hurts like heck!
Should I pull it out?
No... we can't turn back anymore...
Um, my hips... can you... pull them down for me?
I'm so scared I can't do it...
Sure but...
Wait, wait, after a countdown from three...
Three...
Two...
One!
Ouch!
Huh? Zero I ? God, I'm so sorry!
It's... fine... it’s kind of... my fault...
There... it's really inside me... woah...
So um... some bad new...
I’m gonna cum.
Hey, um wait! We don't have a
rubber! I have to pull out or...
Now we've done it... raw and creampie...
Classical uncontrolled lust of the young...
Um, isn't this bad?
Well at least it's a safe day for me...
So virgins look at that kind of stuff, too?
If you keep track, you won't stain your panties
when your period jumps out suddenly...
Um, so...
A couple of more times would still be okay?
Huh? Um, yeah.
Wait...
Your penis is... twitching...twitching again...
More... I want to let out more...
No...
No more... I'm... already...
The insides are slippery and...
squeezing... this is really bad!
Inside... too much... semen... this is...
So much...
No way... I'm gonna cum... no...
This is bad... my body is...
Me, too...
No, it's coming, coming!
No...
What do I do... I think I'm falling in love with you...
What is this...
It's probably the phenomenon called imprinting...
Hey, hey... this time...
Showing you how I masturbate is
embarrassing enough already...
And yet you're making me use this kind of toy...
Does that actually go in?
I'm more worried about the water proof than its size...
It's going in...
What is this... my insides are throbbing...
So it feels good?
Yeah... really good...
Feels like I could cum already...
Well, next up this this guy...
Ah what should I say. it's got a terribly
heinous movement there...
Should we stop?
No, let's do it We bought it together... after all...
It's fine. I washed my butt properly, too.
Won't see a thing even if you looked inside.
The rotor stays inside?
Yeah... the erotic animation I
watched did it like that so...
For now, let's leave it like this.
Well...
It's cold!
It tickles... the hole... my butt hole is wet and...
Well it won't go in unless we get it wet...
But... this is... if you stir it that much...
Looks like it'll be okay now...
It's coming it... it's coming!
No... This is... don't!
My insides are... being stirred up... I’ll... I'll go crazy!
Woah, this is amazing... what kind of erotic
game is this? You're like a dog...
Be quiet! Don't act like you're not excited or anything!
Hurry and come...
Put it inside already!
Well, as you wish...
Could it be that you... came from that just now?
Yeah... I came...
The rotor and the vibrator and your
penis... all rubbing together...
Woah... your insides are throbbing...
the vibrator is kinda... in the way...
Hey, try moving... I'm curious
about what would happen...
This could be... really bad...
My insides are being... messed up... completely...
It doesn't hurt or anything?
No, I'm okay...
Feels like you're trying to kill me...
but still it feels kind of... good!
This... what if someone sees this...
What's with that... if you say something
like that... I'd just feel more...
Gumming...
Ah, it's just as strong as the pleasure you feel...
The misery of having to wipe your own secretion...
I'm done cleaning the table and chair.
It's been an hour already!?
The class is going to be back!
Eh!? Wait, my panties, where are my...
The toys, the toys...
My panties!
Well, in celebration of the end of the finals and work...
Karaoke
Cheers!
Well, about one person is still working hard...
Shut up! Just don't spill your alcohol on my work.
Dude we need it at the print shop my tomorrow!
Alcohol huh... I guess cocktails would be okay...
Today I'm definitely gonna make some impressions
with some good songs or interesting small talk.
As the only girl in the manga study club...
I can't be left forgotten like this...
I need to pick something that can be appealing...
and yet does not ruin the current atmosphere...
This choice will also affect my impression as a person...
Arihara, sorry, but can you pass the remote for a bit?
Sorry for holding on to it for so long...
Calm down, it's fine. this is all natural...
That's right, let's calm down with some alcohol...
I'm so sorry!
isn't this a wrong song?
Huh? Ah, stop the video, stop the video!
No... I over did the relaxing part...
and my mind is going blank...
I can't think straight... any... more...
Um, wait!?
Didn't you hope something like this would happen!?
Hey um, please stop... please stop
with the boobs! Not the boobs!
Don't worry! It's not like I'll lose something...
Guys, please help...
Um... what should I say...
If you try to solve everything by
force... it won't work out...
C’mon, you haven't drunk at all! Are you okay?
If I get drunk... I won't be able to...
I see... it must be hard for you...
Well, then I shall...
Huh?
Let's do more fun things.
Um, wait, this is bad, right?
Huh? Why? Why, why, why?
"Why" you ask...
In general boys like boobs, don't they?
I bet you guys want to do it, don't you?
I want to do it.
Hey... there aren't security cameras
or anything in this store are there?
Don't worry, there wouldn't be stuff like
that such a cheap store like this.
Huh, so despite what you say you're hard...
Well if you give me that kind of excitement...
It’s... in...
Woah, I'm soaked as well... I can't stop this...
Hey... this is bad...
Huh? Don't tell me it doesn't feel good?
You're way too rough! No... pull it out, pull it out!
It's fine, if you want to cum then let it out!
Inside... as deep as you can go!
My boobs... just might feel good...
Cumming... cumming, cumming!
It's coming out... semen is flowing...
Arihara... me too?
Go ahead...
Come...
Creampie already?
Woah, my turn now?
That one doesn't count... this time I'll do it properly.
No... semen is being... stirred around inside...
My insides are... completely messed up
Well, I'll take this side.
Wow, you're squeezing real tight!
Woah... I’m in a gangbang...
This is bad... I’m getting really
turned on! I could go crazy...
Arihara... I’m cumming, too...
It's fine... everyone... give me your semen!
Having a dick in my pussy... in this
position... I can see it completele...
So lewd!
Hey... should we really be filming this?
Just think of it as data!
Instead of tracing stuff we get from
the Internet we can just use this!
And I get excited, too!
Woah, such a pervert...
I'm creampie you again...
I'm gonna cum, too....
So film me while I cum from a creampie! Film it! Film it!
Wha-what... what.
You told us to film it...
This was from the Karaoke the day before yesterday?
You don't remember a thing?
You went all-round full crazy...
Um, so...
About when is the next party we have?
What!?