Gatt...
Mariko.
Mariko. I will protect Mariko.
I will protect Mariko from the humans.
The super-weapon Gatt was chasing after
an impossible, hundred-year love.
I can feel it close by.
I won't be long. Just you wait.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: Nicolai | Edit: Collectr TS & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Ayanami
Hey, watch out!
The battle between Gatt and the
Allied Forces began last night.
Of the twelve divisions that were engaged,
eight were completely destroyed.
The Allied Farces have now retreated
to the Flaren Channel,
and the Eastern section of the continent
has fallen under Gatt's control.
This is the first footage of Gatt in twenty years.
Although it is an android created for defense
more than a hundred years ago.
modern weapons have found no means
of defeating this single robot.
This is truly the form of the demon that
is driving mankind to extinction.
Hey there, lady, nice outfit.
What are you looking for?
Machine fuel.
Lately, it’s been hard to find any,
even on the black market.
I'll sell far five times market price.
That said, if you let me squeeze those tits,
three times the market price will do!
It's been a long trip for me.
Before any bargaining, I want to take a shower!
All right, I'll let you shower as part of customer service.
What a dirty room. It reeks of a man.
Let's start with squeezing these tits!
After I shower!
I didn't think she was a cyborg...
I hate pushy guys.
Where's the shower?
Don't think you're the only one here.
Don't you tease me, now.
I didn't think you'd be so strong.
Tell me your name.
Mariko O'Brien.
Any negotiations come after the shower.
Mariko O'Brien?
So refreshing!
I'm really lucky to find a shower near the front line.
Hi!
Welcome home, Gatt!
MARIKO!
M-MARIKO!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Did you beat all the Allied Forces, Gatt?
It's okay. I killed every single one of them.
I will kill all humans for MARIKO.
All right, great!
In order for me to live happily with MARIKO forever.
I have to destroy everyone who
did horrible things to you.
Because you worked so hard. I'll give you a reward.
Are you happy, Gatt?
MARIKO...
Gatt! Gatt!
Gatt, does it feels good inside me?
It's the best, MARIKO.
D-Don't look!
Even if you tell me not to...
They're having sex.
My former body that is still synchronized with me...
is having sex with that machine
still obsessed with my ghost.
Yes. Yes.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes. Yes. Yes!
Yes! I'm cumming!
Gatt...
Gatt, you haven't cum yet, have you?
Are you still worried about Mariko?
Humans change, you know.
They're different from us.
She's no longer the Mariko you loved!
I may only be a personality program inserted
into the body she left behind...
but it's the personality of the Mariko who loved you.
I'm different from her.
I'll never change.
I can love Gatt forever!
I know.
Then it's all right, isn't it?
She'll come here soon.
Our Synchro Level is strong.
She's close?
When that time comes...
When that time comes, you have
to kill her without hesitation.
Got it.
The Allied Forces endured devastating
destruction from Gatt.
They retreated back to the Flaren Channel,
where Gatt chased them down and
completely destroyed them.
When you were going crazy earlier,
you mentioned "Gatt."
Who are you?
I'm sorry about earlier.
I guess there's no need to hide it anymore.
It seems like I'll be able to obtain
what I've been searching for.
Oh?
The uranium-concentrate fuel stick?
It's you.
Wh-What do you mean?
I've been looking for another cyborg
soldier with guts, like you.
Sorry, but it's a no for me.
You know, Gatt is in love with my previous body.
When I reacted earlier to my other synchronized body,
it was because Gatt was having sex with it.
I'm probably the only one who can defeat him now.
Why are you telling me so much?
Because I think you're necessary.
As I was travelling, I was always searching.
It's okay, isn't it?
It's gonna cost you.
That's fine.
Wow, you're really into it.
It's hard to believe that you had your
guard up against me earlier.
This is the only compensation I can give you!
N-No, not there!
What? Is that your weak spot?
N-No!
But wow, your body is really well made.
You're going to cum soon, aren't you?
Don't hold back.
I'll let you cum.
Oh, no. This guy is seriously too good!
I'm really going to c-cum!
Huh?
It's a shame.
I thought I'd be able to kill you for sure
if I struck while you were cumming.
I was cumming too, so my timing got messed up.
MARIKO!
Huh?
By MARIKO, you mean your previous body?
Even though Gatt said he'd kill you,
I'm not sure if he'll have the nerve once he sees you.
That's why I'll make you die here!
Those tits are stealing my soul!
Don't be so immature!
Enough of this nonsense!
MARIKO...
Where did you go, MARIKO?
Mariko, when your body was destroyed,
it was a mistake to digitally
reconstruct your personality, after all.
Mariko, I have something to ask you.
Yes?
Why do you have to go this far to defeat that demon?
Because it's my fault he went out of control.
Then why did you get rid of your old
body and replace it with this one?
If the specs are the same,
what's the point in replacing it?
It's a long story, so I'll tell you later.
Are they coming?
I have something to ask you, too.
Wh-What is it?
What's your name?
I-It's Koji. Takashima Koji.
A graveyard of weapons.
You escaped to a pretty suitable place.
A perfect place to die, far scrap metal like you.
Unfortunately, the one who's gonna die is you, MARIKO!
By amplifying my digitized brainwaves,
I can access other computer systems.
What do you mean, "brainwaves"?
Are you stupid or something?
You won't be able to raise a shield
while controlling those machines.
If you think you can avoid this,
then show me what you've got!
You're the foolish one.
That's the reason I'm here.
It'll hurt a bit, but try to bear it.
That armor is damn thick.
I'm not getting through much of it.
No, stop!
Stop.
Her back! She told me that pain doesn't synchronize!
MARIKO, can you hear me?
I'll spare you for today.
Please go back to Gatt and tell him,
"I'll definitely stop you."
Did she lie about the synchronization
so I would shoot without hesitation?
Still, what amazing willpower she has!
Seems like he's here to pick you up.
Mariko, you're not the Mariko I once knew.
Next time we meet, I'll reduce you to atoms.
I pity you, Gatt.
You can't feel your love for anything except a sex doll.
Phew, I was horrified for a moment.
It's only just started. Everything has only just started.
This is what Djii-chan and his friends
are making right now.
a nuclear super-weapon for defense.
In the near future, he and his children will bring the day
when war disappears from the whole world, for sure.
Gatt...
Um, earlier today, the military regime
that forced the President to resign...
has taken over almost all of the military
and government facilities.
Ojii-chan!
No! Stop it!
Master Taren, I'm Commander Jenny.
I'm here to make a report.
The stars...
What about the stars?
It's been a long time since I've felt this good.
I can see the stars clearly.
Was Mariko O'Brien captured?
I apologize. We're still searching for her.
However, we've obtained information
that she escaped into the old city.
Sooner or later, we'll be able to arrest her.
It has come, just as I thought.
Let's try using Caligula.
Caligula? The class-A war criminal?
You of all people should be able to use him.
Remember that, Commander Jenny.
Understood, sir.
Major! In fifteen minutes, we'll arrive at the
site of a small scale battle, Area JF5025.
Did you hear that?
So should we finish this quickly?
Your breath smells.
Please go easy on him.
I didn't know this included a shoulder massage service!
Hey, what was that for?
What? I was getting tired of those handcuffs.
Don't try anything funny, okay?
There's only one way a class-A war
criminal like you can stay alive.
All hands, get ready for combat.
I want the area under control ASAP.
Yes, ma'am!
Is the female target there?
Most likely. This time, we won't let her escape.
I have an old friend working at a junk store in that area.
I'll let him guide us around.
I'm going to land in advance.
But the target area is still far away.
I want to do this on my own.
Goodbye, you incompetent failures.
My sensor is picking it up.
The woman who single-handedly took
on a hundred-year battle with Gatt.
It's fascinating.
For a person who's preparing to die,
you seem quite relaxed.
Really...
Still, isn't this fun?
Maybe because I'm with you, Koji.
So am I the compensation for risking your life?
Something like that.
Well, I'll leave it to you.
The robot continues to kill,
towards an eventual end,
with only one goal, just one goal.
It never tires or considers the matter.
The flames from the burning wreckage
will one day fill the air.
The cities will disappear into the seabed.
Acid rain will rot everything away.
More than the blood of the fallen,
the storm of scrap metal wards them off.
Tims drags on.
The robot continues to kill,
with only one goal, just one goal,
forgetting even what it means to be tired.