The ship that was used for the field trip got hit by a storm.
All of the lifeboats were also capsized.
By some miracle, we drifted toward this island.
The girls who survived,
were infected by a strange virus,
and stated to become sexually aroused.
If left untreated, it will cause them to die of a heart attack.
According to Dr. Ichijou, treating the virus,
requires semen to be injected via impregnation.
Everyone resisted at first,
but ultimately their desire to live was stronger,
and eventually their bodies craved for it.
The teachers and classmates who mocked me before,
are now being humiliated by me, and it's so much fun.
Everyday, I get to rape and violate them,
using their mouths,
their pussies,
and even their asses.
I use all of it for my pleasure.
That's right.
I'm no longer the same as before.
I'm the only person who can save them all.
I'm their only savior.
# 2 MASTER'S VERY THICK DICK...
PLEASE FUCK MY PUSSY WITH IT!
A few months have passed since we drifted ashore.
All of the girls have changed completely.
Somebody, somebody please save us.
We're all stranded.
Please, somebody.
Sensei, can we really use that old rusty radio?
No, don't...!
We're now able to contact them.
Doing this while I'm trying to make contact is...
It's perfectly fine.
Let's have everyone hear your erotic voice.
No, stop...
If you fondle my breasts now...
It's, going to come out!
Oh no, my breasts are squirting.
No, please don't squeeze them.
Sensei, your pussy is gripping me tighter as your milk squirts out.
That's... don't say it...
I shouldn't be pregnant with my student's child, and yet...
This just shouldn't be...
My body just became more sensitive after it got pregnant.
My pussy feels good.
Now, now, we still have to communicate our situation.
E-Everyone, right now, I'm being raped right now.
I'm being fucked by my student, while getting all horny!
Please, save us!
Sensei, I'm the one who'll save you and your child.
By pouring in every last drop of my cum!
Please, Shouta-kun, cum with me.
I'm going to cum as well.
I'm going to cum hard too, so please...
Cum!
Make my pussy cum!
This won't do.
No matter how much I masturbate,
even if I plug my ass, it still won't stop!
The more I receive his cum, the more I crave for it.
It's really wet.
So you want me to insert it inside your virgin pussy.
There's no need for foreplay.
Please, just do it.
Insert it already!
It hurts...!
My pussy is tingling all over.
Your virgin pussy is twitching,
and it's trying to grip me tightly.
No!
My womb's being penetrated!
It feels hot, It feels hot!
I'm about to cum.
Here comes my cum!
I'm being impregnated.
It's my first time and I'm already going to be pregnant!
I'm going to bear your child!
It's pouring inside again.
M-My womb already feels full,
but it feels really good!
I'm getting really horny!
Your pussy is really hot,
and you were a virgin just a while ago.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Oh yes, this dick is great!
Stop, don't open my ass like that.
I'm really going crazy!
That won't do, I want to cum some more!
No, no more, or I'm going to lose it!
Please, let me be.
Finish it already!
Don't!
Oh no, I can't stop masturbating.
And my mouth feels like some sex toy.
His dick tastes so great that I can't part with it.
Hey, are we really going to do it?
Yeah, of course.
We're actually being filmed,
while having sex.
Rei, you have to act properly in front of the camera.
Hey, can you see it?
My pussy is completely sucking his sturdy dick in.
See? See? Look closer.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum inside right as you cum.
It's coming.
I'm going to get cummed inside while we do it raw.
Something good is welling up inside me too.
I'm about to...!
It's pulsating all over.
It seems your pussy isn't satisfied yet.
This is it.
We're just getting started.
Just keep on stirring my wet and wild pussy!
Your sloppy expression is perfectly captured by the camera.
I'm exposed like this, and yet I can't stop.
Your dick just feels too good, it's making me go crazy.
It feels great, Rei.
We're going to cum many times.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming again.
Your dick is also starting to twitch.
Please give me all of that white stuff.
Give me all of your cum milk!
It feels hot.
This is really exciting...
Getting fucked while you cum inside is the best.
However, Ichijou-san was the only one who was acting strange.
That's right.
She actually harbors a very big secret.
Stop that.
I said stop!
No!
Hmph, I guess it can't be helped now that I'm found out.
You're spot on.
Everything, was all an experiment for that virus which I created.
Then you know what this is, right?
This vial contains the concentrated form
of the virus that you have created.
Anyone who gets in contact with this virus gets horny.
What if we poured it directly inside?
I wonder what will happen.
N-No way... stop,
stop, stop...!
Stop that!
Why?
Wh-Why do I have to be...?
What are you saying?
We're all here to service our master.
No, no....
This isn't right!
This is just...
Amazing.
Your breasts... the nipples are getting really hard.
Everyone, you're all being manipulated...
This is crazy!
Why do I have to follow this boy's orders?
Master taught us the joys of being a woman,
and the delectable taste of a dick.
Don't...
Not my breasts too!
If you fondle my clitoris as well I'll...!
Ichijou-san, I think you should just let yourself go.
N-No...!
Stop, my body is becoming too sensitive...
I'm going... no...
No...!
If you really don't want it, shall I pull it out then?
No, don't pull it out.
Don't pull it out!
Your cum, I want it inside.
I want you to cum inside me!
You're not polite enough.
Come now, say it.
Master, master!
Master, please pour all your cum milk inside me!
It's been over a week, and now we are...
We are now...
Hurry up, Master.
I can't wait anymore.
Master, please put it in me.
I'm sure you're going to love it.
Master, use my pussy however you want.
Pleasure yourself with it.
Me too, I also think of Master very dearly.
So please, put it in me already.
Violate us, please.
I kind of want you all to plead more erotically, though.
If you will, Master, play with me
no matter if it's with my pussy,
or with my ass.
I can service you well,
with my mouth
or even with my breasts.
My entire body,
is now for you to play with.
You know, right?
I was a virgin not long ago.
So my pussy is sure to be nice and tight.
Look, it's already this wet.
My pussy is the only one that can satisfy Master.
My adult pussy.
Make a mess of me if you want.
So please savor every last bit of it, please!
I want it, Master.
I want your very thick dick to penetrate my slutty pussy.
And cum inside it!