The ship that was used for the field trip got hit by a storm.
All of the lifeboats were also capsized.
By some miracle, we drifted toward this island.
The girls who survived,
were infected by a strange virus,
and started to become sexually aroused.
I shouldn't do this in front of them, but my...
My body just became aroused, and I can't stop it.
No...
I already came many times with my pussy and ass,
but I still feel horny.
So, we really need to have this c-cum for this?
No way, I don't want this anymore.
Why do I...
Why must I have that ugly guy's cum inside me?
#1 Why do I have to be impregnated
by a monster like you!?
Ichijou-san, I still can't believe it.
Th-That my own cum is the cure for this virus.
But that is the truth.
As proof, I'm no longer feeling horny after taking
your cum inside me many times, right?
I-Indeed.
Cumming in my ass and mouth is good,
but cumming in my pussy is still the most effective.
But everyone says that they don't want my cum anymore.
All of them understand,
that if they don't receive cum at regular intervals,
they'll continue to become aroused,
and their bodies will keep craving for it.
If that continues, it'll eventually lead to a heart attack.
Then they'll die.
If Himura-san and the others had just been given cum in time,
then they wouldn't have died.
For us to survive, we need to gather more data about this virus.
Tell me how you administered cum on the girls, Shouta-kun.
Alright then.
It keeps on getting bigger.
I just did it for a while, and it's already...
Sensei, you're quite good at tit fucks.
It feels very good.
Experiment Sample #.1
Inoue Aoi
I really don't want to do this.
But I...
Suck it while keeping those tits rubbing, sensei.
I get it.
Sensei, you seem quite eager to do this.
Do you really want a dick that much?
Of course not.
I just want to finish this quickly.
Please, just cum already.
Sensei, I'm cumming.
N-No...
It already feels so embarrassing, and yet...
And yet I can't stop!
Experiment Sample #.2
Ouama Shiho
Amazing.
I never thought the class president would masturbate with her ass.
No, don't say that.
I-I'm being watched.
I'm completely exposed as I stir my own ass.
I'm willing to give you lots of cum,
if you show me more of your erotic side.
No way...
Oh no, oh no, oh no...!
What is this, I can't believe this...
Sh-Shiho-chan, I can't hold back anymore.
D-Don't say my name so casually.
I'm cumming...!
Don't look!
Your voice sure does sound erotic when you're doing that.
What's wrong?
Experiment Sample #.3
Kisaragi Rei
This is nothing!
Don't move from that spot.
This must be some sort of mistake.
It doesn't feel the slightest bit...
What did you just do?
It's all over my face!
It's okay.
I still have lots left.
Don't move around too much,
or it'll be a lot more difficult for you.
It stinks, I can't breathe, and it feels gross.
This is the worst.
He can still cum?
Just get on with it already!
I'm doing it again with him.
And we're even doing it here, outdoors.
Sensei, your pussy is already this wet.
N-No, this is...
It's just hot in here, so...
Ouch, don't fondle my breasts too much.
Oh, those two are...
No, we're going to be seen.
They're going to see us.
It's getting even tighter.
Are you feeling more aroused in this situation?
No way, that's not true!
Stop, don't pull my nipples like that.
Those two are just standing there.
Maybe they heard your moans just now.
No way...
Oh no, anything but...
I beg of you...
Please, let me be already.
It feels hot.
My asshole feels like it's melting away!
I see, so it's true that you feel more pleasure
when blindfolded like this.
My insides are being pushed aside,
and your dick is getting all twitchy.
We're not done yet.
It's so tight, that I can hear loud sloppy sounds as it rubs inside.
I don't want this, this is embarrassing!
It's because you're the one who's gripping me tightly.
You forced me into this position, that's why I...
The flesh inside your ass feels like it's trying to wrap around me.
My insides are gonna be pulled out of my ass!
It feels hot, it's hot!
My ass is all tingly, oh yes!
I'm going to cum again.
Fill me, pour all of your cum inside my ass.
S-Stop that.
Stop filming me in this embarrassing position.
That's not how you should plead to me.
Now, you have to ask me like I taught you.
If you don't, I'm going to cum outside again.
P-Please cum inside.
Come again?
I said, inside!
I'm telling you to cum inside me!
I don't really feel like cumming inside with the way you speak.
I beg of you, cum inside my pussy.
I can't hold back any longer.
I'm already itching for it.
I want you to cum inside my womb with your thick and big dick!
Oh, so you want me to cum inside that badly.
Yeah! I want your hard thing to let it all
out inside my slutty and wet pussy.
Now that you said that, I guess I'll
just have to really cum inside you.
And I'm going to record it all the way.
Just do whatever you want!
I'm going to do it with you as much as you want.
Then, as you wish.
Cum, while I cum inside you.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Okay, now I've properly recorded how I came inside you.
N-No...
Don't look, don't look.
Don't look at how I came...
That's good, Shouta-kun.
With this many experiment samples,
I think we can continue researching the virus further.
Ichijou-san, I'm...!
I-If you keep on hitting my womb like that,
I'll start to feel really horny.
Ichijou-san, please take this one as a sample too.
I'm happy, your movements are resonating inside my pussy,
that I'm about to cum from them.
Let's cum together, Ichijou-san.
I'm going to pour all of my cum into your womb.
M-My pussy is really moved.
Okay then, cum!
Pour all the cum that's built up inside your balls into me!
Ichijou-san, it's squeezing me really tight.
Shouta-kun, you shall be everyone's savior.
Your semen is the only thing that can cure them.
Me... a savior...