Later.
See you tomorrow!
That person was always sitting on
the same bench reading a book.
She's so beautiful.
Juvenile pornography
Juvenile pornography.
Excuse me, what book are you reading?
Huh?
O-Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
Oh, you're fine.
Sit right here.
O-Oh, okay.
I'll read to you.
O-Okay.
"Hey, let's have sex."
"The girl said, pulling up her skirt, revealing her
lower half that was once hidden underneath it."
"Before the boy opened a world of
women that he never knew before."
"Look, my pussy's already soaking wet."
"Hurry... It's dripping out of me."
"Shut my dirty mouth with your hard thing, big boy."
Um...
Is this...
An erotic novel?
Hey, if you'd like, won't you come over to my place?
I live just over there.
S-Sure!
Huh?
Um...
What's wrong?
You were looking to do something
dirty like this, weren't you?
B-But...
This is so sudden.
Is this your first time seeing a woman's naked body?
Yes.
You're as red as a tomato.
So cute.
Hey, would you like to touch them?
See? These are a woman's breasts.
They feel good, don't they?
Th-They're so soft and they're so hot.
That's right. I'm getting hot from the arousal.
A-Arousal?
You take off the last piece off of me.
Please, okay?
O-Okay!
A-Alright then.
S-So this is her...
This is a woman's...
Private part?
You're staring too much.
S-Sorry!
It's embarrassing if I'm the only one naked.
Let me see your naked body too.
R-Right.
Amazing.
It's already so hard.
So you really got this aroused from seeing my naked body?
Y-Yes.
I'm the same. I'm ready to go.
Bad boy. You shouldn't be going home with strangers.
B-But...
Have you ever been attacked by your mother?
Or maybe by a bad adult?
They'll teach you really bad things, you know?
Th-That... That feels so good!
Really?
I'm glad.
Then I guess I'll try a little harder.
So, do you know why I'm always
in that park reading a book?
Huh?
I wanted to play with a cute boy like yourself.
C-Cute?
You always stay behind after your friends leave, don't you?
My mom's always late home because of work.
No one's really ever home.
I just heard something nice.
Then how about we play at your house from now on?
M-Miss... If you keep doing it so rough, I'm gonna...
Let's do something like in the book.
Here, try reading starting from here.
Uh...
"S-She showed her voluptuous body to me,
not trying to hide even a single inch of it."
"She spread her legs with no shame at all,"
"and then began vulgarly rocking her hips."
Does this look like "no shame and vulgar"?
Huh? U-Uh...
So, can you see it all?
Can you see all of my voluptuous body?
I'm showing you my breasts and
pussy without hiding anything.
Y-Yes, I can see it!
I can see all of it!
Come on, keep reading.
Go on to the next line.
U-Um, "I-It was almost as if she was an animal in heat."
"She was just following her animalistic
instincts... she was craving sex."
That's right. I'm in heat.
My pussy is a dripping mess right now.
I'm craving sex.
"Having her stare at me as if I was some piece
of meat and she was a craven carnivore..."
"My dick became as hard as a rock..."
"And then I took my member and let it slide
into her fleshy hole like the prey I was."
I'm going to prey on you.
I'm going to use my pussy to swallow your rock hard dick.
M-Miss! Th-This is amazing!
This is good... This is so good!
Come on, keep reading.
R-Right.
"She moved her hips up and down lewdly."
"And continued to stroke my dick with her pussy!"
Okay, I'll stroke you lewdly then.
Just like this I'll rub and rub and rub your dick inside me!
Wow! Your dick is getting harder and bigger!
"Before her frighteningly sexy
body, I couldn't help but ask her..."
"E-Excuse me, are you always doing these kinds of things?"
That's my line next, right?
"Oh, yes, that's right."
"There's nothing but sex on my mind."
"I'm a dirty, dirty woman."
"Everything about me being a serious person was a lie."
"The truth is, I'm always craving a
dick and trying to get one inside me!"
"I'm a slave to the dick through and through!"
"Dicks feel so good!"
"They're so tasty! I really love the feeling
of having my pussy dug out by a dick!"
"I want to keep having sex for the rest of my life!"
M-Miss, I'm about to...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna... inside you...
Stop! Don't do it so... Don't do it so rough!
Cum! Cum!
You can be a little rough.
Just really, really mess up my pussy with your dick!
That's good!
More! More! Be rougher!
Mess me up good!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
M-Miss...
It feels so good...
Why... Why...
How did I get into this?
It's your fault for being such an easy guy.
I'm not at fault at all.
All I had to do was... pretend to be docile...
And then you came... running over to talk to me.
That's...
That's not good.
A cute guy like you...
Shouldn't be just giving out his dick this easily.
If you do, you're going to have every last drop from those
balls be sucked out by devious older women like me.
That... Right there... Don't!
What you have stored in here is for the
girl you fall in love with in the future.
You can't just be wastefully shooting
your stuff into a dirty slut like me.
B-But...
You're...
Come on, I'm going to get you to
shoot out your precious seeds.
You're going to shoot your seeds
out inside a perfect stranger!
S-Stop!
I-I'm gonna cum! My dick's gonna cum again!
Miss!
That's good! Cum! Cum!!
Shoot your cum out!
Shoot up this woman's... this dirty pussy with your cum!
It's coming! It's coming!!
It feels so good getting cummed in!
Thank you for this delicious meal of cum!
That was so good.
I came really hard too.
M-Miss?
You started saying things that weren't
in the novel about halfway through.
Aw, you found me out?
Okay, Miss, no one should be here right now.
S-So good! This feels so good!
I-If you're so rough like that all of a sudden, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna c-cum!
This is too...
No... I-I'm cumming!
Would you like to come over today?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч