See ya!
See you tomorrow!
She's always reading at the same bench every day.
What a beautiful woman.
Juvenile Pornography.
Umm... if I may, what are you reading?
I-I'm sorry.
I kinda sprung up out of nowhere.
It's all right.
Sit beside me.
Huh? O-Okay.
I'll read it to you.
Yes, p-please.
"Hey, let's have sex."
"The moment she uttered those words,"
"she discreetly lifts up her skirt,"
"revealing her bare crotch."
"At that time,"
"all he could fixate on were her overflowing love juices."
"See? My pussy is already sopping wet."
"Hurry, hurry while my juices are still overflowing."
"Fill up my naughty "mouth" with your thick thing."
Umm... is that, an erotic novel?
Hey,
would you like to come over to my place?
I live nearby.
Okay.
Umm...
What's wrong?
You were expecting something dirty like this, right?
But...
This is too sudden.
Is it the first time you've seen a naked girl?
Yes.
Your face is bright red.
So cute.
So, want to try touching them?
Here, these are a girl's breasts.
They feel nice, right?
Th-They're so soft,
and hot to the touch.
That's right.
My body is hot because I'm aroused.
A-Aroused?
Strip off the last piece for me.
Please.
Okay?
I-I will.
Well then.
So this is her...
A girl's... thing.
You're staring too much.
I-I'm sorry!
It's embarrassing if only I strip.
Come on, show-me-yours-too.
Huh? O-Okay.
Oh wow.
It's already so lively.
So you became aroused after seeing my naked body.
Yes.
Me too. I can't restrain myself any longer.
You shouldn't have done this,
letting someone take you along like this.
Th-That's because...
Didn't your mom teach you?
That bad grown ups,
are bound to teach something naughtier.
It... it feels good down there.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'll do it more, then.
Hey, do you know why I'm always reading my novel at that park?
I was looking for cute boys like you.
Cute boys?
You always go alone, even after your
friends have gone home, right?
My mom always comes home late because of work,
and I'm the only one at home.
Now that's music to my ears.
Well then, we'll play at your place next time, then.
Miss, if you keep rubbing it hard like that I'll...!
Oh, do you want to do something similar to that novel?
Here, try reading from this page.
Well...
"Sh-She, with her voluptuous body,"
"straddled me slovenly like a crab without hesitation."
"She then proceeded to bend it back and forth lewdly."
Slovenly and lewdly... so like this?
Huh? Umm...
So, can you see it well?
My voluptuous body, I mean.
I'm currently exposing my boobs and body, without hesitation.
I can see it.
I can see everything!
Go on, continue reading.
Read what happens next.
"It... it was as if she was a wild animal in heat,"
"fully immersed in the role, craving for sex."
That's right, I'm in heat right now.
My pussy is so drenched, and I'm craving for sex right now.
"She gazes at me with her misty eyes,"
"causing my dick to grow erect."
"And then, all that was left was to let myself
be devoured by her fleshy canal."
I'm about to devour you.
Your stiff dick is entering my pussy.
Miss... this feels... amazing...!
Wow... oh wow...
Come on, continue reading.
Okay.
"She continued lewdly rocking her hips up and down."
"Stimulating my dick further with her pussy."
Lewdly stimulate, right?
My pussy goes rub, rub,
rub, rub, rub.
Incredible. Your dick is getting even bigger and harder.
"Her amazing presence compelled me to ask."
"Do you always do this, miss?"
I'll read my lines next.
"That's right. All I can think about is sex."
"I'm a dirty slut."
"My nice girl image is just a facade."
"The truth is, I crave dicks. I'm always looking for one."
"Not a second goes by when I don't think about dicks."
"Dicks feel great."
"It feels great letting it grind all the way inside my pussy."
"I love it so much!"
"I want to have sex forever."
Miss... I can't keep up anymore...
Something's coming out.
Something's coming out of my dick.
Stop. Please... please no...!
Cum. Just cum.
It's okay if you're a bit rougher.
I want your dick,
I want it to completely fuck up my slutty pussy!
Oh yes.
Come on, slam it into me.
I'm going to cum, as well.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Miss...
It feels good.
So good.
Why? Why did all of this...
It's all because you're so easy to catch.
I didn't do anything bad.
I was simply enjoying myself in my natural habitat.
You're the one who approached me.
No...
How naughty.
A boy as cute as you,
exposing your dick to me like that.
If you do that, a lewd girl like me
will naturally squeeze out every last drop of semen from your balls.
No, not there... stop!
You should release your load inside someone you like instead.
You can't just waste it on a slutty bitch like me.
But, I'm...
Come on now,
don't waste your precious cum.
Just let it all out irresponsibly inside this
woman whose name you don't know.
Oh no... it's about to come out again.
It's coming out of my dick again!
Miss!
It's all right. Just let it all out.
Let your dick cum!
My pussy... my erotic pussy...
Will take everything you've got!
It's squirting out!
It feels so good to be cummed inside!
Thanks for all the cum you wasted on me!
Amazing.
I came so much, as well.
Miss,
did you actually stop reading the novel's lines?
I've been found out.
Here.
Miss, nobody's looking over here right now.
Wow... incredible...!
Miss, if you keep sucking that hard,
I'll cum in a flash...!
If you keep...
Oh no, it's coming out!
Want to,
drop by my place again today?