See ya!
See you tomorrow!
That woman is always reading a book on that bench.
What a pretty lady.
Juvenile Pornography
Hello... What kind of book are you reading?
S-Sorry for suddenly talking with you.
It's alright. Have a seat next to me.
Okay.
I'll read it for you.
S-Sure...
"Hey, let's have sex."
...said by the girl out of the blue,
as she raised her skirt up,
exposing her naked lower body.
Doing that, a suffocating and strong
woman's scent diffused around them.
"Hey, my pussy is already soaking wet."
"Hurry, my dew is overflowing!"
"Plug this bad mouth up using your hard thing!"
Is that... an erotic novel?
Hey, would you like to go to my place?
It's just around the corner.
Okay.
U-Uhm...
What's the problem? Were you not
expecting something lewd like this?
B-But this is too sudden...
Is this your first time to see a naked woman?
Yes...
You're face is beet red, how cute!
Hey, would you like to touch them?
Here... This is a woman's breasts.
Don't they feel good on your hands?
T-They're soft... and very hot.
That's right. I got horny too
so my body became hot.
H-Horny?
Take off my last piece of clothing.
Do it for me, please?
A-Alright.
T-Then...
T-This is...
Onee-san's...
A woman's... part.
You're ogling too much.
I-I'm sorry!
Isn't it embarrassing for me
to be the only one naked.
Let me see-yours-too~!
O-Okay...
Amazing!
You're already this hard!
You got that horny after seeing me naked.
Yes...
Me too... I can't take it anymore.
You're a bad boy! You shouldn't be
easily going together with a stranger.
T-That's because...
Didn't your mom warn you about bad adults?
They're gonna teach you very bad things!
T-That feels good!
Really? I'm glad.
Then, I'll try to do even better.
Hey, do you know why I'm always reading books at the park?
I'm looking around for cute boys like you.
C-Cute?
Aren't you always hanging out there
even after your friends went home.
That's because mom always goes home late.
There's always no one in the house.
I heard something good.
Then, next time we can play in your house.
Onee-san... If you do it that hard, I'm...
Hey, wanna try doing stuffs like in that novel?
Here, start reading on this part.
W-Well...
The girl, with her plump body
is laid bare in front of me.
She indecently spreads her legs like a crab
then vulgarly shook her hips.
'Indecent' and 'vulgar'
something like this?
Uhm...
How is it, can you see it clearly?
My plump body.
My tits and my pussy too, everything's laid bare.
I can see them... E-Everything!
Hey... Continue reading...
I-It's as if she's an animal in heat,
instinctively begging for sex.
That's right! I am now in heat.
My pussy is already this sloppy.
I'm begging for sex!
A-As her eyes which seemed
hungry for flesh stared on me,
My dick got hard as steel.
There's nothing else to do
than for her meat cavity to prey upon it.
It's gonna be devoured by my pussy.
Your hard dick.
Onee-san! What is this?!
W-Wonderful!
Amazing... Amazing!
Hey... Continue reading...
Okay...
She lewdly pumped her hips up and down...
She stroked my dick with her pussy!
Lewdly stroking, right?
I'll use my pussy and slide it in like this!
Wow, your dick is gradually
swelling up and getting harder!
Trying to ignore her shameful appearance, I asked:
"Are you always doing this kind of things?"
Next would be my dialogues, right?
Ahh... That's right! My head is
full of nothing else but sex!
I am a slut!
I'm just pretending to be decent.
The truth is I love dicks so much that
I'm always looking around for one!
I'm a dick-minded woman!
Dicks feel so good! Delicious!
I love getting hollowed out by rigid dicks!
I love it so much! I want to have sex for all my life!
Onee-san...
I can't take it anymore!
S-Something's coming out from my dick!
Stop! That's... too much!
I hear you! I can hear you!
It's okay to go rough with your dick!
Make a mess of my lewd pussy!
Good! More, do it rougher!
I'm gonna come as well!
Coming!
I'm coming! Coming!
I'm coming!
Onee-san...
That feels good!
So good!
Why... How did things end up like this?
It's your fault for being such an easy-to-get boy.
I never did anything bad.
Just because I seemed a little mature,
you were easily lured.
That's...
That's not good!
A cute boy like you
shouldn't let others easily have your dick.
Otherwise, some slut like me
will just suck your balls dry.
No! Not there!
What's inside here is something you
should only give to your future girlfriend.
You shouldn't waste them inside
the pussy of a dirty bitch like me.
B-But... Onee-san is...
Here, here, here!
Waste your valuable baby seeds inside a woman
whose name you don't even know,
and irresponsibly inseminate her!
Oh no! It's coming out again!
It's coming out of my dick again! Onee-san!
It's alright! Shoot them all out!
Shoot everything from your dick!
Inside onee-san's pussy... my lewd pussy!
Shoot it all inside me!
It's coming out! It's coming out!
Creampies feel so good!
Good job on wasting your semen!
Wow, I also came so much!
Onee-san!
Did you stop reading lines
from the novel midway?
You figured it out.
Here, onee-san...
There's no one around now.
Wow! It feels so good!
Onee-san! If you suddenly suck me hard...
I'll quickly...
I'll quickly... come!
That's...
No! It's coming out!
Wanna go to my place again today?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization