Shit!
No.
No, shit.
Shit!
Let me go.
Forgive me, forgive me.
Coach, I beg you.
Please, let me go.
I would do everything.
Stop.
Forgive me.
I will make our vollyball team win.
Episode 1: Fallen Angel
I am tired out.
You have had three boxes of strawberry bar.
And you will get fat.
Shit! You have gone too far.
Sister.
Keep training in the wild for one whole week.
Too hard, coach.
Over there.
You look, see.
Is the training field.
A scarp?
Stop talking that.
There will be the new players this time.
We were attacked by Fenglin School
and got into trouble in the region preliminary heat.
That is because of our bad skill
and bad physical strength.
Sister.
Our power is not enough.
But we can be stronger.
We can practise in the training field.
Right, coach.
Coach.
Please, teach us.
Please train us well.
It was said you had to get off here and then walk.
Really?
Now?
My neck gets sore.
It is very opaque, I can't see it clearly.
It is hard to get here.
It isn't good not to take advantage of this.
Not good?
It is a free time when we arrive at the hotel.
The most tardy person is responsive for the cooking.
But...
Why not take turn...
Shut up, don't want to escape.
Over.
Begin.
What is the next?
Qita, conscious later.
I have arrived.
Why such a dirty play.
Qita, is it about the training fee?
Maybe I am being hated.
Good, work harder.
Although it is not good for the first day.
But we can finish according to the plan tomorrow.
So, we can...
My knee is trembling.
Sister.
Don't constrain yourself.
Cheer up.
One, two.
Shit!
Good, well done.
That is all for today.
Relax everybody, get ready for tomorrow.
Over, dismiss.
Thank you, coach.
Thank you.
My feet are as hard as a stone,
it'll be OK if I take a good sleep.
Jiumei, there is a natural hot spring.
Hot spring?
The wounded baseball players often come here.
Really? Yes.
It works well at fatigue, strain,
chill, sore on shoulder and so on.
So the women like it, the beautiful woman hot spring.
The beautiful woman hot spring.
That is too good for me.
Very comfortable, very happy.
Very lovely, shit.
Have you seen my shampoo?
Did you forget?
Impossible.
That's all, it doesn't matter.
You have thing again.
But...
I am very hungry, and can't wait for the diner.
You can be fat.
Why Zhenxu...
People wouldn't take the candy into the bath place.
That means.
Beidao has a bad luck.
She have to cook for the first day she came.
No problem, she can't do it
I don't know.
You are a good header, knowing
about the players so well.
OK
Curry is OK.
But onions...
It is you on duty.
How is wrong? Keeping going.
Yes.
You aren't doing quite good recently.
The way you eating has an influence on the efficiency.
The accumulating training
is the duration while racing.
Your muscle is the same as usual.
There is reflexed nurve, but not enough outburst.
It is very hard to enter the final.
Yes.
Coach.
I... I would do nothing.
What is up?
What is wrong? Sister.
Nothing, I am fine.
Sister, shall we go to take a walk?
The kimono fits you very well.
Unph... wait.
Your breasts are a little big.
The uniform isn't fit for you if you become fatter.
Xiaoshao, stop like that
I have the same feeling with you.
No, I have to control my weight.
That is OK.
You serve yourself quite good.
Xiaoshao, stop.
What?
There area
and here.
Yes, you are quite a bad girl, you
haven't consideration for people.
You have gone too far.
But it is very funny.
Shit! The water would ovefllow.
Shit, you that bastard.
There are all girls here.
I got it.
I got much this time.
There is better.
Someone peeps at it.
You
see it?
No, don't distract.
Go to hell.
Climax.
You deserve it.
Goodbye, don't hate us.
I have a sound just now.
Really, where have they been?
Who?
Who are you?
My favorite Boqi isn't there.
What are you looking for?
Mei, it is you?
No.
Don't run.
I would forgive you.
Sister, my purse has disappear.
How come?
Zhenyoumei.
Where have you been while we are taking bath?
We haven't seen you all the time.
Where are you? What are you doing?
Sister, you are...
Stop, you haven't prove, she is our teamer.
Sister, what is your opinion?
I don't know too.
I can't stand it.
Sister
I am a head.
I can say nothing at that time
I am disable.
That is no idear.
But, my purse has been stolen.
And the person unpresent is...
Shit.
What is wrong?
Ziliu, she...
Who...!
This...
Don't look please.
Sister.
Stupid.
I am a loser.
I should save her.
But I dare not.
No.
Coach.
I...
Stupid.
Don't use the way making someone weak to love her.
Someone has said that to me before.
Shit.
Give up the weak
I teach you now.
Gentle please.
Shit! That sound.
I beg you, don't dip into suddenly.
Slowly...
Shit!
I beg you, more gentle.
Gentle please.
I would get hurt, get hurt.
I beg you.
I am very hot.
Great.
That is the end.
No, I can't.
Still, I want to.
Coach.
I need it, give me climax please.
Coach, coach.
What is wrong?
Coach, shit!
The person in black uniform suddenly...
Are you OK?
Sister.
Coach.
Strange.
The clothes, it seems like being cut in knife.
You are awake, Daobian.
What a look you have!
The person in black uniform attacked me.
It is like the fighting invitation.
Invitation...?
Invitation.
Eight o'clock, in Qingtian School
I will wait for you.
What are you laughing at?
Where were you and what have you done just now?
I wouldn't forgive you
if you can't give me an satisfied answer.
Sister.
Sister, sister.
My head is very painful.
Sister, answer me, sister.
Jiumei.
Dnagerous.
Coach.
Coach, what is wrong with you?
Hold up.
Open your eyes, coach.
Coach.
Coach... coach...
Coach hold up.
Stand up, coach.
Coach.
Next episode.
The Qingtian School Vollyball Club, wants to win
their opponent is Heian School having met before
besides, some best players have added them.
Our team fail completely.
Any problem, Xiaojing?
The next Ep. The angel on the ground.
Can we really believe in our coach?