Coach, coach, hold up.
It is very painful.
What should we do?
We have to fetch some serum from the hospital in Shanli.
But.
I go.
That is quite unreasonable, it is wild here.
It will take five hours by bus.
I don't know why the phone can't get through.
The phone wave can't get there.
There is no idear.
Sister.
The poison spreads quickly.
Let me go.
Sister
I won't give up if there is a little chance.
That is the soul of our team.
OK, go.
The angel on the ground.
Very heavy.
Shit.
Zhenyoumei.
Everyone, I will die. Leave here me.
What are you saying? You give up first.
You don't seem like Zhenyoumei at all.
Aren't there many obstacles before?
We have to unite this time.
YouMei, wait.
Strain.
Yes, I conceal it all the time, but now I can't stand up.
Then, when it was.
I want to run together with you very much.
But if I keeping on like this, I just can give you trouble.
So, leave me alone.
Leave me.
No, no, no.
Mei.
How can we do like this?
Haven't we supported each other before?
I will stay here if she wants to.
You.
Stupid.
The coach and the head will die very soon.
Do you understand?
I hate that kind of person very much at this moment.
Zhenyoumei.
Hurry up.
Sister.
We have no time left.
But.
We can't waste her favor.
Zhenxu.
Qingtian School, cheer up.
Go.
Zhenyoumei.
Cheer up.
We must come back to pick you up.
The coach will depend on you.
Coach, don't move.
Come here to help Qilai.
What should we do?
Come back, quickly.
Return them to us.
Qingtian School, cheer up.
There they are!
From this moment on, they mustn't walk.
Why? Why trap here?
I hate snake.
No.
Leave me alone, you go first.
Mei, just a short distant.
I know, have a rest here.
Are you worrying about Zhenyoumei.
Zhenxu.
Everyone is a stupid of friendship.
Mei.
You are holding on till this moment.
Jiumei.
I will take back serum, wait with the others.
Let me send the serum.
Let me do it.
I have to do it.
I want to save him.
And the coach.
Get on.
Watch out.
We have to use the last triumph at this moment.
Fire.
How come?
Shit.
Don't bite the tongue, Jiumei.
Save.
Very heavy.
We can overcome every difficulties
no matter what they are
even if we unite.
Coach.
Everything goes on well?
I don't know, there is nothing in my mind.
Warm water here.
The cool water is bad for your health.
I know your mind.
Endure.
Shit! Very tied.
Wait untill it is relaxed.
How is it?
Wait.
I can run.
Shit.
Sencun.
Consume one round's calorie.
Yes.
It's said the calorie spent on making
love is as much as the marathon.
Well done.
You can run one thousand kilometers more.
We have to use our last triumph.
Fire.
Is that all for the report?
That is
the added picture just now.
But we have given them trouble.
They have a difficulty in walking for the time being
not even the national competition.
Shut up.
Do they think my eyes are false?
Can't you walk for a time being?
This.
They are.
They are the same as usual.
Let us begin.
The effect is quite obvious.
I keep on detecting after you
you came back, that is the result.
Give me one more chance, please.
No.
I have said you have no time.
You have to die once you fail.
The working endured woman.
It can't work well.
It is hard to say.
We can think of another way
if it can work.
Another way?
Yes.
We can get rid of them during the race.
During the race?
Right, the day of the national competition is your last day.
And we have experienced the dificult training.
The day fighting with Anhei Lyceum.
Fight back the strong killing ball.
Good, good.
Everyone has show what he has.
If it goes on, the strongest enemy
of the Qingtian Vollyball Team.
The transfer for My Shitianaizi is meaningless.
Exchange.
Look there.
Blaze.
Thunder.
Laiye.
They are very familiar.
That is to say I can't remember who they are.
Shit! That isn't important.
No time no see, Bencun.
I have expected the day for a long time.
You, you are.
Who is he?
Do you want to understand?
Go to ask that man.
Ask him who I am.
Coach.
You are from Cartoon Club.
I fail.
Don't forget your fate.
OK, I would make you remember this.
This tee off is...
Very retarded you are.
Burst.
Thunder.
Super tee off tornado.
Bad.
Stop.
Go.
Xiaojing, let me see you now.
No, don't look at this.
No, forgive me.
Don't touch him.
But I am very hot.
Endure.
You have to.
That is the end, I need the coach.
No.
You have to think of the competition.
I would give you the reward if we win.
Reware.
OK, we must win when it is our turn to tee off.
Exchange.
You are back at last.
Very slow.
Sorry.
Let us begin.
What is wrong with you?
No, I am fine.
No wonder.
Tornado tee off.
Naked.
Why not attack?
Why can he fly?
Her clothes was paint.
Attack.
Very painful.
Qingtian School wins.
How come?
Coach.
Coach I came here for greeting.
Shut up.
Shit.
Here is all wet.
No.
Look, you can't forget my finger's taste.
It is what it used to be before coming home.
What a long time you endured!
How dirty you are!
Keep this pose and turn back to look at me.
What beautiful skin!
But your body is what I can see.
Coach, I don't know what I
would be if it goes on like this.
Do you scare?
Yes.
This look, letting the coach touching.
But, it is very happy.
Xiaoin.
Although it is regretable
but the coach's touching
makes my deep body itch.
I want to be trampled very much.
Xiaoin.
You are trembling.
Coach, this hand is already.
Happy? Waiting for me?
Do you want to be bullied again?
You can't have it totally.
You are very bad.
No, there.
Coach, forgive me.
No.
You have to be honest.
What do you want me to do?
I know you are a honest girl.
What is up? Unclose your feet.
Shit.
Stupid, you can cry at this time.
My consolation maybe can make you happy.
I can make you as happy as sister.
Very done.
Come, this is the reward.
Very good.
You match me so much.
But.
Is it clear?
Shit.
Jiumei is so honest.
You look, it is all wet.
Shit, don't let me look at it.
To encourage you, I will make you more comfortable.
No, no.
Give me, give me what you have.
That is the first time.
Success, we have won.