SubDESU
Presents
Well then Haruki-san,
we'll now spend our evening at a trendy cafe.
I'm cool with that, but...
Airi...
You called me because you needed the strength of a man, right?
That's right.
Is there a problem?
But, all we did was watch a movie earlier in the morning.
Went window shopping.
And ate lunch.
But what am I really supposed to be doing?
Huh?
Well, umm... You see...
Haru-kun! Airi-chan!
Ayana!
Having an excursion, just the two of you?
I wish you had invited me as well.
I'm sorry but that is not possible.
We're in the middle of a bittersweet date.
There isn't space for you to fit in.
Now I know why we're just strolling around!
But it's quite rare for you  to be here.
Weren't you supposed to be staying at home during the weekends?
Yeah, I was sleeping but I got woken up by a phone call.
Onee-chan asked me to come meet her.
Don't tell me, she's back already?
I don't really get along well with that person.
Then you see,
I didn't have time to change,
so I just came here wearing something over my pajamas.
Just the upper part?
Hey, hey, Ayana.
Coming to meet me in your suggestively naked pajamas; are you trying to seduce me?
This voice...
There, there...
You're weakest spot is right over here, isn't it?
M-My nipples...!
If you milk it...
Wai–
My breasts...
My nipples...
Geez, you're already doing that right after you just got here.
Show yourself, Touko-san!
Why hello there!
Long time no see.
Out of touch with common sense as always.
What are you up to this time?
A little birdie told me,
that both of you split into different clubs?
Yeah!
I'm in the Chemistry Science club.
(Kagaku) (Ka =  change in form)
While Airi-chan is in the Tech Science club.
(also Kagaku) (Ka = subject, course)
But Haru-kun misunderstood and ended up joining both clubs.
It was damn confusing!!
Us from the Kuze family and you two who are from the Hizuki family
are rivals in the scientific realm.
And we must someday settle the score.
And so, the important point is Haruki-san, who knows a lot about our science,
must choose between the two clubs, which is the more superior one.
And also who will be his wife.
Hey, I never heard anything about the "wife" part!
However, this is something between me and Ayana-san.
It has nothing to do with Touko-san, right?
But you know, Ayana is a little weak on the offensive.
So, I thought... I would lend her a hand.
Here, if you come to our side, you'll receive double service from both sisters!
Onee-chan...
Erotic warfare is unfair!
Double breast sets...
Mind not biting the obvious bate, Haruki-san?!
This is severely underhanded!
I really don't like you after all!
Let's go Haruki-san.
We are continuing our date.
H-Hey...
A date?
Hey Ayana, she's already getting far ahead here.
Yeah seriously, having an outing without us; they are just too reserved.
This one's a lost cause.
So I really have to exert some effort after all.
Well, you don't need to rush things, Onee-chan.
Like old times, why don't we...
Huh?
Onee-chan?
Guess it's safe here now.
Hey, are we still continuing this date?
Of course!
Got any complaints?
No, not really. I am good.
Airi and Haruki-san's
Big Date Plan Schedule
Wait at station.
Arrive at theater.
Watch movie.
Exit theater.
Window shopping
by the station .
Arrive at the open cafe.
Meal.
Leave open cafe.
Then there are no problems, right?
Let's resume our date then.
That's some crazy schedule there!
She's serious.
This girl isn't playin' around!
Of course.
I don't plan on letting you sleep toni–
Airi?
Ouch...
Haru-boy obtained!
Touko-san!
W-what are you planning on doing?
Read the atmosphere here.
Were going to continue that earlier session of course.
Here, how's that?
It's an irresistible sensation for adolescent boys, right?
Just give up and join Ayana's club!
Well...
I would rather be happily together as a trio rather than duo, to be honest.
You're unexpectedly stubborn there.
Then I shall use my next card.
How about some pocky?
Seriously?!
Don't you know any other method besides seduction?
Guess it can't be helped.
I'm also a scientist,
so I'll use the power of science to solve this.
Touko-san's special item!
The obedience drug!
Oh good god, I think I am royally screwed!
As the name implies, it's a medicine that allows me to control you at will!
For a medicine, it looks extremely scary!
Rocket Punch!
Crap, so she's already awake.
Airi!
Stealing Haruki-san from me while you knock me unconscious.
What an unfair thing to do!
Hand over that medicine as your punishment!
I'll run my own personal R&D to confirm those effects.
Oh man, this one is more psyched on making me the guinea pig.
This is getting bad, retreat!
I won't let you!
Airi Eye, Search Mode!
Found you!
Prepare yourself!
Airi Buster!
Hey, wait...!
Sto–
Geez!
Oh no, I got careless.
Oh man, and I had planned on using it on Haru-boy...
Change of plans then.
Let's have you do embarrassing things in front of Haru-boy.
Wh... What kind of idiotic things are you...
What is this medicine?
I won't just allow myself to follow...
Wha–?
Haruki-san, please don't look!
Yea well, any idea on how to do that?
Deactivate!
I didn't create you to do this...
That was a nice show.
It was humiliating.
But, I think I just stumbled upon a door to a newer self.
Don't go through it!
Just stay as you are!
Well then, I wonder what I should order next?
Ah, there you are.
Ayana.
You're terrible, Onee-chan!
Leaving me like that...
I'm sorry about that...
Got ya!
Payback time.
I'm going to make you taste your own precious little medicine!
That's...!
It's the space coagulating drug.
I can't move...
My breasts...
What a nice view.
Now then, I shall pay you back for what you did to me earlier.
Wait, time out!
Hey, where are you touching me...!
Oh wow, you really are resisting it like a boss.
This kind of amateur play doesn't even faze me.
Is that so?
Then maximum output!
Hyper Vibration Massage Mode!
No...!
This isn't fair!
Onee... Onee-chan!
When you move, your nipple rubs on mine...
Oh no, I'm about to cum...
Just from that?
Just how  much sensitive are those breasts of yours?!
Ayana?
Onee-chan, I can't hold on, anymore...
Airi, hurry up.
What are ordering me around for?
Do you understand your position in this situation?
Just hurry it up! Use your arms to tease Ayana too!
This is way too intense!
I can't endure anymo–
She's the cutest when she's getting teased like that.
Onee-chan... Onee-chan, your tongue...
Onee-chan, this feels amazing...
I just came, yet these things won't let my orgasms stop...
Ayana...
I can't endure it anymore either...!
Now I'm really satisfied!
Ouch!
Let's call it a draw this time.
Forgive me...
See ya!
I got caught in her  pace again.
That's why I don't get along with her.
So, what happens to the date?
Well, my schedule is ruined so let's cancel it already.
The whole "date mood" is destroyed.
Well to be honest, I don't think there was any such "mood" from the get go...
Hey, have you heard?
The new teacher assigned to the infirmary got some serious gargantuan breasts on her!
For real?
Infirmary
Hey there, you three came together to visit me.
You?
Onee-chan?
What are you doing here, Touko-san?
I'm the infirmary doctor now.
In order to seduce Haru-boy into Ayana's club,
I thought I ought to be in a place much closer.
Boobs...
You probably used that weird medicine to bag this job.
Isn't your special power invisibility?
A simpler approach would have been to sneak in instead, wouldn't you say?
Oh, interesting.
Elementary
Didn't think of it that way.
Are you for real?!
Ah, darn it!
What do I do about this job now?
So you plan on quiting already?
Hey, Onee-chan.
You've already signed up for it so please try and see it through for a bit.
Ayana?
I think, listening to the personal problems of the students, is an important part of this job, you know?
Like during that time when my body became like this due to the accident and I was in a state of shock,
it was thanks to Airi-chan and Haru-kun's support that I was able to move on with my life.
So I want Onee-chan to do something similar as well.
Ayana...
Okay, I understand.
I'm going to do my best!
Come on,
youth!
Touko-san
Clinic
I'll solve it with medicine!
Touko-san's problem consultation room, now open!
What are you suddenly opening up?!
As I said I want to help out troubled kids...
... with medicine.
What a powerful technique.
Moreover, it sounds shady as heck!
How foolish.
Who in the world would want to come to this dubious...
They came by the mountainful!
As expected of the troubled youth!
Okay, leave it all...
Tubes from Left To Right: Weight loss. Chick magnet. Hair Growth. Brains.
... to Touko-sensei!
Thank you very much!
Wow, she is actually handling it like a professional.
As expected of my rival's elder sister.
She might be a fickle person, but her skills are still top notch.
Well since she is offering her services anyway, I guess I'll get some work done as well.
I want to add muscles to my body, shortcut style.
An emergency came up so I'll be leaving.
Okay.
Anyway, it was quite successful, wouldn't you say?
Yes! What kind of problem do you hav–
That's not gonna work, Airi.
No, this Airi's disguise is perfect...
Making me answer subconsciously is unfair!
So, what problem might you be having?
Please, make my... breasts bigger.
Generally you are all like, "What an awesome scientist I am" and this little  thing is your problem?
Nothing wrong with that, right?
Airi, the worth of a woman isn't determined by breasts.
Haruki-san...
The reason why I'm so troubled is because you're always lovestruck whenever you see Ayana-san's humongous breasts!
I'm sorry!
I love breasts!
I'm a breast freak!
But still, it's a bit perplexing.
Actually breast size is not something that has ever been a problem for me,
so I don't know if I really made a medicine for it or not.
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
Well, wait a bit.
I think I have made at least one...
Breast medicine Trial ver.
Touko-san's special female breast growth medicine!
Hey.
Well?
Nothing really happened.
Airi!
My chest...
My body feels hot and weak.
Onee-chan, is this medicine really what it is for?
Eh? That's strange...
Oh my bad. This medicine is not for increasing breast size, but actually increasing breast sensitivity.
What did you say?!
Oh well!
This is an opportunity for me to test out its effectiveness!
What are you planning to do?
I'll expose your naughty side to Haru-kun and plummet your image in his eyes!
That's not fair, Touko-san!
Oh no...
If it goes on like this... I...
I'm cumming!~
Milk's coming out of Airi?
Was it a side effect of the medicine?
It's probably just temporary.
She will be back to normal soon enough.
I-It was humiliating.
My body's moving again.
Alright, let's have another round of that medicine...
I won't let you!
Looks like the tables have turned...
We still have a lot of medicine left.
I'll pay back what you did to me ten times!
Sto-Stop it you two!
I'll be retreating for now then.
That's futile!
Damn, the medicine's still in effect.
If I don't concentrate...
There you are!
Huh?
A-A-Ayana-san?
She chugged it in!!
On top of that, a person who definitely  should be avoiding it's effects, drank it!
The mere sensation of my uniform grazing against them...
My breasts are about to make me...
For real?!
What are we going to do about this?
I guess since the uniform is escalating the problem, maybe we should undress her?
You want me to do it?
You did not have to take off her skirt too, you know!
I'll give you points for that.
How is it?
Do you feel a bit better now?
No...
It's just the wind hitting them,
but my nipples feel like they're being licked all over.
What the heck am I supposed to do about that?!
Touko-san, don't you have an antidote for this?
I was actually planning on getting rid of that medicine to be honest, so...
I don't even have the ingredients to make an antidote.
What an unthinkable disaster!
Well, it seems to wear off if the one affected secretes milk.
So all she has to do is release lots of it.
Wait.
I think I may have ingredients for an antidote in my clubroom.
So Ayana can also create medicines to a certain degree, right?
The ingredients are supposed to be in the inner storage...
Ayana's creatures?
I see.
Ayana's condition isn't normal so they must be worried.
But we can't go through with them blocking the way.
Ayana-san, please.
Everyone, please let us through.
We need to make a certain medicine.
If we don't...
I-If we don't squeeze it out of my breasts soon...
It'd be bad...!
Even though technically correct, the pauses in the sentence is giving out a whole different impression.
I am not sure but it seems she is sick or something.
Either she needs to drink a certain medicine or squeeze something out of her breasts.
Since we are beasts by nature, the subtle medicine option is out of the question.
Let's squeeze it out then!!
Squeeze it and make our master feel better.
No!
That's not what I...!
They've completely misunderstood!
Quick Ayana, clarify the situation to them!
I can't...
My breasts are all sloppy...
Don't touch that...
This intense sensation...
and the milk...
just won't stop...
For some reason, this particular scene is trumping all other erotic incidents she generally ends up in.
What should I do?
I want to join her up there.
What are you two saying at a time like this?
This one seems to be under the weather as well guys.
We need to squeeze a lot to save her too!
Allow me.
What great breasts.
Tres Bien'.  Outrageously Sexy.
Stop...
We'll squeeze it out!
Me too?
If it's come to this, then...
Don't come near me you gang of beasts!
Haruki-san will be the one to squeeze my milk out!
Wa– Don't go deciding something like that on your own!
It seems they're overflowing
from places other than their breasts.
That is bad.
Let's squeeze it all out.
It's sloshy...
Stop rubbing on it already...
I'm going to cum...
I give up...
Even I cannot endure something like this for long...
It's stiff.
And yet it still has a mysterious softness in it.
This type might has an attraction level of it's own!
R-Right?
Small ones have a their own charms...
Ayana.
These creatures are weirdly bold...
Could it be...
you're regularly teased by these on a daily basis...?
Stop this already...!
Geez, I was put through some merciless stuff back there.
It was foolish of me to rely on my own rival.
My bad, my bad.
I'm going to properly make one next time.
No thanks.
From now on, I'll make Haruki-san's heart throb using my own charms.
Oh, to be young!
Do your best, Airi-chan!
You too Ayana.
Oh yeah.
Ayana-san, do you understand?
Looks like we'll somehow be needing Airi's preachy attitude to make it through.