Takahiko-san...
Takahiko-san?
Manami...
Is everything alright? You looked horrified.
So this is Takahiko-san's home town...
It's a beautiful place!
Then, let's go.
Do a lot of tourist come to see the festival?
Hmm... I moved out of the village before I was very small.
So I don't really remember much.
I see.
But it's definitely...
Manami!
Welcome back, Takahiko-sama.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Kagachi-Sama
Celebration of Comforting
Long time no see and you've grown
to be an adult, haven't you?
Yes, it's been a while, father.
Well, it's great you're back.
Bringing such a beautiful bride as well.
I'm flattered.
I'm Takahiko's father, Tomikura Nagatarou.
This is my wife, Ayaka.
Pleasure to meet you, Manami-san.
Nice to meet you, Manami-san. Please feel free
to ask me anything as we're both women.
Yes, it's great to meet you.
As expected... you married.
Yes...
Right after you left home, Takahiko-san.
Ayaka, why don't you show Manami-san
around the house right away?
Okay. Takahiko-san, I'll be borrowing
Manami-san for a while, then.
Takahiko-san?
It's fine. Let Ayaka-san show you around.
Then, let's go.
You must have travelled a long way, are you tired?
No, it's okay...
You must've been surprised that it's
so far out on the countryside.
There's no such thing! The air fresh and feels great.
When, did you marry Ayaka-san!?
Right after you left the village.
I'm pretty sure you noticed as well.
Don't talk like we're the same.
We are.
Me and you and Ayaka as well, we're
all part of the Tomikura family.
I'll have to teach that women what it means
to be part of the family as well.
No... stop... please...
Even though you're saything that, isn't
your pussy is soaked, young madam?
No!
Don't say that...
Your anus is clenching just right as well!
Manami-san, this is a sacred ceremony.
Since you've become a bride to this family, you'll
have to follow the rituals in the village.
So these are customs?
That's right. In the Village of Shironawa there
exists a snake god called Kagachi-Sama.
For Kagachi-sama to protect our village,
once every year, all the women in the
village must sacrifice their bodies.
For the sake of pleasing Kagachi-Sama.
It's too large... I can't take... anymore!
What are you talking about, Manami-san?
Kagachi-Sama, here is for your comfort and pleasure.
Manami-san, don't worry. Takahiko
does not know of this ceremony.
He will never know what happened.
Is that true?
Takahiko-san, I'm sorry... I'm cumming
from a dick other than yours!
That's right. I came back to this village, so that my beloved
wife would be violated by someone other than myself.
And also, to bring back that important person...
Taka-kun! Over here, over here!
Wait up, Ayaka-neesan!
Look, Taka-kun.
It's beautiful.
Taka-kun...
Takahiko-san?
No!
Please stop, Takahiko-san.
Ayaka-san, why with that horrible man!?
You can't... you can't...
Right now...
How dare you, Takahiko...
To think that you'd go for your step-mother...
It was so exciting that I got crazy as well.
Geez, you're such a disgraceful sow!
Let out the horrible acting, to think
that you'd seduce your step-son...
That's not true... there's nothing
between me and Takahiko-san...
There's no way that's true... as proof, you're this
wet despite not doing anything, aren't you?
Please don't say that...
Takahiko, no matter what you wish
for, that woman is already my slut.
Give up on her, and focus on training
your own wife to be your sex slave.
That room's got a hidden camera, hasn't it?
It's been like that since we married.
That's just wrong!
After getting married, every year during the festival
I've been mingling with all sorts of men.
Takahiko-san knows that, too, right!? I'm
not the person from back then anymore!
I've been stained.
That's not true.
Ayaka-san will always be Ayaka-san!
Please leave the village with me!
What about Manami-san, then?
Then... the three of us.
I don't want it to be the three of us.
If you're serious, then make it just the two of us.
I get it.
Please don't joke around like that.
Are you serious?
Ayaka-san... it's great, really great!
You're huge...
It's wonderful... to have Ayaka-san give me a titty fuck...
Ayaka-san, if you do it so much I'll...
Cum-Cummmg!
So hot!
Takahiko-san's dick is amazing!
Yeah, Ayaka has an amazing pussy as well.
So you used this pussy to take in their...
to take in the villager's cock?
Don't say that...
I was just following the customs...
But, but right now... it's only Takahiko-san's dick for me!
If you squeeze so much...
Cum!
Cum lots into my naughty pussy!
Gonna cum!
Cum! Creampie me lots!
There's so much of Takahiko-san's... it's melting inside...
Takahiko-san...
Ayaka-san...
Manami, I'm sorry.
Manami, are you feeling unwell somewhere?
Um, no, that's...
I see.
Why don't you get some rest?
Yes, I think I should.
I'll go take a nap.
Sorry.
Well, let's go, Ayaka-san.
I'm sorry, Taka-kun.
Ayaka... san...
After being beaten up badly, I ran back
to Tokyo without looking back.
I never managed to reach the Tomikura
house no matter how I tried.
And neither Manami nor Ayaka-san contacted me.
Just as I was about to go crazy from anxiety,
A DVD arrived from the Tomikura house.
You can't do that. Manami-san.
Didn't I tell you we're sending Takahiko-san a video today?
But... but cock feels so good!
Sorry about that, Taka-kun. Manami-san is so drawn by cock.
Well that can't be helped, right!? She won't
be able to think about her husband!
Yes... this dick is too amazing!
Manami, if you don't follow Master's
orders I won't do any more!
No! I want more!
Are you watching, Takahiko-san?
Are you watching, Takahiko?
We've trained your ex-bride into a wonderful slut.
Sorry, Taka-kun. Back then, I...
asked to escape with you....
because I was ordered to!
I was tired of just sleeping with Ayaka.
Thanks for letting me enjoy!
Amazing... It's amazing!
Master was so cruel... letting me do something
like saying I'd run away...
C'mon, don't say that.
Manami-san, compare Takahiko and the
villagers here. Which one is better?
The villagers here, of course!
Takahiko, so that's what we have here.
Ayaka won't go back to you no matter how you wait, and Manami has become a cum dump for the village!
That's right!
I want to be a cum dump!
It's not fair to just do Manami-san! Me, too! Me, too!
Hey, are you watching properly?
Does the foreskin not roll back on that tiny
dick of yours? This woman is amazing!
Takahiko-sama is probably drooling and jerking off to this!
How is it?
Your Tomikura blood must be throbbing from this!
Can't control your excitement, right?
Kagachi-Sama is the best!
Have you already cum?
You don't have to think about anything.
Just cum as much as you want.
As much as you want!
Sorry, Taka-kun.
Farewell. Takahiko-san!
The two of us... will find happiness!
Ah, Manami and Ayaka-san will be coming back soon.
I gotta clean up.
Ah. there's so much to look forward to.
The three of us... will live happily ever after together...