Honestly...
I suck at staying up, and I suck at studying,
so staying up all night studying was pretty awful.
Thanks to that, I fell asleep during class
and left my favorite pen behind.
Music Room
I really hope it's still here... It was a limited edition.
There it is!
Thank goodness!
Guess focusing on my studies gave me good karma!
Today started off pretty crummy,
but it's all sunshine and rainbows from here on...
Kagirohi Shaku Kei Another 01
Kagiroi.
The First Night
Honeymoon with a Girl, The End
The first night:
Honeymoon with a girl, the end.
It was storming that day too...
the day my mother was killed by a drunk driver.
She was the only family I had,
as my father divorced her and left us.
That made me the man of the house,
so I was the one the driver apologized to.
It was a good experience.
Before me, stood my mother's killer.
Beside me, a bat. Without hesitation, I...
As far as society's concerned, I've atoned for my sins.
So why?
Why am I still being punished?
Kaede is dead.
So why aren't I sad? I haven't shed a single tear.
Is it because I'm used to seeing people die?
I don't understand my own feelings.
I was...
I was in love with Kaede, right?
Please choose me.
Choose me, not Ajisai!
Choose?
What are you talking about?
By Ajisai, do you mean Minazuki Ajisai from my class?
I want to always be by your side!
I want to give you everything!
My body, spirit, mind... they are all yours!
Everything from the last strand of my hair
to the last drop of blood in my veins!
I won't think about anything but you.
I'll love you for the rest of my life!
If you tell me to die, I'll gladly end my life!
So please! Make me yours!
If you're trying to seduce me,
there are easier ways going about it...
Hey, not out here!
Besides, I was joking.
It's fine!
I... I want you to have every last part of me.
So...
Senpai?
S-Senpai...
You don't have to be in such a rush.
My first time is yours.
K-Kaede...
Th-That was so sudden!
So deep...
S-Senpai...
How does it feel inside me?
Is it good? Does it feel good?
Yeah.
Your tiny tits are so tasty!
I'm glad you like small breasts.
Your pussy is milking me like a cow's udder!
So deep!
You're so tight!
It's blowing my mind!
I can feel you squirming inside me.
It's moving in me!
We're becoming one!
It hurts, but feels so...
Please use me more.
I want you to know every nook and cranny of my body.
I'm all yours now.
I want to become one with you and so much more!
My body is for your pleasure!
This is so embarrassing.
But I don't mind.
I want you to know me inside and out.
It feels so good!
My pussy's getting so excited!
You're penetrating me!
We're becoming one!
Good! So good!
No!
So tight!
I-I'm cumming!
C-Cum! Cum!
Fill my pussy to the brim with your semen!
I want to bear your child!
I want your baby!
It's coming! You're cumming inside me!
It's shooting so deep inside me!
I'm cumming!
I feel so hot! So hot!
Senpai...
I love you.
You there... You're interested in me, right?
Minazuki? I-I'm not...
I'm not interested in you whatsoever.
You can just call me Ajisai.
Why are you still here?
Is it because of the rumor that I sell my body after class?
Are you here to fuck me?
Wh-What are you, talking about?!
You're the one who called me here, Mina... Ajisai!
And this is the first I'm hearing about these rumors.
In any case, what you do is your own business.
Keep it to yourself next time.
Anyway, it's been a year since you've transferred here.
So why are you still wearing your old uniform?
Get your shit together!
Also, what did you do with all the desks and chairs?
What the hell are you up to?!
Tell me! What's going on?
Tell me already, dammit!
What are you after?!
What are you trying to do? And...
And...
And more importantly... Most importantly...
You know who killed Kirishima Kaede, don't you?
Why are you crying?
And what do you mean by "killed"?
I thought she committed suicide.
That's right. It wasn't a suicide.
That day when she told me to choose her,
it was like she was trying to tell me something...
Kirishima Kaede was murdered.
Kaede was? But that can't be...
It's been over a year since you've transferred into my class,
but I've never seen you talk to a single person...
Not even a simple greeting.
And now you want to talk to me?
Something's not right.
But Kaede knew you were up to something.
What did you do to her?
N-No, the reason I asked you to come here was...
to confirm the rumors.
I whore myself out.
Though, I suppose telling you this is pointless.
After all, you caught me in the act, didn't you?
Crap, I'm late.
Isn't that...
Minazuki?
Th-This is bad!
We just did it last week...
You two are such animals...
Th-That's...
Rub it a little more.
My, my... Could you be enjoying this even more than us?
All at once?!
Fine...
I need to help her.
I need to help her, now!
W-Wait! Be more gentle!
Fuck that shit!
We ain't got time for foreplay!
We've only got thirty minutes left!
Hey!
If you hurt me, I'm gonna charge extra
for the damaging the goods!
So you'd charge us extra before telling us to fuck off?
That's just like you.
Don't take off my clothes without my permission!
I really will charge...
I won't let you stop me.
I bought you with my own hard-earned money.
I-I'm the one who chooses...
Not there!
Yes, there. Your job is to make your customers
have the times of their lives!
Fuck you!
Leave my ass alone!
Are you crying?!
You've sold yourself to us multiple times, you whore.
Who cares if we use a different hole every now and...
So you knew?
You jumping in would have seriously hurt my business.
Anyway, I figured you'd be depressed since
the girl you loved killed herself and all.
You won't last long if you keep taking your emotions
out on whoever crosses your path.
As long as you're in this village, at least.
S-Stop!
I didn't come here to...
Just look how hard you've gotten.
If you don't like it, resist me.
Oh yeah, tell me when you're about to cum.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч