You still can't move your body, can you?
Not surprising considering how you just
gulped that drug down with the tea.
Please just keep lying there and rest.
Y-You...
Oh dear, looks like the weather's taken a turn for the worse.
The weather on the day you lost
your mother was just like this.
The minute she was hit by that car...
It made a sound just as loud as the thunder.
I'm pretty sure she was screaming too.
Why do I know?
That's because Kaede was behind the wheel
of the car that hit your mother.
What are you...
The parent and child that came to
apologize to us weren't you two!
Body doubles can be bought for the right price.
You're lying!
You're lying! You're lying! You're lying!!
Why would Kaede kill my mother?!
For my sake, of course.
I begged her to do it.
Aoi-san, you're...
Kagiroi Shaku Kei Another
Kagiroi.
Four Night
The Truth Brought to Light, The Sweet Voices of the Girls
Fourth night.
The truth brought to light, the sweet voices of the girls.
Please choose me.
Please choose me, not Mizuki!
What? You haven't chosen anyone yet?
I guess it's hard to catch anyone's
eyes with that flat chest of yours.
They'll get bigger eventually! I'm sure they will!
I'll give everything to you... my body and mind are yours.
I'll give you everything... from my last strand
of hair to my last drop of blood.
I'll even give you my heart!
I won't think about anyone else
but you for the rest of my life!
I'll love you with everything I have!
If you tell me to die, I'll die!
So please make me yours!
Wow, you're really serious about the Nikubi Festival.
Alright.
N-Now?!
This is too sudden!
I-It's so tight!
Senpai!
It's inside me!
No... Please be more gentle!
This isn't your first time, is it?
Why's there blood?
My body's small, so...
Having a big dick like yours inside me...
Rips me apart.
O-Oh, really? B-But damn, it's so tight!
Being inside you is good... really good!
This is so embarrassing...
Your dick... It's moving so deep inside me!
Keep moving!
Keep shoving it all the way in!
O-Ow...
It's moving inside me!
It's rubbing around inside me!
Holy shit!
I've never had anyone as tight as you!
You're more amazing than Mizuki!
So good!
I'm gonna...
Senpai! Senpai!
It's hitting me so hard! It's banging against me!
It's really... It's really hitting me deep!
Senpai! Senpai!
I-I'm gonna...
Senpai! Senpai...
Your cum's flowing out inside me!
S-Senpai, your cum is inside of me!
I-It's so hot!
Pour your cum inside of me!
Fill my insides with your cum!
Senpai came inside me.
I... I...
I wonder if I'm pregnant with your kid, senpai.
Senpai?
Music Room
That's good!
Do me hardier! Harder!
Harder!
Don't you feel any remorse at all?!
S-So good! It's better than usual!
So good!
That's good... Rub them more!
Rub my boobs!
Y-Yes, pinch my nipples too!
G-Good!
So deep... So good!
Good! Very good!
You're getting so fucking tight!
Th-That's right!
Shove it in me more! Pull my nipples more!
Good... So good!
Do it! Do it! Put a finger into my asshole too!
You...
Last time, you cried about how you didn't want to do that.
There's something wrong with you.
Both my pussy and asshole feel so good!
Good... They all feel so good!
Play with them more!
More... Make me one with you more!
That's good!
More! You're the best!
Use your hips more and make me feel even more pleasure!
Shit...
I-I'm gonna cum!
Cum! Inside! Cum inside!!
Here I go!
Good! Now fill my womb with your semen!
It's going... It's going all the way in!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Y-You...
So for this year's festival, we're e-eliminating
all other participants.
Music Room
This is insane.
It wasn't part of the plan for him to participate though.
A-Anyway, I got rid of Kaede and Mizuki just like you asked.
We're out now.
When you become the head of this
village, remember us, okay?
Of course.
I won't forget.
Oh my.
It's impressive how hard you are despite the situation.
It's no wonder I'm so drawn to you.
Screw you!
Untie me!
If you don't I'll.
Since the old days, when treating illnesses,
this village believed that if you ate something that
had the same infliction as you, you'd be cured.
It was found that the soup of dextrocardiacs had
an effect of perpetual youth and longevity.
People gave up their own children to obtain it.
So, it's quite the valuable thing around here.
What are you saying?
The truth.
Kaede's parents happily traded her for it too.
There's a festival in this village every ten years.
It's called the Nikubi Festival.
It means "The Festival of Two Necks".
But it used to mean "Beautiful Meat".
There'd be a banquet with exotic meats.
Soups made out of other people's meats.
Those who visited the village were the
ones who brought those exotic meats.
And the one who brought the most delicious
meat would be named as the village chief.
That's why the head of the village has
been a woman for generations.
Your father had dextrocardia.
What are you trying to say?
And you, his son, do too.
Wha...
And I'm sure the baby that you and I make will be the same.
What's this sound?!
This smell... It can't be!
Aoi, Nezu killed your mother. Run away from this village.
I even sent him a clue out of pity
since she killed his father too.
Guess it didn't get through his thick head.
As long as there's no one left to oppose me...
I have no chance of losing.
Starting next year, I'll be this village's chief.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч