So you knew?
Having someone perched outside trying to burst
in to save me would damage my business.
Now I know you must be down in the dumps now that
your beloved one is no longer in this world, but...
If you just blame whoever crosses your
path, you won't be able to live.
Or at least, in this village.
S-Stop!
I didn't come here for...
Look at how hard you've gotten.
If you don't want this, you can fight back.
Also, tell me when you're about to cum.
Morning!
Today's so beautiful.
We gotta hurry up or we're gonna be late.
Yeah, let's run!
Good morning!
Who are you?
Huh?! There's no way you've actually
forgotten me already, right?!
I said hi to you the other day. I was right
next to Nezu-sama, remember?
Kaede!
I'm Kirishima Kaede.
Oh right, you were next to that old lady...
Wh-What's your problem?!
How dare you disrespect Nezu-sama like that.
She's one of the most important people in this village.
And she's even going to be taking care of you...
Seriously...
Well anyway, have you eaten breakfast, senpai?
I made some!
I'm fine.
Why'd you even make breakfast anyway?
I have a name. It's Kaede.
Start using it.
So you haven't eaten.
That's not good, senpai.
You need to be more careful with your
diet since you're living by yourself.
What are you doing?!
I might have done it as a joke, but don't actually eat it!
This is a limited edition pencil case.
It's been with me in the best and worsts of times.
It's a one of a kind!
If I were to put its value into a tangible cost,
it'd be nothing short of a hundred million.
What, are you smuggling drugs
in that pen case or something?
Oh good. So you are alive in there.
I shouldn't have worried at all.
I'm not so pathetic that I need you
worrying about me, Mizuki.
Hey, so, you've been hanging around her a lot, haven't you?
It'd be better if you kept your distance from her.
Kagirohi Shaku Kei Another
Kagirohi.
Second Night
The Classroom at Dusk, the Glossy Haired Temptress
Second night: The classroom at dusk,
the glossy haired temptress.
You're not lying about having an idea
of who killed Kaede, are you?
Calm down.
That's good.
Pull on my nipples more!
O-Ow...
S-So hot.
My breasts and my body are getting so hot!
Now, tell me...
What are you trying to do?
You're so rough.
You want to put it in?
You want to put that hard, stiff thing inside me?
Your thing's saying that it wants to go inside me.
Th-This is for Kaede.
But of course.
Go ahead. Put it in.
C-Come on, put it in.
Hurry up and put it inside me!
I-It's coming inside!
Good. Keep going!
Deep... Put it deep inside me!
Wow, you can really reach far in this position.
So you did this kind of rough play
with Kaede-chan a lot, huh?
Sh-Shut up!
Shove it... Shove it in me!
Put it all inside me!
This really turns me on!
So good... Your dick is so good!
I-It's hitting!
It's going all the way inside me!
Shit... Her pussy's so hot and it's wrapping around me!
I can feel it hitting me inside. It's
rubbing against me so hard!
It's hitting my womb...
It's coming... Coming so deep!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too.
Together... Let's cum together!
Cum inside me!
Do it inside me!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
Inside me! Cum inside me!
It's so hot...
I'm cumming...
So good...
It's so warm...
You say that it's all for Kaede, but...
Look how much is pouring out of me.
It's your cum.
You gave me so much.
It feels really good.
If I get pregnant from this...
You'll take responsibility, won't you?
Y-You... You said it was your safe day, didn't you?!
I have a name. It's Kaede.
Use it from now on.
Please choose me.
Please choose me, not Ajisai.
Not Ajisai, me!
Come here. You're hungry, aren't you?
I'll make you some tasty sandwiches.
Huh?
Senpai...
Why are you...
I came to give you back your lunch box.
Oh, you could've just given it back tomorrow.
Oh, really?
I should've washed it first, huh?
Oh, no, don't worry about it.
I just kinda forced it on to you anyway...
Well, it was edible.
That's pretty mean. I worked really hard on them.
Want me to make you some tomorrow too?
You need to help prepare for some kind of festival right?
Don't go out of your way to make it.
It's not out of my way.
I'm always making my own lunch, so
it'd just be a little extra. Just a little.
Well, you've come all this way, would you...
Nezu-sama...
With me, would you...
It doesn't have to be for long, but would
you go with me to visit Nezu-sama?
Is that all?
Sorry.
I'm going home.
H-Hey, senpai, wait!
Sorry, I'll see you tomorrow.
Kaede didn't do anything wrong I was just being immature.
I know that.
But...
Hey, you! Why'd you come all this way just to leave?
Just thinking about seeing her makes my heart turn over.
Sorry, I'll see you tomorrow.
Didn't you want to know more about Kaede?
N-Nezu-sama...
Senpai?
Hurry...
Hurry and...
Hurry up and mess me up!
If you don't mess me up good, I'm gonna tell Ajisai.
I don't need you telling me something
I was already gonna do.
It's pounding... Pounding against me!
More! Move your hips more! Turn me inside out!
You chose right when you switched to me.
Just hurry up and choose me!
Good! So good!
You're rubbing my insides so hard!
My stomach's going crazy!
That's good! Bite my nipples!
Bite them so hard that you could rip them off!
That's good!
Don't stop moving down there!
Shove it! Shove it! Shove it in me!
Good! So good!
Kaede shouldn't have chosen to hang
around that dangerous guy.
I-I've never felt like this before!
It's good... So good!
My mind's gonna break!
Oh my god, it's better than any toy I've ever used!
Meat sticks are definitely the best!
If you choose me, I'm sure I can send you straight to heaven.
It's deep! It's going so deep!
This is so amazing!
I love this meat stick!
I love it! I love it so much!
I'm getting close.
That's fine. Just satisfy me... Make me feel really good!
I've never had a meat stick as good as yours.
It's even better than my dad's!
It's the best!
More! Give me more!
I'm alive! It's so good! So good! So good!
Your meat stick is the best!
W-Wait, your dad is in the potential candidates?
It's here! It's here! It's here! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Go ahead! Cover me! Cover me in your cum!
Crap, I'm not gonna make it!
N-No, you can't cum inside!
You big idiot!
I'm cumming!
Sorry, it felt so good, I...
Don't treat me like I'm Ajisai.
I just felt like going at it on a whim.
Don't get full of yourself!
It might be risky, but...
Let's aim for Aoi's next.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч