Wait!
Why'd you come all this way if you're just going to leave?
My heart couldn't accept the idea of seeing her.
Sorry. See you tomorrow.
I thought you wanted to know about Kaede!
Kagiroi Shaku Kei Another
Kagiroi.
Third Night
The Lustful Woman, Dance of the Malicious Flower
Third night. The lustful, dance of the malicious flower.
Oh dear me. Have you gotten taller again?
Nezu-sama...
A pleasure to see you again.
Aoi-san, there's no need for you to greet me so formally.
Also, I'd prefer it if you called me by my first name.
Of course.
Um, so where is Ajisai?
I had her go home.
I have something I'd like to speak to you about alone.
It has to do with the Nikubi Festival on New Year's Eve.
This will be your first time participating, correct?
Yes.
Kaede mentioned it to me, so I know of the festival.
Do I have to register somewhere to participate?
Not at all. Nothing that troublesome.
All you need to do is work together with another
girl who wants to participate in the festival.
Work together?
Oh, I nearly forgot.
Another letter from your father was delivered.
Another one?
He must be really worried about you.
About six months ago, he started
sending these to me every month.
This is another letter from my father...
And the contents of it are basically the same as usual.
I'm sure he's lonely too.
But, this letter...
There's something off about this one.
Nezu-sama, here's this month's rent and tuition fee.
It's a little less than it should be...
But starting next month, I'll take on more
part time jobs and pay you back for sure.
Please give me a little more time.
Aoi-san, you really are stubborn.
I've told you countless times that you don't need to pay me.
No, I can't do that.
Please excuse me.
Oh dear, you don't need to be in such a rush.
How about I put on some tea and
we can talk about Kaede-chan?
Kaede-chan really was quite taken with you.
No matter what you were doing, she
was always right next to you.
Th-That's not...
She never opened up to me at all.
I really want to know how you got her to open up to you.
Oh my, how dangerous.
I'll clean it up, so stay away from it, okay?
S-Sorry...
Oh dear, resting already?
How nice.
You have quite the impressive dick.
It's so magnificent.
It's so tasty.
Please give me more!
H-Huh?
Am I dreaming?
Sumire-san is sucking my dick?
Oh, it's twitching.
I want to hurry and put it inside me.
I want this huge thing to pierce through me.
Wh-What...
Oh, you're awake?
You have quite the gentle face, but
you're hiding a monster down here.
Its shape, its size... Everything about it is perfect!
Do you mind me continuing?
It's very delicious.
I want to take care of it every day!
It's very splendid.
Wh-Why are you...
Why? Isn't that obvious?
I'm quite fond of you.
An older woman like me might not be your type,
but I've had my eye on you for a while now.
It has a little bit of a bitter taste.
But I like this taste.
And Kaede-chan had this splendid dick
to herself this entire time, huh?
I'm so jealous.
I can't move...
S-Stop!
I won't. You're mine.
You're mine and mine alone.
If you say no, I won't let you cum.
Oh, that's no good.
You can't cum yet.
All of your sperm is mine.
I need you to cum inside me.
B-But I don't want to...
Today is a really dangerous day for me.
So I'd like you to flood my insides with
your cum and give me your child.
Little you is saying that he wants to become one with me.
There's nothing to worry about. If I get pregnant,
you'll only become my husband.
I'll give you my everything every day.
Please leave everything to me.
I've waited for this day for so long.
I've been satisfying myself with
thoughts of you all this time.
And now my dream is coming true!
But there is one thing I need to apologize to you for.
It's coming inside...
Please, I get it already, so please stop!
This isn't my first time.
I wish I could have given you my first time,
but I hope you can forgive me.
My first time
was with your father.
What did you just say?
So good!
I-It's so good!
It's hitting me so deep!
So good!
Amazing! I can feel it hitting against me every time!
It's amazing! So amazing!
It's so powerful!
Yes! That's it!
You're more amazing than your father!
I've never had such a large and impressive dick as this!
So good!
Wa-Wait! What did you just...
Yes! I love this! I love this!
So deep! It's going so deep!
No... I can't hold it in any longer!
That's fine. Give it to me! Give me
thicker cum than your father's!
Fill me up with enough semen to get me pregnant!
I-I'm cumming!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
Cum!! Cum!! Cum!!
Inside me!
Your thick semen...
I want... I want your child!!
So hot! It's so hot!
It's so hot! So hot!!
Tell me everything.
What do you mean?
Don't try to play dumb!
Tell me about my dad and Kaede.
Do you really wanna know that bad?
Don't you get lonely being by yourself, senpai?
Yeah, I guess I do.
But when I feel lonely, I just remember your
cute face and "make myself feel better".
Huh?
Wh-What are you doing?! I'm trying to have
a serious talk with you and you do that?!
Don't do that in front of people!
So you know what this motion means then, huh...
Th-That hurts!
Can't you take a joke...
K-Kaede?
Where'd you go?
Y-You idiot!
What are you doing?!
Kaede?
Senpai, this village...
Nezu-sama, they own me...
K-Kaede?
What are you say...
You fucking idiot!
What the hell are you doing?!
You were about to kill yourself!
My name is Kaede.
Please use it.
Senpai... Thank you.
You still can't move your body, can you?
You just gulped down that drugged tea so easily.
Please just keep lying there and rest.
Y-You...
Oh dear, looks like the weather's taken a turn for the worse.
The weather on the day you lost
your mother was just like this.
The minute she was hit by that car...
It made a sound just as loud as the thunder.
I'm pretty sure she was screaming too.
Why do I know, you ask?
That's because Kaede was driving the car and got
a front row seat to your mother getting hit.
What are you...
The parent and child that came to
apologize to us weren't you two!
Body doubles can be bought for the right price.
You're lying!
You're lying! You're lying! You're lying!!
Why would Kaede kill my mother?!
For my sake, of course.
I begged her to do it.
Aoi-san, you're...
translation: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч