Umm...
This is my Valentines... chocolate...
Did you say something, Misaki?
I-I-it's nothing!
Idiot!
Original Work
Hyokoro
I'm off!
Onii-chan, you idiot.
Little Sister
Chocolate Sex
Wow, she sure is something.
Now I have something to use tonight.
Oh, staring straight down at girls' butts again.
You're thinking of something obscene again, huh?
How indecent.
What I think of is my own business!
Well, guess I can't argue with that.
That's what keeps you unpopular anyway.
Just keep that up forever, okay?
Being perverted I mean.
This girl acting all high-and-mighty is Takaoka Misaki.
I'm Takaoka Makoto, and she is my stepsister.
Possesses elegant beauty.
Has excellent academic performances.
And has outstanding physical capabilities.
But, she also has personality issues.
When we were little,
at the time when both our parents married each other,
we started to live and grow as real siblings.
However,
one day, she just started being pushy.
She started calling me too informally,
and the days where she treats me as a fool just went on.
But that's until today, Valentine's day.
Nothing again this year, huh?
Geez, Valentine's day my ass!
And everybody else is on the love highway already!
This day is really bothersome.
I'll just go home, jack off a bit, and then sleep.
Onii-chan.
Stop that!
Hey...!
Are you always this aroused?
Of course not, you pervert!
Then how do you explain this?
If you keep touching me...
I'll kill you!
So stop... already...
No...
Someone might come in...
Somebody might see...
Stop this already you idiot!
Oh no, that's...
No...!
I'm about to...
We shouldn't do this, you know?!
It'd be bad if we do this!
This is already a crime.
Do you even understand?
If I tell someone about this,
your normal life would end there and then...!
I'm going to tell Mom and Dad about this!
I won't forgive you for this.
Hey, listen...
Are you listening to me?
This is unfair!
Don't!
I... I don't want this!
I'm going to cum!
I-I'm cumming.
Geez, you're just too forceful.
Makoto, you idiot...
I'm sorry!
What was that?
Calm down.
This is my room.
Why is Misaki half-naked in my room?
Half-naked?
So that means, just now...!
H-he saw me.
Him of all people.
Why did he come home earlier than usual?
Wait forget that, I must think of an excuse
that could balance this situation.
Hey, Misaki-san?
What were you doing in my room?
Umm, well...
You know, something like...
Well, however you put it, it looks like you were... masturbating.
Okay, I admit!
I love you, so I went ahead and did it on your bed alone!
Something wrong with it?
Did she just confess?
Crap.
I told the truth.
Then, that's that. So if you'll excuse me...
Wait.
What?
You just bluntly said that you were holding back from me.
Don't blame me for what'll happen then.
So, you were also holding back?
Of course I was!
You have this sexy body.
You just don't know how many times I jacked off thinking about it.
Shut up.
But, you seem to be really docile today.
What did you say?
If it were the usual you,
you would have knocked me straight out by just doing this.
No...
She's moaning...
Her aroused face looks really cute.
Hey, Misaki.
Could you have been fooling me before?
What are you saying?
Can you imagine how much I had to put up with?
Idiot!
I wasn't able to say it for a long, long time.
Wow, Makoto's thing is big.
Hey, you...
No matter how much I tried to show you before,
you never once noticed.
Tried to show?
I felt like I was just being toyed around
with and being treated as a fool.
I just...
Didn't want to confront you directly.
What's this?
It's amazing.
Where did you learn to do this?
From the porn mags under this very bed.
Hey Makoto, do you know what day it is today?
Yeah, it's Valentine's day right?
That's right.
It's been exactly ten years since we first met.
Think of this as an honor, okay?
Because I'm about to give you my virginity,
that I have been holding on for ten years.
I won't forgive you if we don't enjoy this together.
Misaki...
It's right inside.
Yeah, your pussy feels great.
Lecher, pervert!
It's wrapping me tight, and it feels hot.
Don't say it, idiot!
I can't hold back anymore.
It's okay, let's do it.
Let's have lots of sex.
Oh no...
No...
I love you! I love you...
No, I can't hold on anymore...
I can't...!
You're about to cum?
No I'm not!
Here, don't hold back.
I'm not trying to hold back.
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan!!!
Sorry, I released a bit inside.
Wait, it's more than I thought.
It's inside...
What am I acting as her "Onii-chan" for?
It's okay.
I want to have lots more of your cum inside me.
We're not yet finished, right?
Of course!
It's not going to be over
until I've released everything that was built
up in me when I was still holding it back!
This, this is amazing.
Yes! Yes!
Wow...
It feels... It feels good...
This is just as I had imagined it to be.
The very thing that I was fantasizing
about is happening right now.
And Onii-chan was also thinking of the same thing...
Yes!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to release
every drop of it
inside you.
Release it.
Pour everything in me.
I love you...
I love you!
Misaki!
Cum!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan...
After that incident,
I thought Misaki would have a change of heart
with her attitude towards me, but...
This is really something.
Now I have something to use tonigh...
She's still completely the same when we're outside.
Damn.
But I think things are now different than they were before.
That's because we now understand each other's feelings.
I think.
Well anyway, Valentine's Day don't seem so bad after all.
Idiot!