Umm... well, you see...
I... err... l-like you, Mihashi-senpai.
Please go out with me.
You...
Don't you know the rumors about me?
Huh?
It's nothing.
A-Anyway...
I wanted to say that I like you Mihashi-senpai.
Okay then.
Huh?
I said it's okay,
if you're alright with me.
For real?
Thank you very much!
I hope we'll get along well, Mihashi-senpai!
Yes, I hope so too.
Then Taiki-kun,
why don't we go home together?
Okay, Chizuru-senpai!
I wanted you to remove that "senpai" bit though...
Yes, did you say something Chizuru-senpai?
No, I didn't.
Okay, Mihashi-senpai.
— One week later
Chizuru-senpai...
Say "ah".
Starting today, let's study for our end of term tests at my house.
Huh?
I'm going to look over your study progress.
But is that okay?
That'd mean suddenly barging into your place.
It's alright,
I live alone.
What?
Chizuru-senpai lives alone...
Only the two of us will be there.
Taiki-kun.
Oh, Chizuru-senpai.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm going to quickly get changed, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
That's really good for you Chizuru.
I'm envious.
Really?
Chizuru-senpai looks cute in her P.E. outfit.
Shh,
keep quiet.
I'm going to do something good.
It's slowly getting big,
and stiff.
You can't do that, Chizuru-senpai!
In such a place...
No way...
We haven't even held hands yet,
so this thing is...
Taiki-kun,
why don't you just keep quiet?
Okay, Chizuru-senpai.
Chizuru-senpai!
I'm going to punish the boy who can't keep himself quiet.
I already told you to be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Jeez Taiki-kun.
It's getting even bigger and bigger.
Do my breasts really feel that good?
Could it be that you're at your limit?
Are you going to let it out?
It's okay.
Give it to me.
Let it all out.
Your cum tastes great.
There's still some left.
It's delicious.
It already released a lot,
but it's still this big.
Senpai...
I got very wet from sucking your dick.
Umm... this is...
It'll be bad to do it here.
If someone sees us...
No, I'm going to do this because I want to.
Just stay put there and do whatever I say.
Understood?
Okay...
Besides,
your thing here looks like it wants to do it with me.
I'm sorry.
I like someone who is honest.
Oh wow,
your dick is filling my insides.
It feels good.
Your dick feels great.
Oh no...
I'm doing something this indecent in the classroom.
Someone might see us here, and yet,
I'm still doing it with Taiki-kun.
Oh yes...
This is bad, this is something really nasty.
I know that, but my hips are still moving.
It's coming.
I'm cumming!
Taiki-kun.
There, just keep on making me feel good.
More, more, deeper...
I want your dick badly.
That's...
It's hitting my womb.
Force it, force it in more.
Taiki-kun.
I want more of it...
There it is again.
I'm going to cum again.
You came lots again Taiki-kun.
Taiki-kun, Taiki-kun, Taiki-kun, Taiki-kun...
Taiki-kun.
Taiki-kun!
Jeez, Taiki-kun!
Yes, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're fantasizing about,
but we're going now.
We're going to study at my house, right?
Oh, yes...
I'm sorry.
Just wait a bit.
Okay.
Living alone...
Come in.
I already know this, but she's still very cute.
Alone with Senpai...
Senpai is my girlfriend.
What's wrong?
Come in already.
I'm already prepared for it.
Hey, Taiki-kun!
That expression looks gross.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're fantasizing about something weird again, aren't you?
Well...
It looks so obvious.
Oh well.
Just come in already?
I'm going to prepare some tea.
But you know,
you are weird, for asking me out.
Huh, why?
You know about it, right?
The rumors about me.
Rumors?
I don't...
but it doesn't really matter to me.
I'm...
I see.
Well then,
let's start studying.
The rumors about Chizuru-senpai,
were only revealed to me after we started dating.
I never knew,
but it's actually spread throughout school.
It's about Ikeda-sensei and Chizuru-senpai's immoral relationship.
Ikeda-sensei is an eloquent and young teacher,
he's also good-looking.
He was especially popular among the girls at school.
I've also recently seen reports about relationships
between students and teachers at school,
so it's not really that implausible.
However, it was just a rumor about her in the end.
There isn't a shred of evidence to support it.
It's just a rumor.
I understand that very well.
I understand but...
But...
My imagination just doesn't want to let it go.
Sensei...
Come to me.
I want it.
What is it that you want?
Won't you plead for it like you usually do Mihashi?
No...
I want it already!
Then, shall we end this session now?
No, I'll say it.
I'll say it.
Then say it.
I want you to fill my...
wet pussy...
What?
I can't hear you.
I want you to fill my pussy,
with your thick and stiff dick.
Make love to me with it!
Here I go Mihashi.
Did you cum as soon as I put it in?
N-No...
I did not...
It's hitting, it's hitting me deep inside.
Oh no!
Your dick is hitting my womb!
No, I just came so my thing down there is sensitive.
Please, let me rest for a bit.
Sensei!
I love it!
Oh no...
I'm...
I'm starting to lose it!
No!
Something's coming.
It's coming.
It's coming!
I'm going crazy.
I'm scared.
Sensei, I'm scared!
I'm cumming!
Hey, Taiki-kun.
You're not even listening anymore.
Jeez.
I'm sorry.
You seem tired already.
Why don't we take a short break?
I have to ask her.
I have to be sure.
Even if I use a roundabout method...
If this goes on, I'll...
Umm...
Ikeda-sensei seems quite cool doesn't he?
He's in a league far from me in terms of manliness.
What do you think Chizuru-senpai?
Oh, so you did know...
No, it's...
Then that rumor really is...
I guess that's just natural.
I know.
I know about it.
Though I only heard about it once we'd started dating.
I know about it, but I still like you...
You said yes, even though it was one really sucky confession.
There isn't even any chemistry, yet
I'm always the one getting excited.
But still...
I can't just be number two.
I just won't be able to stand it.
So?
Ikeda-sensei is cool,
compared to some guy like me who always
fantasizes about perverted things.
I-I don't want to admit it,
but I think he's far more compatible with you,
and I think it's just natural.
That's why...
That's why I want you to...
to be happy with Sensei!
This is the end.
This is all for the best.
Goodbye to the springtime of my life.
Senpai, goodbye.
That was...
That was for lying to me about not knowing!
Tears...
That was my first kiss, you know?
And thanks to you, it tasted like mucus.
Chizuru-senpai.
First kiss? So you mean...
Took you long enough to notice, idiot.
That rumor you see,
was spread by someone who I thought was my best friend.
Ikeda-sensei once confessed to me,
and when I tried to ask for advice,
that rumor was the result.
I was a victim of someone's jealousy.
I have friends that believed me,
but the rumor had already spread far and wide.
Of course, I properly turned him down,
though, I'm like this so I just made more enemies.
I'm sorry!
I didn't even try to understand you Senpai.
I'm so sorry.
Let's see...
Then maybe you should be punished for it?
Punished?
That's right, as punishment, you need
to tell me why you came to like me.
Are you really okay with just that?
It was love at first sight.
No matter how I look,
you simply just hit the right spots.
The first time I saw you,
you grabbed my heart tight.
You seemed quite harsh at first,
but you're actually quite gentle,
and compared to me, you're also very intelligent,
and with your small stature and round eyes...
Oh, and the lunch you made earlier was also very delicious.
Please stop.
You also have good looks.
Your voice is also very cute,
it rejuvenates my soul, and soothes me.
And of course, just looking at you already
makes my heart throb wildly,
– even now I'm...
– Stop!
I-I understand already.
Sorry for even asking!
So, if you can promise not to lie to me like that anymore,
I'm willing to do a continuation of earlier.
Huh?
Okay!
This is really embarrassing.
Can we stop this after all?
Oh? Are you going to be the one to break a promise Senpai?
You meanie...
Jeez, not my breasts...
– So here then? Alright.
– Hey, wait...!
Senpai your pussy looks very beautiful.
Huh? It's really wet.
There's lots of your love juices.
Senpai, could this be...
Even girls sometimes fantasize about indecent stuff, you know?!
Idiot!
H-How cute!
I also can't hold back anymore.
Can we do it already?
Yes, let's do it.
Taiki-kun...
Chizuru-senpai, it's twitching.
Did you just... cum?
No way, oh no...
It's my first time, and yet...
This is...
Shall we stop this?
I'm okay.
So just move as you want to.
Make me feel you inside me more!
Senpai!
Senpai, Senpai!
Taiki-kun!
Taiki-kun, Taiki-kun!
I'm about to cum!
No!
So this is what semen looks like.
How warm.
It's still hard.
That's good.
Chizuru-senpai...?!
You can't, there's still some cum left...!
It feels good Taiki-kun.
The thought of wanting to be one with someone you love,
is just Human instinct.
You can't stop it.
Taiki-kun.
I love you.
I love you!
Hey Taiki-kun,
do you know why I fell for you?
It's because you looked straight at
me as you said that you liked me.
You're the only one who ever did that.
So I guess that means it was love at first sight for me too.
More, more!
I'm never going to make you cry again Senpai.
That's why, when we graduate,
will you marry me?
That's just too fast!
But, you're just unfair.
This is...
It's okay.
Inside my mind, you're already pregnant with my child.
That's not okay at all!
I'm going to cum!
Okay, cum!
Chizuru!
You're cumming inside me!
Umm, Chizuru-senpai,
am I not good enough for you?
Aw, you're still addressing me like we're just acquaintances.
Even though you called me "Chizuru" earlier...
Well, umm... I...
Chi-Chi-Chizu...
Chizuru!
Then we need to pass the end term exams first!
Taiki!