Um... so... um, I... I'm i-in love with... Mihashi Senpai.
Please go out with me.
So, you don't know the rumors about me?
Huh?
It's nothing.
So, um, anyways. I'm really in love with Mihashi Senpai...
It's okay.
Eh?
I said, it's okay. As long as you're
fine with someone like me.
Really? Thank you very much! I’m really
looking forward to it, Mihashi Senpai!
Me, too. Let's get along well. Why don't we
start with going home together, Taiki-kun?
Okay, Chizuru-Senpai!
It would be totally fine if you just called me Chizuru...
Yes? Did you say something, Chizuru-Senpai?
No, it's nothing.
Okay, Mihashi-Senpai.
KaKushi Dere 3
Lovely Dovey Syndrome
Translation: Snake | Timing: romeyo007 |Typesett&Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http:/www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
One Week Later
Chizuru Senpai...
Let’s study for finals together at my house today.
I'll help you check on your work.
But is it okay for me to just show
up without asking ahead of time?
It's fine, I live alone.
Chizuru Senpai live alone... it'll just be the two of us...
Taiki-Kun!
Yes? Oh, Chizuru-Senpai!
Sorry for the wait, I’ll go change right away!
Okay.
Let's go.
You guys are so in love, Chizuru! I'm jealous!
Chizuru-Senpai’s cute in her gym clothes as well...
Shh, please be quiet.
Let's do something fun.
Oh, it's getting bigger and harder.
You shouldn't do that, Chizuru-Senpai! Not out here...
That's... We haven't even held hands and...
Will you just be quiet!
Yes, I'm sorry, Chizuru Senpai!
Chizuru Senpai!
A bad boy who can't stay quiet needs to be punished!
Even though I'm telling you to be quiet...
I'm sorry...
Amazing... it's getting harder and harder!
Woah... Do my boobs feel that good?
Could it be that you're almost cumming?
Hurry and... let it out!
It's fine, let out lots of semen!
Taiki-kun's semen is tasty!
Oh, there's more.
Tasty! So much... you can let out more right?
Taiki-kun's is still so hard.
Senpai...
I got really wet from sucking on Taiki-kun's penis...
We really shouldn't go this far here... if someone sees...
No... we’re doing it because I want to...
Just be quiet and do what I say! Get it?
Okay...
Besides, this part of Taiki-kun
seems quite eager to do it...
I'm sorry...
I like honest boys.
Amazing! Taiki-kun's penis went all the way inside me!
It's so good!
Taiki-kun's penis feels so good!
No... I'm doing such perverted
things... in the classroom...
Even though... someone might see...
I'm doing perverted things... with Taiki-kun...
So good...
No... even though I know... I shouldn't be doing this...
My hips... my hips won’t stop!
Coming... something's coming!
Taiki-kun... yes... more... make me feel better...
More, more... I want it deeper inside!
No... not there...
It's hitting my womb...
Harder... harder, thrust harder! Taiki-kun!
I want more!
Again... No, I'm cumming again!
You let out so much again, Taiki-kun...
Taiki-kun...
Taiki-kun!... Taiki-kun!
Geez, what’s with you!?
Ah, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you were daydreaming
about but let’s go.
Weren't we going to study at my place?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Um, give me a moment, please.
Oh, okay.
Mihashi
She lives alone...
Please come in.
Woah... She's so cute no matter
how many times you look...
I'm alone... with Senpai... Senpai
who is... my girlfriend...
What's wrong? Hurry up and come in!
I'm thinking of the same things...
Hey, Taiki-kun!
That face is kind of disgusting, you know.
Ah, I’m sorry.
I bet you were daydreaming of something weird again...
Um...
Geez, don't be such an open book.
Never mind, come in and wait for
a moment. I'll go make some tea.
But come to think of it you're quite
weird, dating someone like me...
Huh? Why would you say so?
You know about the rumors about me, right?
Rumors?
I have no idea. I don't think stuff
like that matters, anyways. I...
I see...
Well, let's get on with the studying.
I learned about the rumors about Chizuru
Senpai after I confessed to her.
Though I had never heard of it before, apparently
everyone at school knew about it.
Hey, did you hear the rumor about Ikeda-Sensei?
That she had an affair with Ikeda-Sensei...
He's dating a student, right?
This part is slightly tricky, You'll regret it
properly right now.
Ikeda-Sensei was a young, talented, handsome, and
extremely popular amongst female students.
New of teachers going after their students
pop out from now to then...
So I guess it's not impossible...
But for Chizuru Senpai, it's nothing
but a rumor? with no proof at all.
It's just a rumor...
I should know that, but even so... I
can't stop my negative thoughts...
Sensei...
Come... I want it!
What do you want?
Won't you beg me like you usually do, Mihashi?
No... It's so embarrassing!
Shall we end it like this today then?
No! I'll say it, I’ll say it.
Well then, go ahead.
In Chizuru's soaking wet pussy...
Hmm? I can't hear you.
Please fill up Chizuru's pussy with
Sensei's thick and hard cock!
Please love me lots and lots!
Here we go, Mihashi!
Hmm? Did you cum from just putting it in?
No... I didn't... I didn't cum...
It's hitting deep... deep inside...
No... Sensei's cock is hitting... my womb!
No! I'm really sensitive from just cumming!
Please! Let me rest for a bit! Sensei!
Love you! I love you!!
No... don't... I don't know anymore!
No... coming...
Something's coming...
Coming! Coming, it's coming!
I'll go crazy!
Scary... Sensei! Sensei I'm scared!
Coming... coming, coming, coming!
Hey Taiki-kun! You're not listening at all, are you? Geez!
I'm sorry...
Taiki-kun seems tired, so I guess we'll take a break.
I have to ask her. I have to,confirm...
even if I don't ask directly I should...
If this goes on I'll...
Um, Ikeda-Sensei is really cool, right? He's
so much better than someone like me...
What does Chizuru Senpai think?
Oh, so you knew, after all.
No, that's not what I...
That rumor is... yeah... I knew. I knew about it.
Although I only heard of it after I started dating Senpai.
Even so I'm still in love with Senpai...
But then, I really thought I'd get
rejected, and yet you said yes...
And I was really happy despite feeling that
the relationship was a little one-way...
But I really can't... I can't take it
if Senpai is also dating Sensei...
So?
Ikeda-Sensei’s a great man, and much better than
someone like me who only daydreams of perverted stuff...
I don't want to admit but, he's a much
better match for Chizuru-Senpai...
And that's what should happen...
So please... be happy with Sensei!
It's over now. It's okay, this is how
it should be. Goodbye, my youth.
Goodbye, Senpai...
That was for lying to me about not knowing the rumors!
Tears...
Geez, that was my first kiss, and it
tasted like snot thanks to Taiki-kun.
Chizuru-Senpai, did you just say first kiss?
You're so slow at realizing, you idiot.
That rumor was spread by a girl I thought was my friend.
I asked for her advice when Ikeda-Sensei
confessed to me, and it happened.
I guess she was envious.
I had friends who believed me, but
the rumors got larger and...
Of course, I rejected Ikeda-Sensei...
But then, being me I kept making enemies and...
I'm sorry! I didn't even try to figure out
what the truth was, I... I'm sorry!
I guess... well why don't you take a punishment?
Punishment?
Yeah, as a punishment, tell me
why you fell in love with me.
Oh, just that? First of all it was love at first sight. You
were perfectly my type no matter how I looked.
My heart skipped a beat the moment I saw you,
and you looked like a serious and strict person but then you
had a very kind side, and unlike me you're smart and then,
Your shorter figure and your sparkling eyes... and
the food you cook, the bento last time was great!
Stop...
You have a great sense of style,
and the way you talk is cute,
and you're calm and healing, and I get butterflies
just looking at you, and now we are...
Stop!
I get it, okay? It's my fault, okay?!
So, if you promise never to lie to me again...
we can keep going, from just now...
Huh? Yes!
it's really embarrassing... can we leave it here for today?
Hmm? So Senpai's the one who's
gonna to break the promise?
Meanie...
Not my breasts... anymore...
Down here, right? I get it.
Hey wait, wait!
Senpai's pussy is really pretty!
Huh? It's really wet. There’s so much of lewd juices...
Hey Senpai, is this...
Girls daydream of perverted stuff, too! Idiot!
So cute...
I can't hold back anymore either, can we do it?
Yeah, it's fine.
Taiki-kun!
Chizuru-Senpai... you're twitching...
could it be that you came?
No way... no... it's my first time and yet...
Should we stop?
I’m okay, so... do as you want...let
me feel more of Taiki-kun!
Senpai!
Senpai, Senpai!
Taiki-kun!
Taiki-kun! No...
Taiki-kun... Taiki-kun...
I can't... cumming!
No...
So this is... semen... it's warm...
It's still energetic, huh?
Great...
Chizuru-Senpai...
You can't... there's still semen on it...
It feels great, Taiki-kun.
It's an instinct to want to connect with the one you love.
I can't stop it.
Taiki-kun, love you, I love you!
Hey Taiki-kun, do you know why I fell in love with you?.
Taiki-kun looked at my directly and said you loved me.
You're the only one who's ever done that!
I fell In love with you at first sight as well!
More, more!
I won't ever make Senpai cry again, so...
So... when we graduate, please marry me!
That's too much of a rush! But...
geez, you meanie! This...
It's okay... in my fantasies, Chizuru
Senpai is pregnant with my child!
That's not okay at all!
I'm, I’m cumming!
Okay, come at me!
Chizuru!
No!
Inside... it's coming out!
Um... Chizuru Senpai... is it not okay with me?
Geez, you're still calling me like we're strangers.
Even though you called me Chizuru earlier.
No, that’s well, um, that's... Chi... Chi-Chi...
Chizuru!
Well, let’s start with passing the finals shall we, Taiki?