Um... This is Valentine's Day's chocolate...
Did you say something, Misaki?
I didn't say anything!
Idiot!
I'm leaving!
Translation: Snake | Timing, Typeset, Encode: ShocWave
Onii-chan such an idiot...
Sister Chocolate Ecchi
Wow, this is quite amazing...
This'll be my snack tonight.
Heh, so you're staring at a girl's ass,
thinking about lewd things again, aren't you?
Pervert!
Isn't it my choice to think what I want?
I guess you're right. It explains
why you're unpopular perfectly.
You might as well spend your whole life like that.
Like the pervert you are.
This high-handed woman is Takaoka Misaki.
The step-sister of me, Takaoka Makoto.
Great looks,
perfect grades,
and amazing at sports.
However, her personality is horrible to deal with!
When Misaki and I were still kids, our
single parents married each other,
and we were raised as if we were actual siblings.
But before I knew it, she became really arrogant,
and started to laugh at me and boss me around.
Up until Valentine's Day this year, which is today.
As expected, hone this year as well.
Geez, why does Valentine's Day even exist!?
Everyone being so lovey dovey about it!
It's just a nuisance!
Well, let's just go home and sleep.
Onii-chan...
S-Stop it already...
Are you always in heat?
There's no way that'd be true, you pervert!
Then what's this?
If you keep teasing me like that...
I'll... I'll kill you!
So just stop...
No... Someone will come!
We'll be seen by someone!
So just stop such ridiculous things, idiot!
No! Not there...
No! You can't!
This isn't something you can do, you know!
Doing such things is wrong...
This is crime. Don't you understand?
If I tell this to someone...
Your life... will be ruined!
I'll tell mom and dad about this!
I'll never forgive you...
Hey, are you listening?
Are you listening?
That's... That's so mean.
Don't!
N-No...
I'm... cumming again!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Geez, you're so rough...
Makoto, you idiot...
I'm... I'm sorry!
What was that? Calm down.
This is my room right?
Why is Misaki half-naked in my room?
Come to think of it instead of
half-naked that was more like...
I was seen...
And of all people, seen by Makoto!
Why did he come back earlier than usual?
More importantly, how do I justify this situation!?
Um, Misaki-san?
What were you doing in my room?
Well, you see...
You know, it's that!
Um, nothing really...
No matter how you think about
it, that was masturbating...
That's right!
I like you, so I was getting myself off on your bed!
You got a problem!?
A confession?
This is bad. I blurted out the truth by mistake...
Well, that's all it was, so I'll be leaving now.
Hold up!
What?
You're just going to ignore the fact that
I was holding back all this time?
You've been holding back as well?
Of course!
Growing into such a slutty body,
and not knowing how many times I jerked off to you...
Shut up!
But you're quite docile today aren't you?
What did you say?
Normally, you'd try to kill me
for doing something like this.
No... No...
This is bad... Her face when she's feeling it is really cute!
Hey Misaki...
You're not fooling me or anything, right?
What are you talking about?
How much to you think I've been holding back?
Idiot!
I've always wanted to tell you!
Makoto's is huge...
Wait... You...
You didn't notice despite the effort
I put into appealing you...
Appeal?
I only remember being hit or bossed around...
That's just because, I wanted to be close to Makoto...
What's this? It's amazing...
Where did you learn these things?
The porn mags under your bed.
Hey Makoto, do you know what day it is today?
Yeah. Valentine's, right?
That's right. It's been exactly ten years since we met.
You'd better feel honoured.
I'll be giving you my first time that
I've been saving for ten years.
I won't forgive you if you don't
make me feel good as well.
Misaki...
It's really in...
Yeah, your pussy feels really good!
No!
That's lewd, you pervert!
It's really tight and hot!
Don't say that, you idiot!
I can't hold back or anything anymore!
It's fine. Let do it.
Do me lots.
No... No!
I love you! Love you!
No!
I can't take it anymore! No!
Are you about to cum?
That's... That's not...
Come on, don't hold back.
I'm not holding...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan!
Sorry, I came inside a little...
Actually quite a bit...
Inside...
Why am I reacting when she calls me "Onii-chan"...
It's all right...
Please fill me up with lots of your semen.
We're not done yet, right?
Of course not!
I won't end it until I've cum enough to
make up for all that I've held back!
Amazing! It's amazing!
Yes! Yes!
Amazing!
It feels good!
It feels so good!
Just like I imagined...
All that I've imagined is actually happening!
Onii-chan was thinking of the same things!
I'm cumming!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I'm... I'm cumming!
I think I'm close as well...
This time... I'll put it all inside of you.
Let it out! Shoot lots inside me!
I love...
I love you!
Misaki!
Cum... cum...
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan...
After such an incident happened, I thought
that Misaki's attitude would change...
Wow, this is quite amazing...
This'll be my snack tonight.
On the outside, she's still the same...
Damn it!
But, it does seem that something
has changed from before.
Maybe because our feelings are connected now.
Well, I guess Valentine's isn't that bad after all.
Idiot!