Hey, Hiruaki!
What?
Starting now I'm going to be watching porn...
So don't come into my room, okay?
What?
Nonoka-chan's coming today, so be quick about it!
I know!
She's already here though...
What, are you all prepared already?
Shut up, you idiot! Go kill yourself.
Translation: Snake | Timing: Anon | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Wait!
You're so wet, that what you say isn't convincing at all.
You've been coming to my house
every day after that anyways.
I'm going home!
Really? Go ahead as you please.
Weren't you going home?
If you don't leave already...
Here you go.
It's in.
Don't let your voice out too much.
Hiroaki will find out.
The person in trouble if he finds out, is you!
I guess you're right.
Oh man, it's about to come out.
If you cum inside, I'll kill you!
My bad.
Not inside!
Nii-chan's watching a good one. I'll borrow it next time.
— Several Days Ago —
Ryuutarou-nii-chan.
Another love letter from Sadako arrived in the mail.
Again?
Geez. An ill-mannered stalker like usual.
Someone really loves you don't they, Nii-chan.
Shut up!
Also, there's someone I want to introduce to you.
This is my friend from the same class.
Nice to meet you, I'm Nogaura Nonoka.
For Hiroaki to bring home a girlfriend...
Good for you.
What are you saying, Nii-chan.
It's not like we're in that kind
to relationship or anything...
Please stop that.
Takizawa-kun and I aren't lovers,
and your arrogant attitude is very annoying!
Hiroaki, is this snapping turtle your type?
Huh? What...
How rude!
What's with calling someone a snapping
turtle the first time you meet!
Don't get so full of yourself just because you're older!
Nonoka-chan! Why are you so upset so suddenly?
Isn't you who's getting full of yourself?
Watch out or I'll rape you!
Rape me if you can you lowlife!
Cut it out, you two!
Hiroaki brought home a troublesome woman, didn't he.
If I had to choose between Sadako
and her, I'd definitely pick Sadako.
Ridiculous. Let's stop thinking about all this.
At these kinds of times it's best to fap to
Misaki-chan, and forget about everything.
Nii-chan, help.
Didn't I always tell you not to come in like that?
Why did you call me if you knew it'd turn out like this?
I thought you'd be able to do
something to end this silence.
You guys haven't said a word
to each other the entire time?
Y-Yeah...
Geez!
Nonoka-chan, right?
If you're not Hiroaki's girlfriend,
why are you here, exactly?
Why don't you ask your little brother there?
She's gonna be my future girlfriend,
so I wanted to show you.
Then don't rely on me!
Do something yourself you idiot!
Oh, I know!
I'll rent a DVD!
Didn't you have something you wanted to watch?
We can all watch and enjoy it together.
So let's...
Wait! It takes thirty minutes just to get to the rental shop.
What am I going to do with her?
Sorry, Nii-chan.
I can't take this atmosphere anymore.
So I'll leave Nonoka-chan to you, okay?
Make sure she doesn't leave.
I'll be back real soon!
Well then, what shall we do?
Um, well...
After watching you guys act so
ridiculously I've gotten sleepy.
I'll have to apologize to Hiroaki, but it'd
be a lifesaver if shell leave on her own.
Well then I suppose you can leave...
I'm borrow your bed, okay?
You're sleeping here!?
By the way, didn't you say
something about raping me earlier?
Isn't now the chance, Onii-san?
You...
What!? A kid like you isn't my type!
Is that so? I'm relieved.
You're not my type, but If you taunt me
like that, I can't sit here doing nothing!
For a kid you have really lewd tits.
Hey it's painful! Are you trying to kill me?
I won't shout or anything, idiot.
Sorry.
It's my first time, so please, rape me more gently.
Huh?
Wait, no! That was a lie!
I get it. You're just saying "I'm a lewd girl".
You don't get it at all!
Either way, I'm going to rape you.
Are you really the same age as Hiroaki?
You're way too grown.
– Here we go.
– No way!
What's this? Your tits are dangerous than I thought.
It's coming out. Open your mouth!
Is it over now?
Your face says "I'm not satisfied at all".
No! You've got it wrong!
Don't worry. The real thing starts now.
Wow, you're soaked.
S-Stop...
Your mouth says no, but your body says yes.
You can resist a bit, you know.
I am!
Doesn't seem like it.
Well it's about time.
I'm not ready yet...
W-Wait!
If you move now...
Stop!
Did you cum from just inserting it inside?
I'm being raped...
There's no way I can cum, you idiot!
Well then, I shall rape you without reserve.
Upon closer inspection, you're pretty cute.
Wha... Wha... What?
What did you...
You've gotten really tight!
What? Are you feeling it because I said you're cute?
Moving your hips on your own like that.
Aw crap.
I'm cumming soon.
Where... do you want it?
Shall I just go on, and cum inside?
If you cum inside...
I'll get a baby...
So rough...
I don't know...
I don't know anymore!
Then, I'll fill you up.
Don't!
Just one question.
What?
You're actually in love with me aren't you?
Huh!?
You didn't resist at all.
You idot!
Who would fall in love with the bastard that doesn't even
read letters someone worked so hard on writing!?
Do Sadako's letters have something to do with...
No way!
You didn't even read them properly? You're the worst.
I shouldn't have come.
I even wrote down my name.
My bad.
But I have to say that the writing is
so small, that it was kind of creepy.
So you came today...
You came to see me?
Shut up!
I hate you!
Nii-chan! Nonoka-chan!
I'm back!
Oh crap, I forgot completely about Hiroaki.
Here it is!
Well, goodbye.
Huh? You're leaving?
The DVD...
I'll...
Come again tomorrow.
— One Month Later
Ryuutarou Noved Out
The meet up's at six.
I should get myself cleaned up
in case something happens.
Getting excited over a class reunion
like that, you're so disgusting.
Nonoka!? How did you get in?
I said I was your sister and the
manager opened the door for me.
And how do you know about the reunion?
I searched around your room and found
the notification for the reunion.
You...
What's with that face? It's disgusting.
The way you talk to yourself is disgusting, too.
Actually, upon closer inspection,
everything about you is disgusting.
Well, I'm off.
Wait up!
You're jealous.
What? Jealous?
Who would be...
I can read you like a book.
You picked up girls like this, and did perverted
things with them, haven't you?
That has nothing to do with you, does it?
Shut up! It's irrelevant but I'll kill you anyways!
How scary!
You...
I'm ridiculously in love you anyways.
I've got to get you to bear my children.
Three would be great.
What are you saying...
Who would... With someone like you...
I'm letting out inside. It's okay, right?
Inside...
I'll killl you...
What's this...
I'll give you this so stop with the
breaking and entering, you idiot!
I hate you so much!