Hey, Hiroaki!
What is it?
I'm going to start my video viewing session,
so don't come in here, okay?
Eh? Nonoka-chan's going to come here today.
Do it quickly, okay?
Alrighty.
She's already here though.
Hey, finished getting ready there?
Shut up, you idiot.
Die.
Hey!
You're already this wet,
so you can't really complain now.
You've been coming here everyday ever since that time.
I'm leaving now.
Really, now?
Go ahead then.
Oh?
Not leaving yet?
If you don't leave now...
Look.
It's in.
Don't let your voice out too much.
Hiroaki will find out.
The one who will be in trouble is you.
I guess you're right.
Woah, I'm about to cum.
Release it inside,
and I'll kill you...
Too bad.
It's in me...!
Nii-chan's watching something quite extreme.
I'll have to borrow it later!
— Some days back —
Ryutarou-niichan!
You have a love letter again from Sadako.
Again, huh?
Geez, that girl is still being a creepy stalker.
Nii-chan's really popular.
Shut up.
Also, I'd like to introduce you to someone.
She's a classmate of mine.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Nogaura Nonoka.
Oh? Never thought you'd finally bring a girlfriend here.
You're not bad at all.
What are you saying, Nii-chan?
We don't have that kind of relationship yet.
Please stop that.
I'm not Takizawa's lover,
and I really hate the way you look down on people like that.
Hey, Hiroaki.
Are you really into these annoying types?
Eh, that's...
How rude!
How can you say that after just meeting the first time?
Don't get cocky just because you're older!
Nonoka-chan, what's gotten into you?
No matter how you look at it, you're the one who's being cocky!
I'm gonna rape you, you bitch!
Then do it if you can, you worthless trash!
Stop it already, you two!
Man, that Hiroaki...
Bringing that strange girl here...
I'd choose Sadako anytime over that bitch.
Anytime.
Damn, I feel like a fool.
Let's just forget about it.
At times like these, I'd just have to
finish one round with Misaki-chan
and take everything off my mind.
Nii-chan, help!
Didn't I always tell you not to barge right in?
Why call me in here if you knew this was going to happen?
I just thought that with you here, this
silence would somehow be broken.
What? She's been silent all this time?
Yeah.
Geez!
Nonoka-chan, right?
If you're not Hiroaki's girlfriend,
then why did you come here?
Why don't you ask you little brother over there?
Umm... Well...
I just thought of showing off my future girlfriend to you...
Then don't ask me to do something about it!
Try to do something on your own, you fool!
Oh yeah, I'll just rent some DVD's!
There's something that I want to watch.
I think we'll all have a good time if we watch that.
Well then...
Wait up.
It'd take 30 minutes just to get to the rental shop.
What am I going to do with her during that time?
I'm sorry, Nii-chan!
I can't keep up with this atmosphere anymore!
And so, I'll leave you with Nonoka-chan.
Don't let her leave, okay?
Now, I'll be back in a jiffy!
Okay, so what do I do now?
Umm, hey there...
I'm now getting sleepy because of the boring
comedy you two showed me earlier.
I feel sorry for Hiroaki,
but it'd be a lot better if she's willing to go away on her own.
I see! Then you'd better leave quickly...
I'll be using the bed, okay?
You're going to sleep here?!
Oh yeah, you said something earlier about raping me.
Isn't this your chance to do it, Onii-san?
This bitch...!
Hey, now. I'm not into cheeky girls like you!
Oh, how rebellious.
You're not my type, but...
If you keep on making a fool out of me like that, then...!
You've got great boobs here despite being a kid.
Hey, I can't breathe!
Do you plan on killing me?
I'm not going to scream, you idiot!
M-My bad...
It's my first time,
so please rape me more gently, okay?
Huh?
I didn't mean that!
What I said was not true!
I got it.
That means I just have to be the perverted one, right?
You don't get it at all!
I don't care about that, but I'll still rape you anyway.
But are you really the same age as Hiroaki?
They've grown too much.
Here, we'll complete the set!
Woah, what's this?
It's a lot better than I thought!
I'm going to cum.
Open your mouth!
Finished already?
You have the look of not being satisfied.
That's not it.
That's definitely not it.
Don't worry. We're just getting started.
Wow.
Your love juice is amazing.
Stop...
Your mouth's really harsh,
but your body just goes with the flow, huh?
Why don't you try resisting a bit?
I'm already trying.
Doesn't look that way though.
Now, it's about time.
Wait, I still need to prepare emotionally for this.
Wait... If you move now, I'll...
Stop...
You came from me just inserting it in?
I'm getting raped here, so there's no way...
...I would cum, you know... Idiot...
Then I'll rape you to my heart's content.
Oh?
You're quite cute from a closer look.
Wh-What... What... What are you...?
Wow, it's getting really tight!
What? Are you getting aroused while getting embarrassed?
You're even moving your hips on your own.
Crap.
I'm about to cum.
Where do you want me to cum?
Do you want me to release it all the way inside?
I'm going get pregnant...
if you cum inside, so...
No, you're too intense...
I don't know.
I can't decide anymore!
Then I'll release it all in you.
No...!
I'd like to ask you something.
What?
Is it possible that you're actually into me?
You were way too willing.
A-Are you a fool?!
I would never like a foolish lowlife who
never even read the letter of someone
who worked so hard just to write it!
Huh? Sadako's letter isn't the very least related to...
Really?
The letter wasn't even read properly.
That's just the worst!
I shouldn't have come here.
I even wrote my name, you now!
S-Sorry about that.
But the letters were too small. They were a bit hard to read.
Wait, you came here today, so...
You came here to meet me?
Shut up!
I really, really hate you!
Nii-chan, Nonoka-chan, I'm home!
Crap, I'd totally forgotten about Hiroaki.
Here!
Goodbye then.
Huh? You're leaving already?
How about the DVD's?
I'll drop by again tomorrow.
— After one month
Ryutarou has moved to another place...
Meeting time is at 6:00, huh?
I don't know what will happen there,
so I'll just have to tidy myself up first.
Getting all excited about an alumni reunion.
That's just so creepy.
Nonoka!
Where the hell did you come from?
I told the landlord I was your little sister and she gave me a key.
Wait. Just how did you know about the alumni reunion?
I secretly went into your room and saw the notification letter.
Why you...!
What's with that face?
It's so creepy, you know.
Your self-blabbering is also creepy.
Oh, but when you look at it, everything about you is creepy.
Thank you for letting me in.
Wait.
Jealousy fail.
What?
J-J-Jealous?
Wh-Who...?
Who in the world...?
You're so easy to read.
You perverted old guy.
You've probably done it like this to an ex-girlfriend, right?
That doesn't concern you, you know?
Even if you do that.
Shut up!
It doesn't concern me, but I'll still kill you!
That'd be troubling.
You...
And you're really into me...
Anyway, I need you to bear my children.
And I want lots of them.
Who would...
Want to bear your...
I'm cumming.
I can cum in you, right?
No, not inside...
It's filling me up...
What's this?
I'll give you this, so you can stop being an intruder, idiot!
I really hate you!