Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:            EmptySoul
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                   Meiko
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:     Collectr
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Timed & Typeset by:       EmptySoul
Karaoke by:     EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Quality Control:             Xanth & Calyrica
Encoded by:        Eternal_Blizzard
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
A Mischievous Spring Breeze
C-Crap!
I'm going to be late on the first day.
This is bad.
Hey, Tsuyoshi.
We're in the same class.
It should be fun again.
No way!
You're so cold, Tsuyoshi.
Wait up!
I wonder what's wrong.
See you later.
S-Sure.
What's wrong?
If you don't hurry, you'll be late.
But...
It looks like it can't get down.
Cats don't get hurt even if they fall from a high place, so it's all right.
But it sounds really scared.
It was crying. So I...
Here.
I won't do anything to you.
Come here.
Ouch!
Why you little...
Come here.
You know, that was my breakfast.
Jeez.
Don't climb that high anymore.
Thanks a lot, Yamaguchi-senpai.
You know who I am?
Oh, no! You're bleeding!
It's nothing.
It could get infected.
All done.
It likes you.
Anyway, what should we
do about this kitten?
What should we do?
My, my.
Crap! We're gonna be late!
Let's run!
Right!
Ouch.
Hi.
A date on the first day
of school, Tsuyoshi?
Ah, Minatsu-san!
Good timing!
No more!
Damn. I'll just barely make it.
M-Minatsu-san.
Ts-Tsuyoshi!
Why does he get to ride
with Minatsu-san?!
You really saved us.
I'm grateful.
Then should I pick you up every day?
Really?
It'll cost you.
You'll handle my share of the cleaning at work, okay?
It's like that?
Yep, it's like that.
That's just cruel.
Good morning, Miko-chan, Mizuho.
You're not late today, Tsuyoshi.
Hopefully there won't be a storm.
Miko-chan, let's go on a date.
Sure.
What's with the handkerchief?
Huh? Oh, this?
Well, it's a charm to keep girls away.
What? Then... can I put one on you too?
Here. Let's put all of these on you.
I think the charm will work better that way.
M-Maybe next time.
In that case, how about you, Mizuho?
They're both so shy.
So this is the new classroom.
We've got some cute girls here.
Jeez! Shindou Reiko? I don't like her.
Hey, hey. You shouldn't badmouth a girl on the first day of school.
Oh, another pretty one!
Dummy.
I finally made it.
Hey, Minoru, you should give yourself a little more time.
Shut up!
These girls are your type.
I'm stuck with you two again.
I hope you don't bring down the average score of the class.
Wh-What do you mean?
Well, I wonder.
I'll let that be your homework.
It's your last year of high school.
Make sure to meet the challenges of studying, sports, and youth head on.
Mitsuki-sensei is our
homeroom teacher, huh?
We're in luck.
Are you the type that moons
over older women?
Depends on the woman.
You two, don't waste your youth in useless chatter.
Exactly.
Sensei, is it okay to pursue
love head on as well?
If possible, I'd prefer that
you focus on studying.
There it is. Listen closely, Tsuyoshi.
Why are you saying that to me?
Looks like Yamaguchi-senpai is in Class 3-C.
Hello.
Miyuki-chan.
Beautiful detective Iijima Miyuki reporting in!
You followed me?
Yeah. That's right.
Anyway, what are you doing?
Not bad.
Because we have a new classroom, um...
You lost your way?
Y-Yeah! That's right.
I get it. You're interested in Yamaguchi-senpai, right?
Not really...
Hi there. I'm Satake Haruhiko
from class 3-C.
I love your eyes.
Huh?
My hand will never forget the warmth of her shoulder.
Who could blame her for being shy after seeing this beautiful, noble face?
You really don't like guys, huh?
You don't even talk to the boys in class.
Despite that, you talked to
Yamaguchi-senpai this morning.
Is he the only one that you can talk to?
Because there was a kitten...
Ai, don't tell me you really...
I think you should give up.
I've heard rumors about other girls.
Oh no!
The teacher asked me to take care of a few things.
Ai, I'll talk to you later.
But... even so, I...
Huh? What's this?
That's most likely a love letter.
Huh?
A love letter just as school starts.
I envy you.
Knock it off, Shinji.
Don't look at me like that.
Why don't you find a more private place to read it?
All right.
Tsuyoshi-kun. I wonder what's going on.
Kakyuusei
Tsuyoshi-san, I love you. I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm.
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
Tsuyoshi-san . . .....................................
I love you . . .
I'll be waiting at Uzuki Park at 5pm . . .
I wonder who wrote this.
Tsuyoshi.
Mizuho?
Ever since we started school, I've always liked you.
I can't bear to just stay friends!
Mizuho.
Tsuyoshi!
No, th-there's no way.
Mayumi? You wrote this?
I'll let you play with me today.
No way. There's no way she'd use a letter in any case.
It can't be helped.
I'll go out with you.
Now, a kiss to prove my love.
No, no, definitely not.
Tsuyoshi-kun, it's not good to keep secrets from friends.
What have we here?
Whoa! A-A love letter?!
Give that back!
No.
I said, give it back!
C-Crap!
This is really bad.
What if someone picks it up?
Um...
Did a weird letter fall around here?
What? N-Not really.
Oh, it's you.
Let's see... that's second class 2-A's Minamizato Ai, right?
Seriously, do you keep track of all the girls' names, even underclassmen?
Of course!
So what we're looking for
is actually a love-
Gah! See ya!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Don't tell me you're planning to get your hands on her?
She's an underclassman. No way I'd do that.
I wouldn't put it past you.
Maybe she wrote the letter?
What should I do?
If I don't give this back to him quickly...
I wonder where his desk is.
What's wrong?
U-Um!
Oh, I get it.
You're in the wrong classroom, right?
I do that a lot too.
When I was a sophomore,
sometimes I didn't realize my mistake until the teacher took attendance.
I'm not doing very well today.
What's wrong, Ai?
It's nothing.
Quit acting so distant and
pretending nothing's wrong.
If you don't tell me, then I'll do this!
Stop! Quit it!
All right, I'll tell you.
Th-This...
I see.
How do I return it?
You're not being very honest.
What you're really worried about is...
who is your competitor to be Yamaguchi-senpai's date.
Act, don't think. That's the best thing to do now.
If you stop, then nothing will happen.
Well, because Yamaguchi-senpai is involved, I really don't want anything to happen.
Thanks for waiting.
Minatsu-chan, the next order is ready.
Okay.
Hey, Mina-san, I'll help you.
Minoru-kun, I still won't pay you, even if you help out.
You're so stingy, Master.
I can't afford to employ three people.
I'm counting on you, Tsuyoshi.
Sorry, but I need to leave early.
Wait! You can't leave so suddenly.
Minoru will be glad to do the rest.
Here.
What am I doing?
If you stop, then nothing will happen.
I-I made it.
Is this the wrong place?
Who's there?
Ai-chan?
There's no need to run away.
S-Sorry.
I see. So you're the one who wrote the letter.
Um... here.
I found it at school.
I had trouble returning it.
Sorry!
What's going on?
An underclassman?
Senpai...
How come I was okay when he touched me?
Why?
How was your date?
A really cute girl showed up.
No way. You're kidding, right?
Here's the proof.
It can't be...
because I wro-
Uh, no.
What was that?
You'd better tell me the truth, Minoru.
I wonder who senpai's date was supposed to be?
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
I would've been satisfied with admiring him from afar.
It was just a coincidence.
Right now, I can't help but hesitate.
Under the red cherry blossoms,
a girl learns the meaning of love.
Kakyuusei, episode 2:
Trembling Cherry Blossoms.
Trembling Cherry Blossoms