Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:            EmptySoul
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                   Meiko
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:        Collectr
Timed & Typeset by:       EmptySoul
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Karaoke by:     EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Quality Control:         E_B & Calyrica
Encoded by:        Eternal_Blizzard
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
The Fading Summer...
Good morning!
Good morning, Mahoko-chan.
Good morning.
So, um...
S-Sorry!
I-I'm fine.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
M-Mahoko-chan...
Yes?
On your next day off...
want to go somewhere with me?
Th-The park would be nice.
Huh? Really?
Yeah.
Then how about we go today after work?
Sure.
Flower arrangement? Like western-style flower arrangement?
I'm studying at Makihara Flower School.
Makihara?
Oh, they buy from us a lot.
I want to become a professional floral arranger,
one who's known throughout the world.
I've never told this to anyone before.
But I wanted you to know.
Why me?
Because... you're my... boyfriend.
Mahoko-chan...
I said it.
Huh? Mahoko-chan!
Where are you going?!
I'm faster than you thought, aren't I?
Seems like it.
I'm surprised.
If you can manage to catch me, I'll do whatever you want.
Really?
Yep!
Gotcha!
That's cheating!
I hadn't even started running yet.
A promise is a promise.
But...
People can see us.
Who cares?
Mahoko-chan, aren't you about done?
You can leave now.
Thanks.
Huh? Where are you going?
I'm going to take an early arragement class today.
I see.
Do your best.
I will!
Welcome!
Wel- Mayumi!
Hi.
I've come to check on you, flower boy.
Quit calling me "flower boy."
I think it suits you.
Geez. I can't win with you.
Of course.
So what are you here for?
Like I said, I came to check on you.
As you can see, I'm working hard.
Looks like it!
Something wrong?
Huh? Nothing really.
I'll get going, then.
Right. Do your best.
Huh? That's amazing.
Isn't it?
Also-
I'm heading out.
Nice work today.
Do your best at your class.
I intend to.
Mahoko-chan!
I wonder what's wrong.
Tsuyoshi, you're dense.
She's obviously jealous.
J-E-A-L-O-U-S.
Jealous?
Ah, young love.
Young love. Young love.
My, my. Young love.
Good luck, Tsuyoshi.
Jealous...
Tsuyoshi-kun, did you finish the deliveries?
Ah! I forgot!
I wonder if I upset Tsuyoshi-san.
I can't believe how I acted.
What's wrong with me?
If I let myself fall in love...
What should I do?
I'm falling for him more and more.
I'm scared.
Tsuyoshi-san...
Look at that fish.
He seems sleepy.
Oh, and that one! He looks strange.
Flowers are good and all,
but fish are interesting too, right?
Huh? Mahoko-chan?
What? Y-Yeah, you're right.
You're acting strange
today, Mahoko-chan.
No, I'm not.
If you say so.
I found us a good place to eat.
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry, but I have an
arrangement exam today.
What? Now?
Yeah.
So I have to go.
You should have told me earlier.
If I'd known, we could've left sooner.
S-Sorry.
I'm out of time. I'm really sorry!
Mahoko-chan.
She took the day off?
Yeah. She called me this morning.
Is she sick?
No. She had some urgent business.
Urgent business?
Deliver these to Makihara Flower School. Thanks.
Makihara?
I'm worried about you.
I gave you a chance to make up for being late yesterday,
but it doesn't seem like your heart is in it.
I'm sorry.
Geh!
Mochida-san, I'm convinced you have talent.
That's why I've given you a recommendation to study abroad in England.
I know.
England?
There's no point continuing today.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, you should go home now.
Okay.
Thank you for everything.
What are you doing?
U-Um, I'm here to deliver these.
A-And then I was checking if your plant was healthy. Um...
You're the florist, right?
Good work.
Take that into the classroom, please.
Right.
England...
Why didn't she tell me?
Could it be...
that I'm getting in her way?
Tsuyoshi-chan!
Mayumi.
Hm, studying abroad in England?
She's pretty amazing.
I wonder if I'm dragging her down.
That's for her to decide.
You make things too complicated.
Shut up! I can't help it!
I don't want to get in the way of her dreams!
Even if she's okay with it, I'm not!
Wh-What?
I envy her a little.
Here. You shouldn't slack off on the job.
You should hurry back!
You're the one who dragged me away!
What a weirdo.
Good work.
Need anything else delivered?
Nope. You're done for the day.
Huh?
Mahoko-chan.
Sorry about today.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, I heard some news from Makihara-sensei.
You've decided to study abroad in England?
Kakyuusei
I knew.
About studying in England.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
What's important is that you fulfill your dream, Mahoko-chan.
You think I should go?
Yeah. It's a wonderful opportunity, isn't it?
It really is.
Everyone has dreams that they wish could come true,
and you're getting a chance
to make that happen.
Not everyone has that chance.
That's why... That's why... you shouldn't give it up.
I guess so.
This is my chance to fulfill my dream.
Yeah.
I'll do my best to make it happen.
Is it really okay...
to go to England?
Yeah. Give it everything you've got.
Okay.
Tsuyoshi-san, you're so kind.
All right! I'll do my best.
C'ya!
I'm heading out for delivery!
Drive safely.
Sure.
It's been a few days, and we haven't had a real conversation.
Hi.
It's not good cold.
Right...
Um, you wanted to talk to me?
Knowing Tsuyoshi, he probably told you to go to England, right?
How'd you know?
He's too nice to say anything else.
Sacrifice is part of love.
But my dream is pretty selfish.
Well, it's your business.
It's just that it's painful to look at him.
Painful?
Don't be so serious.
He's just a man. What a pain!
Thanks for coming!
Really, such a pain.
Take care of this.
Right.
That's your last delivery for today.
That's right. Tsuyoshi-kun, isn't this your last day?
Yeah. Thanks for taking good care of me.
You've really helped us a lot.
No, I didn't really do all that much.
Um...
Mahoko-chan, you need to leave early for class today, right?
It's a little early, but you can go now.
Um, but...
Don't worry about it. After all, you're the pride of our store.
Take care!
I really...
Tsuyoshi-san, want to go
to the beach tomorrow?
The beach?
Summer's almost over,
and I'd like to go one more time.
It's a place full of memories for us, isn't it?
Memories?
Looks like tomorrow's going to be sunny!
O-Ouch!
Are you okay, Tsuyoshi-san?
Did you step on something?
Just kidding!
I got you!
How mean!
I was really worried!
S-Sorry.
Just kidding!
Why, you!
Mahoko-chan!
Today was really fun.
We made some good memories.
Memories?
So you're going?
I'm not going.
I told my teacher yesterday.
I said, "It's too soon for me."
But what about what we talked about?
I'll have more chances.
Is it my fault?
That's not it.
I want to study much more.
That's why...
Then...
we'll be together from now on.
No.
I love you, Tsuyoshi!
But... it scares me.
Mahoko-chan.
I need to break up with you.
At this rate, I'll give up
on my dream someday.
Because my heart will be filled with you!
I'm really selfish, aren't I?
I'm taking advantage of your kindness.
I'm not kind.
I'm just a coward.
I don't have the confidence to support your dream.
It's too hard for me.
At this rate, I'll grow to resent your dream.
You really are kind.
Too kind.
Goodbye!
The Mahoko-chan I love chases her dreams.
The sea was already too cold for us to swim.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
Feelings hidden beneath an arrogant attitude that pushes people away.
An awkward girl with awkward affections.
A heart that wants to be honest but cannot,
like a fickle autumn breeze.
Kakyuusei episode 8:
Selfish Cosmos.
Selfish Cosmos