Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:            EmptySoul
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                   Meiko
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:     Collectr
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Timed & Typeset by:       EmptySoul
Karaoke by:     EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Quality Control:             Xanth & Calyrica
Encoded by:        Eternal_Blizzard
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
Dream-filled New Leaves
Miyuki-chan! Miyuki-chan!
Huh?
What happened? You're so giddy.
Tsuyoshi-senpai said...
Tsuyoshi?
M-Miyuki-chan!
Wait up!
Tsuyoshi-senpai said...
Quit saying his name!
Miyuki-chan!
He works at a coffee shop called Dogeza, so...
Dogeza?
So... what about him?
He said he'll treat me to something at Dogeza as an apology for missing our date.
And you want to go?
Yeah.
Please, Miyuki-chan.
Let's go together.
Me too?
No way.
The manager said he'd make you a "special" parfait.
A "special" parfait?
For free.
Free...
No thanks.
Ouch...
No matter what?
Absolutely not.
Open
Miyuki-chan...
Let's go.
Welcome!
You actually came.
Tsuyoshi-chan, looks like you got her to come.
Good job.
Uh, welcome.
Th-Thanks for the ride the other day.
So you called your girlfriend, huh?
Girlfriend...
She's not my girlfriend yet.
So you're attempting to make her your girlfriend, huh, Senpai?
Here.
And here's the "special" parfait.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Eat up, eat up!
Then I won't hold back!
It's so good!
Here.
It's my special topping.
Thanks, Senpai!
Well, enjoy yourself.
I guess he's not all bad.
She loves me.
She loves me not.
So that's what it was about.
Why don't you do something?
"Something," you say...
We're talking about a high-school girl.
And he's an old man with a mustache.
Age means nothing in love.
It's just like she says.
But you know...
Isn't there anything you can do?
I'll give you a 10% raise.
And if you don't help,
you won't get paid at all!
Understand?!
Got it.
Great.
What do you want?
Today, I've come to bring
you some good news.
Yeah, right.
I guess some people in this world really do notice good things.
You see, Miyuki-chan,
there's this guy who wants to date you.
What?! Who cares?
He's such a pure-hearted, nice guy.
You don't want to know who he is?
Not at all.
Why?
Well, that's...
I guess you're right.
You wouldn't want to date someone you don't even know.
I'd better go turn him down.
I just thought it would've been a good opportunity.
After all, I missed my date with Ai-chan.
That's why I wanted to
take her on a proper date.
What does that have to do with me?
A double date.
A double date?
Right! You could bring Ai-chan with you,
and then we could all go on a date together.
That's a good idea, isn't it?
Miyuki-chan?
Hey, Miyuki-chan.
You're acting a little strange today.
Really?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Yeah. Today during lunch,
I got asked out on a date.
What?! That's great, Miyuki-chan!
But... I think I'll turn him down.
Why?
Hey, why?
Well, that's because Tsuyoshi-senpai told me about it.
I can imagine exactly the sort of guy he'd set me up with.
I'm sure he's a wonderful person.
You're gonna live a long life, Ai.
In any case, this so-called
date is a double date.
A double date?
Right. The two of us and
Tsuyoshi-senpai and some guy.
What?! I'd feel much more confident if you were with me.
A date with Yamaguchi-senpai...
What should I do?
Why am I dreaming about Tsuyoshi-senpai?!
But... what should I do?
I'm so tired.
Uh, good morning.
Am I in the right place?
You're here awfully early.
I couldn't sleep.
Me either.
I've been thinking about the date.
What about you?
I'm really sleepy.
So you couldn't sleep either?
What do you want to do about the date?
It's against my policy to be indecisive.
Okay.
I guess I'll give Tsuyoshi-senpai another chance!
I'm saying we should go on the double date.
I feel refreshed.
Hello? Yamaguchi-senpai?
We can meet up tomorrow.
Are you sure?!
What do you mean by that?
Um, then tomorrow at 10am in front of the movie theater.
Tips for successful dates
I wonder what I should wear.
It's the first time I've been
asked out on a date.
I don't know what to do.
Ai-chan.
Senpai...
It's 10:00.
Is he standing us up again?
Let's go home, Ai.
Everyone's so late.
I wonder if Tsuyoshi was just
messing with me.
Yo! Sorry!
Tsuyoshi's by himself.
By yourself?
He's right here. Behind the pillar.
Th-Thanks for coming today.
M-Master?!
N-No way.
Kakyuusei
What?! Master?!
He's the "pure-hearted, nice guy"?
Hi.
So he's the...
pure-hearted... nice guy....
So anyway, that's how it is.
Let's have fun.
Miyuki-chan!
Wh-What should we do?
U-Um...
It's true that he's a little old,
but he's really pure-hearted and-
Shut up for a second!
Miyuki-chan, what should we do?
What should we do...
He's looking at us.
He's smiling too. What should we do?
Well, he did give me
a special parfait before.
Okay.
Just for today, let's have some fun together.
What?
What's wrong? Bored?
N-No. I'm concerned about Miyuki-chan...
I guess it really was unreasonable.
I did something pretty mean to Miyuki-chan, didn't I?
Yeah, so I wonder if it's okay
for me to be happy.
Don't worry about it.
Leave Miyuki-chan to him.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Okay.
Have some.
Thanks.
You're the only one I love.
I'll always be with you.
New York is waiting for us, Mary.
Oh, John, I can hardly wait
to get to New York.
Very soon, Mary, very soon.
My heart is beating so loudly that he might hear me.
What should I do?
S-Sorry!
D-Don't worry about it.
But I...
I cannot get on that boat, Mary!
You go on ahead without me!
I'll be waiting for you, John!
Don't die! I love you!
I love you too, Mary!
More than anything!
You're my only love!
John! John!
Never give up, Mary!
We'll meet again!
I promise!
Here, Master.
Th-Thank you.
Hey, hey, what's next?
Because we've been in a dark movie theater,
Field Athletics
let's spend some time in the bright outdoors!
Master, I'm going to take a picture, so get closer to Miyuki-chan.
Master, you need to relax more.
You're so stiff.
Try sitting.
Good, good.
Put your hand on her shoulder.
Hurry up!
E-Excuse me.
He really is pure-hearted.
Okay. Smile, Master.
I'm so hungry.
Here you go, Miyuki-chan.
Wow, thanks a lot.
And I didn't prepare anything.
No need to hold back.
Thanks for the food!
It tastes like a pro made it!
Eat up.
Huh?
You made this, Ai-chan?
It looks delicious!
I hope it tastes good.
Thanks for the food!
How is it?
It's great! This is delicious.
Let me try.
Ugh! It's so salty!
This isn't fit for human consumption.
Yeah, this is delicious.
Really?
Then have mine too!
W-Well, thanks.
I'm digging in.
You shouldn't overdo it, Senpai.
It was so good!
Thanks for the food, Master.
You ate all of it. I'm so happy.
Well, time to head back.
Why?
Well, I'm happy enough that she ate the lunch I prepared.
Look at these. We got them when we came in.
[Tickets: Field Athletics Stamp Rally]
What have we here?
Field athletics stamp rally?
Basically, you clear various obstacles to collect stamps.
However, there's a condition: it's for couples.
Sounds like fun.
Let's do it, Ai-chan!
Let's do it, Master.
Miyuki-chan....
1... 2... 3... 4...
Are you okay, Master?
I may look like this now, but when I was in school, I was considered athletic.
FIELD ATHLETICS STARTING POINT
Ready! Start!
Didn't you say you were athletic?
When I was in grade school.
Ah...
Are you okay, Ai-chan?
Huh? Ryoko-chan.
She's drawing in a place like this?
You know her?
Yeah, she's a classmate.
Let's go.
She looks so pretty and grown up.
Ai-chan!
Coming!
I'm done for.
Miyuki-chan, go on ahead.
Quit talking nonsense.
Take my hand.
This game requires both
of us to reach the goal.
I-I guess you're right.
She's exactly the type of ideal girl I've been looking for.
Hey now...
S-Sorry!
Master!
Now I'm back where I started.
All right! This maze is the last one.
This way?
That's the path we just came from.
Don't tell me...
What are you doing?
This is such a nuisance.
We've been lost in here
for two hours already.
Ah! You're...
Just as I thought. It's Miko-chan's father.
What do you mean, "Just as I thought?"
Huh? Tsuyoshi-san, are you lost too?
No, I'm on a double da-
Um, just doing the stamp rally with everyone.
Really? You're...
Don't let him fool you!
He's obviously courting this girl.
Courting?
What era is this old guy from?
Silence!
It's bad enough that you made advances on my Miko-chan,
but to be courting another girl as well is exceedingly inappropriate!
J-Just hold on.
I haven't laid a finger on her.
For a man to come to a woman's house is to make advances.
Oh, really?
Now, now. I'm sure if we talk about this we can work it out.
Silence!
I don't want to hear anything from a man dating such a young girl!
He changed targets.
N-No, you're mistaken.
This girl is, um, my niece.
And so, I'm just accompanying her.
Niece?
Your niece, you say?
Y-Yeah.
That's what you call a dirty lie.
You see, we're actually lovers.
Lovers...
That's indecent!
And why is that?
Are you saying two people can't be lovers if there's an age difference?!
They cannot!
Boys and girls
must be
separated
after seven
This is ridiculous.
Let's go.
O-Okay.
Good going, Miyuki-chan.
Yeah.
Young men
must not
enter the
kitchen
This world is rotten!
The stake
that sticks
out gets
hammered
down
Four things
to fear:
earthquakes,
thunder,
fire and
fathers
The stake
that sticks
out gets
hammered
down
Young men
must not
enter the
kitchen
Be fruitful
and multiply
It must be fixed!
The stake
that sticks
out gets
hammered
down
Four things
to fear:
earthquakes,
thunder,
fire and
fathers
The stake
that sticks
out gets
hammered
down
Young men
must not
enter the
kitchen
Boys and girls
must be
separated
after seven
The stake
that sticks
out gets
hammered
down
Male Chauvinism
Let's get out of here.
Okay.
If I were king, then... why then I'd....
Just where do you think you're going?!
Thanks, Master.
Today was really a lot of fun.
No, I should be thanking you.
Were you serious?
About what?
When you said we were lovers.
Nope! It was just for today.
I thought so.
Reality is cruel.
Just like I expected.
Tsuyoshi! No pay this week!
N-No way!
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
A lone girl facing a blank canvas.
Like a sudden evening rain,
passing feelings cause the girl's paintbrush to hesitate.
These feelings are like the fleeting colors of hydrangea petals.
What colors will permeate this canvas?
Kakyuusei, episode 4:
Beyond the Rain Clouds.
Beyond the Rain Clouds