Autumn has really arrived.
Sakigake Station South
Douda!
A new target?
She obviously doesn't like it.
Sakigake Academy Station, Sakigake Academy Station.
Please ensure that you have all your belongings.
Orphan Fansubs presents
Kakyuusei
Rie-chan!
Senpai!
Wanna go see the J-League game tonight?
I've got two tickets.
I have club practice today. Sorry!
I heard that she'd joined a different club,
but ever since summer,
Rie-chan's been giving me the brush-off.
Your outer passing game is weak.
You turn the ball over after two or three
passes around the basket.
To prevent that, look left and right
She just quit the tennis club.
and predict the movements of the defenders.
When did she get so into basketball?
Has she fallen for
her basketball coach now?
Did our time this summer mean nothing to her?
I feel so strange.
Senpai!
I'm flying!
I guess I was just a summer fling for Rie-chan.
Urara-chan!
Urara-chan...
Takeshi! What's the matter?
E-Et tu, Brute?
What?
It's from Julius Caesar.
I'm practicing for the Cultural Festival.
Why don't you join the Drama Club too, Kakeru?
That sounds retarded.
It's got a very exploitable female to male ratio!
I suppose you joined the Drama Club because my little sister did?
Pretty much!
Wherever Mika-chan is,
there I will be too!
We're doing a musical this year.
All the ladies love a leading man,
so my popularity is soaring. Soaring!
What are you talking about?
It's a Shakespeare medley.
You can't even handle
a karaoke medley.
Romeo! Oh, where are you, Romeo?
Ah, my lovely Juliet!
I'm on my way now!
Huh? Onii.
Yo. Keep it up.
Cultural Festival
That's right. The Cultural Festival
is almost here.
Not that I'm expecting much.
Oh, Romeo, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Mika's at it early this morning.
All those cheesy lines are going to make my brain congeal.
The second trimester is half over,
and entrance exams are coming up.
This sucks.
A rarefied rich girl, around here?
Nobody else around.
I can make this work!
Morning!
Good morning to you.
It looks great.
It's nothing special.
You're being too humble.
I don't really understand art,
but I know a good picture when I see it.
Thank you.
Kakeru, you mustn't!
Huh?
I'm sorry. I know it's an odd name.
My mother gave it to him.
Ah, no. I think it's a
perfectly fine name.
He was born when Mother was entering the Nika Art Exhibition for the seventh time.
Note: "Kaketa" means "a bet."
She made a bet that she'd quit painting if she didn't win that time.
And from that, "Kakeru."
Wait-
She won that year.
So the dog's a good-luck charm, huh?
Are you also submitting to Nika?
No, I'm not. But I do intend to submit something next year.
This is a work for the school Cultural Festival.
I just hope I finish in time.
Tell me, which school?
Sakigake Academy.
Hey, that's my school too!
So are you an upperclassman?
Yes. I'm a third-year, Nanahoshi... Kakeru.
Huh? Kakeru?
Yes, the same name
as your bodyguard.
Oh, my! Is that true?
It is.
Note: "Kakeru" means "to run."
My parents used to run track and field,
so they called me "Kakeru."
So cute...
Ah, I thought you'd be mad at me
for getting in your way.
Make sure you finish in time.
I will! Thank you so much.
Oh, what's your name?
I'm Akimoto Hikari, a first-year.
I'll come see you at the Cultural Festival.
Thanks!
I never knew there was such a princess among the underclassmen.
There weren't any girls like that in Takeshi's creepshot collection.
Oh, there she is!
I didn't quite recognize her in her uniform.
Wait, this girl is...
the one who was with Douda!
She looked pretty classy in her casual clothes.
How nice.
Sorry, Urara-chan.
Mika, I'm coming in.
Oh, Romeo, Romeo!
What the f-
What's with you?!
I was just getting into Juliet mode.
My bad.
Do you know a first-year
named Akimoto Hikari?
Yeah, I know her.
So what's the deal?
My pal's short of data.
He told me to ask
my little sister about her.
She doesn't stand out at school,
but her parents are loaded.
Her father's some general high up
in the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Her older sister won the national piano competition twice. It's an elite family.
So a true pampered princess, huh?
Music Cafe
Menu
Raise it a little higher.
Music Cafe
Menu
Kakeru!
It's me!
Oh, it's you, Takeshi.
Don't scare me like that.
I'm playing Othello!
What are you up to?
Where's the Art Club room, Othello?
Turn left, and it's the second one down.
Thank you!
Why's Kakeru going to
the Art Club room?
Art Room
Ah!
Yo. Did you finish it?
Not quite.
Then you shouldn't be helping here.
What if you don't make it in time?
But...
I'll trade places with you.
Take this chance!
I've just now joined the Art Club.
The president's a friend of mine,
so I can work things out.
Um, all right.
Are you sure about this?
It's fine. Just let me handle it.
In that case...
It's finished.
You did it!
Senpai!
Congratulations.
It's thanks to you, Senpai.
Not really.
Hey, Nanahoshi.
Douda!
Kakeru and Kakeru, huh?
Talk about a world of difference.
It's all about the breeding.
I don't have to take this crap from you.
Akimoto-kun, why not display Kakeru at a dog show?
I'll introduce you to a breeder I know.
I'm sure you'll win big.
I appreciate the thought,
but Kakeru doesn't like being talked down to by others.
It'd be a shame if Kakeru were left to languish in obscurity.
Don't call him "Kakeru"
like you know him!
His owner declined,
and you're just being pushy!
Mongrels shouldn't bark.
Say what?
Please stop this, you two.
It looks like you've finished.
I'll carry it back for you.
There's no need to be concerned about
your knight touching you on the shoulder.
Stay. Quit it!
Better than he deserves.
Douda-san was so aggressive that it bothered me.
"Aggressive"?
He was suggesting
a modeling arrangement.
And nude, at that.
Nude?!
Turn this modeling gig down!
Indeed, I'd be embarrassed to see a boy nude.
Douda was... going to model?
Yes. Douda-san is overflowing with confidence.
He's just an arrogant narcissist.
My honey...
Kakeru!
Hikari-chan, let's put this painting up in the club room.
Okay!
Thank you so much, Senpai.
Don't mention it.
Yep, it sure is a good painting.
I'm glad I finished in time.
Senpai?
Gorgeous.
I-I want to draw you, Hikari-chan.
Huh? Draw me?
Yes.
You looked so pure and lovely just now.
But I've never actually painted a real picture before.
I'm not sure if I can draw you well.
If I'm acceptable...
Really?!
Senpai, you certainly are shy.
Ah, no.
I'd be delighted to model for you.
Hikari-chan?
Um, I have a favor to ask you as well.
Senpai, won't you model for me?
Me?
Yes. I'm least skilled at painting human subjects.
My parents and my sister
won't pose for me,
and it wouldn't feel right
to ask my friends.
So my skills continue to suffer.
If I work for you, it works for me.
That's great!
I always wanted a kind
older brother like you, Senpai!
Hikari-chan...
Mamoto
..Store
....Store
Mamoto
Huh?
....Store
Mamoto
Lodge
Yo, Kakeru!
I hear you've joined the Art Club.
You heard right.
Mika-chan told me...
that you asked her all kinds of questions
about Akimoto Hikari.
Mika's such a blabbermouth.
Your hidden motivations are completely obvious to me.
It's not like that.
Liar!
She doesn't stand out, but everyone secretly has their eyes on her.
Rich girls always attract rumors.
Takeshi?
What kinds of rumors?
Rich girls like her tend to think that common-sense taboos are for commoners.
Quit beating around the bush!
In short, she lacks a sense of shame.
Once she's naked, she doesn't bother to hide anything.
Well, she's an elegant, uninhibited, high-class lady, right?
You know how the Akimoto family has a St. Bernard?
Yeah.
Rich girls like that tend to get
pretty familiar with their dogs-
Shut your trap!
S-Stop it, Kakeru.
You're choking me.
I didn't start the rumor,
so don't shoot the messenger!
Yeah, but it's in line with your thought processes!
I get it. I apologize.
That was a shock.
Sometimes I don't understand Kakeru.
Hey, come see me do Shakespeare!
Kakeru, come here, boy!
No, that's so cold!
It tickles!
Not there...
Bad dog, Kakeru!
You're begging again.
You're a lost cause, Kakeru.
Just a little.
Stop it!
A dream?
That was one crazy dream.
Takeshi's nonsense fueled my fantasies.
Sakigake
Culture Festival
Delicious!!
Grilled Corn
We've got yakisoba!
Crepes
Yummy
Welcome!
S.A.                  Live
This play is the product and pride
of the Drama Club!
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
ShakespeareStory opens
today at 2:00!
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Sakigake           Academy
Today at
Drama
Club
Shakespeare
Admission is free!
Come one, come all!
Shakespeare
Yakisoba
Takoyaki
Delicious  Meat Buns
Thank you very much!
Art Club Exhibit
Please take your time.
Hikari-chan.
Senpai!
I bought some meat buns.
Have someone take your place,
and then join me for a few?
Sure!
Oh, no!
I forgot to buy drinks.
Let me go fix that!
Senpai!
Wh-What?
Would you like to leave the Cultural Festival
and drop by my house?
Huh? Your house?
We can do those sketches we promised each other.
I was wondering when I could invite you,
but I could never find the right time.
In addition, my family
won't be home today.
Huh? N-No one?
Won't it be a problem if we're alone there together?
But days like today are awfully rare.
Hikari-chan, if no one
else will be there-
It's all right! Let's go, okay?
S-Sure.
That's wonderful!
Heck of a house.
Welcome.
Sorry. W-Were you waiting long?
No.
Hikari-chan's lips... are shining.
If she put lipstick on,
does that mean...
No, this is wrong! Now I'm thinking just like Douda.
Senpai?
Come on in.
O-Okay.
It can't be...
I had to make do with
the supplies on hand.
Ah, that's fine.
Mother has a studio.
From time to time, she and her friends would call in models and do sketches.
Were these... male models?
Male and female.
And were they... nude?
My mother wanted me to join them, but I was too embarrassed.
Oh.
Because I'd never improve without doing nude sketches,
she wanted me to overcome my embarrassment.
But I haven't made much progress.
I see.
That's why today is a
fantastic opportunity!
And by that, you mean...
I need to be able to openly gaze upon the human form to do sketches, right?
I suppose.
I kept on getting distracted,
so I wanted to sketch
you nude, Senpai.
M-Me?
I can understand if you don't want to.
I can't say I'm opposed.
Thank goodness!
Hikari-chan?
I'll model for you as well.
That way, we'll be even, right?
Can this convenient setup be real?
I wouldn't want you to feel embarrassed.
This way, I can also go all-out.
For the sake of art.
O-Of course.
She sure is daring when it counts.
Maybe Takeshi was right.
If this is for the sake of art,
I mustn't hesitate!
Sorry!
A-Amazing.
G-Getting hard in this situation...
means I fail as a model.
I'm so sorry. I spaced out for a moment.
So my hands weren't moving.
Why don't we switch out the model?
Huh? Yes, let's do that.
A-Are you cold?
No.
But you're shivering.
It's nothing. Please continue.
H-Hikari-chan, do you want to
take a little break?
Are you okay?
Sorry. I guess I weirded you out there.
I can't really be a still model if I'm getting hard.
I even went home to brush my teeth before this.
I can't exactly say
I'm all about the art.
I've got no right
to criticize Douda.
I'm at fault. Maybe it's time I-
Senpai!
I'm so sorry! I... I lied to you.
What do you mean?
I'm really a bad, bad girl!
There's no reason to cry.
I said it was my fault.
You're wrong! This was the result I was aiming for from the beginning!
Hikari-chan?
My sister would bring her friends over,
and sometimes they had sex in this room.
And I would get all hot and bothered watching them through the keyhole.
Don't cry! It's nothing
to be sad about.
At first, I scorned my sister,
but eventually, I came to envy her.
I'd start fantasizing, and my body would get so flushed that I couldn't sleep.
When you were looking at my body,
I was trembling as if an electric current was running through me.
Senpai, please...
I want you to look at me... more closely.
Hikari-chan.
I've never felt like this before.
Please don't hate me.
I'm feeling so warm!
I've never seen a girl masturbate right in front of me before.
Senpai, I'm begging you.
Please show me yours too.
O-Okay.
This is the first time I've seen a man's thing in person.
I can't take it anymore.
Same here.
Hikari-chan...
No regrets, okay?
Very well. But this is my first time.
Still, if it's with you, I can...
S-Senpai!
I-I'm so embarrassed.
Please don't hate me.
Who would ever do that?
And this isn't anything
to be ashamed of.
Senpai!
Hikari-chan, are you ready?
I'm putting it in.
Please do.
So hot...
Today is our very own
secret Cultural Festival.
Let's enjoy it to the fullest.
I'm so happy.
Senpai!
Hikari-chan...
I feel wonderful, as if
my body's melting!
Senpai!
I'm coming!
Kakeru
komorebi ni madoromeba
While I doze in the sunlight under the trees,
kaze no sasayaki wo kanji
I feel the whispering of the wind.
mabuta ni utsutta kimi no egao
The reflection of your smile in my eyes
mabushisugite
is so dazzling.
kagayaku kisetsu wa meguri
Shining seasons come and go.
toki wo kasaneru tabi ni
While we spend time together,
aishiai kizutsuki
we love and hurt each other
otona ni naru
as we slowly become adults.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I'll never forget
kakegae no nai toki wo
those precious moments.
tooku kara mitsumeteiru
I'll look at you from so far away,
ano koro no you ni
just as I did in those days.
kasuka na kioku no naka de
You're smiling at me
kimi wa hohoemikakeru
in my fading memory.
sasayaka na yakusoku oboeteiru yo
I still remember that innocent promise.
ikusen no yoru wo koete
The day I finally meet you
kimi to meguriatta hi
after so many days and nights,
kawarazu ni dakishimete
I want to hold you
kimi wo mamoritai
and protect you forever.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I won't forget anything about you
ano koro no naka de
from those days.
Translation & Timing
Translation Check
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Raws
Zalis
convexity
Collectr
CP, konnakude
Piyo-Piyo Productions
ics-
Next Episode Preview
Graduation season arrives,
and my high-school life
draws to a close.
It's been a year filled with...
the pure love of darling underclassmen.
Blazing love.
Fleeting love.
And now, a passionate love begins.
Fuyuki Tsubomi.
While you're racing,
I want to see the true heart
that you've kept sealed away.
Please look forward to
the final episode of Kakyuusei.
I'll never forget this glittering year
or the days of my youth.