Everybody's studying hard for their entrance exams.
Hikari-chan's been busy working on
her Nika submission ever since then.
I can't study for the entrance
exams in this state.
I can't really go outside
in the snow, either.
I'm so bored.
I don't feel like doing anything.
The future looks pretty bleak.
Math III
Hey, Onii! You alive?
Ever heard of knocking, Mika?
Even I have a right to privacy.
You just don't want anybody flinging open the door and catching you in the act.
As I so often remind you, you are a girl.
Note: Mika uses many typically masculine verb and sentence endings.
Can't you at least try to sound like one?
If that's how you're going to be,
I won't be giving you this letter.
Urara sure has strange tastes.
Why would she go for you, Aniki?
Shut up and hand it over!
If you've got no reason to be here, then get going.
Aw, come on! Can't I get
some thanks here?
Onii-chan, are you doing well?
I'm in high spirits and
doing my best every day.
Whenever I feel lonely, I think of
the time we spent at
the summer festival,
and my heart feels a bit tighter.
Even while I was writing this letter,
I thought about how
much I've missed you.
I'm sad.
I pray that I can return
to Japan soon.
Onii-chan, I can see
you again, right?
Urara.
Urara-chan...
Orphan Fansubs presents
Kakyuusei
Finale
What's going on?
It's the new farewell song.
They're replacing "Aogeba Toutoshi," starting with this year's graduation.
Takeshi, you seem down.
You're not your usual self.
I'm not?
Don't tell me you're getting all sentimental over the graduation ceremony?
I'm not "getting sentimental."
The calendar says it should be spring,
so why is it this cold?
Cheer up, man.
Okay.
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Perseverance
Graduation Essay Compilation
Memories of Three Years
Takeshi's acting depressed.
Is he heartbroken because
he couldn't score with Mika?
Speaking of that...
Ah, it's started.
So pretty.
Fireworks look beautiful
from far away.
They're like flowers
blooming in the sky.
Yeah, I guess so.
No matter what we do,
you're still you.
Huh?
You've got as many different faces as there are different kinds of flowers.
Maybe you show off different faces
in ways and places I don't know about.
But that's okay.
When we're together,
I want you to look only at me.
Urara-chan...
Can you promise me that?
Onii-chan...
There's no need to make that promise.
You're always on my mind, Urara-chan.
Really?
Yes, really.
I'll say it straight.
You're the only one I love, Urara-chan.
Onii-chan, I'm so happy.
Urara-chan...
I love you.
I love you too, a whole lot.
Hey, Nanahoshi-kun!
Huh?
I bet you were having dirty thoughts.
The drool was pouring
from your mouth.
I don't need your flood control!
You haven't written a single line.
It's all good.
You really think I can store my precious memories in a lame graduation anthology?
Well, at least you're graceful in defeat.
But you're a pretty nice guy,
so maybe you've made some good memories we don't know about.
Huh? No way.
Wait, what? Everyone's gone!
They all went to the auditorium for the graduation photograph.
Better get a move on!
Ah! Kakeru!
Can't you laugh it off?
I had to get a farewell
glance up your skirt.
Hey, are you right in the head, Nanahoshi-kun?
Ah, poor little Kakeru.
You've passed your third year without getting into any relationships.
It's still not too late. Want to make some memories with me?
Leave me alone! I don't need any pity from you!
Someone dropped this?
Hey, that's mine.
Give it back.
You're so cool, Fuyuki!
Tsubomi-chan!
I wanna do her!
Moron. She'll do you in
before you get the chance.
Fuyuki Tsubomi?
Kakeru...
Huh? What's up, Takeshi?
You've drifted even further
out of character.
Say whatever you want.
Go out with me today, Onii-sama!
Huh?
Not that I care, but you're pigging out, Takeshi-kun.
I don't need diet tips from the one I'm treating!
So is this comfort food for your sexual frustrations?
Sorry I teased you.
My bad, Takeshi.
C'mon, can't you just give up on Mika already?
Don't cry!
There are plenty of other
nice girls out there!
I can't go for anybody else!
I'm losing sleep just thinking about how I won't be able to
see Mika-chan anymore
after I graduate.
You're exaggerating.
If you want to see Mika, you can just hang out at my house.
Huh?! Really?!
Oh, thank you so much, Onii-sama!
Hey, knock it off!
Kakeru, keep a low profile.
Those girls in back are delinquents from Takahashi Academy.
Getting mixed up with
them spells trouble.
Gulp!
Mika-chan?
What do you want?
Note: Tsubomi also uses masculine pronouns and expressions.
I'm here to deal with you
in Mika's place.
Sounds like a plan to me! Let's go.
Ah, Mika-chan!
Huh? Onii, Minamino-san,
you were here?
Mika! What's the meaning of this?
It's none of your business, Onii!
Mika-chan, did you become a delinquent while I wasn't watching?
No!
So what's going on here?
If I did anything like that,
my school would expel me.
That girl's an underclassman of ours!
Tsubomi-chan may have a foul mouth, but she's really a nice girl!
I-Is she a friend of yours?
She's a strong ally for me and all my girlfriends.
Huh?
When the delinquents from TaCademy were harassing some of my friends,
she came and saved us.
I never thought someone that cute could be so tough!
Back in junior high, Tsubomi-chan was like a "shadow boss."
Kakeru! What are you doing?
I can't leave her hanging!
She's like a sister to us!
Stop it!
You've got the wrong fight!
You still wanna try it?
Ah, sorry. Kakeru!
Onii!
He's your brother, Mika?
Tsubomi-chan!
It's over.
If anything else comes up,
let me know.
If any losers try to start shit,
they'll get wrecked.
Thank you!
No problem. Don't sweat it.
So cool!
Pretty much the opposite of this guy.
Takeshi! Way to just stand there.
Chinese Food
Y A K I N I K U
Nyan Nyan
Tsubomi-chan!
Well, I sure can't study after everything that happened.
Fuyuki Tsubomi, huh?
Give it back.
Y A K I N I K U
Frickin' pests!
Huh?
Don't go stickin' to me
like stink on shit!
Dammit!
Yo!
Mika's big brother?
Hey, I hate to intrude,
but no good will come from running with that gang.
I'll go "touring" with you, so you should ditch those dead-end friends.
What's so funny?
Plenty of guys try to
run a game on me,
but that was the lamest opening yet.
D-Don't be stupid!
I was being serious!
But I suppose I can let you into the touring group, Senpai,
as a special case.
Tsubomi-chan?
You took a few hits for me, right?
I gotta respect that.
Tonight at 8 o'clock, under the
Inonaka Park pedestrian bridge.
Be on time or else. Bye.
When did she seize the initiative?
But this is my chance to pry her away from those dead-end friends!
No matter how lame
she says I am!
I wonder what kind of boyfriend our resident misandrist Tsubomi invited.
I bet he's a real bad-ass hustler.
Senpai!
Sorry, sorry.
You're the only man here.
Don't embarrass us by falling behind.
Yeah, sure thing!
Nii-chan, don't embarrass Tsubomi, either.
I won't let anyone make a fool out of me again!
seven
Ah, here he comes.
I hate to admit it, but I guess I can't match your pace with a scooter.
Here.
Ah, thanks.
seven
Sorry I misjudged your crew so badly. I apologize.
This is the first time I've ever had so much fun talking to a guy.
Quit using "ore"!
Note: "Ore" is a form of "I/me" mainly used by "tough guys."
You'd be a really cute girl if you dropped the badass act.
Huh?
Geez...
Nobody's ever said anything
like that to me.
There you go with "ore" again.
I can't help it!
I've been acting this way ever since elementary school.
Why do you try to seem so tough?
I...
was bullied constantly during
my first years in elementary school.
My classmates teased me and stripped off my panties.
I freaked out and started biting them.
After that, I got confident.
I started toughening up so I wouldn't lose to anyone.
I acted cheerful to avoid grief from my parents,
but once I got to middle school,
I became a "shadow boss."
But why am I yammering on about this?
It's so strange.
Don't force yourself.
You'll wear yourself out trying to act like a man all the time.
Just be an authentic woman. You'll be cuter that way.
Still, I suppose you can't
change overnight.
Once your shell is chipped away,
you can relax.
It takes guts to do that.
Tsubomi, let's go!
Okay!
She's a good girl.
Senpai, we're leaving you behind!
Ah, hey!
Fuyuki Tsubomi has become a mighty fine woman.
According to my father's tales from traveling the country,
a woman's appeal runs in seasons.
She may not stand out in spring,
but she can get markedly more attractive in fall or winter.
I've had my eye on Fuyuki for a while as well.
And now she's in season.
Shrews like her...
yield a pretty good flavor if you pin them down by force.
She'll be screaming for more.
Douda! You bastard.
I won't let you get away with your "major player" routine!
Before we graduate,
I'll be sure to show the difference
between me and a dull guy like you.
What?
Nanahoshi.
Are you looking for one last
pre-graduation humiliation?
Don't get cocky! You wanna throw down or not?
I'll take you on.
This is the championship.
Nobody interfere.
Let's do this American-style.
It's time to decide the true victor.
Decide this!
Is that all you've got, Nanahoshi?!
Fuck you!
Somebody call a teacher!
Nanahoshi-kun and Douda-kun are...
Onii is...
Senpai.
You've cockblocked me
for the last time, asshole!
If you lay hands on Fuyuki,
you're dead meat!
Eat shit and die!
Knock it off!
Haven't you two had enough?
Call this a draw.
No hard feelings.
Minamino-san, that was so cool!
Mika-chan?
Tsubomi-chan? Thank you.
Tsubomi-chan?
Senpai, will you...
go touring with me tonight?
S-Sure.
That's great!
Snow.
Tsubomi?
Let's take a breather here.
The Shizuo boathouse is like
a lounge for me and my team.
It's showing no sign of stopping.
We won't be able to
go back on the bike.
This electric heater isn't enough to warm the room.
And our riding suits are all wet.
We'll catch cold.
We've got some team sleeping bags.
You mean this?
Yeah.
Turn around.
Sure.
S-Senpai?
If you don't undress too,
you'll catch a cold.
I'll look the other way.
O-Okay.
Boat Rentals
The lights might go out.
Yeah. Huh?
It's even quieter now.
Are you cold?
Yes, I'm cold.
You're so warm.
So are you.
I've never seen you
from this close before.
Do you think I can
be more feminine?
Yes, you can.
I... w-want to ask you for a favor.
What is it?
Everyone on the team
is... "experienced."
I've been pretending
to have experience,
but I've actually never
done it before.
Tsubomi-chan?
Because of who I am, I thought I was out of luck in that department.
Am I good enough for you?
Yeah.
You put yourself on the line and fought for me twice, Senpai.
I've never felt so warmly protected by any guy before.
First things first. Stop using "ore."
It's too late to stop now.
Use "atashi."
Note: "atashi" is a feminine form of "I."
I...
That's... so cute, Tsubomi.
Senpai!
Senpai, I'm getting chills
down my spine!
Senpai, it feels so good!
Here I go, Tsubomi.
A-Amazing!
Tsubomi!
Senpai!
T-Tsubomi-chan!
T-Tsubomi!
I'm coming!
Senpai...
Tsubomi...
And that was how my time
in high school drew to a close.
Of course, I failed the exams and wound up in cram school with Takeshi.
And then, the last day arrived.
Today's the day we say goodbye to this school.
Yeah.
You're even more depressed.
My energy's been sapped away.
I don't think I'll be seeing Mika-chan anymore.
Kakeru, you said it's okay for me to hang out at your place, right?
Huh? Did I say something like that?
N-No way!
I might not have to call you.
Turn around.
Huh?
M-Mika-chan!
Will you give me a button from your uniform, Minamino-san?
Huh?
There you have it. You'd better not embarrass my little sister.
K-Kakeru!
I-Is this for real?!
Mika-chan, you can have all my buttons, or even my whole uniform!
Down, boy.
Mika-chan...
Good luck!
Spring has finally come for Takeshi.
And I faced down the climax of my high school life.
komorebi ni madoromeba
While I doze in the sunlight under the trees,
kaze no sasayaki wo kanji
I feel the whispering of the wind.
mabuta ni utsutta kimi no egao
The reflection of your smile in my eyes
mabushisugite
is so dazzling.
kagayaku kisetsu wa meguri
Shining seasons come and go.
toki wo kasaneru tabi ni
While we spend time together,
aishiai kizutsuki
we love and hurt each other
otona ni naru
as we slowly become adults.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I'll never forget
kakegae no nai toki wo
those precious moments.
tooku kara mitsumeteiru
I'll look at you from so far away,
ano koro no you ni
just as I did in those days.
kasuka na kioku no naka de
You're smiling at me
kimi wa hohoemikakeru
in my fading memory.
sasayaka na yakusoku oboeteiru yo
I still remember that innocent promise.
ikusen no yoru wo koete
The day I finally meet you
kimi to meguriatta hi
after so many days and nights,
kawarazu ni dakishimete
I want to hold you
kimi wo mamoritai
and protect you forever.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I won't forget anything about you
ano koro no naka de
from those days.
Huh?
Onii-chan!
Huh? Urara-chan!
I've come back!
Urara-chan!
Urara-chan.
I'm back.
I won't go anywhere.
I'll never leave again.
Really?!
I'll be with you forever
and ever, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan... I love you.
Translation & Timing
Translation Check
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Raws
Zalis
convexity
Collectr
CP, konnakude
Piyo-Piyo Productions
ics-