It happened one evening in June.
Just a dream.
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
I start the day.
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
Translated by:           Moho Kareshi
Always rushing to prevent
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Translation Check:                kokujin-kun
these hearts from crumbling.
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
Edited & Typeset by:        Collectr
These words that attempt escaping
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
Timed by:       Eternal_Blizzard
Karaoke by:            EmptySoul
try again and again to reach your ears.
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
Calyrica
Quality Control:      Eternal_Blizzard
Encoded by:          anonymous
The threads of my feelings
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
all connect to you.
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
When I hear a snapping thread,
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
I tightly embrace its melody.
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
begins to bloom.
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
Nice to Meet You! I'm Tina!
I'm super-late!
Class 3-C
If you're on bathroom cleaning duty,
do your job properly.
Class 3-C
Take care to make our
facilities sparkling clean.
And please,
do not bring the toilet paper into the classroom.
Again.
Tsuyoshi!
Jeez. He's hopeless.
Morning!
Wh-Who are you?
Hey!
Tsuyoshi-kun? Late again?
Y-You're a princess?!
Like, for real?
Yep!
Yep.
Everyone, Tina-san is our new student.
Oh, that's her twin brother, Tim-kun.
Nice to meet you, Tsuyoshi-kun!
Say, a-are you...
Call me Tina.
Your clothes.
It's normal where she comes from.
N-Normal?!
Isn't it against school ru-
Wh-What?
Not another word if you know what's good for you, Tsuyoshi.
He's right.
Are you trying to make us your enemies?
Haruhiko, for once I agree with you!
Well, this is the one thing
we can break bread on.
Right.
Jeez, those boys.
Seriously. They always agree about perverted things.
Disgraceful.
Settle down. We're in class.
Anyway, that's what's worn in her country.
Please be good to her, Tsuyoshi-kun.
Okay!
Got it!
Th-Those guys...
Tsuyoshi-kun!
T-Tina?
C'mon, Tsuyoshi-kun!
Show me around.
Me?
Why?
Because Sensei wants us to get along.
Ask one of the other boys.
I bet the entire male student body wants to get along with you.
I want you.
Come on! Can't you?
Cut it out.
It has to be you!
What're you doing?
Cut it out!
I want you!
Now say yes!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Did someone just squeal?
Who does that during the daytime?
O-Okay. Let's go.
Hooray!
Reading Room
I usually take a nap here.
Keep up.
Slow down.
Not so close.
No way.
Slow down!
G-Get away from me!
Why?
Just do it.
What's the big deal?
That makes me...
want to hold you even more!
Hey!
Tsuyoshi!
What're you doing to Tina?!
How indecent.
It's not-
I didn't want her to.
Stay one meter away!
Otherwise, I won't show you around.
Okay.
There. That's more like it.
In Japan, it's said that students must walk three paces behind their teachers.
So don't act so familiar.
Huh?
What?!
She's floating! She's floating!
I-I can see that.
Why are you floating?
Now I'm not "walking" close to you.
You're missing the point!
Jeez!
Really?
Th-This can't be happening.
This is unimaginable.
She stands out more than me!
She didn't want to tell you,
but she has an illness
that causes her body to repel
gravitational forces and float.
That's right.
That's impossible.
Tina-san!
You are so brave to act cheerful
when you are clearly ill!
Even if you are sick, you are still
a precious classmate to us!
Right, everyone?
Yeah!
To think that I have the honor of teaching you kids.
It makes me so happy.
I can't believe they're falling for it.
What a terrible day.
Everyone's acting weird.
That bikini girl-
Tsuyoshi-kun!
That voice...
Tsuyoshi-kun.
Let's go home together!
I'm busy!
Maybe tomorrow!
Oh, my.
What's her problem?
Pharmacy
There she is.
BIG
FISH
Hi, Maki-san!
Hi, lazy boy.
I'm not lazy.
I don't have time to hang out with you.
You're horrible.
You can't fool me.
If you don't have business here, leave.
I have business with you!
About the other day...
I can get better guys for a date anytime.
Bakery
You can't find any better guys than me.
That's funny.
Th-That girl...
Do you know her?
Bakery
We meet again.
Geh! Tina!
Let's go home together.
Wh-What a strange girl.
W-Well, have fun.
Wait!
Uofuku
Maki-san!
Dad, can you mind the store?
Uofuku
I have a headache.
Okay, I'm home.
See ya.
You're late, Sis.
I'm home, Tim.
So... you live in the dorm?
Yep!
Next to your room.
Wh-Why?
So these are the mysterious new students, Tina and Tim.
Every day, Tina follows me around.
I'm bored.
I know.
I can never talk to Tsuyoshi-senpai alone.
We should get more screen time!
I'm lodging a complaint!
To whom?
Well...
Ai-chan!
Senpai!
Help!
Tsuyoshi-kun!
It's all her fault!
Jeez.
Why is she so obsessed with me?
Maki-san always runs away
when she sees me.
I'll be direct this time.
What are you doing, Sis?
You left the door open.
Seriously. What if he peeked on you?
I-I saw her.
She's pretty well developed.
No, forget about that.
Yeah. I didn't see anything.
I saw nothing.
I can't sleep!
Tired already?
Couldn't sleep a wink.
Morning!
Hi, Tina-chan.
I went to your room,
but you left without me.
Why do I have to wait for you?
Because...
Must be nice living next to each other.
Yeah!
You'd better watch yourself.
I agree!
Good morning, Tina-san.
Good morning, Haruhiko-kun.
Did you remember to lock your door?
Don't forget to lock your windows.
Someone might sneak in and steal your underwear.
Like your neighbor.
You idiot.
She doesn't even wear underwear.
How do you know that ?
W-Well, she always wears this to class!
Well, I guess.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm gonna take a nap on the roof.
I'll join you!
You shouldn't, Tina-san.
He's going to cut class.
Senpai. Hello.
You're...
a first-year in the Tennis Club.
I'm Minagawa... Nana.
Are you here to see Mizuho?
She's not here yet.
No, I...
I'm here to see Tim-senpai.
Tim?!
Got some sleep.
I know a good bakery.
Would you care to...
How did he get so popular?
What does she like about him?
She's still following me.
Say...
Wanna go on a date?
A-A date?
Where'd that come from?
Tim said he's going on
a date this weekend.
With Nana-chan, I bet.
That cheeky...
C'mon.
I bet it'll be fun.
Don't you know what a date is?
Sure.
Mizuho told me.
It's when a boy and a girl like each other.
I really like you!
Well, I don't like you.
I like normal girls.
Girls who don't fly or wear swimsuits.
Normal girls...
Tina!
Tina?
Maybe I was too hard on her.
What's wrong?
She's usually right next to me.
I thought she was really carefree, but...
Tina!
What are you doing here?
I thought you'd want to go home with me.
I didn't see you, so I was worried.
Really?
Listen...
What?
You go first.
You can go first.
A-About that date...
I don't mind.
Really?!
I have a few conditions.
No floating during the date.
And wear a regular outfit.
Those are my conditions.
Okay!
I'll act like a normal girl!
Come in!
G-Good morning.
Is that you, Tina?
I wore a regular outfit, like I promised.
Is it weird?
N-No.
You don't look weird.
Really?
Hooray!
Golden                                            Plaza
Say, where are we going?
I can't wait!
Hey, where are we going?
Well...
I don't care where we go!
Tim!
Senpai!
Are you two on a date too?
What a small world.
Just like you two!
Don't tell anyone, Nana-chan.
Why not?
The other girls will hate him.
What do you mean?
Is that true?
Crap...
Hey! Mind your own business, little brother!
Don't call me "little brother"!
Let's go.
Okay!
Goodbye, Senpai!
He's blushing.
Right?
Come on.
Let's go.
Okay!
Hey, not so rough.
I can't walk like this.
Okay!
Come on.
That was close.
Tina, let's go home.
Already?
I wanna spend more time with you!
I see.
Well, I'm going home.
Wait!
Ow.
Tina!
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Can you walk?
See? I'm not hurt.
I had fun today.
Me too!
You're more quiet and feminine when you're dressed normally.
But...
Tina?
What's wrong?!
Whoa, it's swollen!
You've got a sprain.
Why'd you force yourself?
Why don't you fly like you usually do?
B-Because...
you said you don't like girls
who float in the air or wear bikinis.
I never said I hate you.
But you said you don't like me.
S-So I...
Never mind that. Can you stand?
Are you all right?
T-Talk about a cheap shot, Tina.
What's wrong, Tina?
Tsuyoshi-kun.
Good morning.
Why are you dressed like that?
Tina asked me to lend her a uniform.
I had a spare.
It fit me perfectly.
She's cute in a school uniform too.
Very cute.
But I'm still conflicted about it.
Very conflicted.
Come here, Tina.
You can fly.
You can wear your swimsuit.
Just be yourself.
You don't mind?
No. You shouldn't force
yourself to change.
Okay! I'll do what I want!
Tina?
You don't have to do it now!
I like this best!
Bye-bye!
nami no oto ga suru anata no mune
波の音がする　あなたの胸
I can hear the waves inside your chest
hoho wo yosete me wo tojitara
頬を寄せて　目を閉じたら
when I press my cheek to yours and close my eyes.
toki ga tomatta
時が止まった
Time seems to stop.
tesaguri de aruiteta neiro no naka de
手探りで　歩いてた　音色の中で
I finally found the warmth I was searching for
sagashiteta nukumori ni yatto deaeta
探してた　ぬくもりに　やっと出逢えた
as I walked amid the haze and confusion.
yume wo mite mo ii no futari no mirai ga
夢を見てもいいの？　二人の未来が
Can I dream that our futures
eien ni kasanariau koto wo
永遠に　重なり会うことを
will be forever intertwined?
miageta yokogao ga
見上げた横顔が
I'm looking at your smile
hohoemi wo kureru
微笑みをくれる
as you look up to the sky.
kono mama de hanasanaide
このままで　離さないで
Please don't let me go.
kono mama zutto
このままずっと
Hold me forever.
kore kara hajimaru monogatari no
これから始まる　物語の
Our story is only beginning.
yukisaki wo kimeru no wa futari no omoi
行き先を　決めるのは　ふたりの想い
Our feelings will decide how it ends.
hitogomi no naka de hagureta hi wa
人混みの中で　はぐれた日は
If I get lost amid a crowd of people,
tachidomaru watashi no koto mitsuke ni kite ne
立ち止まる　私のこと　見つけにきてね
please come and find me.
hareta hi mo ame no hi mo uketomenagara
晴れた日も　雨の日も　受けとめながら
Let's keep loving each other,
taisetsu ni kono koi wo sodatete yukou
大切に　この恋を　育てて行こう
no matter what happens, rain or shine.
yume wo mitemo ii no futari no kimochi ga
夢を見てもいいの？　ふたりの気持ちが
Can I dream that our feelings
eien ni kasanariau koto wo
永遠に　重なり合うことを
will be forever intertwined?
kotoba ja tarinakute tsutaekirenakute
言葉じゃ足りなくて　傳えきれなくて
I cannot possibly
konna ni mo anata no koto
こんなにも　あなたのこと
put in words
aishiteru koto wo
愛してることを
how much I love you.