Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:         Moho Kareshi
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:         EmptySoul
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:        Collectr
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Timed & Typeset by:     EmptySoul
Karaoke by:            EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Calyrica &
Quality Control:      Eternal_Blizzard
Encoded by:     anonymous
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
Selfish Cosmos
Whoa!
Good morning!
Morning, Ai-chan!
Morning!
Good morning, senpai.
I'm glad it stopped raining.
Me too.
From now on, we'll get to see each other every day.
Yeah.
I've saved up a ton from work.
It's my treat today.
Damn it!
That driver's such a jerk!
Why you...
Hey, you, apologize, dammit!
Move away from the door.
You're in my way.
Reiko...
This is the attitude you show after drenching someone with muddy water?!
Sadaoka. Hurry up and open the door.
Do you intend to make me late?
M-My apologies, ma'am.
You need to apologize, Reiko!
Oh my. You want me to get on my knees
and beg forgiveness in public?
I didn't say you had to go that far.
Sadaoka. Give him money
to clean his clothes.
Yes, ma'am.
My apologies.
Give him your whole wallet.
It'd be a pain if he says later
that it wasn't enough.
Now look here...
Go ahead.
I don't want it.
Pretending to be too good for it?
I'll never understand peasants.
Senpai, is she a friend of yours?
Huh?! She's just a classmate.
Anyway, she thinks she's the sun and that everything revolves around her.
She's weird.
So she thinks she's the sun?
What was that?
We'll be drawing lots for our new seating assignments.
D-3...
A-3...
Same as last time.
Damn. I can't get away with anything in the front row.
Where's Tsuyoshi?
At the back, just like last time!
He's got the devil's own luck.
Looks like something interesting is going on.
Ugh!
Your face has such a vulgar expression.
Who'd look at you like that?!
He's got the worst luck!
Oh, what a surprise.
You're lucky to have me next to you.
Lucky, my ass!
In any case, what are you doing dressed like that?
It's too early for PE.
And whose fault do you think it is
that I'm dressed like this?!
If you have anything further to say, go through Sadaoka.
You must lose friends a lot.
Oh, maybe you don't have any.
You're a strange one.
You're like a natural airhead.
Why, you...
All right. Quiet, please.
Let's work hard during the second semester.
You don't have much time left in high school.
Let's make some good memories together.
Yes?
Pardon me.
U-Um, we're still in homeroom.
Please pay no attention to me.
Think of me as a stage assistant.
A stage assistant?
Here.
Haruhiko-san ordered
a super-express uniform for you.
It's made from English silk.
I don't know if it will be to your liking.
Who would wear something like this?!
My youthful sweat and tears are, um...
Um...
Hey! What are you doing?!
She instructed me to burn these.
Stop!
Reiko-san. Your tailor, Tamagawa, is as talented as ever.
You recognize quality when you see it, Haruhiko-san.
My...
You!
We're still in homeroom!
Be quiet!
Pardon me.
Shindou-san and Yamaguchi-kun are on duty this week.
You'll start tomorrow.
By Shindou Reiko
How'd I get myself into this?
Wait!
We don't have time to fool around.
We should follow Sadaoka's example.
The flowers stand out too much.
The tag's...
Oh, how lovely.
I see you know the Ikenobo style.
As I'd expect from you.
Unlike someone, Haruhiko-san has taste in art.
I can't take it anymore.
Why do I have to help you
with social studies?
You should just admit
that you're happy to help.
I'll check the other side.
What did you do with the clothes I gave you yesterday?
There's no way I'd wear
something like that!
Sadaoka really tried
to burn my old uniform!
Of course he did.
I'll never understand how someone can dress like that.
You must really go through friends.
I'd rather keep a dog
than have worthless friends.
Ta-da! Hey, Tsuyoshi, how do I look?
Looking good.
You don't mind?
Nope.
Thanks, Shindou!
See ya!
I asked Sadaoka to make sure you wore it.
I'll have to take 20% off his salary.
What's going on?!
Hey. Push the ladders together.
Okay, okay.
I never noticed, but she's got a nice body.
Wh-What are you staring at?
Help me this instant!
If you peek, I'll call the police.
I wouldn't look even if you begged me.
You're so boorish and rude.
You're an insult to humanity!
Like you're one to talk.
What did you say?!
No!
What are you doing?
S-Stop staring and help me already.
Most people don't climb
two ladders at once.
Then you should have climbed up instead.
Why should I have to?!
Why do I have to get something from the top shelf?
You're really something.
The gymnastics club would be impressed.
I can't believe I've become a laughing stock.
You can stay there forever.
B-But...
Say, "Please help me, Tsuyoshi-sama."
Why would I...
See ya.
P-Please.
H-Help me...
Reiko!
Are you all right?
No!
Pervert!
Get your hands off me!
You're such a pervert.
If I hadn't caught you,
you would've been hurt.
This is all your fault anyway
for not pushing the ladders together.
If I had been hurt,
you wouldn't have gotten away with it.
Can't you show some gratitude?!
Are you going to lecture me?
How shameless.
Just be honest.
What was that?
I couldn't hear you.
Get over yourself!
Clean up the rest by yourself.
Kakyuusei
You're paying today?
Only for Ai-chan.
Stingy.
I even skipped out on my club.
Miyuki-chan, the master will
probably treat you.
I wonder if I should be happy about that.
Don't overthink it.
That's right.
Just be true to yourself.
Indeed.
Isn't that Shindou Reiko's car?
Yeah.
She splashed muddy water on senpai's uniform and won't apologize.
That's horrible.
Lovers' Poems
She had a new one delivered later, though.
It's like she doesn't know how to apologize.
She must be lonely.
Everyone sucks up to her,
but no one talks to her as a friend.
Very impressive, Miyuki-chan.
Why two?
Because you're nice.
Thanks, Master.
Their yam udon's great!
It is!
Lovers' Poems
Could I possibly be falling in love
with such a barbarian?
This has to be a joke.
It's simply impossible.
When you exercise, you use energy more efficiently,
and your blood oxygen levels increase.
Your body needs to supply energy more efficiently.
So-
Yamaguchi-kun, read the next portion.
Seems like Reiko caught a cold.
Shouldn't you go see her?
Why me?
You ended up with the uniform.
You go see her.
Say, she can't stop talking about you.
Probably means she likes you.
That's really creepy.
Haruhiko!
You're Reiko's friend, right?
Why don't you visit her?
You've gotta be kidding.
What's with him ?
Please come visit Miss Reiko.
She was mumbling
your name in her sleep.
Is she really that ill?
It could be critical.
It must be hard.
She's such a slave-driver.
Tsuyoshi-san.
Please take good care of her.
This way.
Where are we going?
A pool?
Doesn't she have a cold?
Yes.
I see.
Don't you have a cold?!
Is it really all right
for you to be swimming?
I can hardly breathe
when you're around.
I was just taking a break.
So when you wanted me to visit...
I can't stay home from school forever.
I can't stand you,
but when I see you...
I want to build up
a resistance to you.
That's why I wanted to see you.
I'm leaving.
Please, Tsuyoshi-san.
Running away?
What?
No guy's ever talked back to me before,
except for you.
I'm honored.
You may be a boorish barbarian, but I thought you had guts.
You're just an ordinary delinquent.
Screw you!
You're the rude one!
Then, are you intimidated by my beautiful, Venus-like proportions?
H-Hell, no.
Rub oil on me.
Please.
Fine. Whatever.
Don't bow to me.
Wh-What?
Why are you hesitating?
Keep going.
Don't order me around!
All right, get Sadaoka to do it.
You have the guts to turn down my beautiful, Venus-like body?
You forget your place.
Shut up and keep going.
There.
I wish you were always this cute.
Don't get ahead of yourself!
I'm not like other girls!
Tsuyoshi-san!
Students in charge of the cultural festival will have to work after school.
I've been patient for so long.
What's going on?
Sensei, where's Tsuyoshi?
Yamaguchi-kun came home dripping wet yesterday.
It seems that he caught a cold.
It must've been divine punishment for his rudeness.
Jeez, I'm done for.
Come in.
Huh? Um, y-you're wearing shoes.
The Shindou family's chef will prepare a special meal for you.
Special meal?
Did Reiko tell you to?
I'm sorry, but I'm not allowed to say.
Go on.
Reiko can be pretty cute sometimes.
H-Hot!
It's good.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
Next Time
Once a year, a magical time known as the cultural festival happens for just one day.
Chakkaman Show
With their various feelings overflowing,
everyone looks at things with fresh eyes.
Kakyuusei, episode 9:
Falling Leaves That Pass By.
Falling Leaves That Pass By . . .