What's wrong, Urara-chan?
Urara-chan?
I can't see you anymore.
But I'm glad you're worrying about me so much.
N-No way.
This is my first time.
But it'll be okay, because it's with you.
That's not fair!
I won't regret this!
I'm sorry. My father has been transferred to America,
and my mom says I have to
go there with them.
I've liked you for such a long time!
I-I'm scared!
I-It hurts!
Urara-chan!
I'm so happy. I have no regrets.
I was looking forward to this summer,
so I could be alone with you.
I know. Don't cry, Urara-chan.
I'm sorry!
I don't want to go!
I promise... I promise I'll come back.
Urara-chan...
I promise... I promise I'll come back!
Urara-chan!
Orphan Fansubs presents
Kakyuusei
And here I thought I'd have the chance to be alone with her this summer.
Hi, Kakeru!
Oh, Yukari and Hiromi.
What kind of look is that?
Is this hot weather getting to you?
You're thinking about the lonely summer ahead of you, right?
Kakeru, if it's okay with you,
I'll be your girlfriend for the summer.
Wh-What?
D-Don't you pity me!
Silly girl.
I guess I got dumped.
Kakeru!
What's up, dude?
You look like you're about to die.
You can get so down sometimes.
Kakeru, I beg you!
Please join the tennis club with me!
The tennis club? Why me?
I just found out that Mika-chan is joining the club.
So why do you need me to join?
Listen. This summer,
the tennis club will hold a co-ed training camp at the school's beach house.
What about it?
I don't know if that has
anything to do with it,
but the number of girls who want to join the tennis club has skyrocketed.
And they're all underclassmen.
So what?
You don't know?
Douda is the captain
of the tennis club!
Douda?!
I didn't know he'd become the captain.
As an older brother, aren't you worried about your sister?
None of the underclassmen know what a snake he is.
Aren't you worried about Mika-chan?!
You think I should be?
You're too paranoid, Takeshi.
I don't think Douda has the guts
to touch my sister.
All right, all right! Sorry I asked.
Geez, Takeshi's not wasting his youth.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hang in there! You shouldn't jog
in this scorching sun!
People around here don't even drive
when it's this hot.
You must be having sunstroke.
You should relax in the shade.
I'll call an ambulance.
You just lie down.
I'm going to call now.
I'm fine, really!
If I sit like this for a while,
I should be okay.
Are you in our school's tennis club?
Yes, but I'm only an underclassman.
It's very difficult to make the roster for the summer training camp,
so I thought I should train in addition to regular practice, to avoid being cut.
I hear that more girls will join right before the camp.
Some of them might be better players,
even if they weren't in the club before.
Yeah, there are some people who've played tennis for a long time as a hobby.
Thank you very much!
I feel a lot better now.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
It's nothing! Don't worry about it.
So are you an upperclassman at my school?
Well, yeah, I guess I am.
I'm Natsumi Rie. Thank you very much for everything.
I'm Nanahoshi Kakeru.
I'll walk you home.
I'm fine now, really!
Here!
Hey, Takeshi, I've been thinking.
I've decided to take you up on
joining the tennis club.
Really?! But why now?
I'd do anything for my best buddy.
Whatever. It really helps, though.
I was wondering how I'd approach Douda by myself to apply for the club.
See you tomorrow, then!
All right! Now that I've got a goal for the summer,
I'll take a shower and freshen up.
Ah, man, I've got zits.
Asshole!
I-I didn't know you were in there, Mika!
Mom!
I said I didn't know. Really!
Natsumi Rie. Wait a minute.
Were there any underclassmen that adorable?
I feel like I've seen her before.
But where?
No! Urara-chan!
Food!
I'm coming.
How long are you
going to be in there?
Mika!
Idiot! Mom!
Tennis Club
What a curious turn of events.
Why are you joining the club, Nanahoshi, Minamino?
Because...
I gave it a lot of thought, and that's my decision.
Please, Douda.
Well, I guess it's okay.
Really?!
You two will have to shag balls for a while before you can start swinging rackets.
Think of it as hazing for newcomers.
I understand.
I'll do my best.
Captain Douda!
Nice to see you, Captain!
Can we go to the training camp too?
I don't know. The selection will be made after consulting with the coaches.
Besides, I'm on the boys'
club, not the girls'.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
But if you're selected,
we'll have fun there.
Yes!
Captain Douda's so elegant.
I'm in love!
We're always ignored, you know.
Don't let it get to you.
Maybe you guys can score a little eye candy
while you're shagging balls.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Thank you for the other day!
No problem!
Kakeru, how do you
know Natsumi Rie?
Why do you know her name?
I secretly took pictures of the new students, and she was in my top four.
Oh, yeah! Now I remember.
So how did you approach her? Tell me.
Huh?
Minamino-san, Aniki, why are you here?
Hi, Mika-chan!
We joined the club today.
You're kidding, right?
So much for polite welcomes.
And who says we can't join?
All girls over here for a briefing!
We're going to cover details about the summer training camp!
Usuki-sensei looks great, as usual.
I heard she's going out
with Sanada-sensei.
Hey, do you think
we can make the cut?
Nope, not a chance.
Say what?! Then why did we join in the first place?
Don't worry. Just leave it to me.
I've got this.
So that's how the summer started.
Now we're in the last stage of pre-summer camp practice and selection.
Mika-chan...
Oh, shit. Rie-chan likes Douda!
Hey, Kakeru, we're not impressing Mika-chan at all.
We haven't even had a chance to swing a racket.
All you care about is going to the camp, right?
Our chances of that are
pretty much zero at this rate.
Believe it or not,
I've already gotten permission to go to the camp from Sanada-sensei.
No way! Really?!
Going to the camp isn't all about being a good tennis player.
What did you do to him?
I accepted jobs on the camp cooking staff and first-aid crew.
We'll just help the lady the school hired.
Even if we're peeling potatoes and onions,
we'll technically still be at the camp.
Thanks for the pickup, Senpai!
Good luck. I'll be cheering for you.
Sure! Thank you.
Mika-chan! Do your best!
Yukari? What's wrong?
Nanahoshi-kun.
Help me drown my sorrows.
Geez, you shouldn't be gulping Coke like that.
It's because...
Douda-kun has another new girlfriend.
How pathetic. You shouldn't have fallen for that snake in the first place.
Wake up. You're killing yourself!
I'm just so mad.
She's younger than me.
He had his body pressed up against that underclassman...
under the guise of "coaching" her.
What?! Where did you see them?!
At the Garden Court in the Second Ward,
the one with lights.
No way. That bastard!
How rude!
I'm gonna get drunk on Coke!
No, that's not it.
Like this. Don't swing with just your arm.
Shift all of your weight.
Okay!
In order to shift your weight quickly, you must use your waist.
Your waist, okay?
Right!
Douda!
Senpai?
That son of a bitch is
hitting on Rie-chan!
Let's continue at the camp.
I'll find some time to give you
an extensive private lesson.
Okay. Thank you very much.
See you.
Senpai?
Rie-chan, don't let him fool you!
Nobody even knows how many girls Douda has toyed with like that!
Why are you telling me this?
B-Because... That's...
You're very generous, Senpai.
Thank you for worrying
about me so much.
But I'm not a little girl anymore,
although I can't say I'm an adult either.
Now that I think about it,
I might have the same desire as Douda.
No, it's not the same!
At the very least,
I'm not toying with Rie-chan!
That's right. I'm not like Douda!
Urara-chan...
And then the camp began.
My sister Mika didn't make the cut, so Takeshi lost his reason to go,
but I stuck with it.
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Douda-senpai.
S-Senpai?
Hi. I couldn't get to sleep.
Sakigake Academy Training Camp
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Douda?
Rie-chan?
Senpai!
You can't sleep either?
The ocean breeze feels good, doesn't it?
Rie-chan, have you been
seeing Douda?
I'm sorry. Never mind!
I shouldn't be following you,
jumping to conclusions and trying to be a white knight.
Objectively, I'd have to call myself a busybody.
Senpai?
Well, I know I don't have
any reason to butt in.
It's true that Captain Douda
asked me out before the camp.
Rie-chan!
No, it's okay. I know
what you want to say.
I'm glad that you're worrying about me, but I'm sorry.
I just can't believe
Douda-san is that bad.
I really like Douda-san.
Senpai?
Shh!
Can't you hear that?
Senpai!
I feel so good.
Douda-kun!
Sensei... do you let Sanada-sensei
lick this naughty place too?
You're so bad, Douda-kun.
But it feels so good, Douda-kun.
Douda-kun, I can't hold
back any longer.
You're lying. I know you love it
to death when I look at it.
Not your finger. Put "it" in!
Hurry! Please put it in!
You're so naughty!
What if Sanada-sensei
finds out about this?
Don't tease me. Hurry, please!
If you insist...
Fuck me from behind like an animal!
Here I come.
Douda-kun! Your dick is so good!
Sensei, you're really tight.
Right... there. Good!
Sensei, you have to promise me...
that you'll let me get away with anything from now on.
Yes, I promise.
It feels so good!
Sensei!
Let's continue at the camp.
I'll find some time to give you an extensive private lesson.
I'm about to lose my mind!
Rie-chan! Wait!
Don't do anything rash!
Wait, Rie-chan!
No!
Rie-chan!
Pull yourself together!
I'm sorry.
My mind just went blank.
It's like all the blood
drained out of my body.
I don't blame you.
You've just seen Douda
for what he is.
It's natural to be shocked.
I don't care about
Douda-san anymore!
Rie-chan!
Rie-chan?!
Rie-chan...
I feel so strange.
I'm so hot!
Rie-chan.
Senpai...
Is it okay?
It's going in.
Rie-chan... are you ready?
I'm gonna burst.
I can't think anymore!
Senpai!
Rie-chan!
Senpai...
I'm flying!
Senpai!
Bus Stop
Okay. Take care of yourself.
What about Douda?
Bus Stop
Don't worry! I'm the kind of person who recovers pretty fast.
See ya.
Goshikichou
Gifts
Nanahoshi!
What's going on? Explain!
Resignation
Letter
Natsumi Rie has quit the club.
I'll explain the rest later.
Why are you explaining?
Bus Stop
Listen!
If you don't want me to tell anyone about
what you did with Usuki-sensei yesterday,
Bus Stop
then don't ever think about doing
anything with Rie-chan again!
Nanahoshi, you...
And there you have it.
I'll give the coaches a harmless, inoffensive explanation.
And starting tomorrow,
you have to do all this after practice.
I don't need to be at
this camp anymore.
God damn it!
Now I have my real summer coming.
komorebi ni madoromeba
While I doze in the sunlight under the trees,
kaze no sasayaki wo kanji
I feel the whispering of the wind.
mabuta ni utsutta kimi no egao
The reflection of your smile in my eyes
mabushisugite
is so dazzling.
kagayaku kisetsu wa meguri
Shining seasons come and go.
toki wo kasaneru tabi ni
While we spend time together,
aishiai kizutsuki
we love and hurt each other
otona ni naru
as we slowly become adults.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I'll never forget
kakegae no nai toki wo
those precious moments.
tooku kara mitsumeteiru
I'll look at you from so far away,
ano koro no you ni
just as I did in those days.
kasuka na kioku no naka de
You're smiling at me
kimi wa hohoemikakeru
in my fading memory.
sasayaka na yakusoku oboeteiru yo
I still remember that innocent promise.
ikusen no yoru wo koete
The day I finally meet you
kimi to meguriatta hi
after so many days and nights,
kawarazu ni dakishimete
I want to hold you
kimi wo mamoritai
and protect you forever.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I won't forget anything about you
ano koro no naka de
from those days.
Translation & Timing
Translation Check
Editing & Typesetting
QC
.
Encoding
Raws
Anime-Hentai
Zalis & convexity
Collectr
Calyrica, CP,
konnakude
Piyo-Piyo Productions
ics-
Next Episode Preview
My midsummer love
was like a mirage.
And like a mirage, Rie-chan faded
back into her usual routine.
In the deepening autumn,
I met a lonesome girl.
That frail wisp worked
her way into my heart,
and I just couldn't leave her alone.
Please look forward to the next episode, Kakyuusei 3.
I will protect you.
Dear Kakeru-onii-chan:
Onii-chan, how are you doing?
I'm feeling good and doing my best.
I've even made new friends.
Still, I'm a little lonely.
I miss you, Onii-chan.
We can meet during
this summer break, right?
Surely... Urara.