Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
I start the day.
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
Translated by:           Moho Kareshi
Always rushing to prevent
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Translation Check:                kokujin-kun
these hearts from crumbling.
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
Edited & Typeset by:        Collectr
These words that attempt escaping
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
Timed by:       Eternal_Blizzard
Karaoke by:            EmptySoul
try again and again to reach your ears.
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
Calyrica
Quality Control:      Eternal_Blizzard
Encoded by:          anonymous
The threads of my feelings
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
all connect to you.
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
When I hear a snapping thread,
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
I tightly embrace its melody.
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
begins to bloom.
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
Another Spring Breeze . . .
Senpai!
I love you!
Miyuki... chan?
If Miyuki and Ai-chan weren't friends...
I know!
Oh! Tsuyoshi-senpai.
G-Good morning.
Y-Yeah.
You're on time, for once.
I was having fun chatting with her.
Right?
Yeah.
I told her that we're all going to the shrine tomorrow.
The shrine?
Everyone?
Everyone from the Dogeza Group.
And who is that, exactly?
Well, I've got nothing better to do.
I don't mind.
Right!
Ai-chan?
S-Senpai!
Wh-What's wrong?
U-Um...
Ai-chan, about yesterday...
Um, Senpai,
my family always goes
on a trip at New Year's.
I see.
But I thought I'd look after the house alone this time.
Alone?
I see.
So...
Would you like to visit the shrine with me?
The shrine?
Um...
If you already have plans, it's all right.
I...
I don't have plans.
Sure! Let's go!
Really?
Thanks, Senpai!
Visiting the shrine, huh?
PUSH TO
CROSS
Oh no! I forgot to tell him when and where to meet!
I'm helpless on my own.
No. Even if I'm alone...
Did he go out again?
"You can call me anytime."
A-Ai.
Did you hear?
H-Hear what?
About the shrine visit?
Shrine visit?
We're all going tomorrow.
Everyone?
You mean Dogeza?
Right.
Senpai's coming too.
You'll be coming too, right?
Oh yeah, Ai's going with Senpai.
See ya.
Oh yeah, we never decided
when and where to meet.
Hello?
It's me.
Miyuki?
What's up?
Are you free?
Yeah, why?
I ran into Ai.
She didn't know we were going to the shrine.
Did you speak to her?
Why hide it from her?
Good point.
Will you come tomorrow?
You promised. You'll be there, right?
Sorry. What am I babbling about?
Don't apologize, dummy.
Well, good night.
She...
I wonder if he read my note.
Hello?
Tanaka-san. Thanks for the other day.
Senpai's coming too.
He must be busy.
Open
Listen, about the shrine visit.
Excuse me.
Coming!
Thank you very much!
Master?
Oh, could you do me a favor?
Hi!
Minazu-chan's not here yet.
She'll be here this evening, right?
How'd you know?
So you'll be sticking around until then?
I heard she's coming to the shrine.
Just wanted to check.
You're always the first to know.
Well, see you later!
Don't forget the sales receipt!
I won't!
Hey, Tsuyoshi!
What's the rush?
Supplies? Now?
I forgot to get enough for New Year's.
Only the wholesaler's open today.
Welcome.
Hello.
Um...
I sent Tsuyoshi on an errand.
He won't be back until evening because it's a pretty long trip.
Oh, Ai-chan.
Yes?
Asagayama Station
480 yen, huh?
It's almost evening.
Okay.
See you tonight.
Oh, right.
She's not answering.
Maybe she went out.
The shrine?
You're coming too, right?
Um, I...
Tsuyoshi's gonna be there as well.
What's wrong?
It's nothing!
Sorry to bother you!
Coming!
What do you want?
I'm going out.
I wanted to ask you about the shrine visit.
We're meeting at Yubikiri Shrine at 11.
Are you coming?
Bye.
Aren't you meeting Senpai?
Why did I ask her that?
I'm so stupid.
I trust him, so why am I crying?
He'll get angry with me.
Ah, Master?
It's me.
I'm about to get on the train.
Don't blame me!
Your map's not much help!
Here
Sorry.
Thank you very much.
About tonight...
The train for Suzuki-cho is arriving soon.
What?
Please stand behind the yellow line.
Hey!
About tonight!
Huh? What was that?
Two house blends, Master.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm busy. Gotta go.
Hello?
He's just getting on the train?
Yep.
Aren't you closing early tonight?
Not many people come on New Year's.
It's not fun to go straight to the shrine after work.
Will he make it?
We'll just leave him a note.
I-I don't mind waiting.
I can't let customers hold the fort.
You've got a point there.
We should get going too.
Oh, right.
Closed for New Year's Eve
Good grief.
"Tsuyoshi. We'll be at the shrine at 11."
Good grief. What a selfish old fart.
"Ai-chan came by this afternoon."
What?
We just missed each other.
"You should be more decisive."
"Otherwise, you'll regret it
when you're older."
Master.
Kakyuusei
Ai-chan.
Senpai's with everyone.
No, he wouldn't do that.
Senpai, I'll wait for you at the shrine.
I don't know where or when to meet.
Is she at the dorm?
Where could she be?
Where'd she go?
I've never felt like this before.
Miyuki-chan.
So you're back already?
Where is everyone?
It's no fun without you, so I left.
I see.
I thought it'd be fun if you were here.
And you're actually here.
Hard to believe.
B-By the way, have you seen Ai?
Why isn't he here?
Maybe he's at the restaurant.
What if we miss each other again?
So she's...
I don't know.
Have you tried calling her?
I did.
We never decided where or when to meet.
Where is she?
He's worried only about her.
When I came in, he was smiling for her.
He thought I was her.
He... He was waiting for Ai all this time.
Oh, sorry.
I was just thinking.
Senpai!
You're pathetic when you panic like this!
It's pathetic...
but I'm jealous.
Miyuki-chan.
She must be waiting for you.
You just couldn't contact
each other. That's all.
You're... kidding.
She would've called by now.
You're saying she's waiting for me?
At this hour of the night?
She would wait forever for you.
For better or worse.
Miyuki.
I've watched her for a long time.
When I arranged the date at the park.
When we double-dated.
When we went to the beach.
She was always...
I'll go find her.
She wasn't at the shrine.
All right.
Miyuki. I...
Go! She's waiting for you, and it's freezing outside!
I may as well go home.
Ai-chan?
Senpai!
I knew you'd come.
Were you waiting here all night?
Yes.
They're cold.
They're frozen.
You dummy.
You waited all this time for me.
That's because I...
I believed you would come.
No matter what you do,
no matter who you like,
I'll always love you.
So I won't run from you.
I'll always be thinking about you.
Ai-chan.
You must be cold.
Sorry.
You're so warm.
Senpai.
Yes?
You'll be graduating soon.
I'll miss you.
We can see each other outside of school.
I know,
but I'll still miss you.
We can see each other anytime.
Graduation
Ceremony
CANDLE de naisho banashi
キャンドルで 内緒ばなし
We're sharing secrets by candlelight.
dare kara uchiakeyou ka
誰から打ち明けようか
Who wants to go first?
junban ga sugita ato de
順番が過ぎた後で
But I won't tell them about my love,
ienai koi mo aru
言えない恋もある
even after we've all had our turns.
gofun kurai tokei wo susumeba
五分くらい時計を進めば
If only I could move time
ii koto aru you ni
いいことあるように
at least five minutes forward.
yureru hibi me wo sorashi
揺れる日々 目をそらし
I fool around like I always do
itsumo yori odokete mita
いつもより おどけて見た
and ignore my conflicted reality.
hohoemi no otosu kage
微笑みの 落とす影
I smile through the shadows,
furikaeru hikari wa doko kana
振り返る 光はどこかな
but there's no light when I reminisce.
kitto koi mo yume mo sagaseru yo
きっと恋も 夢も探せるよ
Still, we will find love and live our dreams.
mayou no mo tanoshii
迷うのも楽しい
The perplexity is all part of the fun.
CANDLE wo tomosu tabi
キャンドルを 灯すたび
The room always brightens up
yomigaeru mabushii toki
よみがえる まぶしい時
whenever we light the candles.
itazura na omoide ni
悪戯な 思い出に
I even love when we share memories
tachidomaru jikan mo itoshii
立ち止まる 時間も愛しい
that are embarrassing enough to stop time.
yureru hi ga kieru made
揺れる火が 消えるまで
I will be honest and open up
shoujiki na jibun de iyou
正直な 自分でいよう
until I stop being so conflicted.
sorezore no kage to kako
それぞれの 影と過去
By sharing all of our shadowy pasts,
yorisoeba tomodachi ni nareru
寄り添えば 友達になれる
we will become best of friends.
Open
Long time no see.
Hi.
I was in the neighborhood.
You haven't changed. Neither has the shop.
We only change when we're young.
Oh right.
I need to make a call.
Miyuki-chan.
Use this.
You don't mind?
Nope. The owner told me
to use it and toss it out.
Why get one in the first place?
That's just like him.
Preview
A mysterious girl appears
before the young man.
She is a little whirlwind who floats in the air.
He is the only one on her eccentric mind.
Love can bloom at any time.
Kakyuusei bonus episode:
Nice to Meet You! I'm Tina!