Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
I start the day.
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
Translated by:           Moho Kareshi
Always rushing to prevent
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Translation Check:                EmptySoul
these hearts from crumbling.
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
Edited & Typeset by:        Collectr
These words that attempt escaping
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
Timed by:                EmptySoul
Karaoke by:            EmptySoul
try again and again to reach your ears.
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
Quality Control:      Eternal_Blizzard
Encoded by:          anonymous
The threads of my feelings
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
all connect to you.
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
When I hear a snapping thread,
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
I tightly embrace its melody.
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
begins to bloom.
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
Wavering Winter Trees
Senpai!
Why? Why?
What happened, Miyuki?
I'm such an idiot. I'm really stupid.
You see... I... like...
M-Miyuki!
Wake up!
It's good to see you, Ai-chan!
Um, how's Miyuki-chan feeling?
She caught a cold.
Huh?
She came home soaking wet.
How bad is it?
Don't worry. She'll be fine by tomorrow.
I see.
What brings you here?
I got her a Christmas present.
My!
Just a minute.
My head still feels heavy.
But she brought you a Christmas present.
I'll call her later.
Okay.
I really wanted to tell her
all about yesterday.
Ai...
I know I was wrong,
but...
Mama, where are we going?
Sun Merry
What do you wanna see?
I'll leave it to you.
Sun Merry
Then...
That looks cool.
But she'd probably prefer
a romance movie.
How about this one?
I'd love to see it.
You like stuff like this, don't you?
Yeah, but...
I want to see something you'd like.
You sure?
I want to know more about you.
And we get to see a movie today, just the two of us.
That's enough for me.
I see.
We've never seen a movie alone before.
Last time, Miyuki-chan and the boss were there. It was very stressful.
Speaking of that, I went to Miyuki-chan's house yesterday.
Huh? You saw her?
Sun Merry
She had a cold.
I knew it.
Sun Merry
Hm?
Well, I was worried about her.
Miracle Theater
Me too. She rarely gets sick.
She'll be fine.
Miracle Theater
She's got a strong constitution.
Her mom said the same thing.
Miracle Theater
See?
Let's go in.
Okay.
Come in!
Hello. You must be her mother.
Yes.
Sorry to disturb you.
I'm Miyuki-san's-
Oh, I see!
Thank you for looking after her.
It's all right.
She caught a cold.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
It's all my fault.
Not at all.
Thanks for seeing her home.
"Seeing her home"?
Miyuki! Yamaguchi-san's here.
Y-Yamaguchi?
Senpai...
Satake-senpai.
What do you want?
I wanted to apologize.
You don't have to.
You caught a cold?
I'm better now.
You went to see Yamaguchi after you left.
That's none of your business.
Does Minamizato-kun know that he took you home?
Of course, you caught a cold.
What would she do if she knew?
What would happen to your friendship?
Please leave.
I think I'll go have a talk with her.
Do what you like.
Shit.
I'll tell her.
She'll find out eventually anyway.
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
Sun Road
Year-End
Bargains!
We went on a date yesterday.
If I drop by Dogeza so soon,
will he be upset with me?
But...
Well, if it isn't Ai-chan.
Satake-senpai.
Hello.
Wh-What do you want?
I have something very important to tell you.
Oh, my!
Miyuki-chan!
Can I have the afternoon off, Master?
No. Minatsu-chan and I
can't run things alone.
You have a visitor.
She's your favorite, Master.
Hello.
Miyuki-chan!
Welcome.
M-Miyuki-chan?
I was worried because you haven't been around lately.
Right, Tsuyoshi?
I heard you caught a cold.
Just a little one.
I'm sorry about what happened that night.
Please, have a seat!
Thanks.
But I'm over it now.
I'm never sick for long.
I see.
Ah, right, could you
do me a favor, Senpai?
Me?
Well, could you go shopping with me?
Shopping?
No?
I don't want to force you.
I have to work.
Good point.
Because it's for Miyuki-chan's sake,
you don't need to worry about work.
Senpai and Miyuki-chan were together on Christmas Eve?
That's right.
After our date, they met in secret.
It's horrible, I know.
You're lying.
Lying?
I'd never lie to a cute girl like you.
Why don't you ask her mother?
That...
Well, since we've both been dumped,
how about we repair
our broken hearts together?
Mama, what's he doing?
Quiet. Ignore him.
Come on.
Sauna
Miyuki-chan?
Sorry for dragging you out.
I can't say no to the Master.
Look, that's the shop.
Is that...
I don't have any brothers,
so I don't know what presents to get for guys.
This looks pretty lame.
This might work!
Nice!
This design's a little lame.
How about this one?
Hey!
Looks fine to me.
You didn't even look at it.
I don't understand fashion.
Jeez, then what's the point
of having you here?
Hold still.
Okay.
Better than I thought.
This should be perfect!
This is nice too.
Which do you prefer?
H-How should I know?
Jeez, can't you take this seriously?
Maybe a more mature design
would be better.
How about this one?
So you're still single at your age, Master?
Yes.
Um, have you seen Senpai?
A-Ai-chan.
Kakyuusei
Thanks for coming.
Are you sure that's all right?
Yeah. Thanks for picking one for me.
Okay.
Um, Senpai, do you have
any plans after this?
No, not really.
Then stay with me a bit longer.
H-Hey, wait!
Good. Good.
You can do it.
Jeez.
So close!
I don't have a knack for this.
You suck!
You're in the Athletics Club.
Don't be rude.
Sorry.
You're lame, but...
L-Let me try again.
I'll get it this time.
You look weird, Haru!
I've never done a sticker booth with a guy.
Let's leave.
Wanna give it a try?
Come on.
All right.
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Insert coin     Choose frame    Now pose       It's done!
Please insert a coin!
How to make a print
Please choose a frame
Lower your head a bit.
Okay.
Please choose a frame
What's wrong?
Wh-Which frame do you like?
Slow down.
S-Sorry.
Oops.
Oh, no.
We can't stay here forever.
There.
How about this one?
O-Okay.
This is fun.
Let's get another one.
You look weird.
Yeah, it looks like I have a weird expression on my face.
Well then, we should get going.
Hey, Senpai.
Let's go to the park.
Huh?
Please.
Okay?
Sure.
It's gone!
What's gone?
My shopping bag!
I left it in the booth!
She's not as together as she looks.
Tsuyoshi-kun went out with Miyuki-chan.
Miyuki-chan.
Senpai.
Whoa! It's warm.
Here.
Your coffee.
It's warm.
Are you mad that I dragged you around?
Why would I be mad?
But I... you understand, don't you?
I know I'm hurting Ai.
I know I'm being selfish.
But...
I'm a guy, so I don't want to hurt girls.
But... I just don't know what to do.
Forget about that. It's my fault.
I didn't actually have any plans for today. I was just winging it.
And this will probably backfire, but...
Senpai.
Take it!
Hey, Miyuki.
It's for you.
Is this...
I intended to give it to you all along.
Senpai!
I love you.
Miyuki... chan?
Let me take you home.
You don't want to catch a cold again.
A-Ai!
A-Ai-chan!
Why?
How could you?
Sorry.
Wh-Why are you apologizing?
I can't believe you'd do this to me.
Ai-chan!
Ai-chan! L-Listen!
Please... just let me be alone right now!
Ai-chan!
Miyuki... chan.
I need to talk to you.
Maybe I shouldn't have told her.
Tsuyoshi-kun?
Listen...
Ah, Minatsu-chan.
Could you give me a hand here?
Coming.
I need to tell you something.
Satake-san already told me.
I should have known it was him.
So it's true?
I know it was wrong,
but I don't want to lie to myself anymore.
Tsuyoshi-senpai likes you.
I thought you were my best friend.
I thought so too.
However, I also like him.
I don't want that.
We're best friends, so I can't hate you.
We got along so well.
And we fell in love with the same boy.
I really like you.
Still, I can't change how I feel.
I'm going to take him from you.
Miyuki... chan.
Get mad.
It's easier that way.
I...
I won't give up!
I love Senpai.
I love him more than anyone!
My feelings for him are stronger
than anyone else's.
I'll never give up!
Do whatever you want.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Preview
Next Episode
The depths of their feelings.
The boy's heart wanders.
Worries, hurt, and...
But no matter how bitter the winter, the seasons will change.
The spring breeze will soon blow.
Yes, it's all a part of their youth.
Kakyuusei, final episode:
Another Spring Breeze.
Another Spring Breeze . . .