Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:            EmptySoul
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                   Meiko
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:        Collectr
Timed & Typeset by:       EmptySoul
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Karaoke by:     EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Quality Control:         E_B & Calyrica
Encoded by:        Eternal_Blizzard
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
Gratitude for Gypsophila
Sorry, I was in the back.
Y-You're...
From before...
You're...
H-Hi.
Thanks for helping me before.
U-Um, is your foot all right?
I'm fine now.
I'm glad.
So what kind of flowers did you want?
U-Um...
It's so hot.
Welcome.
Um, I'm not a customer.
I'm here about the part-time job.
So you're the one.
I requested an honest young man.
Honest...
Okay! You're hired.
R-Really?!
I'll do my best!
So you're a third-year student at Muzuki Academy?
Mahoko-chan.
Yes?
This is Yamaguchi Tsuyoshi-kun.
He'll be working here for the summer.
She's Mochida Mahoko-chan.
Nice to meet you.
Same to you.
Try to get along.
Mahoko-chan, show him the ropes.
Sure.
Be sure to work hard!
So, um, what should I do?
Ouch!
That really stings.
Things like this usually make people quit.
You're really good.
It's simple once you get the hang of it.
All right! I'm going to get good at this!
Ouch!
She's good at that.
Yamaguchi-san, this is ready for delivery.
Okay.
I can't believe that I get to work with her.
I shouldn't hold back when it comes to my destiny.
Our fingers are tied with the red string of fate.
Note: An invisible red string of fate is said to link people destined to be lovers.
Are you trying to kill yourself, idiot?!
I-I'm sorry!
Mahoko-chan is cute, isn't she?
Huh? Y-Yeah...
She's my daughter's classmate.
The rules at the school are pretty strict,
particularly about boys.
I see.
Thank you!
Good work.
So, Mahoko-chan, you go to Hazuki Academy, right?
Yeah, but how did you know?
I just had a feeling.
I see.
Can you keep a secret?
You see, I'm actually psychic.
Just kidding.
I heard from the lady I delivered to yesterday.
I hate liars.
You're angry?
Just kidding.
Let's do our best today too.
She got me.
At least it seems like we're getting closer.
Ouch!
Damn you. Ouch!
I won't lose to you.
He doesn't quite have it yet, but at least he's trying.
So hot.
So it was you, Tsuyoshi.
Don't surprise me like that!
I'm the one who's surprised.
What happened to the job at the beach?
I quit.
I'm a florist now.
No way. You're a florist?
Yep, I'm a real florist.
Did something happen to the beach job?
Not really.
Anyway, thanks for covering for me at Dogeza.
Don't worry about it, because I get to spend each day with Minatsu-san.
Why did you quit?
C'ya. Tell Master I said hi.
Hey!
Cattleya, huh?
There's something more going on.
The Giants have now won five straight.
Mahoko-chan.
What's this big flower called?
Be careful, Yamaguchi-sun.
This flower is called a Casa Blanca.
But you shouldn't let the pollen get on your clothes.
That's why we cut the stamens off before we give them to customers.
Be careful with these, okay?
Okay. There's a lot to being a florist, isn't there?
That's what I thought.
Why did you take a job as a florist, Yamaguchi-san?
That's because... well... I like flowers.
I see.
Sorry for asking you a strange question.
I'm the one who's strange.
It's weird for a guy to want to be a florist.
It's not weird.
People who like flowers are wonderful.
Wonderful, huh?
You're flattering me.
Yep. Wonderful.
Mahoko-chan, want some chocolate?
Good work today.
Um, Mahoko-chan!
U-Um, on your day off, um...
what do you like to do?
I like to-
Are you done with work?
M-Mayumi.
Looks like you've been working diligently.
Don't forget your promise.
Promise?
That you'd use your paycheck to do something fun with me.
Oh, that.
Oh? So that's how it is.
Wh-What?
I have some stuff to do. Excuse me.
See you tomorrow, then.
Was I getting in the way?
That's not it!
Don't be so defensive.
This explains why you haven't quit yet.
Like I said!
From A to B...
I haven't done anything!
Seriously?
Wh-What is it?
Jeez.
A popular band has announced that they're doing a nation-wide tour.
Look forward to it.
Next we have the results of last night's game.
Mahoko-chan... about last night.
I don't want to talk about last night.
Yamaguchi-san, would you organize the boxes in the back?
Uh, all right.
Damn it! Damn it!
I wonder what's wrong with Mahoko-chan.
She's been like that all morning.
Look at these! They're pretty.
There's more inside.
We're gonna look around.
Those are nice.
Yeah, they're really pretty.
Right?
Who could I give them to?
She's...
Yamaguchi-san, we have customers.
Customers?
Huh?
Tsuyoshi-senpai!
You're working here now?
What brings you here?
We're here to buy flowers, obviously.
Maybe Ai-chan is, but...
You don't think I would buy flowers?
W-Well...
What are you looking for?
I'm not looking. She is.
This customer prefers practical gifts.
I think I like these best.
I'll take this.
Okay. I'll ring it up.
Here's your chance, Miyuki-chan.
Right...
Thanks for the other day.
Huh?
I mean, for protecting me when those guys were harassing me.
Oh, that.
You saved the day, Tsuyoshi-senpai.
So that's what happened.
Sorry for the wait.
Wow! They're so pretty!
Thanks!
Let's go, Ai.
Okay.
Do your best at work, Tsuyoshi-senpai.
And don't do your best at other things.
C'ya.
Thanks for coming!
You're pretty popular.
I have to leave early today.
The boss knows already.
Traffic's so slow today.
I don't think Mahoko-chan understands.
Isn't that Mahoko-chan?
M-Mahoko-chan!
I got it. Shut up already!
Mahoko-chan. No way...
Kakyuusei
Tsuyoshi, are you sure it's okay to be slacking off?
It's fine.
You'll get fired.
That's fine too.
Well, if you get fired, come back here.
Minoru's no good.
All he does is talk to Minatsu all day.
Do not!
She'll hate you.
Get back to work.
It's fine. I can't summon up the will.
Did you get shot down by a girl at work?
You've got it wrong!
No, I'd say you're spot on.
Sharp as always, Minatsu-san.
Shut up!
This summer feels so short.
Maybe I should quit.
Who was that guy?
Damn it.
I'm too upset to sleep.
You're in a good mood today.
Yeah, I had a great day yesterday.
Can I go again?
Sure. When you smile like this, the flowers are happy.
Well, see you later.
Looks like I was right.
Yesterday was a date.
Want to practice wrapping today?
Okay?
You fold the paper here.
I see.
See. It's easy, right?
Wrapping is fun.
Isn't it?
Flowers look even prettier when they're wrapped together with other flowers.
Keep going like that.
Um, Mahoko-chan.
Did something good happen yesterday?
Come here, Yamaguchi-san.
These are so beautiful.
What are?
Aren't they pretty?
Just like that. You're pretty good at this.
Do your best.
All right! It's starting to look decent.
Want some herbal tea?
It's hot and delicious.
You've been working hard.
Yeah. I'm really into this.
You concentrate well.
I've changed my opinion of you.
Here's some news about the Giants.
Here we go.
The Giants won big yesterday, thanks to Kiyomatsu's consecutive home runs.
Mahoko-chan's a baseball fan.
Earlier today, Kiyomatsu suffered an injury.
He hurt his right foot during practice and was taken to the hospital.
No way.
According to a press release,
he fractured his big toe and is likely to miss the rest of the season.
Hello, this is Cattleya.
Yeah, we have some.
Okay. I'll have them delivered right away.
Suddenly she's in a bad mood.
I wonder what's wrong.
Excuse me.
Yes? Welcome!
Do you have any Casa Blanca?
Yes, um...
Right this way.
Look at this!
Just look at what the pollen from the Casa Blancas did to me.
Those flowers...
If the pollen gets on clothes, it's a real problem.
I'm very sorry.
How are you going to make this up to me?
U-Um...
What do you want?
Yamaguchi-san.
I'm very sorry!
I was supposed to cut the pistels off this morning, but I forgot.
I'm so sorry! It's all my fault!
Shouldn't you have noticed?
U-Um...
I'm sorry. I'll pay for your cleaning.
This was my responsibility.
I'm truly sorry!
Yamaguchi-san...
Right. I understand.
I'll do that.
Bye.
Tomorrow the boss also will come in
to apologize, so don't worry.
And he said we can close
the store for the night.
Thanks.
For covering for me.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not a pro yet.
I can't believe I didn't notice something so basic just because I heard about Kiyomatsu's injury.
Kiyomatsu?
Kiyomatsu
I'm a huge fan of the Giants.
I get very happy when they win and really sad when they lose.
It's stupid, isn't it?
I see. So that's why...
You don't have to make fun of me.
S-Sorry...
I'm sorry.
S-Say, you went with a guy to a baseball game yesterday, didn't you?
Do you know him?
Well, kind of.
How do you know my little brother?
Your little brother?!
Yeah.
S-So he's just your little brother!
You're weird, Yamaguchi-san.
Well, it's time to close the shop.
I have one more delivery to do.
If you want, I can go.
It's fine. I want to do it.
I'm heading out to deliver these. Take care of the shop.
Just Gypsophilas?
Yamaguchi-san?
I have a delivery for you,
Mochida Mahoko-san.
A delivery?
These are for you.
For me?
Yeah.
They're from me... and them.
Thanks.
I'm very happy.
Do you know what Gypsophilas mean?
Uh, I don't.
Then... close your eyes.
Please?
S-Sure.
Gypsophilas mean thank you.
Thank you, Yamaguchi-san.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
They dream about a slice of happiness.
They wish for a piece of love.
Their feelings yearn to connect, yet they keep missing.
While they search for an answer,
the summer days pass in silence.
Kakyuusei episode 7:
The Fading Summer...