I'm so sorry.
What are you doing here?
Mika?
The way you're drooling all over yourself is pathetic, Aniki.
Mika-chan!
Urara! Here I come!
Urara...
So she's Mika's friend.
Orphan Fansubs presents
Kakyuusei
Boy! Spring comes to
young lovers across the world.
But for me,
it's like winter never ended.
This really sucks.
Hey, Hiromi!
Hi, Nanahoshi-kun!
You wanna go for a cup of coffee?
Maybe next time.
I've got a prior engagement.
I see.
Mister! Could you wrap these up?
Next time, huh? She's been saying "next time" for the last three years.
It'll always be this way
for Hiromi and me.
Yo, Nanahoshi.
Douda?
All alone?
You got a problem with that?
Catch you later, Nanahoshi.
Where should we go next?
Asshole!
I bet he's dragging her
to a hotel or something!
Mom! I asked you to shorten my skirt!
Now I can't go to the opening ceremony! It's too embarrassing!
Hiromi!
Catch me if you can!
Hey, Hiromi! Wait for me!
Don't look.
You're...
Urara-chan!
Please be gentle.
This is my first time.
Urara-chan.
Is this okay?
Yes. Softly now.
So softly...
It was just a dream.
I'm losing touch with reality.
Is my last year of high school just going to pass me by?
What's up?
Are you lost?
Yes. Are you Mika-chan's brother?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about the other day.
No problem. Which class are you in?
I'm in 1-A.
Oh, the same class
as my little sister.
Follow me. I'll show you the way.
Thanks.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Urara, I've been looking
for you. Oh, Onii!
Well, see you later.
What was that about?
Your big brother is so nice.
You think so?
He's just a slob who bums around the house all the time.
So not cute.
She and Urara-chan are
as different as night and day.
Though I wouldn't mind a bit of Urara-chan at night...
You're in the way!
If you guys are gonna be useless,
be useless at home!
When girls become third-years,
they're not so cute and sweet anymore.
Yep!
Compared to girls like Hiromi, who've been corrupted by high school relationships,
underclassmen are pure and innocent enough to mold to our liking.
Or so I hope!
Kakeru, wanna come to my place?
Sure.
Excuse me.
Douda!
What an asshat.
Douda-kun! Hey, wait for me, Shuichirou!
She even calls him by his first name.
And you know what that means.
Man, screw him! Screw Douda!
He's got his hands
on Hiromi already!
It's not just a hobby anymore. You can beat the pros now.
If you want, you can
have some of these.
Want some coffee, Kakeru?
Sure, thanks.
No way. He must like Mika.
I love you!
H-He found out.
O-Onii-sama!
Onii-sama, please!
Quit creeping me out!
Onii-sama, please give me
your approval to go out with her.
She's my little sister, you freak!
Seriously...
Nanahoshi
Coming!
Urara-chan!
Good evening.
Mika-chan invited me to spend the night at her place.
I'm pleased to be here.
M-Mika, Urara-chan is here!
Let her in!
Thank you for having me over!
Let's take a bath
together before dinner.
Sure! I brought some extra clothes.
You have a great body.
Thank you. So do you.
I could stand to lose a few pounds.
I won't get horny over
my sister's body.
Let me wash your back.
Thanks!
Mika, you're in the way!
I can't see!
It's so hot! I'll open the window.
Ah, it feels so good.
Hello.
Hiromi? This is a surprise.
Nanahoshi-kun, can you
come out now?
Hey, what's up, Hiromi?
I know that you've liked me for a long time, Nanahoshi-kun.
I've felt it.
What are you saying?
You can do whatever
you want with me now.
Hotel Flower
What? Oh, yeah!
Hiromi, what are we doing here?
Hey, Hiromi!
You know, I never exactly
disliked you, Nanahoshi-kun.
But don't you think w-we're moving a little too fast?
You know, girls don't function as smoothly as boys...
when we have to operate our heads and bodies simultaneously.
But...
Th-The body that I've dreamed about...
i-is right here in front of me.
A-Are you really sure about this?
This is the chance... to make my third-year dreams come true.
Hiromi.
Oh, Shuichirou!
Yes...
Ah! Right there!
You're making me crazy, Shuichirou!
Nanahoshi-kun?
Douda just dumped you, didn't he?
You're trying to forget him
by sleeping with me, aren't you?
Sorry, I can't do that.
I won't be Douda's replacement.
I'm so sorry!
This isn't the Hiromi I know.
You'll forget all about him by tomorrow, right?
Maybe I shouldn't have been so upstanding.
It was my first real chance,
and it would've been with Hiromi.
Urara-chan!
Nope, I was right!
Uncorrupted, innocent Urara-chan.
She could be my first!
Douda!
Nanahoshi?!
Don't even think about it with this girl!
Don't get your panties in a twist.
I'm just trying to recruit
her for my club.
He's telling the truth.
He really is!
Then keep your hands off her!
Are you jealous?
Onii-san, please don't!
Losers are so annoying.
Listen. That guy is a snake.
O-Okay, but...
Why...
Why are you so worried about me?
Because...
you're a friend of my little sister.
I mean, um...
You're like a younger sister to me!
What?
So pretty!
Look!
Boy! She is so cute!
Kakeru!
You're late, Takeshi!
Never mind that.
Mika-chan went to the used underwear resale shop!
What?!
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Lingerie
Image Club
Mock
Sex
Adult   Shop
Sex Master
Hey! There she is! There!
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Urara-chan!
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Schoolgirl
Clothing
Uniforms
Underwear
Oh! Mika's big brother!
Where's Mika?
Oh, she just left.
What? Mika-chan!
He... must really like her.
Oh, yeah!
Come with me!
Ouch! What's the matter?
Your curiosity is going
to lead you astray.
I went there to turn them down.
Schoolgirl     Clothing
What?
You thought we were
cooperating with them?
I... I can't believe it.
We just went in there to tell them not to follow us around,
because a friend from my previous school kept bugging us to join them!
Jubankan Theater
Bunny Town
I'm sorry. I thought you were...
Jubankan Theater
Bunny Town
But I'm glad you're worrying about me so much.
Jubankan Theater
Bunny Town
Urara-chan...
All right! Now Urara-chan and I have bonded!
I guess I should stop
ridiculing Takeshi.
Coming!
Good afternoon!
Oh, hi.
I'm supposed to study with Mika-chan today.
The sky looks kinda weird, doesn't it?
Please come in.
Sure.
Mika went with my mom to my aunt and uncle's place.
They should be back any time now.
Okay!
The forecast for the Kantou area is sunny,
turning partly cloudy.
There's a thirty percent
chance of rain.
They're running late.
Yeah.
The phone!
Hello, Nanahoshi residence.
Oh, Mika. Urara-chan's here now.
Here, I'll put her on for you.
Hello.
Hi, Urara-chan. I'm so sorry.
There are gale-force winds in this area, and the trains aren't running.
My uncle insists that we stay here.
I'm sorry, Urara.
We'll have to cancel our session.
That's okay.
There's a spring storm here.
How about there?
It's not too bad now, but...
We should stay inside
until the wind dies down.
Right!
O-Oh, shit!
Sorry. I took your picture
without asking you.
Urara-chan...
I've had a crush on you ever since
I saw you at the opening ceremony.
I... really like you, Onii-chan.
R-Really?
Wh-What should I do now?!
This situation wasn't covered in any of the manuals or videos!
O-Ouch!
Sorry!
Please be gentle with me.
Urara-chan.
This is my first time.
But it'll be okay, because it's with you.
What do I do next?
I've watched a lot of pornos
and read a lot of magazines, but...
I feel like I'm being swept away!
A-According to those pornos, I should...
Don't look at me.
It's okay. It'll be okay!
You're driving me crazy!
No!
Sorry!
No, it's okay.
But please don't hurt me.
It's okay! It'll be okay!
No... Don't look!
Please don't stare at me.
Oh, sorry.
That feels great!
Here I come.
Ouch! That's not the right place!
Sorry. This was my first time too.
I'm happy. I'm very happy.
Urara-chan!
I won't regret this!
What's wrong?
No way. It's back already?
That was a quick revival.
Let's try again, Urara-chan.
Huh?
Let's try again.
This time, I'll...
Urara-chan...
I-I'm scared!
I-It hurts!
Urara-chan!
I'm so happy. I have no regrets.
Good morning!
Oh, good morning.
Onii-chan...
komorebi ni madoromeba
While I doze in the sunlight under the trees,
kaze no sasayaki wo kanji
I feel the whispering of the wind.
mabuta ni utsutta kimi no egao
The reflection of your smile in my eyes
mabushisugite
is so dazzling.
kagayaku kisetsu wa meguri
Shining seasons come and go.
toki wo kasaneru tabi ni
While we spend time together,
aishiai kizutsuki
we love and hurt each other
otona ni naru
as we slowly become adults.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I'll never forget
kakegae no nai toki wo
those precious moments.
tooku kara mitsumeteiru
I'll look at you from so far away,
ano koro no you ni
just as I did in those days.
kasuka na kioku no naka de
You're smiling at me
kimi wa hohoemikakeru
in my fading memory.
sasayaka na yakusoku oboeteiru yo
I still remember that innocent promise.
ikusen no yoru wo koete
The day I finally meet you
kimi to meguriatta hi
after so many days and nights,
kawarazu ni dakishimete
I want to hold you
kimi wo mamoritai
and protect you forever.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I won't forget anything about you
ano koro no naka de
from those days.
Translation & Timing
Translation Check
Editing & Typesetting
QC
.
Encoding
Raws
Anime-Hentai
Zalis & convexity
Collectr
Calyrica, CP,
konnakude
Piyo-Piyo Productions
ics-
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I'll never forget
Next Episode Preview
kakegae no nai toki wo
those precious moments.
kawarazu ni dakishimete
I want to hold you
kimi wo mamoritai
and protect you forever.
itsumademo wasurenai sa
I won't forget anything about you
ano koro no naka de
from those days.
Onii-chan...
I love you
Episode 2   On sale July 21st
Episode 3   On sale Sept 22nd
Episode 4   On sale Nov 24th..