Going home so late?
It's dangerous out in the dark!
Should we escort you home?
You're the ones in danger.
You can't get a girlfriend, so you hang out here.
I know exactly what you're after.
If you know already, then we can cut the bullshit.
Move it.
No! Let go!
No!
Huh?
She's...
She's already wet!
Ow!
Hey, this guy knows how to fight!
Oriya... kun?
Kakyuusei 2 - Anthology
houkago no ame jitensha okiba
On a rainy day after school, by the bike racks,
anata o matte aiaigasa o yume miteru
I dream of meeting you and sharing an umbrella.
mune no kodou takanari sugite
My heart is pounding too loudly,
ame no oto mo kikoenai
So loudly that I can't hear the rain anymore.
douka zutto kono mama
I hope things stay this way forever.
jan jan jan doshaburi no
While bathing
paatii shawaa abinagara
In a really powerful party shower,
ran ran raran tte utaou
I sing, "La la la la."
mukai kaze mou kowakunai
I'm no longer afraid of the stormy winds.
sora no kanata ni nanairo no reinboo
Beyond that stormy sky is a beautiful rainbow.
Jeez.
What the hell were they thinking at school,
letting a girl walk home by herself at this hour?
I-I was the last to leave, so...
You'd better be more careful too.
Have someone wait and walk you home.
Or perhaps, take a route that's
better lit and more crowded.
Are you okay?
Did they hurt you?
They didn't do anything to me.
What about you?
Huh?
This...
I guess I cut it when I hit one of them.
Episode 2:
Bouvardia ~ Passion ~
Hey, you're going to too much trouble. Seriously.
But if your wound got infected,
you'd have to quit coming to practice,
and then it'd be like they defeated you.
I guess you're right.
Even if it's just a small wound,
you shouldn't take it lightly.
Okay.
All done.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
What are you doing?
O-Oh, no!
What were you thinking?
You really are just a stupid pervert.
O-Oriya-kun?
Wh-What are you...
I'd... better go.
B-Bye then.
I won't have it!
You were eating lunch with a student during class?
What in the world for?
Well Sawamura-sensei?
Yes?
O-Oriya-kun... was eating lunch...
so I went to watch and...
I-It just looked so yummy.
I was running late this morning
and skipped breakfast!
So I...
Before you think it's yummy
or feel like you're starving,
you'd better stop your students
from eating in your class.
Isn't that a teacher's duty!?
If you're running late, you slip in the hall and fall.
And while you're grading tests, you fall asleep.
And if you can't answer your students'
questions, you burst into tears!
Your student-teacher training ends in three days!
Why must you cause me so much trouble?
Stupid guidance councilor.
Spewing crap out of his mouth all the time.
Sensei?
I-I wonder... i-if I'm not cut out to be a teacher.
I'm not really sure why, but..
Sensei, I really like you.
Uh, I have to go... prepare for my next... class.
Sensei?
O-Oriya-kun.
Are you okay, Sensei?
Achoo!
You didn't catch a cold, I hope.
Nope, I'm fine.
Sorry, I'm such an airhead.
I had no idea it would start pouring that hard.
You could've run back to school at least.
You had an umbrella there, right?
Why were you getting soaked at that shop?
It's a mystery to me.
No matter what I do, I can't seem to commit.
I'm still such a child.
At this rate, I'll never be a good teacher.
Don't scold yourself like that.
You're doing your best.
Look at me. I got held back two years.
That's different.
And besides, you're not in the least childish.
You're pretty.
And also...
May I go take a shower?
I think I caught a chill.
Oh, no! What are you doing, Oriya-kun?
Y-Youre making me mad.
N-No, don't look at me.
It's embarrassing.
D-Don't.
Don't...
You can't be enjoying it, anyway.
My boobs are so small.
I am enjoying it.
You're cute.
I really like you, Sensei.
Rouma-kun.
Sensei...
Kazuki-san.
Suck it.
Suck it hard.
No!
Do it harder!
W-Wow!
This feels great!
I love it!
It's okay, Rouma-kun.
I want you to...
come in.
Rouma-kun?
But I don't have a condom.
That's all right.
Today is okay for me.
But still, I want you to be safe.
You're so sweet, Rouma-kun.
S-Sensei, I'm gonna cum.
Then cum.
Yummy.
Sen... sei...
Oh... Oh, no.
Not again.
You can't.
Not yet.
Sen... sei...
Kazuki-sensei...
I'm almost there.
Ryouma-kun.
You're so sweet.
Kickboxing Club
That's right!
Our relationship or friendship
has nothing to do with it.
It's just because I'm the manager.
So there's no problem!
Sup!
S-Sawa... mura... sensei?
Do you need something?
Uh! Well...
Whoa, it's cold out there.
Oh, Tama!
Huh?
Sawamura-sensei, what's up?
Here.
This is for the other day...
and sorry.
W-Wait a sec!
Nanase.
What?
I want to apologize too.
It was your first time, wasn't it?
I didn't consider that.
It was my first?
You're wrong.
But..
I haven't been able to get you
out of my mind since then.
And when it ended like that..
I tried to forget about you.
But I couldn't
It got more intense.
Your face... your body... your voice...
So I...
Thank you, Oriya-kun.
Oh, how rare.
It's a White Eve.
So I guess that's how it ends, Rouma-kun.
Now I feel like an idiot.
Nanase!
No!
Not like this!
Aw, just kidding!
Sorry about that.
You really are stupid and horny,
and a totally impossible guy!
But still, I... find you...
so...
Don't cry anymore.
I'm not sad.
I'm just happy.
What about you?
I'm not really that lovable.
What's so funny?
You think you're not lovable?
Ask this guy for a different opinion.
Rouma...
This is you, isn't it?
Nanase! Nanase!
More! More!
Rouma...
I'm coming in.
Rouma!
Don't worry.
It won't hurt.
It hurts!
Nanase?
No, hurry.
Make the pain go away.
Hey...
Rouma...
am I good?
Yeah.
Better than Tamaki?
Better than Sawamura-sensei?
Am I better?
Yeah.
You are.
You're wonderful.
Nanase, you're perfect!
Rouma...
Rouma.
What the hell am I doing here?
Where do you think you're touching, old fart!
Don't underestimate the strength
of a kickboxing club manager!
H-Huh?
It's here!
It came!
Do I smell good?
Yeah.
How do I taste?
Sweet sour... and milky...
Then can you lick me more?
Found it!
You can do whatever you want to me.
I want to belong only to you.
I wonder if I can do it?
Oh... Oh, no!
I'm close, Nanase.
Slash me open!
Shatter me to pieces! Mess me up!
Drown me!
Stick it in too far!
And then... And then...
Nanase...
We're one.
That's okay. You don't need to wash them.
I'll take them to the laundry tomorrow.
Tama
What's up?
Are you at home now?
Yeah, of course.
Can I come over right now?
R-Right now?
Is it a bad time?
Not really...
bad.
Nanase.
Rouma-kun!
Why are you out in the cold?
Oh, did you come out to meet me?
Y-Yeah.
Of course I did.
I'm sorry, but it turns out everything's okay.
It just started.
I-Is that what was wrong?
I had no idea.
But it's your fault.
So, can we make up now?
Of course not
Aw, don't say that!
nani yori taisetsu na jibun ni love
What's most important of all is to love yourself.
We'll get the chance!
nando demo atatteku dakedo
We get many chances in life,
sou seishun wa ichido dake
But our youth comes only once.
akiba darou ga harajuku darou ga
Whether it's Akiba or Harajuku,
yatteru kotaa zen'in issho sa
All teens are the same.
dasshu de kaette manga to geemu
They dash home and play video games and read manga.
aitsu to anoko no meeru shite
And send e-mails to their friends...
onnaji ichinichi ga naite bakari ja son da yo ne
But we can't spend all day crying. What a waste.
nani yori taisetsu na jibun ni love
What's most important of all is to love yourself.
We'll get the chance!
nando demo atatteku dakedo
We get many chances in life,
sou seishun wa ichido dake
But our youth comes only once.