Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:            EmptySoul
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                   Meiko
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:        Collectr
Timed & Typeset by:       EmptySoul
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Karaoke by:     EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Quality Control:         E_B & Calyrica
Encoded by:        Eternal_Blizzard
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
Chance Encounter in the Sea Breeze
This is so boring.
Tsuyoshi, summer vacation starts tomorrow. Have you made plans?
Nope.
I'll be spending my last summer vacation at Dogeza.
How does spending six hours a day studying at the library sound?
You've gotta be kidding me. You're not Shinji.
Thought so.
Anyway, listen.
I don't spend six hours at the library. I spend twelve.
Where'd he come from?
Dunno.
Both my mom and my cram school teacher say this summer is crucial.
He looks paler every time I see him.
That's lame. He won't get any kind of tan this summer.
Right?
Summer is all about the ocean!
Blue skies, puffy white clouds, youth, and girls in bikinis, of course!
That's true.
Speaking of that, I heard about a great job...
and because you're my best friend,
I'll let you have it. You should do it.
But I already work at Dogeza.
There are girls in bikinis everywhere. It's the best part-time job ever!
Sounds great.
But what about Master?
I'll talk to him.
I'll say you'll be absent for the whole summer.
You can't just-
I'll ask him to let me work in your place.
I get it!
It's because Minatsu-san is-
Huh?
I'll call you later.
Hey, Minoru!
Jeez.
He just wants to be around Minatsu-san.
Oh, well.
His idea didn't sound bad at all.
I can't wait to see those girls in bikinis.
Thanks for waiting.
ICE
Sea House
Seriously, reality bites.
Hey, part-timer!
This yakisoba is ready.
I'll dock your pay if you slack off!
Uh, right!
Thanks for waiting.
Hey, what about my beer?
Sorry, I'll bring it right now.
Hurry, hurry! Let's go!
Jeez.
Yakisoba's up!
Coming!
Just how is this supposed to be a good job? Damn it, Minoru.
It's full over there, so we'll have to settle for this place.
Hey, part-timer! New customers just arrived.
Go take their orders already!
Sure.
Sorry for the wait.
Um, what would you like?
Senpai?
Miyuki-chan.
Ai-chan!
Yamaguchi-senpai.
What are you two doing here?
Why are you here?
Can't you tell?
Taking a break from your job at the café?
Kind of.
It's summer, and summer is all about the beach.
You mean it's easy to pick up girls at the beach, right?
Yamaguchi-kun, here's some more yakisoba.
Coming.
The old man here is really strict.
Yamaguchi-kun!
Right, right, right! I'm coming now!
Oh, your order?
Strawberry ice.
Me too.
I never thought I'd meet Yamaguchi-senpai here.
He's so obvious.
Yakisoba's up!
Got it.
Here you go.
Yakisoba's up!
Another yakisoba!
Got it!
Senpai seems really busy, doesn't he?
Yeah.
Well, we have to get going.
Are you staying around here?
I can come hang out later, if I have time.
Really?
With all the bikini-clad girls around here, won't you be too distracted for that?
ICE
The only girls distracting me are right here. Besides, with this boss...
Well, well, sorry about that.
Do your best, Senpai.
Yamaguchi-kun!
Coming!
Here it comes!
All right! Take that!
You really came.
Hey, Ai-chan! Miyuki-chan!
Wait up!
Here it comes!
What was that?
Oh, no. It's so cold.
Knock it off already.
Take this! And that! And this!
No more.
I said enough already.
Here goes! Take this!
It's cold.
Hey now, that's not fair.
Take this!
Wait for us.
Senpai!
Ai-chan?
What's wrong?
Come quick! Miyuki-chan is...
You're kidding me, right?
You're a woman, so be quiet.
Exactly. I'm a woman.
Don't underestimate me!
It was just a little sand, quit your squawking.
Apologize!
You deaf?
That's right. I can't hear.
Who the hell do you think you are?
What was that?!
So what happened?
While I was putting lotion on Miyuki-chan's back...
I just met some hotties.
Where?
You'll see when we get there.
I've struck out all day so far.
That's it?
Yeah, and then they started arguing.
Jeez.
Why you..
Ouch!
Let go!
I don't think so.
I said, let me go!
This is bad.
You said you'll teach me a lesson, right?
I'll let you go if you apologize.
What?!
Miyuki-chan...
That's enough.
Senpai.
She's a girl, so knock it off already.
Who the hell are you?
This is none of your business!
This girl just happens to be a cute underclassman at my school.
Cute underclassman...
Isn't it a waste of time to be fighting out here anyway?
Please just let it go.
Senpai, you don't need to apologize!
They're the ones in the wrong!
Wh-What was that, you stinkin' brat?!
Cut it out!
Wh-What was that?!
Knock it off already.
Quit acting tough just because girls are watching.
S-Senpai.
Oh, no. It looks like there's a fight.
Jeez.
O-Ouch!
Damn it!
You wanna do it, asshole?
I wonder if they're fighting over that girl?
Probably.
Let's go.
Kakyuusei
Senpai.
Hey, asshole. We gonna do this or what?
It's not worth it.
If you want to hit me, then go for it.
What's this? Gonna chicken out now after acting so cool?
Why you...
Quit it.
M-Mayumi!
Akira, you guys have already lost.
And that guy is my classmate.
What?!
Mayumi, you're here with them?
Well, I'm not dating them. They work for me.
Thank goodness.
This girl seems to be pretty close to Yamaguchi-senpai.
Please forgive them, okay?
Thank you.
They aren't actually bad guys.
I suppose not.
Still, I'm surprised I ran into you here.
Yeah, quite a coincidence.
Still, I'm glad they turned out
to be your friends.
Did you come with those two?
No, I just work here, and I ran into them.
So which one is your girlfriend?
The one with the ponytail?
No way. They're underclassmen.
Underclassmen, upperclassmen. What does it matter?
The same goes for classmates.
Let's get going.
Already?
Traffic's gonna get bad soon.
See ya.
Let's have fun together next time.
Later!
Who was that, Senpai?
A classmate.
I see.
I owe her... and you.
I appreciate it.
You're being awfully nice.
In any case, didn't you take it too far?
That's right. If she hadn't helped, things could've turned out badly.
Maybe we should get going too.
Yeah.
We dragged him away from work and all.
W-Work!
Crap!
You're fired!
Come on, don't fall behind!
We'll be late for dinner!
Wait up, Onii-chan!
Hurry!
My summer is already over.
Damn.
Thanks.
Ouch!
Jeez, today just gets better and better.
Is something wrong?
You're...
You stepped on glass?
There's a lot of blood.
You'll be in trouble if it gets infected.
It's okay. I'll just spit on it.
That's no good!
If you don't treat it properly...
Wait here a minute.
U-Um...
Sorry it took me so long.
I borrowed this first aid kit from the beach counter.
I'll apply some disinfectant.
Thanks.
This will sting a little.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Just a little more. Bear with me.
Sorry about this.
I can't just ignore an injured person.
All done.
S-Say, what's your name?
Why do you want to know?
Um, why?
Anyway, you're all set.
Um, how can I thank you?
I'm fine.
You were the one fighting earlier, right?
I can't stand people who fight.
Mayumi.
It really was you, Tsuyoshi.
What are you doing here?
Fired?
Yeah. So I'm looking for a job again.
I feel responsible for you getting fired,
so I'll use my connections to help you get a good job.
Really?
You're a lifesaver.
In return...
you have to take me out
to do something fun.
You don't really need me.
Don't you have lots of people to go out with?
I want to have fun with you.
So what will it be? Want me to give you a referral or not?
Okay, okay. It's a promise.
We'll go have fun,
so please give me the referral.
Sure.
It's hot.
She's late.
Sorry. Were you waiting long?
About thirty minutes.
How about we go somewhere cooler?
So?
We have some options!
I knew you could do it, Mayumi-kun!
Let's see.
How about street advertising for a cabaret? It pays well.
Welcome, welcome!
We have amazing girls!
Welcome!
No way.
How about a host club job?
Tsuyo-pyon.
He's so handsome!
Um, how about something more suitable for a high school student.
I guess so.
Are you licensed to drive a scooter?
Yeah.
Then how about a delivery job?
Paper delivery is too early in the morning.
No, no, I mean flowers.
Flowers.
Flowers? You want me to be a florist?
No good?
How about farming? Mailroom worker? Anime color filler?
Those are careers, not part-time jobs.
Jeez, I went through all this trouble, and you just keep whining.
But...
All right. Flowers it is.
Hey, don't decide on your own like that.
You need to go there right now
for an interview.
Right now?
Get to it, flower boy.
Jeez... and this was supposed to be my last summer vacation too.
Flowers
Is anyone here?
I hope not. Then I can just leave.
Welcome!
Looking for flowers?
N-No. I'm here about work.
Cattleya
Sorry, I was in back.
Y-You're...
From before...
You're...
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
The first encounter was coincidence.
The second was abrupt.
Feelings toward a boy
begin to blossom quietly.
The initial hesitation.
The subsequent heartache.
Like a tiny flower changing color,
a girl's heart gradually begins to transform.
Kakyuusei, episode 6:
Gratitude for Gypsophila.
Gratitude for Gypsophila