Every Brand-new Day sukoshi
Every Brand-new Day moves a little bit.
Kakyuusei
Anime-Faith & Miyuki no Tamari
Every step by step umare kawaru
Every step by step gives rebirth.
Every Brand-new Day watashi rashiku
Every Brand-new Day be the way I am.
atarashiiku kyou ga hajimaru
A new today starts now.
Translator: Xiaozzfei
Timer: Kyubi_Fox
kuzure oshi souna kokuro
My heart seem to be collapsing.
awatete tsunagi tomete ku istumo
I always fix it nervously.
Editor: SpookyElecric
Karaoke: Kyubi_Fox, Kaze-kun, getfresh
nige dashi souna kotoba
The words run away from my mouth
Styles: Kaze-kun, getfresh
nando mo tsutae youto shiteru
that I always want to tell...
Typesetter: Kaze-kun
kimi ni
you.
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
That all my feeling, which is like a thread is
kimi ni tsunagatteiru
connecting me to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru merodei dakishimete
I embrace the melody that we heard everytime when the thread splits.
Quality Control: fuzion`
Every Brand-new Day sukoshi zutsu
Every Brand-new Day moves a little bit.
Every step by step toke hajimeta
Every step by step starts melting.
Every Brand-new Day be the way I am
sasaykana koi ga hajimaru
my little love is starting now.
#anime-faith@irc.chatspike.net
#miyuki-no-tamari@irc.chatspike.net
Mischievous Spring Breeze
Oh, crap!
It's the new semester, and I'm late already!
Hey, Tsuyoshi!
We're in the same class this semester.
Let's have fun again.
No way!
You're too cold, Tsuyoshi.
Wait for me!
Eh?
What happened?
See ya there!
Su-Sure.
What's wrong?
If you don't hurry, you'll be late.
But...
It looks like it can't get down.
Cats are good at jumping from high places.
But...
She sounds so scared.
I...
Here.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Come to me.
Ow!
Why you...
Come 'ere!
You know, you ruined my breakfast.
Geez.
Don't climb up there again.
Thank you,
Notes: "Senpai" is used to refer to someone more experienced. For example, an upperclassmen or an experienced co-worker.
Yamaguchi-senpai.
You know who I am?
Ah!
There's blood!
It's no big deal.
But if it gets infected...
All done.
The cat seems to like you.
What?
Ah, anyway...
What are we going to do with her?
What shall we do?
My, my...
Oh no!
We're gonna be late!
Let's run!
Yes!
Ouch...
Hi!
Tsuyoshi-kun...
It's the start of the semester and
you're on a date already?
Minatsu-san!
Good timing!
Ugh... I can't run anymore.
Whew.
I'm just in time.
Minatsu-san!
Tsuyoshi?
Why is that guy with Minatsu-san?!
You really saved us.
I'm really, really grateful!
Shall I take you to school everyday, then?
Really?
But you'll have to pay transportation fees.
Well then, when you come to work,
clean up the store for me, 'kay?
What?
Do I have to do that?
That's right.
You're so mean.
Morning, Miko-chan, Mizuho!
Tsuyoshi...
So you're not late today.
I hope it doesn't rain later.
Miko-chan!
Let's have a date next time.
Yes!
What's with the handkerchief?
What?
Oh... This...
It's a magic item so girls keep off me.
Eh?
Well...
I'll also do some magic too, okay?
Here.
We'll tie all of these, okay?
I think the magic will definitely work very well.
Eh?
Let's continue next time. I'm off!
Then...
I'll tie this for Mizuho.
Eh?
Next time, okay!
Both of them are awfully polite, huh?
So, this is the new classroom?
OH!!!
There's a lot of cute girls in here!
Oh my...
Shindou Reiko.
She's going to be a problem.
Hey! Hey!
Don't start flirting with the new girls already.
Oh!
There's a beauty right here too.
Idiot.
Ugh... I finally made it.
Hey, Minoru.
Be a little more punctual, won't you?
Shut up.
There are quite a few girls of your type in here.
I'm stuck with you two again.
I hope you don't pull the class average down once more.
W-W-W-What do you mean by that?!
Yeah, I wonder what that means...
Figure it out as a homework assignment.
Well, well.
This is your final year in high school.
I wish you all a fulfilling study and sports life.
We're pretty lucky to have Mitsuki-sensei
as homeroom teacher.
Don't tell me you're into older women?
It depends on the person.
You two, over there.
Don't waste your youth talking crap.
That's right.
Teacher!
Is it okay to use our youth for love?
If you can...
Though I hope you save some for studying.
So Tsuyoshi,
you'd better remember that well!
Why are you telling me that?!
Yamaguchi-senpai...
is in class C!
Hello!
Miyuki-chan!
The beautiful detective, Iijima Miyuki, appears!
You were behind me all this time?
More or less.
And so what are you doing here?
You have some moves there.
Umm... Well...
All the classrooms changed...
So...
You got lost?
Right!
That's right!
I understand.
You like Yamaguchi-senpai, right?
I...
No-Nothing like that.
I'm Satake Haruhiko of class 3-C.
I want to tell your eyes,
"I love you."
This hand will never forget the
warmth of your shoulders.
Of course, who would blame a girl
for running shyly from my beauty?
Ai, you really hate guys, huh?
You never talk to any of the guys in our class.
But you spoke to Yamaguchi-senpai this morning.
It's okay if it's senpai?
It's because there was a cat.
Ai...
Could it be that you really...
I'll tell you, don't get involved with him.
Rumor has it that he's been with many girls.
Oh, no!
I was supposed to go help the teacher!
Ai, we'll talk later, okay?
But...
I still...
What's this?
That must be a love letter.
Eh?
It's a new semester.
Someone is already confessing their love for you.
Geez, I'm so envious.
Stop it, Shinji.
What's with that look?
You'd better find somewhere quiet
to read that kinda thing.
Yes, yes.
Tsuyoshi-kun...
I wonder what he's up to~
For fans, by fans
Not for sale or rent
Tsuyoshi-san,
I really like you.
Today, at 5 PM,
I'll be waiting for you at the Uzukigidou Park.
Who could it be?
Tsuyoshi.
Mizuho?!
I... Ever since the entrance ceremony, I've liked you.
I don't want to be just friends anymore!
Mizuho.
Tsuyoshi.
Well...
N-No way.
Mayumi?
Could this letter be from her?
Today, I'll go out and have fun with you.
No way.
Mayumi wouldn't write a letter to express her feelings.
I can't help it, so I'll go out with you.
So...
Come give me the kiss of love.
No, no.
Definitely not.
Tsuyoshi-kun...
It's no good to keep secrets from your friends.
What's this?
Oh!!!
L-Love letter?!
Give it back!
– No way.
– Give it back!
Hey?
Oh, no!
Damn!
If anyone picks that up, that's it...
Excuse me...
Did you see a letter here somewhere?
N-Nothing at all.
It's you.
You are...
Ummm... You're Minamizato Ai from 2-A.
You...
Geez... You checked all the underclassmen girls' names?
Of course.
What we're looking for is his lov...
Argh! Bye!
What's wrong with you?
Don't tell me that you're gonna go after that girl!
How could I do that to a younger student?
With you, it's hard to say.
Don't tell me...
That girl was the one who wrote the letter.
What am I going to do?
I have to return this to Yamaguchi-senpai quickly.
Senpai's desk is...
What is up?
I... I just...
Ah!
I understand!
You made a mistake about the class room, right?
I do that too.
This one time in 2nd year...
I didn't even know until the teacher was calling roll.
I'm really wiped out today.
What's wrong?
Ai?
Mmm... Nothing.
Don't hide it from me. You're a bad liar!
If you don't tell me the truth, then I'll do this!
– Stop it!
– Like this, hurry and tell me.
– Miyuki-chan!
– Alright, alright!
– Like this, hurry and tell me.
Here.
I see.
How am I going to return it?
You're not honest, Ai.
Eh?
Ai, what you're really worried about is...
Who Yamaguchi-senpai's dating, right?
Take a step before you think.
This is what you need now, Ai.
If you don't take a step forward,
you'll never get anywhere.
But then again, it is Yamaguchi-senpai.
I don't really want you getting mixed up with him.
Thank you for waiting.
Minatsu-chan.
The next one is ready.
Okay!
Minatsu-san,
I'll help you.
Minoru-kun...
No matter how much you help, I won't pay you.
Notes: Coffee shop owners are typiclly addressed as "Master" in Japan.
You are really mean, Master.
I can't afford to to pay three people.
I'm counting on you, Tsuyoshi.
Master...
I'm going out for a while.
Hey!
You can't just leave all of a sudden!
Minoru will be happy to do the rest today.
Here!
What am I doing?
If you don't take a step forward,
you'll never get anywhere.
I made it.
Did I get the place wrong?
Who?
Ai-chan?
You don't really have to run.
So-Sorry.
I see...
Ai-chan, you were the one who wrote that letter.
What?
This...
I picked this up at school.
I didn't know how to return this...
Sorry.
What's going on?
An underclassman, huh.
Senpai.
Why...
at that time...
was I okay when senpai touched me?
Why?
How was the date?
She came.
She's absolutely cute!
You're lying!
This is the evidence.
What? Impossible!
Because I...
No...
Eh?
What do you mean?
You'd better tell me everything.
Minoru!
I wonder who senpai's date was...
tsukan de Oh! A!
Catch it. Oh! Ah!
sono te ni Sha! Sha!
By that hand. Sha! Sha!
himitsu no chikara
The secret power.
kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
I won't let my this feeling go away.
moshi anata ga
If you
kocchi mitara
look this side
ku-ru na shisen de madowasuno
I will attract by your cool glance.
Considerable
shai na egao
shy smiling face.
sotto misereba seikoune
Show him quietly is the successful way right.
yukkurimada yume wo tsumugitai
I still want to hold my dream inside of myself slowly.
tashikana mono hora chikakuni
The certain thing is very close to you.
to wo nobashite
Extend your hand.
tsukande Oh! A!
Catch it. Oh! Ah!
sono te ni Sha! Sha!
By that hand. Sha! Sha!
himitsu no chikara
The secret power.
jitto shiterarenai
I can't just stay in there.
ha-to ga odori dasuyo
My heart is going to dancing.
mayotte Wasa!
Hesitate Wasa!
koi shite Ya! A!
Fell in love. Ya! A!
naitari shitemo
Even I cry
kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
I won't let my this feeling go away.
Admiring him from a distance is enough.
That was just a coincidence.
For now, I can only wonder.
Surrounded by colorful cherry-blossoms,
a girl discovers the meaning of love.
Kakyuusei Ep. 2 - ~ Cherry-colored Heartbeat ~
Cherry-colored Heartbeat