Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:            EmptySoul
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                   Meiko
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:     Collectr
Timed & Typeset by:       EmptySoul
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Karaoke by:     EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Quality Control:             Xanth & Calyrica
Encoded by:        Eternal_Blizzard
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
Beyond the Rain Clouds
This isn't any good.
President, it looks like it's going to rain.
Shouldn't we head home?
I'm going to clean up first.
Go on ahead.
Gah! Why the heck did it
have to start raining?!
I give up.
It really came out of nowhere.
Ryouko-chan.
Yamaguchi-kun.
Stuck here too?
I guess so.
It's just a quick shower. It'll be over soon.
Ah...
Would you stop staring at me?
I told you to stop.
S-Sure.
Did you hear me?
Y-Yeah.
Jeez, you're such a child.
I need to hurry and change so I don't catch a cold.
Need any help?
Well, I can probably find something for you to help me with.
Right. Look to the side this time.
Close your eyes.
Like this?
That was perfect!
Huh? You took the picture already?
This is a digital camera, so the shutter is silent.
Deji turtles are similar to common slider turtles.
[Note: A pun; the word for a digital cameras is similar to a type of turtle.]
You're funny, Miko.
Bah! What a load of crap.
Okay. Next we'll do Miko-chan.
Look to the side and raise your chin a little.
That pose again?
Girls look sexy in side shots.
What an idiot.
Kanou-kun, want to have your picture taken?
No thanks.
Hey, now...
Tsuyoshi-kun, could you come to the Art Club room later?
Me?
Art Room
I'm here!
And what does the president of the Art Club want from me?
Will you model for me?
Model?
Do you know the statue of Apollo?
Apollo? What's that?
Apollo was the Greek god of the sun.
He represents the perfect image of man.
Wait, does that mean I'm your ideal type?
I feel so flattered.
I just asked you to model for me.
Don't hear what you want to hear.
Um...
I intend to put my next piece in an exhibit.
So you want to be an artist?
Yeah.
You could say it's my dream.
If you put it that way,
then I can't possibly refuse.
Really?
Models just have to stand still, right?
So where should we do it?
Come to my room tonight.
Huh? To your room?
Fresh breath. Check.
Come in.
Hey!
Shh!
So this is what an artists' room looks like.
Hey, have you brought guys here before to draw them?
No.
So you're saying I'm the first guy you've let into your room?
Undress.
Th-That's a little too
sudden, Ryoko-chan.
What are you talking about?
You're a model, so you're not supposed to wear clothes.
Huh? I-I did agree to model...
b-but you didn't say anything about being naked!
That's why we're here instead of the Art Club room.
You promised.
Hurry up and undress.
O-Okay.
I-I'm done.
Undress completely.
What?! Underpants too?!
Of course.
B-But...
A promise is a promise.
Ryouko-chan, are you sure I have to strip all the way?
Quit asking me the same thing.
Then you should strip too.
Huh? Me?
Why should I?
It's not fair if I'm the only one undressed.
Fine.
W-Wait! Ryouko-chan, that's far enough! Far enough...
Oh? Okay.
This isn't right.
Move your arm lower in back.
Stick out your chest.
Th-This is bad.
That should be good.
Not for me.
I can't stop looking.
This is really bad!
Crap!
Stop it. I told you not to move.
I'm not moving.
You can't stand still even this long?
You're such a child.
It's because I'm grown up that I can't stay still.
Th-This part of me isn't subject to my will.
Thanks for all your help.
It's such a strange thing.
A guy and girl doing something like this alone in a room.
Why am I undressed?
What are you talking about?
Oops! Watch out!
Ouch!
Kanou-san?
I just heard a loud noise.
Is everything okay?
Shizuka-sensei?
I'm fine. My easel just fell over.
Oh. Try to be more careful.
Right. Sorry about the noise.
Hey, move already.
Y-Yeah. Sorry.
So heavy...
Jeez, why are they making girls perform manual labor?
There's no point in worrying about it now.
I can't believe we had to do this in the middle of class.
So the Art Club does stuff like this, huh?
Ai, come have a look.
No!
Jeez, Miyuki-chan! That's indecent.
What do you mean, "indecent"?
This is art.
Pretty good body too.
M-Miyuki-chan, let's go already. The next class is about to start.
I feel as though I've seen this person somewhere.
That's right! Tsuyoshi-senpai.
No!
This painting looks just like him.
N-No way.
Look.
It doesn't look anything like him!
I bet it really is him.
Jeez, Miyuki-chan.
I'm leaving.
I'm just kidding.
Wait for me, Ai.
It's such a strange thing.
A guy and girl doing something like this alone in a room.
A guy and girl...
Kakyuusei
Tsuyoshi-kun.
Hey.
There's a small part that isn't quite right.
Can you please model for me in the Art Room for about ten minutes?
H-Hold on a second!
There's no way I'd be nude at school!
Just halfway, then.
Please.
I see. Just the top, right?
Well, I guess that would be okay.
Art Room
Hurry up, Ryoko-chan.
Just a little longer.
Bear with it.
What would someone say
if they saw us like this?
Be quiet. You're distracting me.
I feel a scoop coming.
Hey, Tsuyoshi-kun.
I wonder what it means
to be a guy or a girl.
Why are you asking me
that all of a sudden?
I guess you're right.
No point in thinking about it.
I wouldn't say there's no point.
Sorry.
Weirdo.
Hey. Good morning.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
This.
Huh?
Wh-What the heck is this?!
Hey, Mizuho, what is this?
It was on the bulletin board in the hallway.
Everyone's over there making a fuss about it.
Tsuyoshi-san, someone mean
must've done it.
Y-Yeah.
This isn't some kind of field trip.
It's not nice to take pictures of others without permission.
I-I suppose so.
I can't believe someone took this kind of picture of you.
You should be more careful.
H-Hold on a second.
You've got it all wrong.
How am I wrong?
It's true I was half-naked, but I wasn't doing something like this.
See, I knew it.
Um... well... you see... I can explain.
Not bad, Tsuyoshi.
You're after Kanou Ryoko.
Minoru!
How can you say that?!
This is a misunderstanding!
That's nice.
Anyway, Shizuka-sensei is looking for you.
She is?
Kanou was also called in,
so she probably wants to talk about the pictures on the bulletin board.
What?!
So you asked Tsuyoshi-san
to model for you?
That's right.
I think I believe you.
But you should avoid actions that can cause misunderstandings. Okay?
Having him model for me could cause a misunderstanding?
No, but it's a bit much to have a nude model of the opposite gender in a club room at school.
Well, you see...
I'm the one who suggested making it a nude painting.
You did?
That's right.
You hear about people taking nude pictures of themselves while they're young,
but getting a painting is a pretty rare opportunity.
I give up.
No, that's...
She only did it because I insisted.
I didn't expect it to cause such an uproar.
Personally I don't think there's a problem with a girl painting a nude guy,
but there are people who would see it as a serious issue.
Why did you say that?
Nobody would be surprised at anything I say, so I just wanted to get it over with quickly.
I don't like the faculty room.
He really is like a child.
Apparently that nude painting was Senpai after all.
I'm so surprised.
I feel sorry for him.
What? You feel sorry for him?
He was just modeling, and now everyone is thinking bad things about him.
He was nude! No clothes! Completely naked!
Would someone normally do that?
Listen, he's probably dating that girl.
Dating? You think so?
Otherwise he wouldn't do this.
That's why you need to
give up on him already.
Amazing, what kind of club is this Art Club anyway?
I'm sure they were doing
more than just painting.
If it isn't the infamous Tsuyoshi.
Your reputation among the girls has dropped.
Shut up! It's none of your business.
I guess you had a bad
reputation to begin with.
Satake-kun!
Satake-kun, last night you left this floppy disc in the computer room.
Sorry about that. Thanks for the help.
No problem. The editing was pretty simple.
We can talk about it later.
Anyway...
Shinji, what editing?
I knew it was Haruhiko!
That bastard!
Satake-kun asks me to do things like this for him all the time.
Like make pictures that look like him and a girl kissing,
or switch bodies for nude models.
Shinji, can I take a look at those?
Sure. I still have all the data.
Here.
An eye for an eye.
Ryoko-chan, those pictures were Haruhiko's doing.
He took them with a digital camera.
I don't care anymore. It doesn't matter.
P e r v e r t
This is messed up.
If people are going to be like this,
I don't want to continue.
I'm going to quit painting.
Wait, you can't be serious.
It's your dream, isn't it?
Ultimately, a dream is a dream.
I do the best I can to improve my skills,
but in the end, people just make a fuss over something like nudity.
I'm a fool.
Ryoko-chan...
It was silly of me to speak of art when I'm just a high school club-level painter.
So I can quit with no regrets.
Ryoko-chan...
Ryoko-chan, quit lying to yourself!
I'm not lying.
The other day when you were drawing me,
you took what I said seriously and got undressed without hesitation.
What's that have to do with it?
I was focused only on painting.
You think just anyone
can stay that focused?
You love painting so much that you lose sight of your surroundings.
Don't quit because of something
as trivial as this!
Don't say your paintings aren't art.
I don't know much about
painting and all, but...
No matter what anyone else says,
I know that you were working hard toward your dream.
If you quit now, your dream will have been for nothing.
Tsuyoshi-kun... you...
I'm going home.
Ryoko-chan.
Maybe I said too much.
I hope you'll be happy together!
What?
You were with Tsuyoshi-kun the other day.
I-I know people are saying bad things about you two, but...
I hope you'll be happy
with Tsuyoshi-senpai!
Why should the model and the painter be happy together?
But... um... he was naked, and...
Yamaguchi Tsuyoshi was just my model.
The motif of the piece was the male body. That's all.
The motif?
That's right.
For an artist, a nude body is just like a vase or a landscape.
A vase?
Yes. So my only relationship with him is through my art.
Understand?
S-Sure.
You see, I have my hands full with painting.
Exactly.
That's right. I can't quit painting.
I don't really get it, but...
I'm glad.
Nothing but a model for my art, huh...
P e r v e r t
I'm an artist.
I'll put my feelings into painting.
Tsuyoshi-kun, good morning.
Good m—
Ryoko-chan?
This is the first time I've run into you on the way to school.
That's just because you're usually late.
I was up late last night.
I overslept.
Really?
You oversleep too, huh?
You're gonna be late.
C'ya.
Tsuyoshi-kun, I'm not giving
up on my dream.
Really? Then that painting?
Wait up!
How...
So you have these kinds of hobbies, Haruhiko-kun?
You do things like this?
N-No... um...
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
In the summer sea, the salty breeze and sandy beaches play tricks.
The theater of youth.
In the heat of summer,
when the sun is stained red,
two youngsters have a fateful encounter that causes their hearts to flutter.
Kakyuusei Episode 05:
Chance Encounter in the Sea Breeze.
Chance Encounter in the Sea Breeze