Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:           Moho Kareshi
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                EmptySoul
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited & Typeset by:        Collectr
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Timed by:                EmptySoul
Karaoke by:            EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Calyrica &
Quality Control:      Eternal_Blizzard
Encoded by:          anonymous
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
Winter Stirs . . .
Morning!
Morning.
You're as popular as ever.
It's been like this every day since the cultural festival.
Well, that's because you're Miss Uzuki.
Even in the Track Club,
you're super popular.
It's been crazy because everyone's asking me to pass you love letters.
I hate this.
I know. Don't worry.
I turned them all down.
Thanks.
I wouldn't mind getting one from Senpai, though.
Did you think about what I asked you?
Huh?
About how I asked you out.
Remember now?
Oh, that.
No thank you. I must decline.
I must have heard you wrong.
Um, Haruhiko-san.
There's a tadpole on your hand.
A tadpole?
See?
Th-That's not important!
I think we're very compatible.
Compatible?
One, two, three...
U-Um...
Ah, I see.
Based on our names,
our compatibility is awful.
Th-That doesn't make any sense!
Tsuyoshi-san's the best match for me.
Yamaguchi!
Him again. He's ruining my love life!
Huh?
Miko-chan?
I've been waiting for you.
See ya.
H-Hey!
Don't ignore me!
What's up?
I-I'm sick of competing with you over girls!
I see.
You can have her.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't dumped.
It's a problem of compatibility.
Well, we are, but...
What happened?
Sounds like he got shot down!
Again?
Pathetic.
Where'd Yamaguchi go?!
No!
I have to focus.
Hey, Miyuki-chan!
Miyuki-chan!
A-Are you okay?
You're bleeding!
I'm fine.
It's just a scratch.
Miyuki-chan, are you all right?
Are you okay?
If I remember right, that's Iijima from the track club.
Wh-What's the big idea?!
I'm taking you to the nurse.
I'm fine.
I can go by myself.
No, it's my fault.
S-Stop!
This is embarrassing!
Just be quiet.
But I...
If he's so nice to me, I'll...
Damn him!
He's got Miko-chan, and he's going after an underclassman.
I won't let him get away with it.
Revenge time!
Hi!
Huh? Shizuka-sensei's not here?
Oh well.
Sit here.
I'll disinfect it.
Y-You don't have to.
It's no big deal!
Where's the first-aid kit?
He's overreacting.
Found it.
Looks painful.
I'll just be a minute.
Here we go.
This might sting a little.
It's fine.
Does it hurt?
I'm almost done. Just bear with it.
Sorry about this.
I distracted you in the middle of practice.
It's all right.
Imagine, I tripped because of something like that.
I'm just clumsy, that's all.
All done!
That should do it.
What, already?
Would you have preferred
that I wrapped it in a bandage?
Jeez, quit treating me like I'm a little kid!
Are you okay?
Miyuki-chan. I heard you go-
Ai-chan.
A-Ai!
This isn't-
I-I can't believe you'd...
No!
Ai! Wait!
It's not what it looks like!
It looks like this turned into something complicated.
Well, Miyuki can handle it.
I see.
Here's my chance.
Where'd she go?
Hurry!
Wait!
He wouldn't do that, would he?
Miyuki-chan's my best friend.
She wouldn't do that on purpose.
Yubikiri
Shrine
I should talk things through
with Miko-chan.
Miko-chan!
Huh?
She's sleeping?
Miko-chan.
I-It's me, Tsuyoshi.
Oh, good morning, Tsuyoshi-san.
Good morning? It's evening already.
Is it?
What's wrong?
The sweet potatoes are almost ready.
You're baking potatoes?
Wh-What is it?
Have you gone out with boys before?
Huh? I'm a guy, you know.
Oh, right.
What made you ask that?
I fell asleep wondering about what it would be like...
to go out with a boy.
I see.
Say, why don't you go out
with me for a day?
Okay.
I appreciate it.
O-Oh dear.
What's wrong?
Well, we have a day off tomorrow.
Would you like to go somewhere?
Sure. I look forward to it.
I'll meet you at the train
station at 11 tomorrow.
All right.
Are the sweet potatoes ready?
I'm looking forward to them.
You! Are you trying to seduce her again?
Father, I was asking him about things I don't understand.
Things you don't understand?
Yes, about going out with boys.
W-Well, I should be-
You seem too close with her.
Y-You too, Kamiyasma-san.
Take care, now.
Goodbye!
I wish he could have enjoyed the potatoes with us.
He seems quite shy.
He is.
Miko-chan!
Good morning.
Morning.
You're here early.
Yeah. I got here an hour ago.
That's way too early!
Well, let's go.
Okay!
Where should we go?
I'm so excited.
Is that...
Those two...
Kakyuusei
Everyone looks like ants.
First time on a Ferris wheel?
Yes.
I've never been to
an amusement park before.
N-Never?
I'm surprised your father let you come.
Yeah! I didn't tell him it was a date.
I'm a bad girl.
D-Don't say that.
What was that?
Miko-chan?
It's all right now.
U-Um...
You're hurting my shoulders.
Sorry!
I didn't mean to.
No, it's all right.
Thanks for helping me.
See you at the finish line!
Wait for me.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Hello.
Is Senpai going out with her?
Senpai...
What's wrong with me?
Hi, Miyuki-kun.
Training on a Sunday?
S-Satake-senpai?
You know me? I'm honored,
Iijima Miyuki-kun.
Say, this year's Miss Uzuki is your friend, isn't she?
You mean Ai?
Yes. I heard a rumor that she's going out with Yamaguchi.
Is it true?
Th-They... go to the same school. That's all.
What am I saying?
I have to clear things up.
So Minamizato-kun has no feelings for him?
Maybe I should ask her out.
D-Do whatever you like.
I will. Thanks.
Having fun?
Yes.
But I'm a little...
Tired?
We ran around a lot.
Yes.
If we went out every day,
my body wouldn't be able to keep up.
Saying stuff like that will cause misunderstandings.
But I love you.
That's awfully forward. It's too soon.
I love Mizuho-san just as much.
Maybe I should ask her out next time.
G-Good idea.
I hope we can be friends forever.
Of course. That'd be wonderful.
Thanks.
Why did I say something so selfish?
Senpai's going out with someone else.
I did it for Ai.
Miyuki-chan.
A-Ai.
What's wrong?
I want to ask you something.
I have something to tell you as well.
What did you want to talk about, Ai?
Um...
Is it about yesterday?
That was an accident.
A-Accident?
Yeah. I tripped, and I fell
on him when I got up.
I wanted to explain, but you ran away.
But it was so sudden.
I thought you might...
Might what?
I thought you might like him too.
Don't be silly!
What are you thinking?
I got that vibe at the cultural festival.
No way.
Really?
What a relief.
I was worried over nothing.
I didn't want to cause trouble for you.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe I was jealous of you.
I'm a horrible friend.
Don't worry about it.
I started to hate myself.
No one likes themselves very much.
I think I'll ask him to go out with me.
Miko-chan, do you have a curfew?
Yes, 5pm.
What?! It's almost your curfew!
We should hurry.
Okay.
I can't deal with her dad.
Senpai.
A-Ai-chan.
Hello.
U-Um...
I took her to the amusement park.
We had lots of fun.
Are you going out?
Yes.
We're going out.
I see.
Would you like to go out with me?
You're a friend, just like Tsuyoshi-san.
If we all go out, I think
we'd have lots of fun.
When she says "going out,"
what she means is going out as friends.
As friends?
Yeah.
Not as sweethearts?
Nope.
Um, did I say something strange?
S-Sorry, I have an errand to run.
Sorry.
See ya!
Miyuki-chan!
Bye-bye!
Goodbye.
She didn't say that before.
What's wrong?
It's after five!
Oh dear.
Your dad'll be angry.
He'll be at the gate with his naginata.
H-His naginata?
You're late.
How dare you break your curfew?
What should we do?
I don't know what he'll do
when he sees you.
C-Could you do me a favor, Ai-chan?
Yes?
Could you tell him
you took Miko-chan out?
I can't deal with her dad.
Please.
All right.
But in return, could you do me a favor too?
Yeah. I'll do anything you want!
It's a promise!
Sure.
That okay with you?
Yes.
I went out with Ai-san.
Well, I'd better make myself scarce.
Miko-chan, Ai-chan, see you later.
Going out is a lot of work.
Senpai wasn't "going out" with her.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
White snow is falling.
Next Time
Her love deepens.
They confess their feelings.
Tears fall down their cheeks.
On Christmas Eve, the snow melts to rain.
Kakyuusei, episode 11: A Snowy Night.
A Snowy Night . . .