Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:            EmptySoul
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                   Meiko
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited by:     Collectr
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Timed & Typeset by:       EmptySoul
Karaoke by:     EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Quality Control:             Xanth & Calyrica
Encoded by:        Eternal_Blizzard
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
Trembling Cherry Blossoms
What's up with that guy?
He's holding a girl's handkerchief.
It's that guy.
You mean Yamaguchi Tsuyoshi, the one in all those rumors.
She's late.
I wonder what Ai-chan's doing.
I really should return this today.
No way.
Wh-Why is Yamaguchi-senpai...
Why is he standing there?
I... I can't go home.
What... What should I do?!
Now!
B-Bye!
Huh?
That was... Ai-chan, wasn't it?
Ai-chan!
Hey, wait up!
Can't you hear me?
It's me!
Why... Why is he following me?
Jeez. Why is she running away?
Why... Why is this happening?
Why do you start running when you see me?!
Stop.
Wh-What's wrong, Ai-chan?
I don't know.
Um, why are you chasing me?
Uh, because of this.
Here.
But that's...
I can't take it.
Huh? Why not?
Oh, my.
I wonder what they're doing.
Anyway, let's stand up.
What's wrong? You're acting strange.
S-Sorry.
I can stand up by myself, so...
Okay.
Here. I even washed it.
What? Y-You washed it too?
No way.
I live alone, so I'm used to doing laundry.
I had to do my laundry anyway.
No way.
So you washed the handkerchief along with your clothes.
I can't accept something like this.
Huh? That's mean.
You're saying that you can't use it anymore because I washed it with my stuff?
Th-That's not it!
I-It'd be a waste to give me something like this.
Huh? What did you say?
I'm trying to say that it doesn't belong to me anymore.
Please use it, Senpai.
Anyway, sorry!
H-Hey!
No!
This is terrible.
I'm sorry. And you just washed it too.
Oh, yeah! Will you come with me for a bit?
It's okay, isn't it?
His face is so close to me.
Come on. Let's go.
S-M-L Clothing
I'm glad we could find the same one.
Here.
B-But I...
I already bought it, so you should accept it.
Okay.
I don't want to bother you.
I'll gladly accept it.
This is the first present
I've received from a guy.
I'll treasure it.
Thanks a lot.
Anyway, I need to go. Goodbye.
She's really strange.
It's all right, though.
Yamaguchi-senpai...
Please accept this.
I couldn't sleep at all.
My heart was pounding.
What? Really?
It's really strange, though.
I can't remember much about yesterday.
Like what we talked about.
That's because you were nervous, right?
Even though I was able to go with him and buy the handkerchief...
She's that into him, huh?
Why not go on a date with him?
That's right! Tomorrow's Sunday.
How about I get him to take you on a date?
A date?
A-A date?!
Yeah. I'll ask him for you.
Wait, Miyuki-chan! You can't just suddenly jump to a date.
No way! Absolutely not!
You want to create some good memories, don't you?
Don't you?
But...
Looking good.
Knock it off.
You're creeping out the first-year girls.
What a mean thing to say.
We're helping them get used to the pressure of playing in front of an audience.
That sounds like bullshit.
You could say that.
Mizuho-kun, can I talk to you for a second?
Captain Satake.
When I saw you playing just now, it looked like your grip was a little loose.
How about I coach you a little?
Okay, Mizuho-kun?
S-Sure.
That jerk. I can't believe he gets to put his hands on Mizuho.
Well, it's her choice.
Let's go.
It's annoying.
Maybe I'll go grab a coffee to cheer myself up.
What are you going to do, Tsuyoshi?
I'll pass.
Also, if I show my face around Dogeza,
I'll be forced to work,
even though it's not my shift.
Okay. I'm gonna go.
Minatsu-san! I'm coming, so wait for me, all right?!
Jeez, that Minoru. He never learns.
Whoa! What was that?
Oh, nice.
Hey, Track Girl.
You should be more careful not to attract the wrong kind of attention.
Oh, sorry.
So the rumors were right.
What rumors do you mean?
It could mean a lot of things, Yamaguchi-senpai.
You know my name?
Am I that famous?
In many ways.
What do you mean?
Anyway, there's a really cute girl
who'd like to go on a date with you.
What? Really?!
She'll be waiting for you tomorrow at 1PM at Sekaiichi Park.
Can you make it?
Well, I'm a very busy guy and all,
but yeah, I'll go!
Right, then 1PM tomorrow.
Make sure you show up, okay?
Where have I met her before?
Class 2-B, Iijima Miyuki.
Blood type O. A Cancer.
Shinji, why do you know all that?
This is the information age.
Anyway, I'm off to cram school.
See you later.
G-Good luck.
What a useful guy.
Yubikiri Shrine
A date, huh?
I wonder what kind of girl it is.
She said "cute," though.
I can't wait.
Tsuyoshi!
Wait up, Tsuyoshi!
Cleaning your house?
Yeah. A famous Shinto priest is coming to see us next week.
Miko's dad fell and fractured his foot.
Oh, really? I'd like to help, but tomorrow I have a da-
I have some things to do.
Oh, really?
It's okay. Satake-kun said that he'd come to help out.
What?! You mean that jerk, Haruhiko?
Yeah. When I was talking about cleaning, he said he'd be glad to help out.
Satake-san is such a nice person, isn't he?
Damn that guy!
Miko-chan, I'll help clean too.
What? Really?
I thought you had stuff to do tomorrow.
Uh, well, that's in the afternoon, so...
Are you sure?
Okay, so tomorrow at 10AM.
Okay. Got it.
Thanks a lot, Tsuyoshi-san.
Leave it to me!
Kakyuusei
Huh?
H-Haruhiko!
You're late, Yamaguchi!
What time do you think it is?!
Jeez.
H-Haruhiko, you don't look so good.
I'm not used to carrying anything heavier than a tennis racket.
Seriously?
What are you doing?!
Go move the boxes already!
Okay, sorry about that, Father!
Who are you calling "Father"?
I don't recall being your father.
Get to work, so we can start on the next part.
Yes, sir!
Who are you?
Ah, um, Miko-chan asked me...
How dare you call my daughter by her name so informally?
I wont forgive you for acting
so friendly with her!
I'm gonna set you straight.
Miko, bring me the purification wand right now!
H-Hold on.
Yes, Father.
Ah, that's...
T-Tsuyoshi-san.
Wh-What's this?
It's a mop, Father.
M-Miko-chan...
Did you just call her Miko-chan?!
I-I mean, Kamiyama-san, I overslept.
Good morning.
Father, he's here to help out.
Hmph! All these guys are trying to get close to you.
S-Sorry.
Anyway, move these boxes to the room over there.
Uh, move?
All of them?!
That's what you're here for.
No way.
This?
It's a little plain.
Maybe this.
Actually, that's a little plain too.
Or maybe this.
Ah! Which one should I wear!
I can't decide.
What should I wear?
This is the one!
It's chapstick, but he might think it's lipstick.
Ai-chan.
Yamaguchi-senpai.
It's only our first date.
What am I thinking?
It's too soon for me.
I'm beat.
Me too.
This is all of it, right?
All right! I can still make it.
Good work.
M-Mizuho-san.
You two must've had a hard time, right?
No, not in the least.
I'd expect no less from a man.
Here.
That hit the spot!
My throat was getting pretty dry.
Well done, Mizuho-san.
Good timing.
Well, it's only gonna get tougher from here.
From here?
We're not done yet?
Thank goodness. I got here first.
It looks like I came a little too early.
Huh?!
I need you two to move all of this back into the main shrine.
We only moved it here so that Miku and the others could wash the floor.
You've gotta be kidding me.
You'd better get to work.
It's getting late.
This is really bad! My da-
All right.
What's wrong, Haruhiko?
Bathroom.
Senpai... I wonder what happened.
Oh, Tsuyoshi!
Sorry!
You're late. I need to punish you.
He's late.
That startled me.
He went home?!
Yeah, he told us that something came up.
And that from here on out,
one person would be enough.
Damn that Haruhiko.
I-I'm gonna be late for my date.
Tsuyoshi sure is strong, isn't he?
Make sure you don't overdo it.
I-I said to leave it to me.
Wait for me.
I'll definitely come, Blind Date-chan!
Senpai, I can't do it.
My heart aches.
Even if you came, I would surely... I would...
It's okay. It's me.
Miyuki-chan!
Why are you so surprised?
What a lousy guy.
I came to check up on you.
I didn't think I'd find you here alone.
I can't believe he stood you up!
He's really mean.
He'll pay for this! I'll make sure he does!
Why are you smiling?
Let's go.
Let's go, Miyuki-chan.
Jeez, you've gotta be kidding me.
I'm really late!
Damn it. It's already this late.
Nobody would wait for a guy who's late to a first date.
What's up? You've done nothing but sit there and sigh.
Leave me alone. I'm already beat.
Don't tell me you plan on
skipping out on work?
If possible, I'd like to.
That'd be a problem.
Hey, Tsuyoshi, there's a
cute girl looking at you.
Huh?
Ah, that's...
Oh, no!
Café
Dogeza
Sorry! I'm really, really sorry!
Café
Dogeza
Skipping out on a date. You're the worst!
Café
Dogeza
I'm so sorry.
Café
Dogeza
But even though I was late,
I did go to the park.
Café
Dogeza
And you think I'll forgive you
because of that?
Café
Dogeza
Can you imagine how a girl feels
if she's stood up on her first date?
So would you tell me the name of the girl?
What would you do if I told you?
Well, I'd go and make a proper apology.
No way. I don't want you
to hurt her any further.
Also, I'm a guy, so I kinda wonder what she's like and...
I'm really interested, and I can't let it go.
It's too late!
Stay away from Ai!
Did you just say Ai, Track Girl?
Don't tell me she's that Ai-chan? Minamizato Ai-chan?
It's her, isn't it?
I'm right, aren't I?
Like I said, it doesn't matter anymore.
Just stay away from Ai!
Got it?!
Café
Dogeza
W-Wait!
Fast... Just what I'd expect from a sprinter.
Oh? A member of the track team?
Such a nice physique.
She made my heart race.
What are you thinking, old man?
Hey, what's her name?
Iijima Miyuki.
I see. Miyuki-chan, huh?
My beautiful Miyuki-chan!
Introduce her to me.
Invite her to Dogeza, Tsuyoshi-kun.
Jeez. Another troublesome guy on my hands.
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Today I learned the joy of waiting for someone . . .
Thank you.
♥ Senpai
Thanks for not coming to the date, Senpai.
Because I still don't have the courage to look you in the eye when we talk.
That's why... That's why... until that day...
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling
Preview
New leaves begin to bud.
An early summer breeze carries the feelings of love.
A sudden date.
Two couples.
[Tickets: Field Athletics Stamp Rally]
Their feelings.
In the midst of an unfamiliar situation, casual kindness confuses a girl's heart.
Kakyuusei, episode 3:
Dream-filled New Leaves.
Dream-filled New Leaves