Military Uniform Virgin
Are you awake?
Yeah.
Jeez.
I hurried over here because I was worried that
you'd be hungry, but you were still in bed.
Breakfast is almost ready, so go wash
your face in the meantime.
H-Hey, wait a...
Before breakfast there's something else I wanna eat.
You.
Don't do that I'm holding a knife.
Hey, stop it, I said!
Oh, Rouma-kun.
But breakfast..
Breakfa...
Kakyuusei 2 - Anthology
houkago no ame jitensha okiba
On a rainy day after school, by the bike racks,
anata o matte aiaigasa o yume miteru
I dream of meeting you and sharing an umbrella.
mune no kodou takanari sugite
My heart is pounding too loudly,
ame no oto mo kikoenai
So loudly that I can't hear the rain anymore.
douka zutto kono mama
I hope things stay this way forever.
jan jan jan doshaburi no
While bathing
paatii shawaa abinagara
In a really powerful party shower,
ran ran raran tte utaou
I sing, "La la la la."
mukai kaze mou kowakunai
I'm no longer afraid of the stormy winds.
sora no kanata ni nanairo no reinboo
Beyond that stormy sky is a beautiful rainbow.
Raitsu Academy Senior Year
The Start of my 19th Summer...
Episode 1:
Toad Lily ~ Secret ~
You broke up!?
Oh? Didn't I tell you?
This is the first I've heard of it.
Ever since I started going out with you,
we haven't seen each other at all,
and we haven't spoken either.
I'm telling the truth.
I went through a lot with him, but it's all over now.
Really.
Now you have me all to yourself.
Hey...
Rouma-kun...
Shall we continue?
Sure.
Not yet!
This time... I want it from behind.
Y-You mean anal?
Yeah.
A-Are you sure?
As long as I'm with you, I can be as lewd as you want.
So please...
Tama...
Does it hurt?
I'm fine... I think.
Okay.
I'm coming in.
Ouch!
D-Don't... stop.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It hurts, but.. I'm okay.
Rouma-kun... do you like it?
It's so tight. You're squeezing me... out...
It feels like...
I'm being.... massaged...
from inside.
This is amazing! Tama...
It's a vacuum... a cyclone!
Yes! I think... this might... feel good.
I think I'm gonna cum. Can I?
N-Not yet!
F-For real?
Do it... from in front.
Rouma-kun, I want us to cum... together.
Okay!
Tama... Tama... I'm cumming!
Rouma... Rouma!
Rouma-kun!
Tama!
Ack! What's this?
Oh, shit!
I left that in you!
Which mean...
I don't believe it.
You said you'd never to cum inside of me!
You promised!
Maybe if you rinse it out in the shower...
It won't work!
Your shots are always way too powerful!
I felt it reach my cervix.
It might be too late.
I heard rinsing with cola works.
That's bullshit and you know it!
But it's okay, because we did anal.
I hear if you start off anal you won't get pregnant.
Jackass!
I don't want to see you or speak to you ever again!
It's over!
Kickboxing Club
"You're thirty minutes late.
And you say you're serious!?"
that's what she said.
"It's s not my fault. Somebody didn't wake
me up in time for homeroom."
...that's what he said.
"Since you're the only member of
this club, you'd better show up.
You're taking advantage of us club managers."
...that's what she said.
"If you're supposed to be my manager,
then find me some work already!
That reminds me, if you're bored, wash these for me."
...that's what he said.
Even professional cleaners wouldn't be able
to help this bio-hazardous pile of clothes.
Wash your own fucking clothes! Tell him that.
Shut the fuck up already!
It's not like I planned some
sex conspiracy against you!
Sounds like you kids are having fun.
T-Takato-san...
Today is the day you're supposed
to turn in your club forms.
You should've heard from your faculty
adviser about that already.
Didn't I mention that?
Takato-san, I'm sorry but without the club
president's permission, I can't proceed.
Are you sure?
Unless you turn them in today, you won't be
able to function as a club next semester.
I suggest you speak directly with President Oriya.
Sorry, Yuri-chan.
I've got work today.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Have a nice day.
Since tomorrow's Sunday, give me until Monday.
I don't know what's going on, but you'd
better get this done somehow.
Though it really makes no difference to me
whether you get your forms in on time.
I'll wait until Monday.
Be sure you're done by then.
Shit. I'm surrounded by bitches.
U-Umm...
Starting today, I have film work to do.
I was thinking you might want to come along.
Do you remember?
The first time I met you was in September,
the Toad Lilies were in bloom.
I picked up your wallet in the hallway, and...
Cut!
It wasn't his wallet, honey!
It was his cell phone strap.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you, Yuri-chan?
You're not yourself today. You're acting very strange.
Rouma-kun, you were very good.
But I suggest you talk to your girlfriend
more and look happier as you do.
Ready?
Action!
Do you remember?
The first time I met you...
Cut!
Rouma-kun, keep your eyes forward.
Don't look at me.
I can understand how you want to look at my
pretty face, but contain yourself for now.
After we're finished, you can admire my
beauty all you want. But for now...
Yuri-chan, what's wrong?
Is there something on your mind?
No, nothing's wrong.
I think I'm just tired.
I was thinking maybe what happened
in the club room got to you.
N-No, it didn't
I'd do... I'd do anything for Tamaki-senpai.
You don't need to worry about it.
Really? That's a relief.
But...
Watching the two of you fight makes
me think... I can't go on.
Okay, I'll try to patch things up.
Well, I'd like to say that..
but it's hopeless.
It's just not gonna happen.
But why?
Tama and I broke up.
She dumped me, actually.
Yuri-chan, I had no idea you cared
that much about our relationship.
It's not that at all.
I'm not sad.
I'm happy.
I'm overjoyed.
But you...
I'm a horrible girl.
I've always had my eyes on you.
When I saw you and Tamaki-senpai together,
you looked like the picture-perfect couple.
It made me wish that I too might meet
someone wonderful like you,
and have that kind of picture-perfect relationship.
But that wasn't possible.
When you two started arguing so
suddenly today, I felt strange.
My heart began to pound, and I wasn't sad at all.
And that's when I realized.
Deep down, smothered in my heart...
I'd wished that Tamaki-senpai would go away.
I wanted her out of the way.
Because if that happened,
I could have you all to myself.
I've always felt this way.
I'm a horrible girl, aren't I?
You must hate me,
when I'm like this.
Yuri-chan...
But I don't mind.
I don't care if you hate me.
I don't care if you despise me for life.
Just once, I want you to make love to me!
Senpai, I love you! I'm crazy about you!
Senpai...
Look at me.
Only at me.
I guess it is a little embarrassing.
Would you like to take a shower?
No, you can go first.
Then do you wanna bathe together?
I'm sorry. I'm not very strong.
Don't say that.
It feels good. Very good.
Really?
Okay. Then I'll keep it up.
Is this... because of me?
Does it scare you?
No, it doesn't.
Yuri-chan, let me wash you.
Oh, no!
Senpai! No!
Does that feel good?
Y-Yes, it feels good.
And we'd better clean down here too.
I feel like I'll lose my mind before I'm fully clean.
You're very pretty, Yuri-chan.
You look just like a porcelain doll.
Let me see.
Very beautiful.
No!
You're soaking wet.
I'm embarrassed.
Ready? I'm coming in.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
We can stop if you want.
N-No! Don't ever stop!
All right.
Senpai, how does it feel?
Do you like it?
Yes... It feels great.
Yuri-chan, you're wonderful.
I'm so happy!
So am I, Yuri!
Senpai! Rouma... senpai
Yuri... Yuri... Yuri...
Y-Yuri-chan?
Tamaki-senpai! Good morning.
So that's what's going on.
I just brought these things back for him.
I finally washed his boxing trunks.
I was sick of him nagging me about it.
See ya.
Tamaki-senpai! I hope you'll forgive Rouma-senpai!
But weren't you guys just...
It's okay. I don't mind.
It's just for today.
After today, I'll give him back to you.
No way, really? Are you telling the truth?
I can't believe it.
Aw, please cut it out.
Here.
Wow! I haven't had this much fun in a while.
What should we do next?
There's one more thing I want to ride.
What should we do tomorrow?
It's summer vacation. There are endless possibilities.
Yuri-chan, what's wrong? Are you tired?
Senpai...
I'm sorry!
You'll be on location for half a year, huh.
But you're leaving after today? That's really sudden.
I've known about it for a longtime.
I'm sorry. I wanted to tell you yesterday.
But then... you were so good to me.
I still wish you'd told me sooner.
But maybe... if you told me not to go...
But it's amazing!
A reporter for Date-TV?
It's a big opportunity for your career!
Senpai...
Don't overlook any opportunity!
That's the secret of winning.
The entertainment world is no
different from Kickboxing.
I'm happy for you, Yuri-chan!
Well I do admit your absence
will hurt the Kickboxing Club.
I know I'm gonna miss you too.
But you'll be back!
Six months will whiz by like that!
But my parents said that if I had
to miss six months of school,
I should study abroad.
I-I see...
Don't leave!
Don't leave.
Let's go around once more.
Just one more time.
Just one more?
For good luck.
And goodbye.
Yuri-chan...
I'm gonna cum.
Then cum.
Your hot...
Please release it in my mouth.
Not like that.
No!
No! No!
I don't want to leave you!
Senpai!
Do me a favor. Tie me up.
Please tie me up.
Tie me up so I can't go anywhere!
Yuri-chan...
I can't reach you. I can't touch you.
I can't see you.
I'm right here.
Senpai...
I want to... touch you.
I want... to see you.
It's so pretty.
How's this? Do you see the stars?
I can't see the stars.
I can only see you! I can only see you!
I...
Senpai...
I'm going to cum!
Good. Let's cum together!
I see stars inside of my head!
I'm... I'm... I'm becoming a star!
So I guess that's it.
I'm alone now.
Tama
Kickboxing Club: Second Semester Plans
The party you have dialed cannot be reached.
What the hell! Why won't he answer me?
nani yori taisetsu na jibun ni love
What's most important of all is to love yourself.
We'll get the chance!
nando demo atatteku dakedo
We get many chances in life,
sou seishun wa ichido dake
But our youth comes only once.
akiba darou ga harajuku darou ga
Whether it's Akiba or Harajuku,
yatteru kotaa zen'in issho sa
All teens are the same.
dasshu de kaette manga to geemu
They dash home and play video games and read manga.
aitsu to anoko no meeru shite
And send e-mails to their friends...
onnaji ichinichi ga naite bakari ja son da yo ne
But we can't spend all day crying. What a waste.
nani yori taisetsu na jibun ni love
What's most important of all is to love yourself.
We'll get the chance!
nando demo atatteku dakedo
We get many chances in life,
sou seishun wa ichido dake
But our youth comes only once.