Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Kakyuusei
_
C1Anime Presents
Every step-by-step umare kawaru
Every step-by-step 生まれ変わる
Every step by step, I'm reborn.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku atarashiku
Every brand-new day 私らしく新しく
Every brand-new day, being true to myself,
kyou ga hajimaru
今日がはじまる
I start the day.
Translated by:           Moho Kareshi
kuzure ochisou na kokoro
崩れ落ちそうなココロ
Always rushing to prevent
Translation Check:                EmptySoul
awatete tsunagi tometeru itsumo
あわててつなぎ止めてるいつも
these hearts from crumbling.
Edited & Typeset by:        Collectr
nigedashisou na kotoba
逃げ出しそうな言葉
These words that attempt escaping
Timed by:                EmptySoul
Karaoke by:            EmptySoul
nando mo tsutaeyou to shiteru kimi ni
何度も伝えようとしてるキミに
try again and again to reach your ears.
Calyrica &
Quality Control:      Eternal_Blizzard
Encoded by:          anonymous
kimochi no ito ga zenbu
気持ちの糸が全部
The threads of my feelings
kimi ni tsunagatte iru
キミに繋がっている
all connect to you.
hajikareru tabi ni kikoeru
弾かれる度に聴こえる
When I hear a snapping thread,
melody dakishimete
メロディ抱きしめて
I tightly embrace its melody.
Every brand-new day sukoshi zutsu
Every brand-new day 少しずつ
Every brand-new day, little by little.
Every step-by-step toke hajimeta
Every step-by-step 溶け始めた
Every step by step, I begin to melt.
Every brand-new day watashi rashiku sasayaka na
Every brand-new day 私らしくささやかな
Every brand-new day, being true to myself, this delicate love
Come visit us at #C1Anime@irc.rizon.net
koi ga hajimaru
恋がはじまる
begins to bloom.
A Snowy Night . . .
Knitting for Beginners
I'll do it tomorrow.
It's freezing!
Y-Yamaguchi-senpai!
We need to talk!
A-Ai-chan?
So... anyway... what's this about?
Is that promise you made still good?
Promise?
You said you'd do anything I asked.
Oh, that.
Of course it is.
Then... I have a request!
Please go on a date with me
on Christmas Eve!
Yeah, okay.
Th-Thank you so much!
I didn't have any plans,
so I was wondering what I'd do.
Senpai.
I really appreciate it.
No biggie.
Huh?
Ai-chan?
I said it.
I actually said it!
When did I...
Miyuki-chan?
Ai?
What's wrong?
You look depressed.
I'm fine.
Wanna come to my place
for Christmas again?
Sorry.
W-Well...
I'm going on a date with Senpai.
So I can't this year.
That's wonderful!
You've become very mature.
What's wrong, Miyuki-chan?
Usually, you'd be very happy for me.
You shouldn't jump to conclusions.
I hope things go well for them!
I shouldn't get in their way.
Here.
You're training hard.
Th-Thanks.
Is your knee better?
It was just a scratch.
I thought you'd ask me
to take responsibility.
If I did, would you take responsibility?
Huh? What was that?
Nothing!
About Ai.
You're going on a date, right?
You heard?
Don't you dare back out.
I won't.
If you do, you'll hurt her feelings.
Miyuki, you've been acting weird lately.
I'm in the middle of practice.
Okay, okay.
Good luck, then.
Hi, Minamizato Ai-kun.
You're this year's Miss Uzuki.
I think you'd be perfect for me.
I'll get right to the point.
Ai-chan...
I want you to go out with me.
I...
Are you going out with someone?
N-Not right now, but...
But...
That's strange.
Iijima Miyuki-chan's your friend, isn't she?
I spoke with her about you.
You did?
Yes.
So Minamizato-san has no feelings for him?
Maybe I should ask her out.
D-Do whatever you like.
So I thought I'd ask you out.
No way. You're lying.
It's true.
Ask her yourself.
I was rude to be so direct.
We'll talk again.
I know.
I declined them for you.
Miyuki-chan.
Why?
Hello, Iijima speaking.
Oh, Ai?
What's up? It's late.
Sorry to bother you.
I don't mind.
What is it?
Um, why did you tell Satake that?
What do you mean?
Why did you tell him to do
whatever he liked?
Oh, sorry about that.
I didn't think he'd actually do it.
It's strange.
You've been acting strange lately.
How so?
You've recently stopped referring to Yamaguchi-senpai as that guy...
I-Is that so?
I thought you knew who I was talking about, and I didn't mean anything by it.
Really?
What are you trying to say?
It's nothing. Sorry.
Knitting for Beginners
Ai-chan, huh?
There you are.
Satake-senpai.
I looked everywhere for you.
Oh? You're in a foul mood.
Why did you talk to her?
Yamaguchi's going on a date with her, right?
You knew about them, didn't you?
You're so cruel.
Trapped between love and friendship.
What's your point?
Have things been going poorly between you and Ai-kun?
It's your fault.
Excuse me.
Miyuki-kun, what are you doing on Christmas Eve?
None of your business.
Would you like to have dinner with me?
No thank you.
It's just dinner.
Not a date or anything.
You can't forget about him, can you?
What are you talking about?!
If you won't have dinner with me,
then I'll give up.
D-Dinner...
Dinner... will be fine.
I'm not doing anything anyway.
Kakyuusei
Making a present for someone?
I wish I had a boyfriend.
He-He's not a boy...
Hey, wait!
It's almost Christmas. Do your best!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye.
I made a mistake!
Good. Almost there...
Shit! So close!
One more time.
I already went through 800 yen?!
I was hoping to get Ai-chan
a Christmas present.
Maybe I'm just a cheapskate.
But...
Please, Master!
No.
My dead grandfather made me promise not to pay my employees in advance.
Scrooge!
I don't feel like working.
You've never felt like working.
What's going on?
Minatsu-san!
I'm not lending you anything.
Th-That was quick.
You're too naive, boy.
Everyone's so stingy.
Minamizato
I wonder what Miyuki-chan's doing for Christmas. But...
Knitting for Beginners
Closing
Ceremony
Thanks, Minoru!
You're a lifesaver.
Just make sure you pay me back.
I will.
Go on. Miss Uzuki's waiting for you.
Hi. What's up?
Um, I was wondering
if you're still okay for today.
Of course.
I'll see you outside in front of the plaza at six, after I finish work.
Okay.
I'll be going now.
She could have anyone she wants.
Why'd she pick you?
What's wrong with that?
Everything.
I didn't ask her out.
That's the problem!
Were you waiting long?
Mom, look! It's so pretty!
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
I'm just glad you came.
Ai-chan.
Here.
I got you a present.
Thank you so much!
It's not very expensive.
Um, I got a present for you too.
Oh, thanks.
What is it?
Wow! A handmade scarf?!
Did you knit it?
Yes.
Um, can I open it?
Sure. Go ahead.
What a cute broach!
Huh?
You worked pretty hard.
It's a bit too long.
Thanks, Ai-chan.
No one's made one for me before.
It's perfect.
What's wrong?
It's too big.
A little.
It's a little long for one person, but it's perfect for two.
See?
It's so warm.
Let's have a fun Christmas.
Miyuki-kun. Miyuki-kun!
What's wrong? What are you thinking about?
It's nothing.
Never mind.
Whatever, then. It looks like
we'll have a white Christmas.
I'm leaving.
Why so soon?
I've found the perfect place
for us to go next.
Come on.
We arranged to meet here once,
but I stood you up.
It's all right.
Miyuki-chan tried to force you.
The cherry blossoms fell
like snow that day.
It feels like a hundred years ago.
I feel just like I did back then.
So...
it's hard to believe that we're here alone.
Let's keep walking.
Senpai!
I'm very awkward, and I can't do anything for myself,
and I'm not very good at talking to you.
But... But...
I like you!
Are you sure you really
want a guy like me?
I'm messy and short-tempered.
You're okay with that?
Yes.
But I'm not a fan of girls who cry easily.
I see.
So... don't cry anymore.
I won't.
That's the kind of girlfriend I want.
Girlfriend...
We'll spend Christmas Eve alone here.
A hotel?
I reserved their best room just for you.
Aren't you happy?
Is that...
You take me for an idiot?!
I'm leaving!
Goodbye!
That hurt!
She's so violent.
See ya.
Um, Yamaguchi-senpai.
Call me Tsuyoshi.
T-Tsuyoshi-senpai.
Um, I had fun today!
It was a wonderful Christmas Eve.
I guess.
I'd better go.
Take my umbrella.
Thanks.
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas.
Thank you, Tsuyoshi-san.
M-Miyuki?
Is that you, Miyuki?
You're soaking wet!
You'll catch a cold.
Are you crying?
Senpai!
Why? Why?
What happened, Miyuki?
I'm such an idiot.
I'm really stupid.
You see, I... like...
M-Miyuki!
Wake up!
Hey! You've got a terrible fever.
What on Earth happened to you?
Sorry, Senpai.
Sorry.
You... Don't tell me you...
Wake up!
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) himitsu no chikara
その手に (CATCH UP!) ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Moshi anata ga kocchi mitara
もしあなたがこっち見たら
If you look this way,
Ku-ru na shisen de madowasu no
クールな視線で惑わすの
I'll be puzzled by your casual glance.
Totteoki no shai na egao
とっておきのシャイな笑顔
That shy smile is just for you,
Sotto misereba seikou ne
そっと見せれば成功ね
so I want to show it to you in secret.
Yukkuri mada yume wo tsumugitai
ゆっくりまだ夢を紡ぎたい
I want to take my time continuing to spin this dream.
Tashika na mono hora chikaku ni
確かなものほら近くに
Something real is right next to you.
Te wo nobashite
手をのばして
Extend your hand.
Tsukande (GO UP!)
つかんで　(GO UP!)
Grab on! (GO UP!)
Sono te ni (CATCH UP!) Himitsu no chikara
その手に　(CATCH UP!)　ヒミツのちから
There's hidden power within this hand. (CATCH UP!)
Jitto shiterarenai ha-to ga odoridasu yo
じっとしてられないハートが踴り出すよ
I can't sit still. My heart is dancing.
Mayotte (WHAT'S UP?)
迷って　(WHAT'S UP?)
I hesitate. (WHAT'S UP?)
Koi shite (GET UP!) Naitari shite mo
恋して　(GET UP!)　泣いたりしても
I love, even if I cry, (GET UP!)
Kono omoi dake wa hanasanai
この思いだけは離さない
I can't let go of this feeling.
Preview
She thought falling in love was wrong.
Next Time
But she finally understood.
Her feelings for him came
like the moonlight.
Balanced between love and friendship,
her feelings waver.
Kakyusei, episode 12:
Wavering Winter Trees.
Wavering Winter Trees . . .