The girls who seek for a place to stay
are looking for their very own "gods".
They offer themselves to these fake "gods"
in exchange for aid and patronage.
Sana-chan in wait for a god
It's twitching...
There's no way that I can lick this...
What now? Or are you just gonna
be a good girl and go home?
Going back to that house is the last thing I'd do!
I'll do it!
I just have to lick it, right?
It reeks of a fishy stench!
Wait... This would be too much for me!
I see... It can't be helped if
this is too much for you.
I don't mind it either way.
You really are the worst!
Isn't the one who insisted to do it
only to end up bailing out the worse one here?
I never said that I'll quit!
Yuck... What's up with this taste?
You should at least get used to this
if you plan to keep seeking patronage.
Both the smell and taste are
gradually getting stronger...
His dick is too big!
How could I even lick or taste this thing?!
It's about time you gobble it up.
Huh?
He definitely won't let me stay over if I won't do this...
I-I'll do this.
I don't want my efforts so far to be wasted!
I-It's hitting... It's hitting the back of my throat!
H-How long will this have to go on?
My jaw will get dislocated!
My mouth will get torn off!
Oh, you're awake? Good morning!
What are you doing?
A morning greeting?
Why are you not even sure?
So this is why I had that weird dream.
Oh, what kind of dream?
I reminisced about our first night together, Sana.
It's been about two years already since then...
Oh!
Didn't you love it when I did this, Kei-san?
Here you go. Here's a sock that
you love, freshly taken off!
How is it? Feels good?
Why are you even wearing socks?
You said that you wanted to do it
while I'm wearing socks yesterday.
You really like doing these sort of stuff, right?
Keep that up!
Good job for being honest!
If I remember it right, this part feels good for him...
This round protrusion at the tip...
And its collar as well, they're both sensitive...
He's reacting the most when
I lick his nipples, after all.
He's still the same as before!
Wow, it's pulsating!
It looks like his dick is about to spurt in my socks!
It's okay, shoot it out.
Come!
You're coming!
You're shooting a lot in my sock!
My sock is all slimy now.
It's because you're so lewd, Kei-san.
You're off for today, right?
Yeah.
Then we'll be together through this whole day.
Yeah, together through and through.
Eggs, eggs... Yay!
Eggs, eggs... Yay, yay!
Sana, what are you doing?
Hmm? I'm making breakfast.
Of course, I can see that. I'm talking
about what you are wearing.
I thought that I should accentuate
my old "high school girl" appeal.
It's nothing more than a cosplay
when you wear that now.
Hey...
And here I thought that I'd please you,
who has a fetish for high school uniforms...
It's alright, I won't wear this anymore!
No more cosplay sex for us anymore!
Huh? Oh... Well...
I'm sorry for teasing you, please
don't get angry anymore.
Are you really sorry?
Yeah, you're cute no matter
how much time passes.
It can't be helped, then.
Alright, I forgive you.
Eat now instead, before the food gets cold.
We'll be going out afterwards, alright?
Okay.
Aah—!
Come on, here's your favorite sweet omelet!
Delicious?
Yeah.
One more. Aah—!
No, I can eat on my own...
Aah—!
Oh! Kei-san, you have a grain on your face.
Huh? No way...
Sana, that outfit...
Did you remember it?
Yeah, you were so lewd in the
dressing room back then.
Y-You didn't have to remember that part!
And aren't you the lewd one there, Kei-san?
No, that's not my point!
My bad... That's the outfit we
bought back then, right?
Yes!
I only have worn clothes that my
mother chose for me back then.
It was the first time I chose
clothes for myself at that time.
This one's my favorite, so I
made sure to wear this today!
Huh, Kei-kun!
Yuuka-san!
Yuuka!
Sana-chan is here as well!
It's been a while!
May I have a seat with you two?
O-Okay...
Pardon my intrusion.
It sure has been a while, though.
I'm glad to see that you're alright.
You too, Yuuka-san.
We couldn't contact you
anymore through "DiaFre"!
I already quit on "god-waiting".
Was that so?
Yes!
I'm working in a normal job nowadays.
Oh, however...
I guess having the two of us under
Kei-kun's care wasn't so bad at all.
Huh? B-Both of us?!
I think that he loved it when we were both
doing him at the same time every day.
Huh?! W-Well...
When I think about it, he seemed to love it...
Right!
I really think that it felt so good,
and I think that Kei-kun was pleased.
I have a thing for your body as well, Sana-chan.
Huh? Y-Yuuka-san?
You have such a very pretty skin, Sana-chan.
It's still the same as back then.
Th-That's not true at all.
S-Stop!
You're so cute, Sana-chan!
Your breasts are lovely, and you
have such a sexy figure too.
Yuuka-san, we're in a café!
What should I do? I can't resist her!
This is bad, and yet my body won't move!
If this goes on...
Then, how about the three
of us go somewhere else?
Oh, well... That's...
I-I need to go to the washroom!
Did I go overboard on teasing her?
You sure did.
Huh, but you never stopped me.
Were you hoping that we'll all go for it?
Not at all.
Then...
How about if it's only the two of us, in that toilet?
...like the old times.
She's giving me such a naughty look...
I'll take full responsibility and deal with your needs.
I-I'm sure that you haven't done
it with this hole yet, am I right?
You're the only one I'll only allow
to have this hole and my pussy!
You should take responsibility
by giving me lots of pleasure!
W-Wow! You're scraping my butt hole!
Y-You're squeezing me!
Yes, doesn't this feel great?
You feel it a lot more when I do it this way, right?
I can feel it!
I'll stroke it a lot inside my pussy
and empty your balls up to the last drop!
That would be too much!
Come on, shoot it out!
I want you to squirt it all in my pussy!
You have a splendid dick right here!
It's alright... Come, come!
I want us... to come at the same time!
Yes! This what I'm talking about!
Your semen feels so good!
How about it, want to go there with me?
No, I'm fine.
I already decided to stop doing stuff like that.
Because you already have Sana-chan?
Yeah.
I see! It can't be helped, then.
You've changed, Kei-kun.
You think so?
Yeah!
You never made a face like that before.
It must really be because of Sana-chan...
I still have work, so I'll be going.
O-Okay...
Bye-bye.
Huh, are you leaving already?
Yes, something came up at my job.
I see...
Sana-chan, I wish you all the best.
Should we get going?
You're amazing!
Sana, your insides are so hot,
it feels like I'll get burnt!
You're quite aroused already!
That's because I couldn't hold myself back
after Yuuka teased me!
Were you fingering yourself here earlier?
Th-That's not true, I never did such a thing!
Are you sure? You're already
soaking wet when we started!
I-I don't know about that!
No, you can't! Don't do that!
If you tease me there right now...
H-Hey... Stop moving!
S-Stop thrusting!
Pull it out for now! I'm begging you!
What's the matter?
Could it be that you need to piss?
Th-That's... G-Gosh!
Th-That's right, so stop moving!
Stop!
Is that so? You're just in time, then! I'll help you!
Wh-What do you mean by "just in time"?
I can't believe this is happening!
H-Hey, I really can't hold it in anymore!
Your piss has started to trickle down!
Th-That's because you keep on
thrusting deep inside me, Kei-san!
It's coming out! I'll spray my pee all over!
Same here, I'm about to burst!
I'll definitely come when he shoots it inside me—!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
You're scraping my insides!
This is bad!
If this goes on, I'll end up peeing in climax!
N-No!
I'm coming and peeing at the same time!
Th-This is bad!
No way, peeing feels good!
His hard thing is rubbing
deep against my insides!
My pussy... He's making a mess of my pussy!
It feels great!
I'm the one who knows you the best, after all!
Y-Yes!
W-Wow! You're amazing!
Make me come! Make me come!
Make me come a lot!
Where would you like me to come?
Inside! I like being creampied!
I love it!
I want to feel you the most,
so do it in my deepest parts!
Coming... I'm coming!
I'm gonna come from getting a creampie!
No way, stop shoving your face into my armpit!
No!
Th-That tickles! No way!
You have a sensitive body, Sana.
I-I don't know!
What a nice scent!
Wait... Stop sniffing me!
Your cock became harder than before!
You actually got aroused from my odor...
Kei-san, you pervert!
Wow! Your thing keeps on
moving a lot inside me!
You're wetter than usual.
Does the idea that we're doing it here arouse you?
I-I don't know!
Ahh... No way! I'm feeling it,
I'm starting to feel it!
N-No!
Stop moving that hard, or I won't
be able to keep my voice down!
Your insides feel the best, Sana!
Idiot!
Idiot, idiot... You idiot!
I look like an idiot!
Even being praised for such
a thing makes me happy!
No, if you keep shoving it
down there right now...
Your insides are squeezing me
so hard right now, Sana.
I-I'm telling you, we can't!
I'll really end up moaning!
Did that feel good for you?
Gosh! You went too far, Kei-san!
We're far from done, you know!
N-Not deep inside me! I'll end up losing it!
Don't you love being teased
deep inside your pussy?
I-I love it, but...
But... But my voice will end up...
No... Y-You can't!
I'm coming... Coming... Coming... Coming...
I'm coming already! I'm coming!
Yeah, I'll make you come!
No! You too, Kei-san! Come with me!
Shoot your semen inside my
pussy as we come together!
His cock is hitting me at an unusual spot!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
Kei-san's cock is gradually
turning me into a pervert!
I'm coming! It's yet another big one
coming! Coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming again!
Sana, I'm coming!
Do it! Shoot it in! Shoot your semen inside me!
I'm gonna come! Coming... Coming...
My pussy is coming!
It's coming out! It's coming out!
Deep in my pussy! It's all spurting deep inside!
W-Wow!
This is amazing!
It got totally dark now.
It was pretty crowded there.
But we're lucky to be just
in time for the discount sale.
I feel like you snuck something
unnecessary in there, though.
Are you gonna share some of it with me?
Do you like "bocchi" as well, Kei-san?
The brand naming sense is excellent, after all.
It implies that since you're alone when eating it and watching TV, your hands won't stop.
You're one sad man...
Hey!
But you have me now.
Let's eat "bocchi" together!
Okay.
But we'll be having supper first, okay?
What am I, a child?
I'm done cleaning the room.
Hey, Kei-san.
I wonder if I can stay over for tonight.
No... What I mean is I want to
stay here from now on!
Don't tell me that you ran away again—
It's alright, I already contacted my mom about this.
Ever since then, I got along well with
my mom. And it's all thanks to you.
Me too, I don't want to let go of you anymore.
Not after all we've been through.
Kei-san...
Kei-san, I love you so much!
Well, I already knew that.
Gosh, I don't want to hear that!
I want you to say your feelings upfront instead!
You're the only one I'll ever love... forever.
I got to hear way more blissful
words than I expected!
With that being said, I'll give you lots
of my special treatment for tonight!
You don't have to push yourself that far.
I'm not pushing myself!
I'm doing this because I want to!
I'll wash you up using my own body!
The smell gets more and more intense!
The tip got swollen.
I have to especially give this part more attention!
I can feel the heat from his cock as I lick it!
Get your ass over here.
I'll wash you too, Sana.
You keep on overflowing down here.
It's just like the "great flood".
I'll get drowned from your love juice, Sana!
Gosh, stop exaggerating stuff!
No way, he's licking me so much!
I-I was supposed to be the one
taking care of him, and yet...
I'll use my mouth-pussy to
stroke you down here a lot!
The scent of his cock is mind-numbing!
The tip of your cock keeps
squirting out some fluid.
It tastes so lewd!
Don't rub my clitoris!
Shoot your semen with all
your might into my mouth!
I'm coming!
Coming! I'm coming—!
I-If you lick me down there
so much, it'll end up swollen!
It smells great, it makes me feel horny!
Pervert!
Y-You're even licking me deep inside...
His tongue goes inside and swirls around!
It's messing up with my head!
It's so slippery and having spasms.
Damn! Your pussy is as naughty as always, Sana!
Gosh, can't you be more romantic
with your choice of words?
What are you saying?
Aren't you actually happy
when being called naughty?
There's no way that I am!
How about you, Kei-san?
Your cock is already so hard!
Of course, that's because I wanted
to feel Sana down here.
I'm putting it in.
I-It feels good!
I can feel the way your thing is moving inside me!
I can feel it!
My tits are gonna get crushed!
But it might be making me feel better because he's pressing me down with his weight!
Sana, you're so drenched!
Th-That's because...
...I can't make it stop dripping out!
Kei-san, you're moving way
more gently than usual.
Wanna have it harder?
Gosh, you're an idiot!
That's not what I meant.
You see...
Having it this way feels good to me.
It's like you're carefully wriggling
back and forth inside me.
Like this?
This really feels good!
Your pussy is squeezing
way more tightly tonight!
You can move like you always do
and shoot your semen inside me!
Having you shoot it inside me
will make me come as well!
Don't you love getting creampies, Sana?
You're saying stuff like that again!
But I love it!
I love having creampies so much!
Me too! I feel so happy whenever we do this, Sana!
S-Saying that doesn't make me happy at all!
But... But, I...
I love that part of you, Kei-san!
It's going up so deep! It's reaching my deepest parts!
I-It's reverberating deep
inside me in quick succession!
Wow... it's sucking me inside!
Is my body doing it involuntarily?
It's incredible! I can feel it!
I can feel it deep inside me!
So hot! It feels hot!
It feels so hot—!
H-Hey, bust your nuts!
What? What's happening?
I never talked like that before!
Sana!
Kei-san!
Are you awake?
Sana...
Kei-san...
I'm filled with so much happiness right now!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization