Please.. forgive me, I'll do whatever you say...
So, you finally understand, eh?
This lesson will teach you to behave..
..It'll be our little secret..
Please, I won't disobey you..
Good, you're being honest now...
This will be over when we reach the next station...
Oh by the way, this train won't be
making any stops.. Rest assured.
Special Express
X-Fap Presents
Adultery Train
Why are you giving this job to me?
Oh the Family's Fortune.. But wasn't it you
who said I should get on the train?
W-wha!?.. you're terrible!..
You knew about this from the start, didn't you!?
I thought something was fishy.
..Especially asking me to get on this train all of a sudden.
Yes, yes... I understand.
Jeez, what's up with this meeting?
Good Morning.
Seems like you're troubled with work, huh?
Ah! Good morning~!
Can you believe this Mr Conductor?
I've got to work at the next stop.
Dealing with Family's Fortune is quite troublesome.
It's always been like this..
I finally had a break, or so I thought.
Must be tough even for the staff.
By the way, is the new room to your liking?
Oh~ it's very comfortable!
The bed and cushion, and even using the shower!
But was it really okay? Letting me..
It'll be a secret.
Kaido-san.
Please.. it's almost time for the next stop.
Very well. Understood.
Thank you for your cooperation with the Mithishio Special Express.
The next departure will be at 8 o'clock.
Thank you for using the Mithishio Special Express.
Well then, good luck with your work.
He-he~ I'll bring you back a souvenir.
I'm terribly sorry.
But we cannot accept things like that.
Is that so? Such a pity...
But I'll go take a look at what's there..
Well, I'll be going now.
Okay, take care.
So, that's the manager..
I should give her a lesson on the train.
Please.. spare me..
At this rate, I can't work...
What are you saying? This is nothing,
Compared to what's coming...
Excuse me...
You're blocking the entrance, you know...
You two are crew members, aren't you?
Seriously, not even as much
as a greeting or thank you.
Miki-san, we a have a new guest.
Let's not make her wait...
What the hell are you doing?!
Laying your hands on a passenger?!
It doesn't matter..
Within this train, I permit everything.
Don't fuck with me?!
Doing something like th--
Well then, let's get started.
You should hurry as well, Miki-san.
As for you, I wonder how I'll train you...
Feeling numb? Can't you move yet?
Risa-san?
I did a little looking up on you,
turns out you've recently become a doctor.
How about we do a little experimenting here and there?
I'll have my way with those huge jugs of yours later.
What the fuck are you saying? Stop this now!
You're wrong in the head!
Likewise, you're mouth needs to be taught a lesson.
Seems like you're a bit uncomfortable.
Miki-san, are the preparations done?
Yes... but.. are we really gonna do this?
What was that? You're still saying crap like that...?
Maybe I should train you some more later?
I'm sorry! Forgive me..
Well, that's better.. Let's take a look there.
There's something I've been wondering about for a while;
"How far can a girl squirt?"
No.. even though I say squirt
I don't mean the lower hole, but the upper..
In other words, her pussy... What do you think?
..N-no way.. but that's..
That right, therefore I'm conducting an experiment..
Let us begin...
..N-no! Don't touch me.. P-please stop!
If you don't behave, I'll shock you again..
N-no.. Stop it..!
Oh! Looks like you haven't had a man before...
Now, this will be amusing.
We'll save this for later.
S-stop.. Let me go..
Be a good obedient girl now..
...T-that's impossible..
This place, we'll save for another time.
And here we have your other hole..
I-it hurts, it hurts! Stop...
You're doing fine,
just think of this as a house call.
You're a doctor so you should know, right?
W-what are you s-sayi-
That was easier than I expected...
What do you say we go with something thicker?
Yeah, this should do fine...
No way, there's absolutely no way it'll go in! It hu-
I guess that's enough for today.
We'll give her some time to expand...
Miki-san, I've got business at headquarters
so I'm leaving the rest to you.
You can handle it, right?
U-uh.. yes.
Ah, be sure you do her in the ass..
That pussy is still a virgin.. Take good care of her.
It hurts!
..S-stop...
It's rubbing against the vibrator in my pussy! It hurts..
My pussy... f-feels weird. My pussy!
Ah~, Please wait~! wait~!
Ah-ah-ah, I'm Back~
That was so close~ I didn't think I'd make it..
I couldn't agree more.
I never imagined you'd make it on departure time.
Hehe~ I'm so sorry~
Good Morning, Mithishio Special Express welcomes you and wishes you a safe trip.. Thank you
Oh, this voice..
Yes, she's my replacement for today.
I got concerned when you didn't show.
Oh that's right! Souvenirs! I got some after
work since they looked delicious!
No, but that would be troublesome for me.
Oh please~ I know you've told me,
but at least accept my feelings.
Besides, it's not everyday you get an apple
from an idol called Ringo. Funny isn't it~?
Ah, is that so? In that case I'll gladly accept it.. however..
I know it's a secret! Our little secret, right~?
So, how is it?
The train's vibration feels good, right?
We, the railroad workers are always riding this wave.
N-no more, I can't hold it! Kaido-san!
Ah, yes.. Now's a good time for Ringo-san.
I was a bit unsure about her.. However, once I grab her I know I'll get to see that expression of utmost despair.
N-n-no... Ah!
Oh, Miki-san? Couldn't hold it in again?
I guess it can't be helped, we'll start all over again.
Yes, we'll be arriving tomorrow morning
around 6:25. Ah.. Yes, understood..
Hey, that apple was great. It was delicious.
Ah~ Mr Conductor, is that so? I'm glad.
There's still a lot more.
Would you like to have some with me?
Ah- no, I've eaten enough.
By the way, Ringo-san..
Let me show my thanks..
Not many know about this area
and it isn't open to the public.
What is it?
The stars look pretty tonight, and the
rear compartment has a good view.
Really~?! Is it okay?
I'm so happy!.. Umm, but...
I know, of course. It'll be a secret.
We'll then, I'll get things ready..
Please wait a little.
Okay!
Wow~, it's so wide!
No special customers are using it,
so you'll be my company for today.
You're right I can clearly see the stars.
Thank you, Mr Conductor.
Not at all, but my work doesn't stop here...
Huh?
Oh, awake already?
Just like that...
Keep acting like you're a lost little girl.
Stop it! Please stop! Why?!
Please be quiet...
Why.. why are you doing this.. Mr Conductor?
You shouldn't trust people so easily.
Oh, so these are the
two magnificent tits of an idol..
S-stop it..
I wonder what this part looks like?
No more please.. Stop it.. I'm begging you.
Even this looks pretty.
No, no.. Stop..
It hurts!
Ah, well excuse me..
However, we're carrying on..
It hur-!
You're doing rather well.
Look, even your panties are slowly sinking in..
S-stop.. Don't push anymore.. I can't take it..
There we go, it's all in now..
Noooo...
What are you saying?
You're already overflowing.
Can't you tell?
Had enough already?
Let's see what happens..
Here it comes.
No stop... My insides feel weird..
So, How was it, Ringo-san?
Soiling your underwear in such a manner..
Such a wonderful expression.
Now, let's carry on.
No! O-ow.. Let me go...
Now take this into your mouth..
No!
That won't do... Here, spread those lips open...
Such a thing...is impossible.
Making it wet was for your own good,
but I guess it can't be helped.
Please stop..
Absolutely not... We're just getting started.
Tell me, which hole would you prefer I fuck first?
Your pussy? Your ass?
I-I don't want such a thing... Stop it...
Saying that crap again..
I guess I'll have the leftovers then..
How's that? This is a penis..
I'll make sure you remember this shape and feeling well..
Hu- It hurts!
Sto- Stop!
If you don't loosen up a little, it'll hurt more..
That's right, it's much better isn't it?
Now we've finally become so intimate.
I'm gonna come soon.
No-no-no.. Not inside.. Please!
That would be a hassle,
I'm just gonna fill you up good instead.
Or maybe I should have fucked your ass?
N-No not that.. !
Maybe you'd rather do it with your mouth then?
I'm almost there, if you don't hurry
I'll shoot it inside!
I'm coming!
No! Wait!
Well done.. We'll stop here for now..
And then.. Again tomorrow..
Thank you for riding with us, we will setting off in ten minutes.. Please bear with us until then. Thank you
Translator: BlessedR
Raw Provider: Mydoom
Timers: Fukkii / Snatch
TLC: Alist1
www.ExtremeFap.wordpress.com