Please forgive me... I'll listen to you...
Finally you understand.
You are the vice train conductor here.
Don't make me tell you so many times.
I won't... I won't disobey you anymore...
It's great to hear you being obedient.
This is all going to be over when we reach the next station.
Oh by the way, you will never be able to get off this train.
Why did you put me on shift today?
Wasn't it supposed to be my day off?
You told me to enjoy myself on this train.
W-What? You're terrible!
You knew about this from the start, didn't you!?
I thought something was fishy.
Especially when you told me to get on this specific train.
Yes, yes... I understand.
Jeez, I wonder why they told me to meet up at the destination.
Good Morning.
Seems like you're having trouble with work, huh?
Oh, good morning!
Can you believe this Mr Conductor?
I've got to work at the next stop.
It's so troublesome since they told
me that it was my day off today.
It's always been like this...
It's so disappointing because I thought
I finally got the chance to rest.
Working with the entertainment industry must be a hassle.
By the way, how is your new room?
It's so comfortable here!
The bed and cushion are so fluffy, and
I can shower for as long as I like!
But was it really okay? It seems like
I'm the only one treated specially.
It'll be our little secret.
Mr. Kaidoh...
It's almost time for the next stop.
Yes, understood.
Thank you for riding with the Michishio Special Express.
The next departure be tomorrow morning at 8 o'clock.
Please be careful not to miss our train.
Well then, good luck with your work.
Thank you! I'll bring you back a souvenir.
I'm terribly sorry to say this...
But we are not allowed to accept things from passengers.
Oh really... That's disappointing...
But I'll go take a look at what's there.
Well then, I better leave now.
Take care.
So, that's her manager.
I would really love to welcome her on to the train.
Please... spare me...
I can't work... like this...
What are you saying? This is nothing.
Compared to what's coming...
Excuse me...
Can you not block the entrance?
Aren't you guys crew members?
Seriously, not even a greeting?
Ms. Miki. That is out new "customer".
Let's not make her wait.
What the hell are you doing?!
Laying your hands on a passenger?
It doesn't matter.
I am permitted to do anything on this train.
Are you fucking serious?
You're not going to get away with.
Well then, Let's get started.
You should hurry up as well, Ms. Miki.
I wonder what I should do to you.
How does it feel to have your body numb
and not be able to do anything?
Ms. Risa Yotsuhashi.
From what I've researched you're
working as a doctor, aren't you?
How about we do a little bit of experimenting?
I'll have leave those huge breasts of yours for later.
What the fuck are you saying? Stop this now!
Are you stupid?
It seems like your mouth needs to be taught a lesson.
I feel offended.
Ms. Miki, are the preparations done?
Yes... but are we really gonna do this?
What? You're still saying stupid things like that?
Do you want to be trained again?
I'm sorry! Please forgive me...
Well, that's better... Just watch us from there.
There's something I've been wondering about for a while.
How much can a women's sexual organ expand?
No... when I mean "sexual organ", I don't
mean the lower hole, but the upper...
In other words, her urethra... What do you think?
No way... but that's...
That's why I'm conducting the experiment.
Let us begin...
No! Don't touch me... Please stop!
If you don't behave, I'll shock you again.
No way... Stop it!
Oh wow! Looks like you've never had a man before...
This will be amusing.
We'll save this for later.
Stop it... Let me go.
Be obedient.
That's impossible...
This, we will save for another time.
And here we have your urethra.
It hurts! Stop...
You're doing fine. Just think of it being a urethral catheter.
You're a doctor so you should know, right?
What are you s-saying.
That was easier than I expected.
What do you say we go with something thicker?
Let's see... Taking this for an example.
No way, there's absolutely no way that it'll go in...
No... it hurts!
I guess that's enough for today.
Let's expand this little by little next time.
Ms. Miki, I've got business at the headquarters.
I'm leaving the rest of the work to you.
You can handle it, right?
Yes, sir!
Ah, be sure you do her in the ass
and keep her vagina's virginity.
Take good care of her.
I can't handle anymore of this...
Stop it.
It's rubbing against the vibrator in my urethra! It hurts.
My urethra... my urethra!
Please wait! Waaaiiittt!
Ah-ah-ah, I'm... I'm back...
That was so close! I didn't think I'd make it.
I couldn't agree more.
Sadly a train conductor has
no rights to change the train time.
Hehe, I'm so sorry.
Good morning, Michishio Special Express welcomes
you and wishes you a safe trip. Thank you.
Oh, this voice...
Yes, she's my replacement for today. I
got concerned when you didn't show.
Oh that's right! Souvenirs! I got some after
work since they looked delicious!
No, but that would be troublesome for me.
Oh please... I know you've told me,
but at least accept my feelings?
Notice: Ringo means apple in japanese.
Besides, it's special for an idol called Ringo Nakamori.
Funny isn't it?
Ah, is that so? In that case.
I'll gladly accept it... however...
I know it's a secret! Our little secret! Am I right?
How is it?
The train's vibration feels good, right?
We, the railroad workers are always riding this wave.
I, I can't hold it anymore! I'm going to start squirt!! Mr. Kaidoh!
Ah, yes... Now's probably a good time for Miss. Ringo.
I was a bit unsure about her.
But now that she trusts me a lot, I'll get to see her
expression of utmost despair if I "catch" her now.
No, no.
Oh, Ms. Miki? Couldn't hold it in again?
I guess it can't be helped, we're going
to have to start all over again.
Yes, we'll be arriving tomorrow morning at 06:25.
Yes, understood.
Hey, that apple was great. It was delicious.
Mr Conductor, is that so? I'm glad.
There's still a lot more.
Would you like to have some more with me?
It's fine... I've eaten enough.
By the way, Ms. Ringo, could you
let me show my thanks to you?
This area has no lights from towns or
anything, and it's very sunny today.
What do you mean?
The stars will definitely look pretty tonight,
and the rear compartment has a good view.
Really? You'd let me in there? I'm so happy!
Umm, but...
I know, of course. It'll be our little secret.
We'll then, I'll get things ready.
Please wait a little.
Okay!
Wow, it's so wide!
No special customers are using it, so
you'll be my company for today.
You're right! The stars are beautiful!
Thank you, Mr Conductor.
Not at all, but my work doesn't stop here...
Huh?
Oh, awake already?
I was thinking whether I should do you already.
Stop it! PLease stop! Why?!
Please be quiet...
Why... why are you doing this, Mr Conductor?
You shouldn't trust people so easily.
Oh wow. I thought idols play around
a lot. But these are amazing.
Please stop this!
I wonder what this part looks like?
No more please. Stop it... I'm begging you.
This must be beautiful.
No, no... Stop.
It hurts!
Ah, well excuse me... But let us continue.
It hurt!
You're doing rather well.
Look, even your panties are slowly sinking in.
S-stop... Don't push it in anymore...
I can't handle this much...
There we go, it's all in now.
Noooo...
What are you saying? You're already overflowing.
Can't you tell?
Had enough already?
Let's see what happens... if I do this, and look.
Here it comes.
No stop... My insides feel weird.
So, how was it, Ms. Ringo?
Giving your "first time" to your underwear...
Such a wonderful expression...
Now, let's carry on.
No! Please... Let me go...
Now take this into your mouth.
No!
That won't do... Here, spread those lips open...
I, I... can't...
Making this wet was for your own good,
but I guess it can't be helped.
Please stop... I beg you...
Absolutely not... We're just getting started.
Tell me, which hole would you prefer
I fuck first? Your pussy? Or your ass?
I-I don't want such a thing... Stop it.
Saying that crap again... I guess I have no choice.
How does this feel? This is a penis... Make sure
you remember this shape and feeling well.
Stop... it hurts...
Stop!
Stop...
If you don't loosen up a little, it'll hurt more.
That's right, it's much better isn't it?
Now we've finally become so intimate.
I'm going to cum soon.
No, no, no... Not inside... Please... not there!
That would be a hassle,
I'm really want to fill you up good instead.
Or maybe I should just fuck your ass?
No... that's terrible.
Maybe you'd rather do it with your mouth then?
I'm almost there, if you don't hurry
I'll shoot it inside!
I'm cumming!
No! Wait! Please!
Well done...
We'll stop here for now.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you for riding with us.
Due to maintenance, the express train
will be stopping for ten minutes.
Please bear with us until then. Thank you.
Translator: thepinkunicorn123
Editor: MetaZ
Timing: MrMew
Please visit us at:
www.hentaicloud.com/oppaisubs