What happened?
Huh? Oh, thank god!
Excuse me, may I ask for help?
Sure.
If it's something that I can help with.
Is there anything wrong?
I want to go to this room, but I can't seem to find it.
I'm sorry to say this, but this ticket is for the cart in front.
However, this car is special, and does not allow
passengers to walk through to other carts.
Really? I see...
But, my friends are already in the room.
What should I do?
How about I escort you to a new
seat, better yet, a private room?
But, I don't have money for private rooms.
No, you don't have to pay for this.
It is our fault for not being able to escort
you to the right room in the first place.
You don't have to do that.
You don't have to mind.
How about this room?
Its so pretty!
Please use this room freely until the next stop.
Are you sure I can really stay in this room?
Of course.
Do you like it?
Yes, I like it a lot.
Mr. Kaidoh, do you have a moment?
It's about my next shift...
Yes, I'll be there.
I'll excuse myself then.
If there's anything else, please call me.
It's our new customer, Ms. Miki, please
prepare for the welcoming.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for taking our train.
Passengers changing trains, please make sure
you do not leave your luggage on the train.
However, due to the maintenance for the special train,
the train will only start to run tomorrow after 16:40.
Passengers who will be staying outside, please don't be late.
Oh, excuse me.
Good afternoon. I am Oogimachi, your railway investigator.
May I ask some questions?
What is your name?
Yes, I am Kaidoh, the train conductor.
I'd be glad to help you.
Thank you very much.
I've heard rumors about young women
"disappearing" on this train.
Really? I've never heard about that.
Well, it is probably just a rumor, but...
Apparently, a fansite of an idol stopped being
updated since the idol got on this train.
And there are people spreading rumors
about how maybe she got kidnapped.
Rumors... huh?
Well, this isn't an official investigation.
It's just that I got interested.
These rumors about our special train isn't good
for our reputation. Let me help you with it.
Thank you for your help.
But I don't know much about this train.
Let me introduce to Ms. Imasato.
She's the vice train conductor.
My name is Shoko Oogimachi. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
You already understand, right?
This time, I'm going to make you do the work.
But, shes the train investigator.
It's okay. The "top" will do something about it for us.
Yes?
How are things going?
Mr. Train Conductor! It was very relaxing
here. Thank you so much!
Nono, I'm sorry for having to caused you trouble.
Would you like any cold drinks?
Really? May I?
Of course, you are our valuable customer.
Let me give you some extra service.
Ok then, thank you!
Do you play any musical instruments?
Yes! But this is my friends. I am just the vocalist.
But my friend Orie, I have not been able to get
in contact with them since a while back.
Do you by any chance know anything about it?
Yes, when I checked the room you initially
booked, she was peacefully sleeping.
Oh, when she sleeps she never wakes up.
I guess I was worried for nothing then.
Huh, I can't... move... my body!
What happened?
Miss, are you okay?
Are you going to go to sleep just like your friend?
You can't stay like this.
Ties are just so annoying.
Your shirt's gonna be all wrinkled!
Let me take off you underwear.
Isn't this just relieving.
How are you Miss...
I mean, Miss. Yume Shimizu.
I hear no answer.
This is not good... hmmm... let me give you a massage.
I'm actually very good at it.
How is it?
Let me help you with down there.
Is even this not helping?
Then I guess I'll have to do it from the inside.
So...
I wonder if this is too big?
If you use too much power there, the cup is going to break.
Yes... Just like that...
Yes... Relax even more...
Please rest now, Miss. Yume Shimizu.
Any weird changes recently?
I'm sorry. I don't know.
It seems like the usual.
Do you know the idol called Ringo Nanafuri?
Other than her, there is Risa Yotsuhashi,
who is a doctor. Have you seen her?
Both should have been on this train.
Even the last time when this train ran...
I'm sorry. This is my first time on this
train. Here is the special cart.
What is this room?
Is it a room for an event or something?
Excuse me, can you please turn on the lights?
Ms. Miki?
How do you feel? Was this too early for you?
It... hurts...
I can't stay like this...
It's okay.
This level shouldn't be a problem. Stay like this for a while.
So...
Good morning. You seem to have slept well.
Being the railway investigator seems hard, huh?
You!
Yes?
I am Seiji Kaidoh, the train conductor of this train.
And I am also the representative of this "service".
I domesticate beautiful women who come to this
train, and send them to "specific" customers.
This is the other reason for this train to exist.
Are you Ringo?
I can't handle this anymore... Its getting more
and more into... ah... It's going to break...
Please forgive me! I won't be unwilling to do
it with my asshole anymore... please...
I don't mind, but you're gonna have
to clean the inside before doing so.
I... I can't...
It's coming... Noo...
Take... Take it off... please...
Both of you, please resist it until I finish here.
Now it is your turn.
It's going to be hard the first time,
but you will soon get used to it...
Put me down... you... you... assh...
You're such an aggressive girl... and also very beautiful...
It's making me feel hot.
This time... hmm... lets's see... I'll use this.
Please be obedient.
No...
Stop... it...
Don't move, stay still.
This is a very delicate area, so stay still.
Only this moment of "fun" is my privilege.
I've got to enjoy your face filled with despair.
No, not there... ah.
This is a nice view.
You! I'm the railway investigator!!
Do you really think you can get away with this?
There is no problem. All of that has already been solved.
Especially because there is no railway
investigator called Shoko Oogimachi.
Exactly...
Do you get it now?
There are clients who have "power"
to do these things so easily.
You should learn from now on.
Now lets continue what we were doing.
Starting from... here.
You have got to stop this.
You can't...
Sto...
It's gonna cut through...
It's also very interesting when you still have it in...
You better not move. Or your important part will cut.
I don't want... tha...
It's all fine. I've cut it very nicely.
Now if I do this.
Look what I got.
What are you going to... do?
It's okay, this is still quite thing.
Oh look what's happening... I haven't even
started doing anything. Don't get excited.
No... this isn't...
Here you go, exactly what you wanted.
No...
It's touching the "deep" inside me...
Oh you still don't understand, do you?
It would go even deeper!
Don't put it in that deep!
It cannot be helped... Let me be "nicer" to you then.
More... more... More! Morrreee!!!
Wh... why?
Isn't this satisfying?
You seem to be more greedy for sex that I thought you were.
This will make you feel a lot better.
The end of this will grow longer and shorter.
That... hurry... up... put... that... in...
I shall start.
How is it? Isn't this so satisfying?
It feel soooo gooood!!
I'm cumming!!
Do you understand now? It seems like
you are really into these things.
Yes... exactly what you... said...
Good girl.
Sometime in the near future, I will
let you have mine inside you.
Th... Thank you... so... much... ahhh...
This is just wonderful!
It seems like we're gonna get good quality things this time.
Especially with this many beautiful girls.
All we need is some more... younger girls...
I probably should get back to doing my "normal" work.
Since I don't want to go through trouble, everyone,
please stay like that for a while more.
Thank you for riding this train for a long period of time.
The next stop is...
Translator: thepinkunicorn123
Editor: MetaZ
Timing: MrMew
Please visit us at:
www.hentaicloud.com/oppaisubs