The brainwashing of Lieri Bishop and Naomi
Evans is proceeding as planned.
When night falls onboard this ship, their minds switch off,
and they become my willing slaves.
Of course, they remember nothing in the morning.
Repeating this procedure daily, we exploit
and humiliate them without mercy...
raping their bodies, as well as their minds.
By the time we reach Earth in two days,
their original personalities will have been erased...
their lives overturned.
But Captain, there's something that concerns me.
We've detected a weak signal coming from their room.
It might be some kind of code.
No matter.
Everything will go as I've planned...
as long as we aren't found out too soon.
Yes, sir.
On second thought Lutz...
Sir?
I see.
Oh, I get it now.
Captain?
I understand exactly what's going on here.
Victory is ours for the taking!
Kangoku Senkan
Vol.04: Hell's End
takaku ni sobieru sono akari de
In that light that rises high,
te rashite hoshii no umi no panorama wo
the sea of stars forms a panorama.
kurayami ga shimesu ai no yukue
In the dark that shows love's whereabouts,
mado no mukou no futari no georama yo
two people outside the window form a georama.
yubi ga tsutaeru kokoro no furue
My fingers show the trembling of my heart.
tokoshie sae negaeba kanashimi no hate
Wishing forever just brings ultimate sadness.
anata wo tsurete hikanaide kono mama
I'm taking you along, don't pull me back.
kokoro hayaru kagen no tsuki
As the waning moon calms your heart,
ashita wo koko ni kuzusanaide ima wa
don't let our future be destroyed.
yume wo miseru ai no na wa idea
A love that brings dreams is called an "idea".
Amazing. Master, your cock is so big and hard.
I want it in my mouth. Can I put Master's cock in my mouth now?
If that's what you want.
Watch me suck it, Master.
That's not fair. Naomi, you can't have it all to yourself.
If you can't get me off, I'll have Lieri take over.
Yes.
Master, please kiss my mouth-pussy.
Master, do you like kissing my cocksucker?
Don't you like my tongue better? My tits?
No way. Master likes me. I'm going to make him burst.
Master, your cock is filling my mouth.
It's filling up my whole throat.
If you're ready, cum in my mouth.
What a complete degenerate you are.
I'm a degenerate. Just sucking Master's
cock makes me feel like cumming!
Oh, Master, you had a big load to shoot, didn't you?
Lieri, too. Lieri wants some cum, too.
Master, make me your sperm bank.
Master's cum is... so delicious.
Look at her go.
Master, fill my cocksucker with more jizz.
Pump more hot fucksauce down my throat.
He's cumming in her mouth again.
Master, aren't I the best?
Out of the way, Naomi.
Give Lieri some cum, too, please.
Fill my mouth with it.
Look... Look at all the cum in my mouth!
I can taste your pre-cum, Master.
You sick, perverted sow.
Master, cum for me.
Fucking pig. You like this punishment, huh?
I love it! More! Fuck my mouth!
Here it comes. Get ready for it.
Gimme some! Give it to me, Master!
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
So much. You came so hard.
I want some on my face, too.
And to think these two wanted me dead yesterday.
It's just as you suspected, Captain.
The women were setting us up for an ambush by the New Solar Fleet.
Silly bitches.
Using themselves as bait to trap us. Can you believe it?
Captain, this is dangerous. We should stop them.
Negative.
That would give us away to the New Solars.
This is an opportunity to turn the tables on them.
The incident happened just after 1500 hours the next day.
Piloting remote gun turtles, the women tore through the ship,
mowing down any crew members who stood in their way.
And then they stormed the bridge.
Cease all resistance and come with us.
Do that, and maybe I'll spare your life.
You... You!
What have you done to us?
And how?
What an outrageous offense, Commander.
Keep this up, and you're cruising for a court-martial.
What are you laughing at?
In one hour, we'll rendezvous with our assault force.
There's no escape for you now.
Cooperate if you don't want any further beatings.
All right. I'll cooperate. I give you my word.
I know there's something fishy going on aboard this ship.
There's a section just below us that's cloaked against our scanners.
Brilliant. Hats off to you for figuring that out.
We're getting to the bottom of this.
What is this?
This is our brainwashing laboratory.
B-Brainwashing?
The Neo Terras have learned the art of mind control.
Impossible!
It worked on both of you.
Huh?
You don't remember coming here every day?
What are you saying?
No way. You mean we've already been brainwashed?
The complete process takes time.
So we've been doing it gradually, switching back and forth...
between your old and new personalities.
What the hell?
The switch can be triggered in many ways.
For example, by the simulation of nightfall aboard the ship.
Naomi! Activate the gun turtle! Destroy the ship's systems!
Lieri-sama?
Just do it. If you don't, we'll be...
Too late!
Disregard that last order, Naomi.
Yes, sir. Order disregarded.
Lieri, cancel your rendezvous with the fleet.
Tell them you have everything under control here.
Roger that, sir.
That's how we brilliantly ended their final resistance.
Yes! Good!
Fuck us!
We're slut-pigs! Give us your hot cum!
Get us pregnant! Give us your babies!
Cum inside us!
We want our Master's cum in our pussies!
I want your jizz! Give me a mouthful!
I want it in my mouth, too!
Oh God, I'm cumming!
Fucking sow.
Yes! I'm cumming... I'm cumming too!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I can't take it!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
These women are no longer who they were.
The Lieri and Naomi who once hated me so...
are dead now.
Wakey, wakey, Lieri and Naomi.
You two are looking good.
Bastard!
Your brainwashing is complete.
I don't feel brainwashed.
When we remove the control device from your scalp,
your original personality will be completely
replaced by the one we've designed.
You mean we'll be erased?
Your old selves only exist in the form of
electronic signals from those devices.
But... we're right here!
They don't get it!
Your bodies are just parasites to your new personalities.
Laugh while you can. You'll pay for this!
I promise, I'll send you to hell myself.
That's right. You're all dead men.
Gentlemen. We have two distinguished guests.
Rouse every crew member to greet them!
Yes, sir!
I'm going to enjoy this, Lieri-sama. I've been waiting for it.
Listen to her voice. You can tell she wants it.
In your dreams, creep.
Lieutenant Colonel Bishop isn't satisfied. She needs more stimulation.
Roger that.
Don't touch me, you scum.
Found your weak spot. Get ready for it.
Hey, check it out! What a reaction!
Look at that. She's horny, all right. Fucking great!
She's dripping.
I'm cumming...
Let's get it started!
Nasty bitch. We'll punish you good.
Yeah, baby, yeah! This bitch is hot!
It's coming... It's coming!
No! I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
No more!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
No! No more!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again! No!
You filth! One day you'll pay for thi...
You don't realize the predicament you're in, do you?
No more! Please, no more!
You like being whipped, don't you? Don't you?
You dirty slut!
Fucking whore!
No!
Take that!
Look at her jiggle! I fucking love it!
I'm cumming!
Stop it! I can't... hold it... anymore!
Aw, yeah! Suck it!
I'm gonna... gonna cum!
How do you like that, bitch?
This mouth is better than a pussy!
Seriously? Let me have a turn!
I'm gonna paint you white with cum.
I'm gonna cum!
Now it's my turn!
Swallow my pole.
Holy shit, here it comes!
Damn, that was the greatest.
Come on!
Fuck, man. How many men's cum is this?
This is fucking heaven!
I'm cumming!
Swallow it all, slut!
I've never seen so much jizz.
No more, please!
Her skin's so smooth.
What a rush!
I'm filling her up!
Beautiful. A true miracle of science.
Come on! Gotta keep it going, men!
Vibrators engaged.
This bitch is going to cum again.
I'm gonna blow my load.
Oh, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Look at how she quivers.
Let's pump her full of goo! Here it comes again!
All right, get them up.
Get up.
Well, what do you think, pigs? Enjoying yourselves?
You finally ran out of fight, huh?
You never should have messed with me four years ago!
Revenge is sweet.
Four years ago?
What?
What? You don't remember?
No. What are you talking about?
Unbelievable.
Four years of bad blood, and they don't even remember me?
Are you saying... we've met before? I had no idea.
That was the end of Lieri Bishop and Naomi Evans.
I'll do anything! Anything! Just fuck me!
Oh, yes. You're cumming inside me!
My pussy's... going to split apart!
Harder. More! Pound my hole!
So good! Fuck my pussy!
Cum for us! Give us all of your hot cum!
I'm cumming.
More! I want more!
Finally, after all this time, a taste of victory.
Delicious, indeed, but it'll take more to satisfy me.
This is Neo Terras Battleship Jasant.
We've entered orbit. Please respond.
Welcome to Earth. You are cleared to approach.
Oh?
This is a pleasant welcome.
There will be a grand ceremony.
Lieri-sama and I insisted on it.
Really?
You'll be heralded as a hero for delivering us safely.
And now, by marrying one of these women, I'll
gain access to the New Solars' inner circles.
My dream is becoming reality.
And some day, the New Solars... the Neo Terras... everything... will be mine!