Does that feel good?
S-Splendid!
It's my pleasure to relieve you.
Watch carefully, Major.
You can ejaculate at your leisure.
Use the appropriate language, Commander Lieri.
Yes, sir.
Please dump your backed-up cum on me.
Good. You're just a pig-whore. Remember that.
Yes, sir.
Are you always such an energetic cocksucker?
Captain!
That's private, not part of my comfort duties.
Now then, suck the jizz out of my subordinate.
So this is how you clean off a man's dick cheese!
Is that right, Lieri?
Don't embarrass me!
Answer!
Yes. This is how I clean it.
God!
This pig-whore sure loves cock!
Yes, I love cock. I can't get enough.
Please, give me your cum!
I'm cumming!
Get ready for it, pig-whore!
There's so much...
cum shooting out!
Now it's your turn, Naomi.
Aren't you going to do your job?
What's wrong, Naomi?
As comfort officers, it's our duty to provide release for the crew.
All right.
Pardon me. I'll do it.
That won't do, Naomi.
If a New Solar woman can't fulfill her comfort duties, it looks bad.
Move your head faster. Clean the scum off that cock.
Good, Naomi. Now for the main event.
Move your tongue around.
Seal your lips, and take it long and deep.
No, like this!
Here, suck it!
Swallow it, no matter how uncomfortable you feel.
Into your throat. Deeply. Deeply!
Here it comes.
He's going to cum in your mouth!
Take it all!
Wait! Keep it in your throat.
Slowly take it in.
Admirable effort.
Goodness, that was a lot.
You should've swallowed.
That was a big load.
This cock is so hot!
It's so...
I'm putting it in my pussy.
Faster, Commander Lieri!
Wait, it's huge.
Everything all right, Commander?
It's getting easier.
Really?
– No need to worry.
– Lieri-sama...
See, Naomi? This is how we comfort officers
using our vaginas to further diplomacy.
You're next, Naomi. That's an order.
Understood.
Don't just rub it.
I know.
Come on, do it!
I said I know! Shit.
Not bad. I underestimated you, Naomi.
Shut up. Just get it over with.
Naomi needs some help.
You got it!
S-Stop!
How's that feel then, Major?
Slow down!
Good, Naomi. Move your hips and fuck that prick!
Remember, we're this ship's comfort officers.
I'm ready to cum! Want it inside you?
I don't know!
Cum inside me! Flood my insides with it!
I'm cumming inside you, pig-whore!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Don't cum inside me!
Dumb cunts.
There's no such thing as a "comfort officer".
It was a time of struggle.
After terraforming and colonizing the solar system,
mankind fought over resources and split into two factions:
Earth natives, the "Neo Terras",
and space colonists, or 'New Solars".
Despite the intervention of the Universal Federation Government,
the conflict continued to smolder.
And then...
A.D.2020
Kangoku Senkan
Vol.01: Overture to Brainwashing
takaku ni sobieru sono akari de
In that light that rises high,
te rashite hoshii no umi no panorama wo
the sea of stars forms a panorama.
kurayami ga shimesu ai no yukue
In the dark that shows love's whereabouts,
mado no mukou no futari no georama yo
two people outside the window form a georama.
yubi ga tsutaeru kokoro no furue
My fingers show the trembling of my heart.
tokoshie sae negaeba kanashimi no hate
Wishing forever just brings ultimate sadness.
anata wo tsurete hikanaide kono mama
I'm taking you along, don't pull me back.
kokoro hayaru kagen no tsuki
As the waning moon calms your heart,
ashita wo koko ni kuzusanaide ima wa
don't let our future be destroyed.
yume wo miseru ai no na wa idea
A love that brings dreams is called an "idea".
Gentlemen of the Jasant. We have a secret mission.
Who's the target, Captain?
Lieri Bishop, an up-and-coming New Solar commander,
and her aide, Major Naomi Evans.
She's up-and-cumming alright.
Lieri is onto the Neo Terras and our illegal activities.
She's planning to report us to the Universal Federation Government
when they convene on Earth in one week.
Sneaky bitch! The New Solars need to learn their place.
That's where we come in.
We'll intercept them at Titan Space Station and take them aboard.
During the seven-day journey to Earth, we'll give them one hell of a party.
And yes, we will be brainwashing them.
Yes, sir!
Four years ago, I was part of a kidnapping mission on Earth.
Curtis, bring the car around behind the guest house.
Roger.
Cover the car and fall back to Raining Avenue.
Rayson,
keep the engine running. Begin countdown.
Roger. Ready to go anytime.
Let's rock.
Curtis, sit rep!
It's a gun turtle attack!
Curtis! No...
Fall back! Now!
How did they know?
I've been waiting for this chance.
Welcome aboard the Jasant, Commander, Major.
Lieri Bishop.
Naomi Evans.
Thank you for taking us on, Captain.
There we go.
Why the long face, little lady?
We're glad to have you aboard.
I promise that your trip to Earth will be comfortable.
Captain, enough pleasantries.
What are you saying, Commander?
You're Donny Bohgan of the Neo Terras.
You're joking!
Do I look like I'm joking?
You can't fool me.
If you bring us to Earth unharmed,
I'll see that your criminal record is wiped clean.
There must be a misunderstanding.
I'm reporting the Neo Terras' crimes to the Universal Federation.
That's why I'm going to Earth.
I don't care about a little worm like you.
You can cooperate, or you can die prematurely.
It's a simple choice.
What!?
Captain!
It's Major Evans!
Send backup to the cafeteria!
Crazy bitch!
I'm sorry. She just started taking out the crew.
What? Unacceptable!
Pathetic.
This ship is a flying can of wimps.
What?
You'll regret that!
C-Commander!
That's enough.
Naomi.
Always the hothead.
F-Forgive me.
Thank God, Commander Bishop. For a moment I...
What?
Give up the act. This charade is over.
Wh-What do you mean?
Naomi, what should we say happened here?
I was attacked by four men and fired on them in self-defense.
And then?
In the confusion, the captain was shot.
To death. By you.
C-Captain!
Is this woman really going to shoot me right here?
Next time will be different, Captain Bohgan.
Consider my ultimatum and make the right choice.
Don't panic! I've got this.
I'm in control as always.
A-A gun turtle!
Well, if it isn't the Captain.
He's even dumber than I imagined.
It's almost shocking.
I live to defy expectations.
Hey, drop the gun!
This gun? All right.
Wait!
It's showtime!
Bastard!
What are you doing?
Don't worry. It's just hypno-gas.
No! I can't...
I win this time.
Dr. Magnus, I want you to wipe out their memories of tonight's events.
I have to tell you that there's a risk of permanent brain damage.
Whatever. Just do it.
Yes, sir.
Gentlemen, you're looking at a pair of fine specimens.
We're going to brainwash them thoroughly,
and make them into a couple of cunt slaves!
Yes, sir!
The nanomachines will fill their minds
with false information and memories.
After this, they'll even have new personalities.
Their sexuality will be altered dramatically and their inhibitions suppressed.
Their perception of sexual pleasure will be amplified.
Have you both gotten used to the Jasant?
Would you believe it?
Naomi the badass can't sleep without her favorite pillow.
L-Lieri-sama!
She was up all night playing cards.
We now control you.
At a predetermined signal, your personality will switch
to a personality that suits me and my crew.
That signal is...
Well, that conversation dried up in a hurry.
Is it that time already?
My men are waiting eagerly.
Can you be of service?
Captain, be gentle with us.
Let's begin.
This is great!
Drain your hard cock all over my breasts!
What a place to put your penis! Amazing!
Are you gonna cum? Is my hand as good as my pussy?
Oh, it's going in my mouth!
Wait your turn, everyone.
Aim it at my face!
All over my face...
This bitch is hot!
Sick nympho!
Oh, I spilled it.
– Oh, God... please!
– Die, pig-whore!
– Hose me down with semen!
– I'm gonna cum so hard!
I'm drowning in jizz.
Shit...
Good. Just like that.
Shut your mouth, you scum. Men suck!
Get a face-full of that!
Still not done? You repetitive son of a bitch?
I'm cumming!
Hurry, cum on my face!
Here's another helping.
Again?
How many times do you need? You're still hard.
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm going to destroy you.
Destroy you with my cock.
And you'll love it.
Quit babbling!
What's wrong, Naomi? Don't you like it?
Shut up and cum on me!
More cum down my throat!
They're loving it!
I don't know which one's a bigger slut.
No, this is just my job.
Sounds like the Commander wants more.
N-No...
We wouldn't deprive you of what you need.
– Let's get her wet!
– Stop!
Sergeant, after you.
Thank you. Attack!
– Yes, sir!
– Wait, don't...
Against any enemy...
...we will prevail!
We fight for peace...
...throughout the galaxy!
We dominate the land...
...the seas and the skies!
We'll spread our wings...
...and claim victory!
March forward!
Never surrender!
Long live the motherland!
Third battalion, ready!
Fourth, fifth battalions!
Ready!
Not yet. More!
Go for it, Sarge!
Oh, God. I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!!
Mission complete!
These bitches are conquered. Withdraw!
Hooray!
They can't escape... not from here.
Not from my prison battleship.