Battleship Jasant.
It looks like an ordinary freighter,
but its true mission is the brainwashing of high-profile targets.
Our current targets: Commander Lieri Bishop
and her aide, Major Naomi Evans.
Charismatic military police operatives.
Their destinies are entwined with mine.
During our seven-day journey to Earth,
my men and I will remodel their personalities to our liking.
True brainwashing takes time.
The process involves destroying their old personalities and memories,
then inserting artificial ones into the resulting gaps.
Is the neuro-chem working?
Yes. It's a cumulative aphrodisiac.
Soon, the simple act of walking will cause them to orgasm.
Excellent.
When the ship's time cycle simulates nightfall,
the women switch over to the personalities we've constructed for them.
That's when the sexual remodeling begins.
Kangoku Senkan
Vol.02: Brainwashing Alteraion
takaku ni sobieru sono akari de
In that light that rises high,
te rashite hoshii no umi no panorama wo
the sea of stars forms a panorama.
kurayami ga shimesu ai no yukue
In the dark that shows love's whereabouts,
mado no mukou no futari no georama yo
two people outside the window form a georama.
yubi ga tsutaeru kokoro no furue
My fingers show the trembling of my heart.
tokoshie sae negaeba kanashimi no hate
Wishing forever just brings ultimate sadness.
anata wo tsurete hikanaide kono mama
I'm taking you along, don't pull me back.
kokoro hayaru kagen no tsuki
As the waning moon calms your heart,
ashita wo koko ni kuzusanaide ima wa
don't let our future be destroyed.
yume wo miseru ai no na wa idea
A love that brings dreams is railed an "idea".
Is it me, or is it getting hotter in here?
No, it's the same as yesterday.
But I've noticed a change as well.
You, too, huh? I'll look into it, then.
The aphrodisiac... it's working!
They don't remember last night at all.
The false memories we inserted have become their reality.
It's that time again.
Nighttime on the Jasant.
Get a move on, maid!
Here's your beer.
Nice outfit, baby!
Come on! We've waited long enough!
Forgive me.
Thank you for waiting.
You're fucking-A right!
Gimme!
Hey, I want some, too.
Stop it!
Look at these stiff nipples!
You like being a comfort officer, huh?
– Stop! – It's an important duty!
I can't wait!
Don't!
Damn, she's sensitive.
Shut up!
No!
She's nearly ready to cum!
No... Stop...
Nympho bitch!
No...
Not so fast!
Man, I'm homy.
Stop!
Let's see. What does this part of you taste like?
Look, see how sloppy your pussy is?
Stop it...
Out of my way!
I wanna fuck that!
Me, too!
You're going to make me cum, right, Major?
Me first.
Can I be next?
You're last, dumbass.
What a show!
I'm ready to cum!
So am I!
Major!
I'm cumming!
Me, too! I wanna cum!
On my face...
All over my face!
No...
Aren't you a cutie?
It's Sarge's special move!
This bitch is a grade-A slut whore!
Are you ready for this?
I'll fuck you like an earthquake!
No more!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
You'll never forget me!
I'll pump you full of sauce!
You're welcome, bitch.
Who wants to be a man?
I do! Me first!
You're very good at comfort duty, Commander.
Truly a shining star of the New Solars!
Thank you, sir.
I live to pleasure you.
I'm cumming!
Hold it in your mouth, Commander.
Look at that!
Don't touch me right now.
No! I'm cumming!
More, please! More sex milk.
Oh, my God!
I'm cumming again!
What's our progress?
According to my calculations, the brainwashing
is about 25 percent complete.
Right on schedule.
Yes, by the time we reach Earth, their original
personalities should be completely gone.
"Should be?"
I mean, will be.
Good.
These Aredale class ships are remarkable, aren't they?
Long-range sensors, phaser guns, high-speed capability...
This ship's too good for you, Captain Bohgan.
Guilty as charged.
They don't remember the shame they experienced last night.
Captain.
Yes!
I have a favor to ask you.
We need access to the ship's main computer.
With the same security clearance as you, of course.
That computer controls everything that happens here.
There are safety concerns...
Everything we do will be logged.
We aren't the enemy. What's the harm?
Are they mocking me?
They're up to something, or they wouldn't have boarded voluntarily.
But what?
Well, Captain?
Fine.
I'll give you access to the main system.
A wise decision. Well done.
Four years ago during that attempted kidnapping...
These two prevented my escape.
That was a high-ranking government VIP.
What's your business here?
Enough, Naomi. All suspects have been arrested.
This punk is of no concern to us.
But we still ought to contact local authorities.
CONTACT... CONTACT...
Wait, there's no need for...
Hands to yourself, dog.
Let's go, Naomi.
On that night...
I couldn't even touch them.
Come in.
Pardon me. I have a report.
The Commander and the Major are accessing the main computer.
As I thought.
Studying the ship's layout?
Do they know about the brainwashing lab?
Captain?
The lab systems are all offline.
Let them rummage around, but watch them. Also...
Tell Dr. Magnus he can test the stomach drug he's been working on.
Yes, sir.
Fellatio-doll surgery? Are you sure?
Yes. It's prohibited by federal law, but this is "science".
It will be done.
Popular with post-war prostitutes,
the fellatio-doll procedure transforms the throat into an erogenous zone,
so that orgasm can be achieved by the mere act of giving head.
This procedure is outlawed as a violation of human rights.
No...
It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts!
Brainwashing is 75% complete.
Excellent!
Captain, I don't see a need to rush this.
Me?
Rush? Never.
Naomi, are you all right?
I'm fine. But this is...
Look at you two. What a beautiful sight.
Damn it.
Calm down. It's all part of your job.
Lieri-sama...
Naomi, hold on.
You don't want to strain yourselves.
That mix in your belly is volatile.
It hurts!
Come on, walk.
This isn't part of our comfort duty.
Release us immediately.
I disagree.
I'm feeling quite comfortable.
Please let us use the toilet.
Stop pretending you don't like it.
I know you do. You love it!
Yes. I love it.
Naomi, what do you say?
I love it.
You slave whores will obey my every whim.
My throat feels strange.
Consider that a gift.
A gift?
What did you do to us?
My mouth feels so good!
Fuck my mouth!
It's the fellatio-doll procedure.
Fellatio doll?
What have you done to my body?
It makes your mouth and throat as sensitive as your vagina.
Furthermore, to a man, your mouth feels like a vagina.
The female body, improved by science!
Have you ever felt anything like this?
Stop it... Stop it!
Oh, God! My throat!
Take it! Eat it!
You like that? You like it in your mouth?
Please, stop.
My mouth... Fuck my mouth!
Oh, no!
I'm cumming!
I'm ready to cum all over you.
Here goes!
So much cum...
Oh God, no!
Want some in your real pussy?
Well, Lieri?
Just say where you want it.
I want it in my pussy.
Nasty whore!
Look away.
That's some good cunt!
My turn!
I'm next!
My stomach hurts!
– Let us rest!
– I can't hold it!
Fuck yeah!
That's too hot!
I know.
Can't stop fucking!
Swallow my prick, you pig!
Take the whole length!
Fucking hot...
I'm gonna cum down your throat.
Suck that.
The toilet... I need to go to the toilet!
Here it comes!
It's gonna come out.
– Cumming!
– It's gonna come out.
Don't stop fucking them!
Trade off.
Sir.
Oh, my God.
Take it! Take it!
Fuck, yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'm gonna cum!
You two are tough.
Fuck them even more!
I came!
I'm cumming!
You're really hanging in there.
Gentlemen of the Jasant.
It's time for tonight's finale!
All right, let's do it!
Yes, sir!
Feeling full?
Wait. Please don't...
It'll all come out!
You scum!
Don't look at us!
No!
It's coming out!
How's it feel to shit yourself in front of everyone?
Enjoy it.
Yes. It's good...
No...
They saw it.
Tonight's operation is finished.
Nice work, men.
Mission accomplished!
Look at those wretches.
The doctor thought I was rushing
but it's all going according to schedule.
These two will never escape me!