Our current targets:
Commander Lieri Bishop and her aide, Major Naomi Evans.
Charismatic military police operatives.
Their destinies are entwined with mine.
The key to their brainwashing is sexual humiliation.
We amplify their libidos and assume control of their nervous systems.
They become completely different people.
During the brainwashing process,
we implant false memories into their minds.
We convince the women...
that they are playing an important role...
as "comfort officers" on my battleship.
Then, we use their scientifically enhanced
bodies for our own sexual pleasure,
and mold their personalities in ways that we find satisfactory.
There's no need for alarm.
Until we reach Earth, the women have nowhere to run.
This ship...
is a prison in space!
Kangoku Senkan
Vol.03: Targets Destroyed
takaku ni sobieru sono akari de
In that light that rises high,
te rashite hoshii no umi no panorama wo
the sea of stars forms a panorama.
kurayami ga shimesu ai no yukue
In the dark that shows love's whereabouts,
mado no mukou no futari no georama yo
two people outside the window form a georama.
yubi ga tsutaeru kokoro no furue
My fingers show the trembling of my heart.
tokoshie sae negaeba kanashimi no hate
Wishing forever just brings ultimate sadness,
anata wo tsurete hikanaide kono mama
I'm taking you along, don't pull me back.
kokoro hayaru kagen no tsuki
As the waning moon calms your heart,
ashita wo koko ni kuzusanaide ima wa
don't let our future be destroyed.
yume wo miseru ai no na wa idea
A love that brings dreams is called an "idea".
...and because of that, we can't use the
crew's quarters until further notice.
That's strange.
Speaking of that, what about the new weapon development?
We've had energy conversion trouble.
Looks like we have to go back to square one.
Don't work too hard, darling.
I won't. But neither should you.
If you ever want to talk about your own work...
What's wrong, Lieri?
It's nothing. Don't worry.
Nothing, huh? Just what I'd expect from an elite operative.
Stop it.
Are you sure you're all right?
It sounds like you're having trouble.
Please... stop.
What are you talking about?
My husband will hear you.
Tell your husband that you're a comfort officer.
I can't.
Lieri, is someone there with you?
It's Naomi. She's here.
What? I can't hear you.
There's some kind of noise,
like "slap, slap, slap". Hear that?
Lieri?
Naomi's having a hard time with the training.
She's been suffering from dizziness.
Dizziness? Are you sure you're all right?
Lieri?
Darling...
Stop it!
Lieri.
Lieri!
Sorry. I'm hanging up now.
Your husband's worried about you.
Where's your shame, nympho?
Forgive me, darling.
Your mission's not finished yet.
Today you'll plunge into a new operation.
What?
Stop, that hurts!
Apparently your husband's never tried this hole.
No!
A virgin resource, just waiting to be tapped.
Even comfort officers have to explore the unknown!
Your "elite operative" ass isn't bad. In fact, it's fucking great!
Take it!
You're... you're pounding my hole.
That's right, you're just a slut-whore.
A shameless cunt who fucks in front of her husband!
Your shithole is gripping my cock like a fist!
Tell me... Tell me you like it!
My ass... You're destroying my ass!
You're pounding my shithole!
Lieri-sama... I'm...
Naomi, no!
I know you're not feeling well, but we can't be found here.
Lieri-sama...
Fight through it.
B-But...
Aren't you feeling well?
Oh, dear. Did you catch a sniffle?
Bohgan, you...
What is it, Commander?
What have you done to our bodies?
Believe me,
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Indeed. Come on, Naomi.
Okay.
Fucking awesome!
What a show!
Look. Look at my pussy.
It's dripping wet!
Unbelievable!
Don't look at me!
Hey, she said, "Don't look!"
She means, "Look closer!"
Yes. Get a good look!
Our pussies are hot, wet and ready for your cum.
Shit, for real?
– This is embarrassing.
– What a sex freak!
– I want it! Put a cock in me!
– What a dirty slut.
– I can't wait!
Fuck yeah! This is the best!
So fucking hot!
I can't... I can't stop!
Swallow it all!
My turn!
Give it to me. Give me that cum.
I want to drink it!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Oh no, I'm going to...
I want it! I want your cum!
Naomi, I'm putting it in.
L-Lieri-sama...
Amazing!
Please, Lieri-sama, don't move.
Gimme some of that head!
Come on, don't tease!
Naomi, be careful!
Lieri-sama...
Damn, that's good stuff.
My cock's gonna burst!
What a nasty pair of whores.
Take that, you crazy slut!
Lier-sama...
Does that feel good?
The pig-whores are really showing their true colors.
Good!
Lieri-sama, please slow down.
Suck my dick, cunt!
Here it comes!
I'm cumming!
You fuckslut!
I love this prison!
Take it, pig-whore!
You're nothing but a cocksucking human cum toilet!
I want it!
I want your hot, sticky load!
Fuck!
I'm cumming!
I'm a pig-whore. I like being a pig-whore!
More! More cum!
Dump it on my face!
I want more cum, too. All of it!
Drown me in cum!
Fuck my titties!
Fuck them harder!
I love cock. I love cock.
Cum for me. Dump it all over my face.
More cock!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming too!
Fuck my tits!
So much hot cum...
Good work, ladies. Dinner is served.
Amazing.
Let me eat that cum.
Delicious cock sauce!
This sperm tastes so good.
I love it.
Good!
Give me your fucksauce. Inside me and all over me.
– I'm going... to cum again.
– Fucking pig!
I'm cumming!
Brainwashing is 90% complete.
Which means?
Their old personalities will be completely
overwritten by this time tomorrow.
Good work, men.
You've made me very proud.
But Captain, there's one thing that worries me.
There's an electronic signal coming from their quarters.
It might be some sort of code.
We're close enough to the end of this to be sure of our success.
No need to panic.
Yes, sir.
But, just in case...
It'll be taken care of.
In one more day, we'll have completed this mission.
These women will be crushed.
Mark my words.
The incident happened just after 03:00 PM the next day.
Using gun turtles, the women tore through the ship's sections...
killing any and all members of the crew who got in their way.
And then they stormed the bridge.
Cease all resistance and come with us!
Lying snake!
You should die for this,
you... you... you...
What have you done to us?
And how?
What an outrageous offense, Commander.
Keep this up, and you're cruising for a court martial.
Just a bit longer.
Then it becomes night and the brainwashing kicks in.
After that, it's all over.
Don't play dumb!
Confess,
before you find yourself full of holes.
Naomi!
Lights out, Major.
Guess you don't know...
your way around a gun turtle that well.
Now, maybe...
we'll rape you while you still have your original personality.
You...
I was right to suspect the worst of you two.
You've made a bold attempt on my life.
You're not normal New Solar agents. Who sent you?
What was that blast?
We're under attack! From where?
I don't know. It's off the scopes.
Large heat source approaching!
Wh-What did you say?
It's the New Solars' secret weapon!
Damn you!
Just in time.
Witness our trump card.
Take immediate evasive action!
Surrender, Bohgan.
The special forces will board this ship in moments.
The details of your plot will be made public on Earth.
New Solars Third Division here.
Commence seizure of enemy vessel.
We're ready to board.
Capture the pirate scum!
Yes, sir!
One more day. All I needed was one more day.
Accept defeat.
Once we land, you'll never fly again.
The Earth will be your prison.
Blocks A through E clear. Breach the next section!
Yes, sir!
E-Earth...
So close. I was so close.
October 25, 2020 A.D.
The New Solar authority interns the
battleship Jasant in Earth orbit.
From the military tribunal: (Verdict) The prosecution has produced legitimate proof of illegal activities conducted by the defendants (Major Donny Bohan and 16 of his subordinates.) Defendant Major Donny Bohgan and his subordinates are found guilty of forced prostitution, and sentenced to ten years incarceration. However, pending deeper investigation of the "brainwashing laboratory" mentioned in the official report, the court refuses to take an official stance, and the trial is suspended. In accordance with Article I of the Public Order Act, the charges are dropped.
After that,
nothing was heard about the incident.