Haru-kun, this is a little embarrassing...
My maid, Akina, is attending to me today.
Y-Yes.
You're so hot down here, Haru-kun.
Akina, your fellatio is amazing.
It feels so damn good when
you wrap your tongue around me.
Will you make me come, Akina?
Yes, use my mouth to feel even better.
I'm coming, Akina!
Akina...
N-No, not there...
The way you use your hands is really perverted!
You're all swollen down here.
Since when did you become
such a perverted girl, Akina?
That's not true at all.
Akina, amazing.
You're so wet.
Hey, can you hear it?
No more, Haru-kun! No more!
Put it in!
Here I go.
Akina, it's so hot inside you.
It feels like I'm gonna melt!
I'm coming, Akina!
Haru!
It's so deep...
Your big dick is reaching so deep inside me!
Akina, I'm coming again!
You can't, didn't you just come inside me?
Haru-kun, you're coming inside too much!
It's too much!
Akina, I'm coming again!
Your come is overflowing out of me, Haru-kun!
Amazing, it's nice and slippery from all the come!
I'm- this is bad!
I can't anymore, Haru-kun!
I'm coming too!
Akina!
Amazing, I came this much!
Geez, Haru-kun, you try too hard.
Akina, it's fine-
Huh?!
Haru-chan's dick is hard as ever!
I'm going after Natsumi.
What?
Natsumi-san, did you forget about-
Oh no, Haru-chan, that's a secret.
Haruomi, I'm going next.
Haru-kun is mine!
This is punishment for keeping it from us.
You shouldn't sneak ahead.
Well then, Haru-chan.
Let the service begin.
Kanojo x Kanojo x Kanojo
- Exciting life together with three sisters-
Episode 3- The City: Festival,
Bath and Harem Paradise
Shiki-kun's meal is pretty grand.
Did something happen, Akina?
N-Nothing really...
T-Technically, Haru-kun and I are...
Did Haru-chan say so?
Um, not really...
Haruomi is just in heat.
Mind your words!
Haru-chan is everyone's Haru-chan!
Haru-chan is a boy after all, so as long
as he's around such attractive girls...
I don't think anyone would
blame him for being unfaithful.
L-Listen now, you two!
Natsumi-san!
I need to head out soon.
Wait, Haru-kun!
Here.
Thanks.
Huh?
See you later.
Whoa, this isn't bad.
It's actually pretty good.
Yo, Haruomi
Do you think MinMin Ice can win this year?
The exhibition fair.
The Tanabata district new ice cream products fair.
The summer festival starts next week, doesn't it?
On the last day, the big
shots of the area get together.
You didn't know that?
Your shop won three years in a row.
While our shop ended up third place last year.
Well, it's no surprise since MinMin ice is delicious.
Let's not even talk about Golden Stone
and 101, both of which are national brands.
There's no way Hage-Dazs
could rival MinMin ice's flavor.
I know but I still want to fight this out!
Fight this out?
Yes.
This isn't a request. It's a proposal.
Contract
Excuse me.
Yes, welcome.
One of your famous ice creams, please.
This should do.
All right, you're going to obey me if I win.
And you'll be making a MinMin
ice promotion video for free.
Also, hidden cameras
and the like aren't allowed
I know.
Oh, I forgot to say this, but since our
shop recently joined the 101 group...
...it'll count as my victory if they win.
Akina, Akina, Princess Akina...
I'm home.
Seriously, Natsumi-san's
ice cream can't possibly lose.
Oh well, if this can get the store more
publicity and stop Honnouji's pranks.
I'll kill two birds with one stone.
Welcome home.
Did I surprise you?
But of course!
What's with her?
Natsumi-san.
I want to talk about something...
This isn't good enough after all.
I knew it.
This way...
At this rate...
This won't do.
Natsumi-san.
Making The Highest
Quality Ice Cream
What's wrong, Shiki-kun?
Byakudan, can you read this language?
It's about herbs, right?
Herbs?
Yes, herbs.
It's used in the ice cream, right?
I see... ice cream, you say...
I can translate it for you if you'd like.
Really?
That would help a lot.
All right, but let's go to the rooftop, ok?
Hey, uh, Byakudan?
Stop...
Byakudan, w-wait!
Haru-chan, thanks for finding the notebook.
No need to thank me.
That notebook contains the recipe for
the herb ice cream my father used to make.
I was really happy when you brought it over.
You really helped me again.
Don't mention it.
I'm glad I helped you out.
W-What?
Natsumi-san?
You're so cool, Haru-chan.
Oh...
I mean, go, Natsumi-san!
You're holding everyone up!
I need a special type of lavender
that grows only on that island.
You seem to like that place a lot.
Yes, my father and I often used to take
the boat out there to pick them a long time ago.
We don't have the boat anymore though...
So in Akina-chan's words,
"Haru-chan is a hard worker!"
Huh?
Oh, you two are late.
You're too early, sis.
Driving is cheating.
Huh? Where's Haru-kun?
Uh, well...
Dammit, I'm making no progress at all!
I can't move another inch.
Haru-chan, you're amazing!
My pleasure.
Rest for a bit, Haru-kun.
I'll help out in your stead.
Haru-kun, good work.
Thanks.
Huh? Where's Mafuyu?
Mafuyu-chan is selling written oracles up there.
Ah, there you are.
Looks like you're actually working hard.
That wasn't nice.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Haruomi, draw a written oracle.
Oh, those.
All right.
Kyo (curse)
Yet another predictable outcome...
Lemme try again.
Kyo, Kyo, Kyo, Kyo (curse)
That's because of your bad karma.
"Terrible luck" isn't always a bad thing, you know.
Is that supposed to make me feel better?
Who to wait for the long-haired
blonde who is already by your side.
You should choose
what's small over what's big.
Kanojo X Kanojo X Kanojo
Haru-chan, thanks for the lavender.
It's nothing if it will make
your ice cream taste better.
MinMin ice will win again this year.
We won't lose to 101!
Oh, leave the cleaning up to me.
It's fine.
S-Sorry...
Haru-chan, thanks.
Ever since you moved in with us,
I feel everyone's become happier.
It's the other way around, Natsumi-san.
I'm the one who should
be thanking you and the others.
Well, I suppose I do feel tired every now and then.
I like that side of you, Haru-chan.
N-Natsumi-san...
Hold still, ok?
Natsumi-san...
T-This is...
I'll help relieve
your fatigue, so let it all out.
Natsumi-san, this feels really good.
Your nipples are hard now.
Your dick is standing straight up too.
Natsumi-san...
What is it, Haru-chan?
Haru-chan...
Haru-chan, you really love breasts, don't you?
Yours are just too nice.
Enjoy them as much as you like.
Natsumi-san...
Your breasts feel really supple.
Really, Haru-chan...
Haru-chan, how's this?
I-It's so soft... it feels great.
Natsumi-san.
It's kinda naughty how your dick goes in and out.
Haru-chan, are you gonna come?
The way your breasts squeeze me is amazing...
I'm gonna come.
I'm coming, Natsumi-san!
Natsumi-san.
Haru-chan...
Your butt is so big and soft.
Haru-chan, don't do that...
It went right inside you, Natsumi-san.
Haru-chan, please...
Natsumi-san, I'm putting it in.
Amazing.
Your dick is so deep inside me...
Haru-chan, more!
Squeeze my breasts more!
Natsumi-san, it's so deep and hot inside you.
I feel really good too!
Haru-chan, deeper... deeper!
I'm coming, Natsumi-san.
Shoot your come inside me, Haru-chan!
Your thick come, give me lots of it!
It's good but...
How is it?
It's good but it's no different than usual.
Then that's good.
Huh? Why?
Three days until the exhibition fair, huh?
I'm starting to get nervous.
I'm home.
A-Am I dreaming?
Uh, y-you know...
I'm feeling kinda dizzy.
Mafuyu just came in but now she won't talk.
What's with her?
Haruomi, are you turned on?
W-Well, what am I supposed to do?
I'm in the bath with a cute girl.
Am I cute?
Well...
Maybe if you were a bit more honest with yourself.
You're the only one who says that.
Mafuyu, I need to get out soon...
Haruomi, do you like girls with big breasts?
I don't mind either way.
Your thing moved again.
Y-Yeah, well...
You really are a beast.
Yeah.
Hold still.
M-Mafuyu, where did you learn this?
Your dick is getting bigger.
Face me, Haruomi.
My breasts can make you feel good too.
I don't think that'll work.
But then I can't beat the other two.
Here.
It feels great if you do this.
L-| know that!
Your dick is all big and red.
You feel so good that you want to come, right?
Yeah.
It feels great, Mafuyu.
Go ahead and come, Haruomi.
I'm gonna come.
I'm coming!
W-What, Haruomi?
Look how wet you are, Mafuyu.
Haruomi, n-no...
It feels... it feels so good!
You're about to come, right?
N-Not there!
Did that feel good?
Y-Yeah.
You're still all hard down there, Haruomi.
I'll let you put it in if that's what you want.
Let me?
Put it in!
Fill my pussy with your big dick!
How's this, Mafuyu?
Does it feel good?
It feels good...
Your dick is going all the
way in and making me come.
Your dick is making me come!
I'm coming too!
Come!
All of it!
Shoot all of your come inside me!
So much, so much of your come, Haruomi...
Tomorrow is the day of the exhibition fair.
I don't think I was of any help in the end.
The rest is up to Natsumi-san.
You forgot something.
Fell in love?
AS if!
Believe in Natsumi.
A gentle flavor.
It's very steady with flavor for its
own sake without being too fancy.
I apologize for what happened last time.
But you came again.
Making The Highest
Quality Ice Cream
You really are just like him.
It was delicious. Thanks.
Thanks for visiting!
The 42nd Tanabata District
Ice Cream Exhibition Fair
Main Conference Room
The 42nd Tanabata District
Ice Cream Exhibition Fair
Main Conference Room
Natsumi-san, how did it go?
Not so well!
101 won first prize.
O-Oh no...
Great news, sis!
Our shop won!
It seems that 101 will leave Tanabata
district tomorrow for some reason,"...
So they lost the right to be in the fair.
Didn't this man used to work at Dad's place?
Now that you mention it,
I think I've seen him before.
It's definitely him.
Oh, hello.
Why are the two of you here?
We've come to take Shiki-kun to extra lessons.
Extra lessons?
You’re an enemy.
That's your introduction?
That's what my instinct is telling me.
Look how popular you are, Haru-chan.
Akina, Natsumi, I declare a temporary truce.
Truce?
It doesn't look like my problems
are going away anytime soon.
Huh? Shiki-kun?!
Haruomi ran away.
Huh? Haru?!