Yeah! Here I come!
Oh no! I'm gonna lose, I'm gonna lose!
I'm gonna lose!
Yes!
I never thought I'd lose in a shooting game.
Well this was a wager after all. You're gonna
have to listen to whatever I say today.
I-I know! Just do whatever you want.
Well then, try wearing these.
What the hell are these?
Cat ears?
When she tried on cat ears.
Oh! It looks good, just how I thought it would!
No matter what a cute girl wears, it always looks good!
Ugh... I was actually planning on making you
treat me to a full course French dinner.
I bought these clothes 'cause I knew it'd go with the ears.
H-Hey!
Don't look at me so closely! Idiot!
Huh? Haruna, where's the tail?
Oh! I couldn't figure out how to attach it.
That's... you see.
H-Hey! What are you planning to do?!
It's impossible unless we loosen you up a little.
D-Don't!
Not in my ass...! It can't be possible!
It'd be dangerous if you struggle too much.
No!!
Stop... Stop! Stop it!
Don't put it in!
Don't!
See? It's already completely inside.
It's inside of my ass!
It feels so weird for some reason!
You're doing great Hana! Your expressions are really cute!
Huh? Hey...
Why are you filming?
It's fine, it's fine. I won't show it to anyone.
I just wanna use it to masturbate later.
I-Idiot!
What are you thinking?!
Shougo, you pervert!
You promised you'd listen to whatever I want today, didn't you?
Right?
Really?
Don't show it to anyone, okay?
Don't put it on the internet either, okay?
Of course!
Well then, why not try some poses?
I-Is this alright?
Stick out those hips a little, and let's
have you spread your legs as well.
G-Geez, Shougo, you had this outfit
and camera prepped from the start.
I'm sure you secretly practiced playing
that game too, didn't you?
Correct!
High class Italian delicacies, expensive
sushi, Japanese restaurants.
You made me treat you a lot after all.
You need to get revenge every once in a while.
M-My bad, I'm sorry. I'll apologize so,
this much is enough, right?
Please forgive me already!
Well then, I've got one last request.
A-Are we really going to do it?
There's hardly anyone around at this time.
And it's dark so it's not really noticeable.
B-But, going out in this getup is...
Even if it's outside, you just need to
go to the convenience store below.
It's going to be fine.
N-No one is around, right?
Now! March forward!
Hey! Don't say it out so loud!
G-geez... Shougo is such a jerk.
I'm never going to bet on a game again!
N-No... What's this?
This tail makes it quite hard to walk.
It swings around so much just from taking a step.
It's scrubbing me up!
I'm feeling so strange just from walking down the s-stairs.
This is the fifth floor as well. Will I be able
to make it all the way down like this?
Impossible... It's impossible.
I'm about to pee myself, if someone sees me like this... I...
This is not it... It's a misunderstanding!
This is just a punishment game.
I'm not into exhibitionism or anything!
No!
S-Stop it!
No... I'm not some pervert!
I'm not getting excited... With something
like this being done to me.
Not good. No matter what I say they won't believe
me when I'm wearing something like this.
The more of a ruckus I make, the more people start to gather.
I'll just have to keep quiet and do as they say.
I beg of you. I'll do it with my mouth, so...
P-Please, forgive me with this.
If I get raped this hard, I realty might break!
I will just have to satisfy them somehow, with this.
Lots of hot, slimy stuff is spilling onto me.
It has such a lewd smell.
If this keeps up, then even I'll start feeling horny.
What should I do? It looks like they aren't
satisfied by just cumming once.
Help me... Shougo, help me!
No, I definitely won't be able to hold it together until I get down.
Let's just go back.
Oh no! Someone is coming down!
This is bad! Bad! Bad, bad, bad!
I will be seen like this!
I will be mistaken for a pervert!
If I just take off the cat ears and the tail at the very least...
I-I can't take them out!
With one pull... I'm going to take them out with one pull!
Ehh? Ha-Haruna?
What are you doing?
Sho-Shougo?
Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot, idiot, idiot! Shougo, you idiot!!
And I thought you'd come back crying right away...
You did your best, huh?
Th-That's right! I did my best!
H-Hey!
Shougo, wh-where are you touching me?
Haruna's place is really wet, you know.
No, don't tease me there right now.
You got excited thinking someone might see you, right?
I-Idiot!!
You're wrong! You're wrong!
N-No!
Just be honest.
If you put nyaa after every word, then
I'll do anything to make you feel good.
Wha?! I-Idiot! Who'd do something like that?!
Will you do it? Will you not?
This guy... He's only good when it comes to this sort of stuff.
No...
Oh no... What do I do?
It's because something like that happened...
It feels so much better than usual.
My love juices keep gushing out.
That place is becoming so restless, I can't hold back any longer!
I-I want to do it...
Mm?
I want to do perverted stuff... N-nyaa...
Okay!
Listen, alright? Today is the only time
I'm doing something like this, okay?
It's different than usual.
It's fine, it's fine.
Come on, spread those legs open.
Sh-Shougo, I'm like this now-nyaa.
I want Shougo's penis to be put in-nyaa.
Well done!
A-Amazing!
This is... Sho-Shougo's...
No, don't...
Don't fondle my boobs so much.
Not good, I'm feeling this way too much.
It's just how I thought it'd be.
Having sex with Shougo when he's this turned on, is
so much more intense than usual. It feels so good!
What do I do? My switch seems to have turned on too.
I'm getting hornier, I can't help it!
No! To the end! It's reaching up to the very end!
No! No! No!!
Shougo's penis is so long!
If it keeps hitting me all the way back, then I'll...
I'm cummmg, I'm going to cum!
He's going to make me cum!
Could it be that you just came on your own, before me?
I'm sorry, I came, I came.
Well then, it's time for punishment.
Should we put in the tail again?
I-Idiot! Don't do that!
It's alright! Your asshole is already lubed up with your love juice.
I said, don't do it. I don't want it in my butt anymore.
You forgot to say nyaa at the end so, no!
It's rubbing against me!
Your penis and my tail are rubbing against each other inside.
Something like this is a first for me!
I'm going to go crazy!
How is it? Giving it to you rough a
second time, just how you like it.
Shougo, you idiot! Pervert!
Good, good!
I didn't know you'd feel this good with your butt.
Do-Don't... Don't say it like that!
It's embarrassing!
Well then, how about something like this?!
What?
Stop it! I'll be seen! Everything will be seen!
But you know that feels good, right?
Haruna's insides are gripping me so tightly!
No way... I'm getting excited.
Wearing cat ears and a tail... Even though this embarrassing
getup will be seen by everyone.
I'm getting so excited!
No... Don't pound me so hard!
My boobs are being pushed in.
I don't like my hard nipples rubbing against the window.
Haruna, this feels really good!
Shougo feels amazing too.
Having sex when Shougo's in the mood feels great!
I'm almost losing consciousness!
I can't take it anymore, Shougo! I'm going to cum!
I'm about to cum!
C-Cumming!
I-Idiot! Don't pull the tail!
My ass... My ass will open up!
If you don't properly act like a cat, then
I won't let you cum until the end.
Sh-Shougo... I will take care of you after this!
Okay Haruna, here comes the third one!
Good... Good...
No, it's embarrassing but I can't hold it any longer!
If you're feeling that good, then try acting like it already!
I-It feels good-nyaa.
Shougo's penis is amazing-nyaa.
My pussy feels so good, I'm about to cum-nyaa!
Haruna, that's cute!
You're so cute, Haruna!
I did it-nyaa.
I properly did what you asked-nyaa.
I beg of you-nyaa. Shougo, just let me
cum! Let me cum like this-nyaa!!
Haruna! Haruna!
Haruna, Haruna, Haruna!!
Amazing... It's amazing-nyaa.
Your penis is getting bigger and bigger-nyaa!
It's hitting the back of my pussy-nyaa.
It's being messed up along with my butt-nyaa!
You're doing great, Haruna! More, please say more!
What is this? What is this sex?
Even though I know how it's supposed to feel.
T-This feels incredible-nyaa!
I'm about to cum!
Me too! I'm cumming!
I'm cummmg-nyaa!
I'm going to cum-nyaa!!
It really felt good, Haruna.
I still have a lot of cosplay outfits left.
I wonder what I should go with next?
Shougo!
How much longer are you going to act full of yourself?
No, b-but...
Here you go, Haruna.
This is a new product called Fruit Trifle.
What these are just sweets from the convenience store.
Just leave it there.
It can't be helped, can it?
There are no other shops open this time of day.
I'll have you treat me to the fullest this weekend, got it?
So... you're still mad?
Isn't that obvious?
Thanks to you, my asshole still hurts a lot.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But still... It was pretty refreshing, right?
W-Well, yeah... I guess it's fine to go along with
something like that from time to time.
That's not it! It's not like it felt good or anything.
Or got me excited!
It's not anything like that, okay?!
Even though I said that, I guess something
like this really might become a habit.
I"m walking outside naked in such an embarrassing outfit.
I-If someone sees me like this...
I'd definitely get raped this time!
They're going to get me!
Oh no, I can't hold it in.
No way, it's already gotten so wet.
I'm getting excited
doing something this embarrassing.
When I think someone might see me, my heart starts racing.
And it feels surprisingly good.
I'm feeling it way more than usual.
Maybe I actually want to be seen.
The place with which I masturbate, my dirty appearance.
I want all of it to be seen.
Oh no, just what do I do now?
No... Don't...
Hey Haruna! It'll be troublesome if you let out such loud noises.
It's fine... Shougo will come to help
me if something happens, right?
W-Well of course I will, but...
If you're really so worried, then fuck me
before I get assaulted by someone.
Eehh?! H-Here?!
Yeah, I want Shougo's dick to be inside me right here-nyaa.
I want you to mess up perverted old me-nyaa.
Ha-Haruna!
A-Amazing!
I'm going to cum right away-nyaa!
To think that Haruna would get into it so much.
It never even crossed my mind.
Geez, whose fault do you think that is-nyaa?
This is... This is all because of that game-nyaa!
It's good... Haruna's cat-play really is the best.
Your dick is getting bigger inside me-nyaa.
Shougo, you really are a pervert after all-nyaa.
Well Haruna, you're just as bad now.
I'm also a pervert-nyaa.
Doing it like this in public.
My pussy and butt brushing against
each other feels so good-nyaa!
More... I want dirtier stuff to be done to me-nyaa!
I-I'm at my limit already...
I'm going to cum!
Your penis has become so hot, it's twitching-nyaa!
Cum! Cum! Cum!!
Inside... Ejaculate inside me!
Nyaa!!!
Translator: Maq-kun, Hikarucon
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Slll, Punk4Real
Encoder: Punk4Real