I love you, Sei-chan.
Me too, Ai.
Hold me tighter.
Ai...
I have to go to work now.
I'm sorry, Sei-chan.
There's something that I'm not telling you.
I'm sorry.
If that accident hadn't happened,
we would be living together normally.
It's okay.
It's just been postponed for a bit.
I'm no longer working at the pizza parlor where he works.
And because of that accident, I'm now deeply in debt.
Please don't say that.
We'll overcome hardships like this together, okay?
But... I want to live with Sei-chan.
I'm going to do my best.
So just concentrate on getting yourself healthy again, okay?
I'll be going now then.
Okay.
I'll come visit again tomorrow.
Bye bye!
Excuse me.
I'm Ai!
reason why she won't visit anymore
Ai-chan's really cute.
No, not really.
We specifically asked for you today.
Here it comes again....
You're going to entertain us with your body again, okay?
Please no...!
I'm going to be played with by these men again.
Breast fondling is allowed in this shop.
So I guess you like these kinds of things, eh?
No, please stop.
Not there...
Don't touch it...
No, no...!
Can I join you there, Tomioka-san?
Okay, let her have a mouthful.
Ai-chan, your mouth pussy really is the best!
Stop this... already...
Please.
Now it's time for this thing.
No, please don't!
The way you drive it in sure is amazing, Tomioka-san.
Please, please don't look!
No, no!
I... I...
We can't, we really can't do this!
Stop, leave me be already!
Stop it now!
Stop!
No...
I'm getting fucked in this place...
Oh no, I can't hold it in anymore.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I have to get back to work.
Sei-chan, Sei-chan.
I'm sorry...
I-I'm all dirty now...
Thank you for waiting.
Ai's here!
Ai-chan.
Tsutomu-san, why are you here?
I'm the one who'd like to ask you that!
You quit your former job and now you're in this kind of place!?
Does Seiji know about this?
The pay from the pizza parlor wasn't
enough to pay for Sei-chan's debts.
I started working at this shop and didn't tell Sei-chan about it.
I thought my job was just to chat with them and pour liquor.
But it was completely different.
They did all sorts of indecent things to me.
There were even times that I was invited outside the shop.
Whenever that happened, I always got taken to a love hotel.
But I really needed the money, so I couldn't just say no to them.
Just a little earlier in the shop, I was...
Don't say anything anymore!
I've loved you for a long time now, Ai-chan.
Tsutomu-san, what are you saying?
That's why I can't bear to see you suffering like this.
If you were mine, I'd never let you do something like this.
No...
Don't do this...
Ai-chan.
Stop... Please stop, Tsutomu-san.
I love you Ai-chan!
If other guys were already playing around with you out there,
then just one more like me is me right?
No way...
Because I love you Ai-chan!
What's this? It's huge!
It feels so different compared to Sei-chan's
or to the other guys out there.
It feels tight.
It's entering me.
This is terrible, Tsutomu-san.
You're Sei-chan's senior, you know that we're going out.
I'm sorry Ai-chan, but I can't control my feelings any longer.
Don't.
Please don't!
We can't do this...
Please stop, Tsutomu-san.
I'm going to break.
This is terrible.
This is just terrible.
We shouldn't do this.
We shouldn't do this but...
Wh-What is this?
Oh no.
Are you getting horny, Ai-chan?
I'm not...
I wouldn't.
That can't be.
Just let me...
Ai-chan, I love you.
I really, really do!
Do you hate me, Ai-chan?
Please don't say it that way.
It's unfair.
I don't care if it is.
I want you, Ai-chan!
Stop... please stop!
Stop now!
Let me be!
Let me be already!
If you keep this up,
I really will lose it!
I never knew...
That sex could feel so good.
Tsutomu-san's thing is so big.
It totally fills up my insides!
N-No way, it's swelling up.
His thing is swelling up!
If this continues, I'll
I'm going to break.
I'm going to break down there.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Tsutomu-san?
No, this isn't enough.
What? But men are supposed to be done when they cum, right?
No...
Tsutomu-san, don't...
Don't!
Wow...
No, let me go!
It's going deep inside!
I can't hold on anymore.
I'm going to lose it.
This is just too intense.
It's the first time I've experienced this.
I feel it, I can feel it.
My insides are throbbing.
I'm going to cum again.
I can't hold on anymore.
No way.
Tsutomu-san just keeps on going.
His thing is still rubbing wildly inside me.
Wait, just wait Tsutomu-san.
If you do that, I'll cum again!
No, no...
I'm going to cum again!
Let me go already.
I'll completely lose myself if you keep moving.
I'm going to make you mine, and mine only!
Please, please!
Let me rest for a bit.
No...
My mind's really going blank.
I'm going to lose it...
I won't even be able to think...
Tsutomu-san, I really want to thank you,
for asking the manager to let me work here again.
Thanks to you, I was able to quit that job,
and you even lent me money.
That's why I'm going to do my best to repay you.
Tsutomu-san?!
Stop this!
You can't do this, Tsutomu-san.
No...
Please don't, Tsutomu-san.
I can't betray Sei-chan like this any longer.
Ai-chan...
Don't...!
You can't do this!
Forcing yourself on me like this is so cruel.
If you continue with this, I'm going to hate you.
So you don't hate me yet, Ai-chan?
No...
It's still going in...
It's too big.
Stop,Tsutomu-san.
Don't be rough with me.
Don't thrust it into me!
Stop, stop hitting me there.
You're getting horny already right, Ai-chan?
I'm not feeling horny... at all...
That's impossible when I'm being done like this.
I beg of you Tsutomu-san.
Come to your senses already.
This is too much!
Oh no, I don't feel horny and yet...
No, no!
Please don't go that deeply inside me!
No, not there.
If you do that, I'll... I'll...
No, I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming with your thing deep within me.
I came.
I came...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry Sei-chan...
Are you still thinking of Seiji, Ai-chan?
Of course l am.
I'm Sei-chan's girlfriend!
I'm going to make you forget.
I'm going to make you forget everything about that guy!
Oh, wow!
Something even bigger is coming!
No!
I'm going to cum again.
I'm not supposed...
I'm not supposed to cum...
No, no!
Please stop already.
I'm going to lose it.
Oh no, oh no.
My mind's going blank.
No way...
It feels hot in there.
We're not supposed to do this...
And yet...
No...!
I'm never going to return Ai-chan to him.
Ai-chan is...
Ai is mine!
The reason why she won't visit anymore.
A few days later...
Um, Tsutomu-san?
Hm? What's wrong?
You're dropping by my place again, right?
Well... We've done it many times already...
And I know it's partly my fault, because
I wasn't able to say no properly.
But, I'm...
I'm already with Sei-chan...
So I want us to end... this relationship...
I'm begging you.
I'm really sorry.
Is it going to be me or Seiji?
I'm going to make you choose.
She didn't come to visit me today either.
Ai, I want to see you.
No, we can't do this Tsutomu-san.
Doing this in front of Sei-chan is...
I told you that I'm going to make you
choose between me and Seiji, right?
No way...
How terrible of you, Tsutomu-san.
This is too terrible!
We mustn't do this...
We mustn't do this, but...
No...
But when he enters me.
My body stops listening to what I say.
It's happening again.
I won't be able to think properly again.
This is amazing.
It's so big.
It feels like it's going deeper than my womb.
I'm going to move now, Ai.
Alright but please,
please take it slow at first, okay?
This amazing thing is going deep inside me.
It's thrusting into me.
Rubbing deep inside.
Oh no, I'm letting out such an embarrassing voice.
Sei-chan might hear it.
Well, there's only Seiji in here.
Wow...
The tip of your thing is getting wrapped inside.
I'm going numb.
It feels twitchy down there.
Yes! That feels great!
I'm being filled with your thing.
Use more lewd words Ai.
Lewd words?
What are you making me say!
I said...
No way....
I can't say those kinds of things.
Why?
You've already said them before, right?
That's... that's because it felt so good that I just lost myself.
No, not there...!
I'm going to feel very horny.
Wow, I'm really going to lose it.
Yes.
This feels good.
What feels good exactly, Ai?
There, it feels great there!
Don't say "there".
I can't.
Now, tell me where does it feel good.
That's, that's...
Inside my pussy!
My pussy... My pussy feels great!
My pussy feels horny!
I came.
No... Tsutomu-san made me cum in front of Sei-chan.
His thing is swelling up.
It's getting really big deep inside me.
And stirring up my insides.
I've become such a slutty girl because of him!
We're going to be seen.
Sei-chan will see me being fucked by Tsutomu-san.
It's embarrassing, yet my hips won't stop.
Wow, Tsutomu-san's thing is really lively.
I'm going to cum a lot again.
Cum, please cum in me!
Please make my pussy cum with your cock!
Something big is coming!
Ai?
Ai...?
I'm sorry, Sei-chan.
For doing this so suddenly...
But I was feeling lonely.
So please let me do this.
I want you to arouse my pussy.
Sei-chan, let's do it.
Ai...
Sei-chan, you like school-themed sex plays, right?
It's already been a long time since I did it with Sei-chan.
It feels good.
When I connect with you, it feels amazing.
I really do love Sei-chan after all.
Hey, Sei-chan.
How would you want to do it?
I'm ready to listen to whatever you have to say.
I'm going to do everything that you want me to do.
I want to do it for you.
Sei-chan, it feels really hot.
It's really hot.
Your thing is rubbing inside me, and it feels good.
It feels great!
I want to feel you more, Sei-chan.
Because, because...
If I don't, I'm...
Sei-chan, Sei-chan!
Hey, please.
Please let me love you.
Sei-chan, Sei-chan!
I love you!
I really love you!
My first time was with you.
I was really glad that it was you, whom I really love.
I remember, I still remember.
You made me into a woman, right?
It hurt at first, but...
I endured it, because I loved you.
Since then, it gradually felt better and better.
I still remember clearly.
Sei-chan... Sei-chan...
You know, I...
I want to keep on loving you!
It's true.
Sei-chan... Sei-chan, please let me feel it.
Make me feel good!
Make me feel more aroused!
Cuddle me all you want!
If... If this goes on I...
Hey... Hey, do you love me?
Ify ou really love me,
make me feel good.
It feels hot.
Sei-chan, arouse me more!
I'm going to cum.
Make me cum.
Make me cum with your thing!
It's coming.
I'm going to cum!
It's coming out.
Lots of it... is flowing out in me...
Sei-chan...
Hey Sei-chan,
you're done already?
Sei-chan's thing is getting smaller and smaller in me.
You finish way too quickly, it's very different from Tsutomu-san's.
Tsutomu-san is miles away from you, he never finishes quickly.
Ai, what are you saying?
Tsutomu-san made me feel really good, you know?
He made me cum lots of times in just one session!
He made me cum to the point that I almost went crazy.
I expected something more.
I expected that since it was sex with my beloved Sei-chan,
it would feel a lot better.
I thought that you were capable of taking me back.
I hoped that you could...
I don't know how many times we've done It anymore.
Cum lots inside my womb!
My womb,
is getting filled with babies!
I'm going to get pregnant!
I'm definitely going to get pregnant.
I'm sorry, Sei-chan.
I won't be able to visit you anymore.