Orifushi
I'm finally here.
My name is Shiki Haruomi.
Due to certain circumstances...
...I am now under the care of my
old acquaintances, the Orifushi family.
Huh? I'm pretty sure I already
let them know I was coming.
Are they out in the garden?
Hello?
It's Shiki!
Is anyone home?
Natsumi-san, are you here'?
Sorry Mafuyu. Can you bring me a towel.
Mafuyu?
KANOJO X KANOJO X KANOJO
- Exciting life together with three sisters-
Episode 1- The City:
Gently, Firmly, Little Devil Paradise
Haru-kun, you can use this room.
Isn't this your dad's room?
Are you sure I can use it?
Dad and mom passed away quite a while ago.
I see.
Since then, my sister took over
the family business. She's working hard.
Natsumi-san, huh?
Haru-kun, you've really grown.
Well, of course, I'm bigger
now compared to back then.
You too.
Have I gotten prettier?
To be honest, Akina had become
even cuter than she was before.
Hah, you're blushing!
It's like my pace of
life was thrown out of order.
Once again, welcome Haru-kun!
You took your time, Haruomi.
It's been so long, Haru-chan.
Umm... let's get along.
- I'm digging in.
- How great!
Hey Mafuyu, eat properly!
Haru-chan...
...you're a guy so you gotta eat more!
Ah, ok, I'm digging in!
Umm, Natsumi-san ...
The way you address
me is kinda embarrassing.
On? Why?
I'm not exactly a kid anymore.
But "Haru-chan" is such a cute name!
The "chan" at the end is kinda...
But I feel like we're closer
if I call you "Haru-chan."
The "chan" at the end is kinda...
But "Haru-chan" is easy to say.
BUT!
Ok, I get the point.
Already?
I still have about 12 other reasons.
Here, Haru-chan. Say "aah."
Uh, Natsumi-san, wait—
Hey, sis, you're clinging
on to Haru-kun too much.
Oh my, Akina-chan.
Are you jealous?
Haru-chan, who do you like
the best out of the three of us?
What? Well, I...
I know!
I'll find out who it is.
Ahh, so it is Akina-chan!
Eh? Wait...
And I thought I'd be able to
gently lead you on since I'm older.
Eh? Wait...
The only thing Natsumi
has above us are her boobs.
That's not true.
Sis!
I got to live under the same
roof as the three beautiful sisters.
I must be pretty lucky.
(Chalkboard: Shiki Haruomi)
Like an object buried in a volcanic eruption...
I thought no one would ever notice me.
I never thought something
like this would happen to me.
Not normally, anyway.
Do you have a moment?
Akina told me about you.
I'm Byakudan Midori.
This girl is my good friend,
Himenohara Suzuran.
Suzu, Akina and I are childhood friends.
Feel free to ask me
anything you want to know.
T-Thanks.
Haru-kun, let's have lunch!
It's the first time I made your
packed lunch, so I did my best.
Both of you really get along.
Be careful though.
Akina's the school idol.
Try not to make too many enemies.
I did promise I'd accompany
Akina to her club activities...
...but where's the pool?
Though Akina really has a great body...
There's just no way she'd be in a bikini.
Though“.
What was that all about?
I suppose Akina's really trying her best.
I guess I'll go to the bathroom.
So this is what they call the city rush hour.
Despite yesterday, I'm glad I came here.
W-Wait, Haru-chan's not here...
I-it's poking my butt.
Haru-chan, what should I do?
S-Sorry, I'll move away.
I'm sorry, I was pushed.
Haru-kun, don't move.
At this rate...
If a guy gets an erection, he won't
calm down until he comes, right?
I'll help you come.
Huh?!
Shhh, people will notice if you're loud.
How does this feel?
Akina, where did you learn all this?
Oh, no, it's between my legs!
Crap, Akina, this feels so good!
Haru-kun, don't... don't rub there!
Your thing is amazing, Haru-kun,
it's going in and out of my skirt.
I'm coming!
Wait, Haru-kun!
I did it.
Sorry, Akina, I couldn't stop myself.
Haru-kun, do I have to drink this?
What?
I wonder if Akina's mad about
what happened this morning?
Things turned out that way,
but I guess that makes us even.
Though, I had no idea
Haru-kun was that big down there.
Ahhh, what on earth am I thinking about?!
A-Akina, sorry about this morning.
W-Whoa!
T-That's right, some of
your stuff got on my uniform.
It's going to be so hard to get it off!
Huh?
Geez, you're such a dummy!
Hey, be careful!
Akina!
Ahhh, Akin-chan's late!
Geez.
You should be more careful.
Haru-kun, thanks.
So much has happened today, I'm exhausted.
I know it's a bad idea...
...but it can't hurt to look just a little longer.
You're peeping again.
M-Mafuyu...
Come in.
I... uh...
The peeping tom isn't allowed to move.
You got turned on from
watching me masturbate, right?
If you want me to keep this a
secret from Akina and the others...
...show me what you look
like when you come, Haruomi.
Hey, Mafuyu!
"When I come," you said?
It's gotten like this.
I'll help you.
Hey, Mafuyu...
Quiet.
Aren't I good? I learned it from books.
You're a pervert, Haruomi.
It's all hard from you being so excited.
You want more stimulation, right?
It's cold...
How's my foot?
Does it feel good?
I didn't think I was much of a masochist...
...but this feels good.
You're the kind of guy who gets
off by being stepped on by a girl.
How improper.
You want to come, don't you?
Don't you want to shoot all
that come that you've backed up'?
You're cute, Haruomi.
You're blushing deeply.
You're dick has gotten so big.
Go ahead, come.
Shoot all your thick come onto my leg.
C-Coming!
So this is... semen.
Man, that Mafuyu...
It felt good though.
Natsumi-san?
Tomorrow's a holiday...
...so I guess I'll go help Natsumi-san out a little.
T-This is...
Natsumi-san's store?
Haru-chan, thanks a lot.
No problem, you've
always taken good care of me.
Though, we're not
getting any customers at all.
Exactly!
After I took over the store,
we started losing customers!
Natsumi-san, it's spilling over...
But with the savings
Dad left us and this store...
...we're doing fine for now.
You don't need to worry, Haru-chan.
Natsumi-san has a curious appeal.
She's a little childish but she's also sexy.
After all, she's pretty and her boobs are huge.
That's right, it feels soft just like that.
Haru-chan, if you like my boobs that
much, how about squeezing them?
Natsumi-san?!
Haru-chan, you're so cute.
Natsumi-san, wait...
You have a boner already, Haru-chan?
Here, lay down.
You don't have to feel embarrassed.
It's my fault that you've become like this...
...so I have to take responsibility, right'?
Haru-chan, I want you to
feel good with my boobs.
Natsumi-san, this is bad...
Oh? Haru-chan, your dick has become really big.
Haru-chan, you really like boobs, don't you?
Amazing!
Natsumi-san, your boobs are so soft...
Haru-chan, the sight of your
stiff dick is making my heart race.
Coming, I'm coming, Natsumi-san!
Go ahead, go ahead and shoot your sperm!
So this is Haru-chan's stuff...
It's your fault that I've
gotten like this, Haru-chan.
You have to take responsibility, too.
Does that mean...
You have to have sex with me.
Eh?
Natsumi-san, it'll be bad if we go any further...
A-Amazing... so this is Haru-chan...
Natsumi-san, don't tell
me this is your first time?
You shouldn't worry about
trivial things like that, Haru-chan.
But...
Haru-chan, you're cute.
You can start moving.
Natsumi-san!
Haru-chan, your big dick is
twitching violently inside me!
Natsumi-san, are you about to come?
Yes...
You're reaching so deep
inside me, it feels so good!
Not there...
Excuse me.
Crap, it's a customer!
Natsumi-san?
Poof!
Natsumi-san, you smell of liquor!
Well, I said there's a customer.
Hey, Natsumi-san!
Several days have passed since then.
Nothing about Natsumi-san has changed.
Does this mean she doesn't remember?
Haruomi, you've been going
to Natsumi's store recently.
Do you like Natsumi that much?
It's not that I mind what you do, Haru-kun.
No, I mean, she's always been looking
out for me, so I just decided to help.
It's right in the middle of summer
and profits still haven't increased.
Oh yeah, Natsumi-san, don't you have a van?
How about turning it into an ice cream truck?
We can sell our ice cream at the crowded beach.
That sounds good!
Haruomi, you're pretty good once in a while.
Wow, Haru-kun, you're a hardworking boy!
Akina, stop treating me like a kid all the time.
Sorry.
I'm home.
Huh?
Akina didn't go to her club activities today?
Guess I'll go see how she's doing.
What kind of sleeping pose is that?
Geez.
A-Akina...
H-Haru-kun?!
Y-Yo.
What are you doing here?!
Huh? But you—
N-Never mind, sorry. I'll get out.
Wait!
Stay like this a little longer.
Don't be silly, that's enough.
We'll start feeling like it otherwise.
I don't mind.
Haru-kun, if you really do find me attractive...
To me, you're a wonderful
guy I want to be embraced by.
If you say anymore, I really
won't be able to hold back.
Yes, don't hold back.
Just like how you're not a little boy anymore,
I'm not a little girl anymore, either.
Akina...
Haru-kun!
Haru-kun, my uniform will get all crumpled.
O-Ok.
Akina.
Akina, could you go down on me?
Ok.
When I look up close,
it's pretty intimidating...
You don't have to force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself.
I'm just afraid I won't be good at it.
If it's you doing it, Akina,
I'd be happy no matter what.
Yes, right there.
It feels really good.
Really? I'm glad.
I'll do even more, ok?
I can't believe Akina would do this for me.
Akina, that's really good.
Crap, I'm com—
Sorry I came in your mouth.
No, I'm fine.
Did it feel good?
Yeah, it felt amazing.
Now it's your turn.
Haru-kun.
No, Haru-kun...
Akina, you're really wet.
That's because...
Akina...
I want to put it inside you, Akina.
Ok, put it in, Haru-kun.
It's in...
Does it hurt, Akina?
Y-Yes, for an instant.
But somehow my mind's all blank now.
Here I go, Akina.
O-Ok.
Akina, it feels way too good.
I'm... already gonna come!
Haru-kun, you're still so hard.
You haven't had enough yet, right?
Go ahead, I'm so happy that you
really feel this good with me, Haru-kun.
Akina.
Akina, you're squeezing real tight...
Haru-kun! Haru-kun!
Akina! Akina!
Haru-kun, I'm gonna come!
Let's come together, Akina!
Akina, your favoritism is way too obvious.
Haru-chan, did something
happen between you and Akina-chan?
N-Not really...
T-That's right, it's because Haru-kun has to
work hard to help in the store from now on...
Haru-kun, hurry! We'll be late!
The domestic Akina.
The generous Natsumi-san.
And the devilish Mafuyu.
Come on, let's go!
Oh, ok!
It looks like things will
get more fun from now on.