Orifushi
Finally arrived....
My name is Shiki Haruomi.
Various thing has happen and now I will live with Orifushi's family,
whose relatives from the past.
Huh, I'd already called before I came here though....
Did they go out at the garden....?
Good day~, It's Shiki!
Is anybody home?
Natsumi-san~, are you in home?
Sorry~ Mafuyu, did the door locked?
Mafuyu....?
Kanojo x Kanojo x Kanojo
Haru-kun, you can use this room.
This is your father's room, right? Are you sure I can use it?
Father & mother has been pass away since a long time ago....
I see....
Now with onee-chan, we're working hard in our shop.
Natsumi-san~
Haru-kun...., you're getting bigger.
Well, If compared than the last time we meet~ surely it has....
You're too....
Getting prettier?
Honestly, Akina-chan is definitely getting more cute than the past....
You're blushing....
Strangely, I'm getting trembled with this pace....
Once again, welcome Haru-kun!
You're late, Haruomi.
Long time no see, Haru-chan.
Em~, please look after me.
- Itadakimasu~
- You know.... It's wonderful~
Haru-chan, you should eat more.
It's because you're men, right?
Ah, yes. I'll enjoy it.
Em~, Natsumi-san? About the way you address me, It's embarrassing....
Eh, what's wrong with that?
I'm getting older right now~
But~, It's because Haru-chan is cute.
I'm awkward If you're saying cute....
But~, It's easy to called with Haru-chan.
With "chan"  is....
But~, with Haru-chan is more friendly.
But~~~~
No, It's enough....with that.
Are you finished yet? I have more than 12 reason~
Haru-chan, say ah~
No, Natsumi-san it's....
Please, Onee-chan. you're feeding Haru-kun too much.
Eh, Akina-chan. you're getting jealous?
Haru-chan, in three of us who's got your interest?
Eh? No, It's....
I understand, I'll try to open it!
As I thought, It's Akina-chan.
Eh~, please....
Maybe I'm much older, but I'll lead you with gentle....
Wait....
Natsumi only won in her large breast.
It's not like that....
Onee-chan!
Live under one roof with three beautiful sisters like this,
Maybe I'm the happiest person right now.
Though in the chance of a lifetime, there isn't possibly to meet one's fortune like this.
Surely I didn't think that myself would meet like that around here....
Wouldn't think about that, usually....
Can I talk with you?
I've heard the story from Akina. I'm Byakudan Midori,
She's the new recruitment, Himenohara Suzuraha.
Me & Suzu is Akina's friend from school club.
If you don't understand about something, you could ask anything to me.
You're....welcome.
Haru-kun, let's eat lunch together.
It's my first time working hard to make box lunch for you.
Honestly, you're really close each other.
But, you must be careful. Akina is an idol in this school.
So make sure, you don't make enemy here.
Though I promise to meet Akina after her school club over....
Where's the pool?
But, Akina is really got some style in it~
Something like that wouldn't unwearable though....
Still, what's really happen back there?
Akina's really working hard at her club too.
Think I'll go to the toilet....
So this is what they called train of a city, huh?
The thing about last night, I'm really glad for coming here....
Please, Haru-kun. in a place like this....
It's bumped against my butt~
Haru-kun, what we suppose to do~?
Sorry, I'll move right now....
So..Sorry, I've been pushed back.
Haru-kun, please don't move around.
It will be....
If this thing getting bigger, man should release it soon right?
I..I'll help you release it.
Shh! If your voice get too loud, It will be noticed!
Is it okay with this?
Akina, where you learn this....
No, no.... It's getting touch with Haru-kun's thing.
A..Akina, It's feeling good....
Haru-kun, no! It's getting....
Haru-kun's thing, It's wonderful. It's getting out from the skirt.
Coming out....!
Wa..Wait! Haru-kun!
It's out....
So..Sorry, Akina. I just feel....
Haru-kun, this is....
Shouldn't I drink this?
Yes?
Did Akina's angry about this morning?
After doing something like that....
It would called love, right?
Even so, Haru-kun's thing would be bigger like that~
What am I thinking right now?!
A..Akina, sorry about this morning.
Ri..Right! If your sperm dropped in your uniform,
It will be terrible!
Eh?
Haru-kun is idiot!!!!
Hey, It's dangerous....
Akina!!!!
Huh~, Akina-chan is very late....
Honestly....
Try to be careful, okay?
Ha..Haru-kun, thank you....
After a lot of thing happen, It's really tired today....
I know It's bad after all,
but just a little more it's alright....
You're still watching it, right?
Ma..Mafuyu....
Get in.
This is...., that....
You shouldn't move, when take a peek.
It's lucky to watching my onanism, right?
If you don't want me talking to akina & other,
Let me see your thing too.
Hey, Mafuyu....
My thing?
This thing become like this....
I'll help you with it.
Hey, mafuyu....
Quiet!
It's feel good, right?
Just admit it.
Haruomi, you're pervert.
Your expression tell's that you're tickling enough.
You want more stimulation, right?
Ugh, it's cold.
My leg, how is it?
It's feel good?
It's bad, I'm not that kind of "M" though....
It's feel good.
Man's habbit, with woman's leg they get pleasure so easily.
Unsightly, right.
You want to release it, right?
The sperm you hold it,
you want to full it out, right?
You're so cute, haruomi.
Getting red with all of this.
Your thing become big like this,
It's okay, just let it out.
Spurt to me, the sperm of love.
Use my leg to release it.
Co..Coming out....
This is the sperm....
That..Mafuyu....
But, It's really feel good~
Natsumi-san?
Tomorrow's holiday, think I'll go & help Natsumi-san.
Is..Is here Natsumi-san's shop?
Haru-chan, thank you so much~
No, since you're taking care of me everytime.
Even so, there isn't customer coming here....
That's right~! Since I taking over this shop, the customer is running away~
Na..Natsumi-san, It's flooding....
But, because there's some saving from father & there's this shop,
So it's fine for this time.
Haru-chan, don't have to worried about a thing.
Natsumi-san, surely have strange appeal inside her....
Despite of having childish side, but strangely can look so sexy....
After all, she's pretty & have large breast~
Right..right, feel soft like this....
Haru-chan, If you like breast that much....
Would you like to drink it?
Natsumi-san?!
Haru-chan, you're really cute~
A, Natsumi-san....
Please....
Haru-chan, you're already that big~
There, just stretch it out.
You don't have to be shy.
Because of me, your thing become this big.
I'll have to take responsibility, right.
Haru-chan, I'll let you feeling good with using my breast.
Natsumi-san...., this is bad.
What's you're saying, look how big Haru-chan's thing is.
Haru-chan really like breast, right.
This is great, Natsumi-san's breast feeling really soft~
When looking at Haru-chan's brawny thing,
I'm getting thumpity-tump too.
Coming out! It's coming out, Natsumi-san!!
It's fine, just let it all sperm out.
It's really fine.
This is Haru-chan's....
It's Haru-chan's fault that my thing getting like this,
You have to take responsibility.
And..that is?
You must have SEX with me.
Natsumi-san, more than this It would be bad.
It's..really great, this is Haru-chan's....
Natsumi-san, possibly this is your first time?
Haru-chan, don't have to think trivial matter at all.
But....
You're very cute, Haru-chan.
It's fine to move on.
Natsumi-san!
Haru-chan's big thing, flooding through inside me.
Natsumi-san, do you want to release it out?
Yes, Haru-chan's thing keep hitting inside of me.
It's feel good.
It's great~
Excuse me~
Terrible, It's customer!
Natsumi-san?
Ukh, Natsumi-san? Smell like alcoholic.
Wait, It's customer!
Please, Natsumi-san!
Several days after that,
It seem nothing changed with Natsumi-san.
She doesn't remember after all?
Haruomi, you're going to natsumi's shop recently.
Did you interested with Natsumi that much?
I don't mind at all,
not likely Haru-kun....
Not like that, I was helping just because she always take care of me.
It's already summer, but the sales didn't going well at all.
That's right, Natsumi-san have a car right?
Then, how about we're doing moving shop?
From us, we can gathering people around the seashore.
That's a good idea.
Haruomi, sometimes you're dependable.
That's great! Haru-kun is a good kid, right!
Akina, don't treat me like a kid all the time!
So..Sorry....
I'm home!
Eh?
Is Akina didn't come to school club today?
Let's take a look at her, for a moment.
What?!
What a terrible sleeping way....
Indeed~
A..Akina....
Eh, Ha..Haru-kun?!
He..Hey....
Why Haru-kun is here?!
Why you said, It's Akina who....
No, sorry....
I'll get out right now.
Wait!
Le..let's stay like this for a while....
I..Idiot! Cut it out!
It will be bad situation, right.
It's fine.
If Haru-kun really feel my appeal, at least I want you to hug me.
Like a wonderful man.
If you said like that, It can't hold anymore....
Yes, you don't have to hold it anymore.
Haru-kun is not a little boy anymore & I'm not a little girl too.
Akina....
Ha..Haru-kun!
Haru-kun, the uniform will get in the way.
Ye..Yes....
Akina....
Akina, would you lick my thing?
Yes....
Wo..Wow, If looked this close.
Kind of powerful, right.
If impossible, then just let it be.
It's not that imposible, but I don't know If it will be good.
If Akina who's doing that, I'll be happy whatever you do.
Yes, that way.
It's really feel good~
Really? I'm happy.
Then, I'll doing it more.
Akina, the way you're doing like this....
Akina, right there!
It's feel great.
Uh, not good....
It come out!
Sorry, It came out into the mouth.
Eh, It's fine.
You're feeling good, right.
Yes, It's really are....
Now, It's Akina's turn.
Ha..Haru-kun~
No, Haru-kun.
Akina, you're really wet down here.
It's because~
Akina, I want to put inside you.
Ye..Yes, It's fine.
Come in, Haru-kun.
It came in....
Is it hurts, akina?
Ye..Yes, It hurts....
Now It's over with it....
I'll move it, akina.
Ye..Yes....
Akina, It's really feel good!
I can't hold it....
Haru-kun, you're thing still this hard....
You want to release more, right.
It's fine, I'm happy to make you feel good.
Akina....
A..Akina, It's too great.
Haru-kun..Haru-kun~!
Akina..Akina~!
Haru-kun, I can't hold it anymore.
Let's come together, Akina!
Akina, you're looking Haruomi too much.
Haru-chan, there's anything happen with Akina?
It..It's nothing....
Tha..That's right,
From now on, Haru-kun will be working hard at the shop too.
Haru-kun, quickly!
We're gonna be late!
Household type, Akina.
Generous type, Natsumi-san.
Fearful type, Mafuyu.
Let's going!
Ye..Yes, okay!
From now on, It would be more delightful.