Internet and Manga Cafe
Excuse me,
can I have a moment?
Dicks, dicks!
Raw dicks!
I want it, I want it...
I want it!
Sayama-kun, will it still take time?
I can't wait for a real dick already.
My pussy's itching for it, it wants to be fucked now.
Here, I've brought a customer.
Oh no,
dicks, bring it here.
Here mister, old man,
I don't care who you are,
just give my hole here a date already.
He's a young man.
Mister dick, nice to meet you.
I'm Erika.
I'm going to let you use it for 1,000 yen,
so could you please pour your thick cum inside it?
Afterwards, would you be willing to take
a remembrance photo with me?
Don't worry, faces will remain hidden so please just go ahead!
Okay? Please, oh please already.
Is this part of a hidden cam show?
No, she's just a pervert.
Also, it's actually my hobby to film her having
sex with men she doesn't know.
Not yet? Still not yet?
Is mister's dick not coming yet?
She has sex with just about anyone.
#2 Sakurai Erika does not fall in love
Put it in, put it in, put it in!
My raw, wet and steaming pussy is going to take your dick in.
Th-Then, I'm really going raw, okay?
Hurry, hurry!
Your dick, your dick is going inside!
Hey, lower your voice.
But, it feels so good having it inside me.
Hey mister, do you feel happy?
Are you happy with my pussy?
Y-Yes!
I never thought that my first partner
would be this cute, erotic, and feisty!
So this is your remembrance pussy.
Just do whatever you want with it.
Okay, move now.
There, that's good, that's good.
I can feel it!
It's your first time, but you're good.
We might be compatible with each other.
Damn!
You're really cumming inside now!
It's getting even harder as it cums.
I was surprised by how you came inside me.
Hey, one more, do it once more!
Wait, don't...!
Your pumping cum really fast!
I'm really going to moan loudly with this!
I'm going to moan a lot more, so please
stifle it with a dick, Sayama-kun.
Hurry, I'm going to moan loudly if he cums again.
I'm going to treat you to my mouth pussy.
Sayama-kun, your dick feels...
Your dick is... your dick is...
So this is Sakurai's mouth pussy...
It feels very warm.
Does it feel good?
Oh, its secreting pre-cum all while I'm getting
fucked by someone I don't know.
Yeah, it's the worst.
Mister, you can still cum inside me, right?
Oh wow!
It just came earlier, but it's still fucking me like crazy!
Hey, you're moaning.
No, it's okay even if he cums deep inside me.
I'm about to..!
Cum, cum!
Let your dick cum!
Now then, relax.
This mister was really something.
Your first-time experience in my mouth pussy also felt great.
I'm getting used to this now.
It was really hard to clean up afterwards.
Sayama-kun, you're quite weird.
Guys would usually go crazy just to get the chance to 'do it', right?
Yeah.
But you're still helping me out even though
I've never really let you fuck me even once.
It's really weird.
W-We'll, that's...
Of course, that's because I still like you even now.
Your last partner for this summer vacation has arrived.
Yeah.
I'm going to prepare now, okay?
Oh, just wait.
Eh?!
Your pu-s-sy.
Mister?
If you don't let me fuck you in here even once,
you won't be able to live here anymore.
Stop that, please.
Oh, oh, oh?
Erika, I see you're already quite prepared.
Were you expecting it?
N-No, this is... this is not...!
You say "Please fuck the perverted me," at this part.
Say it now.
No, no...!
No!
I understand.
I, the perverted Erika,
please... fuck me.
Sakurai?
No... no!
Now... let my raw dick kiss your raw pussy.
No, don't...!
I said don't...!
Oh? I see that you've been doing it with another guy.
A boyfriend, perhaps?
N-No, that's not it!
I... I was masturbating...!
I won't be able to...
I won't be able to go back anymore!
My insides are a total mess.
I'm going... I'm going crazy!
Sex... sex..!
Sex is just so amazing!
Shall this old man give you more of it then?
Here, Erika-chan, I'll cum inside.
l-will-cum-inside.
Oh wow...!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
You mustn't cum inside!
Maybe I can impregnate you if it comes out thick enough.
No, anything but that!
That was very warm.
No way, you just came earlier!
One round is never enough, you know.
I'm going to pump every last drop of
my cum inside you before I go home.
No, no!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Well then, Erika-chan, till next month, okay?
Sakurai...
Are you alright?
Somehow... somehow...
I'm fine if you're going to be my personal cameraman,
oh, and no sex, okay?
That's our first kiss.
And it was right after having sex with an old guy.
Hey, Kazu-kun.
Oh, what is it?
Let's... have sex.
It's been like this because it wants to be fucked by you.
Let's have memorable lovey-dovey sex together.
I've been holding you at bay until now.
This lovey-dovey dick,
it's... inserted all the way in!
What in the world is this?
What is this?
Kazu-kun, your dick is really bulging.
I'm sorry, Erika!
This dick... your dick...
It's confessing inside my womb.
I love it, I love it.
Kazu-kun, Kazu-kun... do it more...
Give it all... push it all the way through!
Kazu-kun!
Erika, am I doing sex right?
You are.
You're doing it right.
More than any other big dick,
and my womb is really happy with it!
It's saying that it wants your cum.
I'm going to let out all of my frustrations with this one!
Then I'll apologize for it!
I apologize to this dick, I'm really sorry!
Erika, Erika!
Kazu-kun, I like you... I love you!
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
Oh no, oh no,
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I love you... I love it...
Kazu-kun, thank you...
Sakurai Erika then quit school on the first day of the next term,
and disappeared.
I probably won't meet her again.
Such conviction ensnared me.
To my beloved Kazu-kun.
Are you doing well?
I'm sorry if this too sudden
I went to a lot of places
sampling and testing a lot of dick
along the way
She went away like the wind,
along with my first love.