No... this isn't good, sensei.
Please, stop...
Huh?
I like you!
Sakurai Erika,
the girl that I like the most in the entire world.
Please don't push it in too hard!
Sensei, its tip is rubbing me...!
Oh no... don't...!
Its tip is...
Stop.
Stop...
Please, stop...
Just a while ago,
I confessed my feelings to Sakurai-san.
I appreciate your feelings.
But before I give my answer,
I want to show you something.
Huh?
After those words, she then proceeded to do it with that guy.
Sensei,
discipline me.
Please discipline your naughty student.
I get it.
Sensei...
It's big...!
She has sex with just about anyone.
#1 Cum insider, top class student, Sakurai Erika
Oh wow...
Sensei, you're still amazing, as usual.
It feels hard and it's big!
Stop.
I shouldn't do this, and yet...
Your dick is stirring me inside,
and I really feel horny even though I shouldn't be!
Stop already...
I'm... this is just...
Amazing,
your raw dick is rubbing me inside!
Sensei, your dick is amazing!
I'm going to get pregnant!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
She, who is usually meek and doesn't stand out in class,
is having sex right now in front of me.
And...
This is also my first time being with her.
Sayama-kun, you're the first one to have ever confessed to me.
Huh?
I wanted to show you that side of me for the record,
because the real me...
... really~ loves sex.
The real...
The real Sakurai.
I try to act like the woman of a man's dreams
and then have sex with them.
I also have quite a number of sex friends.
As for you, Sayama-kun,
there are also other girls who look docile
but are actually sex maniacs.
So don't be easily fooled, okay?
Oh, oh?
Th-This is...
So it smells like this.
Cumming while watching the girl you
like getting fucked by someone else...
You're quite the pervert too, Sayama-kun.
You're one to talk.
Yup, we're both perverts.
So, would you like to be in a perverted relationship with me?
Eh?!
Sakurai's not good with gadgets and stuff,
but she sure desires doing it with as many men as possible,
and treating them like her toys.
Erika-chan,
shall we begin then?
Yes.
I thought it was an outrageous idea at first,
but I, who was so desperate to be by her side,
allowed myself to become her personal cameraman,
neither as her boyfriend nor as her sex friend.
I-I'm scared, mister...
Damn, she's getting done by that old guy.
I was really surprised,
when Eiko-chan came to me and tried
to negotiate the rent for the kids.
Because of that, I now get to do it often
with a cute girl such as yourself.
It feels like a dream.
Mister, if you keep on playing with my nipples like that...
I wonder which of your nipples is more sensitive?
Is it this one?
No, it's neither of them!
I'm getting really aroused!
Now then, let me cover you with this
old man's lotions, and my own cum.
Look, your breasts are all sticky.
See? All sticky.
Hurray.
There, that's good, Erika-chan.
Just keep it up and make this old man happy.
It feels cold and slippery.
That feels great.
Amazing...
This hot and stiff dick feels good.
This feels really good, sir.
It feels great for me too, Erika-chan.
Mister, your naughty thing is...
It feels like it's getting stiffer.
Well, you do have to be grateful for your benefactor's dick.
Please, use your dick however you want.
Please give me every last drop of its fluids.
Yes, of course, Erika-chan.
I'll make sure to cum lots on you.
It felt so good, that I just can't stop cumming.
Sa-Sakurai... -san...
Well then, I'll be seeing you again next month.
You can come out now.
Sakurai, I'll wipe it off for you.
The landlord agreed that he wouldn't go all the way,
we usually just do it halfway.
You also weren't able to cum, right?
How can you tell?
I can tell just by its scent,
because you're a pervert.
But, you're also...
Look,
as reward for holding it in, I'll let you touch
my pussy and unload your cum on it.
Well?
How does your first pussy feel?
It's wet with cum and love fluids already, right?
Sa-Sakurai...!
Were you fapping earlier?
Fapping while watching me, the one you like,
while she gave a blowjob to an old man?
Did it feel good?
This feels good.
The mere thought of being unable to fuck you with my dick,
makes it feel like it's going to burst.
What a pervert.
You still have to hold it in a bit longer,
so that you can squirt out all of your built up cum on my pussy.
You're amazing, Sakurai.
Your pussy is starting to get really wet
and make sloppy, erotic sounds.
Oh yes...
I'm getting really horny and wet from watching
my classmate fap in front of me!
Hey, can I cum?
L-Let's...
Let's cum together.
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum!
Me too...!
Squirt it, squirt it on me!
Squirt lots of cum on me!
Oh crap!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
So Sayama-kun's cum tastes like this.
We really are perverts.
Sa-Sakurai...
From that point on,
Sakurai never got a break from sex.
The plays we did started to get more and more extreme.
Sayama-kun, hurry!
We're filming outside today,
and we're going to find really sweaty dicks for our video!
Hey, Sayama-kun.
Do you think I can hunt down any prey I want with this outfit?
I bet anyone would love doing it with you in that.
Then my transformation's a big success.
Peace, peace!
Dick hunt, successful!
BEWARE OF
MANHOLES
I'm digging in...!
You're sucking too hard, lady!
H-Hey, you...
It, it feels really good, but is this really okay?
It's alright.
She's just your average pervert.
Whoa, is that for real?
I'm about to cum!
Miss, can you do it to us too?
Please~?
Oh wow, I'm touching myself while sucking his dick all the way!
Hey, how do I look?
It looks really perverted, Sakurai.
Dicks like these really are the best!
It's so stiff, so full, and pungent.
This is the best.
It feels like it's going to get sucked into your throat.
Hey, it's taking too long, lemme switch!
Let me join too!
Okay, okay!
There sure are lots of dicks.
I'm really happy!
I really am.
All of your dicks are big, and really hot.
I want to drink all of your cum already!
You're going overdrive with the perverted play, Sakurai.
I can't stop!
Cum, cum, just cum it all out already!
Wow, miss, you're really hardcore!
All of your dicks are the best!
Next dicks, please.
I'm not satisfied with just sucking anymore!
Wow, she suddenly took it in!
Sayama-kun, this dick is amazing!
W-Wow...
Your pussy is being opened wide.
Sayama-kun, make sure that you clearly
record the part where I'm being fucked.
It's already about to burst.
I just can't stop, Sakurai.
It's okay.
It's okay to build it up.
Just keep on fucking me.
I also want it there, I want it in my ass too!
Then I'll go.
I'll take this one here.
So this is an ass pussy.
Look, Sayama-kun!
See how all of these dicks squirt their thick cum inside me,
and record it!
I'm about to...!
I'm cumming inside...
Cumming inside feels great!
It feels really good.
That was refreshing.
Man, now I'm no longer a virgin.
Now I can work harder tonight.
Anal sex sure feels awesome.
Sayama-kun, you sure came a lot today.
Pervert.
The same goes for you.
H-Hey,
isn't our next location a bit too risky?
Net cafe sex, now I'm really excited!
Somebody...
Please... make a mess of me...