Haru-kun, not here...
Akina.
My sisters will find out.
Haru-kun...
If you touch me like that, I'll...
Like this?
Yeah.
Rub it just like that.
Your dick is so big, the tip's poking out.
Akina, your boobs are really big too.
It feels so good.
Coming, coming!
Haru-kun, did it feel good?
Yeah. Akina, keep going just like that.
Your come is making
my boobs all slippery, Haru-kun.
Akina, I just came, if you lick there I'll...
EPISODE 2 -
The City: Restroom, Infirmary and Maid Paradise
What did you come here for, Honnouji?
This guy here is Honnouji Tsukasa.
For better or worse, he's a frivolous person.
Actually, he's more of a
troublesome classmate.
I wonder why he keeps sticking around me.
That's not it, it's pretty bad, Haruomi.
101 Ice Cream has finally
extended its reach to this district!
Right.
It's 101, man.
101'?
Good afternoon, Honnouji-kun.
P-Princess Akina!
Why are all three of you together?
I heard there's a 101 shop around here.
I was shopping so I came to take a look.
She also wanted to
see how you were doing.
So, what about 101?
It's no joke.
It's the big shot in the industry in
terms of sales and market power.
Now that you mention it,
your family runs a chain of ice cream shops.
Our No. 1 spot in Tanabata district... it's over...
My status and prestige as the son of
the CEO of Haagen-Dazs is also...
You never had status
or prestige in the first place.
You're just someone who
provides comic relief once in a while.
And? Where will this 101 open?
There!
What?!
You're serious?
Well then, Haru-kun, we're going to take a look.
Let's go, Suzu.
Is that rain?
I've got enough on my hands
just from preparing for my exams...
...but things seem to be taking a turn for the worse.
I'm gonna piss in my pants!
Crap, I need the bathroom!
S-Sorry, Himenohara!
You all... right?
What?!
Himenohara, wait-
Hang on, Honnouji.
Do you really think it's ok to bring
something like this into school?
You're almost as delicious as Princess
Akina when you're angry, Class Rep!
Why, you!
Himenohara, s-stop that...
You actually had that inside
you the whole time during class?
And don't tell me that was
also the case the other day...
It feels good, but you don't have to this.
I won't tell anyone about it.
Do this with someone you like instead.
Penstemon.
P-Penste... what?
Stop, Himenohara,
you shouldn't go any further-
There's no other way.
I've gotta end this quickly.
Himenohara, you're too loud...
Crap, this is bad...
I'm gonna come inside-
Haru-kun, what's wrong?
You're spacing out.
N-Nothing.
Haru-chan, are you tired?
N-No.
Oh yeah, it looks like there'll
be a new 101 store nearby.
Their ice cream is really good.
Hang on sis, they'll be our business rivals.
They're huge, you know?
Really?
Then we'll have to think of something.
Mafuyu, you should think of something too.
Haru-kun!
What are you talking about you voyeur?
Voyeur?
L-it's nothing, nothing at all.
Mafuyu is thinking of
all sorts of ideas too, yeah.
Damn you, Mafuyu.
(Making The Highest Quality Ice Cream)
What the hell?
This should do it.
Today just isn't my day.
It's her.
Natsumi-san, I'm taking the trash out.
Oh, Haru-chan, that's...
That's the job Natsumi assigned to me.
Really?
But it will be easier if I help you, right?
Gross.
Off I go.
Nice!
Princess Akina really is the best!
Dude...
Thank goodness you're a big guy, Haru.
Hey, you!
That's enough of that!
Hey, Class Rep...
Himenohara isn't around, by the way...
Just what do you think you're filming?!
What's wrong with you?
Seriously, guys...
Haru-kyun, it hurts.
A beauty's smile is worth a thousand pieces of gold.
Well then, off to the infirmary.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Infirmary
Excuse me...
Do you have any bandages I could...
Huh?
The nurse isn't here.
Is someone there?
It's Himenohara.
Wait, what does she think she's holding?!
This is bad if someone were to see this!
Wait, Shiki-kun.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Um, I-l...
Wait, don't get the wrong idea. Let me explain!
It's fine. I understand.
I know.
You and Suzu...
mat school ..
Don't you already have Akina?
Himenohara and I are just-
Please, just break up with Suzu.
Of course, I'm not asking you to do it for nothing.
I'll give you whatever you want.
What I want?
You want to have sex, right?
Sex?! Byakudan, what...
You're not going anywhere, Shikikun.
I'll prove it to you right here.
Wait-
Look.
Your penis has gotten so big!
W-Wait, this is-
You would get just as turned on
even if your partner wasn't Suzu, right?
S-Shiki-kun, you'd do it
with anyone, as long as it was a girl.
Don't tell me you...
W-What? At least, I know how to do this.
T-This man's dick...
...it's so big and hot...
My body's so hot...
No, I'm losing my mind...
B-Byakudan?
B-Byakudan, I'm coming, holy crap-
You came this much but you're still not satisfied?
Byakudan,enough“.
Come, Shiki-kun.
I'll definitely make you forget Suzu.
Geez, what's with you?
Shiki-kun, you brute, that's-
Not there!
You're all wet.
Here I go.
Come, I'll be sure to satisfy your huge penis.
Byakudan, you’re actually a...
This is nothing.
Gotcha.
Here I go...
This is awesome, I can't stop...
So this is what it's like to have sex with a guy?
It feels good...
It's not what you think it is!
It's...
Don't tell me you heard everything?
Eh? No!
Wait, Shiki-kun!
No, no, Suzu!
No, don't! Suzu!
Himenohara, that feels-
Crap! I'm c-coming!
Kanojo X Kanojo X Kanojo
I'm home.
So you're home.
Must be puberty.
What was that?
House of Three Immoral Sisters
What the heck is this?
You like it?
Mafuyu!
Turned on?
N-No.
Punishment.
Hey Mafuyu...
What's the meaning of this?
Don't resist.
R-resist?
Resist what?
Haruomi, you're not interested in things like that?
Wanna do it with me?
Like I could?
You scared?
No, that's not the problem here.
Look, Haruomi...
What's this about?
That was... from before...
if you listen to what I say,
I'll make you feel even better.
Where did you learn this from?
It's not healthy to hold back.
You're dick is all hard, Haruomi.
Doesn't it feel good?
How about this?
That silky feeling, crap!
Haruomi, you're dick is all red.
You're trying too hard.
What a cute expression.
You're ready to come?
Mafuyu, wait!
You came already?
You're so cute, Haruomi.
You're a beast, Haruomi.
It's still standing high.
What a strange taste.
Mafuyu, could you untie me?
It's fine, stay still.
Amazing! What's with this?
The way she sucks is no joke!
Here.
M-Mafuyu?
Can you take it?
You're about to feel even better.
Isn't it your first time?
Don't force yourself.
I'll be fine.
You be quiet, Haruomi.
Show me your face when
you feel good, Haruomi.
Mafuyu!
It's fine, don't move!
Geez, you're always so forceful.
Here, I'll make you feel good.
Haruomi!
You're getting wet down there.
You feel good?
Not really.
That's not cute at all.
You're the cheeky one, Haruomi.
What are you doing?
In that case, I'll ask your body instead.
Well, Haruomi?
You're gonna come, right?
You're still going on about that?
Looks like I'll have to punish you for being cheeky!
Haruomi...
My pussy feels so hot!
You're finally being honest.
Just a little more!
Mafuyu, I'm coming!
Haruomi, harder, harder!
Coming!
I'm coming, Mafuyu!
Geez.
You didn't have to force yourself.
You'd be cuter if you were a little more honest.
M-Morning.
You're up pretty early today.
What's the matter?
Packed lunch.
Packed lunch?
I'm making your packed lunch.
What?
Oh yeah, a countermeasure against 101.
I haven't thought of any ideas.
Haruomi, what's the meaning of this?
What?
You, of all people, went to the
beach with these three goddesses?
What do you mean, "of all people"?
Why didn't you invite me too?!
Princess Akina, Natsumi-tan
and Mafuyu-tan, all in bikinis!
Honnouji.
You're going to be misjudged badly for this.
Well? What's the main subject?
What do you think of these?
They're like maid outfits but
I don't think I've seen them before.
Though, don't you think
they're a little too revealing?
Actually, I made these.
What?!
Haruomi, this is a once in a lifetime request.
I'll even give you my video cam.
Please record a video of Natsumi-san
and the others in these outfits for m-
I mean, you...
Oh? Hang on...
Okay, I accept.
Oh, um...
W-We'll sell ice cream in these outfits?
Ah, they're so cute!
Why do they fit us perfectly?
What our shop lacks is impression.
That's why we'll definitely be
successful with things this impactful!
But don't these clothes
look like they're from a sex shop?
N-Not at all!
They're really cute.
You can wear this, Haruomi.
Well then, let's go ahead
and try this on the next holiday!
You can't be serious, Sis!
Welcome!
We're currently having a promotional
campaign here at MinMin Ice Cream!
MinMin Ice Cream is currently doing a promotion!
Please form a line.
Today, you can have double the
vanilla ice cream for the regular price!
Well then, I'll have a double
vanilla ice cream cone.
Right, vanilla it is.
Enjoy!
Thank you very much!
SOLD OUT TODAY!
We did it, Sis!
We did it, Akina-chan!
Haruomi's about to die.
Akina, I'm coming in!
You really like it, don't you?
Haru-kun, you should at least knock!
You don't need to hide it.
It looks really great on you, Akina.
Haru-kun...
Haru-kun, you worked really hard today.
I'll be your exclusive maid for the rest of today.
Haru-kun, this is a little embarrassing...
My maid, Akina, is attending to me today.
Y-Yes.
You're so hot down here, Haru-kun.
Akina, your fellatio is amazing.
It feels so damn good when
you wrap your tongue around me.
Will you make me come, Akina?
Yes, use my mouth to feel even better.
I'm coming, Akina!
Akina...
N-No, not there...
The way you use your hands is really perverted!
You're all swollen down here.
Since when did you become
such a perverted girl, Akina?
That's not true at all.
Akina, amazing.
You're so wet.
Hey, can you hear it?
No more, Haru-kun! No more!
Put it in!
Here I go.
Akina, it's so hot inside you.
It feels like I'm gonna melt!
I'm coming, Akina!
Haru!
It's so deep...
Your big dick is reaching so deep inside me!
Akina, I'm coming again!
You can't, didn't you just come inside me?
Haru-kun, you're coming inside too much!
It's too much!
Akina, I'm coming again!
Your come is overflowing out of me, Haru-kun!
Amazing, it's nice and slippery from all the come!
I'm- this is bad!
I can't anymore, Haru-kun!
I'm coming too!
Akina!
Amazing, I came this much!
Geez, Haru-kun, you try too hard.
Akina, it's fine-
Huh?!
Haru-chan's dick is hard as ever!
I'm going after Natsumi.
What?
Natsumi-san, did you forget about-
Oh no, Haru-chan, that's a secret.
Haruomi, I'm going next.
Haru-kun is mine!
This is punishment for keeping it from us.
You shouldn't sneak ahead.
Well then, Haru-chan.
Let the service begin.