Alright! I got you now!
Oh no! I'm gonna lose! I'm gonna lose! I'm gonna lose!
Aw, who would've thought I'd lose at a shooting game!
As punishment, you have to do whatever I say today!
Y-Yeah, yeah!
I just have to do whatever you ask, right?
Alright then, try these on!
Wh-What are these? Cat ears?
When my girlfriend puts on cat ears
Oh! They look great on you, just like I thought!
Cute girls look great in whatever they have on!
I had intended on making you treat
me to a full course french meal...
That's why I bought an outfit to match the ears!
H-Hey! Don't look so closely, you idiot!
Huh? Haruna, you don't have a tail.
Ah, well I didn't know how to put it on.
Hehehe, well you see...
No! What are you doing?!
I've got to loosen it up a bit or it won't go in.
No! Something like that can't possibly go in my ass!
It'll just be more dangerous if you resist.
No! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Ow! Don't stick it in!
No! Ahh!!!
There! It's already all the way in!
It's... in my ass...
It feels really weird.
Ah, this is great, Haruna!
That expression is really cute!
H-Hey! Why are you filming this?
Don't worry, it's okay! I won't show this to anyone.
I'll just use it for masturbation later.
You idiot! What are you thinking?! You're a pervert, Shogo!
You promised to do whatever I said today, right?
You promise? Don't show anyone!
Don't stream it on the internet either!
Yeah, of course I won't!
Well then, do you want to try posing?
L-Like this?
Stick out your hips a bit more! And try parting your legs.
Geez! You had the costume and the camera all ready to go!
You probably practiced some games in secret too, didn't you?
Of course! I'll have my cake and eat it too!
You've made me take you out to eat so many times.
I've gotta get some payback once in a while!
W-Well, excuse me! I'm sorry. I apologized, so...
Th-That's enough, isn't it? Let me off, already!
Okay, I have just one more request then!
Are we really going to do this?
Hardly anyone is around at this time, and
you won't stand out since it's dark out.
B-But... going outside in an outfit like this...
Well, it's not so much going out, as it is going to
the convenience store right down the street.
It'll be fine!
No-Nobody's out there, right?
Well then! Get a move on!
Hey! Not so loud!
Geez.. Shogo really is a jerk!
I'm so not going to challenge him at any more games!
Th-This sucks! What is this? This tail is rather heavy.
It keeps swaying with each step I take.
It's scraping me on the inside.
J-Just going down the stairs
...feels so weird.
This is the 5th floor, can I even make
it all the way to the bottom?
Nope... it's impossible!
If someone finds me dressed like this, I...
No! You've got it all wrong! Th-This is just a punishment game!
I'm not actually into this sort of thing! No!
Stop! Don't do that!
I'm not a pervert!
I'm not getting turned on by you doing this to me!
Ah, it's no use. They won't believe me
no matter what I say at this point.
Causing a fuss is just going to draw in more people.
I just have to keep my mouth shut and do what I'm told.
P-Please. I'll take care of you all with my hands and mouth, so...
Please let me off with just this.
If I get raped by so many people...
I'll be destroyed.
I have to satisfy them with just this somehow.
I'm all covered tin something hot and sticky.
It smells really lewd.
Doing this is making me horny, too.
What should I do?
No one was satisfied after cumming just once.
S-Save me! Save me, Shogo!
It's no use! I'm not gonna make it all the
way to the bottom! Time to head back!
Oh no! Someone is coming down! This is bad!
Oh no, oh no, oh no! I'm going to be seen at this rate!
I'm going to be labeled a pervert!
If I just take off the cat ears...
I-It won't come out!
A-All at once...
I'll pull it out in one go!
Ha-Haruna... What are you doing?
Sh-Shogo...
You idiot! Jerk!
Jerk jerk jerk! You're a jerk, Shogo!
I thought you'd come back crying right away.
You did really well.
Th-That's right! I did my best!
H-Hey! Shogo...
Where... where are you touching?
Your pussy is really wet, Haruna!
D-Don't!
Don't touch me there right now!
You got turned on by the thought that
someone might see you, right?
Y-You jerk! No! I didn't!
No!
Just be honest with yourself!
If you beg me while adding a meow
to the end of your sentences...
...then I'll do whatever makes you feel good, Haruna!
Ah! Y-You idiot! As if I'd ever do something like that!
Will you do it? Or not?
Th-This guy... He only goes all out during times like these.
No, don't!
Oh no... What should I do?
I just got done doing that, so it feels a lot better than usual.
Perverted juices just keep on flowing out.
My pussy is throbbing, and I can't stand it any longer!
I-I want to fuck.
I-I want to have sex, m-meow!
Okay!
Now listen up.
Me doing this for you is a one time deal.
We won't be doing this on a regular basis.
Yeah, I know. Come on, beg one more time.
Sh-Shogo, I...
I want to be fucked, meow!
I Want you to stick your cock in me, Shogo, meow!
Mm! Good job!
This feels incredible!
Sh-Sho... go...
N-No! Don't!
Don't suck on my tits so hard!
Stop! It's too embarrassing!
Just as I thought. Shogo is rougher than
usual during sex when he goes all out.
It feels really good.
What should I do? I might actually be into this sort of thing.
I feel so horny that I can't help myself!
No! Don't stick it in so far!
Ah! Your cock is hitting me all the way in the back!
No! No! No!
Shogo's cock is so long!
If he fucks me so deeply right off the bat...
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming. He's going to make me cum!
Don't tell me, Haruna... did you cum without me just now?
Sorry!
I came! I already came!
Hehe, then I've gotta punish you. Should I stick the tail back in?
Ah, y-you idiot! Don't do that!
Don't worry! You're wet all the way
up to your ass with love juice!
I said no! I don't want it in my ass anymore!
You forgot to add meow to the end
of your sentence, so no can do!
I-It's scraping me on the inside.
His cock and the tail are rubbing about on my insides...
Th-This is a first for me. It feels like I'm going to lose my mind!
How does it feel getting fucked roughly like
you like it for a second time, Haruna?
You're a jerk, Shogo! Pervert!
I never thought you'd get so horny from your ass, Haruna.
I had no idea!
N-No! Don't say that!
It's so embarrassing!
Alright then, how about doing something like this next?
What are you doing...? Ah, No! Stop!
Everyone can see! I'm completely exposed!
But you see... that's what feels so good about it.
Your pussy is tightening up a lot, Haruna!
I... This feels really good.
While wearing cat ears and a tail...
Even though everyone is going to see
me in such an embarrassing getup...
...I'm really horny!
No! Don't thrust into me so hard!
Even my boobs are getting roughed up!
My nipples are erect and still rock hard!
Haruna, this feels really good!
You're doing an amazing job too, Shogo!
I really love the side of Shogo's personality
where he goes all out!
I feel like I'm going to lose consciousness.
I'm done for, Shogo!
I'm going to cum! It feels like I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!!
You jerk! Don't pull on the tail!
My ass... My ass is going to turn inside out!
I won't let you cum at the end if you don't talk like a cat!
G-Geez, Shogo! I'll get you back for this later!
Okay, Haruna, here we go for round three of rough sex!
It feels good... It feels so good!
It's no use! It's embarrassing, but I can't hold back any longer!
If it feels that good, make sure to beg nice and good!
Good... It feels so good, meow!
Your cock is amazing, Shogo, meow!
My pussy getting fucked this much
is making me want to cum, meow!
Haruna, that was cute! You're so cute, Haruna!
I said it, meow! I begged you properly, meow!
Please, meow! Let me cum, Shogo! Let me cum already, meow!
Haruna! Haruna! Haruna, Haruna, Haruna!
Ah, amazing! This is incredible, meow!
Your cock is getting bigger and bigger, meow!
My pussy is getting fucked all the way to the back, meow!
My pussy is getting stirred up along with my ass, meow!
That's good, Haruna! More! Say something else!
Wh-Whatis this, meow? What's up with this sex, meow?
Even though it's my first time, meow...
It feels so, so good, meow!
I'm about to cum!
Me too, I'm going to cum, meow!
I'm going to cum, meow!
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow!
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow!
Meow~!
Aw man! That was really good, Haruna!
I still have a ton of cosplay outfits!
I wonder which one we should try next!
Shogo... How long are you going to let this go to your head?!
Wait a second, but...
Grrr, Meow!!!
Here you go, Haruna!
This is the newest fruit trifle that just came out!
Aw, come on! You just keep buying
me convenience store sweets!
Set it down over there!
It can't be helped! No other stores are open this late.
I totally intend to have you take me out a ton this weekend!
Go figure... are you still angry?
Of course I am! My asshole still hurts!
Sorry, sorry! But hold on a second...
It felt a bit natural, didn't it?
Y-Yeah, I guess...
I can go along with that act if it's only once in a while...
Come again?! Really now?!
D-Don't get the wrong idea! It didn't really
feel good or anything like that!
And it isn't like I got horny either! It was nothing like that at all!
Even though I said that...
I got into the habit of doing it.
I'm... walking outside in my birthday
suit... in this embarrassing outfit...
If someone finds me this time around,
I'm totally going to get raped.
I'm going to get caught!
It's no use! I can't do it!
Oh no! I'm already dripping wet down there.
I got horny doing something so embarrassing!
The thought of someone seeing me...
...It gets me excited, and it feels so incredibly good.
It makes me even hornier than usual!
Ah! Could it be that I...
...I want to be seen.
Me masturbating... in all of my indecency...
I just might want someone to witness it all.
Oh, boy! What am I going to do with myself?
I can't help myself!
H-Hey, Haruna...!
You shouldn't moan so loud!
Its all good! You'll come to my rescue when
push comes to shove, right, Shogo?
O-Of course I will, but...
If you're so worried about me...
...then fuck me before I get raped by someone else, Shogo!
Come again?! Right here?!
Yeah! I want you to stick your cock in me, Shogo, meow!
I want you to fuck my perverted ass silly, meow!
Ha-Haruna...!
Ah, amazing!
It feels like I'm going to cum straight away, meow! Meow!
I never would've imagined... that you'd
be so into this sort of thing, Haruna!
For pete's sake! Whose fault do you think this is, meow?
It's all on you! It's all your fault, Shogo, meow!
Th-This is great!
Your cat sex-play is fantastic, Haruna!
Meow!
Your cock is getting bigger and bigger, meow!
You sure are a pervert, Shogo, meow!
You too, Haruna... We're two birds of a feather!
Meow, meow, meow, meow!
Me-yow! Meow, meow, meow meow!
Meow! Meow, meow, Me-yow!
Meow, meow! I'm... a pervert, too! Meow!
Fucking outside, and sticking something
in my ass while being fucked...
...they both feel so good, meow!
More! I want to do even more lewd things, meow!
Meow! Me-yow! Meow, meow, meow, meow!
I'm at my limit already... I'm going to cum!
Meow, meow, meow, meow! Meow...
Me-yow! Me-yow! Me-yow! Me-yow! Me-yow! Me-yow!
Me-yow!! Meyoww!!!
Your cock... has gotten hot... and is throbbing, meow!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
Inside of me, meow! Cum inside of me, meow!
Meow!! Meow! Meow...! Meow!! Meow!!
Meow!! Meow! Meow, meow, meow!!
Meow! Meow!! Meow! Meow!! Meow! Meow!!
Me-yow~!