Beautiful and Elite Masochist Lady: Shirogane Irina
She is a lady born into the Shirogane family's
international conglomerate with a quarter of Nordic descent.
She is a woman who possesses a body of exquisitely well proportion which rivals any model, as well as superior intelligence and refined manners
with which she outstands everyone else around her.
Thus, this earned her the title "Silver Titania",
garnering her admiration and envy as well
from the surrounding people.
Contrary to the personification of perfection that others see her as
hides her true nature as a top-notch sow. She is a masochistic woman
who finds the uttermost delight in serving her master Yuuji,
an extremely ordinary male student who discovered
this kink of hers.
An Extremely Ordinary Boy: Sado Yuuji
He is the very example of what a typical boy is,
and he is an admirer of the perfect lady Shirogane Irina.
He however suffers a peculiar complex for having scary eyes,
so he goes on his everyday life trying not to stand out from the crowd.
Staring at his crush Irina has become a daily routine for him,
but never has he ever thought even in his wildest dreams
that his intimidating gaze has actually been
discreetly driving Irina into a corner.
The beautiful and high-class lady Shirogane Irina works
as the student council president of Saint Eurora Academy.
As the heiress of the Shirogane international conglomerate,
she has been schooled from a young age in the same way as emperors would've been on kingship.
The great deal of effort she spent which no one else
could ever do makes her live up to the name
of her magnanimous status.
It was just a mere sudden impulse for Irina to sneak a little peek
in the magazines that were confiscated from male students of the school.
In articles inside each one are what she thought of as something repulsive.
What she saw inside them are indecent pictures showcasing female masochists
in highly suggestive poses and with provocative facial expressions.
With the aim of understanding the mentality and logic
in what she saw, Irina tries to imitate the models in the magazines.
She tightly ties herself up with a rope over her school uniform.
She had both of her legs and arms bound.
At that moment, she felt as if electricity ran through and zapped her.
Arousal has overwhelmed her whole body.
As that throbbing sensation brought her in a trance,
she notices the gaze of a male student from the crack of the door.
Irina confronts Yuuji for peeping on her with his intimidating eyes.
However, her hips give out after he touched her.
She loses her grit from being glared at,
falling on her knees in total defeat with such ease.
And in response, Irina gets herself bound. She then offers her maidenhood
in service to her now self-acknowledged master that is Yuuji,
all while wearing such a face warped in ecstasy.
Initially seeing him as a hostile character,
Irina now changes her opinion of Yuuji into an ideal master to be worshiped.
She wants to get reprimanded even more by him.
And so she lets herself fall in misery
while having her toy squirming inside her in a fully-loaded train,
as her master looks at her with cold and contemptuous eyes.
But at the same time, she can't help herself getting aroused
by those stares lighting up a fire in her...
Original Animation
There's No Way That A Perfect Lady Like Me Will Easily
Kneel Down And Degrade Myself Into A Mere Masochist!
Subservient Masochistic Lady Irina: Punishment by Public Exposure
Last Time on Kanpeki Irina Ojou-sama...
This should be okay... This one as well.
I'll take a look at this one.
President Irina looks gorgeous today as well!
She looks dazzling while working too!
Hey there, Irina-sama is
currently working, you know.
Oh, I get what you're saying though!
It can't be helped if you act this way with me.
I don't mind it when you
act more openly. Thank you.
Goodbye, Prez Irina!
Aren't you Kurokawa-san? Goodbye!
She knows my name!
Prez Irina knows the names
of all students in our school.
She's amazing!
Did you fantasize about me
kneeling in submission,
while thinking of me being at your
mercy for knowing my secret?
That's too bad.
I, Shirogane Irina, am not a woman
who'll submit to your whims that easily.
Watch this!
Do you think that doing this will turn
me into your obedient woman?
You are mistaken. I am no masochist!
So, you have seen through me...
That I'm actually a masochist...
That I am a female slave
who can serve under you...
I'm utterly defeated.
To think that you're a man worthy for me,
Shirogane Irina, to give my body and heart to...
To think that the prez adored
by both men and women
is a masochist who loves being berated...
Even I never knew about it.
Not even my father has ever spanked me!
But when you hit me...
Sh-Showing me how you'll take my virginity
as you nibble my tits...
Your cock is already there before I knew it...
You'll drive me crazy from this!
I'll tease you a lot as your master.
You're being reckless all of a sudden!
You're reprimanding me using your cock!
What's happening here?!
Each time you thrust it deep inside,
the inner depths of my body throbs!
This is incredible!
You are a master of me,
Shirogane Irina, starting today.
You are a man eligible for my subservience!
No, it's just that your enjoyment
is stimulating my nether region.
It's in an unbelievable state right now.
Whoa! Irina-senpai, is this...
While in such a place like this,
the inner depths of my pussy are...
Coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming in such an indecent manner
while everyone's around us!
I went out with you since you said
that you'll hold yourself back.
You're hopeless...
Don't look at me with those eyes, Yuuji-kun...
I can't help but say to all of you
how you are lacking in self-consciousness lately.
We have ten tardy students this morning.
You're slacking off too much!
As students of Saint Eurora, you all should...
...be more self-conscious...
...on how you conduct yourselves...
You're amazing, Irina-senpai.
People are expecting more
than that from all of you.
That would be all.
Jeez, that's no good, Irina-senpai!
I'm sorry for being unable to hold
myself back from having an orgasm!
I'm a failure of a slave.
Let's stop doing risky plays.
Understood.
So, does my apology titjob feel good?
I may still be lacking as
a masochistic female slave,
but let me at least serve you using my tits!
But still, weren't you expecting for a punishment?
I'm not putting it in today, though.
This is my punishment for being
an inexperienced masochist slave!
Ah, it's all because I disappointed you, master!
I'm gonna make your sturdy cock
feel good, master!
Yuuji-kun, shoot your semen out!
There's so much semen...
Just from getting soiled
by your punishment semen...
I'm coming—!
He sure is working hard as a master I serve under.
Yes, he is a man capable of
satisfying your expectations.
Now that you have him...
That's right, it'll be alright now that I have him.
That one person who can make
my wish come true will surely...
Good morning, Sado Yuuji-kun.
Quite a lovely morning we have!
Good morning... Wait, what?
I'll welcome myself inside.
I wanted to see how the master
who I serve under is spending his everyday life...
I'm sorry! I never noticed it...
No, it's alright.
That is bound to happen when I'm in front of you.
No, more importantly...
You're doing this to train a female slave like me.
Didn't you show this to me
as a form of punishment?
Hey, I need to use a toilet...
Toilet?
You're saying that you want to use
this Shirogane Irina as a toilet?
No, I don't!
I don't have such a kink!
Oh, my...
That all happened so fast, what a shock...
Huh?
Irina-senpai?
That is so lewd. You're such a pervert, Irina-senpai.
Just as I expected, you easily
knew what I wanted.
Wow, you're violating my mouth behind the door!
You're so sturdy early in the morning!
This is fantastic!
Shoot your undiluted morning semen! Yuuji-kun!
Yuuji-kun, your undiluted semen is so amazing!
Yuuji-kun, this is so intense!
You went straight to giving me
punishment sex in the toilet!
So good!
Your cock just unloaded itself,
but it's still rock-hard!
'Cause you're so sexy, Irina-senpai.
You're kneading my tits out of
shape and spanking my butt
all while banging me!
Don't you love it more this way?
Yes, that's right!
For a masochistic slave like me,
being spanked by you feels good...
Yuuji-kun, make yourself feel good!
This pussy is for your own
exclusive use, after all!
Yuuji-kun, I'll fall down!
This could be dangerous!
This is your punishment for
being so lewd in the morning.
Tough it out.
We're doing something dangerous,
and yet my pussy feels so hot!
It feels good!
I want to feel you deeper inside me, Yuuji-kun!
My master's cock—!
This position feels good!
You're pounding my deepest parts
into a sloppy mess, it's driving me crazy!
I'll drive you crazy.
Yuuji-kun, my master, is driving me crazy!
Your semen is spurting deep inside me!
I'm...
Someone like me is being driven to
orgasm in such an indecent manner!
And with such recklessness...
Oh, Irina-sama!
You look gorgeous today as well!
Are you in the middle of a break right now?
Oh, aren't you Toudou-san?
Yes, it's warm outside so
I'm getting a nice view of it.
Aww...
Having my name remembered
by you is such an honor!
I am Shirogane Irina.
As Yuuji-kun's masochistic slave,
I have to be dignified...
We'll get caught if you let you voice out.
I understand, our deal is that
I have to act properly
as a student council president
at school no matter what happens.
There was also that abrupt
punishment from the morning.
My voice will be fine.
Oh, Irina-sama!
Isn't it unusual of you to catch a glimpse here?
O-Oh my, how hardworking of you to go
on patrol, disciplinary committee president!
It's because your words from the
other day moved me, Irina-sama.
I have to be stricter since then!
I see...
And here I am, doing something indecent myself.
If she finds out about this...
Oh no, I'm starting to feel it!
That's so dependable of you.
I also am relying on you.
No way, he's going that far at a time like this!
This is getting too wild!
Oh! Thank you!
Thanks for your kind words, Irina-sama!
He shoved the whole thing deep at once! But, I'm...
Oh my, I ended up interrupting
you on your patrol.
This is bad!
Irina-sama, your face is red.
Do you have a cold...
I have my hopes up on you.
I want you to keep it up for
the sake of Saint Eurora.
Yes, I'll do my best!
That was a close one.
We'll be fine, just who do you think am I?
Something this trivial...
Coming up with an idea like this...
Just as I expected from the man I chose!
I agreed to work hard to become an
appropriate master for you, after all.
I'm feeling so good even in a situation like this!
I never felt like this before!
Y-You introduced me to a lot of new things.
I want you to teach me
even more in the future!
That's my job as your master.
Yuuji-kun!
This is our first time in this
position, we're face to face.
You did a great job, after all.
You even know when to use
a carrot, not just all sticks!
You're a brilliant master!
Is that also a reward for me?
You're thrusting deep inside me
while nibbling my nipple!
I'll end up coming before you!
I know that I shouldn't, but I'm already...
No, I will fail as you slave!
I'll make you feel good even a lot more!
I'm sorry, Yuuji-kun!
You're being so intense on me, I'm already...
It's okay, let's do it together.
I'm happy to be able to feel good with you!
No! No!
I'm coming—!
So good!
I'm coming while in my office!
I'm showing my slutty face
in climax to the world
as I get filled with semen!
Irina-sama, pardon my rudeness from before.
How are you feeling right now?
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization