Beautiful and Elite Masochist Lady: Shirogane Irina
She is a lady born into the Shirogane family's
international conglomerate with a quarter of Nordic descent.
She is a woman who possesses a body of exquisitely well proportion which rivals any model, as well as superior intelligence and refined manners
with which she outstands everyone else around her.
Thus, this earned her the title "Silver Titania",
garnering her admiration and envy as well
from the surrounding people.
Contrary to the personification of perfection that others see her as
hides her true nature as a top-notch sow. She is a masochistic woman
who finds the uttermost delight in serving her master Yuuji,
an extremely ordinary male student who discovered
this kink of hers.
An Extremely Ordinary Boy: Sado Yuuji
He is the very example of what a typical boy is,
and he is an admirer of the perfect lady Shirogane Irina.
He however suffers a peculiar complex for having scary eyes,
so he goes on his everyday life trying not to stand out from the crowd.
Staring at his crush Irina has become a daily routine for him,
but never has he ever thought even in his wildest dreams
that his intimidating gaze has actually been
discreetly driving Irina into a corner.
The beautiful and high-class lady Shirogane Irina works
as the student council president of Saint Eurora Academy.
As the heiress of the Shirogane international conglomerate,
she has been schooled from a young age in the same way as emperors would've been on kingship.
The great deal of effort she spent which no one else
could ever do makes her live up to the name
of her magnanimous status.
It was just a mere sudden impulse for Irina to sneak a little peek
in the magazines that were confiscated from male students of the school.
In articles inside each one are what she thought of as something repulsive.
What she saw inside them are indecent pictures showcasing female masochists
in highly suggestive poses and with provocative facial expressions.
With the aim of understanding the mentality and logic
in what she saw, Irina tries to imitate the models in the magazines.
She tightly ties herself up with a rope over her school uniform.
She had both of her legs and arms bound.
At that moment, she felt as if electricity ran through and zapped her.
Arousal has overwhelmed her whole body.
As that throbbing sensation brought her in a trance,
she notices the gaze of a male student from the crack of the door.
As far as Irina can see, Yuuji witnessed her one and only disgraceful flaw.
Irina worries about the situation at hand, having the possibility
of this single flaw about her going public.
As for Yuuji, seeing the woman he admires in such an indecent state is too much of a stimulus for him.
Although it is a relief for Irina to know that Yuuji has kept things to himself all this time, she has now been more conscious of his gaze than ever before.
Moreover, Irina has kept suffering under his gazes which were seemingly
full of disdain, considering those intimidating eyes he has.
Night after night, Irina goes in her own private "sadomasochism room"
that she had purposely built up in a rush.
In this room, she unwinds all of her pent-up stress by simulating a showdown
where she goes against a makeshift Yuuji mannequin and makes him ejaculate.
Original Animation
Beautiful and Elite Masochist Lady Irina: Kneels Down and Suck with Ease
There's No Way That A Perfect Lady Like Me Will Easily
Kneel Down And Degrade Myself Into A Mere Masochist!
This should be okay... This one as well.
I'll take a look at this one.
President Irina looks gorgeous today as well!
She looks dazzling while working too!
Hey there, Irina-sama is
currently working, you know.
Oh, I get what you're saying though!
It can't be helped if you act this way with me.
I don't mind it when you act openly. Thank you.
Goodbye, Prez Irina!
Aren't you Kurokawa-san? Goodbye!
She knows my name!
Prez Irina knows the names
of all students in our school.
She's amazing!
It's that stare again.
It looks down upon me, implying
"beneath that face lies a mere masochist".
Whoa... What are you glaring at? You look scary!
Well... The prez was passing by, so...
Your eyes are already scary as it is,
but it gets worse when you try to focus.
Just because you saw the prez that you admire...
Cut it out.
You two...
What's with you two feasting
your eyes on Irina-sama?
It can't be helped if they're dumbstruck after
witnessing me, an epitome of beauty all of a sudden.
Forgive them.
Yes, I'll make sure to treat them with leniency.
I look gorgeous tonight as well. Don't you all think so?
Well then, you may all go now.
That's right.
The looks that I get from everyone
should all be the same.
And yet...
Did you fantasize about me
kneeling in submission,
while thinking of me being at your
mercy for knowing my secret?
That's too bad.
I, Shirogane Irina, am not a woman
who'll submit to your whims that easily.
Watch this!
Do you think that doing this will turn
me into your obedient woman?
You are mistaken. I am no masochist!
You say that I'm a sow who have such a kinky fetish,
but I'd argue otherwise for those
sneering stares you give me!
You came, didn't you?
I knew it, you're the real masochist here, Yuuji-kun!
The contents of these confiscated materials are lowly.
That woman is in such a humiliating
state, how unreasonable.
Th-This is...
Having an undignified appearance while
being smeared with humiliation...
How unthinkable...
Wh-What are you looking at?
I-I'm sorry!
After that happened,
Sado Yuuji-kun kept giving me
contemptuous stares over and over again.
It's as if he's saying that what's beneath that
mask of that president is a masochist bitch.
Celestine, I think that it's about time
for me to settle the score with him.
Sado Yuuji-kun,
Tomorrow, I'll change that rude
attitude of yours towards me.
I'll make you grovel to my authority!
What did you do to make the Silver Titania
personally call for you, Yuuji?
It's Shirogane-senpai that I admire...
Maybe she'll reprimand me for stealing glances at her.
That can't be.
You're here at last, Sado Yuuji-kun!
Umm...
Did I do something to be called here?
You ask if you did something?!
After all this time—
You dare make me say it myself...
Those eyes!
You're staring at me with those eyes again...
And with such scrutiny...
Don't touch me!
No way...
You rendered me immobile with just a glare...
And you took away my will to resist with just a grip.
This is the proof that you want
to make me your woman!
You're going to use this on me to...
I'm not gonna lose!
I'll never yield to a lowly man
who only sees women as sexual objects!
Wait... Senpai!
What's this? So this is how the real thing is?
Everything's different!
Both the size and smell of it are outrageous!
Shirogane-senpai is touching my...
If I do this...
You press this onto my beautiful face,
thinking of besmirching it with your
obscene secretion, am I right?
No way, I'm stroking a cock while kneeling down.
It's as if I'm a slave!
Senpai, stroke me even harder.
More?
It's not enough so you order me to do better?
You want me to stoop even
lower than this, don't you?
Senpai, I'm about to...
Is that so? Shoot it out.
Let me move away from here
and your insolence will...
Hey, if you keep doing this... Wait!
So this is what semen looks like...
If I keep getting smothered
by the smell of this slimy thing...
This can't be... There's no way that I'm...
C-Coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
Just from stroking a filthy meat stick
and being poured with a huge amount of semen,
I ended up reaching climax!
So, you have seen through me...
That I'm actually a masochist...
That I am a female slave that could serve under you...
I'm totally defeated.
To think that you're a man worthy for me,
Shirogane Irina, to give my body and heart to...
Sado Yuuji-kun,
you are indeed my master!
I am your female slave!
I'm sorry, Irina-senpai!
Oh, forgive me, Yuuji-kun! But you're so mean
for doing another "neglect play" on me again!
Oh, but you're using that sadism of yours
to draw out my true nature
as a lowly woman, am I right?
Wow, and here I am yet to be made
sport of and violated by this.
It's hard, upright and ready to defile me!
Those eyes tell me that I'm gonna be
punished for my shamelessness.
You want to reprimand me, don't you?
You're spanking my butt...
It feels hot and it's throbbing!
Who knew that Irina-senpai
who everyone admires was
a masochistic female slave?
To think that the prez adored
by both men and women
is a masochist who loves being berated...
Even I never knew about it.
Not even my father has ever spanked me!
But when you hit me...
Just from getting my butt spanked...
I'm coming... I'm coming—!
You're a masochist indeed to
reach orgasm just from this.
Yuuji-kun is verbally abusing me!
To forcefully take my first time in
a disgraceful manner like this...
Aren't you such an atrocious man, Yuuji-kun?
But aren't you looking forward
to being raped by me?
Sh-Showing me how you'll take my virginity
as you nibble my tits...
Your cock is already there before I knew it...
You'll drive me crazy from this!
If you look at me with those eyes, I'm...
Yuuji-kun, your cock is inside me!
My whole body now belongs to you!
I'll tease you a lot as your master.
You're being reckless all of a sudden!
You're reprimanding me using your cock!
What's happening here?!
Each time you thrust it deep inside,
the inner depths of my body throbs!
This is incredible!
Even though this is my first time,
you're indecently giving me pleasure!
You're gonna give my pussy that comes easily
a creampie just as you wanted to!
You're shooting your semen deep inside me!
There's plenty of your hot stuff!
I'm being sullied and being
made to come in such a state...
This feels too good—!
You are a master of me,
Shirogane Irina, starting today.
You are a man eligible for my subservience!
B-But why me?
It's those eyes! They instantly
saw through my true nature.
That mere gaze transformed me!
I am convinced that you are indeed
the only man worthy of my obedience!
I have high hopes for you.
You're finally here, Yuuji-kun.
Alright, what kind of obscene training
am I supposed to get today?
We'll just go shopping!
It was just a joke to break the ice on our first date.
Here you go.
You use it to say that you're enjoying our date.
Press the button whenever you feel like so.
So, this is similar to a "like" button...
You're pushing it already?!
Just as I expected from you, Yuuji-kun.
You are indeed my master.
Irina-senpai, are you alright?
Yes, it's nothing.
It will be my pleasure to see
you having fun, Yuuji-kun!
Isn't it fun when we're together despite
not doing anything in particular?
Come on, aren't we going on a train next?
This will be my first time to ride in one,
so I am looking forward to it!
It's unexpectedly cramped in here.
We can only barely move, see?
Yuuji-kun, you're doing it even in here...
Are you feeling nauseous?
You've been shivering every
once in a while since earlier.
No, it's just that your enjoyment
is stimulating my nether region.
It's in an unbelievable state right now.
Whoa! Irina-senpai, is this...
Yuuji-kun...
Not that rough...
Y-Yuuji-kun, right there!
It'll be mayhem if you get caught
right now, so bear with it.
I understand.
A masochist slave like me
should just obey you, my master.
I can't take it anymore!
It is unbecoming of me being here
in the middle of a crowd...
...and coming!
What an audacious man you are.
Exposing me in an indecent manner in a place like this...
I'm sorry!
I deserve to be scolded for coming
in such an unsightly manner.
Your master haven't forgiven you yet,
so here is the punishment for a
nasty slave who came on her own.
You're looking forward to this, huh?
Exposing my butt in such a place like this...
What are you planning to do to me?
You already know, don't you?
Your hot thing is...
Keep your voice down, okay?
Thrusting it so deep all of a sudden...
You're even exposing my tits...
I'm gonna come while in such an indecent state!
No, I can't keep my voice down!
While in such a place like this,
the inner depths of my pussy are...
Coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming in such an indecent manner
while everyone's around us!
I went out with you since you said
that you'll hold yourself back.
You're hopeless...
Don't look at me with those eyes, Yuuji-kun...
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time Kanpeki Irina Ojou-sama...
You're slacking off too much!
As students of Saint Eurora, you all should...
...be more self-conscious...
...on how you conduct yourselves...
You're amazing, Irina-senpai.
This might not be enough as
a masochistic female slave,
but let me at least serve you using my tits!
But still, weren't you expecting for a punishment?
I'm not putting it in today, though.
This is my punishment for being
an inexperienced masochist slave!
Ah, it's all because I disappointed you, master!
I'm gonna make your sturdy cock
feel good, master!
Just as expected, it immediately
detected its target.
You're kneading my tits out of
shape and spanking my butt
as you penetrate me!
Doesn't it feel better when I do it this way?
That's right!
For a masochist slave like me,
being spanked by you feels good...
I understand, I promised that
I have to act properly
as a student council president
at school no matter what happens.