We were caught in the middle of
a panic and how all we can do is run.
Original Work: SPEED "Kansen 5 ~The Daybreak~"
Run from the panic that
started in the middle of the city.
Script: Tashiro Yaemon
Because of it, my sister, Souichi, and the others...
even Murakami-san... we all got separated!
Character Design/Art Director
Sato Katsuyuki
This panic... I-I know it!
Director: Watase Toshihiro
It's the same as four years ago.
It's an epidemic!
Route A
In the World of Hope and Nightmares
Where should we go from here?
What should we do? I'm worried about the others.
The Sato Shrine is nearby.
It's far enough away that it should still be unaffected.
It's probably better than moving around blindly,
don't you think, Ma-kun-senpai?
Yeah, I think so.
Good point. It could get dangerous when it gets dark.
Woman! Pussy!
No! Stop!
Woman!
Pussy!
No! Let go of us!
No! Stop that!
Stop!
Let go!
Let go of me!
It stinks!
I haven't bathed in days!
Clean it for me!
No!
Don't miss a spot!
No! Stop!
I'm going to go to town on this!
– Stop! Stop it!
– It's getting so wet!
No! Let go of me!
Your panties are getting wet, you little slut!
Get in the car, quick!
R-Right!
Sir?
Tae-chan, you too! Hurry!
Sir, where's Sato?
Oh, don't worry. She's fine.
Thank goodness!
Are you okay? Back there, I...
Don't worry about it. How about you?
Are you okay, Ma-kun-senpai?
Yeah, I'm perfectly fine.
Maybe I should've brought my gym clothes.
Sorry about everything.
It's fine.
We need to help each other out.
Um, are we the only ones here?
Nobody comes here at all?
Did our friends come here by any chance?
Frank-senpai...
Oh, right. Where's Sato?
I know you're worried, but please
eat your food to regain your strength.
Sato's in the middle of an important errand.
She'll be back eventually.
Thanks for the food.
Take it easy tonight.
H-Huh?
Ochi-san?
Senpai?!
Take it easy.
What's going on?
I can't move!
Ochi-san? Senpai!
Ochi-san! Minami-senpai!
Could you keep it down?
What's going on here?
What did you do to us?
There's nothing to worry about.
It's just your run-of-the-mill sleeping pill.
You must be tired.
It seemed to be a little too effective.
It's a secret recipe that's only
known by the people of this shrine.
Still can't move, can you?
Why now? You know what's going on outside, don't you?
What's going on outside?! Of course I fucking know!
And this house is now a sanctuary, isn't it?
This island is devolving into hell.
I saw the true nature of man!
This is God's will! He wants us to show
more of the true nature of humans!
Has his mind broken from fear of the epidemic?
A lot of people have already died, right?
But that means we just have to make more!
I'll impregnate all of them and make them women!
Tarja-san! Tarja-san!
I don't mind you helping me to wake them up,
but if you're too loud, we might have some unwanted guests.
What a slim and elegant body.
It's beautiful to me even though we're years apart in age!
I'll penetrate Tanja-chan's body just
like I did with my own daughter's body!
Her breasts aren't as big as her mother's...
but I'm sure the taste is more exquisite.
All right, time to wake up!
Tastes so sweet!
She isn't really waking up. I heard sleeping
princesses need kisses to wake up, but...
Oh, wait, I know!
There's another mouth.
What? I feet strange... Something's not right.
It feels good...
Are you awake now?
I knew kissing you down here would work.
Tarja-san, run!
Makoto-san? What... What's going on?!
My body feels weird!
Should I shove it in without breaking your hymen?
Tarja-san!
Makoto-kun?
I'm so glad you're awake, senpai!
You can move, right?
I still can't really move.
You need to run away by yourself.
The priest is crazy...
I'll try my best to at least protect Ochi-san.
You're worrying about Ochi-san
even in a situation like this, huh?
Senpai?
You never care about anyone else but her.
What'll happen when I run away by myself?
You're not going to protect me, Makoto-kun?
You don't care what happens to me, huh?
Senpai? What are you saying?
Is she infected?
No, she should be immune. It's not like four years ago.
Did the virus mutate?
But when could she have been infected...
Don't tell me it was from the mucus?!
Please get a hold of yourself, senpai!
Quiet down.
Senpai! Don't do this!
You always try to play the good boy.
But what's this?
You're aroused from watching
what's happening to Tarja-chan.
Oh, it's nicer than I thought.
It's rock hard.
I knew it.
But it's uncircumcised. You're a virgin, aren't you?
What a dirty smell.
Senpai, don't!
Just fight back if you don't like this.
I can't move because of the drug.
Oh, right. The drug.
What? Gonna cum already?
I haven't even pulled the skin back yet.
Senpai, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
Hold it in. Look, here comes your pre-cum.
– I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
– I guess this'll be its first time.
That girl's really going at it.
I'll leave him to her.
Now then...
Sir?
Let's get started here, shall we?
No! Stay back!
No!
Suck it.
No! It stinks!
No!
Oh, I see. I guess that leaves me no choice.
Let's start with the procreation!
Stop!
Don't!
Dad, save me! Sato!
Don't worry, your father and Sato are
probably deep into baby-making right now.
He agreed with my idea and now he's doing his best.
Y-You're lying.
I'm not!
What are you doing?
Dad, stop!
No, please, don't!
No!
But I took her first time!
No... that can't be!
This can't be! Sato!
It was a little embarrassing,
but that was my first time with a woman in ages.
I feel like the clock's turned back for me.
Sato took every last drop of my seed too.
You monster!
You're horrible!
All right, let's resume.
It really is tight.
No! Stop! I don't want to!
Save me!
Sato got through this.
It'll be fine!
It's so fucking tight!
You live up to your reputation as a gymnast!
Now your virginity is mine!
No! Dad! Save me!
Sato!
Don't you have ears?!
I told you that they're in the middle of baby-making!
Looks like we're fucking each others' daughters.
What's the word? Sw-Sw-Swapping?
Keep your weird comments to yourself!
Take it out!
Oh, I'm just about there! I'm just about there!
Stop! I can't go on!
I can't!
Oh, so you're ready then, Tarja-chan?!
R-Ready?
To take me in!
To be pregnant!
No! No! No!
If only you just sucked me off.
I might've been a little more lenient.
But now, it's too late!
A lot's built up, so I have no clue
how much I'm gonna shoot out!
But I do know that you're one-hundred
percent going to get pregnant!
No way!
This is a decade's worth of cum!
Don't think I used it all up on Sato!
Here I go! Here I go!
It's going to go deep into you.
Take it out! Take it out!
Not inside!
I don't want to get pregnant!
It's so hot!
More!
Squeeze it! Squeeze me dry!
This... This can't be happening! it's inside me!
It's pouring out inside me! It hasn't stopped coming out!
With this much, I'm definitely going to have a baby!
I feel better.
That was a very satisfying climax.
Now you and Sato are both mothers
of my child. Raise 'em well.
In this position, you'll be able to take in every last drop.
Stay like this, okay, Tarja-chan?
What the heck's happening?
That big thing went inside Tarja-san?
And now she's going to get pregnant
from all that stuff he shot out inside of her?
Please, let me cum! Please!
Oh? So you want to cum?
If you want to cum, Makoto-kun...
Do you want it with my hands? My mouth? My boobs?
Or maybe... you want this hot and wet pussy?
What do you prefer?
Your pussy!
I want to lose my virginity to your pussy, Satsuki-senpai!
That's it?
You don't want to fuck my brains out and cum inside me?
I do!
I want to shoot my cum inside
your womb and get you pregnant!
Oh? You're going to get me pregnant?
What should I do?
Never mind.
What? You can't...
Nope. Just kidding.
I think you pass.
I'll take your virginity, Makoto-kun.
Th-This can't be... Ma-kun-senpai is...
he's going to have sex with her?
Don't forget to say "please", Makoto-kun.
Senpai, please! Please let me put it in you!
That's senpai's dick...
Well said.
I'll take every last piece of you in.
Come on, look.
I think you have a man's dick now.
– It's going to tear... my dick's gonna tear!
– I'm going to move now.
His cute dick's an adult dick now?
He lost his virginity?
– It's gonna melt! My dick's gonna melt!
– It feels good.
They're even kissing?
He's just had his first kiss and he's
moaning like a girl... but he's so cute.
I'm going to be a little rough now.
I don't want you to cum too easily.
How's it feel, Makoto-kun? Good?
It feels really good!
Move a little slower...
No, not happening. Come on, hang in there.
Hang in there, Makoto-kun's dick!
– Senpai!
– So it feels good? It feels good for me too.
Come here.
That feels good?
That feels good, Ma-kun-senpai?
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
No more fun if you cum.
Are you sure? You really want this to stop?
I don't.
I want to keep doing this forever!
But... But I want to cum!
Let me cum!
Senpai sounds so pitiful, but he sounds so cute!
Where do you want to cum?
Inside!
Inside you, senpai!
You really want to cum inside me?
I do!
I want to cum inside!
You're going to cum?
You're going to cum because of Minami-senpai?
That's okay.
I want to see you cum, Ma-kun-senpai!
You can let her make you cum!
What a bad dick. It's going to get a girl
pregnant right after losing its virginity.
You're going to cum inside Minami-senpai?
That's not hair. I want it too.
I want his baby milk too!
Cum inside my soft, wet, and hot pussy!
Give me your thick cum!
You know, this is my first time
having sex and getting a creampie.
Just for you, Makoto-kun.
Senpai!
My body's tingling all over!
Get pregnant! Please get pregnant!
I can tell. I just ovulated.
I'm really ready to get pregnant.
Senpai!
Cum inside me.
I'm cumming!
We're not done yet, are we?
You need to satisfy me more, Makoto-kun!
Huh? Being stepped on feels good?
You're such a pervert.
Looks like I won't be bored, Makoto-kun.
Ma-kun-senpai...
You're quite the girl.
Masturbating while watching your
friend being raped in this situation?!
You really thought I didn't notice?!
No, I... I'm not like that!
I'm not!
I expected nothing less from the daughter of the Ochi's.
I... I... I'm not involved in my family's affairs!
That might be true.
You might not know the darkness of the Ochi family.
But, I need you to take responsibility
for them as their daughter.
R-Responsibility?
You're going to bear my child too!
I think it'll hurt if I'm this sudden.
Please stop!
Please! I beg you!
How about this? Why don't you suck my dick instead?
If you get wet, it won't hurt as much. Also, I'm old,
so you never know. Maybe after I cum once, I'll be done.
– I might not even be able to have sex.
– What should I do?!
You might be able to give that senpai
you love so much your virginity.
Ma-kun-senpai...
Well, I can't really wait, so...
Wait! Please wait!
Hm?
I'll do it...
Hm?! I can't hear you!
Please wait! I'll suck it! I'll suck it! I'll take it in my mouth!
That's not how this goes. You need to beg me.
Please let me suck you off.
Please let me suck your magnificent dick.
All right!
Then get a good taste!
It's so big! I can't breathe!
Oh, sorry about that. I forgot that you're
supposed to be the one sucking my dick.
Go.
It's so big.
Wow, so this is a dick?
Ma-kun-senpai's dick...
It's bigger than Ma-kun-senpai's dick!
I knew you could do it, daughter of the Ochi's!
I'm cumming! Take it in!
It's coming out! There's so much pouring out!
I can't drink all of this!
I'm gonna get pregnant through my mouth!
My stomach's filled!
Sorry, looks like I'm still good to go.
No! This isn't what you promised!
You said you wouldn't do that if I sucked you off!
And now you're wet, so it shouldn't hurt as much!
No!
It's squeezing me so tight!
– I can hardly believe that you're a virgin!
– No!
It's coming inside me!
No!
Okay, I'm hitting it! Drink it all up!
It hurts!
It's too intense! No!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna shoot my seed inside you!
No! Don't cum!
So deep!
Don't move it around inside me like that!
Don't suck them!
Don't suck my boobs!
Don't bite them either!
You're going to stretch out my boobs!
You're going to rip off my nipple!
No!
Nothing's going to come out even if you suck that hard!
I don't have breast milk.
You're going to rip off my nipple!
My first kiss...
I love locking lips with young girls!
Oh, I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum! Get pregnant! Get pregnant!
Ma-kun-senpai! Ma-kun-senpai!
Save me! He's going to get me pregnant!
He's going to get me pregnant in front of Ma-kun-senpai!
Good girl. Finally getting aroused
from the thought of getting pregnant?
Now take it in! I'm gonna flood you with my cum!
No! He's going to cum!
No!
I'm cumming!
I think it's time to introduce you to everyone else.
I'm sure they'll all accept you in no time though.
We're gonna get busy from here on out.
Hm? They're here?!
I can't let my plans be ruined by them!
Come at me, you bastards!
– Now's our chance. Everyone, get up!
– You're not getting past here!
– We're running!
Senpai? I thought you were infected.
We need to get away from here now!
Are you all... okay?
All good.
I'm fine.
Girls are stronger than you think.
Also very stubborn.
And very dirty, senpai.
That's right. We will survive this!
Even if the world ends.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч