Kansen Sodom
Infection
Doing it raw feels amazing!
I can totally feel the shape
of your dick, Head Chief!
I won't be able to let go of you
now after learning about this!
Are you about to come?
I took the medicine just as you
told me, so just shoot it inside me.
Come, Chief Kuroiwa!
So warm...
I can feel you coming inside me.
You're filling me up.
I'll be wearing this in summer.
That almost shows everything, Miho-chan.
I learned from my mistake last winter.
I need more exposure than quality.
My younger brother will be coming in 3 days.
Oh yeah, Mako-chan. Is your
brother's fracture healed?
Yes, his plaster cast was removed yesterday.
Then there will be a cumfest!
Cum? I don't get what you're talking—
Don't move!
Don't try to resist and make me shoot you!
Miho-chan!
Doesn't it smell like squid?
Maekawa-san, don't act
recklessly outside your jurisdiction.
I know.
I should've kicked that exhibitionist's balls though!
Your panties are showing.
Pervert!
I feel bad for that driver...
...a passionate new virgin recruit
won't understand it, though.
...oh, "that one"?
"Whatever you may, I don't believe you."
"Speak clearly so that everyone may hear you."
The "may" here tells about the
intention in the said situation.
May I get your attention, everyone!
It's especially important when the word "may"
is used together with the word "but".
Such auxiliary verbs can go in various
forms depending on the main verb.
Alright, that's all for today.
Oh yeah, Ujiki-kun.
I need to talk to you later, Will that be fine?
Do something about how Miho smells.
It's nothing.
Looks like Yano-sensei is feeling down.
Then he should just get remarried or something.
Wait, maybe I should DM this hot guy?
How's your boyfriend, Natsuki?
We broke up long ago.
He puts it in without any foreplay. It hurts for real.
But since he couldn't come, I always
have to end it with a handjob.
Things like that are such a burden. Oh...
It's Doi-sensei.
He definitely took a picture of us.
You see, Doi has been stalking me lately.
Huh?
I faked some tears when he
talked to me on my failing grades.
Then he misunderstood the situation
and told me "I will protect you" with a half-boner.
I want him to drop dead for real.
I feel bad for you on getting yet another weirdo.
Shut up, geezer-lover.
It's "fatherly-figure fawning".
Do your best!
Go for it!
Yamada-san...
That's right!
...just like that!
Do your best!
You're doing good!
Show them!
So boys shoot that kind of stuff out of their dicks.
That smell... My brother's room smelt the same yesterday.
Miho-chan hasn't taken care of the smell
yet. I wonder if she's aware of it.
Bring it on!
Mako-chan, incoming!
Y-Yeah... I can't!
Wait for me!
Senpai, have you heard the
rumors about Chief Kuroiwa?
He's been seen going in a love hotel while
his wife is in the middle of childbirth.
Oh... Isn't that like, prostitution or something...
They're the worst!
It's that place, right?
I'm not allowed to have a personal
contact with a student.
But I gave you my contact details out of worry
since you said that you need
to confide something to me.
Now I am regretting it. It's because you...
You said that you're thinking about
me when you do something weird.
I don't know how to respond to that.
And sending that picture yesterday
was so mean. You made me feel sad.
Of course, I deleted it immediately.
I hate men who do that,
even if he's a student of mine.
I don't want to hate you even more,
so let's not contact each other again.
Huuuh, I'm not getting uncomfortably close to you!
But maybe it's because your lesson
is so fun that I kinda love it.
Ahh! Did you just mistakenly take that!
I'm not talking about you, what I love is the lesson!
Her head has a loose screw.
Hey, sensei! Are you not lonely with your wife gone?
Right... Shit...
Ehh, you didn't bring one?
Should I go to your house next time and cook something?
Yano-chi!
May I go to the clinic for some tampons?
Mr. Ball! Where are you, Mr. Ball!
M-Mr. Janitor... Good afternoon.
What are you doing in this place?
Stay there and slowly turn around!
Freeze!
Doi-sensei, what are you doing?
Huh, you're done already?
Should I show the real thing,
rather than that voyeur photo?
Mr. Janitor, your pants are so tight and it looks painful.
Did I do something I shouldn't? Was it my fault?
What should I do?
It made me feel happy that a backed up
man used me as a fap material.
Ujiki-kun, weren't you thinking about
lewd stuff since the last time?
Me too, I've been thinking
about your peeled dick as well.
Sensei, your breath tickles me, it's gross.
You're ogling at me like crazy!
It's so obvious which hole you are looking at!
You sure are hilarious!
No! You can't just touch me as you want!
You're a mere perverted teacher. Come one, stand up.
Not that one.
You have such a huge cock! It's hard as a rock!
Now my thigh got sticky from your dirty pre-cum!
What are you go about this?
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!Hey! Hey!
So, do handjobs really feel that good?
How about this one?
Do you want me to tighten up my grip?
You've been using weird toys and
you don't come easily now, right?
This man really is disgusting!
You got so hard, are you close?
I was thinking of letting you come
inside me but you're coming now?
Shoot it out! Come! Squirt!
I'm telling you to come, creepy teacher!
Jeez... You came an awful lot. You're the worst!
Be sure to make me feel good as well, okay?
Umm...
Will it be okay for me to suck your dick?
It's big...
There's a lot of white stuff beneath the foreskin.
I'm gonna suck it now, okay?
It got even bigger than before!
I wonder if the whole thing will fit in my mouth...
I think I'm doing it right.
The gooey stuff keeps on dripping
out. It tastes very salty.
It tastes good.
Mr. Janitor, your dick that
stinks with sweat is delicious.
The tip is swelling even more.
It looks like it's gonna burst!
I'm sorry for spilling it out! There's so
much that it caught me off-guard!
Hey, I want to have sex next! Can't we?
That's unfair, Mako-chan! I want to
swallow some dick milk as well.
It's dripping out!
How does my "pussy juice" taste?
I want it already that I can hardly wait.
I'll put your dick inside, okay?
My hands got slippery from your pre-cum!
It's not embarrassing even if you come
immediately, okay? Here we go.
So stiff! This is an unbelievably hard dick!
My insides are clinging on you since
I'm not loosened up and lubricated yet!
My pussy is getting drawn out!
Ujiki-kun, your dick feels so good!
I kind of like it.
Are you yet to come? Want to try different poses?
Don't be so mean!
Here, hurry up and thrust it in!
More, keep it up!
Your dick is poking me! It's hitting me deep inside!
More! Keep teasing my pussy even more!
Are you about to come? Can't you hold it in anymore?
Alright, give it deep inside me!
I want it deep inside!
Don't hold it in anymore!
You can come any time now.
Shoot it inside! Give me a creampie!
Shoot every drop into my pussy!
Shoot it inside!
Your hot stuff is pouring into me!
Your dick is ejaculating convulsively!
You're still coming! You got a lot stored in, huh?
Uh-huh... Everyone left already.
I don't care about everyone else—
Shut up, you're annoying!
What did you say?
Figure out already how you're troubling sensei.
Making fun of me, you dolt—
Yano-sensei, we're finally alone.
I can't stand seeing you sad like that.
I'm okay with having sex with you.
Senpai.
I'm wet.
I never had a boyfriend even once...
I won't let some geezer from god
knows where to take my virginity!
I'll fight up to my last breath!
Mommy!
Sensei, more! Give me more!
I'll take the sadness away using my body!
I can't do this anymore! I'm sorry, sensei!
Your cock is too much! My pussy will end up loose!
So big!
So big, so big!
So big! So big, so big!
Your dick is so big!
I'm gonna come again! My pussy is coming again!
Do it harder! I want you to thrust it in!
That's so unfair, Mako-chan!
I want to get a creampie from that dick milk too...
This saved me!
Maekawa-san...
Chief Kuroiwa?!
Hoah—!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization