We got involved in a mass hysteria.
We thoughtlessly ran away in confusion.
The whole town was engulfed in a hysteria.
And because of that, we got separated
from my sister, Murakami-san and the others.
A mass hysteria... No, I knew what this really is.
Not again!
Just like four years ago...
It's the same epidemic!
Kansen
Route
In a World of Despair and Nightmare
I wonder where we can find the others...
What should we do? I'm
worried about them as well.
Sato's shrine is just nearby.
It's in a place that's a little secluded,
so we should still be safe there.
Going there now sounds like a better idea
than aimlessly running, Maakun-senpai.
You're right. That sound's good to me.
Right, it will be dangerous once it gets dark.
Woman's pussy!
No!
Stop!
Woman, show your pussy!
No, let go of me!
Young woman!
Female pussy!
No, you can't! Stop!
Stop that!
Let go... Let go of me!
That stinks!
It should be!
I haven't washed it for days!
You!
Eh? No—!
I've been thinking about you!
No!
You can't, no—!
I had my eyes on you for a while now!
Everyone's at me... Stop!
It's delicious, you're dripping down here!
Stop—!
No, take your hands off me!
Your panties are wet, dirty bitch!
Here you go!
Get in the vehicle, everyone!
O-Okay.
Tarja-chan, you should hurry up as well!
Uncle, where's Sato?
Ah, don't worry. She's fine.
Ah... Thank goodness!
Are you alright? About before, umm...
Please don't worry about it.
How about you Maakun-senpai, are you alright?
I'm alright.
I should have at least brought my jersey with me...
I'm sorry for all the troubles we caused.
Don't worry about it. We should
help each other when in need.
Umm, were there anyone else here? Anyone
might have checked this place, or something...
Have you seen any of my friends as well?
Frank-senpai...
Oh, and where is Sato, uncle?
I know how worried you are, but you
all must take a good rest yourselves.
Sato is in the middle of an important
ceremony. We'll meet them afterwards.
Thanks for the meal.
You should have a good rest for today.
Huh?
Ochi-san?
Senpai?!
Have a good rest.
What the hell did just...
I can't move my body.
Ochi-san... Senpai...
Ochi-san! Minami-senpai!
Would you mind lowering your voice?
What is happening in here?
What are you planning to do to us?
You don't have anything to worry
about, I never poisoned you.
It's just a very typical sleeping medication.
I bet you're all exhausted for today.
It just happened to be more
effective than I anticipated.
It's a well-kept secret concoction of this shrine.
You can only barely move your body, right?
Why would you do this... Don't you understand
the situation we're all in right now?
Situation, you say? Of course I understand!
Isn't all this the fault of that girl's family?!
Right now, the whole island is a hellhole!
I saw what human nature is with my own eyes!
This is the will of the God!
I need to show Him more of this human nature!
He broke down from the terror by this epidemic?
A lot have already died but
we can just propagate again.
I'll make sure to impregnate her
and make her into a woman!
Tarja-san, Tarja-san!
It's fine if you want to wake everyone up for help.
But if you make a ruckus, they will come here.
What an elegant body she has. Even someone
as old as me got aroused while in the van!
I'm going to have Tarja-chan... I'm going
to do it with my daughter's best friend!
Her lacking tits are about
the same as her mother Erma.
But that is a turn-on in itself.
Alright, it's time to wake up.
That's sweet as nectar!
You're not waking up. That should
have woken up the princess.
Oh, that's right. There's another mouth down here.
What's this? I feel so light and flimsy.
It feels good!
Have you woken up? I knew that
a kiss down here will do the trick.
Tarja-san, get away from him!
Makoto-san...
Huh, what's this? My body is acting strange!
Should I take your virginity?
Tarja-san!
Makoto-kun...
Senpai? Thank goodness, you finally woke up.
You can move, right? My body is still...
Please, you should at least run by yourself. The priest is already...
I'd make sure to at least protect Ochi-san.
It's still Ochi-san for you even now.
Senpai?
You only had your eyes on Ochi-san.
What will happen when I run by myself?
You won't be protecting me.
You don't care about me, right?
Senpai... What are you trying to say?
Did she get infected? No...
Both of us have already been vaccinated.
It's not like four years ago. Did the virus mutate?
But an infection by contact...
Could it be contagious by mucous membrane?
Please get a hold of yourself, senpai!
You're annoying.
Senpai, please stop doing such a thing!
You really talk exemplary words.
Then, mind telling me what this is?
You're aroused. Was it from seeing Tarja-chan?
Oh, you're unexpectedly well-endowed.
You got stiff as a rod! I knew it.
But it's still covered in skin.
So, you're still a virgin, Makoto-kun.
You smell so lewd!
Senpai, you can't!
You can fend me off if you don't want it.
My body doesn't have the strength because of the drug...
Yeah right, the drug...
What, are you gonna come already?
You haven't even peeled your skin off, so not yet.
Senpai, it's coming out. It's coming out!
No, stop!
Bear with it. Look, I peeled your skin off!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
Nice to meet your splendid dick!
That girl have it in her.
I'll let her handle that boy.
Well then.
Uncle...
It's about time for us to begin as well.
No... Stop there.
No!
Eat this.
No, it stinks!
No!
Is that so. Then it can't be helped.
I'll just settle with the copulation!
Stop! You can't!
Father, help me! Sato—!
You shouldn't worry about them.
Your father and Sato should be
busy copulating at this moment.
She didn't want to but I gave them
my approval. They're both doing their best.
Y-You're lying!
I'm not lying!
What are you doing? You can't, father!
No... Stop, please let go of me!
No—!
But I was the one who took Sato's virginity.
That can't be... That's...
It hurts! Father!
That's so cruel! Sato...
It's embarrassing for me say it, but it's been
a while since I embraced a woman.
I acted unbecoming for my age and humped her down!
She took all of my accumulated baby juice in!
You're a beast! You're cruel!
Then, let's proceed.
You're tight as I expected.
No, stop! I don't want this!
Help me—!
Sato was able to do this, so you should be fine!
You're squeezing me tightly just
as I expected. I'll be taking you!
No... Help me! Father! Sato!
Haven't I told you already?
They're in the middle of copulation!
Is this something like a daughter trading?
Is it called like 'swapping' or what?
Stop saying weird things!
Pull it out!
I'm almost there! I'm reaching it! I'm able to reach it!
End this already. I can't take it, I can't take anymore!
That's right! Are you ready, Tarja-chan?
R-Ready?
Ready to accept it, I'm taking
about impregnating you!
Ouch... No... No!
If you only used your mouth from the start....
I might have reconsidered, although
that would still be impossible.
Having been backed up, who knows
how much I'm gonna shoot!
What I only know is that you'll
certainly be pregnant after this!
No—!
Take all of my juice! It's not only
Sato that's going to get it!
I'm coming, I'm coming! Deep inside! Even deeper!
Pull it out, pull it out! I don't want it inside!
I don't want to get pregnant!
It's feels hot—!
More, squeeze me! Keep on squeezing me!
No, this isn't happening.
It's pouring into me. I'm being creampied.
It's still coming inside me.
If he pours this much inside, I really will have a baby.
It's satisfying. It's a satisfying orgasm indeed.
Oops!
With this, you and Sato are now 'eskimo sisters'.
You're both expectant mothers too.
By having this posture, it won't spill out
and it will be able to flow deep inside.
You should stay in that position for a while, Tarja-chan.
What's happening in here?
That huge thing went inside Tarja-san?
Will she get pregnant from having that much inside her?
I'm begging you, please let me come! Please!
So, you want to come.
Makoto-kun, would you like to come...
...on my hands?
...in my mouth?
...on my breasts?
...or would it rather be,
inside my oozing hot pussy?
I wonder where you would want to.
I want to do it in your pussy!
I want to put my cock inside your pussy
and graduate from my virginity!
That's it?
You don't want to hump on me
like a dog and impregnate me?
I want that! I'll give you a creampie,
and pump your womb with
my baby seeds to knock you up!
Eh?! So I'm going to be knocked up.
What should I do—?
I think I'll stop here.
Nah, just kidding. I think you passed.
I'll have your virginity, Makoto-kun.
This... Such a thing...
Is Maakun-senpai going to have s-sex?
Beg for it, Makoto-kun.
Senpai! I'm begging you!
I'm begging you, please let me put it inside you!
Senpai's cock!
Hmm... Good job.
Your dick is now fully peeled off.
Here, here you go!
You now have an adult cock.
You're tearing it off! My cock is getting torn off!
I'll start moving.
Even when he's that cute, he now has an adult cock?
Did he lose his virginity?
It's melting! My cock feels like it's melting!
I'm also feeling good!
They even kissed? His first kiss should have been me.
He's moaning pathetically, but that's adorable!
I'll move more intensely and push it deeper, okay?
I don't want you coming on your own!
How is it? Does it feel good, Makoto?
Yes, it does!
But slow down a little!
Eh... No way! Here you go.
Go, go! Makoto-kun, do your best with your dick!
You're feeling good! It's feels good for me too!
Here you go!
Does it feel good?
Maakun-senpai, does it feel good?
I'm gonna come already! I'm coming!
If you come now, the pleasure will be over.
Do you want that? Do you want this to be over?
I don't want this to end! I want to keep going!
But... I want to come! Please let me!
Senpai, your voice sounds pathetic! But that's adorable!
Where do you want to shoot it?
Inside you! I want it inside you!
You really want to give me a creampie?
I want to do it! Creampie!
Is he coming? He's gonna come
inside Minami-senpai, right?
But that's okay! I want to see Maakun-senpai's orgasm,
so he should come inside Minami-senpai!
Wanting to knock a girl up at the same
time it graduated from virginity...
What a bad dick.
Is he coming inside Minami-senpai? That's not fair!
I also want it, Maakun-senpai's baby juice!
Alright, you can pour your fluffy,
oozy and hot stuff inside me!
Give me your gooey semen!
You see, it's my first time to do it raw
and this will be my first creampie!
I'm only doing this for you, Makoto-kun.
Senpai! I'll make sure to knock you up!
I'll definitely knock you up!
I can feel it. You're now inside my womb.
You're really ready to impregnate me.
Senpai—!
Shoot it all inside me.
I'm coming—!
We're not done with just this, right?
I want you to satisfy me even more.
Right, Makoto-kun?
What's this, did getting stepped on felt
that good? What an actual pervert.
You're gonna amuse me even more.
Isn't that right, Makoto-kun?
Maakun-senpai...
What an unbelievable girl.
You have the audacity to masturbate
while watching your friends have sex and one get raped.
Who wouldn't notice that?
I was...
That's not it at all!
That not it at all!
As expected from a daughter of the Ochis.
I... I...
Me being from the Ochi family
has nothing to do with that!
That might be how you think, since you were
still kept dark about the secrets your family.
But as a daughter of the Ochi family,
you have to take responsibility.
R-Responsibility?
You should bear my child as well!
It surely will hurt if I suddenly put this in.
Please stop this! Please, I'm begging you!
Hey, young lady.
How about sucking me with
that mouth of yours instead?
Doing that first will lubricate it and reduce the pain.
And I'm old as well so if I come once,
I most likely won't be able to have a sex later.
What should I do? What should I...
And you might be able to give your
virginity to that senpai of yours.
Maakun-senpai!
Well then, I'm tired of waiting.
Wait! Please wait!
I'll do it.
Hmm? I can't hear you.
Wait, I'll suck it! I'll eat the whole thing!
That's not right. Aren't you going to beg for it.
Please let me give you a fellatio.
Please let me eat your cock
using my dirty mouth-pussy!
ALRIGHT!!!!!
Have a good taste of it!
It's huge... I'm choking on it!
Oops! Forgive me.
You were going to suck me.
Go on.
It's so huge!
Wow, so this is what a cock is.
Maakun-senpai's cock...
This is more splendid compared to Maakun-senpai's!
As expected from a daughter of the Ochis!
I'm coming!
He's coming... What an incredible orgasm!
I can't swallow this much!
I'm gonna get pregnant from
my mouth with that amount!
My stomach got full of it.
Forgive me. It seems that it's futile.
No, this isn't not what you promised!
You said you won't do it if I used my mouth!
I told you so... That if you're this wet enough
you won't feel as much pain, right?
No—!
Wow, you're squeezing me this much!
I can't believe how fast this girl learns!
No!
It's inside... It's penetrating me inside!
Alright, I'm almost there! Take everything in!
It hurts! It's so tight! You can't!
I'm shooting it inside! I'm going to
shoot my baby juice inside you now!
No! Don't shoot it inside!
It's so deep! Stop groping me!
Don't suck it!
Stop sucking my tit! Stop nibbling on it!
My tits will get stretched out!
You'll tear it off!
No... Even if you suck on them, nothing will come out!
Nothing will come out of my tits!
You'll tear my nipples off!
My first kiss...
I can't get enough of kissing with young girls!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
Get knocked up! Get knocked up!
Maakun-senpai, Maakun-senpai!
Help me, I'm going to get knocked up!
This old man will impregnate me in front of you!
That's a nice expression!
Are you getting aroused now
that you'll soon be impregnated?
Then take all of this. I'll shoot a lot for you!
No way! He's coming inside me? No—!
I'm coming—!
Alright, it's about time to introduce you to others.
Well, I'm sure that they will all welcome you.
Things are going to get busy.
They already reached here!
I won't allow them to interfere in here!
Come here, you mindless freaks!
It's okay now. Stand up, everyone.
We're going away from here!
S-Senpai... You weren't infected...
In any case, we have to get away from here first!
Is everyone still fine?
It's okay. We're alright!
You see, girls are stronger than you think.
And we're resilient too.
And we're very lewd as well, senpai!
That's right.
We'll make sure that we're... going to survive from this!
Even if... the world even ends.
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization