Ahh... it's gotten hard...
Sensei's dick.
Rubbing on it feels good.
I'm inserting it in now, okay?
Into my... virgin pussy.
Aha, I'm doing it with Sensei.
I'm doing it with Sensei!
Faster, faster, faster!
Hey, hey.
Until I cum we're not going to stop.
More... give me more.
Your dick... your dick is twitching faster and faster...
It's getting harder...
More and....
I'm cumming... I'm gonna cum.
I-I'mcumming.
infection
All of a sudden something unbelievable happened...
The exact cause of it is still unknown.
On that day, in our school...
No...
Disastrous outbreak of infected people in the capital!
A mysterious new type of virus seems to
Violent outbreak in all inner city areas. Current disastrous outbreak resembles
the Touhoku infection disaster from 4 years ago. The government calls for extreme caution
Throughout the town is seemed like a strange virus spreading.
And then...
There...
Good! It's moving around more... more, more!
Ah.
My clit! Bite it a bit, licking alone isn't enough!
If you don't do it properly, I'm gonna suffocate you.
It's gotten hard.
Rubbing on Sensei's dick feels so good.
I'm inserting it in now, okay?
Into my... virgin... pussy.
W-Wait!
My hymen has been torn.
It hurts, and yet it feels great.
The dick is grinding... it's going deeper...
Come on, lick and suck!
I'm so wet... make me cum. Make me cum!
Oh no... this is... great.
Sex is... amazing!
My pussy is hot.
This dick feels good.
I'm about to let it out... I'm about to let it out!
Fast... faster, faster!
Cover me with your semen!
It's coming! Sensei's dick is throbbing.
Sensei is going to spray his dirty semen into his student's pussy.
No... I'm cumming.
Cum! Fill me with Sensei's thick semen.
Me too! I'm cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming...!
Come on...
Please...
Sex, I wanna do it...
Hurry into my pussy,
I can't hold back...
Nii-chan...
What the hell is happening?
I don't really know.
Seems like you become strange if you
do something sexual with them.
Normally, this would be really a great offer but...
What are you saying at a time like this?
We have to run away fast.
You're right. Anyway, let's go outside!
Wait a sec...
Sensei... lick me more...
Le-Let me go.
Please stay calm.
Anyway, thanks for the meal.
Well then...
I'm gonna take care of the butthole.
Stop... licking and inserting your finger
at the same time... take it out!
Oh wow, his dick has gotten big.
It's tastes a bit salty... mmmh.
Hey, don't slack off, make my pussy feel good.
Me too, my pussy is feeling it.
Balls... My balls.
His butt hole is twitching as if it's happy.
I wonder how far it can stretch?
I can't fit any more of his dick inside.
I think it's about to cum.
It's about to burst already?
We're gonna let you cum a lot okay?
No good, I'm about to...
Well then... this is the finishing blow.
It's hot and delicious.
This hot semen, there's just lots of it.
That looks nice.
Milk, penis milk.
It's coming out.
Sex.
Tsugumi.
Is there a place where we can hide?
Eh? Umm.
How about the club cafeteria?
The cafeteria? Alright.
Let's go.
Your dick is hard, it's stirring me up.
My pussy is dripping, it's unbelievable.
It's too rough... I'm gonna cum.
It's ok! Cum inside!
Give me your thick cum.
Give me your hot stuff!
More... give me more of it.
Cum lots!
No way... I came just a moment ago...
I'm not done yet!
I still want your dick!
Let me go.
No, no!
Until I cum I won't let you go.
Thrust it in me more!
That's good, it's hitting the right spot.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
St-Stop it.
Ahh, your dick is hard and feels good.
I never knew that the starting position could
make his dick feel so good in me.
My pussy is throbbing.
If you move like that, I'm gonna cum.
Look, everyone.
I'm being looked at... they're looking at me.
Come on, here, do it properly.
Move your hips!
You're getting that arouse from your butt?
So you get horny from your butt.
You uncircumcised pervert!
His dick is starting to twitch a lot.
It's getting faster.
More. I want you to cum more!
I'm going to squeeze more of it.
Just do it.
Release it all inside me!
More, give me more.
More of your cum, please...
Anybody!
Is anyone still there?
I'm Seino from the swimming club!
Open it please!
Is that really you Tsugumi-chan?
Shizuka-chan!
Thank goodness you're safe.
Both of you too, thank goodness you were able to get here.
Here, come inside.
The situation was also quite bad here earlier.
Surrounded by the infected...
Are the only survivors here women?
Some of the teachers were still here earlier.
But they went to look for help outside, and then...
There doesn't seem to be anyone
outside who's still sane anymore.
They're probably also infected by now.
Is that so...?
Umm, sorry to break the mood,
but can I use the shower?
I'm drenched in their fluids.
It feels pretty gross.
Well, that can't be helped.
I'm gonna go get a change of clothing.
The cafeteria here has food and water,
so I guess we'll be okay for now.
Nii-chan.
Tsu-Tsugumi?
Nii-chan, thanks for saving me.
I was really happy that you did.
Hey,Tsugumi.
Wh-What are you doing?
My body suddenly felt hot, and I can't hold back.
Idiot, stop that!
Nii-chan, you can touch me too if you want to.
My warm and tender parts.
Look here, it's overflowing.
How is it? Does it feel good Nii-chan?
Y-Yeah.
Nii-chan, touch me more.
I'm going to make you feel good as well, okay?
Nii-chan, does it feel good?
I'm quite good at this right?
You know,
I practiced a lot with Nishimi-kun at the swimming club.
What?
Surprised?
We did it in the shower room...
...last summer.
T-Tsugumi, you're...!
Wanna know how we did it?
You want to know, right?
This feels good!
More... Do it more...
They say it hurts at first,
but it didn't hurt for me at all.
I felt really horny.
We did it everday during summer break.
We did it, many times, in a single day.
That's...
Nii-chan, you can cum a lot if you want to.
Squirt lots of that hot semen!
It's coming out.
The fluids of love is rushing out.
Nii-chan, that's cute.
Tsugumi-chan, what are you doing?
Nii-chan, are you aware of this?
This is... don't tell me?
Amazing, right?
Mikami-senpai taught me how to do this.
Mikami-senpai?
He's an alumni of this school, and was
the coach of the swimming club.
He had his perverted eyes on me for quite sometime.
That's enough...
Listen.
I want you to hear my story.
I was invited on the same day, after he tried to talk to me,
and then he made a total mess of me.
He used every part of me,
and even came five times.
He seemed to be more interested in blowjobs
and titty fucks than actual sex.
He also taught me lots of things about it.
This isn't good...
Anymore and...
Well? Feels great right?
Everyone says that it feels so good
that they can't resist for too long.
Isn't this amazing?
You're cock is going wild between my breasts.
You want to cum already right?
It's okay.
I'll drink every single drop of it
So you can cum all you want.
No need to hold back.
Spray it on my breasts, I want you to
use my breasts and cum all over me.
Make your cum's scent mark itself onto my body.
Please cum.
Cum lots.
Release it all!
T-Tsugumi...
Wow...
It's hot, thick,
and has a very strong smell.
No... I can't stop...
Even I can't resist...
...with this erotic scene.
It's been a long time since I did it with a virgin cock.
It's been a long time?
The last time was when I did it with Mikami-senpai.
Underclassmen Kuroda-kun and Oshiki-kun saw us.
They then asked me to let them do it.
Both of them looked quite cute so,
we had a threesome at Kuroda-kun's place.
It was really something.
When I said I couldn't do anymore,
they had already cum eight times.
They came lots and lots.
They said my pussy was the best.
Me too.
I also want to have sex with you.
I want to lose my virginity with you.
Okay then.
Because I love you, Nii-chan.
Then, I'll insert it now.
Oh wow...
So this is real sex...
A raw cock...
Your cock feels very good.
I'm cumming...!
Don't just cum yet.
If you try to hold on,
I'll do something great for you.
Something great?
You see,
I've already had sex a lot of times.
My butt,
my breasts,
and my mouth.
They've all been cummed on a lot,
but my pussy though, has never had anyone cum inside.
This means that I'm still clean there, from
the tip all the way to my womb.
I'm going to give that opportunity to you,
as a reward for saving me...
I'm going to let you takeaway that virginity, by cumming inside.
I want you to let it all out.
Cum inside...
Cum a lot inside!
This is...
...really horny.
Tsugumi-chan, I'm about to cum too.
My pussy is going to cum.
During my first time with Nishimi-kun in the
shower room, we did it at least three times.
It was great.
Three times?
And that was your first time?
During last year's O-bon festival, I did
it with Mikami-senpai at his place.
His parents and other household members
were out so we just kept doing it.
We had lots and lots of sex.
Damn, damn, damn!
I also had farewell sex with Kuroda-kun and
Oshiki-kun during their graduation.
We used three packs of condoms...
Stop it already.
You bitch,
I want you to cum!
I'm your younger sister.
I'm your younger stepsister!
And I'm now being used as an outlet for sex by my brother!
Not yet...!
I'm the one to let you cum.
I want you to cum lots.
Release lots of semen inside me.
I'm cumming.
I'm gonna cum!
Oh no.
I'm cumming.
I'm also about to cum.
Your cum is about to fill me up,
and I'm cumming with it!
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
So this is... what real sex feels like.
It felt really good.
Let's do it more.
Let's keep doing it raw.
I want you to cum more inside me.
Those eyes...
Tsugumi-chan, and Kasumi-san,
both of them are infected already.
But before that...
Let's give Shizuka-chan, who was peeking all this time,
a little punishment.
That's right.
It'd be embarrassing if someone just simply
masturbates while watching us.
No way... so they knew?
It's okay, Shizuka.
Let's all feel better.
With me,
and with Nii-chan.
I'll do it for you.
No...
No, no, no.
No!
No.....!