Hey, wanna go to my house today?
There's this interesting stuff...
Ah... Sorry, Na-chan.
Today's sort of, you see...
What?
Is there anything else more important
for you that with this Nanao-chan?
No, there isn't!
But really, what are you up to? Hmm?
Err... You see...
Umm...
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, There is... Is it about this? This one!
Today as well, huh.
There's no such thing
like "today as well" on it!
So boys are more important
than your girlfriends?
Oh, I'm such a lonely lady.
I already said that it's not like that...
It can't be helped,
I'll just invite the others.
Na-chan!
Well, let's hang out next time.
Okay then, see you tomorrow!
Telephone Call
Are you okay, Misaki?
Y-Yeah... I'm fine.
By the way, Miki, are you
sure about this?
I'm not really scared.
Hey!
Who are you going out with today?
We're about to go shopping.
Huh? Are you not with Nagisa today?
You see, girls in puberty
are busy with sexy stuff.
Telephone Call
Looking for VIP Men: 0120-57-XXXX
I'm on the Heavy Side: 0120-42-XXXX
Looking for Older Men: 0120-52-XXXX
Looking for ****-types: 0120-73-XXXX
Looking for Softcore SM: 0120-72-XXXX
In a mood today for...
Two-shot: 0120-01-XXXX
TC Chat: 0120-51-XXXX
Phone Sex: 0120-08-XXXX
SM Chat: 0120-58-XXXX
Super Two-shot Speed Dial: 120-666-XXX
Don't overdo it.
Both of you should properly
enjoy youth just like Nagisa!
Misaki...
Kanzen Mushuusei (Fully Uncensored)
Is sensei not coming yet?
He's taking so long!
Maybe he's stuck in
a meeting or something...
Nagisa...
Sensei...
Wow, I already got like this!
I-I'm gonna come...
Sensei...
You there! What the hell are you doing!
Hello? Umm, It's me.
Alright.
So, how much would it be?
Then, let's go with that.
How is it? Is Misaki-chan alright?
Ah, I think she's won't be able to go on.
I see...
Hey, I'm just wondering...
Is Misaki-chan pregnant?
So that was it. I knew it...
Is that his boyfriend's child?
Kids these days sure
are on another level...
It's rare for girls like you two to do this
so you piqued my interest, Miki-chan...
Oh, so that's it...
I see... So that's why you went
here together with her.
So, what should we do now?
Huh?
Now that Misaki-chan can't go on,
it means that you'll have to do this alone.
But this doesn't really have anything
to do with you, so shall we end it here.
Umm...
Right, You'll have to return
what I gave earlier.
But if you'll work hard enough for
the price of you two, I'll overlook it.
Doesn't Misaki-chan need the money badly?
U-Umm... I think that I should...
I'm asking what the hell are you doing!
No way! You can't!
This isn't what it looks like! I'm not...
It's not like that!
Really... I swear...
And here I was wondering
what you were up to.
Jeez... What do you mean wrong
when you're like that?
It's your fault, sensei!
It's your fault! I ended up
like this all because of you!
You knew nothing about
what I'm going through...
I see, so it was my fault.
Sensei?
Then, I should take responsibility
for it as a teacher.
Huh?
Heave-ho!
W-W-Wait!
No can do! Come on,
take your panties off.
Spread your legs.
No! We can't do this!
Huh? For someone who
keeps saying no,
you offer no resistance whatsoever.
I easily spread your legs open.
I wonder why?
It already got like this.
You wanted to do it so much that
you couldn't hold yourself back.
Fingering yourself in this place...
Do you even know what you're doing?
What would you do if someone
else besides me came here?
I know... I get it already... So...
Hurry up! Your fingers aren't enough!
Alright, let's do the real thing!
Please do so.
I haven't heard you well, Miki-chan.
I'm saying... Umm...
Please do so.
Okay, I got it.
Let's begin, then.
What's wrong? Is it bigger
compared to your boyfriend's?
Could it be that you haven't
taken one yet in your mouth?
I'm fine. I'll do it.
I never would have guessed
from how you looked like...
You even know how to
do that technique.
Kids these days really
are unbelievable!
Did you have a way older
boyfriend who taught you this?
Or did you try to learn this
from watching videos?
You'd put the pros in
shame just with this.
Here, I'm gonna shoot it out.
How about I come in your mouth?
I-I'm coming!
Miki-chan...
Drink my juice just like that.
I'm sorry.
You're so good that I quickly came.
Okay, it's my turn to give you
pleasure next until I recover.
Now, go up on the bed.
Are you nervous?
Don't worry, I'll be gentle.
Come on, Miki-chan.
Spread your legs wider.
Ah, okay...
You're aroused, aren't you?
Your panties are drenched.
Th-That's not true.
Look here.
You're dripping of juice here.
You know it yourself.
You're more sensitive than I expected.
I'm looking forward to this.
Come on, hold your legs like this.
You're amazing down here.
It looks so pretty.
It's pink and the shape
isn't disfigured yet.
No...
Seriously, I never saw one
this beautiful before!
You really are adorable, Miki-chan.
Ah... Oh, that's right.
Mister...
Look, do you know what this is?
So you know what this is.
But is it your first time seeing one?
Shall we use this one for a bit?
Here, I'm putting it in.
Oh, I never knew about it.
You're actually a very lewd girl, Nagisa.
You're moaning this much.
It's way more different
than how you usually are.
So, you usually keep your voice
down to avoid getting caught.
That's right, you don't
have to hide it anymore.
I already found out how lewd you are.
That's right, it's the best for
the young ones to be honest.
If it feels good then you have to say so.
Come on, say it.
You're wrong! I-I'm...
Am I wrong? How am I?
Don't! No, not like this...
No—!
What's wrong? Are you coming?
You're coming, right?
No—! I'm scared!
No... No... No... No... No!
It's okay, come.
I'll have a good look of your most
embarrassing facial expression.
You can't!
Any more of this and...
I'm... I'm already...
Have you had your fill now?
By the way...
You said that you wanted
a cellphone last time, right?
Huh?
If that's so...
How is it?
You're fine with only this
much vibration, right?
Good... That's good.
Come on, open your mouth.
Good girl.
Alright, it's about time...
I'm putting it in.
N-No, it's too big!
Try to endure it a little.
Ouch!
It's alright.
Your body will get used to it in no
time and you'll start feeling good.
Doesn't this feel good?
Your clit is directly
feeling the vibration.
Wh-What's this? No—!
There's no way that you hate this.
You're dripping a lot.
I bet that it feels good.
I'll give it to you even harder.
Hey... How is it, Miki-chan?
The vibration is set to maximum.
It's incredibly vibrating inside, right?
No... No... No!
No more! No!
Don't do it so hard!
Doesn't it feel good?
Here you go, here!
It hurts! No way, not that hard!
No! Don't do that!
I'm... I'm...
It's okay.
You can come, here you go!
Nagisa!
Oops!
Keep it up just like that!
No~!
Sensei, when did you start filming me?!
Just a bit earlier when
I was giving it to you!
Alright, shall we begin?
Y-You seem way more different
than I thought, sensei.
I'll go to the restroom!
Wait!
Meow! Meow! Meow! Meow!
Hey, hey! Just calm down.
It's not like I'm gonna do anything bad.
That's a lie! You're definitely lying!
It's a given that you're thinking
about something weird whenever
you make that kind of face!
That's right! Something like that.
Shall we start now?
D-D-Don't tell me...
No, never ever!
I'll never ever do something
so embarrassing!
Is that so? You hate it that much?
You don't need the cellphone, then?
Sensei, you're so mean!
Trickster! Con-man!
And also, underhanded!
And also, and also... Umm...
That's how adults are.
I won't settle for anything but
the newest phone model!
Yeah, yeah. I got it. Hurry, stand
up there and pull your skirt up.
Cell-pho-ne!
Alright already!
And for today, we have Nagisa-chan
in the school premises.
Shall we get the afterschool
pissing show started?
Oh, don't take your panties off.
Pervert!
What's wrong? Come on!
It's no use, it won't come out!
It can't be helped. I'll lend you a hand.
Y-You don't have to!
It' alright, okay?
I'm good at making pees come out.
Wait!
No, it's coming out!
You can let it all out.
No...
Sensei... Don't!
Looks like it's coming
out! Do it like usual.
Splash it out, make it splash!
I can't, I can't...
No—!
Whoa, it's coming out! You held it in
so now it's gushing out with force!
That's embarrassing, Nagisa-chan!
No, don't look!
Stop looking!
No way... I'm... I'm...
No, no way!
My pee won't stop!
You sure are lewd, Nagisa.
You're a pervert for being able
to pee in a place like this.
I'm doing such a thing in this room.
Oh-oh... Look at what
you did on the floor.
I wonder what your classmates
would think if they saw this.
That's... That's because...
...you told me to!
That's right...
Everything is my fault.
Look, your panties are drenched and
your cute spot can be seen through it.
No way! I'm dirty down there, sensei!
That's why I'm cleaning it up for you.
You're kidding, no way...
You're slurping my pee!
If you suck it that much...
No...
Wait!
You can't go home when your
panties are this wet, right?
Huh? What's this, Nagisa-chan?
This hot fluid that makes
a string isn't your pee.
So you get aroused from peeing.
That's a lie... You're wrong!
I'm not lying. I took a good shot of the whole thing.
Am I right? You got aroused, right?
Y-Yeah...
I knew it. you really
are lewd, Nagisa-chan.
Okay then, I'll have to
give you a reward.
Come on, go over the desk.
Okay.
Sensei, are you still filming this?
Of course.
I'm going to record putting
it inside you too, Nagisa.
I'm going inside you down here, Nagisa.
It's being stretched wide
like it's gonna get torn apart!
I'm filming it all!
I'm getting a good shot of your
fidgeting asshole as well!
No, don't film that!
No!
Nagisa, there still are
people inside the campus.
I know that you're feeling good,
but you have to lower your voice.
Th-That's because... Not again...
Come on, they'll notice us.
What will we do if they saw us like this?
No—!
Does it feel good?
Hey, Nagisa. Turn more towards
here. Look at the camera.
I won't be able to film
your face while coming.
No, don't!
I don't want you filming that!
Hey, Nagisa. You're about to come,
aren't you? Show me your face!
No... No...
Good work for today.
Don't loiter around
and go straight home.
Don't get into stuff like prostitution!
I'm sorry, did you say something?
I'm a good girl so it's alright!
So don't forget about
my cell-pho-ne, okay?
You came, Miki-chan.
You're so adorable.
Take a look at this.
I already recovered
with this much energy.
Miki-chan...
Huh? W-Wait!
That's the wrong spot! That's my ass.
It's alright, I'm going
to teach you about it.
Here I come!
No—!
No! It hurts, it hurts!
Pull it out! Please pull it out!
Stop moving! Ouch, I'm begging you!
There, it feels so good!
Your asshole is so narrow and tight!
Ouch!
Oh... Miki-chan!
I'm going to make you feel better, okay?
No! No way!
Miki-chan, you can come if you want to.
Mister...
No, no... Stop! No!
No! No—!
No—! Miki!
Help me—!
Did you have fun yesterday?
A lot!
I haven't slept enough today.
Me too!
Good morning!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization