How filthy.
This doesn't look anything like the genuine piece.
However, it was right of me to have done some practice...
Instead of attempting on the genuine piece right from the start.
Humans aren't suitable.
They'll rot right away and become moldy.
If I plaster and let them dry, they lose more and more of their feminine essence.
I ought to collect more materials for my work.
To obtain the girl who resembles the genuine piece.
Girl in the Shell
Brought U By JPz Records & Masurenai
I heard there's a man carrying
a huge black egg with a doll inside of it.
Yeah...
Furthermore, the doll had no arms or legs,
because there's no way they could fit it inside the egg.
Yeah...
But since the doll closely resembles a human being,
you would think it could've been a corpse.
If you take a closer look...
You'll see that it's neither a doll nor a corpse.
It's a girl with no arms or legs living
inside the shell of a black egg.
If ever you encounter that man, you ought
to tell him that you're not the “Girl in the Shell.”
Otherwise, you'll trade places with the girl inside the black shell.
Episode 2
Tokisaka
We haven't informed the school about it yet,
But apparently, there are students
who haven't returned home yet.
So, that makes her the fourth victim, huh?
Thanks to your help, we were able to identify the victim easily today.
Nevertheless, who the funk that it'd turn out to be
four students in a row from the same academy.
I don't think we can consider this a coincidence any longer.
Got that right.
Ouch!
I'm sorry. Was it too hot?
Heh, this is nothing.
Something like this is orange juice, compared to
the boiling water we'll make the culprit drink.
You said it.
Yes, this is the Tokisaka Residence.
It looks like school's been canceled.
They don't have much of a choice with the current situation.
The higher-ups still haven't been informed...
About all the victims who everyone's
been fussing about, went to the same academy.
However, if the culprit is doing a thorough check on the students,
Then the schoolgirls aren't necessarily safe
even if they're not going to the academy.
Besides...
It seems the academy requires students to wear their uniforms off-campus.
There's a good chance for the culprit
to take note of them if they're wandering around alone.
Ah, Goddamn it.
I have no idea what's going on in that damn culprit's mind!
He doesn't give a damn where he dumps the limbs,
yet we can't even find the bodies!
It's related to his objective...
That's something he wants us to believe.
Could it be necrophilia?
That would be easy to understand if that were the case.
Brother.
Miss Kuchiki called just now.
Oh? Touko did?
She said she didn't have to speak to you directly.
But, she left you a message.
What did she say?
Shinzou Mamiya Exhibit
Kept you waiting?
Not at all.
I just got here myself.
Besides, there's still time to spare.
That's good to know.
Actually, I apologize for making come all the way out here.
I don't mind.
Anyway, let's move on to your request.
Although I wouldn't call it an official report.
Okay.
Hey, do you want to look at some paintings while we talk?
I want to hear what you have to say, Mr. Detective...
But I don't feel like going to your office or a café.
Sure.
I found out several things.
Where should I start?
You don't need to be conserved about the fact
that I'm not the real daughter of the Kuchiki family.
So you knew?
Checking my family registration is not that big of a deal.
It's just... I haven't informed my mother
and everyone else that I do know.
I see.
There's also the fact that before she adopted you,
you used to live in Kurashiki, Okayama.
I discovered that your biological mother's
name is Misa Nakahara.
You found out that much?
Set a thief to catch a thief.
Let's just say I used to have a lot of contacts
in the bureaucratic offices back in the day.
It seems I was right about you, Mr. Detective.
Thank you for the compliment.
Still, we were fortunate that there were still
official records available, despite the chaos after the war.
Anyway,
That's all that I've found so far.
I could easily find more if I talk
to your current family members.
I'd... prefer you not to.
I may not remember what my birth parents look like,
but my foster mother is like a real mother to me.
I understand.
Then, I'll have to go to Kurashiki to investigate
more about this Misa Nakahara.
Unfortunately, I don't have to time to leave town at the moment.
Is it about that case?
Yeah.
Sorry, but people's lives are at stake.
I know that.
I'm not in that much of a rush anyway.
I'm relieved to hear that.
By the way, when you said
you wanted me to find the real you, you meant...
Finding your real parents to clarify your true identity.
Is this what you really want?
How I wonder...
That may probably be some of my reasons,
But I'm not exactly sure what I really want to find.
I guess that's what I want you to find, Mr. Detective.
How vague.
That's right.
It's vague.
I am vague.
Touko tells me that I'm a level-headed person,
But the truth is I don't know who I am or where I stand.
I'm an fleeting existence.
But it's not just me.
Everything I see appears vague,
as if they're shrouded in mist.
I never consider anything I see beautiful.
Even so, you still paint?
What I paint is neither a portrait nor a landscape.
What I paint is what's within my heart.
Within your heart?
Indeed, that's why I can't manage to finish any of my pieces.
Is that so?
But for someone who can't see the beauty in things,
you seem rather attracted to Shinzou Mamiya's paintings.
I see the darkness in Shinzou Mamiya's paintings.
I don't see the beauty in things,
but I do see the darkness within.
The darkness?
Indeed.
What makes a colorful landscape beautiful is the darkness.
Darkness is not vague.
That darkness lies within both you and I, Mr. Detective.
Your heart is shrouded in darkness.
But, there's still light within the darkness.
It's may be faint,
But it still shines upon my heart.
Like I'm on fire, and it hurts...
As for this painting,
I can see the same darkness that resides within me.
This is the...
“Girl in the Shell.”
When I learned about this painting,
it made me decide to seek out who I really am.
I wanted to make things clear to myself.
That the “Girl in the Shell” and I are...
Touko!
Touko?
I came here to look at the “Girl in the Shell.”
Who would have guessed that I'd meet you here.
Touko, why's this man?
Don't you remember?
He's a Detective Reiji Tokisaka.
Touko, why are you with someone like him?
We had a meeting.
Just a little rendezvous.
Hey, come on now.
Touko, don't be fooled!
You mustn't be alone with a man.
The relationship me and Mr. Detective
have is nothing indecent.
He would never deceive me.
It's not like you to make excuses!
What ever happened to the usual Touko that I know?!
The Touko I know is refined and beautiful like this painting!
You have to shine and be more radiant than anything else!
Touko...
This painting isn't radiant at all.
You shouldn't compare me
with the “Girl in the Shell” like that.
What?
Ever since Touko met you,
she's been acting stranger and stranger.
Touko, you should stop hanging out with this man.
Touko...
Touko, Let's go!
Observe silence within the art museum.
Stella...
S-Sorry.
Notebook Title: “Corpse Mutilation Case Report No.3”
Notebook Title: “Corpse Mutilation Case Report No.4”
Tokisaka Detective Bureau
Come in.
Wasup?!
Oh, it's just you, Dumbass.
Yukari isn't here today.
I know.
I came here to talk to you today, Detective.
Also, quit calling me Dumbass!
Here for another interview?
That's half of the reason why I'm here.
Detective, you're investigating
the mutilation case everyone's talking about, right?
Beats me.
Don't lie to me!
Yukarin told me.
I didn't expect Yukari to be such a blabbermouth.
And so... so...
I figured I could help out in the investigation.
No thanks.
Come on! Don't say that!
Besides, what could a schoolgirl possibly do anyway?
Don't underestimate the great Tsuzuriko!
Today, I came bearing some vital information.
Shell of
Sheol
What's this? Your novel or something?
Oh, I'll bring mine next time.
This one's written by Shin Katsuragi, “Shell of Sheol.”
Shell of Sheol
by Shin Katsuragi
It's a story about a boy who loses his mother.
For the sake of copying what his mother look like,
he meets a girl...
and chops off a her arms and legs, or so the story goes.
Was his mother a paraplegic?
I'm not sure.
He never mentioned it.
Well, doesn't this look similar to the case?!
Probably some coincidence.
No, it's not!
There's definitely a connection!
The killer might have read this novel!
Or maybe...
Shin Katsuragi himself might be behind all this.
You're reading way too much into this.
That's why I hate writers.
There's no way the culprit would write anything
related to his crimes, just for the world to see.
You think so?
Nevertheless, there's a high possibility the culprit
will target a schoolgirl from Ouba Girls Academy.
Keep a low profile.
Fine!
If that's the case, I'll investigate about it myself!
Investigate? How are you going to do that?
Of course, I'd do more interviews!
Actually, I already got Mr. Katsuragi address
through my connections from the publisher.
I figured I'll get nervous meeting Katsuragi,
So I want you to tag along, Detective.
Don't tell me you're a diehard Shin Katsuragi fan?
Eek!
What? You just want to meet
your favorite authors, is that it?
That's not it!
Detective, you're being such a meanie!
Hey! Wait up, Dumbass!
Quit calling me Dumbass!
Jeez.
I don't have time messing around with schoolgirls.
“Shell of Sheol,” huh?
The boy's mother
was very beautiful.
She was inside
the black shell.
No way.
This can't be the case.
No matter how similar they are...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's gotten rather big now.
See?
Gosh, for a police officer, you lack decency.
I'm a diligent person at work,
But I got to let loose when I'm at home.
I've cleaned it a bit.
Would you mind wrapping it up?
Sure thing.
Yukiko...
Gosh...
Couldn't hold it in?
My bad.
Yet, you're still hard.
Can you still keep up?
I still can't believe something this big can fit inside of me.
What are you saying?
Babies come out from there too, you know.
Well, if ever we decide to have a baby,
Would you mind making mine wider?
If you insist.
Reiji, it really is too big!
How is it, Yukiko?
Getting any wider?
How should I know!
B-But it f-feels so good!
Don't!
Yukari will hear us!
She had a long day.
She's sleeping like a log.
She's still just a kid.
So, moan all you want, she won't wake up.
Reiji! Reiji!
Yukiko!
Reiji, oh, Reiji!
It feels so good!
I'm...
I'm going to!
Yukiko, me too!
That... felt great...
Yukiko, let's settle down.
Do you mean it?
I do.
I'll protect you forever.
Touko!
I'm flattered, Mr. Detective.
Can you really protect me forever?
Yukiko!
Where's Yukiko?
Reiji!
You promised you'd protect me!
Was it a dream?
I understand.
I'll do what I can.
Yes.
My sincere apologies.
Brother, something terrible happened!
Apparently, Tsuzuriko didn't come home last night!
What did you say?!
I'll look around and search for her too!
Wait, Yukari.
It's not safe for Ouba Girls Academy students
to wonder alone in this current situation.
But...
Call Uozumi.
Let the police handle it.
You stay here.
I'm on the case.
Even the police won't take a missing girl lightly.
Okay.
“Shell of Sheol.”
Shin Katsuragi.
Shell of Sheol
by Shin Katsuragi
Investigations Department
What is it, Reiji?
It's freaking early in the morning.
What?!
Another schoolgirl is missing?!
Also, there's something I want you to look into right away.
A novelist by the name of Shin Katsuragi.
There's a high possibility that he's involved in the case.
About that guy you wanted me to look into...
Shin Katsuragi is just a pen name.
His real name is Shinji Mamiya.
Mamiya?
By any chance, is he related to Shinzou Mamiya?
Yeah.
I think he's his son or something.
But apparently, the public is unaware of it.
Also, his workplace is at Shimo.
It seems to be a cottage he inherited from his father.
In Shimo?
Did most of the crimes take place around that area?
Now that you mention it...
Hey!
Don't tell me...
This guy's the perpetrator?
I'm on the case.
Hey, Reiji!
Don't do anything reckless before we get there!
Tsuzuriko!
Dammit! Like hell I'll wait for Uozumi!
The “Girl in the Shell...”
I don't know if it's because of the police's sirens, but...
Shin Katsuragi...
Shinji Mamiya never came back to the crime scene.
On top of that...
We've placed a warrant for his arrest
for the serial killings spree case...
Unfortunately, the whereabouts
of Shinji Mamiya remained a mystery.
I've heard word...
About what happened to Miss Yosomiya.
How unfortunate.
It's all my fault.
If only I had paid more attention to her seriously...
Touko...
Mr. Tokisaka!
Mr. Tokisaka...
Mr. Detective.
What's the matter, Mr. Detective?
Touko, don't you ever leave my sight again!
Mr. Detective?
You won't turn into the “Girl in the Shell,” right?
“Girl in the Shell?”
Of course I won't.
Hurry up and find the real me.
Mr. Detective!
No...
You'll wrinkle my uniform...
No, not there!
It tickles!
Mr. Detective!
You're so wet.
Do you feel it?
Come on...
You're not supposed to say those out loud!
No! Not that!
I'll go mad!
I can... feel you... so much of you...
inside me, Mr. Detective...
Touko, is it all right if I move faster inside of you?
Sure...
Do it however you want.
It feels better for men to do it this way, doesn't it?
Touko!
Mr. Detective, I can feel it deep inside,
throughout my body!
I can't take it!
My mind's going blank!
Touko!
Mr. Detective!
Wanted: Shinji Mamiya
If anyone has information regarding to the
photographed man, please report to us immediately.
- Investigations Department
The shivering wind passes like a stroke on my cheeks.
Like a baby rebelling against the silence.
It held tight to its embrace,
Although the cage simply crumbled away.
Transcending the confined time and space,
The Azure Bird revealed a sign from the stars.
Even the darkside of the moon
Seems dear to me.
Through a waning fissure,
Like a waving tapestry,
I conceal a voiceless shout
Locked within my heart.
My outstretched hands slip away,
Yet my memories can't recall a thing.
This crude body lost in the midst of doubt
Struggles while drifting with a lingering miracle.