Work...
This is my job...
I have a task that I must
see through to the end.
Someone is watching me.
There's a person gazing warmly at me.
Kara no naka no
Kotori
(Little Birds in the Shell)
~Maiden of Despair: Ren Yuuki~
I don't know what it was about that girl that drew me to her.
If I had to guess,
I'd say it was her innocence.
Just like a magnetic pole
will attract its opposite,
she attracted the dark
and sordid side of me.
But what was she waiting for during those many months?
Hurry up, Papa!
Hold your horses.
This looks bad.
But I might be able
to do something about it.
I'll begin treatment right away.
Please do.
Is your house nearby?
Yes.
The weather's getting worse.
I'm sorry...
I'm all out of money,
so this is all I can give you.
I'm fine. You go ahead and eat.
Oh no, I'm not hungry at all.
I don't think your stomach's rumbling in agreement.
Is it really okay?
Yes.
In that case,
I will go ahead and eat.
Say, who's "Fahm"?
You were saying that name over and over in your sleep.
That's none of your business.
I-I'm sorry!
It's going to get colder.
What're you going to do?
You won't survive here.
My father will come for me.
Besides, I don't have
anywhere else to go.
If you don't mind,
you can come along with me.
Oh, she's an Oriental.
And a young one, at that.
Please, let her stay here
for the time being.
I'll put her to work.
She'll be useful to you.
Her name?
It's Ren Yuuki, sir.
I'll give you a trial period.
During your stay at my home, you must follow all the rules of the house.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Very well.
Ren, this will be
your room from now on.
Where did Foster go?
Apparently he had
some investigating to do.
He's leaving Ren
in our care for 2-3 days.
I sincerely apologize for my lateness.
Hmm. So was your investigation fruitful?
Yes. I believe you will be satisfied.
Is that so?
I see.
So that's how it is.
Good work.
I'll be counting on you in the future.
Yes sir.
Please excuse me.
You called for me, Mr. Dred?
Yes. Enter.
I hear you're a good worker, Ren.
Thank you very much.
I have good news for you.
We've received word from your father.
Eh? From my father?
He should be here for you soon.
Now, hurry back to your
room and wait for him.
Yes sir!
Father...
I get to see him...
Father... father!
I knew my father would
come and find me!
Ren, is that you?
Fa...ther?
Ren, I missed you so much!
Ren!!
Father!
Let me get a good look at you.
You really are Ren, right?
Ooohhh, my sweet little Ren!
Oh, Ren, Ren!
No, that tickles, Father!
Oh yeah...
So, you like that?
No, stop it, Father!
No... no...
No... stop it...
How about this?
Stop!
P-please stop, Father!
No, don't...
No, don't do this, Father...
No...
No...he isn't my father.
He'd never do something so awful.
No...
Father...
What happened to my real father...?
Father! Father?!
FATHER!!!
My father...
... is dead.
What was that? Did you
know about this, Clair?
No, I didn't... wait!
Please wait! Just leave
the matter alone for now.
Quiet, you!
What might this be?
Looks like an old newspaper.
"While en route to the station,"
"a man and a woman were
victims of a robbery."
"The man: deceased."
"The surviving woman:
lost consciousness."
"Hair: Black.
Eyes: Green."
This is talking about...
Ren?!
Why?
I thought I told you
never to question me!
But still...
No more!
That girl is a resident
of this mansion.
In accordance with the rules,
she must entertain its guests.
Weren't you there when
she agreed to that...
...on the day she came here?
Bear in mind that you too
have duties to fulfill, Foster.
I'm to blame.
If only I'd been
a little more careful.
I'll wash away...
...all the bad things
that have happened to you.
I'm against this.
She's too young.
I can do it myself.
Don't be so conceited.
Just as Dred said before,
there are all kinds of guests.
If there are guests
who prefer you...
...there are also ones who prefer Ren.
I haven't forgotten the promise I made with you.
Go back to bed,
in your own room.
Ren, you mustn't.
Spread your legs.
You've become so
obedient in so little time.
Thank you very much, Master.
Impressive, Foster.
Most impressive.
What a cute little girl.
What do you think?
Does she suit your tastes?
Yes. "Playtime" with her
should be fun.
Well then, enjoy yourself.
Take care of things, Mr. Foster.
Yes sir.
Now, come on over here.
It hurts...
No...
No...no...
No...stop...
No...
Don't look away.
Please stop!
No...
You showed me yours,
so I'll show you mine.
Come on!
No...noooo!
Now, now...
No, don't!
NOOOO!!
Father!
Father! Father!!
Ren!
I don't remember teaching you that.
Stop it, Ren!
That's an order.
That's about enough.
Put it down.
No... I want to be
with my father...
Don't do it.
You aren't alone.
You're not alone!
Forget about the past.
You can make new memories that will put your mind at ease.
Ah, Mr. Foster.
What happened to your hair?
Ren asked me to cut it.
Please let me stay here for awhile.
You want to? Well, you'd better work your hardest.
I will!
Oh, it's you!
You're all better now!
Thank goodness!
How cute...
Clair, do you know who "Fahm" is?
She's the one who created this garden.
Translation & Timing by Zalis