Brought U By JPz Records & Masurenai
Tokisaka Residence
Tokisaka Detective Bureau
Takashiro Clinic
I heard there's a man carrying
a huge black egg with a doll inside of it.
Yeah...
Furthermore, the doll had no arms or legs,
because there's no way they could fit it inside the egg.
Yeah...
But since the doll closely resembles a human being,
you would think it could've been a corpse.
If you take a closer look...
You'll see that it's neither a doll nor a corpse.
It's a girl with no arms or legs living
inside the shell of a black egg.
If ever you encounter that man, you ought
to tell him that you're not the “Girl in the Shell.”
Otherwise, you'll trade places with the girl inside the black shell.
Girl in the Shell
Episode 1
The man with a “Girl in the Shell...”
Such rumor can be heard recently
from gossips among teenage girls.
As a detective, I, Reiji Tokisaka,
was summoned by a former colleague detective Uozumi to a familiar coffee shop.
Welcome, Tokisaka.
Uozumi's waiting for you.
Hey, Reiji.
Hurry up and get over there.
Or I'll get jealous of you two getting all mushy over a cup of tea.
Cut it out. The thought alone gives me goosebumps.
The usual, if you may.
Coming right up.
What were you talking about with Kyouko?
Just some chitchat.
I wasn't hitting a move on her, so rest assure.
I-Idiot! I wasn't asking you about that.
So, why am I here for?
Got another mind-blowing case?
Yeah, I was thinking if you could lend a hand.
The case started a month ago.
We uncovered some severed limbs
resembling those of teenage girls.
Yeah, it's in the newspaper.
Something about multiple mutilated parts of dead teenage girls were sighted in numerous locations.
The tabloids and their authors wrote everything to whatever they please.
We haven't even confirmed if they're actually dead.
For certain, if they are from teenage girls,
we can't tell if they're young or old enough to be considered teenagers.
Nevertheless, that's all the clues we got.
However, based from the evidence present,
the police are investigating if this is a case of murder.
You guys did the autopsies, right?
Of course.
What's troubling is that there were signs
of life before the limbs were severed.
So they were butchered alive?
Furthermore, crucial pieces of evidence, the bodies, were yet to be found. Only the arms and legs are kept on site.
As of now, the sighted limbs are worth
the total of three teenage girls.
Also, we have no clues of the victims' identities,
let alone the culprit's objectives.
I gotta say that's a mind-blowing case indeed.
So how about it? Wanna give it a shot?
Yeah, I can't let a homicidal maniac run loose.
Luckily, it just so happened I don't have a case at the moment.
I'll be counting on you.
If so happened you need more info about severed limbs,
drop by Takashiro's clinic.
Natsume's place?
I can't stand that hag.
The feeling is mutual.
Is there anyone in the world who doesn't think otherwise about Natsume Takashiro?
I doubt it.
Hey, Tokisaka, what about your coffee?
Give it to Uozumi.
Well, I'll take your offer then.
Oh?
You better not involve Tokisaka
in anymore of your crazy cases.
He doesn't work for the police anymore.
I get it already.
Got something you want from me?
It seems I'm not cut out to be a detective.
Or should I have perhaps expected that
a detective would notice me tailing him?
Mr. Reiji Tokisaka.
How do you know my name?
How I wonder...
You've heard about me from my little sister, Yukari, right?
That uniform belongs to Ouba Girls Academy.
Plus, you faintly smell like my little sister.
To smell like your little sister,
what a degenerating thing to say.
It's nothing like that.
I'm talking about the scent of turpentine oil used in oil paintings.
It's most likely you're in the same fine arts club as my little sister.
As expected from Mr. Detective.
Excellent deductive skills.
I wouldn't call something this trivial deduction.
So?
It seems like you've been following me
ever since I came out of the café.
Do you need me for something?
Oh my, you saw through me as well?
All right.
I suppose you've passed.
My name is Touko Kuchiki.
I have a request.
What, just a request?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to find me...
The real...
The real me, okay?
Well then, Mr. Detective...
I'm counting on you.
Tokisaka
I'm back.
Welcome home. Dinner's ready.
All right, I'll have some.
Yukari.
Since you're in the fine arts club,
I assume you know a student named Touko Kuchiki, right?
Miss Kuchiki?
Why yes, I do know her.
But Brother, why exactly do you know her?
Kind of bumped into her.
So, what kind of a girl is she?
She's kind of unique, in a rather senseless individual is the best I can describe her.
I guess so.
Apparently, she is kind of a tomboy.
Everyone in the academy considers her as an odd person as well.
I rarely talk to her,
so there's no guarantee to what I say is true.
Is that so?
She knew that I'm a detective.
It sounded like she heard it from you.
Oh, that's because your name came to topic
when I was talking to some friends the other day.
When I mentioned that you're a detective,
she was sitting next to me and seemed interested.
She even asked me your name and workplace address.
Oh, come on...
No need to tell the whole world about it.
Was that wrong of me?
I thought it'd be fine since the academy and the teachers
already know my guardian's name and occupation.
Well, that's true...
The real me, huh?
Tokisaka Detective Bureau
Oh, holy shit!
Brother...
Yukari, good timing.
Clean this up for me?
Yukarin, your bro there?
Whoa, this place's trashed!
That was quite a greeting,
yelling out how trashed this place is.
Nice to meet you!
The name's Tsuzuriko Yosomiya!
Yukarin's bestfriend!
Tsuzuriko?
You know the Chinese character for “Spell”
in English spelling, right?
Yeah?
That's what's used to spell Tsuzuriko.
Note: The name, Tsuzuriko 「綴子」 can also be read Tojiko,
which means “Clumsy Girl” or plain “Dumbass.”
So, it's Dumbass then?
Oh, yeah! That's funny!
What the hell!
Quit talking amongst yourselves and changing
other people's names without asking!
Don't get mad, Dumbass.
Quit calling me Dumbass!
You're already getting along.
Anyway, what business do you and your bestfriend have here?
Tsuzuriko seems interested in detective stuff,
so I brought her along.
Another one?
Are all the girls in Ouba Girls Academy a bunch of detective maniacs?
Although Tsuzuriko's just a student,
she writes short articles for people's magazines.
She's a bookworm girl.
Wow, isn't that peachy.
Well, I've only been featured in
like three or four magazines.
So, in order for my work to hit the spotlight
I've decided to work on detective genres to spice things up.
Note: The Seishi Yokomizo Prize is a literary award.
I'm aiming for the Seishi Yokomizo Prize!
Note: Kogoro Akechi and Kosuke Kindaichi are
fictional detective characters in Yokomizo's works.
I don't have any dramatic experiences like Akechi and Kindaichi.
Reality isn't as interesting as fiction.
Wh-Whatever!
It's my job to make it interesting.
Besides, I want you to scoop some
realistic aspect as a reference.
If it's about what detectives do, then...
It's about cleaning.
Jotting, jotting...
Detective work is about clean...
Wait-
Huh?
Perfect.
Having one more will do the job faster.
Cleaning has nothing to do with detective work!
Brother, do you have a moment?
Got something else better to do?
No, I'll help clean...
But...
There's something I have to ask beforehand.
What is it?
We'll be going to the art museum this coming Sunday.
Can you chaperon for us?
Art museum?
Yes!
There'll be holding an exhibit on Shinzou Mamiya.
Notebook Title: “Case 42”
The fine arts club members were discussing
on how we're going to attend, but...
Since it's an off-campus activities on holidays,
we need a chaperon to attend with us.
Notebook Title: “Case Report”
Is that so?
I got it. I'm free this Sunday, so I'll tag along.
Thank you very much.
Well then, let's wrap it up, Dumbass.
Huh?!
Wrap it up?!
Hey...
Did you just call me Dumbass a second ago?
I didn't.
Let it go, Dumbass.
Since you're my bestfriend, you'll help out, right, Dumbass?
So you did call me Dumbass!!
Jeez! Yukarin, quit calling me Dumbass!!
Sign: OPEN
Oh, closing the shop already?
Sign: CLOSED
Tokisaki.
There weren't any customers today,
so I've decided to close the café early.
But, it's okay. Come in.
Tokisaka...
You haven't gotten over Yukiko yet, have you?
It's obvious.
I feel the same as well.
Death of a loved one is the worst way to say farewell.
You're a widow, but still so young.
You should wrap it up and make a fresh new start.
Tokisaka, I don't think you're one to talk.
Neither of us is ready to find a new love life,
but there are times when one gets lonely, right?
I-I suppose.
If you're actually going to console me,
then words alone won't be enough.
Are you sure about this, Kyouko?
Yes...
I don't mind if this is a relationship
where we soothe each other's pain.
I understand...
In that case, this will keep us from being lonely.
Here I go.
Tokisaka...
You're so gentle...
But I want you to drive me wild...
Kyouko...
Tokisaka!
Kyouko, I...
Tokisaka...
I haven't felt this hot for a long time...
I... can feel it...
I feel like I'm about to cum from being embraced by a man!
Me too, Kyouko...
I've almost forgotten how it felt to be inside a woman.
Tokisaka-kun, do me harder!
Kyouko!
Tokisaka!
So this is Tokisaka's...
Hey, Kyouko!
You don't think I can add this in the menu, can I?
Well, duh...
I guess you're right...
If Uozumi knew about this, he'd probably kill me.
Shinzou Mamiya Exhibit
There you go.
We meet again, Mr. Detective.
What a coincidence.
Hi, Miss Kuchiki.
Just call me, Touko.
We're friends after all.
Hey, hey, don't jump on the boat just yet.
Hey, Touko.
Who's he?
You don't have to worry.
This is Tokisaka's older brother, Touko.
Touko?
Yup.
She's my bestfriend, Touko Mizuhara.
Coincidently, we have the same name.
I-It definitely not a coincidence!
It's fate that brought us together!
Don't you think the same way too, Touko?
Yeah, I suppose.
People always meet each other for a reason...
At least, I think so...
Anyway! Touko, you shouldn't speak with men!
Let's go!
My, my...
Teenage girls nowadays are so out of this world.
Amazing...
Touko, she looks exactly like you.
Hey, Touko, did you model for this one?
Really?
But, she really looks like you.
Sorry to disappoint you, but...
That portrait “Girl in the Shell” was painted
a decade before the end of the war.
If you really were the model for this painting,
you would look exactly the same
ten years ago as you do now.
If so, then that means you'd possess eternal youth like the “Girl in the Shell.”
No smoking within the art museum.
Oh, my bad.
I was just bored.
You're surrounded by so many wonderful pieces of art here.
I find it strange that you're bored.
Is that so?
I'm not really into paintings.
This piece was painted by Shinzou Mamiya before the war.
Although the brushwork he used was technically simple,
his bold color scheming proved favorable
to even people overseas.
Wow...
And this piece of here was painted
after the war at Hiroshima.
Apparently, he painted this over several months
while observing on what's left by the atomic bomb.
You sure know a lot.
It's Stella's job.
Is Stella your name?
This exhibit showcases Shinzou Mamiya's
pieces under the theme of “Rebirth.”
Using religion as an inspiration to his work, his pieces
were exhibited in Osaka and Kurashiki Art Museums.
By then, Mamiya created his own series of
religiously inspired paintings about death and rebirth.
We've met before, have we, Miss?
What?
Have these paintings drawn to your taste?
Touko, have you been coming here lately?
You could have invited me to come tag along.
Why did you come here without me?
You also could have told me that
there were wonderful paintings here.
Touko, let's go.
Wait, Touko.
Shinzou Mamiya Exhibit
You're acting as the chaperon for the students today,
so please refrain from smoking.
What, you too?
Besides, are you girls attending a rich and prestigious academy?
Can't you girls even afford someone
better than me as chaperon for the holiday?
There's no helping it.
Recently, many students have gone
missing one after another.
Even the teachers advised us to stay indoors as much as possible.
Is that so?
First time hearing that in my book.
It is possible that the students ran away from home
and the academy hasn't reported it to the police.
Since when did the first student gone missing?
I'm unsure, but probably about a month ago.
How many have gone missing?
Three students...
It couldn't be...
Is something wrong?
Yukari.
Can you get a hold of the personal belongings
of the missing students?
Anything that might have their fingerprints?
Technically they haven't dropped out yet,
so most likely therell be some on campus.
If that's the case, I'll confirm this matter at hand.
Anyway, I hope this hunch proves my theory.
Takashiro Clinic
Natsume...
Natsume, wake up already.
This is a place of autopsy, not a place for a nap.
Tokisaka!
Gosh, it's been a while since we last met.
I've been busy with a few.
Oh c'mon, don't be a stranger.
Tokisaka, aren't we closer than that?
Umm, Natsume...
I need a favor.
Speak your mind.
I'll do whatever slutty things you desire, since you're the one asking, Tokisaka.
Even if it'll hurt, I'll take it down.
Th-That's not the favor I have in mind.
Gosh, you're so stiff as ever!
In favor to my delight, men should only be stiff down here.
Natsume...
Give me chocolate...
And then, I'll show you any autopsy
or victim documents you want.
I-If that's a bargain, then it's a give and take.
Let's leave the minor details aside.
Hey, hold on, Natsume.
Tokisaka!
C-Come on, Natsume-san.
I've waited long enough for your cock inside of me!
Tokisaka-han, don't you want my pussy too?
Looks like you're getting in the mood already.
Come on.
Let's live up the stage a bit more.
Natsume...
How does it feel?
Best squeeze ever, right?
It's amazing...
I'm sure you're the only one who can do something like this, Natsume.
Why thank you.
I'm glad you're making the most out of your stiffness.
You've gotten so big.
The taste isn't half bad, Tokisaka.
Natsume...
Don't cum just yet.
Now, take it in.
Natsume...
Don't make me wait any longer.
It's finally inside!
Deeper!
G-Go deeper!!
Natsume...
So tight down there...
Tokisaka, do you feel ecstatic?!
I feel ecstatic as well!
I'm so happy that I'm being trampled like a virgin!
It's so tight as a virgin's...
Although, mine is a bit bigger...
T-Tokisaka!
This is beyond ecstasy!
Tokisaka, having sex with you is the best thing ever!!
Natsume...
It feels way too good, but I'm about to cum!
Me too!
I'm almost there, so hold on, Tokisaka!
Good!!
So good!!!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming right now!!
I can't hold out anymore!
Just go ahead and release all your sperm inside of me!
No more! I'm cumming!
Hot semen is coming out!!
I'M CUMMING!!!
So then, my hunch was right?
Indeed...
Tokisaka, the fingerprint from the samples you brought match the discarded hands accurately.
Now we know their identities.
Still, it's hard to believe that all the victims
are schoolgirls from Ouba Girls Academy.
Natsume!
You're here too, Reiji?
Perfect!
Another pair of limbs has surfaced.
This is the fourth victim!
What did you say!?
To Be Continued...
The shivering wind passes like a stroke on my cheeks.
Like a baby rebelling against the silence.
It held tight to its embrace,
Although the cage simply crumbled away.
Transcending the confined time and space,
The Azure Bird revealed a sign from the stars.
Even the darkside of the moon
Seems dear to me.
Through a waning fissure,
Like a waving tapestry,
I conceal a voiceless shout
Locked within my heart.
My outstretched hands slip away,
Yet my memories can't recall a thing.
This crude body lost in the midst of doubt
Struggles while drifting with a lingering miracle.