hanime.tv
Presents
A business trip?
Yeah.
It's for a pretty big project…
So I won't be able to return for a while.
I'm sorry about this, Alisa,
but can I leave the house to you?
Udachi!
Good luck!
I will protect the house in your absence.
A-All right!
Here's my chance to be a complete pervert!
I've been waiting for this!
A Story of How a Russian Girl Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household and Lots of Sex Ensued
Chapter 3: Young Wife Maki (Pseudonym),
Soaking Wet and Gasping for Breath
Huh?
That's Alisa-san…
What's she doing in the kitchen so late?
Oh!
She's masturbating with reckless abandon!
Alisa-san's completely engrossed!
No! My body won't stop aching for this!
I'm such a pervert.
This isn't enough!
I want it deep inside me!
This is wrong!
How could I be so razvratnyy, so lewd!
But I can't forget that feeling!
This feels good.
It feels so good I'm soaking wet!
But Kenta-san's cock is harder, and it goes deeper!
Hm?
A-Alisa-san, what was that about my cock?
Are you in love with my Big Magnum?
It filled my pussy so well.
And it was so powerful inside me.
We're going to make some sauce in my pussy.
I shouldn't be doing something so, so lewd!
Is this what you call "double penetration"?
This is my first time seeing it!
My ﻿pussy…
I can't take any more!
No!
Darling…
I can't stop!
My pussy feels so good right now!
Forgive me!
I can feel it inside me.
Darling, you came so much…
Alisa-san, so you can't stop
thinking about my cock…
Now’s my chance.
I'll give you what you want.
I'll fuck you so good.
I came here to change the bathroom light…
But what's wrong, Alisa-san?
K-Kenta-san…
Go ahead.
The shower broke, and I got wet.
Ah…
You'd better get changed.
I just happen to be carrying some clothes
that will look good on you.
Oh no!
If I put these on, I'm sure I'll end up
having sex with Kenta-san again!
But I have a loving husband!
If he sticks his big cock inside me,
I won't be able to hold back!
Um, Kenta-san?
OK, tell me when you're changed.
What? You're not going to do anything to me?
Kenta-san!
Kenta-san, I'm done changing.
Kenta-san…
These clothes are too small.
You're right…
But these are a symbols of a
cute young woman's purity.
Japanese guys love them.
Young woman?
Oh, Yamato Nadeshiko!
Note: Japanese ideal of feminine beauty, predates WWII.
Yamato Nadeshiko do quick changes, right?
Then I'll do one too!
Nin, nin!
You're too easy, Alisa-san!
You're so naive and innocent.
S-She's an angel!
"﻿Banal"? What did you say?
Alisa-san, you're so lovely.
But your husband doesn't make love to you.
No. I can't take it anymore.
Alisa-san!
Y-Yes?
Alisa-san, I should explain more.
With a guy sees you, the ideal
woman, in front of him…
he imagines making babies with you.
Y-Yes…
So he naturally gets an erection, like this.
K-Kenta-san, we shouldn't…
Alisa-san, you want this too, don't you?
Look how wet you are already.
No. I'm embarrassed.
Tell me why you want it.
Your cock is so big, and..
when I think about it inside me…
I can't hold back!
Kenta-san…
Please rub your cock inside my pussy.
Then I'll fuck you good, just like you want me to.
Wow! You're so tight!
It feels so good. I can't hold back either!
No! I'm going to come again!
I'm coming!
He's amazing.
I came so many times when
he was moving inside me.
But when he came inside me, I came again!
Hey Alisa-san, this isn't enough, is it?
I'll make you feel even better.
I can't resist the pleasure anymore.
Such a plump ass squeezed into that swimsuit…
Must have been tight…
Alisa-san, that feels good.
Take me in all the way and squeeze your pussy!
No! I can't do something so dirty!
No! If you rub my breasts like that…
That feels so good!
No!
I'm having sex with Kenta-san
and I'm enjoying it!
Even though I know it's wrong!
No!
I'm… going to come again!
Me too!
Your swimsuit got dirty.
I'll bring you a new one now.
Yes… please…
Sailor uniforms are cute! Milo!
A Story of How a Russian Girl
Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household
and of Hows Lots of Sex Ensued
Yeah, that looks great on you, Alisa-san.
You look so sexy.
Spasibo. Thank you.
Oh, how she has fallen…
Now I just have to make her mine.
How does this feel, Alisa-san? Is it good?
Yes, it feels great!
My pussy feels so good with your cock inside it!
Rub your cock deep inside me!
Why am I saying such lewd things?
You're finally being honest with yourself.
This is he sexiest and most
beautiful you've ever been!
Yes! Your cock…
It feels so good with your cock inside me!
It feels so good when you move inside me!
If it feels that good…
I want you to be all mine.
I saw…
You looked so lonely when
you were masturbating.
If it was me, I'd fuck you until you're satisfied.
W-We can't…
I do love it when we have sex,
but we can't keep doing this!
I have a loving husband, Kouta-san!
If you're serious about Kouta…
let's stop having sex.
We'll become normal relatives…
and we won't have sex ever again.
N-No sex?
Make your choice, Alisa-san.
Will this be the end for us? Will you return
to an unsatisfying life with Kouta-san?
Or will you keep having great sex with me?
I have a loving husband, Kouta-san!
I love Japanese culture, and he introduced
me to lots of it, so I really love him!
But you're right… something was missing.
Kenta-san, your amazing cock and tireless sex
drive filled that empty space in my heart.
So my decision is…
I'll do it! I'll be yours, Kenta-san!
So give me more!
All right! I'll make you feel even better!
Yes! Your cock feels so good!
Alisa-san, you're mine now.
Don't be embarrassed. Be honest with
your feelings, and enjoy this!
Kenta-san, am I being lewd?
Yeah, you're so sexy!
I'm so happy.
Give me more and more of your cock!
Yeah, let's have lots of sex from now on.
I'm gonna come.
Where do you want it?
Inside me. Please come inside my pussy.
Kenta-san, give my womb lots
of your sticky, thick semen!
I'm all yours from now on…
I'm so sorry, Darling.
But he'll take care of me every day now!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
Encoding: Dorans
QA: Dorans
Visit us at hanime.tv
Софтсаб: TFloater