Business trip?
Yeah, I'm working on a pretty big project.
I won't be able to come back for a while.
I'm sorry to do this to you, Arisa, but
could you look after the house for me?
Удачи! Please do your best!
I'll watch over the house while you're working!
Finally! My sex time is here!
I've been waiting for this!
Married in the boonies
My story of sex with a Russian girl
Episode 4: The young wife does some servicing in a maid outfit
Episode 4: The young wife does some servicing in a maid outfit.
It's Kenta-san's scent...
The smell of his sweat is so strong!
The smell is making me so hot!
Kenta-san!
Shove your dick in me!
Stir up my pussy with your hard, erect dick!
I love having sex with Arisa-san, but
watching her masturbate is just as fun.
I wonder what outfit he's going
to have sex with me in next?
I wonder how he's going to plow my body next?
How many times am I going to cum?
Evening! I have a delivery!
Hello? Anyone home?
Huh? I wonder if they're out.
Lights are on though...
Suzumura-san?
You have a package!
No, you can't, Arisa! If anybody sees you like
this, you won't be able to go outside anymore!
But I can't stop this feeling inside me!
I know this is wrong, but I can't stop!
I guess nobody's home.
Oh, wow, I really looked this dirty?
Wow...
My pussy's this spread out and it's pulsing so hard.
My nipples are so hard and tingly too!
I look like I feel really good.
I'm so dirty.
I'm looking at myself masturbate in the mirror!
I'm such a pervert!
But it's okay. Perverts are a part of Japanese culture!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I wonder what Kenta-san's doing.
I should go and find out.
Oh, no, Arisa-san. You gotta be in the right
outfit when you're working in the kitchen.
Kenta-san!
S-Sorry! I'll clean up!
Are you going to punish me?
Well, first, let's get you out of those wet clothes. It just
so happens that I have some perfect clothes for clean...
Oh!
I have something for that! Wait just a second!
Uh... Arisa-san?
Those clothes...
This is from мама.
My mother gave me this.
She knew I'd be moving far away, so she gave me this.
It's my important tool as a married woman.
A real maid uniform?!
Its refined stitching can't contain the sheer
sexiness that's bursting out from inside!
Kenta-san?
So, you know I made a mess on the floor, right?
I did something bad, so...
Um...
It's so hard!
Okay, Master, I'll now begin pleasuring you.
Very well. Be thorough.
Arisa-san, is this your first time giving a blowjob?
Yes, I haven't even done it for Kouta-san.
Does this feel good?
It's so tender. It's so cute!
It reacts differently depending on where I lick it.
Does it feel good when I lick the tip?
Or maybe...
Does it feel better here?
Yeah, it feels good when you lick it, but how about
you try putting the entire thing in your mouth?
Okay!
How's this?
Perfect! Now sandwich my dick in between your boobs!
Okay.
Master, does it feel good?
Y-Yeah, it feels good.
It feels good even though this is your first time!
Thank you very much.
I want to see you feel good, Master.
I think I've... figured out what feels best and where.
She's making it feel so good even though this
is her first time! She's a complete sex monster!
That's good! I'm about to cum!
Drink your master's cum, Arisa!
I'll clean up your dick now.
Your dick is still hard.
Yeah, it is.
I've still got a lot left in me.
So? What do you want me to do?
Please thoroughly mess up my dirty
pussy with your magnificent, hard dick!
Please fill me up with your raw cum!
Very well.
I'll give you a reward.
Kenta-san... So good!
You're being so intense!
I've wanted to make these tits mine!
Okay! Do whatever you want with
my boobs whenever you want!
It feels so good when you rub them!
They're so soft and smooth!
My pussy feels so good!
Stick your dick in me more!
Arisa! Arisa! Arisa!
It's so big! It's so huge!
Your dick's hitting against my womb!
That's right! I'm gonna shoot my
cum in you and get you pregnant!
I want your baby!
Please get me pregnant with your raw cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Me too! I'm about to cum!
Get pregnant Arisa!
Bear my child!
Yes, I will.
I'll bear your child, Kenta-san.
I'm going to have a baby! His cum's filling me up!
Спокойной ночи. Have good night.
Kenta-san? How do I look, meow?
Do I look cute, meow?
You look great, Arisa.
Let's give some dick milk to this cute, sexy cat.
Meow. Meow!
Suzumoto-san
Answer       Reject
Hello?
Ah, Kouta-san?
Oh, yes, everything's fine here.
– Huh? Kouta? Why's he calling now?
– Oh, yes. I'm getting along with Kenta-san.
– Yes.
– What's he up to?
Huh?! Your business trip got extended?!
You're not going to be able to
come back until a year from now?
O-Oh...
Y-Yes, I'm fine.
Yes! Protecting the house is a wife's job!
Meow! Kenta-san, hurry!
You're a pretty dirty cat for growing a tail out of there.
Ah, Kenta-san?
That feels good, but play with my pussy!
Please mess up my pussy with your big, hard dick!
You're still a perv even now that you're a mom, Arisa.
I think this perverted cat-eared
maid needs some punishment.
Y-Yes, please!
Please punish me!
Your dick's so big!
It's rubbing deep in my pussy... it's so big!
You're so beautiful, Arisa!
I know how to pick 'em!
You're letting those big tits of yours flap around
while grinding up and down my dick... what a pervert!
Your boobs are starting to really swell up now.
I'll milk 'em for you.
That feels so good!
It feels so good!
This makes you more of a cow than a cat-eared maid, Arisa!
I-I'm a cow! Moo! Moo!
Here! If I do it like this, it'll go even deeper!
It's so... It's so intense!
Rough! So rough!
I'm... I'm gonna cum!
Okay, then this is the last spurt!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My boobs are cumming so hard, I'm losing milk!
Yeah, it's a little early, but let's give our baby some milk!
Kenta-san! Kenta-san!!
I'm cumming, Arisa!
Arisa, I'm gonna keep making you feel good.
Every day, every night... I'm gonna leave you satisfied.
Да. Yes, of course.
Kenta-san, please keep teaching me more
and more about Japanese culture, okay?
I love perverted Japanese sex.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч