hanime.tv
Presents
Wha!
A business trip?
Yeah.
It's for a pretty big project…
So I won't be able to return for a while.
I'm sorry about this, Alisa,
but can I leave the house to you?
Udachi!
Good luck!
I will protect the house in your absence.
A-All right!
Here's my chance to be a complete pervert!
I've been waiting for this!
A Story of How a Russian Girl Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household and Lots of Sex Ensued
Chapter 2: Young Wife Maki (Pseudonym)
Wants to Go to a Festival
Ah?
Hm?
Alisa-san is up late again?
Could it be…?
Oh!
I was right! She's masturbating tonight!
How lucky!
Darling…
Come inside me!
Come!
Harder!
Darling, if I can't see you, I…
I can't stop this feeling!
I'm so wet.
Even though…
Even though I love you so much…
Darling, love me more!
Heave-ho!
You were so amazing at that festival.
You were so strong, and you
were drenched with sweat…
When I see you like that, I can't control myself!
Come!
I want you to lick the tip.
Alisa-san, even though you've got such a strong
sex drive, you're usually so gentle and polite!
That gap is so sexy!
Darling!
I want to do it so much more!
This cloth still has your smell on it!
It's your sweat from the festival.
You smell amazing!
I'm coming!
Darling…
Please come home soon.
Thanks for another great show tonight, Alisa-san.
Alisa-san, you're lonely without
that guy around, right?
That bastard…
You've got such a sexy wife
and you pay her any attention!
I'd be all over her anytime, anywhere!
I want my hands on her tits and my
cock in her pussy right this second!
Shit…
I've got a boner again.
Anyway, Alisa-san is sexually frustrated.
And I'm always rock hard for her.
Rather than that limp-dick…
I can pleasure Alisa-san so much better!
How can I get myself inside her?
Based on what I've seen, she doesn't
seem to be on her guard around me.
Of ﻿course, if I force myself on her, she'll call
the cops, and that'll be the end of my life.
That's why I'll sit back and observe.
That's right, observation!
All I've got to do is watch her and
create an excuse to get dirty.
Ah! Alisa-san, you're so sexy!
Ah, Kenta-san!
Dobroye utro!
That means good morning!
Eh?
O-Oh yeah, g-good morning.
That's right!
Kenta-san…
There's a festival' soon.
A festival…
I don't know much about Japanese festivals.
Would you please teach me the proper etiquette?
Oh! We just happen to have
some proper festival outfits!
Want to try those on and practice?
Spasibo!
Thank you so much!
I'm in your care, Kenta-san!
Khorosho!
Kenta-san, what is this outfit?
It's called a happi.
Its short length makes it easy to move in.
And what you're wearing on
the bottom is a fundoshi.
Its minimal fabric also makes it easy to move in.
I see!
It's kind of embarassing, but it's so easy to move in!
Yeah! Hooray for cultural exchange!
And hooray for Alisa-san's world-class breasts!
Well then…
A common festival activity involves
carrying around a portable shrine.
Da!
Yes! I know about portable shrines!
I saw that video of Kouta-san carrying one!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Right?
Yeah, you know your stuff.
We don't have the real thing here…
So let's practice using this laundry pole.
Da!
Yes!
I'll do my best!
Heave-ho!
I can't get enough of Alisa-san's breasts!
Spread your legs more!
Thrust it harder!
Yes!
Heave-ho!
A beautiful woman with her body on full display
is shaking her tits in front of my eyes!
A-Alisa-san, I'm going to take a look
from behind to check your form.
O-OK!
Heave-ho!
Ohh!
Look at that foreigner's ass
bounce… It looks so soft!
And her body's moving like a piston!
Oh!
Alisa-san, I'll practice with you.
All right!
That sounds good! Let's do our best!
K-Kenta-san, something's rubbing against me!
That's no good!
You can't worry about the small
things in a Japanese festival.
Rather, bodies thrashing against one another
is something you should enjoy!
You're right. Is this wabi-sabi?
Note: It's not.
But this makes it kind of hard to move!
You're right. I'll make it easier for you to move.
Kenta-san, are you…
inside me?
That's right! I'm inside you, aren't I…
But doesn't this make it easy to move?
See?
I'm doing it with Kenta-san again!
Doing it with someone other than my husband…
Even though I shouldn 't…
What's this?
Alisa-san, is your pussy wet?
Could it be that you're enjoying this?
That's not…
If it's with someone who's not my husband…
But your pussy's been squeezing me since earlier.
Or does it turn you on to have sex outdoors?
No!
Doing something like this outdoors…
We're outdoors and you're spreading
your legs so wide…
You've got a cock inside you that isn't your
husband's, and you're enjoying it.
Alisa-san, you're a pervert, aren't you?
No! I'm enjoying this!
It's as Kenta-san says! I'm a pervert!
This is bad!
When Kenta-san goes in deep,
I can't think of anything else!
I'm gonna cum, Alisa-san!
Darling, I'm sorry.
Please…
Forgive me for being lascivious!
All right, Alisa-san…
Now let's try a different outfit.
I ll teach you how to enjoy a Japanese festival.
Dobroye utro!
A Story of How a Russian Girl
Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household
and of Hows Lots of Sex Ensued
Good morning!
Kenta-san, um…
What's this?
This is a yukata.
They're a traditional garment
that women wear at festivals.
But…
I'm not wearing anything underneath.
Am I wearing it right?
That's right.
Note: It's a misconception that nothing is worn under a yukata.
In public, light undergarments are commonly worn with a yukata.
It started as a simplified version of what
courtesan attire for the masses.
It may feel kind of revealing,
but wearing one is proper etiquette.
Courtesans!
Khorosho!
Wow! I think Japanese courtesans are amazing!
Oh noble, would you care to play with me?
How about it?
M-Me?
W-Well as long as you're enjoying yourself.
Oh noble, please choose me!
Alisa-san's voluptuous body makes any
Japanese-sized clothes look sexy!
Courtesans mostly took care of men's sexual desires.
That's the inspiration for this yukata.
Note: Courtesans were first and foremost entertainers
skilled in many traditional Japanese arts, well-read, and
valued for their beauty, character, education, artistic ability, and wit.
This is what women wear at festivals.
So basically, Japanese festivals are meant for
women to take care of men's sexual desires!
Kenta-san…
Take care of sexual desires?
W-What do you mean?
Basically…
Japanese festivals are where everyone
puts their bodies together.
Like before, lifting a portable shrine…
Making connections with the people around you…
It deepens your friendship.
L-Like before…
To share good spirits with everyone…
It's an honored group activity.
Don't you think it's a great
part of Japanese culture?
I-I see…
You're right.
That Japanese sense of sharing…
It's great!
Kenta-san, please teach me more
about amazing Japanese culture!
I'll thoroughly teach you…
some of Japan's lewd culture, that is!
Alisa-san, you're getting really tight.
We did so much earlier.
Was that not enough for you?
I'm not getting tighter or anything!
I just want to experience Japanese culture!
No! This feels good!
It feels good having sex with Kenta-san!
Even though I shouldn't think things like that!
That's right.
Alisa-san, you're just experiencing
Japanese culture.
So be more honest with yourself.
That's right.
I'm just experiencing Japanese tradition!
So I can enjoy this, right?
Alisa-san, you're finally being honest with yourself.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Having a cock shoved into your
pussy feels good, doesn't it?
Yay! It feels great!
My pussy feels great!
She's completely fallen for my cock…
Now Alisa-san's gonna be hooked on sex!
Alisa-san, I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna give you lots of my sperm inside!
How was that, Alisa-san?
Japanese culture feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, Japanese culture feels amazing.
Kenta-san, spasibo.
Thank you so much.
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
Encoding: Dorans
QA: Dorans
Visit us at hanime.tv
Софтсаб: TFloater