Suzumura Kenta-dono
Results from your recent job interview
Rejected
I'm home.
Здравствуйте.
Hi there. I'm Arisa.
I'm visiting from a northern country.
I'm here with Kouta-san.
I'm his wife.
Oh, uh, nice to meet you!
I'm Kouta's older brother, S-S-Susumura Kenta.
I guess you already know my last name.
Oh, so you're Kenta-san, huh?
Nice to meet you.
I'm glad to meet you!
We just got married a month ago,
She smells so good!
but we've known each other since college.
Her face is so small and her tits are so huge!
She's really interested in Japan, so...
Even her ass is huge!
Just how much sexuality can she exude?!
She might be from the north, but she's like
a fairy! She's so cute! Such a damn cute face!
She's not in high school, right?
It's like, she's straight out of an adult visual novel!
She's even talking to an unemployed bum like me!
Arisa-san's such a good person, isn't she?!
Shit! Why's it always him?! Why not me?! Why not me?!!
Business trip?
Yeah, I'm working on a pretty big project.
I won't be able to come back for a while.
I'm sorry to do this to you, Arisa, but
could you look after the house for me?
Удачи! Please do your best!
I'll watch over the house while you're working!
Finally! My sex time is here!
I've been waiting for this!
Married in the boonies
My story of sex with a Russian girl
Episode 1: The young wife is scared of ghosts
Huh? Is Arisa-san still awake?
This is...
Arisa-san is masturbating?!
Dear...
Одиноко. I'm so lonely.
More! Play with me more!
I'm getting so wet down there!
I'm only using my fingers though...
My stomach feels so good!
I'm so glad that we were able to meet again, but...
Now we have to be apart for so long...
I'm so lonely. So lonely. I miss you so much.
So deep.
I want you to mess me up in my deepest places!
Holy shit!
I can't believe I get to see a girl masturbate!
Especially when it's a hottie like Arisa-san!
Dear... Dear...
Go deeper!
Make love to me more!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm going to cum!
Dear... come back soon... please.
Arisa-san...
You love my little brother this much?
Don't worry, I'll make you feel better!
I know you're lonely without him, Arisa-san.
Those huge tits of yours jiggle like jelly
when you move even just a little bit.
And your pussy looked so smooth
and it was a beautiful pink!
So beautiful!
If I could have sex with that body, I bet it'd feel amazing.
I can't believe he hasn't had sex
with her even though she's so hot!
If it was me, I'd fuck her wherever and whenever I could!
Like right now! I want to rub the hell out of
those tits and shove my cock in that pussy!
Oh, shit.
I got hard again.
In any case, Arisa-san is sexually
frustrated and I'm ready to go any time.
I know that I can satisfy her with my dick instead of
her having to wait for that limp dick brother of mine.
I need to figure out a way to fuck her.
As far as I can tell, she doesn't really seem too wary of me.
Of course, if I attack her out of the
blue, she'll call the police on me.
And that'd be the end of my life.
So first, I'll need to surveil her. Yes, I need to surveil her.
I'll watch her and make an excuse for us having sex.
Arisa-san, you're so hot!
Arisa-san, what's the matter?
Are you alright?
Kenta-san...
On the TV... ghost...
Ghost! I was scared!
So I... I...
Peed myself.
I'm sorry!
Please keep this a secret from Kouta-san.
More importantly, Arisa-san?
With those kinds of horror movies,
sometimes they carry real curses.
C-Curses? I-Is that true?!
D-Don't worry though!
I'll teach you a secret Japanese technique
that will ward off any evil spirits.
Kenta-san, what are these clothes for?
These are the clothes that ghosts wear.
You wear this and purify your body
to expel the evil spirits within you.
Purify?
So I bathe myself in cold water, right?
Yes.
I'll try.
You have to do it right, but don't worry, I'm watching you.
Да. Yes, please do.
Arisa-san's huge ass is right in front of me!
Arisa-san, face this way next.
O-Okay.
Her body's like straight out of a porno
and it's right in front of my eyes!
Kenta-san... Простуда.
I'm cold.
What? That's no good!
It'd be bad if you caught a cold.
I'll warm you up!
Kenta-san?! What are you doing?!
We can't stop the ritual halfway.
So I have no choice but to warm
you up with my own body heat.
I-I see.
I am feeling warmer.
Спасибо. Thank you.
But this is a little embarrassing.
Wait, Kenta-san? What are you...
Kenta-san? This tickles!
What are you saying, Arisa-san? We got to
warm you up or you're gonna catch a cold.
I can't believe my nipples are getting hard
when Kenta-san is just worrying about me.
Kenta-san, not there!
Arisa-san, it's bad for women if their lower half gets cold.
Don't worry, I'll rub it good so it gets warm!
No... Being touched by a man's big hand feels
better than when I do it myself! It feels so good!
And Kenta-san's hard thing is
rubbing against my butt! This is bad...
This is bad, but it's really turning me on!
I can't hold it in any more!
This is your chance, Arisa-san!
We've cornered the evil spirits! They're in your nipples!
Let's force them out!
Kenta-san, don't!
Don't do that!
If this goes on any longer, I...
I... I can't take any more of this!
We're so close though, Arisa-san.
Just a little more and my seme... I mean,
the liquid to repel the evil spirits will...
I'm... I'm about to...
I'm cumming!!
Me too!!
It's so hot...
And there's so much of it too.
It's been so long since I've had a man's semen.
I guess we got the clothes a little dirty.
I'll get you a change of clothes,
so why don't we go to my room?
O-Okay.
Thank you... very much.
Здравствуйте. Hello.
Kenta-san, um, these clothes...
These are clothes for Mikos.
Mikos are women who work
directly for god and do his bidding.
Хотелось бы знать, что это...
Цутураба!
I know about these Mikos.
"Evil spirits begone", right?
So fucking hot!
That's right. They shake this stick and exorcise evil spirits.
Хорошо!
This is wonderful!
This is one of Japan's traditions, right?
It's time to exorcise some evil spirits, yo!
Yo?
Well I'm glad you're happy.
I never thought this cosplay outfit
would come in handy like this!
And now, I'll teach you an even more authentic ritual.
There's an ancient ritual where the Mikos
would take in the sacred artifact, "the dick".
K-Kenta-san, what are you doing?
Ritual?
"Dick?"
What are you waiting for, Arisa-san?
There's no other way to exorcise
the spirit within you than this!
B-But...
Arisa-san, I'm worried about you.
If your precious family got cursed, you'd
want to help them too, wouldn't you?
Kenta-san...
You're right.
You're worried about me, aren't you, Kenta-san?
I understand.
I'll do it!
Are you serious?! You're so easy, Arisa-san!
You're already wet, Arisa-san.
N-No, this is...
Don't worry, it's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Okay, let's start.
Just like that?!
It's completely different than his.
The tip is reaching all the way to my womb.
I-It's so big!
Looks like I went all the way in, Arisa-san.
Okay, I'm gonna move.
W-Wait... Don't move ye...
Her pussy's so fucking soft! And it's sucking me in so hard!
It's so hard.
And it's so big!
It's rubbing all the places that
even Kouta-san hasn't reached.
I've never felt this before!
Arisa-san, how about we move to the futon?
O-Okay.
Okay, Arisa-san.
Take "the dick" in.
Okay.
Arisa-san, are you getting turned on?
Your pussy's been twitching for a while now.
N-No, I'm not!
This is a ritual. I'm not feeling turned on at all!
Really? Okay then.
I think it's time for me to get serious.
This is... This is so good!
Arisa-san, I'm about to cum!
No way! He came inside me!
Kouta-san hasn't even cummed inside me yet...
And with that, the exorcism is complete.
Arisa-san... good work.
Kenta-san...
Спасибо.
Thank you very much.
translation: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч