Business trip?
Yeah, I'm working on a pretty big project.
I won't be able to come back for a while.
I'm sorry to do this to you, Arisa, but could
you look after the house for me?
Удачи! Please do your best!
I'll watch over the house while you're working!
Finally! My sex time is here!
I've been waiting for this!
Married in the boonies
My story of sex with a Russian girl
Episode 3: The young wife gets soaked and enamored
Episode 3: The young wife gets soaked and enamored.
Huh?
That's Arisa-san, right?
What's she doing in the kitchen at this hour?
She's finally just masturbating wherever she wants.
And she's really into it.
No...
I can't hold back my urges!
This isn't who I really am though!
But this isn't enough for me!
I want it deeper... I want to be messed up!
This isn't good.
This is such a mess, but...
My body can't forget that sensation!
Good... It feels so good twirling around inside me!
But I think I want something that can go even deeper inside.
Is Arisa-san thinking about my dick?!
Is she addicted to my big magnum?!
I want that thing that felt like it could
turn my stomach inside out.
I want the thing that ravaged me so intensely.
The thing that made sauce inside me.
I shouldn't be doing these dirty things.
Is this the legendary Japanese art of dual
wielding?! I've never seen it before!
So good... It's digging into me!
It's making such dirty sounds!
It's making me go crazy!
Dear, please forgive this dirty wife of yours!
Please forgive me for being this addicted
to making myself feel good without you!
This is so good!
It's coming! It's squirting out inside me!
Anata! It feels so good.
So you're that addicted to my dick, huh?
Looks like it's about time.
I'll fuck you hard, just like you want.
I came to replace a lightbulb here...
Something wrong, Arisa-san?
K-Kenta-san...
Oh... Душ... The shower broke and I got wet.
Ah...
You need to change.
And as it happens, I have some
clothes that'd fit you perfectly.
No, I can't. I know if I wear these, I'm going
to end up having sex with him again.
I have a husband I love!
If he sticks that huge dick inside me,
I won't be able to resist anymore!
Um, Kenta-san?
Let me know when you're done changing, okay?
What?! You're not going to do anything?!
Kenta-san!!
Ура!..
Kenta-san, I finished changing.
Kenta-san?
These clothes are too small.
Yeah, looks like it. But these clothes show
off a maiden's beauty and purity.
It's really popular with Japanese guys.
Maiden?
https://ru.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Wallflower
Oh, like a Yamato Nadeshiko.
Здраво!
Yamato Nadeshikos transform right?
"Witness my transformation!"
Trans-form!
You're so easy as always, Arisa-san.
You don't suspect anything at all. You're so innocent.
W-What an angel.
Что? What's the matter?
Arisa-san, you really are cute!
There's no way I can leave without doing anything.
My patience has run out!
Arisa-san!
Y-Yes?
There's actually a little more I need
to tell you about the uniform.
When such a perfect girl is presented right in front
of a guy, he can't help but think about procreation.
Right...
So I can't help but get like this.
K-Kenta-san?
W-We shouldn't...
You want to do this too, don't you, Arisa-san?
Look. You're already this wet.
No, this is so embarrassing.
So tell me what you really want.
That huge thing...
That huge dick's going to be inside me...
Oh, no! I can't resist any longer!
Kenta-san, um...
Please rub your dick inside my pussy.
Okay, I'll fuck you hard, just like you want me to!
Holy crap it's tight!
It's gonna be hard to move like this!
N-No, I'm still cumming, so please don't move so much.
Okay, here it comes!
Wow, I was already cumming from him just moving around,
but I came again when he shot his cum inside me!
Come here, Arisa-san. That wasn't enough for you, was it?
I'm going to keep trying to satisfy you, okay?
I can't fight against this pleasure anymore.
Wow, that was hiding this huge ass?
Must've been a tight fit.
Arisa-san, go ahead. Take my dick in deep
and grip it tightly with your pussy!
No...
Don't say such embarrassing things!
No... You rubbing my boobs while thrusting
inside me feels too good!
It... It feels so good!
Oh, no. I'm enjoying sex with Kenta-san!
I shouldn't be, but I'm...
I-I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming again!
Me too! I'm cumming again!
Sorry, I got the swimsuit you changed into dirty.
I'll bring something else for you to wear.
Okay. Thank you.
This uniform's so cute!
Yeah, it looks great on you, Arisa-san.
You look so sexy.
Спасибо.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, she's completely hooked.
All that's left is to make her mine.
How's it feel, Arisa-san? Good?
Y-Yes.
It feels really good!
Your dick moving in and out of me feels so good!
Your dick keeps going deeper and deeper inside me!
I'm saying really embarrassing things right now.
But if I say these things out loud, it feels so good!
Finally being true to yourself, huh?
You're the prettiest and sexiest you've ever looked now!
Y-Yes. Your dick inside me feels so good, Kenta-san!
I'm cumming!
Your dick's rubbing inside me!
If it really feels that good...
Then become my woman.
I've been watching.
I've seen you masturbating out of loneliness.
I can be there for you, fucking you until you're satisfied.
N-No. No matter how good sex with Kenta-san
feels, this can't keep going on forever!
After all, I have my husband!
If you choose my brother though,
let's end this relationship here.
We'll become normal relatives and never have sex again.
N-No!
Choose.
Arisa-san, are you going to go back
to your unfulfilled days with Kouta?
Or will you choose me and have this good
sex every day for the rest of your life?
I have a husband I love, Kouta.
I really love him for teaching me all about Japanese culture.
But it's true that I was left wanting.
And Kenta-san accepted me, filling the void and
my unsatisfied desires with his huge dick.
How do I really feel?
I'll do it!
Любовник! I'll become your woman!
So please, give me more!
Yeah! I'll make you feel even better!
It feels so good! Your dick is so good!
Okay, Arisa-san. You're my woman now.
So no more being embarrassed. Just let yourself feel good!
Kenta-san!
Am I sexy?
Yeah, you're the sexiest!
I'm so happy!
Please shove your dick in me more!
Sure, Arisa-san. Let's have more and more sex, okay?
I'm about to cum!
Where do you want it?
Inside!
Please shoot it inside my pussy!
Let my womb drink your thick, dribbling cum!
I guess my life as Kenta-san's woman starts now, huh?
Dear, I'm really sorry.
But starting today, I'm going to always be satisfied.
translation: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч