hanime.tv
Presents
I'm home.
Zdravstvuyte.
Hello, I'm Alisa.
I'm from a country north of here.
I'm Kouta-san's zhena…
his wife.
Wha…
Er, um… Nice to meet you!
I'm Kouta's older brother, Suzumura Kenta.
I don't need to say the family name, I guess.
So you're Kenta-san!
Ochen' priyatno!
It's nice to meet you!
We've only been married for a
month, but we met in college.
Wow, she smells good!
She's so beautiful!
She's very interested in Japanese culture, so…
That small face! Those huge tits!
And her ass is huge too!
It's like her whole body just oozes sexiness!
And since she's from Russia, her face is so cute!
She's not a high-schooler, right?
And she's married to my brother?
What is this, some kind of H-game?
She's friendly even to an unemployed guy like me.
Alisa-san, you're a great person!
Damn it! Why is it that good
things only happen to him?
What about me? What about me!
What?
Ah
A business trip?
Yeah.
It's for a pretty big project,
so I won't be able to return for a while.
I'm sorry about this, Alisa,
but can I leave the house to you?
Udachi!
Good luck!
I will protect the house in your absence.
A-All right!
Here's my chance to be a complete pervert!
I've been waiting for this!
A Story of How a Russian Girl
Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household
and of Hows Lots of Sex Ensued
Chapter 1: Young Wife Maki (Pseudonym) Is Afraid of Ghosts
Hm?
Is Alisa-san still awake?
That's…!
What?
Alisa-san is m-masturbating!?
Darling…
Ya odinok!
I miss you.
Please be rougher with me.
I'm so wet.
I'm ready for this.
I can feel it inside me.
Your cock's rubbing inside me…
You're going so deep!
Deeper! Don't stop!
Come, come!
I want you to rub all the way deep inside me!
Wow! Amazing!
A woman is masturbating in front of me.
And it's Alisa-san, a drop-dead gorgeous girl!
Darling… Darling!
More… Make love to me more!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Darling…
Please come home soon.
Alisa-san…
You're so in love with my younger brother…
Alisa-san, I'll take care of you with my big penis!
Alisa-san, you're lonely without
him around, aren't you?
Those massive tits jiggle with even your
slightest movement. They looks so soft!
Your pussy's smooth and pink.
I-It was so beautiful!
I bet it would feel great to have sex with that body!
That knave! He's got such a sexy wife, yet
he doesn't pay any attention to her!
If it was me, I'd fuck her anytime, anywhere!
Right this second, I want to knead those
breasts and shove my cock in her pussy!
Ah, shit.
I'm hard again.
Anyway, Alisa-san has unfulfilled desires,
and I'm always ready to fuck.
I can satisfy Alisa-san better than that
limp-dick little brother of mine!
What can I do to get us to fuck?
Based on what I've seen, she doesn't
seem to be on her guard around me.
Of course, if I force myself on her, she'll call
the cops, and that'll be the end of my life.
That's why I'll sit back and observe.
That's right, observation.
All I've got to do is watch her and
create an excuse to get dirty.
Ah! Alisa-san, you're so sexy!
Alisa-san, w-what's wrong?
A-Are you OK?
Un…
Kenta-san!
The TV… There was a ghost!
Ya boyus'!
I'm scared!
So I… So I…
peed.
I-I'm sorry.
Please don't tell Kouta-san about this!
More importantly, Alisa-san…
Did you watch the Spirit Special?
Even though they're fiction,
you really can get cursed.
Cursed?
R-Really?
Don't worry!
I'll teach you a special Japanese exorcism
technique so that you won't be haunted.
Boyus'!
Kenta-san, what are these clothes?
These are…
Clothes that ghosts wear.
If you wear while cleansing your body, we
can drive out the spirit possessing body.
Cleanse?
I have to wash my body with cold water?
Yeah.
OK…
I'll try it.
You have to use the proper technique,
So I'll watch you carefully.
Yes, please do.
Alisa-san's massive ass is before my very eyes!
A-Alisa-san, face your body this way next.
A-All right.
A body that puts porn actresses to shame…
It's! Right here! Right now!
Kenta-san…
Prostuda!
I'm cold.
What? That's no good!
You can't catch a cold.
I'll warm you up.
K-Kenta-san?
What are you doing?
We can't stop in the middle of the ritual.
So I'll warm you with my body heat.
There's no other way!
I-I see.
You really are warm.
Spasibo!
Thank you very much.
But this is kind of embarrassing.
Wait, Kenta-san, what are you do-
Kenta-san, that's kind of ticklish.
What are you saying, Alisa-san?
If I don't thoroughly warm
you up, you'll catch a cold.
Kenta-san is doing this because
he's worried about me,
but my nipples are getting hard!
Kenta-san, not there!
Alisa-san, the lower half of the body is the
worst place for a woman to be cold.
Don't worry. I'll thoroughly rub
against you to warm you up!
No! This is wrong!
A man's large hands feel better
on my body than my own!
And Kenta-san's hard thing
is rubbing against my butt.
Even though it's wrong…
It's wrong, but it feels so good!
I can't take it!
Now's our chance, Alisa-san!
We've cornered the ghost inside your nipples!
I'll help you dispel it!
Kenta-san, no!
No!
Any more and I'll…
I'll… Any more and…
Hang in there just a little longer, Alisa-san.
Just a little more and my come will…
No, I mean my control over the ghost will…
I'm almost there!
I-I'm coming!
Me too!
So warm…
and there's so much…
I haven't seen a man's semen in so long.
Yeah.
Your clothes are dirty.
I'll get you a change of clothes,
so let's go to my room.
Oh, OK.
Thank you… very much.
Zdravstvuyte
A Story of How a Russian Girl
Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household
and of Hows Lots of Sex Ensued
Hello!
Kenta-san, um…
What are these clothes?
These are a miko's garments.
A miko is a servant of God who performs
exorcism rites and the like.
Zhritsa!
I know what miko are!
Begone, evil spirits! Like that?
S-So sexy!
That's right…
Shake this rod to exterminate the ghosts.
Khorosho!
Fantastic!
This is traditional Japanese culture, right?
Watch out for Ghostbuster Alisa!
W-Watch?
W-Well as long as you're happy, it's fine.
To think the cosplay show I did back in
the day would come in handy like this!
I'll teach you a typical ritual.
Ever since ancient times, miko have taken
objects of divine power inside them.
There's a ritual where you take a penis inside you.
Eh? Kenta-san?
What are you doing?
Ritual?
P-Penis?
Eh…
What are you waiting for, Alisa-san!
This is the only way to exorcise the
ghost that's possessing you!
B-But...!
Alisa-san,
I'm worried about you.
If one of your beloved family members was
cursed, you'd want to help them, right?
Kenta-san…
You're right.
Kenta-san, you're concerned for my safety.
I understand.
I'll do it!
Seriously!?
You're too easy, Alisa-san!
You're wet, aren't you, Alisa-san?
No, this is, um…
Don't worry.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
OK, let's begin.
OK.
So suddenly?
This is nothing like doing it with my husband!
The tip reaches all the way to my womb.
I-It's so big!
I'm all the way in, Alisa-san.
I'm going to move now.
W-Wait!
Don't move y-
Foreigners' pussies are so soft!
And yet it's so sticky!
I-It's so hard!
So big!
It's reaching and rubbing all the places
my husband's never could!
It's the first time I've felt like this!
A-Alisa-san, shall we lie on the futon?
Yes!
All right.
Alisa-san, take my cock inside you.
Yes.
Alisa-san, is this turning you on?
Your pussy started twitching just now.
I-It's not what you think!
This is a ritual!
I'm not getting turned on!
Oh? If that's the case…
I'll start trying for real now.
Any more and I'll…
No more!
Alisa-san, I'm gonna come!
Oh no!
He came inside me.
My husband hasn't even done that yet!
Now we've completed the exorcism.
Alisa-san, well done.
Kenta-san…
Spasibo.
Thank you very much.
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
Encoding: Dorans
QA: Dorans
Visit us at hanime.tv
Софтсаб: TFloater