Business trip?
Yeah.
It's a pretty big project.
I'll be gone for quite a while.
I'm sorry, but could you watch over the house for me?
Удачи! Good luck on your trip!
Leave everything to me.
Hell yeah! When the husband's away,
it's my turn to play!
I've been waiting for this!
Married in the Boonles
My Story of Sex with a Russian Girl
Episode 2: "The Young Wife Wants to Go to a Festival"
Episode 2: "The young wife wants to go to a festival."
Huh? She's up this late again?
Wait, is she...
I knew it! She's masturbating again!
My love...
Иди ко мне! I'm cumming!
Do me harder, please!
Without you, I...
I get so hot, I can't stop myself!
I'm getting so wet!
I love...
I love you so much!
Please love me back!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
You were so sexy back then...
So manly, covered in sweat...
Watching this really stirs my borscht.
Don't stop!
I want you to suck my nipples!
God, it's so hot seeing the modest Arisa totally slut out.
My love... My love...
More! I want to do it more!
I can't get enough of your musk.
Your sweaty towel from the festival...
Your sweat is so wonderful!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My love...
Please come back soon.
Good show as always, Arisa.
She's so lonely without him.
Screw him. How the hell can he just ignore
her and not fuck her every waking minute?
That's what I'd do if she were my wife!
I just wanna smash my face into those titties
and plow her pussy like there's no tomorrow!
Shit, now I'm hard again.
In any case, she's sexually frustrated,
and my dick is always ready.
I know my cock will satisfy her,
unlike that limp dick she settles for.
God, I need to find a way to get into her panties.
Well, she doesn't seem too weary of me.
I could try raping her, but she'd call the cops for sure.
Yeah, that's probably not a good idea.
I guess I'll just keep spying on her...
I'll keep my eye on her until the moment presents itself.
God, you're so hot, Arisa.
Oh, hello, Kenta.
Доброе утро! Good morning!
Huh?
G-Good morninging! Howwa you doin'?
Oh, right.
There's a festival coming up soon.
I'm not too familiar with Japanese festivals.
If you don't mind, could you teach me about the traditions?
Oh, I know just the thing! I have some
festival clothes you could try out!
Спасибо! Thank you very much!
I owe you one, Kenta!
Хорошо!
So what exactly am I wearing?
The top is called a "happi".
It's short so you can move in it easily.
And the loincloth is called a "fundoshi".
It's also supposed to be as nonrestrictive as possible.
Oh, I see!
It's a little embarrassing,
but it is easy to move around in!
Thank God for cultural exchange!
Thank God for Arisa's world-class tits, too!
Now then, carrying a palanquin is a typical festival tradition.
Да! Yes, I know about the palanquins!
I saw a video where Kouta carried one!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Like that, right?
Yeah, you really know your stuff.
How about we practice that with this rack rod?
Да!
All right, here it goes!
I can't get enough of her boobs!
You need to spread your legs more!
Okay!
Oh, God, I can see through her top
because of the sweat! Hallelujah!
I'm going to check your posture from the back.
O-Okay!
Her ass is jiggling like jello!
It's like she's pistoning a dick!
Here, I'll practice with you.
Опять эта "цутураба"...
Цутураба! That sounds good. Let's do our best together!
K-Kenta?
Something's poking me!
That's no good. You can't let yourself
be bothered by every little thing.
If anything, you should have fun bumping into everyone!
I-I see... So this is what Japanese culture is like.
But it's still sort of hard to move.
Then I'll make it easier to move for you.
Kenta?
Is your...
Is it inside me?
Oh, oops. Looks like it.
But it's easier to move now, isn't it?
See?!
I'm doing it with Kenta...
It's bad to do this with someone
other than my husband, but...
Huh? Arisa, is your pussy wet?
Are you getting turned on?
That's not...
There's no way I would get turned on
by anyone other than my husband.
Are you sure? Your dripping pussy says otherwise.
Oh, is it because you're doing it outside?
No, being outside doesn't...
Look, you're getting turned on from doing it
outside with someone who's not your husband.
You're a huge slut, Arisa!
Oh, no! I'm getting aroused!
Is he right? Am I truly a slut?
No!
My mind goes blank with every thrust he makes!
I'm cumming!
Forgive me, my love.
My adulterous body has betrayed you.
All right, Arisa.
Let's get you in another outfit so
I can teach you another tradition.
Доброе утро! Good morning!
Kenta, um, this dress is...
That's called a "yukata".
It's traditional dress that women wear to festivals.
I see, but...
I'm not wearing anything underneath.
Am I wearing it correctly?
Yeah, of course you are!
It was made so common women
could dress like those in high society.
Sure, it's a little revealing, but it's
what a proper lady would wear.
Oh, I see! Хорошо!
That's wonderful!
I want to be high society!
"Would you like to play with me, my lord?"
How's that?
M-My lord?
Well, I'm glad you're having fun.
This makes me so happy, my lord.
Her voluptuous body makes
Japanese clothes really stand out.
Historically, women in high society
would sexually service men.
That was the purpose of the yukata.
So you see, you wear it at a festival to do the same thing.
Again?
Sexually service...
U-Uh, what are you...
You see, Japanese festivals are
all about getting closer together.
People get closer and connect with one another,
like we did earlier with the palanquin.
It's all about deepening friendships.
S-So like before...
Everyone shares the pleasure.
It's about the group, not individual.
Japanese culture is beautiful, isn't it?
I-I see.
That certainly does make sense.
The desire for everyone to
understand one another is wonderful.
Please teach me more about Japan's wonderful culture!
Oh, I'll teach you! I'll teach you
all about our beautiful "culture".
You're tightening up.
We did it pretty hard earlier.
Was that not enough?
I-I'm not tightening up...
I'm just experiencing Japanese culture.
That's a lie. I'm definitely aroused.
Having sex with Kenta feels really good.
This isn't right, but I...
That's right. You're only experiencing Japanese culture.
So why not let loose?
That's right. I'm just experiencing Japanese culture.
It's okay if I get turned on, right?
You're finally being honest with yourself, huh?
Does having your pussy slammed by a dick feel good?
Y-Yes... It feels good...
My breasts and my pussy feel so good!
She's totally hooked on my dick now!
She's addicted to sex with me!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna fill your insides with my cum!
How was it?
Doesn't Japanese culture feel good?
Yes, Japan's pleasure-filled culture feels good.
Спасибо, Kenta.
Thank you very much...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч