hanime.tv
Presents
Wha!
A business trip?
Yeah.
It's for a pretty big project…
So I won't be able to return for a while.
I'm sorry about this, Alisa,
but can I leave the house to you?
Udachi!
Good luck!
I will protect the house in your absence.
A-All right!
Here's my chance to be a complete pervert!
I've been waiting for this!
A Story of How a Russian Girl Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household and Lots of Sex Ensued
Chapter 4: Young Wife Maki (Pseudonym)
Serves in Maid Uniform
Kenta-san, your scent…
It smells like your sweat.
Just the smell of you turns me on.
Kenta-san!
Move your cock inside me!
Stir my pussy up with your rock-hard cock!
I can have sex with Alisa-san whenever I want…
But watching her masturbate takes
it to a whole nother level!
What will you make me wear
the next time we have sex?
How will you fuck me?
How many times will I come?
Parcel delivery!
Hello? Anyone home?
Hm? Nobody's home?
But the lights are on…
Suzumura-san?
Delivery for Suzumura-san!
– ﻿No! Alisa, this is bad!
If anyone sees me here, I won't
be able to walk outside again!
But it won't stop throbbing!
This is wrong, but I can't stop!
I guess nobody's there…
Jeez… was I always this lewd?
Wow!
Look how wide my pussy's gotten.
It s flapping around.
And my nipples are so hard.
They feel so good.
I'm so debauched!
I'm masturbating along with myself in the mirror.
I'm such a pervert!
But that's fine.
Perverts are a part of Japanese culture!
I'm coming!
I've come so many times…
This is…
Oh dear…
This won't do, Alisa-san…
When you're working in the kitchen,
you've got to wear the right outfit.
Kenta-san!
I-I'm sorry. I'll clean it up right away!
A-Are you going to punish me?
Well first you've got to change
out of those soiled clothes.
I just happen to have some clothes for you that…
I've got something just for that!
Just wait!
Meow.
Um, Alisa-san, what are those?
I got this from my mama, my mother.
It was a parting gift.
It's my precious trousseau!
It's a real maid uniform!
It shows grace and elegance but also
exudes an unconcealable eroticism!
Kenta-san…
I got the floor all dirty…
I did something I shouldn't, so…
You're so hard!
Master, I'll service your cock now.
Very well. I leave it to you.
Alisa-san…
Is this your first time giving fellatio?
Yes. I haven't done this to Kouta-san.
How should I do it to make you feel good?
The tip feels squishy.
Milo! It's cute.
You get harder when I…
Right here…
Does it feel good when I lick the tip?
Does it feel good…
Yeah. It feels good when you lick it.
But try filling your mouth with it, and
move it in and out, like a pussy.
OK!
Like this?
Yes! Now put my cock between your breasts!
OK!
Kenta-san, does this feel good?
Y-Yeah!
For your first time, you're great at this!
Thank you.
Since it's you, Kenta-san…
I know what places make you feel good!
This is just her first time
and she's so good at giving head!
What an amazing sexy beast!
Just like that. I'm gonna come!
Drink your master's sperm, Alisa!
Let me clean your cock.
Kenta-san, your cock is still hard.
That's right. I can come a lot
more times than just that.
So, Alisa-san, what would you like me to do?
Master, please put your amazing, hard cock
inside my lewd pussy and rub it thoroughly!
Please fill my pussy with your thick semen!
Very well. I'll give you your reward.
Kenta-san, that's so hard!
I've wanted to make these breasts mine.
Yes! Use my breasts however you want!
It feels great when you rub them.
They're voluptuous!
My pussy…
Your cock…
Alisa!
Yes!
Please master, fill me with your thick semen!
That's right. I'll fill you with my
sperm and get you pregnant!
Master, I want your child!
Get me pregnant!
I'm coming!
I'm gonna come too!
It's too much!
Get pregnant!
Alisa, have my child!
Yes, I'll have it.
Kenta san, I'll have your baby!
Thank you so much master.
Spokoynoy nochi! Good night!
A Story of How a Russian Girl
Suddenly Became a Part of
My Back-Country Household
and of Hows Lots of Sex Ensued
Kenta-san, how do I look?
Do I look cute?
It looks good on you, Alisa.
I'll give this cute, sexy kitten some cock milk.
Meow!
Incoming call
Kouta-san
Hello?
Oh, Kouta-san…
Oh, yes. Everything's fine over here.
Yes, of course! Kenta san and
I are getting along really well.
– A call from Kouta-kun?
– ﻿Calling at a time like this…
I wonder why he's calling.
What?
Your business trip's been extended?
I see.
You won't be able to come back
until a year from now…
I-I see.
Y-Yes.
I'm fine.
It's fine. It's a wife's duty to protect the house.
Meow! Kenta san, come on!
Jeez…
Sprouting a tail from here…
What a lewd kitty…
It feels nice…
It feels nice in my ass,
but please do my pussy too!
Please rub your hard cock inside me!
Jeez… even after becoming a mom,
you're still a massive perv.
This lascivious cat-eared maid
needs some punishment.
Yes!
Please! Please punish me!
Your cock feels so good!
It's throbbing inside me.
Alisa, you're beautiful.
You're my woman after all!
Showing off your massive breasts and pregnant
belly while moving your hips…
You're such a pervert!
It's too much!
That's too hard…
Your breasts have really developed.
I'll squeeze the milk out for you.
My breasts are leaking!
That feels so good!
Alisa, you're not a cat maid anymore…
You're a dairy cow!
I'm a dairy cow…
Your dairy cow…
Here. If we do it like this, it'll go in even deeper.
Kenta-san, that's too hard!
That's so hard.
I can't take it.
All right. This is the home stretch!
I'm coming!
That feels so good!
You're stirring up my pussy!
Yeah. It's a little early, but let's
give our baby some milk!
Kenta-san!
I'm gonna come, Alisa!
Alisa…
From now on, I'll always make you feel good.
Every day and every night,
I'll make sure you're satisfied.
Da. Yes.
Of course, Kenta-san.
Keep teaching me lots of Japanese culture, OK?
Perverted Japanese sex is the best!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
Encoding: Dorans
QA: Dorans
Visit us at hanime.tv
Софтсаб: TFloater