I applaud you for having the nerve.
E-Excuse me.
I- I m sorry.
Excuse me.
Um... I'm sorry.
Wait, you
What is it?
W-What?
How many women were you planning to
run into before you got into trouble?
Were you planning on tickling anything
Wait, don't answer that!
He actually has a cute face.
That's right...
Tell onee-san what you were going to
do, and we may very well forgive you.
Just kidding.
Hey now, you're misunderstanding me.
I wasn't planning on doing anything like that. It
I wasn't planning on doing anything like that. It -
Shhh...
A real guy doesn't make excuses.
And that, is how I met my tutors...
「﻿The first lesson is a suddenly fierce climax!?」
Sakura
I'm home!
Why are all of you following me!?
Well, because...
We were going to this house from the start.
And why are you here?
And you even said. "I'm home "
Well of course, this is my home
Who are you?
Forgot where you live?
He really is a bad kid.
No wait, what I'd like to know is who all of you are.
Oh. Touya. you're home.
Dad!
From here, we have the language expert, Rio Onadera.
Nice to meet you.
Mathematics expert, Nagisa Shiono.
Sup.
English expert, Sara Akizuki.
Pleased to meet you.
Biology expert. Amane Amamiya.
During your summer break, they are going to be your tutors.
Huh? You never told me about that!
Oh? I didn't tell you?
Oh yes, I'll be on a business trip.
So everyone, please take care of my son.
Yes, we'll do everything we can for your perennial son.
That's different from what a tutor's job is.
I can't concentrate on studying.
That's wrong.
Think harder when you answer.
l-m sorry
Great, it's all over my skirt.
Wait here while I go change.
All right. I'm really sorry.
No worries.
Here I am.
Sara-san. that was pretty fast !!
W-Why are you dressed like that...?
My luggage hasn't arrived yet. so I don't
have anything to change into.
Well, uh... In that case you can just borrow some clothes.
I can't do that!
We're in the middle of a lesson!
We can't interrupt your crucial study time.
So let's continue.
Sorry but l'm going to sit on your bed.
With my skirt off, I'll feel better not sitting on the floor.
Then it'd be better if you put something on.
All right, let's pick up where we left off.
Now I really won't be able to study.
It's still hot in here.
I wonder if I should turn that up.
All right, go ahead.
Now where's that remote control?
That's too tempting!
The remote's over here, Sara-san.
Oh, that's where it went.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Wait that isn't the remote!
So stiff.
S-Sara-san...
Since your already getting warmer
I'm sure you'd be alright anyway.
Urn, I thought we were supposed to keep studying.
Well, even so...
With it this hard it'd be a pain to study.
Well...
So, if I make you come it'll be fine, okay?
This isn't right!
Okay.... Let's study quietly, shall we?
Well?
Do you like them big?
You like big breasts, don't you?
So just enjoy yourself.
Wa - Sara-san, what are you ?
Breast fucking...
Well, Touya-kun? Is it good?
Yeash
Is this your first breast fucking?
Don't tell me this is your first time even
being touched by a woman's breasts?
Well for that...
I say "no comment".
You're cute.
Feel free to come anytime you'd like.
Hey...
I'm getting there...
Already?
Well, you're young so you can't help it.
Then get ready for my last spurt.
I'm coming!
Now we can continue our lessons.
I don't think I'll be doing anything for a while.
What a day...
I may not make it if it's like this everyday.
A-0 Drink?
Did Dad buy this?
This'll work.
That's horrible!
Now for a nice soak in the bath.
To begin wjth, I already did something with one of them...
and since those other girls are there too,
how could anyone expect me to study.
That feels good.
C-Crap, there's someone in here.
Is... Is someone there?
Touya-kun!
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't think anyone was in here.
Touya-kun...
Not only in the train...
But the bath too?
That's just a misunderstanding...
Miss Rio.
I know that some young boys are curious
about seeing women naked.
But I can't believe that you would do it...
I'm telling you, this is all a misunder
If you really want to see a woman naked...
I'll show you, so...
Don't try to get a look anymore.
Swear to me.
Well, I'll go ahead and show you...
But it's just this once...
So promise me you won't do any more bad things.
But it's not really like I did anything bad.
All right...
Well, Touya-kun?
Well. Touya-kun?
Can you see?
Yes...
Good then.
But, with the steam it's pretty hard to see.
Give me a second.
Well?
Now I can see it better.
It's a pretty pink color...
It actually looks kind of rough.
Well this...
This is the clitoris.
Then under there's the skin folds called the labia.
Yours is pretty, no fluttering or anything.
R-Really?
Thank you.
Rio-san...
Could you teach me about some other things?
Sure...
This is the urethra
That's where urine comes out.
Under that is the vagina.
That's where... a man inserts his penis.
Hey. Rio-san...
Some kind of liquid's flowing out of your vagina.
Huh?
That's, love liquid.
Love liquid?
It makes it easier for the male to insert his penis...
Since it's flowing out...
Does it want me to put in my penis?
N-No!
Looking only, Touya-kun.
You're getting big.
It's not fair at all that you get to look.
Let your teacher have a look.
Up!
♥ No! You're perverted, Rio-san! ♥
It's all right, meve your hands.
But...
Okay.
When erect, a man can't pee until he releases his semen, right?
That isn't necessarily true.
Since I'm the cause of this, I have to do something.
I'm obligated to take care of this.
As a teacher, and as an older woman,
That's quite uneeded
Rio-san!
What are you doing?
I don't have much experience at this...
So I'll have to try my best for you.
Rio-san...
That feels nice...
So this is Rio-san's labia.
They're squishy, just like another pair of lips.
Hey! Don't tease me!
I'm not teasing you.
I'm simply sharing a moment with you.
You're really not satisfied with just looking, are you?
You're young, so you can't help it.
That feels great
Hey, Rio-san... Is it alright if I touch your clit?
Sure just be sure to be gentle.
Will do.
Didn't you say just the clitoris?
Sorry sorry.
This time I'll use my fingers on it.
Your fingers are inside.
You should really do what you say you'll do.
You teach things so beautifully, Rio-san.
I'm learning plenty from you too.
On my own.
Since you're taking the time to teach me.
I just want to do things right.
It feels like you've already really been studying about this.
I-I won't let you do better than me.
No! I can't hold it!
Wow...
Are men supposed to ejaculate this much?
We I no, this is a little off...
This is my second today too. so that much
isn't definitely supposed to come out.
Touya-kun...
Don't sneak a peek on anyone anymore, okay?
But just in case...
If you can't help yourself again, just come see me.
Hey, if you don't get going, Nagisa and the others will catch you.
Right.
I'm acting as his caretaker.
I have to accommodate him in any way that I can.
Touya-kun, can't you even do these?
Ow.
I-I'm sorry.
No wonder your grades aren't all that great.
This calls for an alternate method.
Huh? What are you doing?
What I am I doing? Can't you tell by looking?
But, we aren't going to any pool.
Then just why are you in that outfit?
Ambiance! Ambiance!
Starting now, I'm going to give you
my fullproof pro-wrestler regiment.
Huh? That's crazy!
Don't worry! I know what I'm doing!
Of course, if you get any incorrect, it's gonna hurt a little.
Say what!?
Don't look so scared.
AI! right, here I go!
Why aren't you getting fly of them correct?
This time I'll really make it hurt.
This hurts plenty enough.
I can't go on.
Don't give me that!
Now matter what. I'll make this easy
Huh?
Uh huh... No wonder you can't study right.
Now what?
out of Nagisa nee-san's nice body.
Looks like Touya-kun got too much stimuli
Oh well then.
Today we'll have a change of lessons.
I need to teach Touya-kun the most
important lesson in being a man.
Why do I always have to put up with these things?
Did you say something?
Oh no, nothing at all!
Ugh, those two are supposed to be studying,
but all I'm hearing is a bunch of noise.
Come on Touya-kun!
Get yourself inside me!
Okay...
Here goes...
Right there.
It's inside.
So big.
It's hitting my uterus.
Its so-hot and slippery inside you.
It's so wet.
How is it?
It's the inside of a woman.
It feels incredible.
I'm feeling really good.
Those two are having sex.
And I haven't even gotten a chance to tutor yet.
So strange...
And they're doing it during the day.
Disgusting.
Nagisa-san!
My tits... Suck my tits too.
Right.
Good!
Hurry!
Kiss me.
Good!
Tight... It's tight, Touya-kun
Touya-kun...
Today isn't a safe day, so do it outside.
All right.
I'm coming! I m coming!
What... What is all this?
So much of it.
Again...
What's up with me today?
Oh, don't worry over it.
People have different amounts.
And you were really big, filling, and really intense.
But, this is really different from how I usually am.
Now that I think about it, there was that A-0 drink...
Was it all because of that?
This is the first time I've had it this good.
You're actually quite a stud, Touya-kun. So be more confident.
Nagisa-san...
Nagisa-san, was it really that good?
Doing this on my own, is somehow pretty lonesome.
We're still doing this?
Of course! ♥
Preview
Why is Touya-kun getting so hard?
It looks like we have to do something now.
Huh!? We have cosplaying too?
All right.
If it's to help Touya-kun study, I'll do everything that I can.
LESSON.2
Join us for our naked lesson.
NOT FOR SALE. RENT, AUCTION OR PAYSITES
And please buy the R1 DVD If this, actually comes to the U.S.