Sakura
Come in.
S-Sara-sensei, why are you dressed like that?
It's hot today, so I thought I'd teach in a swimsuit.
Then I'll just turn up the...
No way. If you turn it up I'll just get a headache.
But, it's hot out today.
Then why don't you wear your swimming shorts?
I'll pass.
I brought something cold to drink, so that should tie you over.
This...
It has some good stuff.
So, drink up.
When I drink this, my body gets all... weird.
You're a man aren't you? Drink it like one!
Women have to swallow this stuff heartily.
W-Where did that come from, Sara-san?
Oh, I was just kidding...
Unless, you actually want me to!?
O-Of course I don't!
「The second lesson is a turn-on! Cosplay Lesson!」
Uh, Sara-san, I don't get this part.
Hm? Where?
R-Right here.
This problem...
Well for this...
Oh...
Touya-kun, did you get a hard-on again?
I-I'm sorry.
Young men really do have strong sexual drives.
You have to tell me these things before study time, all right?
Uh, alright.
Since we have no choice...
I'll give it to you good.
Does that feel good?
You really like breast fucking, don't you Touya-kun?
Oh, sure.
But you know, your dick seems bigger than I remember.
R-Really?
Should we move on to something better today?
I know that you like a breast job, but this
should be fine with you too, right?
All right then, let's go...
It's really snug in there.
This is the first time I've felt something like this.
How is it? Inside my pu**y.
It's really hot and wet. It's sticking to me.
l-lt's really good, Sara-san.
We're just getting started. I'll make it feel even better.
Wow...
You don't have to do a thing, Touya-kun.
I'll do everything and anything.
Sara-san, l'm going to...
Let it go whenever you want to, Touya-kun.
Explode all the sperm you have into me!
Sara-san!
Coming!
I really felt that.
Not only did your dick get bigger, but
you have a lot more semen too.
Next is Amane-san's lesson.
Amane-san's a different kind of teacher,
so I guess she won't come to my room.
Touya? Enter.
Excuse me.
What the...?
You're late!
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
My last lesson ran long, so that's why I'm late.
You're a man, so no excuses!
And besides, didn't you come from Sara-san's English lesson?
Do you really need extra time for that?
Well, we were just, doing a lot of things.
Dodging the question...
Fine then.
Your lesson for today is a test.
Here, take it.
Another test?
Didn't we just finish one?
This isn't some little teaching game we're playing.
I'm not as easy as Rio-san and the others.
I'm not getting this...
Her attitude's a little questionable...
But Amane-san's really a beautiful woman.
Oh, crap...
You! The hell are you doing!?
I'm sorry! I acted on impulse!
You've got a lot of nerve to do that while I was asleep.
Uh, no, I didn't really mean to go that far...
Prepare to feel pain!
What in the...
Uh, just what are you going to do to me, Amane-san?
I'm going to sample what guys do in these situations.
Isn't that a little... perverse?
It isn't perverse
This is for the sake of researching animal behavior!
Did she have to say "animal behavior"?
What's wrong? I'm just trying to help you ejaculate.
Do it whenever you feel like it.
Come on, let me see it erect.
I can't do it when I'm like this.
Can't?
You're pretty picky for such a damn pervert.
Who was it that was masturbating in my room during a test?
I'm sorry...
Damn. Be like that...
Close your eyes for a minute.
Don't look until I say to.
O-Okay...
All right, open your eyes.
Well? Can you get going with this?
A-Amane-san! You're actually into that stuff?
H-Hey, don't get the wrong idea.
I only got this as a present from a friend on my birthday.
W-What are you doing, just ogling me?
I thought this was the part where the guy says
if these clothes look good or don't look good.
So... cute...
l-lt got erect?
Why did it suddenly do that?
W-Well, uh...
It's because you're so cute, Amane-san...
Cute!? Me!?
If you don't quit the jokes, this punishment isn't going to end.
I'm not joking at all.
You really are, Amane-san.
If that's really true, show me some proof that you mean it.
Right, I want you to masturbate so I can see.
M-Masturbation?
Onanism.
No, I know what it is, but...
Oh, right. In order to masturbate, you need some stimulation.
This is a major service.
Come on, look at me and work it.
Work it...?
W-What now? Isn't this enough for you?
You sure are hard to please...
All right, that should be enough.
I went this far...
So you better show me something good.
Now, work it!
Hurry up
Someone help me...
Oh my, Touya-kun. Getting kind of bold...
Nagisa-san!
Hi!
Why are you here?
Well, it was unlocked...
Amane-chan, you look like you're doing something interesting...
This is... uh...
I knew that you were peeking.
And that you might try something here.
But I never expected this...
Y-You knew I was there?
Pretty much.
You knew and you didn't
This has nothing to do with you
No, no, Amane-chan...
If you act angry, he'll go limp.
In that case, I'll just do things on my own.
If you really act that harshly towards men,
you'll never grow to be a woman.
I guess you'll just have to be the celibate tutor...
W-What are you !?
What!? Amane-san's a virgin!?
N-No, of course I'm not...
Oh, is that right?
In that case, Touya-kun's dick is all ready to go.
Why don't you show us what kind of moves you have, Amane-chan?
Fine with me.
Wait, Nagisa-san...
Come on now.
Do whatever you want.
But, just do it gently.
Okay...
OK, put on some protection.
That just looks weird. Don't suck on my nipples!
Hey, a woman has to have that done if she's ever
going to be a wife and a mother to a baby.
I thought you of all people would know that.
O-Of course I do!
Amane-san, turn over and move your butt toward me.
L-Like this?
You have a really cute ass.
Wow, you're already dripping down there, Amane-san...
S-Shut it...
All right, I'm putting it in...
Do it gently
Please be gentle...
I will...
Ow.
Amane-san, should I...
It doesn't hurt, so... Keep going.
Amane-san...
Having Touya-kun's huge dick as your first may be a bit much...
I told you, it's not my first
If you say so. Touya-kun, go all out then.
Okay...
Amane-san, are you alright with that?
O-Of course...
All right then...
It looks like she's having a good time even though it's her first...
Shows how good Touya-kun really feels.
When I remember Touya-kun sticking his
dick in me, my body gets so excited...
Nagisa-san's masturbating while watching us...
How embarrassing.
Amane-chan, between masturbating
and watching, which feels better?
I-I can't say that!
Gosh, she's still being stubborn.
Touya-kun, stop.
If it doesn't feel good then you won't object
to stopping here, right Amane-chan?
B-But I...
Come on, if you want more, then just say so.
His penis feels good, right?
If we stop here, I'll be suffering too, but...
H-His penis feels good...
Hm? Did you say something?
His penis feels good! It feels much better
than masturbating by myself!
So please keep going!
Amane-san...
All right well said.
Touya-kun, would you kindly rock her world?
Sure thing!
Wow!
That feels so good.
Same here, Amane-san.
You two really make it look good.
Amane-san!
This is an... orgasm?
I came at the same time.
You're really big, Touya-kun, but you're also really skilled.
I'm even surprised myself...
Maybe it really is that drink after all.
Hey, will you come over to my room?
Seeing you two really put me in the mood.
Nagisa-san...
Nagisa, I bought some ice cream so do you want
What are you eating, Nagisa?
Taya-kunph...
Oh, I see. Then you wouldn't want any, right?
I'm sorry that I interrupted you
Rio-san!
What about me, Touya-kun?
I had no idea Touya-kun and Nagisa-san were so involved.
Rio-san...
Touya-kun...
Uh... Anyway, I'm sorry, Rio-san!
Why are you apologizing, Touya-kun?
This is my fault.
I'm sorry for interrupting you.
I had no idea that Nagisa-san and you were together...
That's not true at all, Rio-san.
Nagisa-san and I aren't a couple or anything.
We are more than friends of course, but...
The one that I love is you, Rio-san.
Despite that I still betrayed your trust.
I'm very sorry!
So sorry!
Utterly sorry
That's enough, Touya-kun!
Rio-san...
Well, you know, I love you too, Touya-kun.
That's why when I saw you and Nagisa-san
doing that, it broke my heart.
I want to be your girl, Touya-kun.
Would you accept that from me?
Rio-san...
Touya-kun...
No, I m too embarrassed to.
You have a beautiful figure, so don't hide it.
You're alright doing this with me, right?
All right, here goes.
Does it hurt?
Oh no, l'm fine.
Your breasts feel so nice and soft.
Your hands feel good too, Touya-kun.
Good to hear. This wouldn't work if neither of us felt any good.
Yeah.
Move yourself back and forth.
Touya!
Touya-kun! I m almost at an orgasm
I'm almost there too.
Touya-kun...
And so, Rio-san and I started our relationship as a couple... but...
Touya-kun, if there's anything you have
a question about, be sure to ask me.
Hurry and finish the test so we can go to the pool.
Ask me anything you need to about women.
Anything about pleasure centers or hot spots...
I'll teach you and let you try it all on me.
Sara-san, stop taking all of Touya-kun's attention.
You're doing the same thing, Nagisa-san!
We're in the middle of studying, so don't you interrupt!
Ahh! Rio-chan's so scary...
Touya-kun!
Touya, I bought this new outfit to see if you think it looks good.
Yeah! It looks perfect on you
R-Really?
But just so we're on the same page, I didn't buy this just for you.
You're a beautiful woman Amane-san, so
anything you wear would look good
You little... TRAITOR!!
Yeah, what about it
Move it!
Do you wanna die!?
Do something you
Hey wait, put that down!
You shut up, Touya-kun!