Kagome, Kagome,
little bird in its cage.
When, oh when, will you escape?
On a moonlit night,
the crane and tortoise slipped.
Who is the young man behind you?
The Kawarazaki Household 2
The Third Horror
Devil's Labyrinth
Stop! I'm begging you!
S-Stop!
It seems like you haven't
been forgiven just yet.
Your pussy sure is a pretty pink color.
All right now. I'm going to inject
this into her pearl-like clitoris.
It'll start feeling better soon.
Anna. Anna!
Well? Who do you prefer,
me or that pissy-smelling woman?
Kengo-san! How cruel! How cruel!
Your real punishment starts now.
No!
Anna...
Like that's going to stop me, Anna.
You belong to me!
Anna!
Damn, it's raining.
Maki-san.
I'm so hot.
I shouldn't. I have Anna.
It's your fault for not letting me do anything to you, Anna!
I'm so hot!
Yuma-san?
Maki-san... you looked so beautiful.
Yuma-san, you were watching?
Oh my God, how embarrassing!
Don't! We can't do it here. No!
Ow! Th-That hurts!
I'm so hot!
No!
Stop!
What's the matter?
Does it feel better
when you touch yourself?
What's gotten into you, Yuma-san?
You want me to hurry and stick it
in you already. Right?
That's the spot! Fuck me, Yuma-san!
Ah! No, don't!
All right, then I'll put it in you.
Don't make it hurt!
It hurts! Be more gentle!
If you want me to go easy on you,
then beg for it properly!
It looks like you're about to cry.
Don't pull out! Don't pull out!
All right, I'll stick it in here, then!
It hurts! Please don't go overboard!
It feels so good! Don't stop!
Yuma-san! More! Fuck me harder!
It hurts! No!
Be gentle with me!
That's good, real good, Maki!
Keep acting like it hurts! It turns me on!
Wow! Amazing!
No! Fuck me harder!
Please... choke me.
Wring my neck... Yuma-san.
Choke me.
How does it feel?
Like this? How about now?
More! Stronger! Stronger! More!
That's good! It feels really good!
Like this? I'm going to choke you more.
It feels great!
This is going to... make it come out!
I'm going to pee! I can't hold it!
I'm going to lose my mind! More! Harder!
It's coming out! It's coming out!
I can't take it! It's amazing! Incredible!
More! Choke me more! Harder!
The blood...
The blood won't come off!
It feels... like I had a really long dream.
Good morning, Yuma!
The rain yesterday was unbelievable!
How about a walk in the garden?
You had a strange dream?
Yeah.
This mansion sure is huge.
It feels like we're in the woods.
What was the dream about?
Tell me.
Uh, I don't clearly recall what went on.
You see, the thing is, you coming to my room, Anna,
is like deja vu, or something that
has happened to me before.
It sort of felt like that.
Hm, deja vu, huh?
Oh, speaking of that, the night before
my uncle's birthday celebration, I was...
Come again?!
Last night's.... birthday celebration?
What's gotten into you?
Why are you acting so surprised?
I can't remember a single
thing from yesterday.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Can you tell me what happened last night...
at the birthday celebration?
Sure thing. Some fancy food
was brought out,
and uncle seemed to be in a good mood.
But out of nowhere, Tomoki suddenly turned down uncle's allowance,
and that wrecked the party.
I just... can't remember.
Natsuko-san and Kengo-san, who came
to do a story on the mansion,
seemed to be rather distressed.
Ah, you remember those two, right?
Yeah. They came here to do a story,
and I remember being
introduced to them.
Did... you remember something?
Yeah.
Film? Why do you have that?
Inagaki-san said that Natsuko and her fiancé
left first thing this morning, but...
It was lying here.
His... broken camera.
The hole I dug is gone as well.
It isn't around here at all.
How strange. I wonder if someone picked it up.
Hey, let's develop the film.
This place really has everything.
Tomoki loves photography, so my uncle
built it for him when he went off to college.
This is the last one.
What's this?!
When... did we take this photo?
Huh? We took it yesterday morning! Everyone was there.
I'm losing my grip on reality.
I can only remember the dream.
The fact that there's a photo proves it.
Before my uncle's birthday celebration,
I also remember getting into
Tomoki-kun's car, but aside from that...
I was dozing off on my bed in my room before I realized it.
That guy... Come to think of it, at that time,
he said he was going out into town
with Maki, Mustafa, and you.
Make sure to suck it more thoroughly,
Tomoki-sama.
Yes, like that. Very good.
Well, now, allow me to lend you a hand.
Please sto-
It worked on him.
Why won't it work on me?!
Good job, Natsuko-kun.
You'll make a fine Kawarazaki manor maid.
Maki-sama, the master is calling for you.
Yuma-san!
Allow me... to wash your back.
No way! Cut it out!
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope!
Seems like he's snapped.
Serves him right.
He tried to rebel against me.
Moreover, he laid hands on Anna!
You aren't sucking it hard enough! Get off!
Inagaki, I'm at half-mast.
Let's make sure that damned Tomoki knows who his master is.
Bring him here.
Yes, my master.
Don't talk back! Who do you think
got you to where you are?!
Huh?!
Your time is up, old man.
This will enable you to give better blowjobs.
Will you tell me what happened?
Who got you so hot and bothered
that you soiled your swimsuit?
Now...
Come now, spit it out.
Tell me the name.
If you can't tell me,
then I'll go about it like this.
My, my.
No! Don't!
I'm going to be ruined!
Well, look at you.
You are such a naughty girl, my lady.
Semen? Don't tell me...
What are you doing? Don't stop!
Maki-sama has lost her virginity.
How should I break it to the master?
I have to find out who did this.
She sure is careless.
Where could she have gone off to?
Yuma!
My uncle, Inagaki-san, and Mika-san
are nowhere to be found!
Tomoki isn't around, either.
I wonder where everyone went this early in the morning.
About this... Where's this room?
It should be good about now.
I'll stick this in there for you instead.
Stop! Don't do it!
Ah, that feels nice, Tomoki. Oh!
You're not half bad. Oh!
I'll give you a treat.
Give it to him, Natsuko-kun.
Yes, my master.
Stop! Don't do it. N-Natsuko!
I have to do as my master tells me to.
It's my duty as a maid, naturally.
Natsuko... Why?
What's gotten into you?
Ah, that feels rather nice.
It seems that you have
your uses too, Tomoki.
Well then, here's your reward
from the master.
Oh, that's nice! That a boy, Tomoki!
You're rather good at this!
J-Just like that!
Just like that.
Inagaki, is everything in order?
Yes. The fruits of our three days of labor should start blossoming any time now.
I see.
Your supposedly virgin hole is expanding
and inviting my fingers in.
I can feel that! It feels great!
Do mine in the same way! Harder!
Just like that!
Be more gentle!
It hurts! That feels good!
Oh no! I can't take it!
It feels so good!
More! More!
That's the stuff! Just like that, Maki-sama! Good job!
No! It feels so good!
I can't take it!
I'll make you feel just a little bit better.
How's that? You're wetter than
an otter's pocket, Maki-sama!
This is up next.
It's a bit of a behemoth.
All right, now open up your pussy lips nice and wide.
How does it feel, Maki-sama?
Do you like the tail end of this one?
You're taking in such a big one.
Well?
Which do you like better,
that man or this?
It feels good! Oh so good!
Filling up your bottom lips turns you
into quite the chatterbox, doesn't it?
Don't stop! Just a little more! Don't stop!
In that case, hurry up and spill it.
Tell me the name of the man
who did this to you.
I'm cumming!
Go faster!
I'm cumming! Yuma-san!
Yuma-sama. That guy?
See? That window.
To be continued
Next.Time
The Fourth Horror
Spiral of Despair and Sadness