Please...
Hey, I'm begging you.
I'll do whatever you say!
So please have mercy!
Please...
I won't think about that anymore.
I'm perfectly content just being the tutor!
Wait. I'll stay away from this house entirely!
I won't tell anyone on the outside
about this house either.
So please don't kill me!
I ain't gonna kill ya.
I'd never kill a woman like you,
with a pretty body and all.
Really?
Yes, really.
However...
I need to punish you a little.
What?
Just to make sure you won't get any stupid ideas
like taking the place of the
Kawarazaki family's daughter.
No!
Wh-What are you doing?
No! Stop it!
What are you doing?
What are you doing to me?
Was it the mouth on your head that said you
wanted to join the Kawarazaki family?
Or was It...
Stop it.
...this mouth?
No! Stop it!
Wh-What are you doing?
How is it?
Delicious?
What did you put in?
What is it?
Don't worry.
Hot. It's really hot!
It's the usual drug, just twenty times more potent.
No, it's completely different.
It's hot!
Down there... feels so hot!
I hope you'll get lots of pleasure from it.
You may never regain your sanity.
Gozen!
Um... U-Um..
What do you want this late at night?
My humblest apologies.
But actually, um, well... Kyoko died.
Oh dear. That does present us with a little problem.
P-Please, sir.
Please help me!
I really liked that woman's body.
Is her body still in good condition?
I don't like to waste things.
Very nice.
Leave it to me.
Don't worry about anything.
Kawarazaki Mansion
Part 2
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: v1touch |Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
Alice-san!
How? Why?
Rokuro-san, why are you
spouting such nonsense?
I am Kawarazaki Kyoko.
But Alice-san...
Rokuro-san?
How dare you call me by the
name of my former servant!
Or are you losing your mind, dear?
Mother, hurry!
Okay.
Coming, honey.
What are you standing there for?
You're in the way.
Oh, good morning.
Are you sleepwalking or something?
If you stand still in the middle of
the hall, we can't get through.
Sachiko-sama...
You've been hired by this house,
so you should do as we say.
Otherwise, you won't be able to leave in one piece.
Rokuro-san?
Misako-san...
What is it?
Misako-san, did you know all along?
You knew, but you couldn't tell me anything?
Uh, well...
I thought so.
What I saw last night with Kyoko-san wasn't a dream.
Um, Rokuro-san...
Rokuro-san?
I made him swallow something.
Alice... I mean, Kyoko-sama.
Sleep well, Rokuro-san.
And when you wake up, you'll
forget all the nastiness.
Forget everything, and do exactly what I say.
Misako-san.
If you do, you may become
me someday, Misako-san.
Yes, Mistress.
Gozen...
What should I do about this?
You don't need to worry about anything.
Now, it's not a big deal.
Just do like that girl over there.
The young mistress?
Yes.
Just join with her.
But, sir...
I don't mind.
Come here, quickly.
Just like when you kidnapped me.
What should we do about Rokuro-san?
What do you mean?
He's still not used to the ways of this house.
He seems confused.
It's Nanbara's fault!
That dirty old man.
He doesn't think things through.
You're right.
But thanks to his negligence,
I'm in the position I am now.
See?
It's okay, right?
That hurts!
Dammit, I don't care what happens.
I'll take my time in tasting your body.
Unlike in the past.
I've gotten pretty hard now. Suck me off.
What's wrong?
Come on.
What?
Long ago, you used to suck on it like it was candy.
Oh, or would you rather have a
different kind of honey instead?
Come on.
What's wrong?
Just putting it in your mouth doesn't please me.
Use your tongue.
Yeah, that's nice.
Wait, it's coming.
You've gotten pretty good at it.
Maybe because Gozen trained you so well?
I guess I filled up your mouth
better than he did, though.
Now then, I wonder if you've
gotten good this way too...
This time, I won't pierce you so suddenly.
I don't want another dead body on my hands.
You're all wet.
No! No, no.
I guess I can put it in now.
Wait.
Entering now would be nice,
but let's test out this drug instead.
Rei will prefer it this way too.
No.
Don't put anything weird inside me. Please!
I'm begging you.
No. Stop it.
Stop it, please.
I'm begging you!
No!
No.
I don't want to lose myself.
No!
Don't. No...
She's ready now.
It's about time, right?
Yes.
No!
I can't take it!
I'm cumming!
Hey, what's happening?
Hey, answer me.
Good work.
Thanks to you, I got some good ingredients.
The fluids from a man just before
ejaculation make the perfect drug.
What the hell are you doing!?
It's his punishment for killing Mother.
Shunsuke!
Thanks to this moron, our plan to make
Rokuro our big brother has gone haywire.
Should we also crush Rokuro?
Not so fast!
You guys promised you wouldn't hurt Rokuro!
Look who's talking big.
And who brought Rokuro to
this house in the first place?
Rei Onee-sama sure is cute.
I don't want to hear that from you!
You make me hard.
Shut up!
That's right.
If you suck me dry, I'll spare Rokuro.
Hell no.
You have too much.
I don't think you understand me, Onee-sama.
This isn't a request, it's an order.
Fine, I'll do it.
Just don't kill Rokuro.
Let's kill him.
That will solve our problem.
Good idea.
I think that's a good idea.
Mother, you can take care of it.
No, I don't want to kill him.
Then what do you propose?
You do it.
No way!
I don't want to touch a man!
But...
You should do it.
You're the head of this household, after all.
Right, Mother?
Good point.
Then, I'll have Misako-san do it.
Take care of it, please, Onee-chan.
Sure.
Um, um, Mistress Rei?
What?
What is it?
Well...
Spit it out.
Why did you bring Rokuro-san to this house?
Huh?
Because I'm a brat.
Right...
Last time Nanbara got out, he tried to kidnap a girl.
But Rokuro saved her.
That’s why?
Yes, it is.
Because I'm a brat.
And because I wanted to degrade an innocent man.
Here's what I promised.
Thank you for the money.
Thank you.
What's the matter?
I'm sure it's not anything bad.
You'll be paid in full, just a different party.
Make sure you see them, that’s all.
Um, but...
You mean you can't drive?
I can drive, but...
Don't worry.
I know you can do it.
We're having problems now that Nanbara is gone.
Please?
Let me think about it.
The number you have dialed is no longer in use.
Please check the number and try again.
We need to test a strong-willed
woman every now and then,
or there's just no fun in it.
Well, I don't hold a candle to you, Professor.
I really gotta hand it to ya, Gozen.
You give us so much of the good stuff.
It's nothing, it's nothing.
You help me out too, Professor.
It's the least I can do.
No, no, I insist on thanking you.
I really like it.
Ah, yes, the "goods" are inside the car.
It's what you asked for, correct?
Oh, will you do me that favor?
The media has been on my ass lately.
Hey.
Rokuro-san, unload these goods into the house.
Yes! That's wonderful!
More! More!
Please!
Onee-sama?
Shunsuke.
Will you do it again?
You're the chauffeur now, they tell me.
Yeah.
Didn't you dislike cars or something?
When I was a kid, a car just like this almost hit me.
And just the sight of it scared me.
And you saved her?
This car almost hit a girl.
And you saved her, didn't you?
Really?
I don't remember anything like that.
Listen...
When I was little, I was kidnapped,
brought to this house, and renamed "Rei."
I was forced into this car.
I see.
And no one saved me back then.
If you'd been there, would you have saved me?
Well, maybe.
What would you say if I asked
you to run away with me?
No way.
I don't want to get fired for indulging a child's whim.
That reminds me, you offered me your body earlier.
I've thought it over, and I'm okay with it.
Idiot!
Am I not good enough?
Yes?
Yeah? Come in.
Huh?
What's wrong, Misako-san?
Um, Rokuro-san...
Well...
Please... make love to me.
Huh? What do you mean?
Please make love to me.
Why?
This isn't like you, Misako-san.
No, this is very much like me.
All this time...
Someone made you say that.
No!
It was Rei, wasn't it?
She was acting weird earlier today.
No. It's not only Rei-san.
Nanbara-san and the grandfather
have always been this way.
So I don't mind.
Misako-san.
This place pays much more than a soapland!
And my family really needs the money.
It's for them. That's why I'm here.
And besides, couldn't do it with
Nanbara-san, but I could with you.
Misako-san, let's escape.
I didn't mean for that.
I don't think you belong here.
But... I can't...
You can.
Huh? Misako-san?
Misako-san?
Rei!
Rei's gone too?
Ready?
Yes.
Misako-san?
Sorry!
Miya-san.
Have you seen Misako-san?
No.
It must be Rei.
Rei hid her somewhere.
I don't think that's true.
Yeah, but...
Sachiko-sama has me,
but Rei-san has no one.
Everyone in this house is lonely.
Then where is Misako-san?
Well, she's...
It's okay.
Sachiko-sama!
Have a little more faith in Rei.
But I...
Misako's in the hut.
Misako-san!
You're awake, boy?
You bastard, what have you done to her?
Something wonderful.
I'm going to lead her into an existence of ecstasy.
Wh-What the hell?
Don't be so pissy.
You tasted some of it yourself, Rokuro.
You fucking liar!
Maybe you don't know then?
If you join our family, you can
experience many wonderful things.
You still doubt me?
Then let me show you what true ecstasy is.
You idiot!
I'm not into that!
Oh, so you dislike boys?
Then what about this?
How about women?
Shall we continue what we were doing last night?
Stop it!
Back off!
Don't touch me!
You don't like it?
Then...
Get away from Rokuro!
Rei!
Rei.
I don't like this.
She's trying to overthrow me.
Rei Onee-chan...
What's going on?
Why didn't you leave last night?
H-Hey, wait a minute.
What's going on? Explain!
You should have run while you had the chance!
Hurry.
He's still not dead.
Go! Hurry!
But what about Misako-san?
It's too late.
Grandpa ruined her, and she's not coming back.
And I was hoping we could all run away together.
I'm sorry.
Rei...
This place won't last long.
Hurry and go.
But what about you?
Get out of here, jackass!
Rei...
I'm all the way out here?
It's you?
Get in!
Hey, how did you know I was here?
I was asked.
And I was paid.
In the beginning, it was the same.
I was paid to tell you to work here.
It was you?
Yes, it was me.
I'm sorry.
Rei... huh...
What did you say?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
15 Years Later...
Nothing has changed...
It can't be...
It's different... It's completely different.
That's not them!
Father!
Welcome back, Father!
Wh-Who are you?
Jeez, Father!
Did you forget because you've
been gone for so long?
It's me, your second daughter, Rei!
No way...
I was just thinking that I'd like to do it with Father!
You're Shunsuke, right?
You're Shunsuke, aren't you!?
Onii-sama! Father has returned!
Stop! This is all wrong!
You're all different!
Don't come! Stop!
Stop it!
Father is so weird.
I think fun things are just around the corner.