Kagome, Kagome,
little bird in its cage.
When, oh when, will you escape?
On a moonlit night,
the crane and the tortoise slipped.
Who is the young man behind you?
The Kawarazaki Household 2
The First Horror
Toying with the Sacrificial Lambs
A dream?
Understood, Anna-oujosama.
I shall take my leave now.
They said they'd come and pick us up.
Oh, okay.
In the past, this place used to be bustling.
It seems to have quieted down.
I feel like I've seen this scenery somewhere before.
Is this deja vu?
No, it's nothing.
More importantly, are you sure it's okay for a stranger
to crash your uncle's birthday party?
I want you to come along.
Don't get me wrong!
I want to introduce you
to my uncle, Yuma-kun.
Young master Tomoki,
where are you?
Maki-oujosama, would you happen to know
the whereabouts of your elder brother?
I think my brother is out back with Mustafa.
Oh, is that so?
My lady, that water is for visitors.
You came to pick us up, Tomoki-kun?
Did Inagaki-san have his hands full?
Inagaki? Where in hell would he get
a car to come and pick you up with?
Listen up. The Kawarazakis are not the same as before.
They used to take in countless
children such as us
to train as servants to serve
their every whim for amusement.
The Kawarazaki family
has changed since then.
Maki... Maki-oujosama...
Doing something such as this...
Young master Tomoki...
Master must never...
Inagaki...
I... What's gotten into me?
I'm so hot!
Enough with the chitchat!
Keep it up! Don't stop!
Y-Yes, Maki-oujosama.
Why can't you stick it in me
to make me feel even better?
Th-That's...
Lick it!
Hey. It's my job to protect
my lady's tight virgin pussy.
It smells so good.
From behind... It should be okay to take her from behind.
That's fine! Do it, Inagaki!
As for how things are now...
The industrial and financial world, as well as
the rest of the world, has backed away from us.
They left one by one as the years went by.
The only ones gathering at the mansion for his birthday are Maki and I...
and you guys.
Next year, you two will be the only ones to show up.
Why will we be the only ones next year?
Well, that depends on whether or not you guys are still friends in a year.
I can't be bothered with him anymore!
I told him that clearly this morning.
Maki-oujosama...
Oh! You are tight!
You are so nice and tight.
Inagaki! H-Hurry up!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming, my lady.
Get on with it already!
You should cut ties with
our uncle as well, Ayaka.
The only reason he paid for our room and board was because he wanted us to drift apart.
This is where you'll be staying.
What about Anna?
I do believe Anna-oujosama is taking a shower in her own room.
Please ring this to call us
if you need anything.
I'll be taking my leave.
I thought I'd get to stay
in the same room with Anna,
even though I've only held her hand.
Serves me right for getting my hopes up.
Even so...
Don't get me wrong!
I want to introduce you
to my uncle, Yuma-kun.
Mustafa!
I have brought you some cold water.
Oh, thank you.
That damn Tomoki.
Were you scared shitless, Inagaki?
Yes, my master.
Will you forgive
my transgressions this time?
Not yet! Keep going!
Yes, my master.
Ah, Anna-oujosama.
Inagaki-san, you were home?
Huh? Uh, yes.
At the master's request, I was preparing the main dish for everyone.
I know you went through a lot of trouble, but I'm not all that hungry.
That's a concern.
All right, I will prepare
something else right away.
Oh no, you needn't bother.
Ah, Yuma. Should I give you a tour of the mansion?
Yeah. I'll be right down.
H-Hey, you two, have you seen Mustafa?
No.
I-I see. No...
Where could Mustafa have gone?
Could he be off chasing
raccoon dogs again?
Dinner is ready.
Then let's eat.
Welcome to the Kawarazaki manor.
So you want us to wash down
overcooked meat with water, huh?
Meat is only delicious when it's rare.
Only poor people eat
their meat well done.
Would you like to join me
for some tea in my room?
No thanks. I'm a bit tired today.
Sorry.
I just... might be tired myself.
I feel really thirsty for some reason.
I have brought you some cold water.
How did you know?
Thank you!
I thought it was down this way, but...
A magic mirror?
Well, Suzune-kun? What do you think of this new pleasure?
That... can't be what I think it is!
What's going on?
Well? You should be pretty full by now.
I'm going to pee myself
if you keep that up.
I'm going to pee myself!
All right then, we have to show them something nice.
Ah, no!
Don't do that!
Oh, it's cleaning up nicely!
It's coming out! I'm going to pee myself!
Damn, those sick bastards!
I didn't bother to save her either.
Why?!
I'm th-thirsty.
I got an indirect kiss.
I'm so hot.
I'm so hot. Do something
about it for me!
I-I'm burning up too!
Don't do that, Maki-san!
All right, then!
Hurry up! Hurry up and
give it to me already!
Yuma-san, why are you doing this?
Are you feeling it?
I'm scared.
There's nothing to fear.
Yuma-san, I've loved you
ever since I first met you,
but we can't have sex!
No! Uncle will punish me!
Don't! I'm getting horny!
I'm so hot!
It hurts!
It hurts! Yuma-san!
It hurts, Yuma-san!
It hurts! Stop it!
Yuma-san!
It feels good! Oh, so good!
I'm going to lose my mind!
It feels so incredibly good!
My, my, to think that Suzune-kun went and left that out in a place like this.
I'll just increase the dosage
a little for them.
They showed up after all, huh?
Yes. Think of it as a way
to celebrate your birthday.
To be continued
Next.Time
The Second Horror
Invitation to Die