Semen? Don't tell me...
What are you doing? Don't stop!
Maki-sama has lost her virginity.
How should I break it to the master?
I have to find out who did this.
Ah, that feels nice, Tomoki. Oh!
You're not half bad. Oh!
I'll give you a treat.
Give it to him, Natsuko-kun.
Yes, my master.
Well then, here's your reward
from the master.
Oh, that's nice! That a boy, Tomoki!
You're rather good at this.
J-Just like that!
Just like that.
Inagaki, is everything in order?
Yes. The fruits of our three days of labor should start blossoming any time now.
I see.
How's that? You're wetter than
an otter's pocket, Maki-sama!
This is up next.
Don't stop! Just a little more!
Don't stop!
In that case, hurry up and spill it.
Tell me the name of the man
who did this to you.
Go faster!
I'm cumming! Yuma-san!
Yuma-sama? That guy?
The Kawarazaki Household 2
The Fourth Horror
Spiral of Despair and Sadness
She sure is careless.
Where could she have gone off to?
Yuma!
My uncle, Inagaki-san, and Mika-san
are nowhere to be found!
Tomoki isn't around, either.
I wonder where everyone went this early in the morning.
About this... Where's this room?
I think it's over this way.
See?
That window.
See? Over there.
It looks like it was taken
from inside the room.
It should be somewhere near my uncle's library, if I'm not mistaken.
What is it?
Let's go look.
Huh?!
Hey, Yuma,
this totally looks like a guillotine.
Yuma?
Maki-chan!
Yuma!
Don't!
What's the matter? Does it feel
better when you touch yourself?
I should hurry and stick it in you already. Right?
What's gotten into you, Yuma-san?
Well? Be honest!
Fuck me, Yuma-san!
All right, then I'll put it in you.
No! Don't make it hurt!
It hurts! Be more gentle!
Don't be a spoiled brat!
If you want me to go easy on you,
then beg for it properly!
Yuma-san, it hurts!
Drown in the first stage of pleasure!
Consider it punishment for not doing as you were told!
Take a good long look!
This is what happens to those who
don't follow the rules! Inagaki!
It's time.
Kengo-san!
Natsuko? Where am I?
Kengo-san! Kengo-san!
What's all this?
What are we doing here?
Kengo-san! Kengo-san!
Time's up.
Inagaki-san, what are you doing?
Maki-sama made a promise
to Mawatsuna-sama.
She is being punished for breaking
that promise by being a slut.
No, don't!
Don't make it hurt!
Wh-What is this?!
You guys killed Tomoki-kun
and Suzune-san!
Now, now, don't be silly.
Tomoki-sama got too caught up in
rough sex and killed Suzune-kun.
Then he hung himself out of shock.
Liar! Tomoki-kun's hands
were tied behind him!
Yuma!
What's this I'm feeling?
Hey, Yuma...
What are you going to do?
Uncle!
Anna. I've been waiting
for this moment to come.
Mika-san?
Seems like today is one of your safe days, Anna-oujosama, so...
I will be using this to get you nice and loose.
How does it feel, Anna-oujosama?
Don't stick it in there!
Stop it! Uncle, why are you doing this?!
That's nice, Anna.
That's the face I want to see.
Maki betrayed me too.
You kept your promise to me, your adopted parent, just like you were told.
Anna, I'm grateful for that.
Inagaki, it's time to start the ceremony.
Yes, my master.
How does it feel to finally
have that thing off?
Stop it! Make them stop, Uncle!
This is a medicine that will make you feel
good and stimulate your sex drive.
It seems that Inagaki's dosage was a little inadequate.
In that case, I will shoot it directly into here.
No!
Anna!
Stop him!
Yes, sir.
Anna!
You son of a bitch!
Yuma! No! No!
No! No!
No!
Anna!
Kagome, Kagome,
little bird in its cage.
When, oh when, will you escape?
On a moonlit night,
the crane and tortoise slipped.
Who is the young man behind you?
If I could just... go back to that time.
A dream?
It looks like no one is home.
I'll try to call again in a bit.
Oh, okay.
In the past, this place used to be bustling.
It seems to have quieted down.
It feels like I've seen this scenery somewhere before.
Is this deja vu?
No, it's nothing.
More importantly, are you sure it's okay for a stranger
to crash your uncle's birthday party?
It's not like that!
I want to introduce you
to my uncle, Yuma-kun.
That place looks like it has a nice view.
Want to go look?
Y-Yeah.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah, it is, Anna.
I've always... always wanted to do this.
Me too.
This is my first time.
I feel shy but also happy.
How does it feel?
Does it feel good?
It feels so good!
I can't take it! More!
More!
No! Don't tease me!
Ow! No! Don't stop!
It hurts!
It feels so good!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Don't pull out! Don't pull out!
No! Not there!
No!
Ow, it hurts!
No...
N-No! I'm so hot!
I can't take it! I can't take it anymore!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Kagome, Kagome,
little bird in its cage.
When, oh when, will you escape?
On a moonlit night,
the crane and tortoise slipped.
Who is the young man behind you?