Kagome, Kagome,
little bird in its cage.
When, oh when will you escape?
On a moonlit night,
the crane and tortoise slipped.
Who is the young man behind you?
Yuma-san, I've loved you
ever since I first met you,
but we can't have sex!
No! My uncle will punish me!
Stop it! I'm getting horny!
I'm so hot!
It hurts!
It hurts! Yuma-san!
Yuma-san!
It hurts! Stop it!
My, my, to think that Suzuna-kun went
and left that out in a place like this.
I'll just increase the dosage
a little for them.
They showed up after all, huh?
Yes. Think of it as a way
to celebrate your birthday.
The Kawarazaki Household 2
The Second Horror
Invitation to Die
Geez, you're hopeless!
You become totally enamored
when you get a camera in your hands.
You lose track of time completely.
Y-Yes?
Your clothes have dried,
so I've brought them to you.
Thank you.
May I inquire if your
companion is your fiancé?
Yes. Wh-Why do you ask?
Your companion said that cheerfully when I brought him his clothes.
If you had told us ahead of time, we would
have put you in the same room.
No, we're fine.
Dinner will be ready shortly.
I will give you a tour around the mansion after dinner.
She's rather beautiful.
Yes. When she was looking to do a story
on an old western style house,
I looked into her personal affairs
and ran a background check.
I didn't expect her fiancé to come, though.
All the better.
It simply means we have to rethink our hospitality a bit.
Just tweak things a little, Inagaki.
Yes, sir, I understand.
I just wish I could get this over with.
I turned down his invitation last night.
I wonder if it upset Yuma.
Anna...
My...
Anna!
She's mine. She's mine...
now and forever!
Anna... forever!
Tomoki-sama.
I-I called out repeatedly.
Y-You saw! You saw me! You saw me!
You saw me like this!
Didn't you? Didn't you? Didn't you?!
Please calm down!
Tomoki-sama, it won't come out!
Keep going just like that!
It won't come out!
Suzune!
T-Tomoki-sama...
Suzune, that feels incredible!
It feels really good!
Suzune!
It feels so good!
It feels good, Suzune!
Incredible! Suzune! Suzune!
T-Tomoki-sama...
Suzune...
Use it on me, too!
Suzune! You're my new fuck buddy!
Lick the ground just like Mustafa did!
Stick your ass out this way!
T-Tomoki-sama...
Hurry up and do it, Suzune!
I'm your master!
You will do it!
Tomoki-sama!
Here we go, Suzune!
Howl! Howl, Suzune! Just like Mustafa did!
Tomoki-sama... Tomoki-sama!
Suzune! Suzune! Suzune!
Howl! More!
More!
That a girl, Suzune.
Mustafa! Mustafa!
Please... be more gentle.
More! Beg me more!
It just makes me harder!
Stop! I'm going to lose my mind!
Maki!
You must be tired.
It's okay for you to take a moment's rest.
Why am I doing this again?
You're digging your own grave so we can
get rid of your body when you die.
I'm digging my own grave
for when I die?
The blood...
The blood won't come off!
Good morning, Yuma!
The rain yesterday was unbelievable.
How about a walk in the garden?
This mansion sure is huge.
It feels like we're in the woods.
Yeah, it takes about an hour just
to go around the garden once.
It wasn't this overgrown in the past,
because our gardener used to tend to it.
This place...
Maki!
Maki! Maki!
Now where did that Maki run off to?
First Mustafa, now her.
Good morning!
Maki-chan! Good morning!
You were taking Mustafa for a walk?
Yup! He howls outside my window
first thing in the morning.
Yuma-san, there you are!
Good morning!
Anna... I... Wait here.
Impossible. Was I dreaming?
Mustafa and Maki are still alive!
The hole... The hole l was digging is gone!
It's not here! That dog's head...
Was I... only dreaming?
I'm thirsty!
Everything is kept so clean.
The mansion's big,
so it must be difficult, right?
The master loves everything to be
clean and orderly, you see.
Pardon the interruption,
but that's the master's private room,
so please refrain from taking photographs or going inside.
But this is a beautiful antique stained glass window, so...
You're so hopeless, Kengo-san.
I'm sure there are plenty more where
that came from. Let's go.
I can just come back later, I guess.
Wait up!
There... has to be something here!
Hey! What are you doing?
You were searching for Maki and Mustafa. Did you find them?
I was searching for them?
What are you talking about?
Maki, Mustafa, and Anna
are all waiting in my car.
They want to go shopping in town.
It's unfortunate,
but my car only seats four.
You'll be staying home.
This is the perfect job for you.
Oh, sorry.
Kengo-san said the sunset was so beautiful.
Also, he wanted to photograph a mansion
where the light came in.
I'll let him in there later.
Please, drink up before it gets cold.
Okay. Thanks for the tea.
My, how delicious!
Is it Royal Sub's Second Club?
Yes, the lycum tea that was sold until the end of June.
Our butler, Inagaki, bought it up
easily in a small auction.
It blends in nicely with our well water.
It smells nice and tastes delicious!
I'll be sure to let Inagaki know.
Please eat the cookies as well.
Welcome to Kawarazaki manor.
We went past the bridge.
Where are Maki-san and Yuma?
I lied... about them waiting on the bridge.
Anna!
Just how long are you going
to remain asleep?
Wake up already.
S-Stop this! Natsuko!
It can't be helped!
You broke the mansion rules, Kengo-san!
Get on with it already!
Well, Natsuko-kun,
it's time to punish your fiancé
for breaking the mansion rules.
Yes, sir.
D-Don't do it!
Well? How does it feel to be punished by your fiancé?
It isn't fair that you're the only one getting punished, is it?
I'll be administering the same punishment to your fiancée.
Stop! I'm begging you!
It seems like you haven't
been forgiven just yet.
Your pussy sure is a pretty pink color.
All right now. I'm going to inject
this into her pearl-like clitoris.
It'll start feeling better soon.
Anna. Anna!
Stop it!
Please stop!
It looks like they're having quite a bit of fun over there.
That being said, you look like
you're enjoying yourself as well.
You got excited from watching your fiancé getting raped.
Your ass wants it, too.
Inagaki...
Punish Natsuko-kun as well.
Yes, my Master.
I'm c-cumming!
Not yet. I won't let you cum that easily.
Your fiancé is starting to enjoy it.
That's good. That's good, Sho-kun.
Mika, make him cum once more.
Yes, my Master.
Natsuko! Stop it! Please, stop!
You still have some fight left.
Fret over her some more.
Well? Who do you prefer,
me or that pissy-smelling woman?
Kengo-san! How cruel! How cruel!
It seems I can't satisfy you.
All right, then, let's find
something you like.
Your real punishment starts now.
Please... Please forgive me already!
No!
Anna... Anna...
Like that's going to stop me, Anna.
You're mine. You belong to me!
Th-This is...
To be continued
Next.Time
The Third Horror
Devil's Labyrinth