A trip, huh? Just the two of us...
Okay.
Are you sure?
Only if it's overseas.
Overseas?
Yep.
That's what everyone's doing these days, you know?
I've found a nice little gig for
you to earn some extra cash.
Gig?
Yes. It pays 30,000 yen.
Well?
I thought it sounded too good to be true.
It doesn't sound like very difficult work.
And?
You're going to be a servant
at a rich person's mansion.
Yes?
Kawarazaki Mansion
Part 1
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: v1touch |Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
So you are Saito Rokuro-san?
Oh.
I am the mistress of this house.
Kawarazaki Taizou's wife, Kyoko.
I'm Saito Rokuro.
Nice to meet you.
We have plenty of servants at this house as it is,
but my daughter insisted that
I get her a manservant.
Quite a problem.
Uh, yeah.
Seriously, there's not much work to do.
Well, it can't be helped.
We'll put you to work anyway.
Okay.
If you have any questions about
your duties, ask Misako-san.
Oh, hi.
Or ask Alice-san.
Nice to meet you.
Alice-san!
Alice-san?
I-I'm fine!
But...
Now then, Rokuro-san,
I'm counting on you.
Right.
Alice-san!
It's nothing!
Really!
That isn't so at all!
That reminds me.
The girl who collapsed back there...
You mean Alice-san?
Is she ill?
Well...
Welcome home, Miss!
This man will be working here
as a servant for a while.
He is Saito Rokuro-san.
Thank you, Captain Obvious!
Who's that?
Mistress Rei.
She looked angry.
Well...
Remote controlled cars?
That's a good model.
Wish I had one.
Rei-san!
Dinner is served.
Don't want any.
But...
I said I don't want any!
Ah, hello?
I can’t come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message after the beep.
It's Saito Rokuro.
I'm home.
I know it's a bit late, but I just
wanted to let you know
that I'm at the mansion for
that,servant gig right now.
I'll call you later.
Bye.
Something smells?
I can't place it, though.
Come on, come on.
Walk straight ahead.
All right.
Good, right there.
You're a bitch-dog.
And bitch-dogs need to act like bitch-dogs.
The mistress?
Please, have mercy.
I can't hold out much longer.
Dogs don't talk, bitch.
Well, fine.
Do it here.
Right here?
Yeah, that's right here.
Very well.
Rokuro-san!
Please wake up!
Good morning.
What are you doing?
Last night...
Yes?
Well, maybe it was those flowers I smelled.
Huh?
Um, good morning.
Are you used to it yet?
I guess two days isn't enough to tell.
Um, you're the younger daughter.
Yep. I'm Rei.
You're in a better mood than last night.
Huh? Oh, that Well, I hate Misako.
Really?
She seems nice to me.
She fools everybody that way.
By the way, do you like the work here?
Oh, well, I appreciate the high pay,
but it seems a bit dull, because
there's really nothing for me to do.
If you want something to do,
I think you'll find it really soon.
I think fun things are just around the corner.
What do you mean?
Good question.
How about kidnapping me for starters?
That's stupid.
If I did that, I'd lose all my pay.
Oh, well.
In that case, you can earn it back by pleasuring me.
If you don't mind, wanna start right now?
Thanks, but no thanks.
I like things to stick out a bit further.
Ask me later when you've developed more.
What the hell!
I'm really sensitive about that!
Ow.
What the hell's her problem?
Who's there.
Oh, it's you.
I'm Nanbara, the driver.
So he's not her husband.
An affair?
What's wrong?
Um, nothing. Nice to meet you.
You sure are a lucky guy.
Our young mistress is blossoming, isn't she?
Huh?
Never mind. You'll know what I mean eventually.
Hope we can help each other out, brother.
Ah, that's right.
I'm still just a larva.
Out again tonight?
Hey, can ya get the car for me?
Nanbara isn't around.
Sorry, but I can't drive.
I don't believe you.
Someone your age without a license?
I have a license,
I just can't drive that car.
You know, that kind of car?
What the hell!
I'm surprised my mom hired such a moron.
Very well.
Then go find Nanbara for me.
So whaddya think?
I'll show ya some fun.
Okay.
You'd better agree.
Otherwise it's pointless to pay you so much.
Um...
What is it?
Sachiko-san says she wants the car.
Fine.
That tickles.
We can't!
We can't, Mom.
Shunsuke-san...
Alice!
P-Pardon me.
Don't go, Alice!
Shunsuke-sama!
Hey, Mother!
Can I go play with Alice?
Yes.
Take good care of him, Alice-san.
Yes, Mistress.
Come on, Alice!
Misako said the cucumbers
in the garden are ripe now.
Let's go pick some.
I apologize, Mistress.
Alice, hurry!
Wait for me, Shunsuke-sama!
Rokuro-san!
Rokuro-san, are you there?
Shunsuke-san? I'm coming in.
What?
She asked me to clean it, but it's already clean.
Huh?
That smell again.
I guess the people in this house
really like that smell.
What the hell is this?
And this too?
I don't care how perverted his mom is.
It's a little strange for a kid to have all this.
What's this?
Oh, I thought so.
It couldn't be.
Oh, shit!
This is really bad.
Why?
Is someone in there?
Well, never mind.
Huh?
Huh? But that wasn't Shunsuke's voice.
You summoned me?
A-Alice-san?
Enter.
Yes, sir.
You're quite lazy, Alice.
I-I apologize, sir.
You really are trash.
Please forgive me, sir!
If you want my forgiveness, then lift up your skirt.
Yes, sir.
Oh,
you're such a problem, Alice.
You're all wet.
M-My humblest apologies, Master!
My heart... My heart is distracted by dirty juices.
It's that smell again.
With just the remote vibrator,
you're that wet already.
I wonder how wet you'd get if I stuck it inside?
You're so slippery.
Please have mercy! Please have mercy!
Alice is a very dirty, naughty maid!
That's not true at all.
Come, stand up.
Face me.
And spread your legs.
Very nice.
You're very pretty, Alice.
I love you veiy much.
Here is your reward.
Thank you, Master.
How was it?
Did it feel good?
Yes.
How so?
Um, my pussy was throbbing hard.
And... And then...
Lots of dirty juice came out.
Yes.
If you're a naughty maid, I can't let
you release so much dirty juice.
I apologize, Shunsuke-sama!
If you want me to forgive you,
then pleasure me, Alice.
I will.
Lick it.
That's not right Strip it down.
That's right.
Very good, Alice.
Mother doesn't hold a candle to you.
If only you were my mother.
Alice, I think I feel strange.
Shunsuke-sama.
You're all dirty, Alice.
I'll make you clean again.
You mustn't.
I can do it myself.
No. Don't move.
See? Look in the mirror, Alice.
Your pussy is soaking wet with dirty juice.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Then touch it yourself to make it feel even better.
Well? Does it feel good?
Yes. Very good.
That's good.
My thing has gotten big again.
What should I do about it?
Um..
What?
I can't.
Seems like I can't hold back anymore.
Please, Alice?
U-Use my...
U-Use my body.
How should I use it?
I don't know how at all.
Inside of here.
Inside of this lewd part of me.
Put yourself inside of me, please!
In here?
N-Not there.
Beneath it.
The flowery part.
Here?
Yes.
Right here?
Yes!
Rokuro-san?
Rokuro-san!
I heard the news.
Saito-san, right?
He's a good-looking guy.
I saw him when I was walking in.
I won't let you touch Rokuro!
Oh, don't suggest something so silly.
I would never lay a hand on someone you
chose for your family, Mistress Rei.
I'll see you again next week, Mistress Rei.
Good evening, Saito Rokuro-san.
Huh?
Oh, hi.
Huh? She's a tutor?
I'm not sure about Mistress Sachiko,
but Mistress Rei wants to go to Tokyo U.
That girl, huh?
Fat chance.
Wouldn't finishing school be better for her?
Are you used to the work here yet?
What? I guess so.
But this house is freaking weird.
The kids are perverse,
the mother seems to be into S&M,
and even the servants are strange.
Um, I wasn't talking about you, Misako-san.
I'm just as bad as the rest of them.
I belong to the Kawarazaki family.
Misako-san!
The high wages are barely worth it.
But...
Rokuro-san...
there's still a chance for you.
Go back to Tokyo and look for a normal job.
You seem to be in a really good mood.
Oh? Maybe I am.
Did something good happen?
Something good with a maid?
Maids aren't my thing!
But that boy...
Oh, you mean Rokuro?
He's going to be the eldest son, right?
Yeah.
That's what they're planning.
And why not let me be the “young mistress"?
Heh. I wondered why you wanted to talk.
If you do that, Rei won't stand for it.
What the hell!
She's just a kid.
Well, good luck to both of us.
Good evening, Rokuro-san.
Oh, good evening.
Making a phone call?
Sorry.
I don't mind.
It's only a phone.
Use it as often as you wish.
О-Окау.
I suppose being cooped up in a house
like this makes you miss Tokyo.
Or your girlfriend?
No.
You don't seem happy.
Are you sleeping well?
Um, yeah...
You liar.
I see circles under your eyes.
Well...
I'll give you some medicine,
to help you sleep better.
You'll feel much better.
No way I can feel better with this going on.
Guys, what are you doing?
Let's go.
Sachiko-sama!
It seems like Rokuro has tried
to phone outside many times.
That won’t do.
I know. I'll do something about it.
You'd better.
Or else I won't listen to your wishes.
Change.
Yes, sir.
Come on.
It's the usual.
No!
It's the one we usually use,
but I made the dosage a bit stronger.
I see!
Not strong enough to make her into a doll, but close.
The time will come later!
A-Amazing.
It seems like the drugs are stronger than usual.
Pull it tighter.
Tighter, please.
How's this, Kyoko?
How was that?
Good, right?
Come on, Kyoko, say something.
What's wrong?
Hey, Kyoko!
Wake up!
Hey, wake up, Kyoko!
Was that a dream?
Um...
Oh, good morning.
You're up early today.
Um, where's the mistress?
The mistress?
She should be down any minute.
Really?
Is something the matter?
Mother, hurry!
Rokuro-san!
Jeez, Mother, you take too long!
I'm already starving!
Oh, good morning, Rokuro-san.
It can't be.
Impossible!
To be continued...