Akkun... If don't mind doing it...
...with you. I mean...
...going all the way.
Koharu, I'm scared.
I have a fear of being betrayed by the person I fall in love with.
Akkun... You have nothing to worry about.
I'll always stay by your side, Akkun.
I would never betray you, Akkun.
Ko-Koharu...
I love you, Akkun. I really do.
I'll say it as many times as I need until you believe in me.
Thank you... Koharu.
Akkun... What will I do?
My apartment... burned down.
Monster Family House
The Nightmare of Living with Family who Rape my Girlfriend
~Genzo Chapter~
That won't be a problem at all.
I'm sorry I came here all out of the blue like thus.
Your neighbor is the one who fell asleep with a cigarette
There's no need for you to apologize, Koharu.
Arata, well first need to figure out
where Koharu is going to sleep.
Why not have stay here? We have plenty of available rooms.
Oh, I couldn't. I'll be okay, really.
You were living alone, right, Koharu-san?
Yes. My parents have already passed away.
That settles it then! You can't leave your lover
to fend for herself at a time like this, Arata.
Wh-What are you trying to say?
Your lover is in a pinch.
It's only natural to want to help her out.
Koharu just might be the one who will become your wife.
It's just a precautionary measure.
I-I couldn't...
Hurry up and get over here already! I've
got something good to show you!
This is incredible!
How about my nuts? Do you like my nuts?
Yes!
How about my cock? Do you like my cock too?
I love it! I couldn't go on living without your cock!
M-Mom...
Are you sure you should be saying that
so loudly? Your son might hear you!
I'm sorry, dear!
I'm a terrible mother! I'm female swine!
I can only think of your cock, Genzo-sama!
I'm nothing but female swine!
Cum now! Cum, you whore!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Now there's another flower to pick!
We don't need to hold ourselves anymore, pops!
I guess you're right.
Akkun...?
Koharu-san...
Sorry for making you do this.
Oh, it's no trouble at all. I love cleaning
and I am indebted to you.
What has Arata told you about me, Koharu-san?
Uh... Akkun didn't really talk about his family all that much...
Well... he probably hasn't said anything good about us.
No, he would never...
It's okay, I'm a terrible father.
I already had a wife and son, yet I fooled
around with Arata's mother.
I ended up getting her pregnant.
Sir...?
I'm the type of person who is never satisfied
until I get exactly what I want.
Your tits are the real deal, and you have
some nice meat on your bones there.
You also have a lovely face, and an innocent demeanor to boot!
I want to make you mine, Koharu-san!
What on earth are you doing!?
Are you going to tell Arata? That you stopped his father
from making advances on you as a woman?
Of course I will!
Oh? And how do you think telling Arata that will make him feel?
He's bound to be hurt.
That I came onto you while under the same roof.
He'll regret that he couldn't protect you.
How can you say such a thing?
Akkun is already upset about his parents, so why would you...?
He might break up with you if I show him this video.
P-Please... Don't do that!
Well then... That means you're willing to listen to my requests.
Let's skip the formalities.
You just have to let me see you naked
once without telling Arata.
That's right. Think about your future with Arata.
I'm so sorry, Akkun.
If only I had been more careful...
...then this sort of thing would never have happened.
Not bad! Are those the sort of underwear that Arata likes?
Y-Yes... Akkun likes cute underwear like this.
Take those off too and get naked.
Don't hide yourself with your hands.
I want to see all of you, Koharu.
H-He can see everything including
my breasts and down there...
Everything I have will be seen by someone other than Akkun.
That's quite a body you've got there.
So this is what Arata has been groping
and licking all by himself.
D-Don't say it like that...
Please don't talk about Akkun like that.
Let me have a look at your face.
His tongue is in my mouth, licking everything.
Stop this...
Do you enjoy perverted kisses like this with Arata as well?
A-Akkun doesn't kiss me in such an indecent manner.
Alright! Now say it just like I told you!
P-Please... daddy...
P-Please look at my dirty pussy...
...to your heart's content.
Please have a good look all the way into...
...the cock-loving pussy of a cheap cheating whore...
Ah! This can't be real! He's licking me.
The pussy of a young girl sure does taste different.
You taste sweet and a little salty, Koharu.
Wait... This...
I've gotta let Arata in on this.
That your pussy tastes rather good.
Don't! Stop! This isn't what we agreed on!
Y-You said you were only going to take a look!
I... love humiliating women, you see...
Th-This can't be happening!
Please, anything but that!
Here I go!
No! You can't stick it in!
That's a good girl! Let me do it! Let me do it!
It hurts!
Akkun.. this is all a lie.
All of it is a lie!
Somebody help me! I'm going to tear!
Akkun is the only one I love!
Oh, it's wrapping it quite nicely.
I can't get enough of this! So this is the pussy of my son's lover!
No!
I'm going to cum already.
I sure came quickly.
That Arata! I won't forgive him for hiding
such a fine woman from me!
What are you doing? I thought you were done already.
So tight!
Take that!
Please let me go!
It's all the way in!
Not all the way! Stop! Stop!
I'll fuck you all the way to your core!
I'm going to get ripped apart!
Well? You do love this right, filthy whore?
Stop! No!
Round and round we go!
Ah, man! I'm cumming!
Koharu-san, I... I...
Stop...
Stop! Stop...
We're just getting started.
Until morning... We'll be at it all night!
Damn...
I came inside of you.
How cruel...
So what? It's my cock's fault, Koharu!
I can't wait anymore! I see! More! More!
Take that! I can't get enough! You have such a slutty body!
I'm going to cum inside you again!
Your pussy sucked it out of me!
I can keep going and going...
Please let me go!
My balls and cock are demanding that I...
...rut around in the same places that that bastard has been in.
I've got a special treat for you. I'm
going to cum all over your face.
It's been quite a while since I've had such a rut!
He ended up raping me the entire night.
He kept on going and going without letting up...
Licking and fucking me... Over and over again...
He was relentless.
Your pussy is as hot as magma inside!
Oh, I'm going to make it so that you just
can't be satisfied without my cock!
There you go getting all tight on me again!
For fuck's sake...
I can't believe you want my cock so badly.
I'm raring to go again!
I'm not going to give up!
I had sex
with Daddy
Seven Times!
Shower... I need a shower...
I reek of him and his sweat...
Oh? Awake already?
A-Akkun...
What's the matter? Why are you so surprised?
I-It's nothing... I was just spacing out a little.
Are you feeling okay? A lot has happened,
so you must be exhausted.
No... Sorry to make you worry. I'm okay, really.
Okay, then... but don't push yourself too hard.
Th-Thank you for worrying about me.
Well, aren't we all friendly first thing in the morning?
This is how we always are.
U-Umm...
Arata... go fetch the newspaper for me.
My hip hurts, you see. Sorry, but could you go get it for me?
Fine...
You can't be serious...
Do I really have to pose like this?
Akkun, please...
Don't look this way. Because right now, I...
...am doing something so shameful.
Don't look at me!
I'm exposing that part of myself.
I lifted my skirt up all by myself and am showing it all to him.
From that day on, I, Koharu Hinomoto...
Became Akkun's girlfriend... as well as Daddy's woman.
I haven't taken a shower since this morning.
So this stickiness in my mouth has my taste mixed in as well?
This is all too much!
That a girl! It's about time you stopped with
just the licking and started deepthroating.
Deepthroat your penis? Yes, sir.
I can't think of anything else aside from his penis.
Hey, let me see your face.
I want to get a clear look at your cock face.
Saying I have a cock face is too cruel.
That's not right! I don't have a cock face! You've got it all wrong.
Deeper! Go deeper! Deepthroat it all the way to the hilt!
That a girl! Just like that!
How cruel! It's going in to my throat.
My mouth is full of his penis.
Oh, I'm going to cum. I'm going to cum in your mouth!
That's right, drink up!
Take all of my seed into your mouth pussy!
Drink up, Koharu!
Hey! You aren't doing what I told you to do.
I... am nothing but a dirty cock-loving whore.
Please give me your... magnificent and powerful cock!
I see, I see. You've grown to love my cock, have you?
What is this?
I don't know why, but I'm getting wet down there.
Well? Has your tit-pussy gotten you all hot and bothered?
It's gotten used to the taste of my cock.
I'm not getting any pleasure from this.
You're not Akkun. I'm doing this all for him!
Alright. I'm going to cum onto your breasts!
Take it all!
The body of a young woman sure makes a difference
in my sex drive and how much I cum!
How cruel...
It's bitter... and even if I want to spit it out
the stuff keeps seeping through my mouth completely.
Koharu said she was going shopping with some friends, but...
I wonder what she's up to right now?
You perverted maid! Beg to your master!
Master... Fuck me in my asshole...
in my ass-pussy with your cock.
I want it so bad! Please pulverize my
asshole to your heart's content!
Tearing me... It's tearing me open!
I'll stop here. Your asshole has expanded a lot. How disgraceful!
Don't look! Don't look!
Don't play coy with me! Your asshole is sucking it up!
Well? The more I pull, the harder it rubs, and
the more intense the sensation is, right?
Take it out... Please take it out!
You want me to take it out? Huh?!
You damned perverted female swine!
Don't push it in any more. Please take it out!
Your asshole is eating it all up! I'd be able to pull it
out if you would quit squeezing onto it so much!
Wow, it's so tight!
No! No!
Don't tell me you came from anal.
Your asshole opened nice and wide,
and I could see clear to the back!
You came without your master's permission.
This is part of your punishment!
I'll fuck your asshole nice and good with this cock!
Don't! If you mess with my insides...
...I'll be ruined!
This is incredibly difficult.
My legs hurt! Please hurry up and cum...
Your pussy is getting tighter and tighter.
I'll punish your pussy as well!
Don't, please!
Wow! My cock is going numb! I can't get
enough of my son's lover's asshole!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum from my ass-pussy!
You're going to cum from being ass-fucked? Cumming
like this makes you a sexual deviant, you know!
No... I...
Go ahead and cum from that lewd asshole
of yours while apologizing to Arata!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming from being fucked in the ass!
I... I'm sorry... I...
I came... from being fucked in the butt...
from being fucked in the asshole...
Your asshole is sucking in my cock!
Your asshole is tightly clamping down
on my cock. I can't pull out.
You are such a fucking pervert.
I'm... a pervert...
Don't think we're finished here. I won't
let you rest even if you already came!
I'm gonna go at you full-force!
No! Don't pound my asshole! No!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming from being fucked in the asshole!
Who would've thought your first time
doing anal would feel so good?
I'm looking forward to how you turn out.
I wonder if Koharu has come back yet...
She didn't look well this morning...
Koharu? Are you awake? It's me. Are you asleep already?
C-Coming! I'm awake, Akkun.
I'll open the door now.
Koharu...
S-Sorry! I was a bit busy just now.
I... Akkun is right here in front of me...
You look really tired, are you okay?
I-I was just doing some exercise in my room.
I'm breathing hard and I'm excited.
This can't be happening! How could
I be like this in front of Akkun?
I'm sorry for bothering you at such a late hour.
No, thank you, really.
Akkun... I love you, Akkun!
Oh no!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum right in front of Akkun!
What's the matter?
You look like you're in a lot of pain...
I'm okay! I just overdid it a little.
I'm okay, really! Don't worry about me!
Why?! How can it feel so good even
though I might be found out?!
I'm so sorry!
Alright, I'm gonna get going then.
Make sure to bundle up before you go to bed, okay, Koharu?
Just hurry up and go, Akkun! I'm...
...going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Koharu... Where are your manners?
Good night...
It felt...
...so good.
Ah, you pig!
My body feels like it's full of poison.
My body is so hot, yet it feels so good somehow.
Hey, Koharu-chan... Can I speak with you for a moment?
Yes? What is it, sir?
Koharu-chan, you sure seem to be getting
along with my pops pretty well.
Yeah, um...
My dad has a video camera in his room, so I saw it all!
I watched you getting your brains fucked out.
U-Umm... Please...
...don't tell Akkun!
If you want me to keep my mouth shut... then
shouldn't you be showing me your pussy?
Wow, are you kidding me?
Are you satisfied? This is embarrassing.
Hold up now, lower your hips some more. I know you can.
That's the spirit!
You're gonna be my fuck buddy now too, Koharu-chan.
Huh? I'm... going to get raped not only by daddy,
but by big brother as well? This can't be happening...