Ak-kun...
I... I'm okay with... doing it if it's Ak-kun...
Um... all the way...
Koharu, I'm scared.
Even if I fall in love with someone with all my
heart, I'm scared that they might betray me...
Ak-kun... It's alright.
I'll... always be beside Ak-kun.
Whatever may happen, I won't betray Ak-kun.
Koharu...
I like you, Ak-kun. I love you!
And I will keep saying that until you believe me.
Thank you.
Koharu...
Ak-kun... what do I do?
My apartment... was burned down in a fire...
KOHARU NO. 00
In a House Where Monsters Live
NTR Cohabitation with the Absolute Worst Family
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
There's no way that you are just trouble!
I'm sorry... coming here all of a sudden.
It happened because your neighbor fell asleep
smoking, it's not your fault, Koharu.
Arata, for now, we have to consider
where Koharu-san should live.
Why can't we just let here stay here?
We have tons of spare rooms.
Um, that's...
I will be okay, so...
Koharu-san, you lived alone, right?
Yes. My parents have already passed away...
With that, it's even more important,
you shouldn't leave your girlfriend
alone at times like this, Arata.
What... what are you trying to do!?
My son's lover is in trouble.
Of course I'd want to lend her a hand.
Koharu-chan could end up as the bride in our house, too.
Just think of it as a rehearsal.
That's...
Hurry and come here! I'll show you something good!
Wow, wow!
Is this it!? Is this what you love!?
Yes, yes!
Is this dick... is this dick what you love!?
I love it...
I can't live without this dick...
M-mom...
Are you sure you want to say that out loud?
Your son could hear!
I'm sorry, dear.
Mom can't take it... Mom is a bitch!
I'm a bitch that can think of nothing
but Genzou-sama's dick!
C'mon, cum! Go ahead and cum!
No, I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
With this, there will be a flower in the family, too...
Geez Dad, don't...
Ak-kun...
Koharu-san.
Sorry, even getting you to do work.
No, it's fine. I enjoy work around the house,
and besides I'll be troubling you from now on.
What have you heard about me from Arata, Koharu-san?
Uh... um, I haven't really talked about
family with Ak-kun before...
Well... it's not like he would say anything good.
No, that's...
No, no. I'm the worst as a father.
Even though I had a wife and a son, I was
in a relationship with Arata's mother...
I even made her pregnant.
Uh, father?
It seems like I am the type that can't control
myself when it comes to something I want.
Um...
A busty chest... a plump butt...
With a cute face and that pure-hearted personality!
I... want to make Koharu-san mine.
What are you doing? This...
Will you tell Arata? That his father
seeks you as a woman?
Of course...
Oh? I wonder would Arata would think after hearing that.
I'm sure he'll feel hurt.
He'll think that it was his fault
for bringing you to this house.
He'll regret that he wasn't able to protect you.
How can you say something like that!?
Ak-kun is already in pain from this family! Why!?
If I show him this video, you guys
might end up breaking up.
That's... please stop!
If that's so... you'll listen to my request too, right?
Let's avoid difficult discussions.
All you have to do is show me your naked
body once without telling Arata.
That's right. For the sake of your future with Arata, too.
Ak-kun, I'm sorry...
If I had been more careful...
It wouldn't have come to this...
Wonderful!
So, is that underwear adjusted to Arata's taste?
Yes... Ak-kun likes these cute ones, so...
Takes those off too and get naked.
Don't hide it with your hands. I have to see all of you.
I'm being watched...
My boobs, and that place... are all being
looked at by someone other than Ak-kun!
Wow, what a splendid body!
So my son had this all to himself... he
was rubbing and licking it, huh...
No like that... don't talk about Ak-kun like that.
Here, raise your head.
His tongue is coming inside... and
licking all around my mouth...
Stop already!
Are you enjoying these perverted kisses with Arata, too?
I don't... have these improper kisses... with Ak-kun...
C'mon, say what I just told you earlier.
Please, father...
Koharu's... perverted... pussy...
Please look at it lots!
The pussy of a man-loving... promiscuous...
cheating woman...
Please look closely all the way inside...
No way! You're licking me!
As expected a young woman's taste is different!
Koharu is sweet... with a little bit of salty!
No... stop... not this!
No...
Then I'll go and tell Arata,
that his woman's pussy tasted quite good!
You can't! Stop...
This is different from what you promised!
You said that you'd only be looking...
I...
I just love embarrassing women!
That's...
Please spare me from just that!
Here we go...
No...
It's going... You can't!
Good reaction of yours.
No...
It's painful...
Ak-kun... it's a lie...
– Let me go!
– This is... all a lie! So...
Help me! I'm going to break!
I... I only love Ak-kun!
Wow, so tight...
This is great.
My son's lover's pussy...
No...
I'm cumming...
I came in a blink of an eye.
That bastard of Arata... to hide
such a good woman from me...
I can't forgive him.
No way... Didn't you finish!?
Tight...
You, you...
How is it? It's all the way in!
Stop! Stop it!
Your insides are twitching, they want it!
They want to have a child!
I'll break... I'm going to break!
How is it? It's good, right? Be honest!
Someone help...
What about this?
This is bad, I'll cum...
C'mon...
I am... I am...
Stop it, stop already...
No...
Just getting started...
Until morning... all night...
Oh dear...
I came inside...
You're horrible...
What? You're still sucking on me!
I can't hold back anymore!
I see, that's how it is, more!
More!
Here... it's great!
What a slutty body!
I'm already about to cum again! Inside!
Wow... it's sucking me dry...
I can go on forever!
No!
Please let me go already!
You're still sucking so hard on me...
Do you like my dick so much!?
Are you asking me for more!?
Cumming!
Here's your reward!
I'll spray it on your face!
C'mon! I haven't been so excited in a long time!
In the end, for the entire night...
I was continuously violated.
With no time for rest at all,
I was played with... licked...
and over and over again...
I was relentlessly thrusted through.
It's so hot! This is great!
I'll make sure that you can't be satisfied
without my dick anymore!
You're clamping so tightly on me again...
Geez... I didn't think you'd want me this much...
Compared to Arata... I'm far, far...
above and beyond him!
I had sex with Father 17 times.
Shower...
I've got to... shower...
I... I smell of sweat... and Dad...
Oh, are you awake already?
Ak-kun!
What? Why are you so surprised?
It's nothing, I was pacing off a little, so...
Are you not feeling well?
A lot has happened, you must be tired.
No...
I'm sorry. It's really nothing...
If you say so...
But please don't force yourself to anything.
– Thank you for being worried about me...
– You guys are sure up early and happy.
It's just a normal morning.
Um...
Arata, please get me the newspaper.
Huh?
My hips are bugging me.
Sorry, but please.
I get it.
No way... I have to make that pose!?
Please, Ak-kun...
Don't look this way...
Right now, I...
I have to be in such an embarrassing pose...
Don't look at me!
I... I'm showing that part of me...
Lifting up my own skirt... and showing it!
From that day on, I, Hinomoto Koharu...
Became both Ak-kun's girlfriend...
And Father's woman...
I have yet to shower this morning, you see.
It must taste great.
Then there's also my taste in this sticky stuff?
That's... too perverted!
Good. It's about time you not only lick...
but also suck on it and make me feel good.
Suck on... his dick...
Yes... I understand...
I mind is going blank... from this penis...
C'mon, raise your head.
You've got to show me your dick-face.
That's such a cruel way to say it!
That's not true! I don't have a dick-face...
It's not true...
More, go in deeper!
Take it all the way to the base!
That's right, more like that!
This is horrible! It's going so deep...
My mouth is so filled by his penis!
Woah, cumming, cumming.
I'll cum in your mouth!
That's right, suck it all out.
Receive all my seed with your mouth pussy.
I came so much, Koharu.
C'mon, beg like I taught you to.
Koharu is a fellatio-loving... perverted bitch!
Please let me eat... your strong and great dick!
I see, I see.
You've started to like this... you like my dick!
What is this?
I don't know what it is... but it's making that place hot...
How is it? Is your chest-pussy getting turned on?
You've already remembered the taste of my dick, right!?
That's... there's no way I'd feel good from this...
This isn't it, Ak-kun!
This is all for you, Ak-kun...!
Cumming... I'll creampie between your breasts!
Cumming... take it all!
As expected with a young woman
I can cum more and harder.
It's amazing...
Even though it's already the second
time... there's so much...
It's trapped in my throat... with such a weird smell...
Koharu said she was going shopping with her friends...
I wonder what she's doing at the moment.
You perverted maid! Now beg to your master!
Master... Koharu's anus... ass-pussy
has been twitching for so long...
Please tease me lots!
No... It's spreading...
Let's stop it here...
Where your anus is most spread... what a slutty position!
Don't look, don't look!
Don't lie to me, just look at it sucking so hard!
– How is it? The more I tug the better
it feels rubbing inside, right?
– No... take it out, please take it out!
– How is it? The more I tug the better
it feels rubbing inside, right?
– No... take it out, please take it out!
You want me to take it out, huh?
You perverted sow!
Master... please pull it out!
It's wrapped around so tightly, I've
got to more strength to get it out.
It's really tight!
Here!
No!
No... cumming!
– No... No...
– To think you came from anal...
Your anus is wide spread, and
I can see all the way inside!
Cumming without your master's permission,
looks like you need punishment.
I'll be sure to grind your ass plenty with this.
No... If you tease me with that...
– I'll...
– Tight...
– I'll break!
– Oh, this is great.
It's tight!
– My butt... is so full...
– It's wrapping more and more tightly just like a pussy!
I'm going to punish your pussy like this, too!
No! Don't rub it inside...
Wow... it's twitching so much...
My son's lover's asshole is incredible to play with!
I'll cum...
– I'm going to cum from my butthole and my pussy!
– Are you cumming from your butt!?
You must be a pervert to do something like that!
That's not true!
I'm...
You slutty ass maid!
Cum while apologizing to Arata!
I'm cumming!
From my asshole... I'm cumming!
Ak-kun I'm sorry...
Koharu came from her butt... from her asshole...
Oh, your butt is sucking on me...
It's so tight on me I can't pull out.
What an incredible pervert.
I'm... a pervert...
C'mon, c'mon don't pace off.
I won't let you rest for a single moment, you...
Take this! Right away!
Go crazy!
No... don't thrust into my butt... No!
No way... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming from my asshole!
Cumming!
To think you'd get so used to
anal during your first time...
I'm looking forward to even more growth from you...
No...
I wonder if Koharu is back yet.
She looked like she was feeling quite bad this morning...
Koharu? Are you awake?
It's me. Have you slept already?
Coming...
Ak-kun? I'm still awake. I'll open up now.
Koharu...
Sorry... things were getting a
little hectic for me just now...
Koharu?
I... even though Ak-kun is right in front of me...
I'm being violated... in such a perverted outfit!
You seem to look like you're really exhausted...
Are you okay?
I was exercising for a bit... in my room, so...
I'm panting... and I'm getting excited...
No, not in front of Ak-kun like this! Why?
Sorry for coming to bother you at such a late time...
No, it's fine.
Thank you, Ak-kun...
I... I love you, Ak-kun!
No, I'll cum!
I'll cum in front of Ak-kun!
What's wrong?
You really look like you're in pain.
I'm okay... I'm just a bit tired...
I'm really okay! Don't worry...
Why? Even though he might find out...
It feels good! I'm sorry!
Then, I'll leave for now.
Sorry...
Take a warm bath and get some good rest, okay?
Yes...
Ak-kun, hurry and go...
I'm already... going to cum...
I'm going to cum...
Koharu, don't forget your greetings.
Good night... Ak-kun...
No... why... why was I excited...
Why did it feel so good?
Great.
It's like a poison is seeping through my body...
My body is so hot... but somehow that feels good...
Hey, Koharu-chan!
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes, Onii-san?
What is it?
Koharu-chan seems to be getting along
really well with Dad, aren't you?
Huh?
There was a video camera in my Dad's room, so...
I saw it, you see.
I saw how hard you were fucked.
Um...
Please... don't tell Ak-kun...
If you want me to keep quiet, you've
got to show some sincerity, right?
Woah, wow, really!?
Is it enough already? It's embarrassing...
No way. C'mon, lower your hips more.
You can do it, right?
That's right, that's right.
From now on, Koharu-chan will also
be my sex friend as well, ok?
Eh? Not only do I have to bear it with Father,
but also with Ak-kun's brother?
That's...