Blackmailed and violated, they continued
to rape me over and over again.
Before I even realized it...
I had become...
A slut.
Hey, it looks like your favorite movie
is airing around midnight.
Wanna watch it together in my room?
Sorry, I can't. Your brother already asked
me to do a few things for him.
Oh, I see.
I'm living here free of charge, after all.
I need to make myself useful somehow, right?
Yeah, you have a point.
It feels as if we've been growing distant, though.
It might just be me,
but it looks like you've been more interested
in my brother and father recently.
I wonder if I did something to make you hate me.
No, not at all. I...
There's no way I could ever hate you, A-kun.
Koharu...
I love you, A-kun.
Yeah, me too.
A-kun, move your tongue more!
You can be a lot rougher with me!
This is so frustrating!
Monster Family House
The Nightmare Of Living With A Family Who Rapes My Girlfriend
~Triuraph Arc~
No! I can't let myself get turned on by this!
Even though I know I shouldn't...
Shit, Koharu! Your pussy's still so tight
after having a taste of dad's cock.
My body's changing!
My body's changing into a slutty one!
Is it really okay for you to be doing this?
Aren't you my brother's girlfriend?
I can't keep doing this.
I can't keep lying to A-kun!
I need to stop doing this once and for all!
I'll fuck you so hard that you'll forget all about him!
It feels so good!
I'll make you cum with my huge cock!
No!
If you move your huge dick like that,
I'm going to get really turned on!
I'm going to cum! He's going to make me cum!
I can't! I can't!
I'm c-cumming!
I'm cumming!
Not inside!
Whew, I let out a lot.
Cumming inside is the best, isn't it, Koharu-chan?
Please, no more!
Come on, you gotta stop saying that.
How's this?
You like it here? Is that your soft spot?
Your pussy's twitching. You gonna cum?
Come on!
Not inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum inside!
No, please don't!
I'm cuming!
Wow, it's sucking me in!
Shit, I came buckets.
– Look at all that cum.
– Please, I beg you.
Let this be the last time.
I really do love A-kun.
I don't want to lie to him anymore.
Please let this be the last time!
Yeah, sure. I have one condition though.
C-Condition?
Yeah, just one.
It's so cold and slimy...
It's only cold at first.
Soon, your entire body'll be nice and warm.
What is this?
This? I swiped it from my dad.
Apparently it's a fucking strong aphrodisiac
from some foreign country.
Aphrodisiac?
All you have to do is apply it to
the sensitive spots like this...
No! It's coming inside me!
It's inside my ass, too!
If you can go a day without masturbating
or anything with this lotion on,
then I'll let you off the hook.
What's happening?!
My body's twitching! I'm starting to feel weird!
If you're gonna throw in the towel, do it now so I can see it.
Please stop! I've already decided this is it.
My nipples, pussy and ass are itching.
I want to play with them!
Koharu, are you listening? You can't masturbate at all.
You'll have to last until tomorrow night?
Is he serious?
Can I really endure this for an entire day?
I'm so horny!
My nipples and clitoris are so...
They're throbbing so hard!
I feel like I'm going to explode!
Oh, Mr. Eggplant, you look amazing!
You're looking so perverted!
A want to put it inside my pussy and my ass.
I want it to mess me up so hard!
I need to stay strong, but I just can't...
I'm already so wet!
Koharu?
Wh-What's the matter. You okay?
A-A-kun? You just startled me, that's all.
I'm okay.
But your face is red and you're breathing
pretty hard. You don't look okay at all.
Wait, if A-kun has sex with me,
that wouldn't count as masturbating, would it?
A-kun, could you come with me to my room?
I want to sleep with you!
Sleep with me?
You mean take a nap together?
No, not that. I mean...
I want to be physical with you. I want to have sex with you.
Yeah, I'm glad to hear that,
but let's wait until you feel better.
I'm fine! I'm not sick at all, so please, A-kun!
If we don't do it now, I...
Koharu? Right now her face reminds me of...
Fuck me! Please fuck me harder!
Your dick feels so good!
You fucking slut!
Your son's watching.
How does that make you feel?
That's fine. I don't care.
Just fuck me harder!
Guess that's that. Take this!
Please cum in this failure-of-a-parent's pussy!
You really are acting weird, Koharu!
You have a fever.
Let's just lie down for a little, okay?
Y-You're so mean, A-kun!
I practically begged you to have sex with me.
Why aren't you doing anything?
What's going on?
Yo, Arata.
I drilled a hole between our walls.
Try looking through it tonight.
You might see the best thing ever.
Best thing?
I had a bad feeling. My mind was going crazy.
Even so, I went to the hole...
And looked into it.
A-kun, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
This is as far as I can go. I...
So, what's your answer?
Please, I beg you. Let me cum!
I can't hold on anymore!
Please! I'll let you fuck me anytime and
anywhere you want, just like a sex doll!
Do me! Fuck me! Make me cum!
Th-This can't be happening!
I'm nothing but a slut!
I'm nothing but a sex toy!
Please make me cum! Make me cum!
Please, I'll do anything. Just make me cum!
Okay then, I'll take you up on that.
I want to be fucked so hard by your cock!
My pussy, my mouth, every part of
me is your personal cum dumpster!
Well, since you've been such a good
girl, I'll give you your reward.
Please paint this dirty girl's face white with your semen!
Here I go. I'm cumming!
Wow, there's so much!
Today's your sexniversary. Smile more!
Yes...
Today's my sexniversary!
My cum's been building up.
We're going all out tonight!
All out?
Shit yeah, you're already dripping wet!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
You shittin' me? I only just put it in.
Well then, I guess I'll just keep going.
Take this!
– I'm still cumming! No, don't! No, please stop!
– You're clampin' onto me!
Do you love cocks that much?
I do! I love cocks!
They're so thick and strong!
I love the thing that's hitting me so deep inside!
Hey, how 'bout you twerk those hips, slut?
I will! It's embarrassing, but I'll thrust my hips!
You're going in so deep! You're touching my womb!
We're in the embarrassing baby-peeing pose.
Ain't this your favorite?
It is! It feels so good!
I'm getting so turned on!
If you're gonna cum, apologize to your boyfriend.
You don't want him to have any hard feelings.
Yes! I'll do it!
A-kun, I'm so sorry!
I can't be your woman.
I can't live without your brother's big, hard dick anymore!
I really can't!
So you're finally being honest with yourself?!
I'm about to cum!
Cum! Cum inside me!
Oh yeah!
You're sucking me in!
This can't be happening...
Fuck yeah! I'm gonna fuck you like the animal you are!
I can't believe I've turned into such a slut!
A-kun doesn't know about this.
I want to be even more of a slut!
– Turn me into an even bigger slut!
– I'm gonna cum again! Take all of it inside your womb!
Cum inside me! I'm going to cum too!
I'm cumming!
– Fuck, you're so tight!
– It's coming inside me!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Koharu? Koharu?!
How's this? Take this!
It feels so good!
No, I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum again!
He's gonna cum inside me!
I'm cumming! I'm still cumming! I can't...
Oh, no! Something big's coming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
Where did I go wrong?
What could I have done to prevent this?
I don't know. I can't think of anything!
You went after a girl I trained?
You'll never grow out of your bad habits.
If a hot girl's living in the same house as me,
how can I not go after her?
Koharu's my woman.
It's fine if you're her warm-up.
Anymore than that? Fuck off.
Hey, what the fuck? That's not fair.
I love slutty girls, too!
I have the right to make her my woman too!
Let's stop fighting.
If possible could we, um...
Have a threesome?
Fuck, I only get the mouth?
It's only fair. She was mine first.
Fine! I'll use her pussy the next round,
and the round after that.
You're incorrigible.
Koharu likes mine more anyway.
You're not rough enough. She doesn't like that at all.
That's what I should be saying. Right, Koharu?
Looks like the only way to settle this is to ask her directly.
So it's gonna be that kinda tight? I ain't gonna lose.
What do you think, Koharu?
Both dicks are amazing. They hit different
spots, but they're both really great!
Were hoping for a more specific
answer on how they're different.
Your dick goes deeper,
spreads me wider and gets me wetter.
What about me? What about mine?
Your dick makes my body go crazy
and is definitely more rough!
Koharu definitely has a talent for sex, doesn't she?
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
M-Me too!
I'm gonna give you a present for cumming.
Give it to me! Give it to me!
Both of you, put your dicks in me!
Let's have make-up sex!
Fuck, you're sexy! How does having
two cocks inside you feel?
I love having them inside me!
They're working me hard, like pistons!
You love kissing when you're getting fucked, don't you?
I do! I love this dirty kissing!
I'm going to make you cum!
No! I'm gonna cum!
I'm really going to cum! You masochistic slut!
Here we go! We're gonna cum inside at the same time!
Do it! Cum inside at the same time!
I'm cumming!
Oh, no! It's coming out!
It's going deep down your throat!
Fucking masochistic slut! You love this, don't you?
My nipples are getting so hard!
It's going deep down my throat!
It's hitting the back of my throat!
You're just a masochistic bitch. That's
not how you should be speaking.
You fucking anal lover.
It's going so deep!
Now I have to punish you by shoving
this all the way down your throat!
Your dicks are going so deep in my ass and throat!
Please punish me more with your cock!
Spray your punishment inside me!
Drink it up!
Okay, pose for the camera.
That's good. That'll make a good picture!
Two dicks at once? You're amazing Koharu-chan.
You're a man-pleasing machine.
You're sucking me so hard!
Koharu-chan, do me too! Quick!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
Now for the finishing touch.
Let's go out with a bang!
Take this!
This can't... this can't be...
Arata?
We don't need you in this house anymore.
Get out.
Yeah, it's annoying to see your depressed face around here.
Just leave Koharu and get the fuck out.
A-kun, I'm sorry.
Koharu?
Koharu, you tell him too.
Yes...
I've become this house's communal pussy.
I can't live without their dicks anymore!
From now on, we'll be fucking you day and night.
Koharu won't be able to enjoy herself with
you around. You're just in the way!
I don't want to hear this. I don't want to hear this!
Sorry, A-kun.
I'm their woman now,
so I can't be your girlfriend anymore.
So...
Leave this house.
So as thanks to everyone, I have prepared
a small offering for this celebration.
Just hurry the fuck up!
I can't wait any longer!
Is that so? Okay then...
Today's party is for my dirty pussy.
Everyone, please have a blast!
This is a bit embarrassing, but I'll do my best!
What a cute girl!
They're turning me into a performance.
They're taking pictures of me like this! No!
My pussy is being stared at!
It's so embarrassing!
Come on, spread your pussy wide open!
I wanna see all the way inside!
Okay!
I'll show you everything!
Please look at my exposed pussy!
Koharu, you want this?
I do! I want your cock!
Plunge your cock into my perverted
pussy in front of everyone!
You're even wetter than usual!
You getting turned on?
There are so many people here watching me get fucked.
Why am I getting so turned on?
I'm such a perverted woman!
Please watch more of me!
Watch this embarrassing scene!
There are so many cocks. I'm so happy!
Show me how perverted you can get!
Please use me to masturbate!
We're going to have to punish you
for being such a fucking slut.
This is amazing!
Everyone please look at my perverted face! Look at me!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
My nipples! Not like that!
How about here?
I'm cumming!
Oh, no! I'm gonna cum from this! I'm gonna cum!
Oh crap!
I can't hold back anymore!
No!
Look at her go!
She's so fucking hot!
I'm cumming!
No!
It's coming out!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna break. I'm going crazy!
No! Oh, no!
I'm cumming!
It's overflowing.
Your dicks are rubbing against each
other inside my slutty body!
Your cocks are going so deep inside me!
It feels so good! I'm such a slut!
I'm sorry for having such a dirty body!
Thank you for taking such good care of me!
I'm so glad to have all these beautiful cocks to myself!
They're rubbing against me deep inside!
So good! My tits are gonna cum! They're
gonna cum because of your cocks!
I can't see Koharu anymore.
After being kicked out of their house,
I moved into a small apartment.
There, I lived a reclusive life.
A-kun, are you watching?
Koharu No. 09
I haven't seen Koharu since I left.
I can't live without this anymore!
Please fuck me harder with your cocks!
I could only see her in these DVDs.
I have so much sex with your brother and father!
I love it! I'm so happy!
Even now, I'm sure they're still fucking her...
Inside that house of animals.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hyakupercent | punk4real