Ak-kun...
I-if it's with Ak-kun then...
I'm fine with doing it.
I mean... until the end...
Koharu, I'm scared.
That even if I seriously fall in love with someone.
I'll be betrayed by them again.
Ak-kun...
It's alright.
I'll always be by your side.
No matter what happens, I'll never betray you.
K-Koharu.
I love you, Ak-kun, I really love you!
I can say it as many times as you want until you believe me.
Thank you... Koharu.
Ak-kun... what should I do?
My apartment... got burnt down...
You're not being a bother at all!
I'm sorry, coming over so suddenly.
It's because the room next to yours
caught fire... you didn't do anything wrong.
Arata, for the time being we have to think
of a place where Koharu-san can stay.
She can just stay over at our place,
we've got plenty of rooms anyway.
U-umm I couldn't do that! I'll be fine by myself.
Koharu-san, you live alone don't you?
Yes...
My parents are no longer around so...
Then all the more reason!
You can't let your lover live alone in times like these, Arata.
W-what do you mean!!
The lover of my son is in trouble.
Of course I would want to lend you a helping hand.
Koharu-chan might become our family member after all,
It'd be just like a rehearsal.
T-That's a little...
Hurry up and come over here, I'll let you see something amazing!
Awesome, Awesome!!
Is this it? Is this what you love?
Yes! YESSSSSS!!!
This dick! Do you love this dick?!
I-I love it! Sacchin can't live without this dick!!
M-Mom!
Are you sure you wanna say it out so
loud? Your son might hear it you know?
Forgive me Arata. Y-Your mother is a no good! She's a pig!!
She's a pig who can't think about
anything else but Ginchou-sama's dick!!!
Here, Cum!! CUM!!!
Oh no! I'm cumming! I'M CUMMING!! I'M CUMMIIIINNNG!!!!
Now we'll have a flower in our family.
That's right, your wish for a daughter will be granted now, huh, pops.
That's right...
Ak-kun?
Koharu-san?
I'm really sorry, making you do this much for us.
No no. I love housework, besides, you're doing me a favor as well.
What have you heard about me from Arata?
U-u-umm... Ak-kun didn't really talk about his family much so...
Well, there's no way he would've said
something good about me anyway.
N-No, that's not...
No, no, I am the worst kind of father you know.
Even though I already had a wife and
son, I thought about Arata's mother.
I even got her pregnant.
Father?
After all, I'm the type of guy who can't sit still
until he gets his hands on what'he wants.
U-Umm...
Even though you're a bit plump, you've got a
good ass, a cute face, and a great personality.
I want to make Koharu-san my own.
What are you doing?
Will you tell Arata? That you did something like this with his father?
Of course I will.
Oh? What will Arata think after hearing that I wonder?
He would be hurt for sure.
Knowing that you were forced to do something
like this with his own father in his own house?
He would be frustrated that he couldn't protect you.
Why are you saying something like that?!
Even though Ak-kun is already suffering a
lot from the death of his parents, why?!!
If he sees this video, then you guys just might break up.
N-No way... Please don't do that!
In that case you'll have to listen to what I will say.
Lets' not make this too difficult to understand, ok?
You just have to show yourself naked to me
once while keeping it a secret from Arata.
Yes... for the sake of your future as well.
Ak-kun forgive me...
If only I were more careful...
It wouldn't have ended like this.
OH! Splendid!
So, is that underwear Arata's fetish?
Y-Yes... Because Ak-kun loves these sort of cute ones.
Take that off as well and stand naked.
Don't hide anything, I want to see Miharu's everything!
He's going to see everything!
My boobs and that place as well.
All of it is going to be seen by someone other than Ak-kun!
You have quite the body, don't you.
Arata's been keeping this amazing body
to himself, groping and licking it all over.
T-That's not...
Please stop talking about Ak-kun!
Here, show me your face.
His tongue is coming in... and licking all over the insides of my mouth!
Please stop!!
Do you enjoy doing perverted stuff like this with Arata as well?
Ak-kun and I have never done a disgusting kiss like this.
Come on! Do it like I told you to do.
Please, Father...
L-Look at... K-Koharu's perverted pussy... lots and lots!
T-The pussy... of a cheating woman whose pussy craves and
loves men... deep inside... Please look to your heart's content!!
No way! He's licking me!
As I thought the pussy of a young girl sure is different.
Koharu's taste is sweet and a little sour.
P-Please don't! No wayyy!!
No, that place is!!
That's why let me teach you, that
your pussy has a pretty good taste!
Don't!! Don't...! That's not the what you
promised! Y-You said you'd only look!
I...
Love seeing the embarrassed look of women... you see!
N-No way!!
Please anything but this!
Here I come!
Don't...! Don't put it INNN!!!
What a good reaction.
Dooon't!!
It hurts!
Ak-kun... It's a lie... This is all a lie!!
Help me!! I'm gonna break!!
I only love Ak-kun so...
Now, just squeeze!
I can't stop! The pussy of my son's lover!
Dooon't!!
I'm cumming!
I came so quickly.
Arata that bastard! Hiding a girl like this from me, I can't forgive that!
No-No way! Weren't we done?!!
You! You!!
No!! Forgive me...
How's it? It's reaching all the way to the back?!
No! Don't do this! Don't do thiiisss!!
Your pussy's twitching so much! It wants me. It wants this dick!
I'll break... I'll break!!!
How's this! Its good isn't iiit?!!
Here! Here!
Don't! Dooon't!!
How about this?
No good! I'm cummmg!
Come on now! I'm... I'm...
Stop this! Please just stop this! Stop!
Come on, we're just getting started!
I'll fuck you 'till morning!
Darn it! I came inside!
Y-you're horrible!
Oh what? It's nothing to worry about!!
I can't hold it in anymore! Thats right! Thats right! More! More!!
There! I can't stop! Why do you have such a perverted
body! If this keeps up then I'll cum inside again!
My bad, I got too into it!
I can do anything!
Please forgive me already!!
Talking non-stop like that! Did you really like my dick that much!!
Is that how you ask of a request from someone?!
Here's a present for you! I'll be sure to hit it right on your face!!
It's been a while since I've been this fired up!!
In the end I continued to get raped all night.
Without getting even a little bit of rest...
I got teased and licked over and over!!
I was just forced to take it.
Your pussy feels so hot, like magma!!
I won't let you rest until I'm completely satisfied!!!
Really, making me get so fired up!
Really, to think you made me give you this much!
I'm still far away from Arata though...
I won't lose!
I had sex 7 times with Father.
Shower... I have to take a shower...
I smell of sweat and Father all over.
Oh? You woke up already?
A-Ak-kun?!!
What is it? Getting so surprised.
I-It's nothing. I was just spaced out.
Are you sure you're not feeling sick? You
must be tired because of a lot of things.
I'm sorry, it's really nothing.
Well it's fine then.
Don't push yourself too hard okay?
– T-Thank you for worrying about me...
– You're getting along so early in the morning aren't you?
– T-Thank you for worrying about me.
It's just normal.
U-Umm...
Arata, go get me the newspaper.
HUH?!
My back hurt you see. I'm sorry, but could you please?
I get it, already.
No way! Do I have to make that pose, no matter what?
P-Please Ak-kun... Don't look this way...
Right now... I...
T-This... This embarrassing pose!
Please don't look at me!
I'm sticking that place out.
I'm letting him see everything by pulling my skirt up myself.
After that day I... Hinomoto Koharu...
Became Ak-kun's girlfriend and...
Father's woman.
I haven't even had a shower yet.
I must smell quite a bit.
Then my taste is also mixed up in this sticky thing?
That is way too lewd.
That's good... Now stop just licking and
make me feel good by swallowing my dick.
Swallow your dick...? OK, I understand.
I can't think about anything anymore, because of this dick!
Here, show me your face.
I want to get a clear view of that hole-for-dicks of yours.
To call it a hole-for-dicks is way too cruel.
That's wrong, I'm not a hole-for-dicks, I'm not!
More! Do it harder! Swallow all of it to the base.
That's right! Just like that.
So... So cruel... He's pushing it down in my throat even
though my mouth is already filled with his dick!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I'm cumming inside your mouth!
That's right! Swallow all of it!
Accept my seed in your mouth pussy!!
That was splendid Koharu!
Come on! Beg like I told you to!
Koharu is Father's favorite dick pig!
Please let me... have more of your huge, sturdy dick!
I see, I see. So you've come to love this dick of mine, huh?
Ahh! W-what's this? What's happening? I don't
really get it but that place feels really strange.
How's this! Is your boob-pussy getting excited? You
already remember the taste of my dick don't you?
Th-There's no way I'm feelng good from something like this.
Ak-kun it's not what it looks like! This is all for Ak-kun's sake!!
I'll let it all out between your breasts ok?
I'm cumming! Accept all of it!!
As I thought, it feels really different when
you let it out on the body of a young woman.
It's so horrible... Even though you already
came once, cumming this much again!!
But still why...? It has such a strange taste...
Koharu, she said that she was going shopping with her friends but...
I wonder what she's doing right now.
You perverted maid! Beg from your master!!
M-Master... This ass... This ass pussy is twitching and is really horny!
Please tease it... Tease it a lot!!
No! I don't need it!!
Try to stop me like this! This unsightly thing
that I'm doing to our asshole right now!
– Don't watch! Please don't watch!!
– Don't lie!!
It's getting so damn excited!
How's this!? The more I move it the more you
feel good that you can't help but crave it?
Take it out! Please take it out!!
You want me to take this out?!
HUH?!!
You perverted female pig!!
Please take that out of my butt!!
I can't take it out if you're holding on to it so tight, can I?
Oh, it's really tight!
– No! Noooo!!
You came from your ass? Your asshole
is so open that you can see really deep!
To think that you disobeyed your
master, this calls for a punishment, right?
With this I'll put your asshole back in place...
Dooon't... Please don't tease me anymore!
I'll go crazzy!!!
This is something! Damn!!
There's so much... inside!!
Your pussy is squeezing my dick so hard!!
I'll also let your pussy have some while I'm at it!
Please don't move it around so much!!
Amazing! It feels like it's shocking me! The
asshole of my son's lover is amazing! I can't stop!!
Nooo! I'm gonna cum from my ass and pussy!!
So you're cumming from your ass? Someone who
cums in a situation like this is a pervert you know?
NO!... I'm not a pervert...
You shameless asshole maid, go and apologize to Arata!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum... F-from my asshooole!!!
Fo-Forgive me...
Ak-kun I came from my asshole... Forgive me...
Your insides are squeezing so hard!
It's holding it so tight that I can't set
free. Really, you're one hell of a pervert!
I... Came so much.
Here, here! Don't get tired on me now!
I won't let you rest just now! You! You! We're going again!
Don't! Please let my ass rest!
I can't take it anymore! I'm cumming!
I can't take in that much! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cummiiiinnnng!!!
To have gotten this excited with your hot ass... I'm
looking forward to your growth from here on out.
I wonder if Koharu's back yet.
She didn't look too good this morning...
Koharu? Are you awake? It's me. Did you fall asleep already?
Y-Yes...
Ak-kun, I'm awake... I'll open it now.
Koharu?
I'm sorry... I'm feeling a bit off right now.
E-Even though I'm right in front of Ak-kun...
I-In such a perverted outfit... I'm being raped!!
You seem to be moving a lot for some reason.
I-I was just doing a l-little exercise in my room so...
I'm still a bit shaky...
I'm getting excited...!
No! In front of Ak-kun like this, why?!
I'm sorry, disturbing you at this time.
No, thank you! Ak-kun... I really love you!!
No! I'll cum! I'll cum in front of Ak-kun!!
What happened? You seem to be in pain...
I-Its alright! I just worked up a sweat so.
I'm completely fine so, don't worry okay?
Why?! Even though I might be found out,
why do I feel so good? Please forgive meeee!!
Well then I'll be going now.
I'm really sorr...
Try to keep yourself warm, ok?
Ak-kun hurry up and go away...
Cause I'm already... gonna cum! I'll cuuuuuummm!!!
Koharu, what happened to the farewell?
Good night... Ak-kun!!
A-Amazing!!... I did it...! I came!!
Why did it feel so good!!
Smile!!
It's like some poison is spreading through my body.
My body is so hot but somehow it feels good.
Yo! Koharu-chan!
Do you have a minute?
Yes... onii-san.
What's the matter?
Koharu-chan, you're getting along really well with father, aren't you?
Y-Yes uhh...
There is a video camera in father's room so I saw it you see?
Koharu-chan getting fucked all over.
U-Umm...
I... I beg of you, p-please don't tell Ak-kun about this.
If you want me keep my mouth closed.
Don't you think you'll have to pay the proper price for it?
Amazing, are you serious?!
Are you done yet? It's embarrassing.
No, no... lower your hips more, you can do that can't you?
Yeah... Just like that.
From now on Koharu-chan will be serving me too okay?
Huh?! Not just by Father...
But will also be raped by Onii-san?!
No way!