My body...
which has been threatened and forcibly raped,
eventually became completely lewd,
without me... ever noticing it.
Oh, that movie you liked is going to be aired tonight on TV.
Want to watch it together at my room?
I'm sorry, Ak-kun.
I've been asked by onii-san to do a few errands this evening.
Is that so?
They're letting me stay here for free, anyway.
I have to at least be of some use to father and onii-san.
Okay?
Well, that's right,
but it's just that we haven't been getting along well as of late.
Maybe it's just me though,
but you seem to be a bit too fixated
on your brother and parents.
Maybe... you're starting to hate me now.
I would never feel that way toward you!
There's absolutely no reason for me to hate you!
Koharu.
I love you, Ak-kun.
Yeah, me too.
Ak-kun... move your lips more.
I would've wanted him to be more forceful to me.
This is really frustrating!
Monster Family House
~Shou Chaprer~ The Nightmare of Living with Family who Rape my Girlfriend
N-No...
I mustn't feel aroused with this!
I don't like this and yet.
This is good, Koharu-chan.
Your pussy is squeezing me tight, just as I raised it to be.
I'm being changed.
My body's become lewder!
Oh wow.
But I wonder if your boyfriend would actually allow
me, the brother to do something like this.
We really can't do this.
I mustn't betray Ak-kun anymore like this.
I have to put an end to this.
I'm going to make you feel so good that you'll forget about him!
Oh yes.
Here, let me make you cum with my giant dick.
I'm going to get horny if you keep pushing it hard like that!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
Don't... don't!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
It's about to come out!
I came pretty well.
Cumming inside is the best, don't you agree, Koharu-chan?
I beg of you!
Please don't thrust it deepl...
There you go again.
You may say that,
but look, how's this?
I'm still going to cum, so don't you dare talk to me like that!
Aren't you actually about to cum with
your pussy twitching like this, eh?
Here, here!
No, not there!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum inside again.
Please stop already!
It's over.
Amazing.
It's sucking me in.
I came quite a lot.
Really, a lot.
Please.
Let me go this time already.
What?
I really love Ak-kun,
I don't want to lie to him any longer.
Let's end this here now.
Got no prob with that, but on one condition.
C-Condition?
Yup, a condition.
It feels cold.
And it feels slimy.
It's only cold at the beginning.
You're going to start feeling real hot soon.
What is this?
Oh? This you see.
Took it right out of pops' place.
Look, it says it's an imported extra-strength aphrodisiac lotion.
A-Aphrodisiac?
You apply it to sensitive places like these.
It's going inside me!
It's seeping into my ass as well.
You're going to spend the entire day tomorrow
with this lotion rubbed on you.
I'll then forgive you if you can hold on for
the entire day without masturbating.
What is this?
My body feels really hot.
I'm going crazy with it.
Give up now, and I can still give you a really good time.
Please rub it on me.
I've already decided that this is too far already.
My nipples are feeling all tingly,
both my ass and my pussy too!
I want to play with it, I want to play with it!
Koharu-chan, are you listening?
Don't forget, no masturbating for the entire day tomorrow.
N-No way.
Can I really hold on in this state?
I'm itching for it.
My nipples... my clit.
It feels so tingly!
I'm going to cum!
The eggplant... looks amazing.
L-Looks indecent.
I want to put it in.
I want it in both my ass and pussy.
I want to stir this thing inside me.
I-I've got to hold on... and yet.
And yet, I'm so wet down there already.
Koharu?
Wh-What's wrong?
Are you all right?
A-Ak-kun!
Well, it's just.
It's just that you surprised me.
I'm okay.
But, you seem to have a pained expression,
and you're breathing heavily too.
That's not really something that looks okay.
That's right.
If I get Ak-kun to do me, it won't be counted as masturbating.
Ak-kun, can you please come with me to my room right now?
I want to lay down with you!
L-Lay down with me.
You want to sleep together?
Th-That's not what I meant!
Not that, but well.
I want you to do me.
I want you to have sex with me.
I'm happy that you said that,
but I want to do it when you're feeling better.
I'm really fine!
It's not that I'm sick or anything.
Please, if you don't do it right now, I'll!
Koharu?
Her expression, it's as if...
Do it, I beg of you!
Do it more to me!
Your dick just feels too good!
Your slutty bitch!
Your son is peeping at you right over
there, are you okay with that?
It's alright.
I don't care, just keep on fucking me deeply!
Jeez, can't be helped then.
Here, have some more!
Fill me up with my own parent's love juice!
You're really acting weird, Koharu!
Maybe you have a fever or something.
Anyway, why don't you take a break?
Okay?
Y-You're so terrible, Ak-kun.
I'm already desperately asking you to do it with me.
And yet why do you insist on that?
I wonder what that is.
Hey there, Arata.
I drilled a little hole in your room.
Try to peek sometime during the night.
You're going to see something that's definitely interesting.
Definitely interesting?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
It's really bothering me.
But then I inevitably.
Peeked inside.
Ak-kun.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
I can't hold on anymore.
Well? Have you decided already?
Please.
Please make me cum.
I can't... hold on anymore!
I'll do anything.
I can get my pussy as slutty as you want it to be.
So fuck me, rape me!
Make me cum!
Th-This can't be.
This is it.
I think it was right after all to have given in.
So please, I beg of you.
Mess me up, make a complete mess out of me!
I want you to cover me with your cum, make me feel amazing!
Give me all your cum!
I'll go ahead, then.
Please totally rape me with your giant dick!
Make me into your personal cum dumpster.
I don't care if you pump it in my mouth or pussy!
You're amazing today, Koharu-chan!
Looks like I'll have to properly reward our good girl here.
Please give it to me!
Squirt all of your cum onto this slut, onii-san!
I'm cumming, it's coming out!
Oh wow.
You came lots.
Today's the day to remember your body.
Try to smile a bit more.
Yes.
I'm... celebrating my body today.
I've got it quite built up too,
so I'm getting real serious tonight.
Getting real serious?
Amazing,
I just put it in, and it's already so wet.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
For real?
We just barely started.
Then I'm going to tease you a bit more.
Here, have some more!
I'm still cumming.
– No, please stop... don't!
– You're really not letting my dick go.
Do you love cocks now, Koharu-chan?
I do!
I love dicks!
It's thick, and it feels good!
And this thick thing is penetrating me really deeply!
Hey, slutty bitch, try moving your hips more.
I'm doing it!
I feel embarrassed with my ass, but I'm still doing it!
It's going deep, it's going deep!
Look, your position is like a child taking a pee.
You like this kind of embarrassing stuff, right?
I love it!
It feels good, I'm getting really horny!
You need to ask forgiveness from your
BF before he ever finds out himself.
He might get weirder ideas and lash it out on me!
Yes, I will!
Please listen! Ak-kun, I'm really sorry!
I just can't have yours anymore.
Because I can't accept anything else but onii-san's!
I can't be satisfied by anything else!
Yeah, that's right!
You've finally become completely honest with yourself.
I'm about to cum right now, though.
Cum.
Cum inside me!
Oh wow.
It's sucking it all in.
This can't be.
This is just.
You really came like a wild animal earlier, eh.
You know that I never really knew,
that I'm actually this much of a slut!
I want to be more slutty!
– I want to become more slutty!
– I'm going to cum inside again!
Take every single drop of it!
Cum, please cum inside me!
I'm going to cum, I'm about to cum again with it!
I'm cumming!
– It's squeezing me really tight!
– Amazing!
It's pumping... flowing inside me!
I'm going to get pregnant.
Koharu... Koharu!
Here, have some more!
So intense! This feels too intense!
No, please no.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming again.
I'm going to cum hard again!
I'm already cumming... and yet,
I'm about to cum again!
Oh no... something really big's coming out!
I'm cumming again!
What went wrong?
What should I have done to keep her with me?
I don't know.
I don't know a single thing.
Good grief, I never thought you'd lay your hands
on the woman I'm currently taming.
I really can't lower my guard down to your tendencies.
If I'm living with this erotic bitch, then of course
I won't be able to resist doing her.
Koharu is my woman.
I can let you nibble a bit here and there,
but I demand you cease doing any more than that!
Hey, hey, you can't say that to me, pops!
I'm quite fond of this bitch too!
I have the right to make her my woman too, you know!
Umm...
Please stop fighting.
If possible, well...
The three of us can get along well.
Damn!
I only get a blowjob?
Don't say that.
Anyway, I'll still take the first fuck.
I'll accept if I can do her twice after you do!
What a helpless chap you are.
Because it'd actually be better for her, right, Koharu?
You always do it too roughly.
Why don't you try to be the one holding her instead?
I could very well say the same to you, right, Koharu?
If it comes to this then we'll just have to
see who can "grab" her more firmly.
A contest between men, eh.
I'm not gonna lose!
How's this, Koharu?
Your dick feels more slender than his, but
it hits different spots so it also feels great.
I'd like you to describe it to me more in detail.
Dad's dick when it hits me deeply...
it just feels so different!
How about me? How about mine?
Onii-san's dick feels far better when it fucks intensely.
Koharu, you really do have a talent for sex.
I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum as well!
I'm going to cum on your cumming face, Koharu!
Cum, just cum!
Please do it.
Put it inside my pussy as well.
Let's all get along together and have sex!
That's good, you look really erotic.
You're gonna taste my casual dick this time.
Oh wow, it really hits me hard.
It's pushing in and out like a hot piston!
You love doing this while getting fucked, right?
I love being kissed while fucking.
Then cum, you bitch!
No, don't!
I'm really going to cum!
You really are a perverted masochistic bitch.
Here I go, get ready to be cummed inside both ways!
Please, cum inside me on both sides!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
It's going to come out!
I'm penetrating your throat already.
No!
You masochistic pig!
You also love doing this, right?
Oh no!
It's getting distorted.
Please forgive this sex swine for being such a slut.
Once you become my woman, you don't
just hang around freely anymore.
You even became this ape's sex partner!
You ass fucking-loving slut!
I'm very sorry!
This is punishment from deep within your throat!
Just cum. Please cum deep inside my throat!
Dad, you too, please cum inside me!
Please pump me with all of your "punishment" inside my pussy!
Take it all!
Alright, Koharu-chan, do a peace sign.
That's good, we're taking really nice pics out of these.
That's amazing, Koharu-chan.
Sucking two dicks at once.
You're truly built to be a sex vessel by men.
Whoa, you're sucking quite hard.
Koharu-chan, do it here too, quickly!
I-I'm cumming!
I think I can still cum.
Now for the last course.
We're going to squirt it all on you!
I'm cumming!
This...
This can't be.
Arata.
We no longer need you in this household anymore.
Go out.
Pop's right.
It just pisses me off to see that annoying face of yours.
Just leave Koharu here.
Ak-kun... I'm really sorry.
Koharu!
Koharu, please tell this man off as well.
Okay.
I'm...
I'm now the personal pussy of this household!
I can't get away from onii-san and Dad's dicks anymore.
We're going to have sex all day long, regardless
of whether it's day or night.
Koharu can't really enjoy herself well if you're around.
You're nothing but a nuisance.
I don't want to hear this...
I don't want to hear this!
I'm sorry, Ak-kun.
I'm completely theirs now.
I can't become your girlfriend anymore.
That's why.
Leave this household already.
Everyone, I, Genzou, would now like to present
to everyone who works hard during the day,
a humble form of entertainment to which this banquet shall...
Just get on with it already!
I can't hold on any longer!
Is that so? Well then...
Everyone!
You are all about to celebrate my slutty pussy's party.
Please enjoy the banquet!
I'm dying right now from embarrassment,
I'll do my best!
This cute girl is actually.
I'm being watched and having my picture taken by everyone.
They're all taking pictures of my very shameful self!
Oh no.
Everyone's ogling at my pussy.
This is really embarrassing!
Hey, open up your pussy more!
Let's see its insides!
I understand.
I'll show it.
I'm... going to completely open it!
Please look carefully at my completely exposed pussy.
Please look!
Hey, Koharu, do you want this?
Do you?!
I want it!
I want your dick, onii-san!
Put it inside my slutty pussy!
Fuck me in front of everyone!
Here we go!
You're a lot wetter than usual.
Are you getting horny?
I'm doing something bad, and yet this
masochist slut is getting really horny!
I'm a completely lewd bitch!
Please look!
I want everyone to watch closely how.
I shamefully have sex like this!
Dicks, dicks everywhere.
I'm getting so horny.
Show more of your slutty self!
Please enjoy all of my embarrassing spots.
Now we have to really punish this perverted slutty cow.
This is just amazing.
Everyone, please watch.
Watch my slutty face's stupefied expression!
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum!
I'm going to cum already.
No, not my nipples!
Don't push it like that, please.
How's this, then?
Oh, I'll go for this spot, then.
I'm going all out.
No... please not there.
I-It's going to come out.
I'm about to cum!
I can't hold it in anymore!
No, stop...
It really feels like she's squeezing me.
This is going to feel really good when I cum!
No!
It's really coming out!
I'm going crazy.
Everything in me.
No, no, please...
I'm cumming!
Its rubbing.
These dicks are all rubbing inside my bloated pussy and ass.
These two incestuous dicks are fucking me hard!
These two hard and stiff dicks.
Mom, I'm a real pervert!
I'm sorry for being such a dick-loving cunt.
Thank you... for giving birth to me this way.
I can really enjoy these wonderful dicks this way.
It's coming out.
I'm about to lactate.
My nipple dicks are about to cum!
I can no longer meet Koharu.
After getting kicked out of that household,
I've been living my days inside the room of
a small apartment... in complete silence.
Ak-kun, are you watching?
The only way I could meet her,..
Ak-kun, I can no longer...
– ...is by watching the life that she's living on that household,..
– ...have sex with you.
– I'm always filled with dicks in this home.
– ...inside these DVDs.
Both Dad and onii-sama are giving me lots of sex.
Making me really, really happy!
I'm sure... that she's being raped in that
household right at this moment.
That...
That house where all the beasts reside.