I returned to Japan after 10 years.
I was shocked by the change
I saw in Ryouichi.
It was the result of injuries
sustained in a childhood accident.
Brain damage affected
Ryouichi's motor skills.
He became an easy target
for school bullies.
The accident was my fault.
To take responsibility for what happened,
I agreed to do anything he wanted.
I soon found out that...
the accident did not affect
his sexual endurance.
Having sex made him confident...
and he vowed to get revenge
on the women that taunted him...
by raping them one by one.
I agreed to help him get revenge...
to make up for my sins...
and for love.
Keraku no Oh: King of Pleasure
Episode 3
Hot, it's hot Ryouichi!
Shut up, you're my fucking slave!
I've noticed that you've started
to talk back to me recently.
I just think...
that what you're doing isn't right.
Please stop!
I don't care if it's right or wrong.
I just want to teach those
fucking snobby bitches...
a lesson with my huge cock.
That's all I want.
But...
And you, my mouthy slave,
are in need of a lesson.
Wait, Ryouichi!
Stop, please stop!
Your punishment!
It burns!
Please stop it!
No!
I think you're enjoying this.
I don't!
Just suck on this!
I thought you were supposed to
do everything I tell you?
To make up for what you did.
This is all my fault!
I was the one that caused the accident!
I'm responsible for making him into
the horrible monster he is today.
I have to follow him...
even to hell, if that's what it takes!
Stop!
Now, for the ass!
No, wait!
Not in there!
Shut up, you know you like it!
You're still dripping wet.
No, please don't!
All right!
I'm going to cum now!
God!
I'm cumming!
Take this!
I'm not finished!
I still want more!
I want to be more than a slave!
I'm in love with Ryouichi.
I love him!
Come on, move it!
Yes!
I'll do it!
I've made my choice!
Tamana Tsukino!
She's it!
She's going to be my final target.
Such a quiet little bitch!
She always gives me these disgusting looks.
It's been pissing me off.
I'll show her, God damn it!
I think that snob will be an
excellent final victim for me!
Chihiro!
Get me information on that
bitch, and make sure it's good!
Let's stop this!
Let's not do this!
You're still being mouthy!
Forgive me!
I promise!
I'll do what you want.
You're supposed to be my
slave, you understand me?
Yes!
Good.
I'm cumming!
Cum!
Oh God!
I'll dump a thick load of my jizz on that bitch!
I'll teach that stuck-up bitch a fucking lesson!
Ryouichi...
All those snotty little whores!
I'm make sure all of them submit to my huge cock!
I feel a lot better.
It's so God-damn convenient
to have a willing sex partner.
Ryouichi!
What, you want more sex?
No, just let me hold you for a minute.
If that's what you want.
Dear God, please.
Bring him back!
I want the sweet Ryouichi that I used to know!
My cock's hard and ready, as usual.
Did you find out anything useful about Tamana?
She's very quiet, so I don't have anything yet.
You're a useless little slut!
I'm sorry!
All I know it that she goes into the
second storage building every day!
Second storage building?
Where they keep the old PE equipment?
Yes, she's always studying...
under that big tree at
the edge of the courtyard.
She looks around, then goes
into the storage building.
She's the student council
president, so she has the keys.
I thought I'd take a look...
to see what she's up to.
You can't be serious!
She's a fucking bookworm!
She always covers her nose
with a handkerchief, right?
It's not because he smells bad.
Well, you know...
he does have a very unique fragrance.
My nose is very sensitive.
I'm not trying to make him feel bad.
So, she doesn't like the way I smell?
I think she's sensitive to smell in general.
Unique fragrance?
I don't get it!
Tell me, what do I smell like, really?
Tell me the truth.
It's not like I really care.
You smell a lot...
like cum.
Like cum?
Then that probably means Tamana
knows what cum smells like.
I guess.
Good, Chihiro.
Make me cum, quickly.
Sure.
Yeah, that's good!
Don't swallow, spit it out on your hands.
Now, don't wash your hands
off, you got that?
Just finish class before washing your hands.
Sure.
During the war, there were many
factors complicating the issue.
...the war involved too many
clans wanting results
for different reasons. As
a result, the consequences...
Chihiro, Chihiro.
What's up?
Can I ask you something?
Never mind!
Sorry!
What's wrong, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Will you clarify your last point?
Hey, are you sure you're okay?
Excuse me!
What is it, Tamana?
I'm feeling really sick.
Can I please see the nurse?
Sure, go ahead.
Chihiro, go with her.
I'm fine, I'll go by myself.
I'll go and make sure she's okay.
That's fine.
Thank you, Chihiro.
Sure.
I got it!
I bet she has a sperm fetish.
Let's see if I can use this...
So, what happened to Tamana?
She went into the storage building.
Now, for our next plan, your
job is going to be to approach...
No!
Say what?
No, I refuse to help you!
Damn it, you're my slave!
Listen to me, Ryouichi!
She's obviously got personal issues...
so her attitude isn't personal,
it's not about you.
There's no reason for revenge!
What the...
So, you're still not going to help me?
No!
I just can't do it!
Stupid cunt, just cum and get it over with.
Yes!
Oh yes!
Cum, that's right!
Get over it, I know you're still
going to help me, Chihiro.
I won't!
This isn't about revenge anymore.
I know you just want to fuck her.
What?
I thought...
you would eventually understand!
But you didn't!
What happened to the sweet guy I used to know?
I want him back!
I want the old Ryouichi back!
She's never going to understand my feelings.
Fine, I'll just finish this by myself.
Ouch!
What is this?
Gross!
What's all this?
It smells like cum!
I can't think straight.
It's coming in through my nose
and controlling my mind and body.
Ryouichi!
Wait, I hope this isn't your idea of fun.
Why are you doing this?
Why? You know why, damn it!
Always covering your nose with your handkerchief...
whenever I'm around, like I'm a pile of shit!
That's a misunderstanding.
It's not because you smell bad...
I know that!
I know it's because you just can't control
yourself around me, since I smell like cum.
You have a hardcore sperm fetish.
Stop, let me go!
Don't touch me!
Don't be shy.
I've got all the cum you could
ever want, packed into my balls.
Here!
No!
Yuck!
Come on, I did this just for you!
No!
Are you mad because I removed your clothes?
I just thought you wouldn't want to keep
wearing your cum-soaked uniform.
It's drenched all over with cum, see?
You really do have a strong fetish!
Here, take a good whiff!
Let me check out your tits.
I didn't think they'd be this big!
Let's check out your pussy.
You don't like that?
Come on, you're soaking wet down here already.
Well...
Wait a minute.
Tamana, you're not a virgin!
Tell me, how did you lose your virginity?
Like vibrators?
No, stop!
Feels good.
I'll stick in your ass if you don't tell me!
My brother...
Your brother?
It was my brother-in-law.
Tell me the whole story.
When I was young, he would creep
into my room every night.
He would shove his cock into
my mouth while I was sleeping.
That doesn't sound like fun.
I hated it, but it started to happen every night.
Soon, I couldn't forget the taste of cum.
Then, he started to jack off between my thighs.
Dry fucking.
But eventually, it escalated.
That's a really fucked up thing to do.
What a prick!
No don't, that hurts!
You're not a virgin, but you've
never done anal before, right?
Blame your brother-in-law.
Almost in!
There, I'm inside you!
Here we go!
I like going where no man's ever gone before.
Please pull it out!
Pull it out!
Fine, then!
I'll play with your pussy, and
you won't feel the ass fucking!
This sensation...
I'm getting fucked in my
pussy and my ass at once.
I think you like this...
I'll let you cum for now.
It feels strange.
Heat... I can feel his heat inside!
It's warm.
It feels so good!
What's happening to me?
I'm scared, I'm scared!
No!
Do you like the way my cock smells
after it has been in your ass?
It smells.
It stinks.
I like it!
And I thought she'd be frigid!
Sucking my cock after it's been in her ass!
Does it taste good?
You like my cock?
My cum will taste even better!
It's the best, I love it!
Your brother-in-law taught you well!
I want to taste your cum inside my mouth!
So, that's what you want!
I'll fill your mouth with the biggest,
thickest load you've ever swallowed!
I'm cumming, and you're going to swallow it all!
Thank you!
I really like this kind of fetish!
Wait, Ryouichi!
You don't need to tie me up, I won't run away!
Shut up, this is for my enjoyment now.
I'm sure you'll like it.
The rope's digging into me!
It's scraping against my skin, all over my body!
It feels good!
In addition to your cum fetish,
I think you're also a masochist.
No, that's not true!
You're a liar, you like this!
That hurts!
I feel it!
I can't handle it anymore.
I want you to fuck me right now!
See, you are a masochist!
Please...
Just admit it.
Yes, I'm a masochist, I'm
a masochist whore, all right!
All right, I'm going to purify
your violated pussy...
with my gigantic, awesome cock.
God, you've got a tight pussy!
You're going to get fucking hammered!
Hammer me, harder!
I want it hard!
I want you to just fuck me until I pass out!
This feels too good!
I can't hold back!
I'm cumming right now!
Tell me, I have the greatest fucking
cock in the whole universe, right?
You're the best!
No, I can't take anymore!
My God!
I'm cumming!
No, wait, in my mouth!
Please dump a big load inside my mouth!
Please!
All right, open wide!
Here!
Ryouichi!
Are you finished?
Yeah, I did it on my own.
I don't need you anymore!
Since that day, we both mutually
started to avoid each other.
All the women that he raped out of revenge...
started to treat him well afterwards.
They all started to look after
and take good care of him.
He smiles when he's with them.
He smiles at them like they are his lovers.
He even started to take his studies very seriously.
Soon, he had a lot of new friends.
I was no longer a part of
Ryouichi's life in any way.
That's when I found out that I was moving.
My father's job was taking us back to America.
Ryouichi!
More!
It's so nice to be young!
Ryouichi!
I flew back earlier than my family...
so I'd be back in school for the new semester.
What's going on!
Ryouichi, why are...
Your mom suggested that I should study abroad.
I regained my confidence, so I
was going to let you live your life.
But, I was kind of lonely.
I'm staying at your house
and you can be my slave again!
Ryouichi!
Ryouichi, Ryouichi!
It's kind of fun to fuck on a plane!
Foreign babes!
Chihiro's step-mom was really something else!
Big boy!
Come on, you're great!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
I hope they're all slutty, just like her!
Yeah, I'm going to fuck as much as I can!
Fuck girls from around the world!
I understand now.
For Ryouichi, getting sex is nothing
but a game that he needs to play.
He's too young to understand love.
I'm just happy to have him back!
Yes, yes!
Yes!
The End