Yes!
Yes, oh, yes!
Baby, I'm cumming hard!
It's too bad...
you are never going to be of much use.
It'll be a shitty life, anyway.
So it's best to just get shot out,
and die inside a tissue paper.
It's really for the best.
It's not any of your fault, by the way...
that you ended up
being my God-damned sperm.
He locked his room
and won't come down to eat.
Please, don't turn out like your brother.
Keraku no Oh: King of Pleasure
Today, we have a new student,
and her name is Chihiro Himenoki.
Hi, my name is Chihiro.
It's nice to meet you.
Chihiro has spent most of her life
in America because of her father's business.
So please be kind and show her around...
as she's still unfamiliar with things here.
Okay.
Your assigned seat will be...
Gosh, no.
Well, can you sit over there for just today?
Sure.
Everyone, please open your textbooks.
We'll start on page 55.
It's good to see you, Ryouichi.
Hi Ryouichi!
Just don't.
You don't want to be my friend.
Watch out, he's coming!
Holy shit!
God-damned freak!
You're a piece of shit!
Fucking die!
You can beat him harder than that!
Gimme that!
I really can't stand looking at your face!
It just ruins my day.
Fucking die!
Damn it!
Just fucking die!
Stop it!
What are you doing to him?
Wait, you're that new girl.
Why are you defending him?
He's just a fucking pig.
Pig?
Oh yes, a damned pig.
You're a smelly, fat, filthy pig.
Actually, a pig probably would be
offended by that comparison!
I'm sorry! It's my fault!
It's because of that accident, right?
You weren't the type
of person to get picked on.
You were fun, and nice, and friendly.
Your family and the doctor
said you would be just fine.
That's why I left here to go to America.
If I knew that you really weren't all right...
if I knew all that you suffered...
I would have been back here much sooner.
Well, there's nothing you can do now.
Just forget about it.
I can't do that.
I need to make it up to you somehow.
If there's anything I can do...
anything at all, I want to know about it.
Anything?
Yes.
Really? Anything?
Yes, I'll do anything!
To be able to fuck such a pretty girl...
it's just unbelievable.
It stinks!
Just kissing makes me rock hard.
Stroke it! Suck on it!
Wow!
I don't think I've ever seen
one this big anywhere!
Just suck on it!
He smells!
What's this?
Were you lying to me earlier?
But...
You said you would do anything.
Just suck on it already.
Yeah! Just like that!
Deep throat it this time.
Strange.
I know I suffered brain damage
after that accident, but...
it seems like my cock was not affected.
Now, you can give me a
real blow job, all right!
This is good.
This is so much better than
jacking off to porn in my room.
Real nice!
Yeah!
I'm cumming!
You've got some gigantic tits.
I especially like these nipples.
Do these get fondled often?
I'm a very, very good girl.
Real pussy.
This is a real pussy!
No, not right there! Please don't!
This is too fucking great!
Don't stop!
Keep on sucking!
This is how pussy tastes.
Now.
This is really nice.
A wet pussy just waiting for my cock.
This is great!
Fucking my first crush like this!
It's almost straight out
of a stupid romance novel!
I've never had such a big cock!
I can feel you filling me up all the way!
I'm cumming! Inside you!
No, please don't cum inside me!
You don't have a choice, baby!
But, please don't!
I'm cumming!
Let's change positions!
No more, please!
Please don't!
I've never felt like this!
All I can feel is your cock in my pussy!
I like it!
Fuck me harder!
Oh, God!
Like that! Keep going!
This is so good!
I'm going to cum!
Let's just stop!
I can't take it anymore, Ryouichi, please!
We're not going to stop
until I'm completely satisfied!
Damn it! Damn it!
I can't stop!
It keeps getting hard.
God damn it, damn it!
I can't stop...
getting real hard.
Shit!
This has given me a lot of confidence.
My cock is going to be an amazing weapon!
Those bitches have something
serious coming now.
Revenge?
Chihiro, your job is to tell
me anything that will help me.
But wait.
You said you would do anything, right?
This is all your fault to begin with.
Oh yeah...
My cock...
is going to be my greatest weapon.
Chihiro...
you are under my command.
Anything?
I saw her...
in the restroom doing it.
I can use that.
What is this?
What the hell do you want?
Well, let's take a look.
How did you...
You're a little rich girl, and the school bully.
I never thought you were so damned kinky!
Let's see what the school thinks of this.
Are you trying to blackmail me?
You don't like the fact that I exist.
I feel bad, and just really want to
make it up to you somehow.
Therefore...
I thought I would do it my way
by giving you what you really want!
Please don't!
Let's fill her up good.
See if you can hold it.
You like it in the ass, right?
So this can't be that different, right?
It's coming!
No!
You hold her down!
No, I can't take this anymore!
Just let me go!
Ryouichi, I think you're going too far!
Shut up! Hold her!
I want you to shit all over yourself!
No!
The stench is gone now.
We've got one more thing.
Can you can drink this for me, now?
Maybe it should be warm...
to soothe that poor stomach of yours.
Ryouichi!
I'm just kidding.
I don't want her to puke!
Besides...
Help me!
You're just too fucking big!
Hurts!
Strange. I thought you
really liked it in the ass!
Not something this big.
I can't take it!
Think of it as a bad case of constipation.
Please no more!
My God!
I don't understand.
I'm getting used to it.
Yeah, this feels pretty damn good.
Oh, yes!
Baby, this was the best fuck ever!
I've never felt so good in my life!
I'll never pick on you again, I promise!
I'll make sure that nobody
picks on you again, okay?
Just fuck my ass.
My anal toys feel like nothing
compared to your gigantic cock!
That's great Ryouichi!
Now you won't get picked
on anymore, right?
I still like pussy much better.
Wait, no, please not there!
No!
What the...
This really hurts.
Oh, no Kaya!
You're still a virgin!
No, this hurts!
A virgin that really likes
to be fucked in the ass.
This is funny.
My God!
Oh, yeah.
More, more!
Yes, yes!
Yes!
God, I love your cock!
I don't understand.
Is this what Ryouichi
wanted to do for revenge?
Just shut up.
Just do as I say, all right?
Nagawa's so pretty, but
she doesn't have a boyfriend.
Do you know why?
No.
I just found out.
Here's a list of the textbooks you need.
Take that to the bookstore.
Can you share with someone for right now?
Sure!
Do you have a minute?
I'll be right back.
What were we...
talking about just now?
Textbooks.
That's right.
Who is it? What is this about?
Why Chihiro!
And Ryouichi!
You don't want the school to know
you're a dyke, now do you?
That's not true!
I didn't think you would
be stupid enough to do this!
Oh, really?
I'm used to people calling me dumb,
along with other choice names.
So I am stupid enough to do this!
What do you want...
I really want to see you in action.
I've only seen lesbians fuck in videos.
Chihiro should be all right for you.
She's one of the prettiest girls in school.
Ryouichi?
Just do it.
You know you fucking owe me, right?
Two sexy, beautiful girls. Better
than most boy-girl porn scenes.
You have such soft, pretty skin.
Almost like silk.
No, wait!
Your clitoris is erect already.
It feels good.
This feels really good!
You really are a doll.
I want to make you cum hard, okay?
You're really wet.
Such a naughty girl!
I don't know.
Will you please...
eat my pussy while I eat yours?
Sure.
Yeah, fantastic! Just like that.
Yes!
I think I really like it!
I love it!
Keep rubbing just like that!
You should fuck a man on occasion.
We will try!
No!
Stop, I didn't agree to this!
I didn't say you were done yet, right?
But...
I've always wanted to fuck
an older, experienced woman.
You like her fingers but you don't like mine?
It's not good to play favorites
with your students.
You stink!
You know, you're a real bitch!
You don't know what it feels
like to be looked down on!
Do you, you stupid cunt?
Please, just stop!
Please stop Ryouichi, you're hurting her.
Stop what?
You want me to stop?
You think she's more important
than I am, don't you!
It's soft and warm.
This is just heavenly.
Don't close your eyes!
This is going to be pumping your pussy.
So you might as well take a good look at it.
No, it's really filthy!
What?
This is what you get for that!
I'm cumming!
Miss Oh-so-high and mighty...
now has my jizz all over her face.
Are you okay?
Go away.
I'm not completely finished with her!
My teacher...
really needs a good cock fucking.
No, I can't take this!
I don't think so dear.
Your pussy is still dripping wet.
You like cock!
Of course, of course not!
And you said it was filthy!
But you're just another cock-hungry whore!
This is good!
I know it's a filthy, dirty piece of meat, but...
please, can you just ream my
pussy like there's no tomorrow!
I'd do it without your permission.
Fuck, I love it!
Filthy big cock!
I want you to pound me with it hard!
I thought you liked women, right?
Do you want me to stop and
switch with Chihiro right now?
No, no.  Please don't stop, please!
I want my pussy pounded!
I can't live without this disgusting cock!
You can fuck me please, anytime you want!
I can fuck you?
No, I'm doing you a service
so you can beg for my cock.
Please, please!
I'll do anything if you'll
just fuck me when you can!
What a fucking slut.
Your big cock is just spreading my pussy.
I love it!
I love your hot, hard, meaty shaft!
My pussy...
can't get enough pounding!
I guess I do owe him something.
I was responsible for
messing him up like this.
Just wait.
I'll get everybody!
To be continued...