I returned to Japan after 10 years.
I was shocked by the change
I saw in Ryouichi.
It was the result of injuries sustained
in a childhood accident.
Brain damage affected Ryouichi's
motor skills.
He became an easy target
for school bullies.
The accident was my fault.
To take responsibility, I
agreed to do anything he wants.
He wanted to have sex.
I soon found out that...
the accident did not affect
his enormous sexual endurance.
Also...
his penis was extremely
large and very thick.
Having sex made him confident...
and he vowed to get revenge
on the women that taunted him.
I agreed to help him with his sick plan...
to make amends for the accident.
This is...
the story of Ryouichi's
journey for revenge.
Keraku no Oh: King of Pleasure
Episode 2
Don't just stand there, you fucking moron!
You piece of shit!
You deserve to fucking die!
Ryouichi, are you sure you're okay?
About what?
You passed out after the incident
today with Kanata, so I...
Be quiet!
But Kanata...
I'll get that bitch for what she did.
Kanata's a raving bitch of a captain.
All right, Chihiro.
Get me useful information about her.
She'll pay for what she did,
the God-damned bitch!
Kanata, may I spar with you?
Yeah, I'm coming!
Everybody, stop!
What's with all the weak-ass sparring?
You're big boys, right?
So what the hell's gotten into you guys?
You're fighting like wusses!
If you don't like it,
I'll spar all of you at once!
That will just save me from
having to watch you pussies!
Is that all you've got?
Clean up before you leave!
Something's up with her.
Let's see.
Is she playing with herself?
That's how you found out?
Yes.
Kanata said...
"I'll spar all of you at once!"
During judo practice...
she was...
getting really excited.
Kanata...
left practice early...
and headed for the restroom.
I peeked into her stall.
She was moaning...
and masturbating!
More!
Pin me down completely!
Fuck all my wet holes!
Yes, rape me!
She wants someone stronger.
So she has rape fantasies, right?
Yes!
Damn it!
I want to cum so badly!
A reward for your good work today!
Go ahead.
Wait Ryouichi, where are you going?
Take a guess.
You're not...
My plan is ready to go.
That dyke's getting pinned down
like she wants by now.
Stop, let go!
Come on, stop!
Having fun yet?
You asshole!
You're very lucky.
Everyone wants to help you fulfill
your ultimate fantasy.
Now don't be shy!
Everybody here is down with gangbanging!
I want to be next.
Suck on mine!
Mine first!
Me too!
Captain, you've got a lot of talent!
Kanata, hop on my hard stick!
I know you want it, right?
No, I don't!
Lift her up.
Sure.
Bring her down slowly.
No, not there!
No!
I think I stuffed her backdoor!
No, pull out, ouch!
How about a good blow job!
Let's get it on!
Come on, suck it!
Damn, this feels good.
Come on, I want a turn, too!
Stop!
The pussy looks lonely, guys.
Shut up, pig!
Yeah, I get the pussy!
This is what I call a genuine gangbang!
My turn to assfuck!
No more!
Pull it out now!
God, I'm going to cum!
Damn!
Me too.
Kanata, that was fucking awesome.
Captain, make sure to clean up!
Thank you, captain!
It's not over yet!
I'm not done with my part of the revenge.
No, not with you, bastard!
Here!
Like my meaty cock, bitch?
Come on, what are you looking at?
Fuck me!
Call me master!
Master!
I'll do anything you want!
So fuck me!
If you insist.
You have to?
Inside my house?
Fucking while your girlfriend's
parents are home...
is part of the whole
adolescent experience, right?
I've had it rough, so I deserve
to make up for that with sex.
I'm home.
This is Ryouichi.
We'll be studying in my room.
Hello!
Chihiro, is he your boyfriend?
Nice to meet you! I'm
Chihiro's stepmother, Mariana.
All right?
We won't need any snacks.
I know.
I understand.
I won't bug you guys.
Were you shocked?
Mariana's my stepmother.
Chihiro
I wouldn't mind fucking an American!
Please, promise me you
won't touch her, okay!
Let's try something new today!
Since you're used to my monster cock,
this should feel small inside you.
Stop!
Stop, don't say that!
Look, your pussy is so
wet it's dribbling out!
No, I can't take any more!
I can see deep inside!
You don't like me looking at it?
Let's see if you like
getting fucked like this!
No!
Not there!
Stop!
There's no reason to be ashamed!
It's clean and washed.
No!
Don't put your tongue in there!
It's too much!
I don't want to!
I don't want to cum like this!
No!
Stop!
All right, then.
Time for some DP action!
I can feel the damned vibrator
tickling my cock!
Kiss me so I won't scream!
I don't want her to hear me!
Go ahead, scream!
We can even have her join us
for a fun threesome.
Yeah, about the next target...
What, you have more?
Yeah, it's going to be
the school nurse, Miyako.
That bitch! I went to see her one
day because I was feeling sick...
and she spent more time
chatting with her boyfriend.
She was on her cell phone forever!
What is it?
What's your temperature?
Over 100.
Okay, go home!
Then she has the nerve to tell me this!
Put the filthy thermometer
in the disinfectant.
So, is that your reason?
That's right, so the first step is
to find that bitch's weakness somehow.
Ryouichi, I can tell you
something right now.
I went to her office one day.
A girl was already there...
with a badly scraped knee.
Ouch!
Does it hurt?
She was being pretty brutal
while cleaning the girl's wound.
I think she has a strong sadistic streak.
Her face was flushed, and
breathing really heavily.
She'll pay!
Miyako!
Nurse's Office
I just scraped up my knee!
Sit facing me.
Yes.
Did you fall somewhere?
I was going down the stairs just now.
And I tripped.
Let's disinfect the wound.
Please!
Does it sting?
Yes.
It won't take long. You don't want
a scar on your knee, do you?
Ouch, this really hurts!
All that rough cleaning is
more likely to leave a scar...
than the scrape itself!
You don't want a scar on
these pretty legs, do you?
Your job is to keep her distracted.
I can't take any more of this!
I'll try.
Ms. Miyako, I can't hold back any more!
Chihiro!
But...
Ryouichi!
What is this?
Untie this rope and let me go!
Don't lie to me.
Why would I lie to you?
I know that you think it's okay
to be tied up on occasion.
Ryouichi!
Have you gone mad?
Come on, your voice sounds
like you like that!
You'll have a lot more coming.
Let me go!
I don't like filthy stinking pigs like you!
Chihiro!
Chihiro, I think Ms. Miyako would
enjoy it if you licked her pussy.
Yes, I think so.
Make sure to get her oozing with juice.
Chihiro!
Ms. Miyako likes your work, baby!
A reward for your hard work!
Yeah!
God!
Chihiro!
Here, taste my filthy spooge!
What?
Giving up so quickly? I only cummed
on your face, you little whore!
Ryouichi, don't you think
you've done enough?
Please, let's stop doing this!
Stop your jabbering, it's still payback time!
Stand over there!
I think I'm going to shoot out a load!
Don't think I'm done
with your pussy just yet.
I'll keep fucking
until you stink like me!
Come on Ryouichi, stop it!
Please!
Hey, at this point she won't
let me stop fucking her.
Please!
I want your cock hammering
me until I pass out!
Punish me with your hard cock!
All right, baby.
Thank you, I want you to
fill my pussy with cum!
Please, I want you to give me more!
Soon, you won't be able to get my stench...
off your body!
I just...
want him to be the sweet guy
he used to be!
I want him to be...
the Ryouichi that I loved so much...
again.
To be continued...