And now for tomorrow’s weather:
Seems like most areas will be clear and sunny.
The predicted highest temperature will be about the same as
today... it will be a little cooler in the morning and evenings...
Hey, isn't it cold in here?
It will be nice and comfortable during the day time.
It's because Nao's dressed lake that.
A little bit of shower is expected to when
the weekend approaches, and...
It’s warm from the heating over here.
Continuing from that, here is the weather
forecast for the weekend.
But it feels good over here!
Over Saturday and Sunday Aomori
is expecting it’s rain to decrease...
If you're not watching the TV, turn it off.
Hey Sis, did you know? If your hormones are well balanced,
your skin will be pretty and have fewer wrinkles.
Isn't that common sense?
Oh I see. But do you know what
you should do to achieve that?
Isn't it to pay attention to your body and live healthily?
There's a much more fun way!
Listen to this:
When females have sex, they will release estrogens which
help balance and adjust their other hormones.
These estrogens will help keep your skin beautiful and young!
What in the world are you reading?
That doesn't matter, right?
Just because it's winter break doesn't mean
you don't have to study, does it?
It's fine.
More importantly, how is Sis doing with Hiroki-san?
What?
Well, look at your skin! It’s just like what this magazine says.
Stop paying so much attention to random articles like those...
And get yourself a boyfriend!
Or it’ll be another lonely Christmas this year again!
What's with that!? Mind your own business and go suffocate
Hiroki-san with those giant boobs or something!
Yours are surprising large as well, so why
don’t you go get a man with those?
What’s wrong, girls?
If you fight like that, Kinichi-san will be laughing at you.
Kinichi-san? Who was that again?
What are you talking about?
He’s your cousin who’s living with us for a month
while he prepares for his test for medical school.
Oh right.
Can I get you girls to pick him up at the station this Sunday?
Presented by Erobeat | http.//www.erobeat.net| #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: romeyo007 | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Fiendish
~Diaries of Breaking Mother and Sisters~
Chapter One: Nikaidou Nao
He should be here by now but...
I wonder where he is...
Nao, your phone.
Okay.
So, this one.
Itou Kinichi
Huh? So you are...
Oh my, you've grown up, Kinichi-san.
Thanks for letting me stay here. I really appreciated it.
You must be tired from travelling. Let’s
carry your luggage to your room first.
Show him around.
As expected, a future medical student
is different from the common.
Ah, I guess...
Shouldn't you be humble when praised?
It’s over here.
It’s THIS way!
Sorry about the mess, it's a room we haven't been using.
It's fine. I can study pretty much anywhere.
Then just stay at your own house.
Nao, the key.
Oh, right.
Then, I'll call you it's time to eat.
Huh!? Hey! Geez!
Be sure to study hard!
Oh my god unbelievable!
All he did was touch your hands, it's nothing.
No way! Is he actually out cousin!? Way too disgusting!
You shouldn't say things like that.
Sis was speechless when you saw him
at the station as well, weren't you?
That wasn't really...
Anyways it’s a no! It’s absolutely a no!
It’s only until his exam is over.
But that'll take a month! In a month the air he breathes
is gonna fill this house and well all suffocate!
My apologies.
I don't feel like eating!
Um...
What?
What is it? Talk!
About my underwear... was it left in
the washing-machine or anything?
Your underwear!
I thought it might have gotten mixed with Nao-san’s...
What the heck!?
Ouch!
Ow, owww...
What is this?
Blood?
Stuff like teeth marks on your nipples or bruises on
your body don't just appear out of nowhere, right?
That person probably just got drunk and
lost her virginity without memory of it.
Eh?
If that's not the case, the only advice
I have is to go see the doctor.
I guess...
I'm done with the shower! You can use it next!
Okay!
Quiet, please.
If you're that loud, Mom or Manami-san will find out.
Nao-chan? What's wrong?
What's wrong, did anything happen?
It's nothing, just a cockroach.
Oh okay. Please don't scare me like that.
I'll be working tomorrow as well, so I'm going to go sleep.
Well done.
Then, let's continue.
Stop it already!
Don't you care what happens to this?
My cellphone...
What is this!?
Don't you remember?
What do you mean...
That doesn't matter anymore, right?
Either way Nao-san's first man is me, so let’s get along.
No!
Either you listen to what I say, or this video
is sent to all the addresses in this phone...
Stop!
That's not an answer...
...I'll listen to what you say, so stop...
Then come over here, please.
In exchange, please end this from now.
Please stick your butt this way.
Nao-san has been shaped to fit me perfected now!
Your body is very honest!
No, you can't!
I'll cum, I'm gonna cum!
Stop...
You lied...
It's fine, I only sent it to my own mail.
With this Nao-san can make her debut to
the whole world through video websites.
Whenever I want it to happen.
I'm off to work then!
Me, too.
Please lock the doors for us.
It's pointless.
Huh?
I mean have a good day!
It's a white Christmas this year!
A white Christmas is exciting no
matter how old you get, isn't it?
C'mon! Nao, you've been a little down lately, haven’t you?
Really?
You have! C'mon, It's Christmas
let's be more happy and cheerful.
There's no way I could be happy
with someone like this around.
Huh?
More importantly, what happened to Sis and Hiroki-san?
Don't you usually go on a date for Christmas?
He's been on a business trip since the day
before yesterday, so he's not here.
Although I wish his boss would be a little more considerate...
Huh? Nao, that...
It's nothing.
It's a kiss mark, isn't it?
Huh? So you did get a boyfriend!
Is that true?
Hurry and bring him home to introduce to us!
I hit it when I was doing the laundry, that's all!
Don't say weird stuff like that, nothing happened!
So it s just a bruise? It looks like a kiss mark to me.
I wouldn't want anyone like you to say that!
Nao-chan, what's with that attitude?
That's impolite to Kinichi-san!
No, It's fine. All I'm thinking about at
the moment is my upcoming exam.
That's quite remarkable, Kinichi-san.
He’s grown up and responsible. Nao should learn from him.
I’m fine, leave me alone!
Nao!
Geez, always such a child.
No, I think she's grown in to a great adult.
Please don't panic. But thanks for letting me in.
I was thinking of leaving these photos if you didn't let me in.
Hand them over!
You said you'd listen to whatever I say, right?
Are you like enjoying doing stuff like this!?
No, I'm in fact very, very sad.
Because you hate me, right? All women are like that.
I am merely avenging myself.
Well I guess it's more of punishment that avenge.
So I'm actually full of sorrow, can you understand?
You reek! You're disgusting!
See, as expected.
H-hey!
Let's hurry up.
If I don't go back quickly computer-kun
will automatically upload the video!
Are you blackmailing me?
No, I'm just inviting you. But if we don't
hurry, someone's in trouble, right?
Well then, please drink this.
Um, where was it again? Oh I remember now.
Just one pill.
Disgusting..
We don't have time.
What... what did you make me take!?
Something to warm up your body. Your
heart will be warmed up as well.
It works quite quickly, see?
What, what was that!?
I could say that it gives you hyperesthesia
all over your body...
Or more simply, your whole body
has become erogenous zones.
This is a product of my studying as well...
And you say you're preparing for med school!?
You perverted idiot!
Idiot? Then can Nao-san make a drug like this?
Wouldn't want to be compared to you...
The effects are remarkable. Your pussy
juices are overflowing already.
Nao-san, your speech and your actions
don't agree with each other.
I'll make it so they match up!
It hurts! Stop that!
You're self-indulgent, aren't you!?
It hurts! It hurts so much it's good!
It's wrapped in a skin... like a banana...
Yes... yes... yes...
Nao, are you there?
Sis?
Did you want some cake? I brought it over.
Just leave it there.
Don't stop...
Huh?
It's nothing! Just leave it there. Please.
Well, I'll just leave it here. Good night.
Please... do me more.
It's cold... feels good!
Nao-san do you have exhibitionism? You’re squeezing tighter.
I guess you must be feeling it.
Ouch!
Sshh. If you make loud noises here, the neighbours will notice.
You’re loud, Nao-san!
I need to pee...
Well, go ahead.
No... No... No!
Nao-san wonderful! I'm going to cum!
Nao-san, you'll be sure to listen to everything
I say from now on, right?
Only if you do me one more time.
The drugs used on the target this time were ?the special sleeping pills and aphrodisiac.
Together they achieved an effect greater than expected, and satisfied my curiosity greatly.
The drugs used on the forge! This time were the special sleeping pills and aphrodisiac.
Together they achieved an effect greater than
expected, and satisfied my curiosity greatly.
The next target...
minikui kaibutsu
The hideous monster
karada wo hau no
lise its body,
arawa ni natta watashi no shiroi suhada ni
On my bare, white skin.
mogaki kurushimi
Amongst struggle and suffering,
kyoufu kara nozoku no
peeking through fear,
michi no yorokobi ga
an unknown joy and pleasure.
mushi wa mata (hase de shiba wo mitsuke narete kurasu)
he bugs (find grassland near water and live their lives),
kigi no asobi ni fukeni
Play amongst leaves as they age and die,
kurai minazato ni shizumikonmde yuku
and then sink into a dark swamp.
shinenn no oku he
Deep into the abyss.
kobannda ude ga
My resisting arms,
chikara nakushite
Lose all the strength.
wakiagaru shoudou
The impulse building up inside,
tomadoi kakusezu
does not hide my confusion.
Kawaita kokoro
A dry, thirsty heart,
shimikomu akui
where malice seeps through,
sabishisa ueteku
Loneliness grows,
ibitsu na kyouki ni
into a distorted rapture.
Kono toki
At this time,
mi wo yudanetai
entrust you with my body.