Are you alright, sir?
Um?
Hiroki-san?? Aren't you Hiroki-san!?
What's wrong, why are you at a place like this?
More...
Do me more...
More!
Hiroki-san! Hiroki-san!
Yes... more...
It's hot...
More, more...
Presented by Erobeat | http.//www.erobeat.net| #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Fiendish
~Diaries of Breaking Mother and Sisters~
Chapter Three: Nikaidou Hitomi
I’m home.
Is no one around?
Manami? Are you there?
Manami!
Are you okay, Manami?
Who...
I'm mom!
Get a hold of yourself, Manami!
What’s wrong? Did something happen?
...with Hiroki...
Huh?
Welcome back.
Kinichi-san.
Please look.
What?
Hiroki-san was doing these things...
Stop!
Here! Please look closely.
Hey kid! Be sure to film it all!
It hurts!
No!
So cruel...
There's more.
Nao!
Both Manami-san and Nao-san were enjoying it...
It's hard for me to believe...
That's right... the police...!
That's won't help.
Since they both agreed to having sex.
I found it troubling...
That they got in the way of me studying...
Well, I'll be back in my room.
Manami-sans sure likes to have sex.
Oba-san must be the same.
Hey... more...
I'm digging in.
Kinichi-san, are your studies going well?
Yes, well...
Since I'm taking care of Kinichi-san instead of my sister,
I'd be so sorry if you don't pass the entrance exam.
Also it seems like some people have already lost it...
But then on the other hand, Hiroki-san was such a pervert.
I think it was good you found out before you got married.
That's right.
Thank you for the meal.
No seconds?
No thank you. I'll go back to my room to study.
Good luck.
I'll bring you dessert later.
Thank you very much.
Kinichi-san, I brought some snacks.
It’s open.
Is studying going well?
I'll leave it here.
Oba-san.
Please wait for a moment.
I'll take a quick break.
What, what are you doing!?
It's fellatio.
That's not what I'm asking!
How dare you make Nao do such a things!
She was the one who insisted it.
Kinichi-san's dick is really tasty!
I love it!
This...
My pussy is so wet... I can't take anymore...
Put your big thing in...
It's good!
My pussy... thrust more!
You're even more slutty than usual today.
Did you get excited having your mom see you?
That... that might be it...
Then moan more, and moan with a larger voice.
Do all you can so your mother can hear.
And show all of it to her.
With a louder voice!
Kinichi-san!
More... my insides... rougher... mess me up!
No... No!
It's hitting inside!
Let it out inside!
Let out lots... and lots!
First Manami and now even Nao...
Just because they're younger??
Well, whatever happens, I should at least inform him.
Yeah, and by the way...
I think there's something...
Hmm? What's wrong?
Uh...
What's with that, Hitomi?
So, is everyone alright?
Uh, yeah...
What? I can't hear you very well.
Yes. Everyone's alright.
I see. How's Kinichi-kun?
Um, I'll call you again.
Who... who are you?
Darling... is it you, darling?
You came home...
Yes, it's great!
No, don't stop!
Happy New Year everyone!
Gross! What is this!?
That's what Otoso sake tastes like.
We're drinking it to wish for health in the upcoming year.
So where'd you get the Tososan?
You bought it?
I got it from my sister.
Kinichi-san brought it over.
I see...
Drink more, Nao.
Eh? I guess I'll have to...
I'll have some, too.
Manami-san, Nao-san, why don't
you go make New Year's wishes?
Sounds good. You should come, too, Kinichi-san.
I have to study.
Then I'll help you wish for passing the entrance exam.
Kinichi-san... more... there, yes...
Do me more, Kinichi-san...
Kinichi-san, more...
More...
Why?
No, no, I can't.
I can't stop... this is too good...
It's coming out... no...
Kinichi-san!
Please continue.
What are you talking about?
Get out!
You don't have to yell. I'll leave when I finish the test.
Now, let's start.
Hey...
I'll put my dick inside Oba-san's pussy again.
What are you talking about!?
There's no way I'd let you do that!
Please listen closely.
I said, put it in again.
You remember it, don't you? My mark.
No way, you...
This will be the second time!
You are already mine!
No way...
No!
See? It feels good, doesn't it?
They've stretched so far.
You can let out voice more.
You've gotten more sensitive.
All thanks to my drugs.
Haven't you felt it after drinking coffee or the Otoso?
Please make me cum with your mouth first.
This... I can't...
Shut up.
Take it deeper.
Cumming!
You remember the taste of my sperm, too, don't you?
With this...
You are satisfied, right?
Although it has gotten stronger,
it seems like the drugs are doing well enough yet.
Let's put another on in from behind.
No... no there!
You say no but it went in quite easily.
Seems it's already been spread before.
Could it be that you enjoy anal with Oji-san already?
How surprising.
As expected from an experience woman,
Too... to large...
even such a size can be taken in properly.
Amazing...
Yes... yes, more...
My mind... my mind's going crazy...
I'll become stupid!
I'm turning into an idiot!
That's fine!
Let your true self be free.
C'mon!
More, thrust more!
Thrust my pussy and my ass!
Kinichi-san...
Oba-san is mine.
You two are having fun alone!
Geez, how nice, Mom...
Jealous?
Alright, let's do it together...
So, how did it go?
I failed.
You failed?
Another year?
You're going back?
Thinking back on it, the main reason I failed this test...
was because I got distracted in the final stages
of reviewing, and lost concentration.
That's all your fault!
In the following year I'll have you
pay back to me with your bodies.
Of course, no objections.