Nao-chan? What's wrong?
What’s wrong, did anything happen?
It’s nothing, just a cockroach.
Oh okay. Please don't scare me like that.
I'll be working tomorrow as well, so I’m going to go sleep.
Well done.
Then, let’s continue.
Stop it already!
Don't you care what happens to this?
My cellphone...
Mom? Did you hear shouting?
Apparently a cockroach.
Presented by Erobeat | http.//www.erobeat.net| #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Fiendish
~Diaries of Breaking Mother and Sisters~
Chapter Two: Nikaidou Manami
Unknown Number
I'm off!
Ah, me too!
Unknown number again?
What is this?
Nao?
You don't look well.
It’s nothing. I’m fine.
Really? Are you sure you’re okay?
I'm fine!
I also think you don’t very well.
Stop it!
Nao-chan?
I’m worried.
I’m sorry. It's not something you have to worry about, Sis.
I'll be off to bed. Goodnight.
I wonder if it's because her hormones are off balance...
Would you like some coffee, Manami-san?
Oh thanks, I’ll have some.
Here.
Thank you.
I’ll be off to study for my exams now.
Yes...
Hiroki... Hiroki... more...
Yes... more...
Hi, I'm Nikaidou who ordered a cake a few days ago...
Nikaidou-sama, right? Please wait for a moment.
I'm home!
Manami-chan, could you bring cake to Nao's room?
Kinichi-san says he doesn't like sweet stuff.
Alright.
Nao, you there?
Sis?
Care for cake? I brought some up.
Just leave it there.
Don’t, don’t move...
Is something wrong?
It’s nothing! Just leave it...
please...
Then, I’ll leave it here.
Studying. Do Not Enter!
Kinichi-kun? The student that’s studying at your place?
Yeah, there’s something he wants to talk with us about Nao.
About Nao-chan?
Yeah, she hasn't been very well lately.
Well, it s quite hard to imagine Nao not being well.
When did this start happening?
It’s not the best to say this, but it
started when Kinichi-kun came...
Good evening.
Kinichi-kun!
Nao-chan!
I'm sorry for calling you guys so suddenly.
Here.
Thank you.
Let me introduce: This is Nishiyama Hiroki-san.
Nice to meet you.
Before all the greetings, I have to show you guys something.
Please look at this.
I was really surprised. She looks just like Nao-san.
This was sent many times.
Nao-san hasn't been well from the shock of it.
So that’s what’s been happening.
Yeah.
This is horrible! I've been getting
stuff like this on my phone, too!
Really?
Yeah, but I didn't want you worried, so...
Doing such things to someone so pure
like Nao-san... I can’t forgive this.
We should give this to the police...
Wait. We can’t just show it to someone else,
even if it’s just someone who looks alike...
What about the source?
I can’t tell. The address is hidden. It’s probably
from somewhere outside the country.
Well, for now...
Video Deleted
What a horrible person to do this!
It’s possible that the Nikaidou family is being
spied on. You guys should be careful, too.
Yeah...
Sis?
What's wrong?
Hey...
What’s wrong? Please be clear.
The washroom!
Manami!
Mana...
Huh?
Vacancy
Hey... Come, Hiroki-san! My pussy is so soaked already!
Please thrust Hiroki-san's thick cock into me... into my pussy!
Oh geez... maybe I should sue that store.
Sis, is your stomach better?
You should take this.
What's with that?
It’s for your period, but it works as a pain killer, too.
I heard from a friend before.
Nao-chan... about yesterday...
It’s fine now. Kinichi-san will do something about it.
Kinichi... san? Well I guess that’s fine.
But if there’s every anything you should tell me and...
Huh? I’m suddenly feeling sleepy...
Sleep.
No!!
Hey, watch it.
What is this?
What is going on here!? A dream??
A dream? That’s right, it s a good dream.
Don’t joke around!
It’s fine, right? This is just a dream.
I'll scream!
Do as you please.
No on outside will be able to hear you.
Nao! Nao!
Nao-san won't be coming.
She’s become my sex slave already.
You're lying!
I’m not. She was upset about it for a while,
but she's happily my sex slave now.
So you're the one who’s been sending
those crazy emails to Nao and I!
Why would you do something like that!?
It is because I am in love with the two of you.
You’re sick!
Well then why don’t we make a deal?
If Manami-san does whatever I say...
I won't touch Nao-san anymore.
Like I'd believe you!
I see...
Well, we'll get your sister to debut
to the world on the internet.
There’s a limit to how similar two people can look, you know.
You’re the worst!
What’s wrong?
Is that really Nao?
That’s not the problem!
See? I would like to resolve things peacefully.
And I’m sure that you’d like to do so, too.
See?
Your body says so, too.
What is this!?
What do you mean "what is this?".
Those are love juices, of course.
Did you get turned on my the video of Nao-san?
That’s not...
Then what could it be? What should you do?
What do you want to do?
If I listen to what you say, then you
leave Nao alone. For sure, right?
Yes, I won’t do anything.
Not me, at least.
Beautiful...
Those large boobs, too, but that heart
thinking for your sister is beautiful.
What is that thing!?
It’s a specially modified vibrator.
Then, please spread your legs.
Stop it!
You don't care what happens to Nao-san?
If I don’t return to my room in time, Nao-san’s video will
be automatically uploaded to sites all over the world.
Please don’t hold back when it feels good!
It feels good!
Amazing! This is the first time I've seen something like this.
Maybe the drugs worked too well.
It hurts! No!
No, no, no, no, stop!!
I said, stop!
My glasses...
Kinichi-san...
Is it fun!? Do you enjoying laughing
at me for having bad eyesight!?!
Thank you very much...
Did you think I’d say something like that?
Stop... stop it...
This is punishment.
It hurts!
No!
Oh, a used pussy has a different sensation from Nao-san.
The feeling of the vibrator pushing on
the other side is pretty good, too.
This feels... weird...
Why am I... feeling good...
I put special drugs on the tip of the vibrator as well.
Your expression is wonderful.
That’s... don't take photos!
Let's get you to suck on it again.
I can’t believe something like this could feel good...
The way your tongue wraps around is great.
Well then...
Let’s get you to use those giant tits to squeeze it.
It’s cold...
They've become even sluttier boobs now.
Well, please pull back the foreskin and
squeeze it between your boobs.
Yes.
This is great!
It feels good...
Hey, you can't forget about the titty fuck
and only focus on feeling good yourself.
Cumming... cumming, I’m cumming!
I’m cumming from my butt and chest!
Cumming!
Geez! How dare you cum on your own.
Hey, some of Manami-sans poo is sticking on it.
Please clean it up.
How about it? Don’t you want more of this?
I want it...
Well then please, as much as you wish.
Even if it's for your sister, what would
Hiroki-san think if he sees this?
Hiroki-san, you’re too rough!
It’s the work of your drugs, huh?
But even... Hiroki...
by the way, to clarify things, I haven’t
done anything to Nao-san.
More, more!
It’s not fun to just be watching. Let’s enjoy ourselves, too.
Yes... it feels good!
Hiroki-san, more... thrust me more!
Yes!
That's... Sis, does having your butt
hole teased feel that good?
Don’t ask... such things!
Cumming...
Cumming, cumming!
Cumming!
This is far, far from the end.