The Kingdom of Bastarauge, home of Princess Eleasteria
Elshe Bastarauge.
Her beauty is valued more than any nation's treasure.
However... you can not escape from here...
The tables have turned.
Slutty-Princess Diaries
Episode 1: Defloration of a Princess
How do you feel, Princess Eleasteria?
Or should I call you Elena?
Distol, how dare you kidnap me and imprison me in such a
place.
Do you not have any manners as a gentleman?
You are a tough one.
However, I hope you understand your situation.
I am the only one here.
Even if you cry for help, no one will come rescue you.
No! If you come any closer...!
What!? Don't touch!
How dare you, you know the consequences!?
Must I remind you that you are not a princess any more?
You're just a... bitch!
No!!
Stop it!
Stop it, don't look!
You have a well shaped, well sized chest.
These are something any guys would like.
If you continue any further, I'll make sure you pay the
consequences!
You better be ready, I'll be teaching you true pleasures.
I will not! Let go, let go now!
You will soon change your thoughts.
Stop it, it's dirty!
Stop it!
What's wrong? Does it feel good?
Of course... not...!!
Of course not what?
Looks like the princess is very sensitive right here.
That's not true.
No, not right there!
No, that is my, that is my...!
What are you doing!?
What am I doing? Look at you!
No, right there is, right there is...!
No, please stop!
You're so wet... what a princess.
This is torture... you looking at my thing...
So, you get turned on by torture. What a slut!
No, that's not true!
You can say whatever you want, but your body won't lie.
Princess Eleasteria, you know what's coming, right?
Sto...
Sto... No...!
Look at this closely. This is going inside of you!
Distol, if you stop now, I'll forgive you... so please!
I don't need your forgiveness!
Stop!!
How does it feel being rubbed?
What's wrong? Do you want it?
Stop, stop, please stop. I beg you mercy.
Why do you do this!?
You don't need to... know!
You are tight.
Pull out, pull out! It hurts, it hurts!
So this is your first.
So cruel... my virginity lost to this...
Don't move!
Elena's vagina twitches and clutches onto my meat.
Some of you may wonder why I am doing this to Elena.
There is a reason why and I will tell you.
I was raised as the prince of Kingdom Asteria.
As an orphan, I did not have a real family, however...
One person cared and loved for me until the end... Queen
Rosaria...
Brother. Brother?
Di, what's wrong? Didn't you notice Qoona calling you?
Nothing Mother... I was just day dreaming a bit.
Are you feeling OK?
I'm al right Qoona, thanks for asking.
Brother, that tickles.
Qoona, Mother and I will be traveling far away tomorrow.
Will you be OK?
Qoona...
I'll be al right, I won't be sad
We will be back, so please wait for us.
Yes, I promise, Brother...
Don't cry, Qoona.
Otherwise, Mother won't be happy.
King Bastarauge was hungry for power and wanted my
kingdom, Asteria, to himself.
Bastarauge framed us with violation of territory, blocked us
in with this army, and gave us only one option.
Everyone can tell that this was a con pulled off by
Bastarauge.
However, as a small nation, we had no choice but to do
what they wanted us to do.
As a result, Bastarauge took many of our resources
and limited the power of our army... thus leading to the
collapse of the kingdom.
There is still more to this...
Basterauge requested two hostages from the royal family
The two were Queen Rosaria and Prince Distol, which is
me.
Mother, Brother. I will get some flowers wishing you a
safe trip.
Thank you, Qoona.
I will protect you once we get there, Mother.
Di, you...
Mother, you cared for me even though we're not related.
Now, it is my time to protect you.
Although we don't share the same bloodline, you will
always be my son.
Yes.
Don't forget about Qoona.
She likes you more than anyone else.
Of course, Mother.
I promise.
You better keep it, Di.
Few days after we arrive at Bastarauge.
Mother passed away!?
That's right.
But how!?
I am truly sorry about your mother. We will have a funeral
for her.
Why, what happened!?
It's sickness
That can't be! She was very healthy yesterday!
That's the reason, there's nothing more to it!
What did you do to my mother!?
Distol, watch who you're talking too!
What are you guys doing? Get the prince!
Hey, let go now!
Distol, I will lock you up for one month. Cool off a bit.
Ever since, I trained myself with a sword.
I cursed myself for being weak. I must be strong.
I don't want to lose something important ever again.
I have to be stronger than anyone...
Princess Eleasteria.
How many times I have to tell you, call me Elena.
I'm sorry, Princess Elena.
Please forgive me.
You don't need to apologize long as you understand.
Well, is there something you need, Princess Elena?
I just came for a morning walk, I don't need you.
Princess!
Oh, it's you guys. Don't scare me.
I'm sorry, Princess Elena.
Sorry for being rude.
However, Princess. Please avoid talking to this man.
Cecil, it's not up to you to decide who I can talk to.
But...
Distol, please forgive their rudeness.
I don't mind.
Calm down. Any ways, Princess
The king is calling you.
My father?
Yes, he said please hurry to the conference hall.
Al right.
Lets hurry, Princess.
Yes, you're right.
Elena always seems nervous around me.
Is it because the way General Cecil looks at me?
Her other guard, Yuno, is an Elf from faraway.
It is said that she is a great wizard.
She must be a tough foe.
I continue to train myself with a sword day after day.
I worry greatly about Qoona, my sister.
Then one day, a tragic news is brought to me.
Hello Queen Elizabeth.
You always practice hard.
I'm still an amateur with swords.
I was wondering if I should tell you this but I think I should.
What is it?
The King will be calling you to his throne soon.
Whatever you do, don't get a temper.
Is it something about me?
Mother, this isn't a place for a queen.
Please return.
Di, my father is looking for you.
Try going to his throne room.
OK.
What is up with Elena's attitude toward the queen?
I know they aren't related, but isn't it a bit too harsh?
Distol, at your service.
I have heard news that the seal is losing its power.
The seal?
As a precaution, the Church has requested for the
Holy Maiden
which will be chosen from your kingdom, Asteria.
Don't tell me...!?
That's right, the chosen one is
Princess Qoonashirea Elasteria.
Qoona!? Qoonashirea is the Holy Maiden!?
King Asteria acknowledges the situation and the
ceremony should happen within the next few days.
That can't be true!
It's something to be proud of.
That's all I have to say, leave.
Many years ago, this world was terrorized by the
Demon King.
He was powerful as any god and had a horde of monsters
under his control.
He brought the Dark Age to our civilization.
However, exactly 1000 years ago, the Elder of Time
successfully sealed him.
To keep the seal intact, there is a great price to pay.
Which is a sacrifice.
During the times of war, when people have hatred, the
power of the seal becomes weaker
In order to strengthen the seal's power, the Church
requests for a sacrifice.
The sacrifices are all a virgin, pure in heart.
Ones chosen as the next sacrifice are imprisoned in the
Tower of Ceremonies for a year
The ceremony uses the sacrifices life source to strengthen
the seal.
The completion of the seal means the death of the
sacrifice.
These girls are praised and honored by everyone for
sacrificing their life.
Thus the reason why they are called Holy Maidens.
Once entering the Tower of Ceremonies, a magical barrier
surrounds the tower.
Once the field is up, not a single soul can go in or come
out.
Qoona is the one chosen to be the next Holy Maiden.
Once again, I wasn't able to protect the one I love!
Am I powerless?
Shit! Why does it have to be Qoona!?
That's not right!
What was the purpose of all this training!?
Was it all pointless!?
I got you!
A monster, but why? Don't tell me...!
You have done well.
You are strong as rumored, Prince Distol.
It is an honor to meet you.
You! Who are you?
Please disengage. I don't have intentions to fight you.
What?
I am your partner. I have come to help you.
What do you mean, partner?
I'm sorry, but I had to test your power.
Test? How dare you!
I can't... move?
I told you, disengage your weapon.
I just want to talk one on one with you.
Screw that, I have nothing to talk with a person like you!
Even if it's about your beloved sister, Princess
Qoonashirea?
What... did you just say!?
Do you not want to save Princess Qoonashirea?
...Al right.
Speak...
Finally looks like you're going to listen.
As you already know, once accepting the ritual and
entering the Tower of Ceremonies, there is no way out.
Even if you do manage to escape with the one, she will
still be bound to the power and only shorten her life.
That's right! If that wasn't in the way, I would've already
saved Qoona!
Well, I know the way to neutralize that power.
The way to save Princess Qoona from death.
I can provide you that power.
The power and knowledge to save Princess Qoona.
The power and knowledge to save Qoona... those words
better be true.
Of course, although there are few things.
Few things?
Correct, I want you to invade Bastarauge
and steal the royal treasure.
Treasure?
How... that is impossible.
No one in the world can do what you've just requested.
But there is a way... with the power and knowledge I will
give you.
Besides, you have a reason to invade Bastarauge.
What did you say!? What are you saying!
Let me show you the truth behind your mother's death.
Bastarauge!!!!!
Have you come to a decision?
It was all a plan just to get Roasria to himself.
Alright, I'll do what you want! Give me the power!
Even if it means changing your future?
I will give my soul to the demon if I can revenge my
mother's death and save Qoona!
Understood...
Is something wrong?
No, just surprised that you're cute like your voice.
Who knows, this voice and body might be an illusion.
I suppose you are right... what should I call you?
I'm sorry. My name is Eleanor.
Nice to meet you.
What are you doing?
A ritual that is needed for the blood pact.
This is...
Yes, so please, Sir Distol.
Here.
Sir Distol, let me have.
Amazing... it's out of this world. You are a witch.
Don't torture me, please.
Is this really your first time... you slutty witch!
You're the first... who accepted.
It feels really good!
I feel it deep inside... Sir Distol.
More, give me more...
Sir Distol.
It feels good!
Eleanor, I will make you orgasm!
As you wish...
Sir Distol... your cum all over me... it's so thick.
Accept your new power...
Qoona...
This is my... new power?
With this new power, I can clear out this forest.
Amazing... With this power Bastarauge will be easy to
conquer!
The blood pact ritual is now done.
You can not go back.
Yes, I know. This power is for Qoona!
Shall we get started, Master?
Everything changed that day.
What is it!? What is happening?
Prince Distol is attacking!
An Attack? Did he lose his mind!?
The frontal defense is annihilated, the prince is heading to
the palace.
How dare he.
And General Cecil isn't here...
How many?
Just one.
W, what!?
If you don't want to die, flee.
Get him dead or alive!
How pathetic...
Distol!?
How are you doing, Princess Eleasteria?
I'm sorry for not knocking.
I'm surprised that you didn't run away in this noise.
Why are you doing this, Distol?
I don't need to answer you.
Is this the price... for the power?
Master?
Eleanor, what's is it?
The army is regrouping, please hurry.
Al right, ready the horse.
Eleanor, please take care of Elena. Wait for me at Asteria.
And you?
You should know.
Yes, who is it?
It is I, Distol.
Prince Distol is here to see the beautiful Princess
Qoonashirea Eleasteria.
Brother! Brother!!
I'm back Qoona, sorry to keep you waiting.
I wanted to see you.
Me too.
But I've been chosen as the Holy Maiden. I have to
protect everyone.
I won't be able to see you anymore.
About that Qoona, listen to me closely.
I will rescue you, Qoona.
But that means bringing chaos to this world.
Listen to me carefully, there's not much time.
There's a lot of things I must do to save you.
Brother...
Qoona, promise me that you will stay strong. I will come
save you.
Brother... Brother...
Al right? Wait for me.
Brother!!!
In order to save Qoona, he needs to do two things.
One is to take the treasure inside the castle of
Bastarauge.
The other is to corrupt Elaine's purity and weaken
her seal within.
I know, I will weaken the seal within Elena!
What's wrong, you feel it?
Of course not!
That's a pity. I must go in deeper.
What are you going to do!?
Seems like you're liking it, Princess Elena.
Be quiet, that's not true...
And you call yourself a princess? What a slut!
How's this!
It's tightening... does it feel that good?
Why is my... body...!?
Yes...
I hope you like it.
How do you like the feeling of being ejaculated inside
while losing your virginity like this?
My virginity... taken... like this...?
Although I did violate her, she isn't corrupted yet.
I will continue to violate her until she looses her dignity
and pride. I will corrupt her no matter what.
I will do anything to save Qoona, even if it means creating
many enemies.
This is like... It doesn't matter!
Even if it means being responsible for a new dark age!
To be continued...