This is the girls' bathroom!
Wait, Hajime...
Oh, geez!
I did something bad yesterday, didn't I?
Something bad?
I didn't use a condom and came inside you.
You may be pregnant.
Pregnant?
There's a chance...
I mean, that's what happens when a guy cums in a girl.
Well, yeah...
I'll take responsibility.
I appreciate your concern,
but we don't know yet if you knocked me up or not.
In any case, that's not the reason
why I've been avoiding you...
And I don't think what you did was bad!
I'm glad to hear that.
You're so silly.
Oh my god, that feels so good!
N-No!
I can't wait any longer!
Amazing! Your dick is bursting inside of me!
It's twitching so hard!
Cum inside my pussy!
It feels so good!
After that, a lot of things happened,
and Megumi and I started dating.
I'm not sure if I should feel happy or disturbed
by how far your relationship has come.
Uh, yeah, how do I put it?
I guess it's kinda weird, huh?
Well, whatever. I'm glad you two
understand each other's feelings now.
Now that my job as Cupid is done, I'll see myself off.
Are you sure okay with this, Misa?
Wh-What do you mean?
You actually like Hajime too, don't you?
Huh?
What was that?
If you don't like him, nothing will happen
if you take a Love Pill right now, correct?
F-Fine! I'll take one and prove you wrong!
L-Like, what the heck?
I'm not attracted to Hajime the slightest bit,
so I have no idea where you got the idea.
Hajime!
A-Are you okay, Misa?
Why'd you take so many?
If I didn't take that many, I wouldn't
be able to prove how I really feel.
But now I can!
I love you, Hajime!
You're finally being honest with yourself huh?
You're acting like drugging your
best friend was a good thing!
Man up, Hajime.
You're my boyfriend, aren't you?
Hajime...
I love you!
Misa, wait...
C'mon, show him your body.
You have to be more assertive if you
want your feelings to reach him.
No! I...
I love you, Hajime!
I love you so much!
I peed all over you...
So you really loved him this much...
I'm sorry.
I asked you for romantic advice when
you felt this way about him...
You know how I am... I'm a weirdo who never fits in.
But Hajime spends time with me anyway.
He's always right by my side, no matter what!
How could I not fall for him?
Hajime...
Just for now, could you give her an answer?
If you're not against it,
I want you to accept my feelings.
Both of you are okay with this, right?
Our first kiss...
That really calmed me down.
My heart's been so topsy-turvy lately...
I haven't been able to sleep properly because of it.
And now we've had our second kiss.
Oh, yeah...
That's right.
My actual first kiss was with this guy, wasn't it?
Is it okay for me to take your other "first" now?
Sure.
This hole is just for you.
So make lots of love to me, okay?
Are you okay?
I can take it out if it hurts.
No, I think I'm okay now.
The Love Pill is still in effect.
But I think I'd like it more if you were a bit gentler.
Sure.
Oh, so that's how it is.
And here I was stressing out about
not being able to handle him.
I wish I asked him to be that gentle for my first time.
I feel kind of cheated.
This is so good!
Your dick...
It's messing up my insides!
It's slamming against me so hard!
I'm about to cum.
That's fine!
Cum deep inside me!
Let it all out!
Make my pussy overflow with your cum!
I-I can't do that!
What if I get you pregnant?
What would you do?
I would...
I would take responsibility, of course.
Shit, I'm at my limit!
I'm gonna fill you up!
Here it comes!
It's coming out!
Your cum is pouring into me!
So good... It's so good!
My womb is being filled with your seed!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I can't say I don't feel conflicted about all this...
But seeing her look like that puts me at ease.
And with that, everything had been resolved,
and we all lived happily ever after...
At least, that's what I hoped would have happened.
You tell the best jokes, Misa.
I'm telling you, I'm not joking.
So explain to me why you're the
girlfriend and I'm the mistress?
I mean, isn't the mistress supposed
to be the one who comes in later?
Huh, what's that?
Weren't you the one who said that time
doesn't matter when it comes to love?
Very well.
How about we both take Love Pills
and see who Hajime likes more?
Sounds good to me. That's how we confessed
to him in the first place anyway.
I'll respect whatever the outcome is.
Actually, we both know he likes both of us equally,
so how about the person who pleasures him
better gets the right to be his first wife?
And so...
What the...
Good morning, Hajime.
What the heck are you...
You too?
You two... I'm gonna cum!
That's fine. Cum!
Hajime!
I'm cumming!
Hajime...
Do me.
Your cock's inside me!
Wow.
His dick is sliding in and out of you so hard.
I'm gonna cum inside, okay?
I'm gonna fill you up with my semen!
Do it!
I feel it! Your hot semen's pouring inside me!
Me too, Hajime!
You're being so rough!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming so much!
No! I can't stop cumming!
My pussy won't stop cumming!
Right there!
Yes!
It's so good!
You're amazing, Hajime!
I love you!
It's just a feeling, but I'm pretty sure
you impregnated me just now.
Yeah, I think so too. We both definitely
got pregnant from this.
And here we were so hung up on who he loved more.
I promise to never stop loving you two.
And if you're okay with it, I want both
of you to stay by my side forever.
Kimekoi! - Love Decision!
The Reason Why I'm Going after a Girl Out of My League and My Childhood Friend
Part 2
Who's the First Wife?
translation: hikarucon
timing: ragingheartsexcelion
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч