Your lips taste so sweet, Hajime-kun.
You look cute when you're blushing too.
I never thought this would happen.
Hajime-kun, do you know how much I like you?
Let me show you.
Your dick is so tasty, Hajime-kun.
Hey, w-wai...
Holy crap, love pills are the best!
It all started back then.
Yeah, I never thought they'd be this effective.
Who would?
So?
So what does that have to do with you needing the love pill?
Do you know Saginomiya Usagi?
I want to confess to her.
Huh?
I wanted some kind of insurance or more like just
a way to increase the chances of her saying yes.
So I got a love pill from, Misa, but...
Ха-ха...
Hajime-chan!
I can't believe the special ingredient in this thing...
Geez, you're so big, I can't fit it all in my mouth.
It's so quick to react, isn't it, Hajime?
I'm gonna...
I bet you haven't even thought of a way to make her drink this.
I'll throw in a freebie and get her to drink this for you.
A few days later
Morning.
Mornin'.
Saginomiya-san...
She really is out of my league.
I really want to at least be her friend.
Wow she really got her to swallow it!
Thank you!
What's going on with me?
It's been like this since morning.
It's getting so hot.
What's going on?
Hajime-kun...
N-No!
Whenever I think of him, I...
My fingers...
My fingers aren't stopping!
What happened?
Hey, look...
Wait, is that... Is that a side effect of the drug?
Nurse's Office
My fingers... I can't stop my fingers!
What is this?!
I'm getting so sensitive?
If this keeps up, I'm gonna...
This is bad!
No...
Right here...
It feels so... amazing...
Even though I've never done this before...
Why?!
It's not enough! It's not enough!!
My pussy is... My womb is...
They're both craving a dick!
They don't want my fingers, they want a thick dick!
No... I need more! More!!
I want a dick!
Dick!
No... I... I... I...
Oh boy, this is bad.
It looks like it just heightened your sensations.
Don't look!
Being told not to look by a girl who's
masturbating in front of me... What should I do?
I can't help it!
I really... can't... stop!
It's not enough!
It's not nearly enough!
You know something about this, don't you?
Well, how about you come down to the
pharmaceutical club room after school?
You'll understand when you come.
Wait!
Science Prep Room
Geez, Misa...
She said I'd understand if I came here, but...
Well just go and get it over with.
Why do you have to say it like that?
How else should I say it? Even my
first rate drug didn't affect her at all.
It didn't?
It's like she already had feelings for you
so she would've been okay going
out with you even without the drug.
So she's okay?
Yeah, she's fine. Just give her space and she'll be fine.
Now that you get it, go to her already.
She should've left to go to the club room already.
Go already!
Mukouyama-kun...
Um...
I need to stop this!
Uh, are you feeling okay?
Um, Saginomiya-san?
Mukouyama-kun...
I came here because Misa told me to come here, but...
Why did you...
Why did you c-come here...
Uh, I...
I, uh...
Saginomiya-san,
no, Megumi-san?
I like you.
How do you feel about me?
I-I...
The way I feel about you?
Can you tell?
It's bad.
After you said you liked me, I...
I want you!
I want you so bad, I can't help it.
Me-Megumi-san...
It's unseemly, isn't it?
I'm so wet aren't I?
Y-Yeah...
Yeah, you're wet.
You're incredibly wet.
It's dripping to the ground.
I want you!
It's crying because it wants you so bad!
It wants your dick so bad, Hajime-kun!
It's gotten this wet because it wants you so bad!
Megumi-san...
You're okay with this, right?
Yeah.
After all, I like you.
Please take my first time.
Hajime-kun!
Hajime-kun, that feels so good!
Hajime-kun, I want to do it too.
So this is your dick...
It's so wonderful.
How is it so wonderful?
– If you suck it that hard...
– Wonderful, so wonderful!
Hajime-kun, your dick is so amazing.
It's so energetic.
I want this... inside me.
Megumi-san...
Hajime-kun!
That's...
So good... Hajime-kun!
Oh my god, you're licking my pussy!
It feels so good!
Hajime-kun!
Hajime-kun? Put your dick inside my pussy!
Shove it deep inside me all at once!
Yeah, I was gonna do that.
Ah, it's inside!
Hajime-kun's dick...
It's so amazing!
No...
So good!
My womb feels so good!
Hajime-kun!
No...
It's gushing out...
It's so hot...
You're not an animal, how'd that work on you?
I thought that'd make you give up on her, but...
My plan backfired on me, huh?
I really messed up.
Hajime-kun!
I feel like something even more
amazing's right around the corner.
These love pills are the best!
Love Decision!
The reason why I'm going after a girl out of my league and my childhood friend
Part 1 The magic drug that makes my romances come true
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч