We're in the girls' restroom!
Wait... Hajime-kun!
Jeez!
I did something bad to you yesterday.
Something bad?
What I mean is,
I didn't wear a condom and
suddenly came inside you.
You getting knocked up won't be a surprise.
K-Knocked up?
That's right.
Won't you get pregnant if I come inside you?
W-Well, that's...
I'll take responsibility.
I'm glad that you feel that way,
but it's not a sure thing that
I'll get pregnant so easily.
I was avoiding you earlier today,
but it's not because of that reason.
And I never once thought
that you've been cruel on me!
Glad to hear that, Megumi-san.
Just call me Megumi.
That feels good...So good!
No!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
Wow, your dick is inside me!
It's throbbing inside!
Shoot them all out inside my pussy!
Amazing!
A lot of stuff happened after that time.
Megumi and I became lovers, but...
I feel like you just got me caught up
in all of this and you don't even care.
That's... Well, yeah...
I've been trying to think on what to do about it.
Oh well, you somehow both ended up
being lovey-dovey so it's all good.
Well then, I'm done playing as your
cupid so you'll have to excuse me.
Misa, are you alright with leaving us just like that?
W-What are you saying?
The truth is you love Hajime-kun too, right?
What's all of this out of nowhere?
If you really have no feelings for him,
then take a HoreKime pill.
F-Fine! I'll just have to swallow one, right?
W-What's the big deal?
It's not like I thought that Hajime has been
kind of cool lately or anything, okay?
Hajime...
A-Are you alright, Misa?
Why did you take that much dosage of the drug?
That's because I won't be able to be...
true to myself if I don't take plenty of it.
I'm already... like this!
I love you!
You're finally being honest with your feelings.
You make it sound like it's good,
but are you alright with drugging your friend?
Hajime-kun, show me the man that you are!
Are you not my boyfriend?
Hajime... I love you!
Wait... Misa!
Here, here. Let's show him your body?
Here... If you won't say it properly,
your feelings might not reach him!
No... I... I love you, Hajime!
I love you so much!
I peed on Hajime-kun!
Misa, you really loved Hajime-kun so much.
Forgive me for asking for advice about love
not knowing about how you feel.
It's because I have this conceited personality.
I've always been withdrawn in the class.
But even so, Hajime befriended me.
He's always around and always
helps me one way or another.
Of course I'd fall for him!
Hey, Hajime-kun.
I want you to reciprocate her feelings just this once.
Hajime... I want you to accept
my feelings if you won't mind.
Megumi, Misa, are you both fine with this?
It's our first kiss.
It soothes my heart somehow.
I've been feeling fuzzy in the past few days,
and I couldn't even properly take my sleep.
And this is our second kiss.
Right... That's right.
I actually gave my first kiss with this cutie.
Can I take your first now?
Okay!
This will only belong to you forever!
So please love me a lot, okay?
Good!
Are you alright, Misa?
If it hurts that much, should I pull out first?
Nah, It's getting better now.
I ran out of ingredients to
make more HoreKime drug.
But I'd love it if you will be gentle on me.
Alright.
I see...
Being left out watching would
really build up some stress...
He wasn't gentle with me at that time...
It's somehow unfair.
Your penis is incredible, Hajime!
I can feel it inside my belly!
Your pounding is reverberating inside!
I'll be coming any time soon...
Yes! Alright!
Squirt to my deepest parts! Shoot as much as you can!
Fill my pussy up with your semen until it overflows of it!
T-That's not good! What if you get pregnant?
What will you do when that happens?
When that happens...
Right... I'll take responsibility of course.
I'm... I'm gonna come!
I'll be coming... plenty inside you, alright?
Your semen! It's pouring in me!
So good! It feels so good!
Your semen is filling up my womb!
Coming... I'm coming... I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Yeah... There are still various issues
I'd like to point out about us three,
but after seeing Misa's sleeping face like this, I'm now lost for words.
With that said, it looked like the issue
among us three was already settled...
But it turned out that the world
is not such a gentle place...
There you go again, Misa.
You really love joking around.
I've been telling you that I'm not joking.
Let me ask you then.
How did you become his girlfriend,
while I became the No.2 girl instead?
Don't you think that the one who came
later should step back and make way.
Well, well well, but you just said it earlier,
that it doesn't matter who's the first or last one.
Fine.
We'll make our HoreKime drug
and then make Hajime take it.
Yeah, when he's already high with both our HoreKime,
Let's have him decide which
one he chooses between us.
But I'm sure that he'll say he love us both.
Then it should be like, whoever
can make him feel good more
will become the legal wife, right?
And then...
Good morning, Hajime!
Wait... You... What are you doing—
Wait... Megumi!
Megumi, Misa... I'm gonna come!
Okay... Come!
Hajime!
I'm coming!
Hajime...
Give it to me as well.
Your dick is inside!
Wow...
Megumi's pussy is chomping Hajime's dick in!
Megumi, I'm gonna come, okay?
I'm gonna defile your womb with my semen!
Come inside!
Your hot semen! It's pouring in me!
Hajime! Me too!
That's too sudden!
Coming... Coming... Coming!
I'm coming!
No... I just keep on coming!
I can't stop my pussy from coming!
Incredible!
Oh no!
Oh my! It feels so good!
Hajime!
I love you!
I know this is kind of far-fetched,
but I feel so sure that you got me pregnant.
Yeah, I'm sure you got pregnant with this.
Coz with that much love, I'd feel down even if I won.
I swear to love both of you from now on.
I'd love to have you both by my side,
if you're fine with someone like me.
KimeKoi!
The Reason Chosen by the
Flower of the High Cliff
and My Childhood Friend
KimeKoi!
The Reason Chosen by the
Flower of the High Cliff
and My Childhood Friend
Final
Chapter
Which one is the legal wife?
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project