U-Um, please put your cum...
Into this top idol's pussy already!
Alyssa-chan's pussy is being spread so much!
There are magical beings called "witches"
that exist in this world.
Th-There's no way that I feel good
from something like a dick.
So hot!
It's spreading into my womb!
It's just pumping out inside of me.
They store magic particles called mana
within themselves and then release it as magic.
The only way for them to build up mana
within themselves is with the semen of a man.
So basically that means that me,
the biggest supplier of mana in the school.
Oh, your dick! It's destroying my baby room!
I can really hear the sound of the semen inside me!
Pump your semen full of mana
inside of me while everyone's watching!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
Your raw semen is pouring into me!
Sperm... sperm... sperm...
It means that I can have sex
all I want with the elite witches!
What are you smiling about?
O-Oh... I was just remembering something from the past.
It was probably just some kind of sexual fantasy, wasn't it?
You pervert.
Y-You're just imagining it.
Yes? Right.
That's all I have to report.
I understand...
Furuike-sensei said that when we get back...
you need to go to the staff room.
Your magical name is Rina Witch
Your magical name is Rina Witch.
Idol familia
Good work on the mission, Iizuka.
First, have a look at this.
Okay.
This is the data of your mana replenishing activities.
Is this...
That's right.
Both Koyanagi and Alyssa's mana limit has...
dramatically increased this month.
Alyssa=Rina/Tanaka
Class: Witch
Ranking: A-Class
Gender: Female
Height: 159cm
Three Sizes: 93/95/89
прикольные размеры. гы-гы...
Koyanagi Rina
Class: Witch
Ranking: A-Class
Gender: Female
Height: 151cm
Three Sizes: 88/53/79
However, though their mana replenishment
should be increasing through pleasure,
it doesn't seem like that's happening.
So that means that my technique is lacking?!
That means that I haven't been satisfying them at all, right?
Exactly.
This may sound harsh, but...
If this continues, you'll only serve as a burden to them.
We might even have to disband your team.
No, that's the last thing that I want to happen!
Then you'll need to improve your technique, Iizuka.
If you really don't want to be separated from one another,
then try and get through tomorrow's special training.
I don't care what kind of training it is.
I'm gonna get through it!
I talk big, but all I'm doing is causing those two trouble.
Toshiya-kun!
My heart all about it.
We heard all about it.
You're pathetic, but we'll help you out.
Alyssa-chan... you're so cute!
Toshiya-kun, that being said, we'll make sure that we give
the special training tomorrow everything we have, okay?
What?!
I'm not helping him out of kindness,
I'm just worried about my standing. That's it.
Thanks you two.
Don't get the wrong idea! I-I'm not doing this beca...
I can't betray their feelings!
Mana Witch
Alyssa-chan Handshake Event
You're looking just as cute as always, Alyssa-chan!
Oh, thank you!
Please do come again!
It's been a while!
How have you been doing?
Oh, it's nothing.
Please come see my show again!
Okay Alyssa-chan, you can take a break now.
I did it. I survived!
Alyssa-sama's Dressing Room
Hurry up and take it out already!
This is supposed to be training
for mana replenishment, right?
Hurry up and get it over with!
That aside, idols really do have a lot of fans, huh?
Of course we do.
Let's turn this on.
No, Toshiya! My uniform's gonna
get dirty from my ass-juices!
Alyssa-san, are you okay?
I-I'm perfectly... fine!
I'm having my partner massage me!
If you keep moaning like that, somebody's gonna notice.
Oh no, they'll hear me!
They're gonna hear my dirty voice...
It's just that, you're making a lot of noise...
This massage is just too good.
I can't hold my voice back because
it's so good. It's embarrassing,
so if you could just distance yourself from here, I'd...
Let's turn it up!
There. If you drop the vibrator, you're gonna get punished.
I... I'll be out soon!
I-I'll see you soon.
Toshiya, the vibrator's falling out.
I can't let it because I'll be punished, but...
I'm gonna cum with my ass and my pussy at the same time!
No!
It's falling out of my asshole!
I hate this! I hate punishment!
I'm not a bad girl.
It's my asshole that just let it out by itself.
Don't worry, Alyssa.
My punishment is that?
Nope.
This is special training for mana replenishment,
so of course we're gonna have sex, right?
Don't put it in all at once!
The real punishment comes after this!
You're the worst!
I had my anal virginity stolen by a pervert
who gets turned on by bullying girls!
So I guess I'm the only one getting turned on by this?
You're not... in your right mind if you enjoy having anal sex!
Your virgin asshole is the best, Alyssa!
If you keep widening my asshole with your dick like that...
It's never gonna close again!
Please stop now!
Or else what? You'll cum!
I'm not that perverted!
I'm not gonna cum with my ass!
Then I'm just gonna cum by myself.
Let your ass taste the flavor of my cum!
Stop being weird!
Just shut your mouth already!
Don't tease my asshole anymore!
It's gonna flow out of my asshole!
You're still cumming.
You came too much.
Okay then, this is where the punishment starts.
Alyssa-sama's Dressing Room
I'm so glad that I'm able to see you again, Alyssa-chan!
Thank you.
You look kinda sexy today.
Th-That's not...
True...
Isn't that Rina-chan from Mana Witch?
There's no way she'd be out here dressed like that.
But that girl really has a hot body.
I wanna do horrible things to her tits and ass.
Toshiya-kun?
I bought them.
Thanks.
How was it?
I was hoping for a more normal
special training, that's why I wore this...
Rina
Well, both you and Alyssa are idols, so you're pretty famous.
I had to really thing hard about how I was
gonna take you outside into the public like this.
This is the first time I've done this in my life.
But it turned you on, didn't it?
Actually, I've been so nervous
that my legs won't stop shaking.
All right then, how about we sit down?
Okay.
But...
This position...
Toshiya-kun, your thing is hitting me!
You're getting real hot down here, huh?
We can't!
Not out here.
It'll be fine as long as you keep it down.
No. I can't. There's no way I can!
You're so big and hard right now!
I'm getting so turned on!
Now!
You just stuck all of it in me all of a sudden.
My pussy's not even ready yet...
My hips are just moving on their own!
I feel so tingly! My hips aren't stopping!
You need to hide your face with the sunglasses
or else people will recognize you.
Th-That's too hard!
Because of your dick, I can't stop moving!
Your dick feels so good!
Your dick is twitching which means something, right?
It means that it likes my pussy, right?
I want to make this special training work
for the sake of this dick that I love so much!
Hey, that'd be Mana Witch's new song, right?
Yeah. It's a great song, isn't it?
Rina-chan's part is just perfect too.
Don't say that when I'm having
a dick shoved into me right now.
You've attracted the gaze of so many people.
I bet a lot of them are gonna go home
and masturbate with you in their minds.
I'm gonna be violated?
People are gonna use me to masturbate?
People are gonna fantasize about me and masturbate?
I'm getting so turned on, my pussy's getting so hot!
Give it to my pussy! We might be found out, but I don't care!
All I want is your milk, your semen, inside my pussy!
Kiss my womb with your dick!
Toshiya-kun! Cum! Cum!
Let's cum together!
I'm cumming!
Rina!
Your cum is rushing into me!
There's so much of the dick milk
that I love coming inside me!
I'm gonna pee!
Your dick is amazing!
Breathe out a kind, pale breath.
Recite a verse that no reader would know.
There's no use if it doesn't hit!
You can see the results of the special training.
What I want to do?
Well, we've already done a lot of dirty things together...
So you should already know
what I want without asking me, right?
Yeah, of course. I know.
Huh?
R-Really?
W-Well isn't that surprising.
All right then, let's go now.
Wait! Wait just a second!
Shopping District by the Station
Rack Drog Store
Why did it end up like this?
You wanted to go for a walk naked
with a vibrator in you, didn't you?
Who would want that?!
Hey, come on. If you're not focused,
the magic you're using to hide yourself is gonna wear off.
I know that!
This doesn't make me feel good at all!
Then let's make it a little stronger then.
Huh? I thought I heard somebody
scream for a second there.
A girl?
No... maybe a cat.
They're gonna see me!
My dirty voice is gonna be heard by so many men.
I've been hearing weird sounds too.
Is a hole somewhere leaking?
Don't look!
Don't look at my embarrassing place!
Don't look at my pussy leaking!
Let's go to the next place.
No, stop. You're moving too fast.
My legs can't keep up.
Oh, no! It's coming out!
Don't look!
Stop!
Please stop!
This isn't right! Why am I getting turned on by this?!
Don't cry so much, Alyssa.
But this is just too embarrassing!
I can't take it anymore!
Toshiya!
There there.
I'll comfort you.
Your dick...
Your dick's coming inside me.
No! No!
If you squeeze me so tightly, I'm gonna...
I... I can't help it! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too!
Your juice is coming inside me! It's flowing deep inside me!
Oh my god, it's digging inside me!
My head's going crazy!
My magic's gonna turn off!
If this keeps up, I'm gonna become the Perverted Witch Idol!
It's all because of your dick, Toshiya!
I can't hold my moans back!
You're gonna cum while having
people listen to your moans, right?
Yeah! When you cum, my magic's gonna disappear!
Cum, Alyssa!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's cumming!
Everyone saw me!
But at least your magic's gotten stronger.
Story land
Toshiya-kun, my dream is to...
Welcome.
How I want to replenish my mana?
You know, before I became an idol,
I wanted to do things to make people happy.
Isn't that the job of an idol?
No.
To be more specific, I wanted to make guys happy.
Do you mean that...
Now, please excuse me.
Dear customer, your scent and your manly body...
I love them so much!
Your nipples are already hard, I see.
Your nipples are erect like your dick.
Don't worry, I'll take good care of your dick too.
I've made sure to study all of your erogenous spots.
How is it? You play with my breasts like this all the time.
I never thought it could feel this good.
Because of you, my nipples have become very strange.
Your dick is getting bigger.
Does that mean that you're about to ejaculate?
Yeah!
I'm just about there!
You're going to cum, right?
Please don't hold back and cum whenever you'd like.
Would you please show me how you cum?
Please hurry and cum!
Rina, I'm cumming!
It's cumming!
Your cum...
It's soaking my body.
There's still...
Semen...
Left for me to drink, right?
Rina!
How does it feel?
Do my wet, lubed boobs feel good?
It's so big, hard, and amazing.
And it's so tasty!
Your pre-cum is so tasty, it almost tastes like the real deal.
It's swelling up.
You can shoot it out whenever you want, okay?
I can't let her take the lead like this.
D-Dear customer?!
Please don't!
I'm the one who is supposed to...
No!
Don't lick my pussy!
Let's feel good together.
He's making me feel good
with his tongue while I'm working!
Let's cum together then!
Please shoot your load into my throat pussy!
That feels good!
I'm going to cum too!
I'm cumming!
You still have some services left to do, right?
Of course.
Next, do you think you could...
Use my pussy to entertain yourself?
Please allow me to service you with your
own private pussy, for you and you only!
I'm gonna go all out at once!
Come.
Come deep inside my pussy!
So deep!
Your rock hard dick!
It's already cummed twice, but it's still so hard and hot!
There...
It's hitting all the g-spots!
It's doing a deep kiss with my womb! So good!
The entrance to your womb really is sensitive, huh?
You've showed me that countless times!
Now my womb expects it!
It's gotten better at squeezing your dick tightly!
Your dick's twitching so much,
I feel like my pussy's gonna explode!
Does that mean you're gonna cum?
Yes! My womb's already...
But...
I'll make sure to hold on until you cum!
Please let out a lot of your cum whenever you'd like!
I'll cum soon, okay?
Okay!
Please let my pussy taste more
of the only cum I've tasted in my life!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum with the semen flowing inside of me!
It's coming out...
There's still so much coming out.
So much dick milk...
This is the end!
Thanks to that special training,
this level of attack is a piece of cake now.
It's because we all tried really hard together.
Let's keep doing our best and doing whatever
we can to keep the world safe, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: akin
encoder: bakaproxy
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч