後向きで歩いて見たら
ushiromuki de aru ittemitara
when I walk while facing backwards
意外と広がってるかもよ
igai to hirogatteru kamo yo
the world seems to be wider than I thought
大勢の一部でしかない君
oozei no ichibu de shikanai kimi
you are but a part of the whole crowd
私は嫌いじゃないけどね
watashi wa kirai ja nai kedo ne
though I don't hate the way you are
動き始める予感がする
ugokihajimeru yokan ga suru
I get the feeling that I should start moving
そこから踏み出すために
soko kara fumidasu tame ni
and that's when I make a step
何か止める必要などはないさ
nanika yameru hitsuyou nado wa nai sa
there isn't any reason to stop
行こうよ、手は握いて
ikou yo, te wa nigiite
hold my hand and let's go
上げる風で帽子が壊され
ageru kaze de boushi ga kowasare
may our hats not be broken
ないように
nai you ni
by the wind blowing ever stronger
High Aspirations
Shimuro Aikido Doujou
Your breathing out of rhythm, Shin'ichirou.
Focus on your training.
Ugh...
I've been working hard so that I could
get closer to Aoi-senpai's level.
Senpai is someone who is talented
enough to even inherit the doujou.
She's a goal beyond my reach.
Let's end it here for today.
Huh?!
It will be trouble for me if you get injured.
I'm sorry.
Was my effort all for naught?
Shin'ichirou.
Huh?
Will it be fine to consult you about something?
I don't think someone like me would
be of any help for you, though...
It has to be with you who's a childhood friend of mine.
It can't be anyone else.
Aoi-senpai, what is it that you
want to consult me for?
I'm bad at dealing with men.
You know about that, right?
And you also can't spar with any men
besides me, your childhood friend.
That's—!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Be more careful!
Okay...
Hasn't the number of pupils that I have to coach
in place of my father increased lately?
I won't be able to uphold our
reputation if I stay this way, right?
And so this massage is to get you
used on being around with men,
So, this is supposedly an "endurance training".
You can say that...
So, this means that she doesn't see me as a man.
There's no point to continue attending in this doujou...
Huh?
Did you say something?
Nah, I didn't.
Shin'ichirou, you look kind of strange.
Please don't bother about me.
Don't bother on what?
Hmm?
Ahh...
That's so obscene!
I'm sorry! My hand slipped...
I'm sorry as well...
It's also because of carelessness on my part.
To think that I'm shaken up
by trivial matters like this...
I really am ashamed of myself...
Senpai...
If you can't bear even something like this,
you won't be able to overcome your fear
of men no matter how much time passes.
You're right, but...
I have a suggestion...
What is it?
High Aspirations
I'm done with preparations.
What preparations?
Why is there a need for me to be blindfolded?
This training will be useless if
you know where I'll touch you.
I-Is that so?
Alright, let's begin.
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
Hey! That's my...
Please endure it.
I  understand...
Don't touch me there!
This is a training!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Please bear with me!
Stop teasing my sensitive spots!
Hey, are you listening?!
If you can endure this, you should
be able to maintain your posture!
I understand...
I'm gonna go a little rougher on you, alright?
Rougher?
Senpai, please don't move.
What are you—
I feel something hot on my breasts!
Hey, stop doing that!
Shin'ichirou, stop it already!
The tip is rubbing against me!
Senpai!
Don't be so rough on me!
That's enough for my endurance training!
Shin'ichirou!
I'm coming already!
Coming? What are you talking about?
H-Hey, stop!
What is this smell?
What did you just do...
What's the meaning of this?!
Senpai, this isn't what it looks like!
I don't know what came over me!
My conscience is clear!
Is your conscience really as clear as you say?
I should believe what you're saying, right?
Tell me the truth!
Please forgive me!
I always thought about wanting to be
in a relationship with you, Aoi-senpai.
Huh?
It's nothing but a one-sided love.
I know that someone like me isn't suited for you...
And that my efforts are all in vain...
Is that how you've been thinking all this time?
He confessed his love to me...
It's my first time getting one...
I always thought of him as
nothing but a childhood friend...
Shin'ichirou...
Huh? What am I doing?!
You're angry because of what I did yesterday, right?
No... I'm not angry.
Huh?
I'm aware of it.
I know how much have you been
working hard, Shin'ichirou.
So don't say depressing stuff
like all your efforts were in vain.
Aoi-senpai...
I am no good at dealing with men.
But thanks to your diligence...
See?
Senpai!
I can now touch you just like this.
Do you still think that all
your efforts were in vain?
No...
Hmm!
I'm all sweaty right now. Are you fine with that?
I don't mind.
Umm...
I want you to be gentle.
Okay.
He can see everything...
I can feel his breath... It tickles!
He's licking my important place...
If he keeps touching it in a very naughty manner...
Won't I end up getting wet?
Aoi-senpai!
I never got a good look at it yesterday.
I never thought that it could get this thick...
Alright then, I'll get right into it.
Yeah... I'll leave all of it up to you.
I can feel my strength leaving out of my body!
Aoi-senpai!
Just wait!
Don't just move all of a sudden!
Hey, listen to what I'm saying!
You're being way too reckless!
So, this is your body heat... It feels so warm!
Don't thrust it that deep inside me!
This is bad, I'm starting to lose sight of my standing.
He's a younger boy I knew ever since we're
young and thought of like a cute puppy...
To think that he's having his way on my body...
It's reaching my deepest parts
like it's gouging me out!
I can feel his pulse with his palpitation!
Ugh, I'm coming!
Huh, inside me?
What is this sensation?
It's like my consciousness is fading...
It feels like you're scraping my insides!
You sprayed it all over me again...
I'm sorry!
This is supposed to be my first time.
Won't you be a little more gentle to me?
Will this be alright?
Yes.
I'll start moving, okay?
Okay...
This position is great!
You're hitting right at the spot where it feels good!
Does it not hurt?
You can go deeper inside me...
That feels great!
I'll push it in deeper!
My body went limp now!
It's the same scraping sensation again!
My body feels so hot!
Senpai, you're squeezing me tightly!
Don't say stuff like that!
If you're going to shoot your semen,
then pour it all inside me!
Now that I'm looking at it,
isn't it quite a cute thing?
Aoi-senpai?
You came such a huge amount...
It means that you love me that much, huh?
Senpai, you're beautiful beyond belief—
Huh... Why did it grow big again?
My lust won't subside so easily.
Oh, well...
How is it? Are you feeling good?
Can you feel how my insides are?
You really like my breasts that much, huh?
I can't show this improper state
I'm in to anyone but you!
Senpai, you're beautiful no matter how you look!
Stop saying embarrassing stuff!
Your thing feels so good!
My feelings are in disarray!
That's right.
Nothing else matters anymore!
I'm all yours now!
Didn't you endure all those hardships?
Or rather, weren't you lonely?
Keep pouring more of it into me!
Taint my insides with your stuff!
I can't think of anything else anymore!
Nothing else... I can't anymore!
I'm gonna come!
I swear...
I'll surely become a man befitting of you, Aoi-senpai!
Shin'ichirou...
High Aspirations
So that I can get the honor
to stand right next to you...
Yes, I believe in you.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization