Good morning, Kensuke-kun.
Aren't you Shiina Kasumi-chan, the girl
who just transferred in yesterday?
Why are you here?
What do you mean, "Why"? I'm here to wake you up. And...
I found out that you've gotten pretty hard down there.
Look at this.
Guys sure are energetic.
Kasumi-chan...
If guys can't hold it in, they masturbate like this, right?
What's going on?
Why is Kasumi-chan doing this?
Jeez, it's so sticky already.
But that's a natural reaction.
It's so slippery.
You know, my panties are getting wet as well.
Look at the juices flowing out.
Look at it, Kensuke-kun.
Kensuke-kun, look at it carefully.
K-Kasumi-chan...
When girls can't hold it in, they...
Kasumi-chan!
Your nipples are getting hard.
So are yours!
I-I'm feeling weird.
I'm going to cum, Kasumi-chan!
Kensuke-kun!
I-I'm cumming!
This is your...
Wow, you came a lot.
I-I'm sorry.
Speaking of which, it looks like it's still hard.
Hey, want to do it?
Oh... Oh God!
Kasumi-chan...
Kensuke-kun, harder... harder!
This is amazing!
I'm starting to get numb down there.
Crap, I'm gonna cum.
Let's cum together!
Kasumi-chan...
Cum, Kensuke-kun... cum inside me!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too!
What's the matter? Are you okay?
It was a dream!?
Kimihagu
Episode 1
Kumhagu
Morning!
Why did I have that dream?
The colors, the sensation of touch,
and the melting feeling when I put it in there were so real!
I guess I have a thing for Kasumi-chan.
Both of you, being in a relationship is against the school rules.
A students job is to study.
Love can wait.
As long as I'm around, I won't allow anything
that destroys our school's morale!
Minami.
She's being a busybody as usual.
Seriously, it's none of her business, is it?
Wait, dating is banned at our school?
Yeah, it got banned when that Yuuki
Emiri became the disciplinarian.
I don't give a damn if she's the principal's
daughter or whatever.
I can't believe she changed the school rules by herself.
Oh?
What do you mean by "Oh"?
Because of her, my club was forced underground and
has to hold its meetings in the church basement!
Mi-Minami!
Kasumi-chan?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Morning.
Good morning.
Why are you in such a rush?
I wanted to go borrow a book before class starts.
Umm, is the library is over there?
Yeah. Oh, so you like to read?
Kensuke, why don't you show her the way?
It's the real deal!
No, forget that.
Wh-What?
You love the library, don't you?
The library? I haven't even been there.
W-Well...
I'll be fine by myself.
Thank you very much, though.
Kensuke...
She just got here. Why can't you be a little more helpful!?
Fine.
I tried to create a chance for the two of you to be alone.
Why don't you mind your own business?
You're such a sore loser.
So let's have Kensuke-kun and Madoka-san go on a date.
Love Club
D-Date?
Go home and get ready, and then meet
at the fountain in front of the station.
Dating is basic to the art of love.
So I think this will definitely be a valuable experience.
All right!
I've never gone on a date before.
I'd be fine with Minami,
but with Madoka-chan? Dang, I'm nervous.
You've never been on a date before?
What a bummer.
Senpai? Senpai?
Y-Yes?
To be honest, I've never been on a date.
Oh, really?
So please take good care of me!
D-Don't worry.
There's a first time for everything.
Let's try our best.
Okay!
Kensuke-senpai, you're so reliable!
Isn't this your first date as well? Quit acting tough.
Innocence makes you cute.
Should we go have something with meat for lunch?
It's the first time I've used my cell for this kind of thing.
Kensuke-senpai...
Madoka-chan!
Did I make you wait a long time?
Nope, I arrived not long ago.
Oh, I didn't know this is what you wear casually.
No, I picked this just for our date.
I thought it would add to the atmosphere.
Umm,
does it look bad on me?
No, you look really cute.
I'm glad.
I wonder if they'll be all right.
Isn't that why we're here to spy?
Follow me.
My heart is thumping really hard.
Yeah.
I guess you could say were a couple for the day.
Oh? I didn't think Madoka-san would have the guts to do that.
Really!
What's the point if Madoka-chan is
the one who takes the initiative?
I wonder how this will turn out.
Miren-senpai, are you enjoying this?
Why did you join the Love Club?
I've always been really shy,
so I never had much confidence in myself.
So I thought joining the club would help me change.
O-Oh, really?
What about you?
Oh, me? Well...
Minami forced me into it, and... uh... well...
Kensuke! Kensuke!
Look at this!
Look, it's a love letter!
Love letter?
It's from Jimiko!
Jimiko?
Umm... Give that back, please.
Let's see.
To Kisaki Kensuke-sama,
I've always been aware of you.
Huh?
This is great, Kensuke!
Go out with her!
Jimiko and Kensuke sitting in a tree...
Cut it out!
Damn, I can feel the heat from here.
I said to cut it out!
Kensuke, just go out with her.
I don't even like Jimiko!
I can see your panties!
At the end of the letter were words of parting.
Before long, I found out she was transferring out.
I hurt a girl by saying some really terrible things.
Ever since then, I've lacked the courage to pursue love.
Madoka-chan, over here!
Why this sudden rain!?
Anyway, let's go find a place to take shelter.
This place is...
a love hotel, isn't it?
I didn't even notice.
What the hell am I doing?
Umm, Kensuke-senpai...
Yes?
I guess people think we're lovers.
That's why I decided to become bolder.
I don't think I should run away from here.
Kensuke-senpai, am I not good enough for you?
No, not that... Well...
All that work for nothing.
I wonder if they'll be all right.
Hopefully nothing happens.
If nothing happened on a date, it d be boring.
Are you sure about this?
Yes. Please go ahead.
Wow. This is a girls breast.
Her breasts look heavy, but they're really soft.
Kensuke-senpai...
This is amazing.
It's different from when I touch myself.
How is it different?
My heart is thumping harder than usual.
And I'm getting really hot.
Take this off if you're feeling hot.
No!
Don't worry. It won't be embarrassing.
Show me your breasts.
You breasts are big and beautiful.
Are you getting turned on?
No...
But your nipples are telling me otherwise.
That's...
D-Don't do that.
Wow, they're pretty stretchy.
It's not lair for you to have all the fun!
I want to...
Kensuke-senpai, it's hot as well.
M-Madoka-chan?
Huh? Does it feel bad?
No, I'm just a bit surprised.
Should I use my mouth instead?
It tastes really good.
I'm cumming!
Please cum inside me next.
Are you okay?
Don't worry about me and start moving.
All right, then.
Don't bite my breasts.
And lewd sounds are coming from down there.
Senpai, make me feel better.
How's this? Does it feel good?
Yes!
Wouldn't this... be even better?
My breasts again...
No... No!
Madoka-chan, I'm going to cum!
Me too!
Just a little more!
Don't hold back. Just cum inside me!
I came inside her.
I'm glad we were connected till the last moment.
What are you doing here!?
Uh, well...
Miren-senpai told me to pass on a message.
A message for me?
Yeah, she'll be busy during tonight's confession session,
so she was wondering if she could switch with you.
Tonight!?
I have my own plans as well.
I see.
Well then, go talk to Miren-senpai about it.
Whit!
About yesterday's date...
What did you do with Madoka-chan after that?
Alter that?
I'm asking how the date turned but!
Well, it was just a normal date.
What?
Kensuke, ever since you were little, you always
looked away when you were lying.
Spit it out!
Something happened, right!?
Let go!
You idiot!
I'm sorry, Kensuke.
Are you angry?
No, but I'm soaking wet now.
I'll lend you my T-shirt and jersey.
What are you doing?
Wet pants are heavy.
It's easier to take them off when you're still in the pool.
It... It's fine...
Don't worry. No ones here to see.
Stop!
Hey, stop! Cut it out!
Your boxers came off as well.
Minami!?
No, at this rate...
What's with this?
Well, after seeing you in your swimsuit...
I'm really happy.
I can't believe that I turned you on.
I'm not as cute as Kasumi-chan.
My breasts aren't as big as her's either.
That's why I'm happy you think of me as a girl.
Minami...
It's so hard.
It tastes strange.
Something's coming out.
That's great.
Wait, if you do that...
No, I'm not going to wait.
I want to make you feel good as well.
Minami...
This is embarrassing.
It's easier to put it in this way.
Are you okay, Minami?
It hurts a little, but I'm line.
I've finally become one with you.
Kensuke, if you pound me like that...
I'm going to scream with pleasure!
You made me feel like I was in heaven,
so I'm going to have to return the favor.
It's deep inside me.
It's amazing!
It's the first time I've see you look so erotic.
That's because you keep making me feel good.
But you don't hate it, right?
Let's kiss, Kensuke.
Please...
That was my first kiss.
Wow. I can hear weird noises from down there.
And my insides are trembling.
You're getting tighter.
That's because you're...
No! You re getting bigger!
I'm getting even more turned on now,
because you're so perverted!
No, stop it.
I'm going to feel weird!
I'm sorry! I can't hold it in, Minami!
It's okay Kensuke, cum!
Your semen is so hot.
So that's how it turned out.
I died!
Who the hell would stop by this late at night?
Someone's here.
I heard you'll listen to peoples troubles.
Y-Yes.
I can't believe someone s actually here.
I guess I can look at her face.
Kasumi-chan?
Umm, is everything said here going to be confidential?
Yes, of course.
What could Kasumi-chan's problem be?
I have someone I like.
But I was rejected once before.
I want to confess again, but I don't have the courage to do it.
I'm afraid I'll get rejected again.
You're kidding me.
She's liked that guy for a long time,
so that means it can't be me.
Am I out of luck?