I heard you'll listen to people's troubles.
Y-Yes.
Yes.
What could Kasumi-chan's problem bet?
I have someone I like.
But I was rejected once before.
I want to confess again, but I don't have the courage to do it.
I'm afraid I'll get rejected again.
You're kidding me.
She's liked that guy for a long time,
so that mean it can't be me.
Aw I out of luck?
Kimihagu
Episod 2
Love Club
Sorry I'm late.
Good evening, Miren-senpai!
Good evening!
Oh? Kensuke-kiin's nowhere yet?
Well, uh...
He's here already.
Whatever. I'm not suited for her anyway.
He's been depressed since we discovered him like that.
Kensuke-senpai, cheer up!
I shouldn't have been born into this world.
Yeah, I'm just a stupid clown.
What happened?
Well, we tried asking him,
but he's in his own world, so we don't really know.
Oh, I see.
Yeah. That means I've lost my chance.
Based on what you just said, that would seem to be correct.
I knew it.
Cheer tip.
What you need to do now is find a new love.
That's easier said than done.
How about I pretend to be your girlfriend to cheer you up?
I mean, it's my fault for making you stay there last night.
Kensuke-kun, what'd you like me to do to cheer yd up?
I'm sorry.
I'm still an amateur at being at alone with a girl.
And yeah, I don't really know what to do.
How about I give you some suggestions?
What would you suggest?
You know, there are lots of things I
want to try when I get a boyfriend.
Could you help me with that?
Sure...
Umm, Miren-senpai?
What?
"Things I'd like to try"?
You know, despite the fact that I'm
the president of the Love Club,
I haven't gone out with anyone yet.
So, I'd like to try it once.
Jeez, your penis is leaking juice.
That's because...
You're so dirty.
It's a little bitter.
Kensuke-kun, do you like this? Does it feel good?
It's getting harder by the second in my mouth.
I-I don't know.
Just cum whenever you want.
Dammit, I can't hold back.
Crap!
Don't worry. You can let it all out.
I'm.... I'm cumming!
W-Wow!
Did that feel good?
Yeah, it was awesome.
That's great. It's my turn next.
I'm surprised you're the type who
likes to peek from underneath.
No, uh...
I'm just kidding. You can do whatever you want.
All right.
I didn't expect-
Wow...
It's so wet.
W-Well, that's only natural after I gave you a blowjob.
So you got wet when you were giving me head.
No! Don't say it out loud!
I can make you feel better, right?
No! That's my clitoris.
I can't hold back anymore.
I want your... I really want it.
I want to put it in as well
It's huge.
Are you okay?
It didn't hurt as much as I expected.
Does it feel good?
My breasts are sensitive.
Your nipples are huge when they get stiff.
No! Don't say that.
This is amazing as well!
Miren-senpai, you're so lewd.
Don't play with my breasts so much.
I'm going to cum again.
It's okay. Just cum. I'm going to cum too.
But at this rate...
Don't worry. You can cum inside me.
I'm cumming!
It's flowing into me.
Miren-senpai...
Do you feel a bit better now?
Yeah.
This is my first time being in a library since elementary school.
I love the library.
Patrolling during lunch break is a tough job.
No, I mustn't do this.
But I really can't stop!
This is amazing.
There's no rule against masturbating while in school.
I'm not breaking any rues!
I... I really want to be fucked in the toilet!
Hey, we're going to fill up this hole too!
I can't believe you're so perverted.
My dear princess, I'm gonna cover your face with my cum.
More! More! I want more!
I'm sorry, Kizaki-kun. That must've hurt.
No, I'm fine.
Really? I feel bad about it.
Don't worry about it so much.
Oh, and this is the book you just dropped.
Thanks.
You're here to check out some books?
Yeah.
I'd like to, but I don't know where to start.
If that's the case...
Here, this is my book. You should give it a try.
Can I really?
Yeah.
I love this book. I hope you'll like it too.
Thanks! I'll start reading it the moment I get home.
Hey, you two!
Shit, Yuuki Emin!
What's with that reaction!?
N-Nothing, really.
So what's up?
Both of you are acting suspiciously.
You were being all secretive in such a confined place.
Don't think you can get past my radar.
Don't ignore me!
Hold it right there!
Are you going to ditch Yuzuki Minami and be a playboy!?
Why are you saying that here?
My informants have been telling me
that you're very close with her.
Both of you walk together a lot, so you must be going out.
We're just classmates, so there's nothing
strange about that, dumbass.
Let's go, Kasumi-chan.
Hey!
I'm not done with you yet!
What's up with Kensuke-senpai?
He's been grinning ever since he arrived.
I don't think it's good to be depressed,
but this is a bit too strange.
Sorry for the wait!
Come on in! Don't be shy!
Okay...
K-Kasumi-chan!?
Why is she..
Well, she said there's a guy likes,|N but she's to shy to tell him.***
So then, I got her to come here.***
Is it all right, Miren-senpai?***
We must not abandon those who are troubled by love.
Yup.
Aren't you glad?
That's all we need to buy.
Yeah.
What is it?
Well, are Kizaki-kun and Minami-chan going out?
Kensuke-senpai said they've been
friends for a long time, that's all.
And Minarni-senpai said that being friends with
him is the worst thing ever or something.
I see, so they're just friends.
And yeah, did you know that Kensuke-senpai and I-
I can't tell her that I had sex with him at a love hotel.
But I might stand a chance alter all this!
I'll get to do it again if I become Kensuke-senpais lover!
Madoka-chan?
Perhaps it'll be a classroom after school next time.
He'll call me to an empty classroom, and then..
Madoka-chan.
Kensuke-sen-
K-Kensuke-senpai?
Stop.
Why should I?
They're nice and big.
Why did you~
I can't hold back.
Despite the fact that we're going out, someone
always interferes when we're about to do it.
Nice reaction.
You must be really sensitive.
Don't do this.
Don't just play with my breasts.
My breasts are the most...
Are you going to cum from this?
I can't...
Wow! What's this!?
That's amazing.
Kensuke-senpai,..
What? Don't tell me you want it down there?
Your reaction is amazing.
Deeper... Even deeper...
Man, I'm really turned on now.
It's so damned wet.
You're too rough!
But it feels good, right?
That's because...
Your huge tits are going to break the windows.
That's because you keep on pushing me.
Don't be so rough!
I'm going to start screaming.
Kensuke-senpai, please ram it in harder!
Please, give it to me harder!
Harder, right?
If you suck my breasts as well..
You said harder, didn't you?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Me too! I can't hold it any longer!
Then please cum inside me.
I love you, Madoka-chan.
Kensuke-senpai...
Madoka-chan?
What's the matter?
I love you, Minami!
Please go out with me!
Also, you've got to look the person to
whom you're confessing in the eye.
Minami, I love you!
Kasumi-chan?
Kasumi-chan!?
What's the matter with her?
Perhaps she didn't know that this was
practice, and she was shocked?
No way! Why would she?
Because she likes Kensuke-kun.
Kasumi-chan likes me?
No, that's not possible.
This picture...
That's me, right?
And that's Jimiko...
Jimiko?
Wait, d-don't tell me!
Kasumi-chan!?
Oh, Minami?
Oh right, you're Kasumi-chan's roommate.
Kasumi-chan hasn't returned to the dorm yet!
Kensuke, have you seen her?
Hey, Kensuke!
Madoka-chan?
It's raining. You'll catch a cold without an umbrella.
Madoka-chan!?
I was rejected again.
Don't be sad.
If you really do love him,
you should bless his opportunity for happiness.
Loving a person without expecting anything
back is the essence of true love, isn't it?
Kasumi-chan!
Kizaki-kun? Why are you here?
I heard from Minami that you didn't go back to the dorm!
Huh? It remember telling Minarni-chan
that I was going to the church.
Anyway, I'm really sorry about that.
I was kinda numb after seeing your confession, so...
You got the wrong idea!
You've always been like that, right?
K-Kizaki-kun?
Ever since you transferred out during elementary school,
I couldn't bring myself to love someone.
But when I met you again...
Well, at first I didn't know that you were Jimiko.
I fell in love with you at first sight.
Liar, you confessed to Minami-chan.
That's not true!
I'm just friends with her!
And what you saw was merely practice!
Practice? Really?
Really.
You,re the one I love.
Remember to bring her back safely.
I'll be at Miren-senpai's place, so don t worry.
Can I stay, Miren-senpai?
Of course.
Isn't this beer?
Non-alcoholic.
What if Minarni-chan comes back?
I don't care if she sees us.
That's embarrassing.
Your heart's thumping, isn't it?
Yeah, I'm a bit excited.
Your nipples are stiff.
Don't say that.
No...
Wow, so this is your...
Don't stare at it.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
No, don't lick it!
It's delicious.
It's not!
It's dirty! Thats the hole I pee with!
It feels amazing, Kasumi-chan.
It's hard and warm.
I'll be happy if you feel good.
Dammit, I can't hold back.
I want to put it in.
I want to become one with you.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Please don't stop halfway.
All right.
It's all the way in.
Does it hurt?
It hurts, but I feel even happier...
Because I'm together with the person I love.
Let me feel more of you!
Kasumi-chan, I love you!
I love you!
I love you too!
I've always, always loved you.
It's so warm and wet inside you.
It's amazing.
I want you to make me feel better.
Dammit, I can't hold back!
Just cum inside me. Let it all out inside me!
Give me all you've got, Kensuke-kun!
I can't hold it... I'm cumming!
Information from Informant #2.
There's a temp file as well.
This is...
So they're going out.
Now they have no excuses.