後向きで歩いて見たら
ushiromuki de aruitemitara
when I walk while facing backwards
意外と広がってるかもよ
igai to hirogatteru kamo yo
the world seems to be wider than I thought
大勢の一部でしかない君
oozei no ichibu de shikanai kimi
you are but a part of the whole crowd
私は嫌いじゃないけどね
watashi wa kirai ja nai kedo ne
though I don't hate the way you are
動き始める予感がする
ugokihajimeru yokan ga suru
I get the feeling that I should start moving
そこから踏み出すために
soko kara fumidasu tame ni
and that's when I make a step
何か止める必要などはないさ
nanika yameru hitsuyou nado wa nai sa
there isn't any reason to stop
行こうよ、手は握いて
ikou yo, te wa nigiite
hold my hand and let's go
上げる風で帽子が壊され
ageru kaze de boushi ga kowasare
may our hats not be broken
ないように
nai you ni
by the wind blowing ever stronger
Kimi Omou Koi
(The Love That I Feel For You)
Volume 2: Not The Love I Exactly Wanted
I hold on to a certain belief.
Nothing else matters as long
as I have a racing swimsuit!
And yet, you'll be treated as
a pervert just from beholding it!
You'll even be branded a criminal!
I only want to peacefully
be with racing swimsuits!
Do I have no other choice
but to become one with this?
Jeez...
What do you think you're doing?
Who's there?!
So, it's you again.
Narumi-kun, the swimming club's president.
You're Kuroe-san from the public morals
committee. Why are you here?
As an authority, I can't let you go any further.
As the club president who should set a good
example, you'll stir up a huge uproar instead!
Y-You're wrong, I just wanted
to peacefully be with this thing!
You're talking gibberish again!
Get your hands off!
Anything but that... Anything but that!
Are you fine with this getting torn apart?
Will my love for racing
swimsuits never be allowed?
Nobody will complain if you're
keeping your hobbies to your own.
However, aren't you giving the girls
dirty looks all the time during practices?
We've been receiving complaints daily.
I told you that if I'll have the swimsuit with me...
Don't tell me that you're planning to join
the practice while wearing this?
Yes...
I can't allow you to drag
the swimming club in a crime.
Please forget about racing swimsuits
and focus on club activities.
If I could only forget about them that easily,
I would've never joined
this club in the first place.
I knew that you'll say that.
I don't really want to do this,
but it seems that I'll have to take care
of that passion of yours by myself.
Huh?
This is a little tight on me.
This is my duty as a public morals
committee member as well.
You may now come in.
Why is Kuroe-san wearing the swimsuit?
Is this some kind of a prank?
If you who's a regular in nationals get expelled,
it'll be a huge loss for the school.
If you'll be able to focus on the club
by settling with me in a swimsuit,
then there should be no problem.
That sounds too good to be true.
Is there a catch to it?
You're being rude.
You don't have to look if you don't want to.
Will it really be alright?
Well, this is my duty as a public morals member...
The emanating smell of chlorine and sweat
is clashing against the shiny
gloss of her body line.
Stop whispering embarrassing
things close to my ear.
Please don't move!
That's...
This sticking sensation that
softly clings to my hands...
It's like a dream to be able to admire
a racing swimsuit this much!
Wh-What are you doing?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Leave it all to me.
I understand...
It's so smooth wherever I touch!
The way it's squeezing my arms
is captivating! This is the best!
You don't have to describe each and everything!
Can I have you do as I say?
Alright...
Slowly lie on your back.
Like this?
Please bear with it.
You can't touch that place!
I'll have to touch such a beautiful curve as this!
Beautiful?
No way, where are you licking?
Narumi-kun...
You went overboard...
If you make such a face,
I won't be able to hold back!
Wh-Wh-What are you doing?!
At such a place as that...
I'm feeling the material's
smooth texture directly!
No, the tip is rubbing against me!
The stimulation is way more than I imagined!
Your thing feels hot!
Now I've done it...
I know she said that I can do whatever I want,
but I sure went too far yesterday.
Now what kind of payback
will she demand from me?
There's no need for that.
Kuroe-san?!
You don't notice your surrounding
when you're in your own world.
It was the same yesterday.
That's not it! That wasn't intentional!
You don't sound convincing at all.
Where are you getting at?
Your accumulated lust...
Kuroe-san?
I'll have to release it.
Otherwise, the embarrassment that
I went through would be for nothing.
Why are you going this far?
This is also a duty of the
public morals committee.
I want you to let me give you a release
until I can satisfy you, Narumi-kun.
Kuroe-san, you're the best!
Are you really fine with this?
Please lower your hips and
let me get a closer look.
Like this?
You're touching me in a naughty way.
Where are you licking me?
Narumi-kun, it's about time.
Are you really sure about this?
I already am mentally prepared for this.
Please do it as you see fit.
Kuroe-san...
It doesn't hurt, so please keep going on.
The swimsuit is clinging tightly to my body.
What should I do? My body became sensitive...
It feels so slippery...
I wonder if I was born a naughty girl
The swimsuit is gradually digging into me.
There's no way I'll be able to
hold myself back from this!
Narumi-kun's thing is swelling inside me!
Huh? Wait!
This feels good!
Narumi-kun, let's feel good together!
Please keep thrusting it more in me!
When you thrust it that hard into me...
This feels crazy!
Just how much do you love swimsuits?
Can't I love both swimsuits and you
at the same time, Kuroe-san?
Gosh, what are you talking about?
Not my nipples!
If you keep staring at me like that...
No!
If you thrust it that deep inside me...
Narumi-kun, I want you to come!
I'll be taking it all in!
I want more of your thick semen!
Please pour it inside me!
From now on, I'll have to give
you a release. Is that clear?
Why are you going this far?
B-Because it is my duty as a
public morals committee member.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization