Yukio doesn't want a child like you.
He likes real women. Experienced women.
You must be Hayato-kun.
Yeah.
What's past is past. Can't we simply
live together peacefully now?
Unfortunately not. l'm very selfish.
l want you two out of here.
What?!
l guess you don't agree...
Of course not!
Well, how about we settle this with a contest?
Contest?
You can't mean... The contest you're talking about...
Exactly. A ''woman breaking'' contest.
Yukio's not living up to the bargain.
He's up screwing around with some
other women right now.
lt's not true!
l did it all for Yukio.
So why.
Reika! Where are you? Reika!
Thank you. l'm sorry to have troubled you.
lt's nothing. By the way, it's dangerous walking at night.
even on your own property. Especially with this rain.
Here you go. Drink this. lt'll warm you up.
Thank you.
But why is the lady of the Mimura house out
walking alone in the rain?
l needed to get out...
l'd stayed inside that house for so long.
l see. lnside the house.
Yes.
And just what were you doing inside the house?
What!?
ln the house what were you doing? Were you being tied up? Beaten?
Such a noble and wealthy family... and the lady of
the house enjoys bondage and S&M!!
l know some people who would be delighted to find out.
l'd be so busy with people coming to see me about this.
What are you talking about? Don't be silly. l should be going now.
No No! Let me go!
lt hasn't stopped raining yet. Why don't you stay a little longer?
Oh! She's great! The lady of the Mimura house is
awesome. She's been well educated.
l'm so sick of you fucking rich people.
l can't believe l'm doing this with you. Am l dreaming?!
Reika! Reika!
Ah! You smell so good. This is why l love young women.
Am l turning you on just by looking at you?
Not so fast. l prefer to take my time with these things.
What a nasty girl... Look how wet you are!
You taste a little sharp though. lt must be the coffee you just had.
Don't hold it in. C'mon, let it out!
No! l can't hold it... l have to go!
Awesome! You young girls always taste a little different...
Stop! No!
How's that? Would you prefer the real thing?
Well, you'll have to wait little longer. l'm gonna enjoy myself like this a while.
Stop! Please.
You keep asking me to stop but l can tell you're having a good time.
Ah No, l'm coming.
More more more more... Oh... Oh...
So good. More. lt feels so good.
l... l'm... l'm coming! l'm coming! Ah! Ah! Ahhh....
l made sure he's going to keep his mouth shut. Our secret is safe, so don't worry.
You're not angry!? Even after what l've done?
l have no choice. You lost it after seeing what l did.
Because you did the same thing...
lt's different. Yes, l had sex with those two
women. But l didn't know them.
They just showed up out of the blue. l was
practically raped by them.
Please believe me. This is Hayato's doing.
Think about it. How could he have known l was with two women?
Don't you think that's strange?
And he told you at the exact same time!
This is some trap he's sprung in order to win the contest.
Please believe me! The woman l love...The only
woman l want to have sex with is you, Reika!
Even if that was a trap set by Hayato, you still had sex with other women.
That was... lt will never happen again.
That's not the problem.
What?
That's not the problem!
You saw me! l was turned on by a guy like that!
l'm no longer satisfied by normal sex. You want to win, right?
l don't care who set this up. That's not the issue here.
lf you can still have sex with other women, use that energy on me!
l don't know what l'd do if l became Hayato's woman.
Reika!
Nice shot! You got it!
What happened to Reika?
Looks like she had a little fling at the caretaker's house.
But nothing's changed between them since she came back to the mansion. Did we screw up?
Screw up? Not at all.
Reika's starting to lose faith in him.
More importantly, Reika's realized one thing about herself.
Her body's not satisfied by normal sex anymore.
And either are her feelings.
This room is exactly the same as it was when dad was still alive.
l remember how he used to look so serious when he read.
l'm sorry... Father.
l can't do it. Reika's not satisfied having sex with me anymore.
lf this continues, Hayato will get this house... Reika...everything.
l just don't know how to make Reika get off like Hayato does.
Father.
How's this? You like it better like this, Reika?
This this is my father's diary..
My father got my mother off like this?!
As long as l have this.
What happened to you? We've never done it like this.
We're not finished yet.
Things start getting serious now.
Does that hurt? Or does it feel good, Reika?
Yukio's changed. l'm sure that l'll choose Yukio now.
But.
There's something.
You don't have to take your clothes off. No sex today.
What do you mean?
Sometimes we should just talk.
We see each other everyday, but we only have sex. lt will be nice for a change.
Don't look at me like that. You must get tired.
You're having sex with two men.
You're having twice as much sex as we are.
Even that's not enough for you?
You don't have to leave.
What?!
Even if l win this contest, you can stay with me.
Everyone, watch carefully!
lf you don't, you'll be fired, no matter how long you've worked for us.
There, it's all in. Yes, there are people are
watching, but don't worry about them.
l know it's hard. You don't have to hold it.
C'mon, you're a good girl. Let it out.
N... No! Ah No! l can't... hold it. No, l can't
hold it. No!!!
Reika, how does it feel? Everyone's watching. Does that make you happy?
Yes. l'm so happy.
You really are such a slut!
You're amazing, Reika. No matter what we put in you.
Ah right there. That feels so good.
Suck me, Reika!
Check this out, everyone. Look how wet her pussy is!
This is proof of how much she loves me. Don't you agree?
lsn't that right, Reika?
l'm gonna come...
l'm coming... l'm coming!
The sex is getting harder and more perverted everyday.
The two months have passed so quickly.
But my heart has not had the time to make up its mind yet.
Yes l'm confused...
Only one more day.
What?
We'll know who the winner is by this time tomorrow.
That's right.
As we have the same techniques, l think l can figure out who the winner is.
But
You've already made up your mind as to who the winner will be.
lt's too late for me now.
Well lf l lose, l'll just go back to my poor,
single life. There's not much else...
By the way... Reika, l
No... lt's nothing.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Today's the day.
Yes, it is.
Of course you're going to chose me, right?
Yes.
Well then, l'll make you happy today too!
No, you don't have to today. You must be tired.
You're going to win so just rest today.
No, l can't do that..
No. Ah Yukio today is
Ah! Yukio! There's no question. l'm gonna pick you.
So You really don't have to do this.
More? l'm gonna make you come so hard.
l won't lose to anyone. l won't lose.
Yukio No! Stop! Please!
You don't have to try so hard. From now on.
What? Yukio...?!
Hayato.
Why are you sleeping?
You idiot! What are you doing? Today's her decision.
Wake up, Yukio!
l want to see you suffer before my eyes from here on.
You have to relive the hell l was forced to go through.
Yukio! Yukio!
ldiot. You're dead... but what about our contest?
Do you regret it, Yukio?
This means that Reika and this house are now mine. lt's all mine! Say something!
l'm now head of the Mimura family. l'll feed yours and your father's bones to the swine.
Do you understand?
Stop.
Stop!
Reika
l just wanted to live in this house with you and...
...our kids.
Hey, check it out. Wow! Look at that. That's wild!
What a bitch in heat you are, Miss Mimura!
More! No! l'm coming l'm coming!
And so begins round three...