The Mimura Family
We have an enormous fortune, amassed over generations. There is nothing we can't have in life.
But no one knows about the scar two twin brothers have left on the face of this family.
''Plunder or Rape'' Part One
Reika... l'm so sorry to have to put you through all this. You're like a sister to me.
l don't know what to say to the spirits of your dead parents.
lt's alright. l've been in love with you ever since l moved into this house.
No!!
Reika... There's no turning back now. Would you rather lose your virginity to that guy?
You're so cute... Reika.
Reika, are you ready?
lt hurts!
Only for a little while.
Reika, does it feel good?
Yukio!
Yukio, l feel strange... l feel hot...l'm so hot!
Reika!
Yukio, Yukio. lt feels so good...
Reika, l'm gonna come!
That first experience was rather shocking.
But... that was just the beginning. The
things l would later be forced to endure...
What are you doing?
Do it now!
NO!!
l'm not a nice guy like him.
But...
You can't refuse. You must obey me.
Do you think you're turning me on by doing that?
That was pretty good. This is next.
What's this?
Do it in there.
Pee!
Good. l can see perfectly like that.
Well? Why don't you get started?!
What's wrong? Do you want me to help you?
No! Don't just bob up and down! Use your tongue!
Right. Good! You're a quick learner.
l'm coming...
Don't spit it out! Swallow it!
Why? Why do l have to do this?
Father! Father, hold on! Be strong, Father!
Father...
Yukio...
Father! l'm here!
Uncle...
Yukio... l don't have much longer...
Father...
Listen carefully! Yukio, you have a cousin about the same age as you.
A cousin!?
This is my last request. Find him and allow
him to live in this house with you. Please...
Father, what do you mean? Father! Father? Father!!
That's how my uncle passed away. Yukio and l were left to live alone in the mansion.
But my uncle's final words hung over me like a dark cloud.
Those words were a confession...
What are you going to do now?
lt was my father's last request. l'm going to honor it.
l see...
And then a few weeks later... he showed up.
You must be Hayato-kun.
Yeah...
l'm really happy that you've come. You must be tired...
lt's been so long. l was starting to think you wouldn't make it.
Come in. You'll catch a cold. l'll have them get
you a change of clothes and prepare dinner.
Hayato-san...
What do you want us to do?
We'll do whatever you want, Hayato-san.
l have an interesting idea. First, we'll have a
little fun. Then all of this fortune will be ours.
Hayato-san, dinner is ready, sir.
l'm coming.
This is our first dinner together. l asked the cooks to use all their skills in preparing this meal.
lf there's ever anything you want, just ask.
Well... if you say so...
What?
First of all, l'd like you to listen to a
story l heard from my dead father.
A story about your father and mine...
A story about our fathers?
Our fathers were identical twins but they hated each other from the day they were born.
So l've heard.
Then one day they fell in love with the same woman.
Their fervent hatred for each other finally came to a head.
They made a bet and agreed that which ever won
would get the family fortune and the girl.
A bet? What was it?
A contest actually... using a woman.
A woman?
The woman they both loved. The woman who would be your mother.
They would see who could turn her into their sex slave first.
l guess you could call it a ''woman breaking'' contest.
Breaking?
You're lying!
The woman you're talking about... My aunt
would never agree to something like that!
Their bet was for everything. They didn't
care about anything else...
even the feelings of the woman they loved.
You're crazy! l never heard anything about this.
Of course not. lf this kind of story ever came to light,
the distinguished Mimura family reputation would be ruined.
You there! Do you know anything about this?
Just what do you want? We brought you here to this house as my father asked.
You'll now be able to live life without having to
worry about anything.
Do you have a problem with that?
Yeah. l do.
What?!
As the family's first born living son, l should be
the head of the of the Mimura household now.
Don't you agree?
What's past is past. Can't we simply live together peacefully now?
Unfortunately not. l'm very selfish. l want you two out of here.
What?!
l guess you don't agree...
Of course not.
Well, how about we settle this with a contest?
Contest?
This all started with our fathers. lt should be finished the same way.
You can't mean... The contest you're talking about...
Exactly. A ''woman breaking'' contest.
What are you talking about? That could never happen!
Well, if you don't want to do it, that's fine with me.
l'll see the secret of the Mimura family is leaked though.
lt will ruin this family. l'll simply go back to my old life.
But you'll both be forced into poverty, something you've never experienced before.
l don't want half. l want it all...or nothing!
lf you're a man, you know what has to be done... golden boy!
No, Yukio! Don't listen to him!
l'm quite serious. To tell the truth, it would be faster if l just killed you.
So what do you say?
B...But...it's not really possible.
First of all, there's no woman who would agree to it.
Yukio!
Yes, there is. The perfect person...
Yukio.
l'm busy.
Are you really planning on going along with him?
l can't help it. He's serious. As long as he's here, we can never live in peace.
That's why...
Please understand. l have to protect this house.
But the woman you're going to break is...
Do you think l'd want to sleep with any other woman but you?
l've loved you for a long time.
l don't care what happens as long as l'm with you.
Please! No matter happens to you...we'll be together...in this house.
Yukio...
There was no turning back. ln two months,
when the contest was scheduled to end...
...no matter what happened to me, l'd make sure Yukio won.
Or at least that's what l thought as the contest began.
How's that? Hot?
But you know what? Soon you'll be dying to feel pain like this.
l don't think it will take long.
No!
Stop!
lt hurts...
Please! Let me down!
No!
No... Stop!
No! Stop! Please!
You're lying. Your body's telling me the truth.
He hurt you...
How could Hayato do this to you?
l can bear the pain, but he treats me like a slave...
But l'll put up with it. For you, Yukio, and to protect this house.
Reika...
Ah... Yukio. l love you. l love you so much.
Reika, l love you too.
Yukio. Yukio. Me too. Me too.
Reika, this is awesome. l'm gonna come.
Reika...
l'm coming...
Looking at Reika, it's easy to tell that Yukio poses no threat.
There's no doubt you're winning.
Of course. No matter how much she denies it, the fact is...
that that woman's body is opening up more and more every day.
But while her body is mine, her heart still belongs to him.
But feelings don't really matter anyway.
That's right. Sex and love are two different things.
Reika's also starting to realize it.
We need to make our move soon.
Which means?
That means it's our turn.
l have an idea that will help sway Reika's feelings away from him.
Stop!
Stay away!
Don't tell us what to do young lady!
You're gonna have some fun with us today.
No!
What a sweet smell! l can't stop!
So well mannered. Not like us.
This is great! What a feeling!
Hayato's taught her well. She gives great head too!
l've told you before. Use your tongue more.
Good. You can do it.
Hayato, l can't hold it. l'm gonna come.
Me too.
OK. Come together.
ls Yukio-san here?
l have good news for you.
It looks like Yukio's upstairs in his room with two hookers from town.
While l'm down here breaking you.
You're lying. That's not true.
Whether you believe it or not, that's up to you. But you can't change the facts.
Please make yourselves comfortable.
Thanks.
Hey, he's pretty cute.
This will be both business and pleasure then. He looks yummy...
l'm sorry to have kept you waiting. What can l do for you?
Why... why are you doing this?
We're gonna show you the time of your life. You just sit back and enjoy yourself.
Here l am trying my hardest to break you and Yukio's slacking off on his end.
He's enjoying himself with other women.
You lie!
Ahhh... Stop!
Do you really want us to stop?
Don't be shy. l know how good this must feel.
lt's awesome. He's so hard. Filling me up.
Lick me harder. Use your tongue more. That's it. You're doing great.
Ah... That's it. More. More.
You're finally getting into it.
You'll never wanna fuck another woman again. l'm gonna take you to heaven.
Reika, Yukio doesn't want a child like you. He likes real women.
You're lying. Yukio...
Yukio, who always holds me so gently...
And when l get tired... he lets me sleep.
Yukio having sex with other women...
l don't believe it...
Yukio... Yukio...
Yukio!