Welcome.
Thank you all for participating in our hotel's special tour.
Just as you've read in the pamphlet,
while you're here you can do anything anywhere
and at any time to any of the girls on this island.
You may even ejaculate inside any of the women here.
There are breasts here that are are as soft as water
balloons and care so large, you might think they're fake.
You'll also find nothing but
smooth skin wherever you touch.
The insides have also been adjusted to be the perfect feel.
In addition, every girl holds an interest in sex,
as well as desires to be pleasured.
They are completely ready to serve all of you.
Every woman here is a woman you'll
never find in the outside world.
Every woman here has been raised
using the most cutting edge this world has
to offer so as to better pleasure all of you.
They are all here to make sure your
dicks don't go home unsatisfied.
The resotr island where it's OK to cum inside the vagina whenever you like
I-I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum again!
This is my... fourth time!
Good, go ahead!
I'm gonna cum too! Want that? Huh?!
Alright, I'm gonna cum inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
More... More!
Deeper!
So... So good!
I want to drink your cum!
I want you to cum inside me!
I want you to mess up my pussy and cum inside me!
Ну ладно хоть не "чан"...
Please rub them more, Inamura-san!
More... You can be rougher if you want!
Our boobs are as sensitive as our pussies!
Our nipples feel just as good as our clits!
I'm cumming!
No! I'm cumming!
I'm pretty sure I came twenty times in six hours.
But thanks to the performance drug the hotel
gave me, I wasn't even close to being done.
If anything, my dick was harder and bigger than ever.
Hey, how many guys have you been with?
Huh? Huh?
M-My apologies, I stopped keeping track.
The employees of this island have
learned the best techniques for pleasure.
If it's what you desire, we'll submit to any rough play...
We'll do it with pleasure!
President! I can't believe I get to cum inside
such a young and beautiful thing like her!
You have a face like an idol, but your
pussy and tits are even more impressive!
Thanks to this drug, no matter how much I
cum, my dick's not even close to going down!
I'm planning on cumming a lifetime's worth of cum here!
Just putting it in feels amazing! I could cum forever!
You're different than those one-night stands I have.
It's like you're looking at your mentor!
It really gets me going!
I never thought I'd be this sexually active at this age.
Hey, you there!
Yes?
I want to do it with you next.
Come here.
Stick your ass towards me.
Oh, of course.
Very well.
Another gentleman was using my mouth
earlier, so my pussy is still unused.
So it's still filled with lots of love juices.
And this is exactly what I
expected from a slut of this island!
You really are a wet mess down here.
Here!
Your love juices are squirting out of you!
How many guys have you been with?
U-Um, I know I've had sex with about ten people, but...
After that, I don't remember!
This is really good!
We're so compatible!
You're perfect!
Thank you very much!
Please enjoy my pussy as much as you'd like!
The soft flesh in your pussy is really great!
It feels so good!
It's... It's hitting me so deep!
I've decided!
I'm gonna make you mine!
They're aphrodisiacs. They'll make you feel good!
Gulp 'em all down!
Sir, you mustn't!
This is supposed to be a one a day drug!
I'm gonna cum!
Oh, it's getting tighter!
Your pussy's tightening around me while it's cumming!
No! No!
The... The drug... The drug, it's...
It's too effective!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
You got even tighter!
Good! Just keep cumming!
I'm cumming!
My pussy's gonna break!
Please, let me go!
Let me go!
What are you saying?!
You've been doing it bareback with guys
all this time and getting cummed inside!
This should be nothing!
I-I'm gonna die!
I've cummed too much!
No! I'm gonna die!
Stop! Stop!!
I thought we could do anything we want to on this island.
My deepest apologies, Sir.
Hurting the girls in any way is against the rules.
T-That's my...
That's my prostate!
Pr-Pr-Prostate...
Please respect our rules when
trying to pleasure yourself, Sir.
What about you?
Will you become submissive if I put my dick in you?
Your cool demeanor's just an act, right?
I'm gonna get revenge for our President.
Prepare yourself!
Very well.
Please try your best.
It's inside! It's inside!
It's inside me!
I like this position!
I love the feeling of a long, hard
thing banging against my pussy!
You're moving your hips?!
Very good, Sir!
My love juices are spilling out!
It's... It's so good!
Holy shit!
It's squishing me so hard!
It's too good!
It's coming! It's coming!
Your dick's reaching my womb!
Oh, shit!
Shit!
If you keep moving like that, I'm gonna...
Sorry, I can't stop myself!
I can't stop!
Your dick's too good!
Sh-Shit! I'm gonna cum!
I'm being sucked dry!
Sorry, I think I made my pussy too tight.
Wow, the chief is so amazing.
She can make any guy cum in the blink of an eye.
She has techniques that keeps the
owner of this hotel satisfied every night!
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
I-It's huge!
Everything about it is amazing!
I-I don't think I've ever seen anything like it!
Would it be okay if I tried my
hand at cumming inside you next?
Y-Yes!
Of course.
G-Go ahead.
Wh-What is this?! I can't believe it!
His dick is so big, it displaced all the cum inside me!
N-No! No!!
Amazing. I've never seen the chief in this much ecstasy.
I-It must be quite the pleasurable dick.
Oh god. Oh god!
It's hitting all the right places!
It's hitting all of them!
My womb's already accepting him!
If he cums now, I'm gonna get pregnant with his baby!
What is this?!
I've had a lot of pussy today, but her pussy's
tightness is on a whole different level!
Every time I try to shove it deep, the
walls of her pussy push me back!
Its like her pussy has a mind of its own!
It's squirming so much!
What should I do? I've never had anyone but
the owner go so deep into my womb before!
I think I'm gonna cum!
I'm... I'm gonna fall for him!
No! I'm the owner's woman!
I'm the owner's woman!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! This is gonna make me cum!
It's so good!
The pussy that the owner has been training every night is...
My pussy's going crazy!
It... It's so good! I can't...
I'm... at my limit.
I'm gonna cum!
It's so good!
Come! Come! Oh, no!
No!
No! No!!
I don't need the owner anymore!
Please, cum! Cum!
My stomach's swelling up...
No... I'm gonna lose it.
I can't be his anymore. It's over...
Oh crap, I can't move anymore.
I can't even stand.
Heh, I made a cum waterfall.
Wow, that amount... I want to have that in me too.
Please do that to me too.
I-I'm pretty tight.
Not only do I get tight ass pussies,
but I get to do it with these beauties!
I want to be covered in your cum as well.
Me too!
Please cum in me until it overflows from me!
And they love sex!
This is basically heaven!
Holy shit!
Inamura-sama...
This was different than anything I've ever
had. It was longer and filled with affection.
I was so close to becoming yours.
You really have quite a fine dick, don't you?
I'm sure that many women here will
become yours while you're here.
It seems that you're enjoying yourself.
Please continue to enjoy yourself fully while you're here.
Um...
Yes?
I... I will make you mine!
I'm not that easy of a target.
Just you watch!
I'm gonna make her mine by the end of this tour!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч