This island can't be found on any map.
It's a great ways off of any charted boat's route.
Even satellites can't find this island.
It's about the same size as Hawaii.
And the entire island is basically one big city.
It's called Baburuki.
This resort island was built in secret and is
a paradise for politicians and VIP guests.
Even among the elite, very few know of its existence.
Welcome.
Thank you all for participating in our tour.
And thank you for waiting.
We are very grateful for you choosing to
stay at the Tou Hotel during your stay.
W-Wait a second.
They're all hotties with impossibly large chests!
The tour that all of you have signed
up for will last one month.
While you're here you can do anything, anywhere,
and at any time to any of the girls on this island.
That is the law of this island.
The resort island where it's OK to cum inside the vagina whenever you like
Every inhabitant on this island, including myself
have been raised using the most cutting-edge techniques
this world has to offer to enhance your pleasure.
Everyone, please direct your eyes over here.
They're not just big and bountiful,
our nipples are toned as well.
And also...
We have the highest quality vagina.
They're always hot and wet inside.
It's filled with the right amount of viscous love juices.
We've just met, but she's already showing us her pussy!
Of course, it retains its reproduction functions as well.
It's the highest quality of pussy with pleasure prioritized.
They're as soft as water balloons.
And they're so large that you may think they're fake.
You'll find nothing but smooth skin wherever you touch.
The insides have also been adjusted to be the perfect feel.
Everyone also holds an interest in sex,
as well the desire to be pleasured.
They are completely ready to serve all of you.
Every woman here is a woman you'll
never find in the outside world.
Then, for instance, we could have sex right here and now?
Yes, of course.
No woman on this inland is an exception.
Please use us whenever and wherever you'd like.
Really now?
Holy shit!
A girl I just met is...
Somehow is sucking my dick right now!
That's good...
This is too good!
It's so warm and soft...
It feels so good!
I-It's like my dicks being devoured!
Are you serious?
I-I'm cumming!
Thank you for using me so soon.
Doing them, it's really...
Really that simple?!
The Tou hotel is comprised of suite rooms.
Please sit back and relax.
H-Holy crap.
We monitor this island with numerous security cameras.
If you find a girl you like, you can have them
delivered to your room at any time.
How about it?
O-Okay...
Uh...
How about this girl and then this girl over here.
Oh, this girl too!
Understood.
I'll arrange for them to come immediately.
For real?
I really get these incredibly hot girls?
Thank you for choosing us.
My name is Maki.
Mika!
I'm Narumi.
All reasoning I had before I came to this island...
Look, boobs!
All of it got thrown out the window!
It's fine I can do it in the hallway.
She feels too good!
Her ass is so soft!
Her tongue feels so good!
Her tongue technique is so good!
Her tits are touching me.
She really is perfect everywhere!
He's so aggressive!
His big, hot thing is hitting against my stomach!
I'm gonna go inside you now, okay?
Of course. Whenever you're ready.
Is this really going to fit?
You're kidding!
Wouldn't that rip her apart?
It's huge!
I-I can do it raw, right?
Y-Yes, that's fine.
You can even shove it all the way in at once if you'd like.
This is amazing!
It's nothing like an onahole!
Her insides are so wet and slippery. They're moving too!
They're sucking me in!
What is this?
I've never had anything like his before.
It's completely different!
It feels so good deep inside me!
My back is arching!
I love vaginas!
And I can use this hole as much
as I want for an entire month!
And not just this one, but any hotties' on this island!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
What's going on?
This is amazing!
My pussy is already making preparations to cum!
Yes! My dream boobs!
And they're even bigger than I imagined!
They're like huge pieces of pudding!
N-No, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
So good... It's so good!
Huh? You're cumming already?!
That's way too fast.
It really feels that good?
I-I've never had sex like this before!
It's so good!
It's too amazing!!
My body's being thrust into!
Boobs! Boobs!
Boobs! Boobs!!
No! No!
I can't hold back!
There's no way I can!
Alright, let's fire off the first shot inside this woman.
Inside her! Inside her! Inside her!
Shoot my cum inside her!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
She's holding me?!
No! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
What is this...
I already orgasmed on my first go with him.
The cum he shot inside me is soaking into me.
It feels so, so, so good...
This is definitely going to get me pregnant!
Inamura-sama!
Do me too!
Shoot your seed inside me with that huge dick of yours too!
Th-This is good. She's so small and cute!
Hurry! Hurry!!
Oh no, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming already!
This is too stimulating!
It feels so good!
– This is my second one! I'm already having sex with another girl!
– It feels really good!
You're gonna break me!
I'm gonna break!
She's completely different than the girl I just had.
She's just a little tighter... It feels so good!
No...
Your dick's completely different
from onii-chan's... It's so good!
They can even have those kinds of illicit relations here?!
As expected of a woman from this island!
Hey.
You looked the other way at first, right?
Narumi-chan was on a date with her boyfriend today!
B-But then you reserved her...
So she's just pouting a little.
H-Hey!
It feels so good!
Hinamaru-sama, you're the best!
So good! This is so good!
My stomach... It's being knocked against!
Do it! Do it!!
It's coming! It's coming!!
Wow...
My entire body is covered in cum...
Hey, so...
You probably hate me now, right?
N-Not really.
This doesn't really bother me at all.
Really?
Even though your date was ruined and
I just came all over your friends?
So, you can have sex even if you hate me?
Y-You're being too peristen...
You're gonna get the cum of the guy that
you hate, shot down your throat!
What is this? His dick's so big, it's
hitting me so deep! It feels good!
This is bad! This is bad!
It's rubbing against me so deep! I might like this!
Wow, this is so amazing!
I'm falling head over heels for this dick!
I can't control my hips when I'm sticking
my dick into a hot girl like you!
How's it feel?
Your mouth is better than an onahole.
So this is a real irrumatio?
It feels good to have my throat get fucked!
I love how rough he is!
I like this guy!
He was a little annoying at first, but
that doesn't matter anymore!
How could I ever hate a person with a dick like this?!
There's so much!
It's like he's peeing inside me.
I wouldn't mind drowning in this guy's cum.
Seriously, how wet are you getting
before I even put my dick inside?
I guess that's the genetically manufactured
sex body at work.
If it being in my throat felt that good,
if he puts it in my vagina...
I just came from him putting it inside me!
It's hitting all the places that have never been hit before!
It feels too good!!
I don't think I'll ever get tired if I'm able
to keep fucking these sexy girls
with great bodies and great pussies like this!
More! Rub it in me more!
Mess my pussy up!
Master Dick! Master Dick!!
Oh look, you're moving your hips by yourself now.
You're like some kind of animal.
You little slut.
You're a dick addicted slut!
My pussy's going crazy!
It's becoming the shape of Master Dick!
I won't be able to go back to other
dicks if my body remembers this!
This is the best! I want to be fucked
by this guy for the rest of my life!
I'm gonna cum!
Take it all in with your womb and get pregnant, got it?!
Yes! Yes!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming too much!!
Cum... No...
No! No! No!!
I can't believe this. There's so much!
My womb's swelling from all the cum!
So...
Who was better? Me or your boyfriend?
Y-You were, Inamura-san.
Yours was better than any dick I've had until now.
If we go by order, I'm next, right?
I can't wait any longer.
No! Not fair!
Mine was the shortest!
One more time!
This is the island of sluts I've come to expect!
I haven't even been here for an hour and
I already have a high grade harem!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч