l'm so happy we can go to the same college in April.
Yeah...
You studied very hard for me, right?
Hey, are you listening Suguru?
Yeah...
Give me a kiss.
Y...yeah...
Relax a bit.
Come on, relax.
l am...
lt hurts.
Sorry.
Hazuki, open up.
lf you don't open...
No, turn off the lights...
No, come on.
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Don't...stare at it.
No to that too.
Stop.
No, not there.
Suguru, l'll lick yours too.
Really!?
Yeah, l even studied so l can make you feel better.
Well, does it feel good?
Yeah...
So happy...
Hazuki, can l stick it in?
Yes, OK.
Here l go...
l think it goes in here...?
lt...!
Hurts!!!
Are you OK?
Yeah...
Do you want to stop?
Don't stop, l'm fine...
OK...
Suguru, you're inside me...
lt's so warm...and wonderful.
Hazuki, you're warm too, it feels good.
This hurts...
Does this really feel good?
lt's so tight, l can't....!
C...cuming, Hazuki!
P...pull it out!
Amazing, your sperm is all over me.
You must've been really waiting for it.
But we can have sex anytime now.
Thanks for keeping the promise, Suguru.
Are you listening, Suguru?
Sorry....
What's wrong, why are you apologizing?
l'm really sorry!
What, did you cum inside?
No, it's not that.
What is it then?
Fa....iled
Huh?
l'm sorry, l didn't get accepted to college!
Didn't get accepted?
Yes...
Why?
Sorry.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
l wanted to...have sex...with you.
So sorry!
That's it...?
Yes, but l will study hard to
get in next your so Hazuki...
You damn liar!!
No girlfriend, no school...
But it's my fault for lying...
l shouldn't have made such stupid promises.
l think l'll just kill myself by jumping off...
Someone walking into the river, can't be...!?
A suicidal person!
Don't do it!
There's no need to be suicidal because of school!
She's cute.
Sorry, are you alright?
My brooch.
Oh, you were looking for a brooch.
Yes.
l dropped it off the bridge.
What does it look like?
lt's about this big, kind of round
it's white with a touch of blue
and l put a string around it to use it as a pendant.
But you don't need to help me...
lf l don't it might get dark and loose it forever.
Besides, it's my fault you're wet.
Where is it...
l don't know what l'll do
without my mom's memento...
Did it drift away?
Don't worry, we'll find it!
lt's OK, l'm sorry...
What are you saying, isn't it important?
Don't give up.
Lets find it!
But...
We looked everywhere...
lf she dropped it from the bridge...that's it!
Found it!
See, it's here!
lt was just stuck between the rocks!
Thank you so much!
Here, don't loose it again.
This is my contact.
Give me a call, promise?
Of course.
What are you doing, Suguru!!
U...um, what's your name!?
Hey, Suguru!
Who is that girl!?
l'll call you!
Suguru!
Ha...Hazuki, no! There's a reason...
Who is that girl you flirt, liar, perv, can't pull out man!
Listen to me, Hazuki!
Stupid Suguru!!
Hey, wait up.
Hazuki...
Ouch!
Oh my, don't be causing anymore trouble.
Thank you very much.
But, why are you so nice to me?
Do l need a reason?
How can l not be kind to a lost
crying kitten in the rain?
Take a shower, you'll catch a cold.
l'm coming in.
Are you cleaning well?
Are you still crying?
Don't be so stiff.
Wow, you're especially stiff here.
Oh, what's this...
Let me clean it.
Oh, you're so energetic.
Sorry...
So cute.
Well, does it feel good?
Yes.
lt's big and very manly...
lt's twitching.
Don't worry...about a thing.
Be proud, you're a man.
After all, l'm really into you, right?
So big...
lt's hitting me deep, l know you can feel it...
Move your hips... thrust upwards...
This is so great...
l...it's in deep!
Cuming...cuming!
Miss...
lt's Yukiko, Boy.
Yukiko-san...
Lets...continue.
Great...it's big and thick...
Stir the inside, more!
lnside, it's deep inside...
More...more...!
Feels good...
Going to cum...
Cum...inside me!
Give me...give me all you got!
Cuming!!!
lt was great...
You were...wonderful.
Why was l...so wild today?
ls it because he looks like him?
Oh well, it was great.
lsn't this...a man's clothes?
Oh, you're awake?
Good morning.
l had a great time last night.
lf you don't mind...
You can live here.
Well?
Yukiko-san!
Hold on a second.
OK, OK...who is it?
Sup, it's me, let me in.
Hold on, l'm still in my pajama,
Hurry, come here...sorry, hurry!
Wait here, sorry, please wait!
Hey, what's going...
So sorry.
At least give me a call first...
(note: Thank you and good bye)
l got rejected from school and
broke my heart 3 times in 2 days...
Should just leave...
You broke up with Suguru-kun!?
Don't yell out of no where, Sis.
You surprised me.
l'm the one who's surprised.
l mean why, you guys were madly in love.
But Sis, he lied about being accepted to
college and took my virginity!
Then, he flirted on the same day.
That's because you made him wait too long.
lt's great that you saved your virginity until you're 18
But it's really sad for Suguru-kun, waiting a year for it.
lt's not my fault, it's his fault.
Not only he lied, he took my virginity...
l can't trust him anymore.
l'm never going to see him again!
So that means he is single and looking.
l think l'll go comfort him.
No!
Why, you broke up right?
You're never going to see him, right?
Yeah, but...
So, l can have him, right?
Yeah...
Alright, l'm going for him!
Hey, wait up!!
Suguru, you're...
Stupid!
Why...
Won't you call me...?
Now l have to live in this city alone.
So sad...
Hey guys, welcome to the Skalabe Theater.
We have great drinks and nude girls!
Uncle's apartment should be around here.
Where is it?
Hey there, boy.
Are you looking this way because you
want to see the nude show?
What!? No way, not a nude show.
Oh, were you looking at my tits then?
Um...
l'm looking for this apartment.
Let me see...
Oh, it's here.
Huh, l'm looking for an apartment.
Here, here, we have a customer coming inside!
Hey, wait!
Welcome.
To the Skalabe Theater.
Here, come this way.
Um, wait...l'm not, well...
VIP treatment for you.
Bring some drink over here.
l wonder what came over her?
lt's rare to see her sitting with a customer.
Maybe she likes him?
What, is that true!?
He is kind of cute.
She's beautiful...
Tits...
This was really a nude show...
Boy, my tits are bigger you know.
Oh, that's right! l was looking for my apartment.
l told you it's right here.
Huh, but this is a commercial area.
The apartments are upstairs.
We all live here.
What!?
Welcome to the Skalabe Theater.
There's only one room on the
5th floor so it's easy to find.
This room is big...and is furnished.
There's a balcony too.
Hazuki lives somewhere in this city too...
Hazuki...
Oh, did l keep the lights on?
Huh, she is...
l worked up a sweat.
l need to shower.
What, she's taking off her clothes in my room!?
Did l leave the windows open too?
A pervert, someone help!
No, l'm not!
Help me, someone!
Wait, it's me!
Sorry!
W...wait, listen!
Please listen!
Calm down, it's me!
Sorry...
You pervert!
Die!
Kill him!
So he's the perv!?
Ai, call the cops!
What, cops!?
Alright, fine.
Wait, l know this person.
What!? He's not just a perv, he's also a stalker!?
Stalker!?
You damn bastard!
l'm not!
You girls alright?
Hey, Mama-san and manager.
So, you're the perverted asshole!
Show me your face!
Su...Suguru!?
Uncle!
Hey, l'm really sorry.
l totally forgot that l lent this room to Suguru.
So l let Urara-chan move in here.
You're so cruel, Uncle.
Hey, don't worry.
l have a very special room waiting for you.
Take a look and be surprised, it's freshly built!
What!!!?
Man, it was hard work!
lt took me three days to make.
Good job on the house, eh?
Oh, l'll live here!
What!!!?
Hey, what are you saying?
You'll catch a cold and die!
But...l can't have Suguru-san live here because of me.
There's no way we can let a girl live here!
l'll live here!
l can't have Urara-san live at such a place.
Such a place!?
Suguru, you too!!?
He is right.
l agree.
Congratulations, Urara-chan.
But...
l know!
We should live in that room together!
What!!!?