Ladies and gentlemen
On behalf of your captain and the entire crew,
thank you for choosing the island resort's special tour.
As I'm sure you're already aware...
For the duration of your stay, you may take part in
any sexual acts with any women at any time.
You may also come inside them.
As soft as water balloons...
Nipples so large you won't believe your eyes...
Smooth skin wherever you touch...
Bodies perfectly plump for embracing...
And what's more, they're eager for sex.
They want to feel good...
They wish only to please you...
We're sure you'll see that they're nothing
like girls from your usual society.
ln order to best please you...
All women on this island are trained to
have a heartfelt desire for your cocks.
An Island Resort at Which It's OK to Suddenly Come
lnside Any Vagina You Like at Any Time You Like
I-I'm coming!
I'm going to come again!
This is the fourth time!
All right!
I'm going to come.
How does it feel?
OK, I'm gonna come inside you.
I'm coming!
More!
Deeper!
Yes!
I want to drink your come!
I want you to come inside me!
I want you to stir up my pussy and make me come!
Rub them more, Inamura-sama!
M-More!
You can be rougher with me!
O-Our breasts are as sensitive as pussies.
Our nipples feel as good as clitorides!
Note: Plural of "clitoris", pronounced "cli-TORE-ih-deez".
The more you know.
I'm coming!
No!
I-I'm coming!
I've come more than 20 times in the past 6 hours.
But thanks to the hotel's provided
sexual enhancement pills...
ln fact, it's getting harder and harder!
My cock's not getting softer.
And it's getting noticeably thicker and longer too.
Hey you...
How many guys have you done it with?
W-Wha?
I-I'm sorry.
So many I... can't keep count.
We employees have mastered even the
most difficult sexual techniques.
lf you so desire...
We'll bear even the roughest erotic play!
President!
We can come inside these young, beautiful
women as much as we want!
I can't get enough!
Their big tits and pussies put
even gravure idols to shame!
Thanks to that drug, no matter how much
we come, we'll never go soft.
I'm gonna stay here and come
for the rest of my life!
I just put it in a little and you're already gasping.
I'm gonna come so many times!
After I've done it just once with a girl,
she looks at me completely different.
lt's like she's looking at a senpai she longs for!
I can't get enough of this!
I never thought I'd be so popular at this age.
Hm?
Ohh! Y-You there!
Yes?
I want to do it with you next.
C'mere.
Show me your ass.
All right.
Very well.
I've just been doing face-fucking so far...
So my pussy is still unused...
lt's... thoroughly lubricated so even clients with
large cocks can thrust all the way inside with ease.
This is why you're a bitch on this island!
lt really is soaking wet.
Here I go!
Love juice is squirting from your pussy!
How many guys were you with?
Yes!
I remember 12 of them...
but I can't remember after that!
This is amazing!
We're a perfect match.
You're a rare find.
Thank you!
Please thoroughly enjoy my pussy!
The lumpy flesh inside you feels really good!
That feels great!
You're reaching my deepest spot!
I choose you!
I'm definitely going to make her mine!
lt's an aphrodisiac. I hear it works really well.
Come on! Swallow all of them!
Sir, you mustn't!
This drug is meant to be taken once daily!
I'm going to come!
You're getting tight!
Your pussy's getting really tight all of a sudden!
No!
The drug...
lt's super effective!
I'm coming!
You're coming again!
All right! Keep coming!
lt's going to break...
My pussy's going to break!
Please!
Please stop!
Stop!
What are you saying?
You've done it bareback loads of times.
You can't back out now!
I-I'm going to die!
I'm coming too much!
N-No!
I'm dying!
Stop it!
I can do anything I want on this island, right?
Pardon the interruption, Sir.
Cruelty and violence against our
girls will not be tolerated.
My prostate!
Pros... tate...
So for the sake of your enjoyment,
please respect our rules.
All right, Sirs?
Even you...
Once you have a cock inside you,
you'll get meek and docile?
You're just a bitch, right?
I'll take revenge for what you did
to the company president!
Prepare yourself!
Very well.
Please do try.
lt's going in!
You're inside me!
I like your cock!
It's huge and hard, and it's rubbing
the inside of my pussy!
My hips are moving on their own!
Sir, that feels great!
My come is dripping out!
Yes! That feels great!
Y-Yes!
You're getting so tight!
This feels too good!
I'm coming!
Your cock is reaching my womb!
No!
lf you do that, I'm gonna...
I-I'm sorry.
I can't stop myself!
I can't be stopped!
Sir, your cock feels too good!
No!
I'm coming!
You're sucking out my come!
I'm sorry.
My pussy got too tight.
That's our chief!
No matter who she's with,
she makes them come in seconds!
She's knows all the excellent techniques needed to satisfy
our hotel's excellent owner night after night!
Um... Excuse me.
Y-Yes?
I-It's huge!
lt's hard, and it has such a wonderful shape!
I don't think I've ever seen one like this!
Can I try coming inside you next?
Y-Yes!
Of course!
G-Go ahead.
What is this!?
I can't believe it!
All the semen that was inside
me is being forced out!
Not like that! No!
Wow!
lt's my first time seeing the chief like this.
I-It looks like his cock feels pretty good.
No!
He's hitting my pleasure spots
with his massive cock!
He's hitting all of them!
My womb is opening!
lf he comes inside me now, I'll get pregnant!
What is this feeling?
The girls before were great.
But she's on a whole new level!
When I try to put it in deep, she
pushes back from inside!
lt's like her pussy is a separate living
thing, with a will of its own!
I-It's wriggling around me!
What should I do?
Someone other than Owner-sama
is deep inside me!
I'm going to come!
I'm going to fall in love!
I'm Owner-sama's!
I'm all Owner-sama's!
I'm going to come!
Y-Yes!
Owner-sama trains my pussy every day!
And this man's going to destroy it!
Yes!
I can't take it!
I'm gonna come
Here comes a big one!
Your big cock is amazing!
Come!
No!
Someone other than owner-sama is inside me!
Please, come!
Come!
My tummy's getting bigger.
No!
I'm gonna fall in love...
I-It's no use...
That was so tiring.
I can't get up!
lt's a semen waterfall...
Wow!
I want you to come that much inside me too.
Please fuck me next!
I-I'm pretty good at this myself!
I get to do it to my heart's content with a bunch of
amazing girls I've just met... And they're beautiful!
Me too...
I want you to make my tummy
swell with your semen too.
Me too!
Come inside me until I can't hold it inside!
They're asking me for sex!
I feel like a god!
This rocks!
lnamura-sama...
That kiss was like nothing I'd ever done before.
lt lasted so long.
And it was full of love.
Just a little more and I would have fallen for you.
You have a truly spectacular cock...
I'm sure you'll make many women
fall for you later on in your stay.
lt seems you're still ready to go.
Please thoroughly enjoy your evening.
Um...!
Yes?
I-I...
I'm gonna make you mine!
That won't be easy, you know...
Just you wait!
Before this tour is over...
I'm definitely going to make her mine!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: Asuka_Langley