l'll live here!
What!?
Hey, what are you saying?
You'll catch a cold and die.
But...
lt's my fault that's Suguru-san's forced to live here.
We can't have a girl living in that dump!
l...l'll live here!
l can't have Urara-san living in such a place.
Such a place!!
You too, Suguru?
He's right.
l think it's settled.
Be happy, Urara-chan.
Uh, but...
l know, we can live in that room together!
Wha!!!?
l won't allow it!
A boy and a girl who just
met living together, l'm jea....
l mean, that's really unmoral!
But, they said they knew each other.
Mama!
lf the two...don't mind.
Anyway, l won't allow it!
And so, l'm moving in with you guys.
l...l'll be fine with Suguru-san...
What, fine, how?
Guys are sex starved wolves
especially young ones like him!
Hey, that's so mean...
Shush!
lf you try anything funny, l'm kicking you out.
Understood!?
Y...yes.
Time to eat!
You can down that fast, Ai-neesan.
l'm not going easy on you for kissing up.
No, it's nothing like that.
Wow, Ai-neesan can cook well too!
lt really is delicious!
l'll accept your compliments.
lt is really good!
Yeah, much better than my cooking!
Such a manly way of eating...
Delicious!
Oh Suguru-san, there's food on your cheeks.
And now it's gone.
Damn it, l won the battle but she won the war.
No, it's not over yet!
Oh, there's sauce on your cheeks.
There, it's gone.
Hey, what are you looking at.
l think l should pull the red card.
What?
lt's fun eating as a group.
Feels like we're a happy family.
Admit it, you were staring at me.
That's not true, please forgive me!
The bath should be ready now.
Ai-neesan, you take the bath first.
Oh, l'll go in later.
Urara-chan, you first.
Suguru-san....wash me.
Not there!
We have to clean it.
No, it's driving me wild!
What's with the face, thinking something perverted?
l, l'm not!
Lets see...
W...what are...?
This is honest.
Well, if you keep touching it...
See, l knew it...
lt's...it's so big...
Pervert...
l knew it...l can't have you living with Urara-chan.
B...but...
Come stay with me...
...please.
Suguru-san, Ai-neesan, l'm finished.
Ready for next.
l, l forgot something in my room so let me go get it.
Suguru-kun, help me.
l'll tell you where the trash is too.
Come!
OK.
S...see you later.
Oh, see you.
What did you forget?
Just come in.
Ai-neesan...?
Ai-neesan...
Sorry about earlier, l didn't mean it.
Forgive me.
Please...
Lick it, touch it...
lt's big!!!
Deep...it's hitting...in deep....
Hey, lets live together.
l'll do anything.
Ai-neesan...
lf you feel uncomfortable here, we can move out.
ls that a no...?
lt's not that...
You like Urara-chan, don't you...
l don't know...
lt's not fair...
l thought l was first...
Shesh, l though l had my eyes on you first.
But l'm not giving up yet.
l will...have you fall in love with me.
Great, harder, make me cum!
Oh...more, more!
Great, it got bigger!
Cuming...l'm cuming!
Good night...
Oh, Suguru-san.
Welcome home, you're late.
Where's Ai-neesan?
Well, she said she'll sleep in her room.
Really?
lt's going to be alright, right?
Sorry!
Don't worry...about us living together.
Because you're a great person.
(But l just had sex with Ai-neesan)
Although it's only until a room becomes vacant...
l don't want this to end...
A great person...
ls she seducing...welcoming me?
She is, she has to be!
Alright...
Hmmm...Mama....
l don't know whether to be happy or sad.
Someone help me...
What!?
Why do we have to work at the store?
Urara-chan, it's cute!
Yeah, it really is.
People who work at Club Sukalabe live upstairs.
Thus meaning, if you live here you must work here.
Hey, no one told me that!
Shush, if you want to live here, listen to me.
That hurts, Ai-neesan!
l got studies!
You're going to fail anyway so just work here...OK?
Besides, there might be good things happening.
Please let me go...
But Urara-chan is working here.
School might pay for tuition but not her living.
Yep!
Tuition?
The school you got rejected from
she passed with the top grade.
l know, instead of wasting money on a school
how about getting lessons from Urara-chan?
That sounds wonderful!
l will teach you.
lt's decided.
Any complaints?
Fine.
But l'm still going to school.
Mama Yukiko?
When we're alone together, please call me Yukiko-san.
Mama, can you help me out?
lf you need a release, come over anytime.
l'll be waiting...
Mama?
Coming.
Suguru-kun.
Hey, Sakura-san.
Do you want to hang.....!
Yes?
Fucking!!!
Pervert!!!!!
Ouch, what the?
Shit!
What are you doing Suguru?
Hey, why didn't you call me!
Sorry, but you rejected me...
l mean after all that...
Of course, after...
But...you're not going to apologize?
l was surprised when your parents said you're here.
Sorry.
Hey Suguru.
lf your studying for school, it'll be easier
from home...why did you come here?
l'll loose concentration at home.
And if l'm studying near you
l thought l can study harder.
lt makes me have more confidence.
l'm sorry, l know you hate me after what l've done...
l don't hate you.
Suguru...
Bring your face up.
Hazuki!?
Let me..cheer you up.
Suguru, Suguru..
Hazuki.
There!!
Hazuki, you're so wet...
So warm...
Feels tingly.
lt's driving me crazy!!!!!!
l'm going in.
OK...
You alright?
l'm...fine.....
Come.
Feels...good...inside...!
Hazuki...Hazuki!
Amazing, it's deep, your thing is in deep!
lt's so warm.....strange..!
No, it's driving...it's driving me crazy!
Cuming, cuming....cuming!!!
l'm going to cheer you up more.
l'll make you dinner.
l'm opening the fridge.
What, you have nothing in here.
l, l just moved in last night so...
l see, that's disappointing.
l wanted to cook for you.
Or...do you want to eat me out again?
Ha, Hazuki!
l'm home!
So you are back home, Suguru-san.
l'll start on dinne.....?
Suguru!!!
You lying piece of shit!!!
Hey Sis!
l don't want Suguru after all, you can have him!
Are you alright!?
l'm sorry...
lf only we didn't live together..
You would'nt have gotten
in a fight with your girlfriend.
Don't worry, we were....already broken up.
Really?
Yeah...and l'm finally over it.
l have to get accepted next year.
l can't think about girls.
l...
l wish you luck.
Thanks.
l...was an orphan.
Mama Yukiko was in the same orphanage
and always took care of me.
Even after she left the orphanage
she continued to support me.
But l was really happy when
she asked me to live here with her.
She told me about the people she lived with.
So l knew everyone right away
when l first met them, but...
The happiest thing is that
l was able to see you again.
l was waiting for your call...
l was really happy when you helped
me search for my mother's brooch.
l'm so happy to see you again...
So happy to live with you...
So happy that l have a family...
l'm sorry for her, but...
l want to be with you forever!
Please don't leave me.
l won't...
Alright, lets get started!
W...with what?
What else, your studies!
l have to help you study now that
l am officially your private tutor.
But!
l thought we're going to start a new life?
We are a couple, right?
No!
No, you will need to hold your
urges in until you pass the test!
What!? But!!!
Do your best and lets go to the same
school together next year, OK?
Not this again...
This is hell...someone save me...