I know this is sudden, but our company is going bankrupt.
What?
Seriously?
Yeah, that's it, period.
Thank you all.
No way!
He's got to be kidding.
Time is running out.
In the Staff Kitchen
Kininaru Kimochi
So what do you have to say...
at a time like this?
Actually, this is the perfect time to tell you this.
U-Um, I've...
been in love with you since I joined this company.
But I've never been able to tell you how I felt until now.
I was wondering... if I could kiss you as a last memory here.
Nishizaki-kun!
Yes?
I love you too.
Manager...
N-No further! I mustn't...
Banging you from behind... in the staff kitchen has been my dream!
Nishizaki-kun.
Wait...
You're a grown-up,
so I bet you want more than just kisses.
W-Well...
I take that as a "yes."
What is this, huh?
You're wet already.
How cute, Nishizaki-kun.
You must like this, Nishizaki-kun.
Hear that lewd sound?
You're getting even wetter, Nishizaki-kun.
Are you ready?
Nishizaki-kun...
Great!
This is awesome, Nishizaki-kun.
This is so good.
You're amazing.
Your pussy is swallowing my cock.
So cute.
There they are.
You've got such a nice body. Really!
I like the size and shape of your boobs.
I-I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum inside you, Nishizaki-kun.
No, don't! Please cum outside!
I can't hold it any longer.
I-I'm cumming!
That was amazing.
Hey, that's not fair.
You weren't the only one
thinking about doing this.
Let me do it, too.
As you wish.
Let me have fun, okay?
I guess you've never had sex with two guys at the same time, right?
I wanted to do this so bad that I feel like I'm dreaming.
It's pretty tight.
Looks like she's sensitive, too.
Her pussy lips are sucking my cock in.
I'm cumming, Manager.
Me too.
The company's going bankrupt anyway...
...so why not have fun, huh?
You guys can join us.
You have to wait your turns though, okay?
W-Wait a second.
Please stop.
This is cruel.
No!
Please let me go now!
Suck my dick, will you?
I'm cumming!
Hey, did you hear that Nishizaki-san is having sex with everyone?
Really?
I can't believe I'm having sex with our secret idol.
This is like a dream come true.
Let's try another hole here.
It's really tight.
Nishizaki-san...
I'm cumming.
Me too.
Cumming... Cumming!
It's not yet time for a break, Nishizaki-san.
You can drink our cum as much as you want.
I'm cumming.
Nishizaki-kun, can I do it, too?
No! Help me...
Staff kitchen
Let's have fun together, huh?
Come on, move your hips!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah!
More. More!
No, you're thrusting too hard!
I'm going crazy!
Both your boobs and pussy are amazing.
Your boobs are so soft.
It feels good.
I've never felt this good.
Please do whatever you want now.
Feels good...