Executive Producer: Yoshiki Takeda
Original Author: Naizou Kurada
Screenplay: Kiyoshi Mizukami
Drawing Director: DeCaprio
Hey... Yuu-chan.
Director: Yuichi Oyamauchi
But...
Sparkling Sibling ~Sex Crime~
Yuu-chan... Yuu-chan!
Wake up, Yuu-chan!
It's already morning. Hey, Yuu-chan!
Shut up...
Good morning, Yuu-chan!
You gotta wake up already! Or you'll be late for school.
God... What's your problem?
What do you mean?
Your beloved sister came to wake up her little
brother so he wouldn't be late for school.
That's not it... I meant what's wrong with your clothes!
This? It's fine, its my house after all.
What's wrong? Did it make you wake up?
She doesn't think of me as a man, does she?
If you keep walking around in
that clothing, I'll rape you!
Really?
Yuu-chan...
What? Uhh.
But Yuu-chan... I'm...
Not into BDSM at all!
Shut up!
Get changed and come down quickly.
What time is it now?
Shit, look at the time! If I don't hurry, I'll also be late!
Wake me up earlier then!
It's your fault for not waking up! I'm leaving now!
Wait!
My older sister, Akane, is my father's
remarried wife's daughter.
Which means... She's my step-sister.
I have nothing against my father nor my "new" mother.
The only issue is that this pretty woman
suddenly became my sister.
Hey! Wait!
The next bus comes in 15 minutes...
I'll never make it in time now.
Yuu-chan, I'll run instead, so... bye!
This pattern...
She's definitely going to...
Fall down.
Hey, you! Are you alright?
Do you need an ambulance?
Damn that stupid sister.
Kanzaki!
Hey, Kanzaki!
What happened? You alright?
Did you get into a fight?
Kind of.
Dude, there's no way Kanzaki would get into a fight!
Haha, he probably tried harrassing
a girl and got attacked for it!
Am I right, Kanzaki?
Shut up! It's not like that!
You're such a child, Yuu-chan.
I'm telling you it's not like that!
Grow up already.
You should learn some self-control.
Dude, Yoshioka... what are you saying?
Is your brain working properly?
I've learned... that women are not something to lay your
hands on, they're something to watch from a distance.
Huh?
Th... this place...
It took me ages to find this spot. The VIP seat for
appreciating the beauty of the inside of skirts!
Found? It looks more like you made it.
But even then...
We can't see the most important place!
Yeah!
Yes, that is the point!
This feeling when you don't see something that
can almost be seen! It gives us excitement!
Are you an idiot?
What's so fun doing this?
This is just the same level as how primary school
kids flick the skirts of their classmates.
Grow up a little!
How dare you! What other "important"
things are there then?
Follow me.
Hey stop it.
Hey can you lend me that?
My boobs are growing larger again!
Eh... I envy you.
I'm still size A!
Oh god!
Can you lend me your comb?
Th... this is...
If we're observing things, we should look at
"everything" instead of just underwear!
From here, you can't see us from the main
court, so you'll never get caught!
It took me so long to find this location.
Hey, don't you feel hot?
You're right... Can someone open the windows?
Oh shit!
Woah! We saw it!
Oh no!
I lost... Misaki, I lost...
It's good that you understand.
No, this isn't good enough!
I don't get satisfied so easily from just
looking at naked girls like you guys.
Also, Japanese girls are becoming outdated.
What's up with that?
I mean... Why don't you guys grow older?
Yup... just like this.
Th... this is!
Oh wow! She's licking them herself!
I didn't expect foreign women
to be able to do these things!
It's true that Japanese girls may
not able to do these things.
Actually, there's one nearby.
Really? Who?
Who is it?
Our leader, Yuka Tachihara!
What the hell are you looking at!
Leader!
You guys are not allowed to bring
these kind of books to school!
There is a really deep reason fan this.
I don't care about your stupid "deep reason"!
I'm confiscating this!
I'm going to mention this in the
next meeting, so be prepared!
You guys are such perverts!
Tch, she's a bitch as always.
I know right... Such a waste of
the baby face and nice body.
But still, why would she do that to her childhood friends...
Is he alive?
No idea.
Yup, Tachihara Yuka is my childhood friend.
We used to play together a lot when we were
young because we lived close to each other.
Thinking of it, the thing that awoke
something in me was her nice body.
But god knows when she turned into
a girl with such a strict personality.
She wasn't like this before...
Nurse Room
Excuse me.
Ouch... Dammit, I still feel pain
in various parts of my body.
I wonder where Tachihara got that giant hammer from.
My head's been in pervert-mode
whole day since this morning.
No, no, I need to calm down a little.
Huh?
What's this noise?
Ta... Tachihara... What is she doing?
Amazing!
Um...
Huh?
Damn... I've seen Tachihara doing such...
And...
I wasn't able to sleep properly last night.
Uhm... Good morning! Ye-yesterday was...
Tachihara...
Hey Kanzaki, come! Look at this! It's amazing!
Oh yea?
Since then, Tachihara and I stopped talking,
and it became very awkward.
Oh well, I still have my sister.
Hello?
Yuu-chan, I left some documents at home today...
Can you bring the brown envelope
on my desk to my workplace?
Eh... Do I have to?
Don't say that Yuu-chan... Come on...
P-L-E-A-S-E?
It should be around here...
God... Why am I wasting my school holiday on this?
Woah! Grown women are so much better!
Sis!
Men's toilet...?!
Boss, I'm still in my work hours...
If someone finds us...
Don't!
Come on, I'm stressed having to work over hours...
and also, isn't this situation so exciting?
No...
Boss!
Shit, I can hear everything clearly!
It's getting pretty wet down there... You ready for it?
Oh, this is...
This? Your brother just came in and
asked me to pass it on to you!
My brother?
Yuu-chan, are you awake?
Aw, he's left his erotic books all messy again.
Sis...
Oh, Yuu-chan, did I wake you up?
Thanks for bringing me the documents today.
Hey sis.
Yes?
Sis, do you do these things often?
Huh?
I saw you... walking into the men's
toilet and... doing things.
Yuu-cha...
Are you... Are you dating him?
No, Yuu-chan. Stop it!
You don't understand my feelings!
Dressed like that everyday... There's no way
a guy can handle looking at that normally!
No... Don't.
No, Yuu-chan don't! Sto... Stop it!
Do you think it's okay for us to do this? We're siblings!
Yea, we're siblings.
Siblings with no blood relation!
I love you Sis... I've always loved you.
I tried keeping my feelings inside,
but the feelings just kept growing.
And you're dressed like that?!
I can't handle it anymore.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do anymore!
Yuu-chan...
Will you promise me?
Huh?
Forget everything that will happen tonight.
Okay?
Sis...
Just tonight... promise?
Hey, can you open your legs a little more?
Sis, you're amazing... my hands are so wet now!
Yuu-chan, come inside me.
How is it Sis? Do you feel it?
Does it feel good?
It feels like I'm going crazy!
Then, lets be crazy together!
No... not there!
Everything went in.
No, Yuu-chan... It's going to break!
It's tight.
It's so good, Sis... I feel like
it's trying to suck it all inside.
Don't... make it so... intense!
Does it still hurt?
Yuu-chan... I'm feeling it with my asshole...
Yes... feel it more!
Sis... I'm already going to...
M-me too!
Sis... Sis!
Yuu-chan... Yuu-chan!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... with my asshole!
Ahh... Yuu-chan!
Sis!
Don't forget, Yuu-chan...
You're going to forget everything
tomorrow. Understood?
To that promise... I did not reply.
Not long later, Sis got married to that boss.
Oh dammit, we've ran out of the cold drinks!
I'll go buy some!
Oh, should I go instead?
No, you don't have to. Make yourself at home here!
Yes.
Kanzaki-kun... why?
No, I'm here for my sister...
Wait, so Sis's husband is Tachihara's brother?
Yes.
I didn't know...
It's surprising to hear that
Akane-san was your sister!
Then does that make us...
I guess you can call it siblings?
It's so strange.
Ye-yeah.
Kanzaki-kun!
Huh?
Do you remember... that time?
Well... um...
Tachihara?
Please Kanzaki-kun! Don't hate me!
Wha...
Ever since I was a kid, I loved you Kanzaki-kun.
That time... I was...
God, I can't believe boys enjoy reading
these books! Such perverts!
Why Kanzaki-kun... Why don't you look at me?
Do you only like girls who do things
like the women in these books do?
I wonder if I can do that too...
If I was able to do this... Will Kanzaki-kun like me more?
I did it! Kanzaki-kun, I can do this too!
Kanzaki-kun...
Since then, I wasn't able to look at your face anymore.
Because, I thought that you think of me as a slut...
But... but I...
Yuka.
Huh?
Yuka?
I'm looking at you Yuka. Yuka, does
it look like I think of you as a slut?
Yuu-kun...
Congratulations, Yuu-chan!
Sis!
Onee-san!
I feel happy for you! For making
such a pretty girlfriend!
But then Yuka-chan, there's a little
secret between me and Yuu-chan!
Secret?
Wh... What are you saying, Sis!
To be my brother's girlfriend, you need to keep this
secret! I wonder if you can keep it, Yuka-chan.
Sis... Are you going to...
If it's for Yuu-kun, I can keep any kind of secret!
What?
How nice! You're such a good girlfriend!
And like this...
Welcome!
Good evening! Onee-san!
Sis, where's your husband?
He's out for work. He won't be back until tomorrow.
So, also tonight, until morning we can...
It's not also tonight, Yuka-chan!
Ah, that's right.
Tonight only... tonight only... Alright?
Forget everything tomorrow.
Oh, yeah.
I have got Yuka involved in this dangerous game.
In the end I wasn't able to get over Sis... but...
Sis's "just tonight" is going to happen continuously.
Translator: thepinkunicorn
Editor: MetaZ
Timing: MrMew
Quality Check: Applepiee