Last summer...
...l met Chihiro, my first sweetheart, and started a long-distance relationship.
But l had a chance to date another girl unexpectedly.
l ended up having sex with her, but l was really just a victim of circumstance.
l was regretting what happened...
Then, l walked past Chihiro while l was on a date with the girl...
...and l didn't know what to do.
l absolutely don't want to break up with Chihiro.
l was willing to accept any blame to get her back, so l chased her...
...only to find that she was on a date with a strange man.
l know l screwed up.
But she also cheated on me.
We are finished.
Hikuson...
What's going on?
Are you looking for something?
M-My dog is...
A dog?
Hikuson, where are you?
Hikuson!
lt's so cold!
He might not be here...
Hikuson.
l don't know what to do.
Hey...
Hikuson!
ls it?
Hikuson, come out from there.
That's right, you should listen to your mistress.
Wait!
Are you all right?
Hikuson!
Chihiro, been waiting long?
Not very long.
Really?
That's good.
l haven't seen you for a long time.
How have you been?
Head over heels in love?
Excuse me.
Can l have a tea with milk?
What?
Don't play dumb.
lt's about Fukuroi-kun.
You bumped into a high school friend, who had moved away...
...and the two of you fell in love with each other, right?
How dramatic!
Yeah...
lt's so lucky that we are close to my place.
You would catch a cold if you went back home with wet clothes.
l'm sorry.
Don't say that.
Here we are.
No one else is home, so you can take a shower.
Thank you very much.
Here.
You are such a troublesome dog.
Your mistress got drenched to the skin.
Miku-chan is her name...
She's cute, but she still seems immature.
All right...
She may act young, but her body is sure mature enough...
l finished taking a shower.
Thank you very much.
Okay, it's my turn.
Please take your time.
Excuse me.
l can't leave my relationship with Fukuroi-kun vague.
l should talk to him and make it clear...
Hello?
ls this Fukuroi-san residence?
Yes.
Well...
Well, only Masato is here right now and he's taking a bath.
Hello?
What?
Who is she?
Actually...
She was just in this bath a minute ago.
My love affair with Chihiro is over.
Who cares if l make love to other girls?
Since then, Miku and l often met.
We both love reading, and we can talk for hours and hours.
However, we are just friends.
We get along, but we don't have any special feelings.
ls that so.
Anyway, Chihiro-chan isn't the only woman out there.
Don't be disappointed and good luck.
Yeah.
l won't be able to attend this party, either.
How about Chieri-chan?
l broke up with Chieri.
What a relief!
Why?
l can't get along with that sex animal.
l heard about your breakup, but l didn't know she was a sex fiend.
ls she perverted?
She's just into the normal stuff...
...but she's like a cat in heat.
Let's work together here on Christmas Eve.
We'll get an extra 50% per an hour 'cause it's overtime.
After l met Miku, l started working on my unfinished novel again.
But actually l am wondering how much...
...of what l put into the novel is the truth...
...because the story is about Chihiro and me.
ls that true?
Kind of.
That's wonderful.
Fukuroi-san will be a novelist.
l don't know if l really will.
Sure you will.
You definitely will.
You think so?
Good luck.
Only books and Hikuson used to be my friends...
...so l hope my new friend, Fukuroi-san, has his dreams come true.
Miku...
Please let me read it after you're done.
Sure, no problem.
ls it difficult to write a novel?
Not really.
l wonder if l can write.
You can.
What kind of story you want to write?
Well, a love story.
Sounds good.
l'm looking forward to reading your love story.
But, l can't do it...
Why?
l've never been kissed, and l've never had sex.
So, l can't write a love story.
ls that so?
You can't write such a thing without experience, can you?
l-l have no idea.
l want to write a love story.
Fukuroi-san!
Please kiss me.
My love affair of Chihiro is over.
l can do anything l want.
Miku wants me to.
Are you sure?
Yes, l want to write my own love story.
All right...
Oh, not there...
Shall l stop?
Here...
Touch this...
Yes, move slowly.
You're so good.
Move faster gradually.
Yes, make more noise.
Good, very good.
Don't let it go.
Keep sucking.
You may feel a little pain, but you'll have to get over it for sex.
Good, Miku.
Are you turned on?
Feels good?
l'm coming in.
Miku, this is sex.
So good, l feel like l'm melting.
Oh, l'm climbing.
lt's great.
l feel so good.
Such an innocent girl opens her heart for me.
She may not be able to do anything without me.
Oh, l'm coming.
Miku, l'm coming.
Come inside me!
Hey, Chihiro...
...has something been wrong recently?
What do you mean by that?
l felt something different when l met you last time.
lt's strange that you always hang out with me, who doesn't have a boyfriend.
Maybe you haven't been getting along well with Fukuroi-kun?
N-No, nothing like that.
Actually, we don't see each other much, because we live far away.
But, we talk on the phone everyday...
ls that so?
lt's true.
Chihiro isn't telling the truth.
But, l'm sure the cause of all this is Fukuroi-kun.
As a friend, l can't ignore it any more.
What?
You used to be Masato's classmate in high school?
Oh, l'm sorry.
He skipped work today.
He didn't show up because he has a cold.
A cold...
You know what...
You're his former classmate, that means you are a friend of Chihiro, right?
Yes.
Seems like they broke up with each other.
Masato is stupid to break up with Chihiro-chan, she's a great girl.
He won't get a girl like her again.
Excuse me...
Chihiro and Fukuroi-kun broke up?
When?
Oh, you didn't know?
lf you know what's going on, could you tell me?
All right, but here is not appropriate...
l'll finish my shift soon, so after that...
Why don't you let me know about Fukuroi-kun before doing this?
Don't rush me.
l have a terrible memory.
l am trying to bring the details to mind.
Well, what's with all the noise?
You're dripping everywhere.
But you came here for an important errand, didn't you?
Shall l stop in the middle?
No, don't stop it.
Oka-kun, have you remembered anything?
Wait, if you rush me too much, you'll make it harder for me to remember.
Well, Masato and Chihiro-chan...
Yes?
What happened to me?
l've become very forgetful, haven't l?
Oh, no.
Hey, Masato, how's your cold doing?
Kanna?
l heard from Oka-kun about what's going on...
Fukuroi-kun, you've really misunderstood Chihiro.
Misunderstood?
l saw Chihiro kiss somebody.
That gave you a big shock, l guess.
l haven't heard that Chihiro has a new boyfriend.
Even if you did see her kiss a man...
...l guess she was a victim of circumstance...
...or there was some good reason.
l agree, a kiss could happen under some circumstances.
lt's just a kiss.
l will ask Chihiro about the kiss.
l'll persuade her to do something...
...like apologize or explain it to you.
So, if Chihiro apologizes to you, please think about her again.
Chihiro hasn't said anything to me, but l know she still likes you very much.
Good news, right Masato?
You didn't start to hate her, did you?
This is a good chance to see her again.
That guy probably wasn't her boyfriend, and it was just a kiss.
lf you compare that to when l made love with Rei...
E-Excuse me.
Miku...
How are you?
Thank you for coming, but l have friends visiting...
l can't send them away...
l see, you have no choice.
Sorry.
Take this...
Vitamin C is good for a cold, l heard.
Oh, strawberries, thanks.
Please get well soon.
lf you are not well, l'm not well, either.
Yes, l'll recover soon.
Kanna.
Fukuroi-kun!
l have...
...to go.
Kanna.
Miku appeared, but l hadn't even introduced her to my friend, Oka.
Kanna, who was trying to mediate between Chihiro and me...
...was pretty shocked to see her.
After everything, l lost my chance to go back to Chihiro.
Did they go home because l came by and they took the hint?
l feel bad.
lt's not you.
You think so?
Fukuroi-san?
Could you do me a favor?
What?
Could you come with me to the Christmas party at Marine Palace?
Okay, sure.
Great!
You'll catch my cold.
l don't mind, as long as the cold is yours.
Miku!
lt's so good!
You went all the way to Namikaze City for me.
Thank you...
Chihiro...
l am fine.
l assumed that Fukuroi-kun and l had already broken up.
There's no problem.
So...
Sorry, l need to find a restroom.
Fukuroi-kun...
He's been seeing another girl, like l thought.
What to do?
l have no idea what to do.
Miku started to write a novel.
She used to be shy...
...but since she started writing, that's changed.
And she'll probably complete her novel before...
...l finish mine, because l'm so lazy.
lshimaru-san.
Chihiro-chan, do you have any plans for Christmas?
What?
l'm really impressed.
You story is so well organized, even though this is your first time.
l feel your character's passion first and foremost.
lt's interesting.
Really?
Oh, l'm so glad.
l'll read once more later and give you detailed comments.
Yes, please take care of me, my teacher.
Stop calling me a teacher.
Oh teacher, please let me read your novel soon.
Not finished yet.
lt's taking so long.
You're suffering from writer's block?
l-lt's not like that.
lf not, why don't you let me read it?
lt's okay, even if it's not finished.
No.
You should be looking forward to reading it.
l have to go to the bathroom.
You're so mean.
Without completing the novel, it seems...
...that my relationship with Chihiro is not really over.
However, l am being impolite to Miku.
l have to take care of her, she'll probably be relying on me from now on.
Fukuroi-san, this...
What is this?
ls this mine?
l'm sorry.
l took it and brought it home...
...because l was dying to read your novel.
After finishing, l wanted you to read it first, anyway.
Fukuroi-san, this story is based on real life, isn't it?
ls it true?
Yeah, some of it is based on real life.
Fukuroi-san, you still love her, don't you?
l hope you win back that love.
Win back love?
What are you talking about?
l'm going out with Miku right now.
How can you say that?
No, l'm not the person you are in love with.
You love the girl from this story.
Miku!
Fukuroi-san, you taught me how to write.
l have confidence in myself for the first time in my life because of that.
So, l want to return your kindness.
l want to do something for you.
Miku, you are...
l'm fine.
l have confidence in myself, but l'm sad because you are leaving me.
lf l write novels and express myself...
...l'll have a positive outlook on life.
l thought that Miku was immature, but she has become independent.
l was mortified, she pointed out my true intentions...
...which l had not realized.
Fukuroi-san, go see her!
l'll go see Chihiro.
lt's for myself.
l don't care what happens...
l'll go or l'll regret it...
...for the rest of my life.
That's life.
lt doesn't always go like a novel.
l'm so stupid.
lt's too late to...
...win back her love now.
lt's absolutely unrealistic.
Chihiro.
Fukuroi-kun.
Chihiro, why you are here?
This is so silly...
We're doing the same thing.
l went to your place, and then l heard you went my place...
...so l hoped you'd appear here.
ls that so...
l'm sorry.
l decided you were wrong for me without being sure.
l was wrong.
Forgetting about what l did, l blamed you.
Chihiro, why don't we go out again?
Yes!
Chihiro...
l'm coming!
Chihiro, l love you very much.
Fukuroi-kun...
Here l come.
You're so good...
Chihiro...
l love you...
l'm coming!
l-l'm coming!
The second chapter of our relationship started like that...
Finally, l've figured out how to develop the story l've always wanted.
Thanks to Chihiro, for everything.
Fukuroi-kun...
Yes?
Kiss me, please.