What a cute girl.
Breasts...
Belly button...
But l don't know about this bit.
All the times l've seen it, it's blurred out.
Fukuroi-kun.
Do you know me?
Who are you?
Have you forgotten me?
l have a feeling we've met before.
l moved here right after high school.
Now l go to a local junior college.
l decided to take a summer job at the Marine Palace.
Today is my first day.
Of course, it's for the money...
...but more than that, l am hoping to meet a girl.
What should we do now?
Well, it's such a nice day...
l just can't picture myself doing those things with a girl.
l wonder if l'll ever go to a hotel like that.
At one point l wanted to be a writer and tried to write a novel.
l wrote for a while, but then l realized it was just a pipe dream.
Well, my name is Yoshiro Oka.
l'm pretty serious, studying is my hobby.
l hope we can become friends this summer.
Pretty smooth, aren't you?
lt's good to be outgoing, but make sure you get your work done.
Of course.
Not a problem!
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Okay, next!
Yes!
My name is Masato Fukuroi.
Oka and l are classmates.
We hang out together.
Nice to meet you.
Great, l'm counting on both of you.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for waiting.
Yes, one moment please.
Yeah, actually l am a model.
Really, wow!
Oka is already working on that girl.
Chieri-chan, huh?
She's too good for Oka.
But look at him, he's really going for it.
l don't think l could do that.
Why are you just standing there?
Work, work!
l'm sorry.
Tiring, isn't it?
lt's tiring to have a job.
Right?
How would you know?
By the way, what do you think about Chieri-chan?
She's cute isn't she?
Well, yeah...
Don't even think about trying, she's mine.
Then, why ask me?
Sorry.
You can't have Chieri-chan, but don't worry...
Just look out there...
There are plenty of cute girls on the beach.
They're up for grabs, it's great!
Hey Masato, you're still a virgin, right?
Y-Yeah.
This is the perfect opportunity to meet a cute girl and get some action.
Oka is right.
But for some reason...
...l'm thinking about the mysterious girl...
...in my dreams, not the girls down on the beach.
Welcome.
C-Can l take your order?
Fukuroi is getting used to this job, isn't he?
Yeah, l've been giving him some tips.
Still room for improvement though...
Right...
And what about yourself?
Oh yeah, Table Three asked for another beer!
Excuse me...
Welcome.
lt is you, Fukuroi-kun.
So, you did move here.
You're taller.
But you really...
...haven't changed since high school.
That makes me happy.
lt's her.
Have you forgotten me?
You're Chihiro Asaoka?
Yes!
Have l changed?
l guess you're a little taller, too.
That's all?
Chihiro.
Waiting long?
Not really.
Let me introduce you to my friend from high school.
This is Masato Fukuroi.
l just bumped into him.
What a coincidence!
l'm Shingo Kunimi, nice to meet you.
Y-Yeah.
Same here.
Chihiro is staying at my house for a while.
Please come and visit.
Sure.
Shall we go?
Yes, see you later.
Shingo-san!
Good looking chick.
Friend of yours?
You've got yourself quite a rival.
Not only is he the son of the city councilman...
...he competed in the National Ski Championships.
Don't you just hate his good looks?
N-No, l'm not interested in her.
Are you sure?
Yes, l'm sure.
Well, you don't stand a chance anyway.
But, boys will dream.
Only a fool would throw away his fantasies.
Chihiro-chan's gotten so pretty.
l can't believe l said...
''l guess you're a little taller, too.''
l had a crush on her all through high school.
Now l realize that l've never gotten over her...
Fukuroi-kun...
Chihiro...
You're beautiful.
You've become more beautiful than l've ever imagined.
Thank you, Chihiro.
Kiss me.
C-Chihiro, l love you.
l've been waiting for this so long.
Me too.
ls this your clitoris?
Does it feel good here?
l'm not sure.
That feels good!
ls this right?
Does it feel good?
Yes, very good.
lt's big.
lt's just normal size.
Fukuroi-kun, do you want me to put it in my mouth?
What?
Only if you want to...
That's nice.
So wet and smooth...
l wonder if it feels this good inside her.
Maybe it's even better.
l'm going to come.
l want to come inside you!
Stop it.
l can't hold back!
Was that a good dream or a bad dream?
l'm not sure...
Those two!
But the likes of Masato annoy me even more.
Hey, Fukuroi!
l'm sorry.
Come on, pay attention.
Yes.
By the way, l heard from someone...
ls your friend from high school called Chihiro-chan?
Yes.
She is the cousin of that guy, the city councilman's son.
She's staying at her uncle's for the summer.
Really?
That makes you happy, huh?
N-Not really...
Legally, she could marry her cousin.
Yeah, they must be lovers.
Life's rough, isn't it?
Cheer up.
This is the spring of your youth.
Thank you very much.
The Boss tells me this great news, then starts talking crap.
lt didn't comfort me at all.
Hey, Masato.
Come here a sec.
We're on duty now, what is it?
There's a crack in the wall.
You can see right into the women's shower.
No way.
What happens if we get caught?
Who do you think is taking a shower?
lt's Chieri-chan.
Chieri-chan?
Don't you want to see her?
l wanted to keep it to myself...
...but l thought l'd share with my poor chick-less friend.
You should be thankful.
Can you see?
Almost...
She's turning this way.
l want to see!
Yes Chieri-chan!
Turn this way, please!
Chieri-chan's looking for a boyfriend.
l will make her mine.
Maybe it's a waste of time thinking about Chihiro.
Maybe l should go for someone around here, like Oka is.
Looking for a boyfriend...
Chieri-chan...
l'll do it for you.
That feels good.
Stick it in...
Stick your penis into me!
lt feels good, Chieri-chan.
B-Boss!
lt's none of my business, but you are on duty now.
l'm sorry.
Clean that wall and get back to work.
And you might want to consider locking the door when you're in the toilet.
Yes.
You're really buying?
Order anything you like.
Today is payday, so my pockets are full.
Masato, you pay for your own.
l know.
l'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
Masato...
Yeah?
l'm gonna do it tonight.
l'm gonna do it with Chieri.
l envy Oka.
lf only l had half the nerve he has.
There's still a lot of summer left.
l'm sure something good will come your way.
lt's Chihiro-chan and Mr. Handsome.
Yeah.
Come on, why don't you do something to take her from him?
That's impossible.
You have nothing to lose.
lf you're so hung up on saving face and being cool...
...you'll never get a girl.
This is your chance, go!
Ouch!
G-Good evening.
Good evening.
Um...
We finally met up...
...let's get together, just the two of us, and reminisce...
...that is, if you have time...
...when it's convenient for you.
How about tonight?
What?
Are you busy?
No...
But, what about your boyfriend?
Well then, take good care of her.
Yes.
l wonder if Fukuroi-san's gonna be okay?
Who knows...
By the way...
Um, well...
Yes?
Uh, well...
You're acting strange, Fukuroi-kun, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Damn!
l always know what to say in my fantasies.
Why can't l come up with anything in real life?
Fukuroi-kun, why did you move without telling anyone?
Everyone was really surprised.
My father was suddenly relocated by his company.
l didn't want to move.
l had no choice.
l've been thinking about you this whole time.
What?
Chihiro is sitting next me now.
So close l can feel the warmth of her skin...
She is not a distant dream, but the closest person to me.
The person l adore.
Excuse me...
Yes?
Yes, well...
Kunimi-san sure is a handsome guy...
Yes, he is.
Even from a guy's standpoint, he's good looking.
l could never compare to him.
That's not true.
You're handsome too.
l read your story in high school and thought...
...how amazing, to be able to write something like that.
That story...
l'm embarrassed.
Are you still writing?
Not anymore.
Why?
l'm not any good.
l thought you wanted to be a novelist.
l thought you were a great guy with a dream.
l should get going.
Yeah...
l thought you were a great guy with a dream.
Damn.
Huh?
That's Oka's bicycle.
That's no good.
You can suck better than that.
But you're distracting me too much!
No excuses!
All right.
Look Chieri...
What's this?
Pervert.
l'm going to come!
So good!
l'm coming!
Tastes funny.
But l don't mind, because it came from the man l love.
You're so sweet...
So much came out!
l can give you more.
Wanna go for round two?
Oka had sex with Chieri, just like he said.
Meanwhile, l screwed things up with Chihiro.
At this rate, l will never go out with anyone.
Becoming a novelist with just an imagination...
That was a really stupid idea.
But, boys will dream.
Only a fool would throw away his fantasies.
You have nothing to lose.
lf you're so hung up on saving face and being cool...
...you'll never get a girl...
l'll apologize Chihiro for that awkward parting.
Then, l will ask her out again.
lt's so beautiful.
Yes.
Kunimi-san, don't just watch, come join me.
Which one you want to try next?
Here is your change, 340 yen.
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
Fukuroi-san seems to be getting better.
lt looks like it.
Oh?
Kunimi-san.
Hello.
Chihiro is going back home today.
ls that so?
l won't see her for a while.
What do you mean?
l love Chihiro.
l've wanted to marry her since l was a little kid.
But Chihiro told me that she can only think of me as a brother.
l think maybe she likes you.
l have a feeling.
Kunimi-san.
Chihiro's at the beach.
She said she was going for a walk before leaving.
l think maybe she likes you.
Fukuroi-kun.
l-l've always loved you.
l have always loved you, too.
You smell good.
l've waited for this day.
So have l.
Ouch.
S-Sorry.
Be gentle with me.
Sure.
lt's so beautiful.
lt's shiny.
Don't stare at it.
l'm embarrassed.
Does this mean your body is ready?
l don't know.
This is my first time.
Ready?
Yes.
Ouch.
l'm sorry.
Shall l stop?
Don't stop!
Please keep going.
Feels good...
Yes...
l'm starting to feel strange...
Strange?
More...
More, faster, faster!
Like this?
Yes, yes, more, more...
Fukuroi-kun...
Deeper!
Chihiro...
Yes, right there...
l can't hold back any longer.
Me neither...
l'm coming!
l'm so lucky to have my first time be with my first love.
Me too.
lt'll be a long distance relationship.
We'll make it work.
Yes!
Come and see me when you finish your new story.
l'll be waiting.
Right!
l feel like our bodies connecting has connected our hearts.
l've got to finish my novel so l can see Chihiro.
l once thought l didn't have talent.
But now, l know l can write something good.
And l'm sure it's because Chihiro has given me the strength.