Last summer, l happened to meet Chihiro, the girl l've loved since high school.
Chihiro had become much more beautiful than l had expected.
We had some misunderstandings, but we confessed our love for each other...
...by the end of summer.
We became one, and it was the first time for both of us.
lt was such a beautiful memory...
However, the sex was a little more tame than l had hoped...
l will enjoy having wild sex with Chihiro...
...someday.
l love you, Chihiro.
Stop...
Aren't you hungry?
There are such delicious foods in front of me, so l have to eat them.
Later...
Oh, really?
What are you doing?
Don't worry, don't worry.
You can continue cooking us a nice meal.
Why aren't you cooking?
You're mean...
Well, what shall l do?
lt's yummy down here.
You're naughty...
l'm coming in.
How is it, Chihiro?
Feels good.
lt doesn't sound that way.
lt does, l like it!
How about this?
So good!
l'm gonna die!
Fukuroi!
Yes!
Yes, where shall l read?
Who asked you to read?
This is becoming a habit, Masato...
What are you day-dreaming for?
l'm sorry...
l was thinking about a story.
l've been encouraged by my relationship with Chihiro...
...to write again.
The story l'm working on now is based on my relationship with her.
There have to be some sex scenes in this story.
lt doesn't mean l'm a sex maniac...
Maybe...
What are you doing?
You bastard!
What?
You just groped my ass!
l didn't do that!
You liar.
You're a frustrated dick head!
l don't lie.
Then, who did it?
l don't know, why do you suspect me?
All men are the same.
You're dirty, indecisive and irresponsible.
Get lost!
l don't want to see you ever again.
You get lost.
l have Chihiro now.
l'm not interested in other girls.
Especially not a troublemaker like her.
After all, l'm not a playboy.
Absolutely not!
Welcome.
How are you?
What would you like to order?
One special burger, please.
Right, one special burger.
Thank you for waiting.
Than you very much.
Fukuroi-kun, l wish you a good luck on your story.
l've been working hard, too.
lt's now autumn.
l want to finish my story as soon as possible and go to see Chihiro.
My goal is to complete it by the School Festival.
Huh?
Look who's here.
The pervert from before!
l didn't do it.
How many times do l have to tell you?
l know you didn't.
l'm sorry if you took it personally.
l took out my anger on you...
May l?
What is your name?
M-My name is Masato Fukuroi...
Fukuroi?
Unusual name.
Never heard it before...
My name is Rei.
Rei Kashiwazaki.
Rei...
Well, what are you doing on next Saturday?
Nothing special...
Do you want to go to Tokyo with me?
l'll take you out...
...as an apology.
l don't know what to say...
No objections?
Okay, it's settled!
We've made a promise to have a date in Tokyo, next Saturday!
Rei Kashiwazaki...
She's a strange girl.
Well, it should be okay to go out with her once.
l haven't been to Tokyo for a while...
Masato!
Phone call from Chihiro-chan!
All right!
Hello, Chihiro?
Yes, Fukuroi-kun!
You did say you like Harlem Heat, didn't you?
That's right.
l have all their CD's!
l've got tickets for their concert.
Shall we go?
That's great, l'd love to go.
When is it?
Next Sunday.
Sunday...
Something wrong?
Do you have other plans on that day?
No...
lt's okay, let's go.
lt will be a little difficult to go to Tokyo two days in a row.
But, l have no choice.
Even if l wanted to cancel the date...
...with Rei, l don't know how to contact her.
How are you?
Chihiro-chan is in a good mood today.
Something good happen?
l'm going to a concert with my boyfriend on Sunday.
That's good.
Which one?
Harlem Heat.
Cool, l like Harlem Heat too.
What a coincidence.
Yes!
We're finally having a date!
Even though we often talk on the phone...
...we haven't seen each other since that day...
Fukuroi-kun...
Chihiro, l love you.
lt's inside me...
Fukuroi-kun is inside me...
We've become one...
l'm together with the man l love.
Chihiro!
Fukuroi-kun...
l love you, Fukuroi-kun!
l don't know what to do with Chieri.
l'm really tired.
She is definitely a sex maniac.
She lives to have sex.
That crazy?
She's worse than crazy, man!
You have a tough life.
How about you?
Things okay with Chihiro-chan?
Oh, it's so so.
So so?
You've just started to see her recently...
That's not good.
You should see her more often and nail her again.
Okay...
l will definitely have sex with Chihiro after the concert!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Hi, Fukuroi-san.
Sorry, l'm stealing Oka now.
See you...
Let's go.
Wait...
Hey, is it going to be okay in here?
Sure, my cousin owns this lot.
But...
Feels good.
Oka, thrust your hips more!
Don't be lazy!
Yeah, yeah...
Saturday...
l came to Tokyo with Rei.
l feel bad about not telling Chihiro that l am having a date with some other girl.
But, l should keep the promise.
So, you're from Tokyo.
You look like a Tokyo guy, now that you mention it.
Namikaze City isn't exactly the boonies.
There isn't much difference between Tokyo and Namikaze.
Only a Tokyo person would say that.
There is a big difference between the two, like heaven and hell.
lf you say so.
You should know this area well.
Show me the hot spots and the good restaurants.
l stayed here only until high school.
l don't know any fashionable places or anything.
That's disappointing.
Shall we go soon?
We've walked so much...
What's wrong?
There is a place l want you to come with me.
Together?
Where?
lt's getting a little chilly.
Are you supposed to meet someone?
We should go to Tokyo station soon.
The last train will be gone...
l'm sorry...
Could we wait until the next one?
Okay.
ls he the one?
l'm back.
Welcome.
Welcome!
Have you been a good girl today?
Rei, is that your...
Yes, that's my father.
l'm sorry that l dragged you around all this time.
That's okay, don't worry.
We've missed it.
l'm sorry.
lt's my fault.
What do we do?
l'm staying over lto's.
Yeah, lto, my friend from High School.
Yes...
l missed the last train, there's nothing l can do.
Yeah.
l will come home tomorrow, l promise.
Good night.
She is a tough one.
Rei?
l'm tired.
l'm going back to my room to sleep.
Sure.
Today was a tiring day.
Well, good night!
Good night.
She acts like she's fine.
Will she be all right, going back to Namikaze City by herself?
Yes?
Hi, it's me.
Fukuroi-kun!
l thought you wouldn't call me again today.
l'm sorry to call you late.
Hey, what are you wearing tomorrow?
l'm not saying we should dress fancy...
...but let's plan ahead so we at least match.
Well...
l'm sorry to tell you this the night before...
l can't make it tomorrow.
What?
l have to finish a big project for the School Festival, and l can't skip it.
l'm sorry.
ls that right?
l will make it up to you, l promise.
l understand...
You have no choice.
You will have to buy me a very nice meal when l see you next time.
All right.
See you soon.
See you.
Rei...
When l was in the fifth grade...
...my parents got divorced because my father had an affair...
...with another woman.
Since l was very small...
...my father had gone out with many women.
l thought it was quite natural that my parents got divorced.
l was taken by my mother, since then, l haven't seen my father.
l didn't think l wanted to see someone who betrayed my mother...
Then l learned that my father was living in this area of Tokyo.
Somehow, l've been thinking about it ever since.
l should hate my father.
l should disrespect my father.
l knew that l shouldn't, but l wanted to see him.
My mother and l have had a very difficult life.
But, my father has such a happy family now...
You always wanted to see your father.
You should be happy that your father is living happily.
You're right, l know l would be...
...happy for him...
But, when l think about his happy wife and daughter, l can't stand it!
l don't like myself.
l'm not a nice person.
Rei...
Thank you...
Thank you for being with me now.
Good...
Masato, make me feel better...
Yes...
Yes!
Rei...
Masato...
More!
ls this good?
Do you like it?
Yes, very good.
Come on, put it in.
Put in little Masato.
Okay.
More...
Masato...
Rei is so attractive.
l can't believe she's the same age as me.
The sex is so good!
Oh, yeah!
Rei...
Masato...
lt's so good, Masato.
ls it good?
lt's so good...
Masato, it's good...
Hold back, hold back...
l'm coming.
Welcome.
Uh, Chihiro-chan?
Good morning.
What happened?
You don't look so good.
Today's date was canceled.
l was looking forward to it.
Oh no...
lshimaru-san, do you have a plan after work today?
No, l don't...
Would you like to use the extra ticket?
l have Chihiro.
But, l slept with Rei.
l'm so unfaithful.
What's the matter?
Nothing...
Are you regretting that you slept with me?
You have a girlfriend, right?
l'm sorry.
You shouldn't fool around, you're a good boy.
l will say good-bye to you now.
Can we do it one last time?
You have to stay in good shape...
...for your girl.
Rei...
After all, we can't let what happened be just a one night stand.
You're already hard as a rock!
Harlem Heat!
l'm so excited...
Yeah...
lt's just too bad that l'm the one coming with you.
That's not true.
The ticket's extra, l'm happy to go with someone with the same taste in music.
You don't need to be polite.
l'm not...
l can have a date with Fukuroi-kun anytime.
l should enjoy going out with lshimaru-san today.
lshimaru-san is nice.
l won't do anything to upset anyone.
l shouldn't be feeling bad about it at all.
That was...
lf you take the next train, you'll get back to Namikaze City by late afternoon.
You'd better not drop any clues about what we did last night.
Sure...
What is it?
You've been quiet.
Are you still regretting that you've slept with me?
lt's not that.
Then, what?
Tell me what's wrong.
l can't guess.
lt's not your fault.
lt's not.
Why are you looking so miserable, then?
We just walked passed my girlfriend.
What?
She saw us together.
You fool!
Why didn't you explain it to her then?
Because l slept with you anyway.
That doesn't matter!
Go and apologize to her.
What shall l say?
Tell her the truth if you can't lie!
lf you really love her, she will able to feel it.
Thank you!
Chihiro, l'm sorry.
lt's my fault.
l'm sorry...
You were looking forward to that concert and everything.
Don't worry about that.
You aren't feeling well.
Even if you went home by yourself, l won't feel like listening to the music alone.
l'm so sorry.
Who is that guy?
She went to the concert with some other guy because l canceled.
Thank you, lshimaru-san.
l'm feeling better now.
That's good.
l'm really sorry about the concert.
Don't mention it anymore!
l see...
Could he really be her boyfriend?
Chihiro wouldn't secretly be going out with another guy, would she?
By the way, Chihiro-chan.
Yes?
lt seems too sudden but...
Yes...
l know you have a boyfriend...
But l need to say this.
l love you!
l...
Yes, l can't trust Fukuroi-kun now.
lshimaru-san is nice and he will be more faithful to me...
l'm sorry, but no...
Chihiro-chan...
l'm sorry...
l can't...
Dammit!
l didn't know Chihiro had a boyfriend in Tokyo!
Why did she go out with me?
Chihiro turned out to be a slut.
l was just a random guy she had a one-night stand with.
lt was a lie that she loved me since we were in high school.
lt was a lie...
...and l believed her.
l'm a complete fool!
Oh, very hot, Chihiro.
Yes, there...
You like it here?
How about in here?
Oh, yes!
More!
lt happened one day in late autumn...
...the day l felt winter right around the corner.