Guy!
Finished!
Next goal is coming,
leave it in your hand.
I know!
What are the milk bottle's overlay
and mud,
add medal's needle for'?
You try to look back,
How many dangers have we spend?
We are as a team of special attract,
which is the loyal machine to country.
But, it is not the country now.
We are living for our own glory.
The guy has come back.
Having been to New York!
Using a team of troop,
but not to say it is the ghost of white-hair.
There is no way to kill Mi.
Go! Indian!
This is my glory! Captain Mr.Bai.
The last attracting
Following to Cimuguijie.
I convince you,
you never could win the Mi for one time.
Estimating me again!
How about?Madam.
Nice!
You are creditably Luomaniganli in 78.
One more again!
You are too immoderateness, Mi.
It is Madam?
I am Mrs. Cimuguijie now!
I am not killer Mi!
I see ,Madam!
Boss really have chosen
this woman as wife.
Ligu!
Yes Madam!
Your dressing up don't look like you!
I think I must not be found!
I believe enemy can't think we are here.
No, we will be found.
GPX is not a easy question.
You...
Later, you will be opponent of USA.
The guy must run after here.
Then Boss!
At that time it is the chance!
We will see who would win at last.
The last end!
Stop!
Who are you?
This car hasn't registered!
Minister Shiji!
Boss, something is wrong.
What? Zuozu, Liqi.
All of them are policeman on the street.
What?
Too many.
It has set the surrounding net.
Strange!
All of them are old-age policeman!
What? It is classical troop
Follow right now.
Everybody is very exciting.
You didn't find clue jet?
Don't worry, captain!
Take it easy same as before.
Enjoying at same time.
Copter?
Not only one!
Fools!
Why do they wave hands?
It will be put out of existenced!
It was thought
it is copter of reinforcement.
It is our own state,
nobody dare atrract it.
Except me!
Stop, Zu, don't attract the copter.
Why? What is happened?
Because you attracted the copter.
White-hair gost!
He used the troop copter
same with us on porpose.
You want to try, Zu.
Isolated in the forest.
When we have surrounded by Vietcong,
what kind of feeling
do we have to wait the copter.
Only copter is the backbone of life.
It is the living chance!
It is also everything that guide wife,
lover and family.
How should I do? Captain?
Life belt
Appearing the Vietnam battlefield.
Long time no fight.
Yes.
What are you finding without porpose.
OK, come on.
Kill him, kill him, kill him!
I am Captain Mr.Bai, every director,
all things have finished!
Dismiss!
You can go home!
GO HOME!
We can be in use that
they have been to utmost.
In classical troop,
it remained you and me.
We can pretend to
get on copter for running off.
In fact, they are waiting for us.
Wonderful fighting!
Are you the director
in the classical troop?
Right, Mr.Bai.
Vice director!
Speak out!
Order you, the name who killed me!
Who is the GPX's headman.
I won't say even if I have last breath.
If you want to know, kill me.
Ready go!
You are creditably
professional teams vanguard!
Ownsome attract!
The opponent is me this time.
Cimuguijie! Boss!
You are awake, guy!
We have said you will speak out GPX.
Do you want to know GPX, help us cure.
Same as in Vietnam.
Help us cure, even give a woman to us.
Then we will speak out.
Death.
This is not Vietnam.
What's this place?
Follow mw.
This way.
Give you a surprise, right?
You two
My ship,White-haired gost!
Take the Kongmu back to transfrom
which used in the Second War.
In the name of moving ship,
you can receive the licence of sailing.
There are all the medicine facility
and 40 professional doctors
and more than 70 nurses
including the copter
which send the patient into hospital.
You have saw.
White-hair gost
hasn't eat the food for a week.
But Zu,
that guy is on the contrary with him.
Eat much food.
Doing exescise in house.
How are you going to do?
What time are you going to see until?
Boss?
Speaking out by beat is faster than it.
That guy is waiting for chance.
Chance?
To us, they know.
They are the only clue.
Delay as soon as possible,
you will be worry if you are waiting for us.
Waiting for attracting chance
in this method.
So wait! Waiting for that chance.
Too bad! Asking for doctor!
Something is wrong with White-hair gost.
It has been put into
propriety nutrition.
It doesn't matter.
There is no danger about life.
It is nothing with you.
I am in outside,
call me if you have something.
What?
The thorned wrist is very painful,
asking for nurse.
OK,wait I.
What?This liquidum?
Darned.
This guy!
Nutrition succus bottle has been changed
into soap succus by me.
If it is injected into body,
it will distroy the blood.
This woman is going to die soon!
Help me!
Asking White-hair gost.
Get ready the food for us especially
and listen to us.
Is this your cavalier?
White-hair gost.
Speak out!
So, you have known this,
if you want to change the condition,
ifs very easy.
You and one more leave here,
others go.
Two to two, same condition.
The decisive battle will be started
in this Kongmu.
Limiting the weapon!
Installing the explosive first,
Kongmu must be sunk in four hour.
In case that I was defeated,
about GPX, all what we have know.
Recorded in the recorder in advance.
How about, only one place for survive.
Death battle.
At last, we will receive succuss.
But who will win?
Do you want to bet?
OK
Then, choose your parter.
Have you deceided?
It's me.
Mi!
Go at full pelt together!
Excepe me, Mrs. Cimuguijie.
Nobody!
Do you hear it?
Fighting with a little girl,
we have been ignored into this step.
Are you kidding?
The guys are the expert of attracting.
Only Boss and Mi have no chance to win.
Boss has agreed?
You said I have no qualification?
I am a professional killer too.
But.
Mi, don't speak anything.
Change with one of us.
Everybody don't want to see Mi to die.
Thank you!
Most thanks are your favor.
If this battle was defeated this time,
the revenge has no end.
Cimuguijie will lose in the former lover.
I must win!
I will live with Mi.
Good luck,Boss!
There are only four persons on ship.
About GPX, the recorder.
On the antennae on the bridge.
If we lost.
Listening all things about GPX
from there.
I see.
Apart soon under gound.
At end, we will start the battle.
This is the closedown world inside.
That is to say,
In the country, there are two,
organization without aid
and no way to run away.
Last battle, last attracting!
Start out!
Be quick!
It can't fight, be quick!
No, the war has started out!
This is what White-hair gost said
in the copter.
That is the sign for starting war.
This is the Vietnam method.
There is no justice and supervision
on the war.
Since it has been apart,
Defeating enemy is everything.
I know.
You have way.
This is vietcong's forte active.
Cimuguijie! Boss!
Are you OK?
Of course!
Dangerl Cimuguijiel
It is really marvelous,black-hair gost.
I am really happy fighting with you!
Cimuguijie, kill Bail
I Will find Zu!
I will distroy the time
which they cooperated.
One to one!
Mi!
See you on the deck,Cimuguijie!
Only we two,
pack away him in one breath.
And..
It is so sudden!
It is very interesting, little girl.
Originally,
I want to enjoy you then kill you,
but there is no time,
I will kill you in one breath.
Are you feel happy?Bey!
Darned!
Ship begin to sink!
Boss! Mi!!
I will kill you.
Come on, white-hair ghost!
There is only one hour until ship sink.
Only you and me,
can get on here.
Janpanese swordman heard
a man named sword
will say Bye each other before fighting.
Speak out the last words first!
If it is here now,
I will wait for Mi.
Ten minites again.
Give me time to wait for Mi.
OK
I won't let Mi die.
I will kill you in my own hand.
This is my last glory.
Why do you help me?
Because of accident.
Because of accident? Right!
Do we have the decision battle?
You are marvellous!
Go ahead!
Using it to get on the deck.
Continuous battle in my life.
I have never fight with woman.
But at last, maybe I will fight with
you kind of woman.
This is my hope!
Go ahead!
Be quick!
Zu!
Ten minites has passed.
This is all!
Mi, Cimuguijie!
Zu!
She has been drown for me!
Come on!
Ready Set!
Go!
Run off on propose?
This kind of dead place,
it is not easy to find it!
Zu must find this kind of
dead place!
He can die in White-hair ghost hand.
Good!
A sentence named despair.
Sorry, I must send this sentence to you.
White-hair ghost!
Your renvenge,
when you heard this recorder, you
will understand this sentence meaning.
GPX is one of chance in CIA.
GPX's real name,
is not movie make.
The former name is
GREAT
PERSON X
Something in the world.
Reseach thuggism methods machine.
So ifs headman of CIA.
The headman of making movie.
Is the something in finance industry.
That is the auditorship
for collecting the information.
And it is not exist.
Before you go back to USA,
CIA superior has been
dismissed at that time.
It is another man now.
Your renvenge opponent is not exist.
Even if it has, that is the CIA too.
Even if it is State Union.
Dispair will bring new life sometimes.
White-hair gost!
You are marvellous man!
It must be open the future.
You defeated us!
After it, it has become into revenge!
How about later? Cimuguijie?
If the scar is still on my body,
my revenge won't finish.
About this thing,
I leave it in your hand, CIA superior.
Tell me the end after finishing!
I see, President