Good night, white-hair ghost
Right, ifs No. 2 leader now
Cimuguijie
Are you Mi?
I researched your auditorship,
I want to meet you
We'll meet on the hummock
at 2 o'clock tomorrow
Boss,
there's something wrong with the car
What? What's the matter, Zuozhu?
I'd seen the engine before we started
There's a wire touch
the conduct electricity
between the admeasure machine
and constringe machine
If we only look at it simply,
we can't find it
and there's a hole in the oil kong
the petrol's lost little by little
Then what about the car?
Don't worry, Liqi
As long as we drive it quietly,
it can't burst
Why didn't you say that earlier?
Boss, so
even if we go there
maybe that guy won't come
It doesn't matter, Ligu Go, Zuozhu
I want to research that guy who
follows with us
Is it Laosilaisi?
He's asserting our speed, ifs right
Here he comes!
Ah, the Mi
You come here
please your wet clothes
There's some clothes here,
please get on the deck after that
You understand?
Mi, it's the center of the sea here
what's more
we have much time,
let's have a good talk
I'll kill Jialilu
and you come to kill me
Do you know who the leader of GPX is?
Right, I destroyed the engine
so this ship only use the sail
It's impossible that
you want to control it
If you kill me, then you'll die
Ah, do you think I scare to die
You're really great,
as a tool of murther
can it be used?
No!
So cool!
Mi, ifs time to drink
Really? Can't it be connect?
What's the matter with you, Mi?
Are you afraid? I'll smash
your cool heart
No!
Is it that girl who never cried?
How come she became so?
My odium
Will he deal with the heart?
Where're you, Mum?
Mum, you're there!
Mum!
Xihu... Biji
It's very toilsome,
please give me the medicine...
Please give me the medicine... I beg you
I may promise you
Please give me the medicine
That grandma takes it
It seems that that girl is Mi
Hey, who let her take herion?
I think grandma know something
She took it two nights
but she didn't know anything
she only took good care of Mi
Medicine!
It seems that she know nothing about GPX
Listen, don't use this way any more
Yes, sir
Did you deal with the thing
about the hospital? Yeah
Boss, ifs impossible that
we'll revenge the guy like this
I only want to give you an advice
I hate doctor!
And I'm not sick
If you're not sick
you killed so many people,
why do you still keep quiet?
And your eyes when you saw fire
What happened before...
on earth?
My wife
named Biji died
How did you love her?
I can't say it out
but ifs true
Do you love her now?
Do you know the meaning of the red road?
The ebullient love
Biji liked this kind of flower very much
I'll send you a flower like this
Mi, the present's a little rude
but I'd like
to take it
Genie
Ligu, what's the matter on earth?
Boss bought the hospital
and doctors and nurses
What?
Maybe you love that girl?
Wordy!
Patrol seriously!
I know, Ligu
I'll use the therapeutics to you now
Please relax
Open your eyes
Is it you who's in picture?
And another one is your mother, right?
Don't look at other place,
look carefully
Come here!
Please think carefully
what happened when you were a child
Where're you, Mum? Mum!
Mum!
Mum! Mum!
Mum, help me! I beg you!
Mum, I beg you! Help me!
Mum Mum!
No!
Guijie!
You called out my name
You only violate me
and I'm being ravished
It's useless
I'll not tell you anything
I don't know anything
It's teacher who took in the order
and I only act on the instructions
Teacher?
Right, he took good care of me
Mum dislike me
because I'd not were born
she sell me to teacher
Mi!
Why did you kill yourself?
It means that Mi really loves Boss
Then she'd not kill herself
so I said you were a child
Liqi
Mi's a professional killer
she's in love with Boss
she has to choose to die
You understand?
It's really complicated
I... I...
Only in order to get the intelligence
about the organization
I huged Mi
And my excuse is that
she wants to kill me
And I normalize my action
In fact, my heart is full of evil desire
For my private desire, I... Mi
And Mi saw through my heart
I regarded Mi as a tool
Listen to me, Mi
Let me make expiation
Mom Mom
Mam!
Mom! No!
Mom! Open the door!
I beg you not to present me to others!
Mom! I beg me, let me in!
Mam!
Mi, go away!
If your performance is excellent,
you're a good kid
Mi
When I see you to recover
it'll be time for us to
be Nunc Dimittis
What's it?
Cimuguijie
Bad! The opponent is Classic Force
And the opposite army arrive here too
It's OK Bullets always miss the target
Don't worry.
You're really a boss
How long can you stand to
fight against them?
Guys They're soldiers
retiring from the 2nd world war
and the Vietnam War
I've asked the great guy
Liqi, tell every doctor
to take sanctuary at present
OK!
Cimuguijie!
Cimuguijie, why do you protect me?
The driver knows the destination
Wait for our contact!
They're coming!
Everybody, get ready to fight!
Wait, I didn't heard it need to be cured
Guy!
Let's start!
We'd team them a good lesson!
The guy is very doubtful!
Who're you'?
Sir!
Mi, I come to end the final situation
Ah, what do you want to do?
Mi, you can't provent me
Cimuguijie!
They rush here!
They won't last long.
They like battle?
How come!
Cimuguijie!
I come to see you!
Sir!
I'm your opponent
Do you believe you can win me
with the skill I taught you?
Mi, you're an disquarlified killer
I'll beat you now
How dare you say that?
Cimuguijie
You... from today on
we'll have USA as our enemy
USA?
Bad:
Boss! This ism?
Mi saved me
It's not OK here, boss
Most of them are wounded
Go! Boss!
How come ifs so! Their truck!
Let me do with it!
Captain Bai, ifs me
Sorry, it failed
No...
they didn't return to the villa and grot
Got it, we must succeed next time
(Mediterranean. Golusika)
Do you still want to revenge?
Cimuguijie
The opponent is a nation
A nation? He means USA
I will do it,
No matter who the opponent is
I won't stop fighting
till the revenge is finished
To kill or to be killed
I'll follow you
forever