It is said villagers in the dorp
are much passionate for searching gold
There have been
many moneybags appearing.
Yes, such fellows
called Gold-searching men
No wonder.
Are eager to become rich men
in one night.
Yes, I've heard there are
some Japanese amony them,
although ifs only rumors.
Ah,
lam planing to
have a influencing report
in this program
So Kouxia will be on vocation.
Are there on earth
Japanese in them?
It is said the Japanese is male
called Liaohuamu.
Liao means surface.
Firstly, go cross Nilu Forest
and then to Bilian
just there,
they got the final information.
And then to Balema
Besides, Bilian is called
the city of Wulubu
Wulubu is a bald mount
which enters the midland,
so it can be called 'Gateway', is it'?
BELEM
In this place,
chasing and hurting vulture
is prohibited
It may be the king of birds, is it?
So they give food to them.
It's Amazon creditably!
Excitingly
Is it she, a beauty standing
at the fortress of Gashiduo Road,
challenging Gashaman
Pretty!
Miss Xihu is so beautiful.
Mr.Ahsahe'?
Mr.Ahsahe!
What's matter? Who are you?
Ready! Set!
What are you doing? Stop!
Let me go!
Lady, Amazon is a terrible place.
It is much fortunately
to have so little pains.
How about back Japan right now.
Maiden?
Hu...Xihu?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing
Good, you are fine.
But I am sorry
lam reckless at that time.
Never mind.
I want to have a rest upstairs
Too surprising,
You are maiden.
I will take you to the Police,
even you are killed,
I will bring your body to there.
Your karate is useless.
I am the vanguard of the soccer.
I don't want you
to vistit Liaohuamu any more,
so I intruded you and
thought you may go back Japan for fear.
But it seems you will not go back.
You wanted to make
a sincere apology to me just now, yes?
If you swim in the river
full of the maneating fish
I can accept your apology.
It is to say, you are ate up by them.
Maneating fish find the quarry
by their smell,
after confirming safety,
they come to chase their quarry.
So leave them as soon as see them coming
doing actions, no stop
to leave them away.
In this way, they can't come close.
Your hair...white before?
Colored black
Japanese came to this place
color their white hair into black.
A hurt on the back.
I was once the vanguard of soccer.
That guy
what?
He wants to prevent
our legwork on gold diggers.
I put my dreams
in your shoes
look it after returning the hotel
gold sands?
Gold?
The guy is Liaohuamu
Stop. . . stop!
What's wrong? Xihu
The guy is Liaohuamu,
a Japanese gold digger.
What? Liaohuamu!
The guy who attacked Mr. Ahsahe
made him faint yesterday.
Hey. guy!
Wait, Mr. Ahsahe!
Now we owe nothing to each other
Mr. Photographer
Wait! No force!
Sorry, I treat you right now.
No, thanks.
But legwork must be stoped right now,
ifs the most important!
Back home.
Liaohuamu,
How about we have a talk
We all are Japanese,
why he refuses being interviewed?
If you tell us the cause,
we will not trouble you
Wait!
Wait, we are reporters.
We must find him even lose our life.
Gold digger Liaohuamu
You have no right to stop us.
This is called Gaola,
the purest gold of 99.99
To now,
How much viaticum remains we have?
Take it back!
You think every problems
can be solved by gold,
even reporters' conscience
can be bought by gold.
Absolutely impossible.
Pick it up! What a pity, Xihu!
Come!
OK, come here!
The guy will not give it up so easily!
Pick it up!
The gold represents my youthhood.
Do you know? I want to give it to you.
The youthhood all?
Yes! My world!
Pick it up! Xihu!
This guy!
Don't call her so casual!
IS it?
The gold is the result of
your sweat and blood,
the result of your hard work
for a long time, your youthhood.
Do you think it worthy?
This, returen to you.
It's useless to me.
Gold diggers can
be divided into three kinds.
Winner, loser and victim
Winner find gold.
Loser find no gold
but they create victims.
This is the final warning.
Stop reporting now, go back!
If you don't want to be victim.
Which kind you belong to?
I'm loser, as well as avenger
Avenger?
Yes! I'm avenger!
So confusing
Winner, loser,
ls the guy mad?
But he is great.
The gold is valuable,
equal to billions of Yuan
bring it to the Police.
I'm loser, as well as avenger
avenger... avenger
What's on earth the meaning?
In a word, set off right now.
Don't stay here any longer.
Worst! Sankou
Take the gold carefully.
The guy's?
They are local gold diggers
Stop!
What do you want to do with her?
Don't touch her,
otherwise I will beat you.
Don't lie to me!
You've said you don't want the gold.
It's Liaohuamu himself, put it down.
I've said you are not worthy of
our confidence.
I know better about white-haired ghost
than you.
White-haired ghost?
Yes! It's Liaohuamu
A cold-blooded guy.
For money, he can kill everyone.
Just like a demon.
Such a guy never put down gold
without sake.
Hey! Speak out!
Where did you get the gold?
I don't know. I don't know.
Really?
This is poison cicala called Masajia
Formal name is Ladabule
If pinked by it, man wants to get woman
and woman wants to be embraced by man,
closest to her.
What do you want?
Stop! Stop please!
We do nothing.
It Masajia itself flying here.
Why not to stop
on the stern of this girl?
OK, we give all the gold we have to you.
You also got our camera!
Please, stop!
Try!
Try to move your stern!
Throw Masajia out soon,
otherwise you will be bited.
That is Indian's superstition.
Even bited by Masajia,
you will be all right.
It's me, give the gold to them.
You don't agree? You scraps.
Yes, we are waiting
You come here without help.
Are you the boss of
those wandering dogs?
Watch your mouth! How about cooperation?
Liaohuamu.
What a pity!
I never sell gold to sinister gang.
Sinister gang?
Yes, they are sinister gang.
They outsmart Brazil government,
gather gum hum gum diggers
and then bring them
to their organization.
I've knowed being followed up by them,
so put the gold down here on purpose.
There are two purposes
One is to make you experience dangers
in person
then you stop the legwork.
Another one is
to unveil those guy,
drive them out of this place.
If you dare, fire now!
These little-caliber bullets
can't threat me,
Yes, we are clear about it too.
To deal with
long-life white-haired ghost
of couse, we should have some odds.
Liaohuamu
I saw you buying this toy,
you are hesitating
to choose an elephant toy
or a person-like toy,
but finally you bought
a person-like toy of love.
To who?
You fall in love with a woman,
so surprising.
It's easy to have a talk.
How is it going? Liaohuamu.
Don't you care if the lady get hurted?
How about accept this dealing ?
Despicable guys.
Never forgive you.
Ah...monster
Run, run.
I will surrender to the Police.
A hearing is waiting for me.
It takes half a year to prove that
lam innocent and released.
In this case, our legwork can't go on.
To me,
when I take taxi back,
I should say "Pozhishalu" in Brazilian,
Most of Japanese pronounciation
can't help you,
so use this way to remember,
Boshizhoulu'
This pronounciation is surely helpful.
Ah, you are from a remote place,
want to see the man, doesn't it'?
Ah, is he still here?
Two weeks have passed away!
The legwork has finished.
You have no proportion.
You want to say good-bye to me, is it?
I have given my resign letter
to the legwork group.
I come here
for the person-like toy
and my future.
I will never leave you alone,
be with you
day and night,
even you go bathing and to washing room.
Why?
Hatred
I hate you
I want to take avenge on you
for the shame you brought to me.
If not succeed, I'd like to die.
It's obstacle,
besides it's not a good place
where woman can live.
At last,
you will become the food of vultures.
You protect me
if vultures attack me,
You kill them,
vultures don't attack strangers.
Can you shoot them down?
If for me,
Impossible,
May I go with you?
Take me there?
A great farewell.
You don't want to
leave without saying a word,
don't want to
say good-bye frankly as well,
and you speak out
the bet with hatred as an excuse,
and make the impossibility
as the prelude of goodbye.
An performance for leaving
is much suitable for you,
is it?
Can you accompany me to the port?
The gold you gave to me
is kept here.
I present a small scrap
to the officer of the Police,
so policemen will not interfere me
if you walk with me to the port.
I will not throw you away
if you go back Japan,
I will unveil you sooner or later.
There is a Japanese saying,
It dosen't matter.
Bye-
I think I will not forget you.
But perhaps you will not remember me.
Good-bye!
I win!
You shoot vultures, don't you?
For me!
I want to be with you. I love you!
Xihu!