Several months after that
We live on the land named Amazon
In this mysterious place
as if he lost himself
and tried his best to look for gold
From then on, all is our time
and we spend our time with Huamu
But I know
There's no room for me in his heart
He always looks to the faraway place
as if his heart was covered
by a dark curtain
He called himself avenger
I don't know what that means
But I'll follow him
even I lose my life
I, Kouxiaxihu,
can give up my auditorship
as a reporter
That's the Ice Race
living nearby
and it's the battle between them
and the invading Northern Step Race
And the Ice Race
is almost defeated
OK, ifs a chance
At this time
I know the real ID of Huamu
Ready Set!
Famous Stars of American Soccer
was arrested because of hiding drugs
(The molder of a super star )
(Commit Suicide With lover)
Only one of them died, is it a murder?
Is it... That man...
The emeer of Ice Race
in order to show thanks to him
for driving away the other race
he said that he'd share us some treasure
hide“ by him
The fortune of Kingdom Portugal
which colonized Brazil before
We have heart about the legend
about that
Is this your survival purpose?
Cimuguijie
The super star
abandoned by the world a few years ago
You're Cimuguijie
So your name is Cimuguijie
I'll tell you why I call myself Avenger
It's just because of
the woman who hurted me
When I was an international student
in USA
I was a vanguard in a soccer team
And I always ranked first
no matter in USA or Japan
I was very popular
I decided
I must join American Professional Team
Just
in the last summer of my collegehood
In order to become the best team of USA
we took part in a match in Japan
And I met Xiazi
Are you Cimuguijie of the team?
Hey, do you fall in love with Xiazi?
Xiazi.
Hey,
I don't care what famous star you are
Do you want to die?
Oops?
If you're a soccer player
can you have a match with me?
If you can stop the trolley
with your shoulder
I'll think ifs OK
Look, Miss Xiazi
really falls into love with him
Maybe this kind of man
suits to her very much
This is the beginning of
the short summer of Xiazi and me
What's up?
Why do you run here suddenly?
The football thrown out by you
caused a scar
I heard that it won't disappear forever
If you feel sorry,
please tattoo me in it
You want to tattoo me yourself?
This... Oops?
I like blue lizard most
How can I do that?
Be gentle to me
You're my first lover
Xiazi
Open the door!
What do you want to do? Open the door!
One day, we were attacked by someone
and taken to a villa
We began to doubt our eyes suddenly
It won't be wrong
He's a super star of world fame
And there're many men and women
The professional athleted,
the champion of Olympic Game
The worlds famous movie star
The professional athleted,
the champion of Olympic Game
He's a famous star
What? Scared?
Ifs the premonition of one episode
just now
And there're many others too
GPX
(Super Blue Movie)
Performed by famous actors
It's the best blue movie
who're you'?
Show us these movies.
What do you want to do?
We're attracting you
to act as Cimuguijie
the famous soccer player
in Japan
and USA
You're selected as the glorious
star of the next movie
What?
And she
is your competitor
Of course ifs not free
It's the performance fee
I refuse! No way
If you do like that
You'll lose your popularity
in the future
You're crazy!
I'm not afraid of your threat
Xiazi, let's go
Well... guy!
And in the next few days
I was set by the heels
and I didn't have any food
One day...
Xiazi!
What' re you doing'?
Stop! Stop! Don't hurt her any more
Then you promised to play the role?
No!
Cimuguijie, you can't lose
You must act in that movie.
I won't let you pass
You turned against me!
Xiazi!
Cimuguijie, get ready
I'll burn you
It's nice
As long as I'm burnt
I can't perform in that movie!
Wait!
We can't damage
the important merchandise
It's nothing but to
sleep with a woman for one time
Xiazi!
Nobody can get Cimuguijie!
Nonsense, what's the matter?!
Cimuguijie, you brought much herion
and marijuana to sell in Japan
with your auditorship as
an international student
We found 1 kg herion
when we searched your home
If you'd applied for
the wanted oder earlier
you'd not kill your wife
only because of profit
How come... ifs so!
Sentence
Cimuguijie who broke the drugs rules
and killed one person
You made a crime,
and will be prisoned for 10 years
It's some evidence I never saw
A few days later
I learnt in prison that
my mother committed suicide
Cimuguijie! You...!
Hair!
After serving my sentence
I left Japan for Brazil
In order to get the gold for the avenge
Don't fool me
You asked if I could make
a 70-foot ship myself
who're you asking?
It's not bluster
I'm the best ship manufacture expert
in Bilian
I can settle
any problem myself.
You mean you were introduced by Luobi?
Are you the partners of those
who smuggled?
No!
I only wanted to go to USA
Hum, do you want to stow away?
Don't believe Luobi too much
It's the subscription
who're you'?
The hair is all white
Ah... It seems good
And finally, we invited
this woman architectural expert
HEY
Shall we make a ship in the forest?
Take these to USA
And don't let anyone ese know it
So we'd guise the ship
with the gold and treasure
Gold ship?
And the reward is one third of
the treasure
That's too little
I'll piss as long as I see gold
And I've devorced three times for it
Will you promise? Biji?
Yeah...
I'll make a gold ship for you
Do you know although gold is very heavy
ifs very weak for swash and grind
And its heat-resistance ability
is also very excellent
So if we melt it
and use is as the balancer
It won't be found
only if we cover it with some wood
And then we'll make some space
between the gold and the wood
and hide the treasure in it
So it'll be perfect!
Gold Ship
will be finished
It's too hot
What do you want to do?
Want to hug me?
That bad girl can't be compared with you
Oops... is it nice?
What?
It's funny, I'm waiting for the chance
I'm waiting for you to start
Your face can't be so near to this man!
You guy!
Biji, stop!
What do you want to do?
I need you
We need you now
Before I arrive in USA
I still have something to do!
The ship is almost built finally
When it'll start its voyage
He fought against his worst opponent
CPX
That mysterious organization
has the power to use
national orgazination.
Facing the terrible orgazination
he'll challenge it with
the obtained gold
Then I'll follow him anywhere
till the avenge is over
And the across named Xiazi in his heart
will won't disappear
( Licha )
We started our voyage at daybreak
from Jiao to Bilian
and then after cross,
we'll go to America
I can get the Visa to USA
from Lubi
at Bilian Port
It's Luobi
We've promised to
conclude the business in Bilian
But ifs too obvious
The Passport and Visa
and allowance to leave the port
Thus the work is finished
Minister Gang?
What's the matter?
You paid money as several times as
the fake document needs
I think there must be some secret.
It's powerful It's really so.
Turn out the treasure you collected
Cimuguijie, dangerous!
Xihu!
Stop him! Kill them!
When'll you leave?
Think about it carefully!
We'll arrive at Bilian Port soon!
Sea Police are searching ships
leaving the port
We'll be arrested if they find the body
What...
Will I do with the bad final situation?
You'd have her bathed
and let her lie on bed
and always oath her hand
A dead person can't
come back to life again
What'll you do if they search the ship?
No matter what we do
they'll find the gold and treasure.
Do you want to give up
what we have done?
Wow? Cimuguijie?
Biji, would you get off the ship
after the ship get near to the port?
Oops?
I'll cancel the agreement between us.
I'll exchange the treasure into cash
after I get to America
And I'll post to you what you'd get
What's up? Suddenly?
It's impossible to operate the ship
by oneself
I see
I don't accept your money
The bracelet is enough
Stupid]
This guy! Trifled with me
You'd only say See you
if you return to Japan?
No kidding!
I always work very hard
and make food and wash clothes for you
And I'm hugged by you everyday
You'll say goodbye to me only after
saying that you Japanese wife comes?
Hey!
You'd say something!
And what hell is your wife?
She's always lying for ill
And takes much sleeping draught
She sleeps in daytime,
and gets up at night, isn't she a bat?
She's nothing but weakness
Look here
It's so vivid?
Let's start!
Beast!
I love you! Don't abandon me!
Take me with you!
I'll do everything for you!
I love you
I really love you
Biji
You must hug me
Are you unsatisfied with them?
I won't let them pass by
Do you have any other thing to do?
Live on and reach your goal
Biji
You really have a sound sleep
Take her away
It's really a pity to abandon
such a woman, see you
Biji, start the voyage!
Yes, sir!
Xihu!
Cimuguijie
I'll always pay attention
to your avenge
We'll reach Jialifu Sea
It starts
Let's start from now on!