Great, this banner is very good.
That's our job.
Thank you.
Sun will define cardinal virtues
That's real
conquer the dark
art is the same
said as roma dola
the word is about...
Wu
I feel glory
that is wonderful for a producer
and then please look
your next traget
that is...
Yes. jewel biji.
The lover of jewels
Not only America
The Top model of world
And the partner of jewel biji...
...is this man.
Professional soccor.
New York
Vengeance teams attacting vanguard,
the tean ganger of Jorgelugi,
is the man of Stone Biji.
People call him the White Hair gost.
[white hair evil]
Very good material
to create that kind of man.
On the other side,
Jorgelugi is a famous
trader in the world.
Half a year ago,he got down to
the financial world.
At this age,how can get
so much treasure.
No matter the feat of uniting the vengeance team
in half a year
adding his tresure,
he is not a penny the worse.
Stone Biji can appear in the media
throughout American.
It was said that it was his support.
Women are a easy job,
no matter money or power.
[White Hair Evil and Stone Biji]
was said to be
the union of
[Hundred Million Yuan Romantic history]
To CPX, it is a big trade.
Members all over the world
have asked for reservation enjoy.
It mustn't fail
because the reservation fare is
very high.
I see, I response for
the commanding work of Wangluo.
Any good idear?
Looking for his past.
Being a man,
he has to have much past.
It is buring up.
White hair ghost.
I must beat you down.
New York.
Paita Mansion.
Master, welcome back.
Miss Biji had already
gone to the cellor.
Cimnguijie, very especial.
OK,Biji.
Will they come?
The guys?
Yes, they will sure be.
So we make use the media.
Buy the TV program.
Roll the Biji tornado
throughout the world,
and unite the vengence team.
Bring yourself back to the soccor world.
The GPX fellows.
Must be caught
Our bait
feel it.
The car is following from just now.
Thank you, Maddam.
Maddam?
Is that good?
Except miss Biji,
who can you call for maddam.
Before I leave the world,
I call miss Biji as maddam.
I believe master would not blame me.
Thank you, Feicabali.
Thank you for your help.
No, it is now
you need my help.
Thank you ,Bali.
How could you say so?
It is really you often help.
Had announced getting cancer
remain only one year,
I not only get help but so much money
from my master
I could make all my life.
So my family needn't worry
about live.
Buy your life,
if possible, I hope
the world would say sorry to you.
You are too welcome.
My life
maybe it will lost tomorrow.
I am very satisfied
if I can work for my master.
The CPX organization
must check my past.
They threat me by this .
If deeply investigated,
It doesn't worth
when they know my auditorship.
Must stop their investion about you
when they come near to our bait.
I see, just let it to me.
Bali, take it.
It is very cold at night.
Maddam, this is...
This is my first time to thank you,
maddam.
We had to depart now.
Master, master.
Must make it sussce.
The lake residental place
is called sexal doll.
I had ask you to stop talking.
Will I see the entrepot tomorrow.
Hay, just say it out truly.
Feichabali.
Why have you so much money, Jorgelugi.
I think you would not know.
No.
Action.
No any exchanged condition,
Bali just tell me Jorgelugi's past.
I won't kill you then.
So.
I see, I see.
Stop.
Diamond and gold.
Master found
many treasures of Portugal
in Brazil somewhere
had been moved to American secretly.
They buy a ship.
To get rid of the gold and diamon.
Diamond had been got rid of.
The gold and the ship
is the same as usual.
So.
Where?
Cimnguijie, it is burning
like the sun in your heat,
right?
Xiazi, Xihu,
Cimnguijie's love toward you never change.
Although a little jealous,
this is the first time,
Cimnguijie and me fight toghter
in the place of you.
CPX's fellow had control the ship,
right?
Same as we thought.
Bali
is very brave, the old man
is waiting.
The last moment of one's live
is in the sun,
next time in the bottom of the sea.
My life is rather histrionic.
Hum, putting an act.
Nunc Dimitts, old man.
Bad guy making someone feel boring.
They.
They will die?
They won't satisfied as us.
I haven't hear the name of GPX.
GPX, it is a ture name.
The God make the blue movie.
That is to say,
it is the union of that kind of union.
I am the superviser of Sunuomudili.
I come to canvass you.
Canvass us? You are just making a joke.
The expence of the show
is the ship full of gold.
How come?
It... it is you!
Steal the ship.
Go with me.
The ship would be hand over to the police
if you don't come.
They will become prison.
GPX'works is not only blue moive.
Right, no one can make it
except the god.
Because the performers
are very famouse in the world.
They are pop star,
sport expert.
They are also hanesome men
and women all.
Just like you.
GPX had a system of menbership.
The menbers is full of the world.
They all big pot
controlling the final world.
Although they are all old people.
To see GPX'works,
they mind how much money they spent.
Why?
That is the GPX's movie.
I will do the work in the place of you.
Make the blue moive,
no one can be better than me.
I am No.1 in the world.
I make it all buy my feeling.
Eye, lip.
Breast,
It is so.
Feel it by yourself,
you will reach the climax point.
All my moive is the best in the world.
Right! Good!
I can bear it, if it is so.
Can't come out.
Cimnguijie.
Biji, what did you said just now?
Cimnguijie is my name.
It seems
you haven't pay much attention to.
Biji, let me show you.
What do you mean by this?
That is the true purpose.
Her face shows
that she wants to make love with our Cimnguijie.
It is too serious.
Yes, she surely want to.
Because it is the man
who want to make also can make it.
White hair...
Devil
What is wrong on earth with me?
I will not satisfied
no matter how many I do.
Titllation is not so strengh like this.
It is very strange.
But want again when wake up.
Wait! Don't stop.
Do you want me, Dili?
Very much?
Because I had put [Spring of Lalushixi]
In your body.
Spring of Lalushixi?
It is the anaesthetic, hiden here.
It can control the feeling
of No.0 anaesthetic.
It is a very interisting attributes.
If it is suck in from hiden place,
it has to from the same place next time.
Injection is unuseful too.
Dili,
you have no Linghao already and
I can't bear any longer.
Why?
Why wipe with Linghao?
Say! Say it out!
Darned, if you don't say,
I will beat you to death.
Bear, Biji, do bear.
Untill the woman can't stant it.
Shit! Hard bone.
Kill you.
Linghao...
Here?
Paint it here?
No good,
you will die if I don't caress you.
Shit!
Kill him! Kill him!
Wait! Don't kill him.
Unlock! Unlock his manacles.
Free him!
Hold me... Linghao.
I refuse.
Who is the boss here?
I beg you, hold me.
Who is boss?
Galilu.
Call him come here!
I would hold you then.
You had promise me, hold me!
Quick, please!
Why? Tell me why?
I had lost the most important thing
for you.
It is more imporant than life.
Why?
I sweared from that time on,
I must be a vegeaence in my life.
You? Cimnguijie?
Right I remember.
You are Cimnguijie.
The pop soccor star.
But Why?
I am a vengeaence!
Just only you had said
you were a vengeaence!
I came from the hell to kill you all.
Save me, Balilu?
Linghao is confused by that guy?
I really love Dili and his art
from my heart.
It is the same to Dily.
I came out according to your order.
It showed that she never minded
I was in danger.
Love is much like the glass.
Take it carelessly,
you would hurt yourself.
White gost.
What you looking me for?
I want you to say something
about the GPX organiziation.
What does it help knowing this?
And I have not the duty
to tell you that.
Then I will force you to do that.
Galilushabilu.
Before we die,
some of you must die or hurt.
Including you, Galilushabilu.
Funny, but I don't want my followers
to fight with little potato.
If you win, I promise.
OK.
It seems it is funny.
Action.
Stop, Biji.
They will fire if you fire.
Cite is an expert
at using the falchion in the world...
It will be a funny game
with the White ghost.
How to attact and defend is
the most interesting point.
It is a very good feat, right?
Moive is funny,
but the men's war to the knife is also very funny.
Cimnguijie.
Biji, put down your gun.
I don't want to lose any perfect thing.
Survival is a behavior,
Luosu had said so.
It is time you take action
to drop down your gun.
If you do so,
we can also put away our gun.
Biji, only if be alive,
Nice future is waiting for you.
Great.
It is time to make an end.
If a coverture,
Cimnguijie can win.
We must beat that guy down.
Is there anything that can be use?
Cimnguijie! Use me!
Let me stop him!
Biji:
At last, I can stand
in the same position with
Xihu.
Biji... Biji!
You will fail then.
Stop... stop!
I will do as you told me.
The boss of GPX is you?
No, I am just in charge of produce.
The head of our organization is another.
Who is that guy!
You can't say... you should say.
I don't know! Why?
I know only a little.
It is a girl bringing the message here.
That is not true.
The represented girl?
That is all,boss.
Just burn it.
Isn't the GPX
the part of Mafia?
Right? Answer!
Right, it has no relationship
with the Mafia.
It is another organization.
You have to help me in the future,
to get close with
superstratum of the organization.
Biji, you wait and see,
it is over
for the GPX produce department.
It depends on you totally,
the Galilus are all on my hand.
But,it is only me left in the future.
Repose, Biji
burial with my love
Almighted God,
please take the gost with you,
sent her to the seventh heaven.
[Riddle]
Messager?