Hey, did you know?
Hmm?
About the DVD that curses you if you watch it!
That's ridiculous! It's nothing but a rumor, right?
Then, shall we watch it?
Eh?
Ka-Kazuya...
Little Devil
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
So Sticky and Covered in Juice
Little Devil Girlfriend
Koakuma Kanojo.
I'm fine, I'll definitely be fine!
As long as I don't meet Kazuya today,
there won't be a problem!
Kazuya-kun, the crush of me, Akuno Mika!
But... I don't think this love has a future any more...
Because my body is...
Now a succubus...
Hey! Akuno-san!
That voice is... Kazuya-kun?
Why would I see Kazuya-kun at a time like this?
Crush
That looks really heavy. Should I help?
I-I-I'm o-okay!
Please don't come near me.
What's wrong?
I can do it on my own, so... please leave me...
It spilled around quite a bit, didn't it?
I should help.
No! Don't come over!
I'm sorry! That was unintentional...
Akuno-san?
Ah... I can't take it anymore...
I... I can't hold back!
That's right, I... when I think about Kazuya-kun...
My body becomes like this...
Kazuya... kun?
What happened? What's with that chest?
I got busted!?!
No!!
Akuno-san!
And then, anyone who watches this DVD will be cursed!
No way!
Art Room
What are you talking about? There's
no such thing as curses!
Then let's give it a try, Kana!
Huh!?
S-Sure!
I watch it and tell you all my impressions of the video.
As expected from Kana!
Yeah!
The curse... does exist..
Because... Mika's become an erotic devil!
I only watched the DVD for fun and yet... why?
Why did my body!?
What do I do? Kazuya-kun saw me...
He saw my slutty body...
This tail... when I rub it like this...
it feels so good I can't stop!
Ah... Kazuya... kun...
You must hate such a slutty girl like me...
You might not ever want to talk to me again...
Kazuya-kun!
Kazuya-kun... Kazuya-kun!
I can't... I can't anymore!
Akuno... san!
Kazuya-kun... don't look... I don't want you to see!
No... no...
Akuno... san?
No!!
Nooo!!
Kazuya-kun saw me like this... I can't be a bride anymore!
Um... is your body okay?
It turned back right away yesterday...
but it just won't today!
It's... it's all... Kazuya-kun fault you know!
Wait...
Kazuya-kun turned by body... into such... such...
Huh? What, what am I saying!?
Woah!
Kazuya-kun!
Come on!
Love you!
Mika loves Kazuya-kun!
That's not what I wanted to say...
By that you mean...
Even just now, I was thinking about
Kazuya-kun while masturbating...
I want Kazuya-kun so much I can't help it...
Akuno-san!
No...
Akuno-san, I...
Kazuya-kun is so daring!
No... don't rub my boobs so much!
This is like a dream... to think that
I'd be doing this with Kazuya-kun...
Hurry... hurry and give it to me!
Here, right?
Akuno-san...
Woah... Kazuya-kun's is deep inside...
Even though I just came, I'm losing it again!
Akuno-san is so hot and sticky down here... it feels great!
Don't... if you do it so roughly I’ll... I'll cum right away!
Sorry... I can't stop!
Me too... I've always...
I've always always been... in love with Akun... with Mika!
No way... if you... if you say that now...
Cumming, cumming... cumming!
You came again, right?
There's so much.
Could it be that you were really
happy from my confession?
Idiot! There's a reason behind this...
I see... Then, to turn that body back... Ah!
Yeah, I have to get excited lots and
lots, and ejaculate from this tail...
This is... really like a guy's thing...
So make me cum lots...
Make me feel better with Kazuya-kun's penis!
You can cum lots inside so...
Amazing... your pussy is squeezing so hard...
Mi-﻿Mika...
There, there!
Not there!
So energetic... it's getting harder and harder!
That's because... I'm being touched by a person I love...
My boobs and my tail feel good!
Wait... wai-
This is...
I've been storing up milk, too... so suck
it out with Kazuya-kun's mouth...
There... there... more...
Amazing... it's sweet, and really tasty...
Suck it... suck it all out! And then turn me
back into the Mika that Kazuya-kun loves!
Again!
Amazing...
Mi-Mika...
Kazuya! I... I have this slutty succubus
body... are you really okay with this?
Again!
Kazuya... Kazuya, I love you...
Mika! I... don't care about those kinds of things.
I love both the erotic Mika and the usual Mika!
Kazuya, Love you...
That's right... more... thrust more...
feel good from Mika's pussy...
Wings... not my wings!
You can feel it from here too, Mika?
No... don't... don't lick them so much!
You're insides are squeezing like crazy again.
I can really feel it... I'm going to go crazy...
Are you going to cum again?
But... you're stimulating my pussy
and my tail at the same time...
Cumming... cumming!
I'm gonna cum, tool
Let it out! Let our so much that you'll...
You'll get me pregnant!
Cumming... again!
In the end, our love came true thanks to the curse, but...
The curse itself...
It seems like it felt so could I can't
go back any more... or something.
Take responsibility, okay?
No!! Kazuya-kun!
Looks like my love still has a long way to go.
Wake up!!
Kazuya-kun!!
It's still fine... we can still do this!
Koakuma Kanojo.
So this is the DVD that's said to be cursed...
Kana, please, could you watch it for me?
Kana is the only one that can help us!
A DVD that's rumored to curse you if you watch it?
Ridiculous, they're just rumors, right?
I have to watch it and tell my Senpai's my impressions...
So please, Kana-sama!
Note: Daimyoujin is a title of god, and Namu is a chant.
The Kana Daimyoujin, Namu, Namu...
I guess there's no helping that. Sure, I'll
watch it and tell you my impressions.
What's... this? There's nothing on this DVD.
Thank goodness... geez, what a waste of worrying.
So Onee-chan watches erotic DVD on her own, too!
Mai, when did you...
I'm back.
Hey, pass it to me later, Okay?
Huh?
Is it something really crazy?
No way! Don't look!
It's still too much for you, Mai. Not for kids, okay?
Besides, you should only watch these things
after you've become an adult like me!
But...
Haha, I would never want my younger sister to know
that I'm getting scared from a cursed DVD rumor...
But my body is already an adult...
I have bigger boobs than Onee-chan, see? See?
That's one word too much, Mai.
Sister's Ring.
Don't be so cheap!
Geez, only her body's grown up.
Huh? Eh?
Wait, what?
This situation...
Onee-chan?
Mai... my body is... hot..
It's fuzzy down there... it's really strange...
Geez, so much trouble...
Don't get so fussed up from
sticking a vibrator in yourself!
You perverted sister!
Onee-chan...
No...
Mai, actually, I was watching a DVD that
is said to curse you if you watch it...
And then, it felt fuzzy down there and...
Woah, so this is a penis...
This is the first time I've seen a real one...
It’s different from in the manga, unexpectedly grotesque!
Mai, should we go to a hospital or something?
So it's like this here...
Hey, Mai are you listening?
Hmm?
Yeah, leave it to me! Mai is on Onee-chan's side!
I'll do anything for Onee-chan!
Leave it to you?
No! Mai!
Wow... it's hot and hard...
Wait, Mai... stop...
You're this large... are you turned on?
That's not true...
Oh, so it's soft here...
It's like a marshmallow!
Stop it... not there...
No... I can really... feel it from that place... it feels good!
No more! Don't do it anymore!
It's coming out!
So this is ejaculation? It feels so good!
What is this? It's still coming out.
It's really sticky and it smells weird...
Mai...
Hey...
Onee-chan... this is?
Yeah... the ejaculation just now... felt really good.
So let me do it more with Mai's boobs.
Onee-chan, something's kind of wrong here!
Hey... Onee-chan...
But my penis is twitching... I can't stop...
This is gross, Onee-chan...
This is a first... I can feel that place twitching
and the boobs squeezing...
Penises are amazing!
Again!
Mai's boobs feel so good I can't stop ejaculating!
Suck on it.
Mai's mouth feels good, too.
Hey, suck on it more.
No way... she just ejaculated and
yet she's getting large again...
This is painful... so painful...
No! Again... I can't hold back anymore...
Mai, I'm letting out more again... in your mouth...
No...
Onee-chan... let's stop already...
C'mon, you have to be a good girl and drink it all...
Hey, hey!
Onee-chan...
Her eyes are losing focus...
I guess I'll just have to teach your body then.
Not there...
No...
Even though you say that, Mai's pussy is this wet!
You felt it from the titty fuck, right?
That's not... true...
No... what do I do... being teased
by Onee-chan feels so good...
Even though we're both girls...
Well then, I'll have to teach your body thoroughly.
Onee-chan...
Geez, you're so wet already!
This time I'll put it in here for you.
Let's feel good together.
No, not there!
Onee-chan is coming inside!
What's this., you're squeezing
so hard... I'll get excited, too!
I... this is my first time... and I'm
being violated by Onee-chan...
Mai... you're so cute... I'll make you're
virgin pussy feel really good!
If you do it so roughly I'll go crazy!
It's fine... go crazy! I think I'll cum again, too!
I'll cum lots and lots inside!
No... you can't cum inside, Onee-chan, please!
No way... Mai...
Onee-chan!
It's coming inside... it's coming...
Semen is flowing inside...
Again?
I'm still getting you to make me cum again, Mai!
If I lick your ears, your pussy squeezes real tight!
To think we'd be the same in these
kinds of things... we're really sisters!
Stop it... please... Onee-chan... pull it out...
My insides are so full of semen!
I'm sorry, Mai... your pussy squeezes so nicely...
my penis can't stop... letting out sperm!
No! Onee-chan!
I didn't know... I didn't know that.
that a penis could feel this good!
More! I want to ejaculate more!
Woah... she just came and yet...
She's pouring more hot stuff inside...
No more! Spare me already!
Onee-chan!
I'm going to cum... I'm cumming from
having sex with Onee-chan!
Mai's pussy is twitching! You re feeling it, aren't you?
Your penis is amazing... I'm cumming again!
Me too... I'm letting outs again inside your womb!
Onee-chan, I'm cumming!
Yes, it's gone!
I bet it was because I let it all out.
My pussy is clean now!
Mai, look, look! I'm back to normal!
Mai, you...
It's not fair that only Onee-chan gets to feel good...
I wanted to...
I wanted to ejaculate too...
This time I'll creampie Onee-chan lots!
No... No!!
And then, to undo the curse,
you have to do lewd things...
No way...
But, you'd do it, right? Lewd things.