Do you know what "aphrodisiac" means?
Oh, what's that?
That's something that really makes you horny, right?
Yup.
The one they sell at adult specialty shops.
Would it really feel good?
I heard that there's a girl in the other
class who has really big tits.
She seemed to have been very happy after
doing it with her BF for an entire night.
Now I want that too.
I want to be one with someone too.
I'm starting to crave it badly.
I really want to do it now.
What is this scent?
I'm steadily getting horny.
There's a big whiff for everyone here.
Little Devil Girlfriend.
The Animation.
The Verz Non-Associated Magic Academy.
All students come here to study the art of magic.
Oh, Kazuki!
You've been early lately.
Did something happen?
Oh, it's just you, Hibiki.
Nothing, just the usual.
What's with the "it's just you"?
You have a very cute girl walking with you to school, you know.
Cute? I wonder where that girl could be?
Man, I really wish I could go to school
with a really cool BF instead of you.
Sorry I'm not your boyfriend.
Hey Kazuki, don't you have someone you like?
Of course I don't.
Then, I saw this very cute thing at the store yesterday!
Wow, really?
Hey, why don't we go there today?
No way.
I haven't even said anything!
Elves always act kind and loving around everyone.
Besides, Elena is a real cutie with a great body.
Men are sure to be swarming all around her.
Jeez, he'd usually fight back at this point.
Ta-da!
If you're really that serious, how about using one of these?
What's that?
A secret love potion that's actually getting
popular with girls as of late.
Does it work?
Not sure.
But you don't have the guts to confess to her, right?
Why don't you just treat it as a sort of charm?
If you don't, somebody else will get to her.
O-Okay.
Okumura-kun,
what did you want?
W-Well.
I tried to call her out naturally.
Oh yeah,
I thought we'd be thirsty so,
here.
Oh, me too.
Umm.
Y-You know... I've always wanted to have a chat with you.
When I had just transferred to this school and
didn't know where my classroom was,
you were there for me.
Also, when I tripped at the station,
others just watched me as they walked by.
Here.
I thought that you were a really kind person.
We're both from different classes so I never
had the chance to speak with you.
Thanks.
No, I really shouldn't use this potion after all!
Okumura-kun, are you all right?
I'm okay.
Love potion my ass.
This is nothing but an arousal boosting drug!
I'm starting to get dizzy.
I'll call for some help
Elena-san's panties.
If she calls other people here, I might be labeled a pervert!
B-But!
Somebody.
Her thing is sucking it in too much!
I-I have to make sure she doesn't see me like this.
I-I think it'll be fine if I just take a small break.
I-I'm alright.
B-But!
Umm.
Is it painful in, umm.
That reaction, she found out!
I'm done for.
Getting a boner when it's just the two of us.
I'm a pervert no matter how she looks at it!
Umm, Okumura-kun.
Let me help you!
Help?
What are you going to do?
It's bulging so much, it looks like it's in pain.
Elena-san, what are you?
You look so pained with it, so I want to help, even if just a little.
There aren't really many elves around.
That's why we need to be well-versed
in methods that ensure procreation.
It's my first time, so I'm not sure if I can do this well.
Just remain still, okay?
It's so stiff, and hot.
Elena-san, if you keep doing that I'll.
Please be relieved.
The tip feels like it's being held.
I'm cumming!
M-My ears.
I'm sorry!
It's alright.
Have I made you feel relieved, Okumura-kun?
Oh, uh, yeah.
I'm glad then.
I know this may be too late already given the situation,
but I...
So hot.
Huh? Why am I doing this?
I-I don't want to, and yet...
Elena was affected by the potion too?
My body's insides.
Why?
Feel so hot.
This erotic Elena-san.
I can't hold back anymore!
No...
Elena-san's breasts,
they're so soft and tender.
This spot feels so soft too.
Doing this slutty act in front of Okumura-kun.
This is so embarrassing.
What's... happening to my body?
Elena-san.
It's gotten big again.
I feel horny.
My insides are very hot, and I'm really craving it already.
Please, fill me up, Okumura-kun.
Elena-san!
Wow, your thing is completely filling me.
It's all the way in.
What is this?
It's my first time, and yet it feels so good.
Please do it more gently.
My hips just won't stop!
No, no.
I feel all tingly.
I'm cumming!
It's pumping inside me.
I can feel it flowing.
It's bulging inside.
It feels like my womb is about to be pierced.
This is embarrassing.
Elena-san, your insides are amazing.
It feels so wet... so good.
Sorry, I'm about to cum again!
It's pumping again, and I'm being cummed inside again.
If you cum this much inside.
I'll get pregnant.
Your insides squeeze me tightly whenever you cum,
and it feels great.
I can't stop cumming either.
I never imagined you'd be this lewd.
No, I'm really embarrassed.
But, it just feels so good I can't stop!
More, more!
I-I'm about to cum again!
Oh, oh wow.
Not my ears.
Stop.
It's really squeezing me very tightly!
I'm cumming!
I can still keep it up.
I feel like your cum is seeping through me.
I'm going to cum lots inside again.
Impregnate me directly into my womb!
Little Devil Girlfriend.
No way.
Okumura-kun, please do it harder.
Elena-san.
Kazukt-kun and Elena san are really kissing.
Okumura-kun, I'm getting horny.
Elena-san, I'm still.
No way, this can't be.
Huh? Why did it surprise me so much?
I was the one who pushed him to go for it.
Hibiki!
Going home already?
Kazuki.
Then let's.
Why is he in such a good mood?
Why don't you just go home by yourself?
Huh? What are you getting mad for?
No reason, and don't you have somewhere you need to be?
Did I do something wrong?
I just feel like being alone!
What's wrong, Hibiki?
I'll just tell you a few really good stories, so can you just...
Don't come closer!
Kazuki? Please hang on!
Kazuki!
Infirmary
This is the worst.
Things didn't go as planned.
I'm the one who's liked him ever since we were kids,
and yet he was taken away by someone he recently met.
Do I just watch over them now?
I don't want that!
If I drink this love potion,
he should begin to love me too.
Hibiki?
What are you doing?
Why sucking your dick, of course.
That's not what I meant!
But, you love it, right?
It's so stiff already, see?
I wanted to suck on your dick, that's why.
What are you saying?
Hey, is this what's known as cowper secretions?
N-No.
That's just lewd, Kazuki.
I-If you keep doing that, of course I'll.
I wonder how it tastes.
Kazuki, these lewd juices just keep flowing out.
I-I said stop.
What's wrong with you, Hibiki?
You're really acting strange today.
I just wanted to let the dense Kazuki
experience my feelings firsthand.
But.
H-Hey.
Stop it.
Then will you do something about your boner too?
If it's rubbing there, then I just.
It looks like it's craving it from over here.
After all, it's just so stiff and hot.
Hey, aren't you embarrassed being aroused like
this even while your dick's being violated?
S-Stop.
For you to be on the verge of cumming while I do this,
Kazuki's such a pervert.
S-Stop.
You mean like this?
Amazing.
No, I can't keep this on any longer with so much cum.
Oh, my socks are also completely drenched.
There's so much of it here.
Hibiki.
Your cum feels thick and tastes delicious.
My cum.
So Hibiki, do you.
There's lots of it here too.
What a waste.
I just came, so it's still sensitive.
Stop!
It's still so stiff.
It's bulging.
Kazuki, this is amazing.
You're moving your hips so much.
So it's about to come out already, huh.
Just go ahead.
Go ahead and cum inside me all the way.
Stop.
I-I'm already.
Kazuki.
Stop... I'm going to cum!
Wow, it's really pumping it in me.
The hot stuff just keeps flowing out.
What a waste.
I have to put it in again.
It's still very stiff.
I can feel your dick still penetrating me hard.
It's hitting me!
I'm about to cum again.
It's okay, just cum lots inside me!
I'm cumming!
You came so much that my insides are filled to burst.
It'll just overflow now if you keep cumming.
Huh? Did that feel so good you passed out?
I guess you can't resist much at this
point, so I'll free your hands now.
Kazuki, you're sucking on my nipples too hard.
Let me go.
No way,
your dick is bulging inside me.
Just cut it out, Hibiki.
I'm not going to let you do things your way anymore.
Just what in the world happened with me earlier?
I just forced myself on you.
I'm such a pervert!
Forget about what happened earlier!
What? Huh?
You're going to, right?
O-Okay.
But,
my feelings were genuine back there.
I-I didn't do anything.
I can't say I really believe you from my vantage point.
Please don't bother my Kazuki so much,
Ms. Pervert.
Kazuki, she's definitely a bad girl!
You know that's not true right, Kazuki?
Stop acting all lovey-dovey!
What are you doing?
I can do anything if it's for Kazuki.
I-I won't lose!
Hey Kazuki, give this to me, please?
No way.
If I get a blowjob from both of you I'll!
J-Just wait!
Oh wow.
Then, whoever gets to make him cum the most wins?
Okay.
I'm going to die if this continues.
I have to... escape!
Hey wait, Kazuki!