Do you know what an aphrodisiac is?
Nope, what's that?
That stuff makes you really horny, right?
Yup, that's right.
They sell them at the adult shops.
Does it actually make you feel good?
I heard that a girl over in the next class used it.
She said it had some amazing effects.
She was making a big fuss because she really
bonded with her boyfriend or something.
Aw, I'm so jealous.
I wanna bond with a guy too.
I feel kinda hot now.
Yeah, I really wanna do it now...
What's this smell? It's so arousing...
I have some for all of you.
Koakuma Kanojo 2 Animation
Unrequited love.
This is Vers Magic Academy Affiliated School,
where the vast majority of students
spend their time studying magic.
Hm? Hey, Kazuki!
You've been coming to school pretty
early lately. Something happen?
Oh, Hibiki. Nothing, really.
Jeez, what's with that attitude?
Can't you show some enthusiasm at the fact
that a cute girl is trying to walk with you?
Wow, really? I don't see any
cute girls around, though!
I wish I had a really cool boyfriend
to walk to school with instead of you.
Sorry for not being your boyfriend.
Don't you have a crush on anyone, Kazuki?
Like hell I do.
So, like, I stopped by the store yesterday,
and it was fine, so cute.
Wow, really?
Wanna go there with me today?
It ain't happening.
I didn't say shit!
Elves are nice to everyone.
Not to mention, she's super pretty
and has a great body.
You really don't think she has a line
of guys waiting for her already?
What, he's not even gonna
say anything back to that?
Ta-dah! If you're really serious about her,
how about you try this?
What's that?
It's a super popular love potion that's
been secretly circulating amongst the girls.
Does it actually work?
Who knows? But it's not like you have
the courage to ask her out, right?
Why don't you give it a shot?
If you don't hurry,
someone might snatch her away.
Okumura-kun, did you need something?
Y-Yeah...
I just kinda went with the flow
and called her out here...
Oh, right! I thought you might
be thirsty, so I bought these...
Oh, me too...
S-So...
I've been wanting to talk with you for a while now.
When I first transferred into this school,
I didn't know anyone but you helped me find my classroom.
And when I fell down the stairs at the train station,
everyone just stood and stared...
Here you go!
I started thinking that you were a pretty nice guy.
It was hard for me to tell you this
since we're in different classes, but...
Thank you.
Yeah, I definitely can't use this potion on her!
O-Okumura-kun, are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine...
Love potion my ass, that's just a damn aphrodisiac!
My head's starting to feel dizzy
I'll get someone!
I can see her panties! If she brings someone here,
I'm gonna be labeled as some kind of pervert!
But I can't...
Someone...
It's eating up her panties!
I have to do this without her noticing.
I think I'll be okay after lying down for a bit...
B-But...
Um...
Is the one in pain, um...
Shit, what's with that reaction? Did she notice?
I'm fucked... No matter how you spin it, getting a boner
when we're all alone just makes me look like a pervert!
Um, Okumura-kun, please let me help you!
Help me with what?
It's so swollen. It must hurt a lot.
Elena-san, what are you doing?
You look like you're in a lot of pain,
so I was hoping to relieve some of it, even if only a little.
My kind is numbered, so I know how
to plant a seed within me with absolute certainty.
I don't have actual experience,
so I might not be too great at it...
Please stay still, okay?
It's so hard and it's getting so hot.
Elena-san, if you keep doing that, I'm gonna...
Please let yourself feel good.
My tip is hitting something...
Not my ears...
S-Sorry!
That's fine. Do you feel better now?
Uh, yeah...
Good!
The timing isn't the greatest, but...
I...
I feel so hot!
Why am I doing this?
I don't want to do this!
Is she affected by the drug?
My body feels so...
Why?!
It feels so hot...
She's acting so sexy right now.
How the hell am I supposed to hold myself back?!
D-Don't!
Her boobs are so soft and fluffy!
It's so soft and springy.
I'm getting so wet with him right
in front of me. This is so embarrassing!
What's the matter with my body?
E-Elena-san, I...
My vagina is so hot and tingly. It wants you so bad!
Please fill this hole with your dick!
Elena-san!
Oh my god, your dick is inside me!
It's filling me up so much inside!
This is my first time, but it feels so good!
It's so deep, it's so deep!
Elena-san, I can't stop moving!
My pussy is throbbing so hard!
I-I'm cumming!
I can feel your cum dribbling out inside me!
It's pumping inside me!
I can feel your dick getting bigger!
It feels like my uterus is being pulled out!
I'm so embarrassed...
Elena-san, your pussy is so amazing.
Your pussy is dripping wet and feels so good!
Sorry, I'm gonna cum again!
It's pulsing inside me.
I can feel it pouring inside of me.
If you keep cumming so much inside of me,
I'm going to get pregnant. I really will!
Your pussy gets so tight
every time you come! It feels amazing!
I can't stop cumming either!
I didn't think you were this slutty!
I'm so embarrassed, but I can't stop myself!
More! Deeper!
I'm gonna cum again!
There's so much cum coming out insi...
No, not my ears!
You're gripping me so tightly!
I'm cumming!
I'm not done yet.
There's so much semen flowing inside of me!
I'll keep cumming inside you!
Make me pregnant with your cum!
Koakuma Kanojo.
No way!
Okumura-kun, please do it harder.
Elena-san...
They're kissing? I can't believe it!
Okumura-kun, I'm getting so horny!
Elena-san, I'm...
This can't be happening!
Wait, why am I so shocked?
Wasn't I the one who pushed him to do it?
Hibiki! Going home?
Kazuki...
Let's go home together!
Why are you in such a good mood?!
How about you go home by yourself?!
What? Why are you so mad?
No reason! Don't you have
someone better to go home with?
Did I do something?
I wanna be alone right now.
What's the matter, Hibiki?
I have something huge
to tell you about, so cheer up...
Get away from me!
Kazuki?! Get a hold of yourself! Kazuki!
Nurse's Office
This is the worst...
Nothing's going my way today.
I've liked him ever since we were kids,
but he gets stolen away by someone he just met?
I can't believe it.
Am I okay with just being a bystander?
No, I don't want that!
If I drink this love potion,
I should be able to make him fait in love with me.
What? Hibiki?!
Wh-What are you...
What do you mean? I'm sucking your dick.
No... That's not what I meant!
You like this, don't you? You're so hard.
I wanted to suck your dick, Kazuki.
What are you saying...
Is this the fabled pre-cum?
Huh? No, that's...
Kazuki, you're so dirty.
If you keep doing that, I'm gonna...
I wonder what it tastes like.
Kazuki, your dirty fluids are starting to stream out.
S-Stop it! What's the matter with you,
Hibiki? You're acting weird today.
I was trying to help you notice
my feelings since you're so dense.
What? But...
Hey, stop it!
Then how about you stop being so hard?
Your panties are rubbing against me...
It doesn't look like you want me to stop at all.
Just look at how hot and hard you are.
Don't you feel embarrassed about
being jacked off against your will?
Don't...
You're gonna cum from this? You're such a pervert.
No, stop...
Like this?
Wow, look at how much you came on me.
I need to take these off.
My socks are drenched too!
Look at how much of your cum is on them!
Hibiki...
Kazuki, your cum is so raw and delicious!
My... cum?
So, Hibiki... you're in lo...
There's so much here too!
What a waste!
I'm still sensitive from when I came, stop...
It's still so hard!
It's getting so big!
Wow! It's so bouncy!
You're moving your hips so much!
You're going to cum again, aren't you?
Give it to me!
Cum inside me next, okay?
No, stop. I'm already...
Kazuki...
No, stop, I'm gonna cum!
Wow, it's throbbing inside me.
There's so much hot stuff coming out of me!
What a waste. I need to plug it up.
It's still so hard!
I can feel your dick reaching so deep inside me!
It's hitting my womb!
I think I'm gonna cum again.
That's fine. Cum lots inside of me!
I-I'm cumming!
You've cum so much inside me
that my insides are soaked with it.
Even if I keep your dick in me,
I think it's going to overflow!
Did it feel so good that you lost consciousness?
It looks like you can't resist anymore,
so I'll untie you now.
Kazuki, you're sucking my nipples too hard!
Let go of me...
You're kidding! Your dick is getting bigger inside of me!
I-I-I'm cumming!
You're done, Hibiki!
I won't let you have your way with me!
I'm gonna cum!
What the hell was wrong with me? The way I was
acting made me look like some kind of pervert!
Forget what just happened!
Huh? What?!
You got it?!
G-Got it!
But...
My feelings for you are real...
I-I didn't do... anything...
You guys really can't fool anyone looking like that...
Don't try anything on my sweet
Kazuki, okay? Miss Pervert.
Your Kazuki?! That girl's a massive bitch!
That's not true at all, is it?
Stop getting so turned on!
What are you do...
I can do anything if it's for you, Kazuki.
I-I-I-I can too!
– Kazuki, give it to me!
If you both suck my dick, I'm gonna...
Then how about whoever makes him cum more wins?
Okay...
I'm gonna die at this rate...
I need to retreat!
Wait!
Kazuki!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: aux
quality control: fyurie