Hey, did you know?
Huh?
About the DVD that puts a curse on you when you watch it.
That's foolish.
It's just a rumor, right?
Then, wanna watch it?
Eh?
Ka-Kazuya...
Drenched sand sticky in sweat
Little Devil Girlfriend
It's okay.
It's definitely going to be okay.
I just need to stay away from Kazuya-kun for the entire day.
I, Akuno Mika is in love with Kazuya-kun.
But, this love may never be mutually replicated.
It's because my body is now...
The body of a demon.
Hey, Akuno-san!
That voice... Kazuya-kun?
Of all times, why did he have to show up now?
That looks heavy.
Shall I help you there?
N, n, no, it's okay!
Please don't come near me.
Eh?﻿
What do you mean?
I can do this myself.
So please leave me be...
You sure made a real mess there.
I should help you after all.
No, don't come!
Sorry, I just...!
Akuno-san?
Oh no...
I can't stop it anymore.
That's right.
Whenever I think of Kazuya-kun,
My body...
My body becomes like this.
Kazuya-kun?
What's with those breasts?
He found out!
No!
Akuno-san?
Tsun-Devi.
They say that anyone who watches this DVD becomes cursed.
No way!
What are you saying?
There's no such thing as a curse.
Then why don't we check it out Kana?
Eh?
O-okay then.
I'm going to watch it, and tell you what I think about it.
That's Kana for you.
There is such a thing as a curse.
Because I became a horny demon like this.
I only watched it because I thought it would be interesting.
Why?
Why does my body have to become like this?
What should I do?
Kazuya-kun saw me...
He saw my indecent body...
This tail...
I can't help but feel good while stroking it like this.
Kazuya-kun...
You would hate someone as horny as me, right?
He might not want to talk to me anymore.
Kazuya-kun.
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Akuno-san?
Kazuya-kun, don't look.
Don't look please!
Akuno-san?
No!
He just saw me doing it...
Now I can't get married anymore.
Is your body okay?
And I even turned back to normal quickly yesterday.
Now I can't turn myself back.
Well, it's your fault too, you know.
You're the one who made my body like this.
Eh?
What am I saying?
Kazuya-kun!
Come on.
I like you.
See, I like you Kazuya-kun.
What? I didn't intend to say that!
That means...
Even earlier, I was playing with myself while thinking of you.
I just want you to be mine no matter what.
Akuno-san?
Come.
Akuno-san, I...
You're quite daring, Kazuya-kun.
Don't fondle my breasts like that
No way...
I can't believe I'm actually doing this with him.
Give it to me already.
It's here right, Akuno-san?
He's deep inside me!
I just came earlier, I think I might just pass out.
It feels hot and wet inside, Akuno-san.
It feels good.
No...
If you keep doing it intensely like that...
I'm going to cum quickly.
I'm sorry.
But I can't stop.
Me too.
For a long time now...
I've always liked you, Akuno Mika.
No way...
That's just now...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
You came again.
You sure squirted out lots.
We're you really happy when I confessed to you?
Stupid!
I can explain some of this.
I see.
So that's in order to bring your body back to normal.
Y-Yep.
I need to get all horny and cum out lots from my tail.
So this is really like a guy's dick?
That's why you have to make me cum lots.
Make me feel really good down there.
It's okay to cum inside me.
Wow, you're pussy is squeezing me tight.
M-Mika...
There, at that spot!
No, not there!
It's going wild.
It's starting to get harder.
That's because it's being touched by someone I like.
My breasts and tail feel great.
Hey, wait...!
I'm...!
My milk's been built up there.
That's why I need you to suck it out.
There, right there!
Do it more.
Wow, it's sweet, and delicious!
Take it all.
Get it all out.
And return me to my old and normal self!
It's coming again.
Oh no!
Mika!
Kazuya.
I may have the body of a horny demon,
but would you still accept me?
There it is again!
Kazuya...
Kazuya, I like you.
Mika, I don't care about that.
Whether you're the horny Mika,
or the normal Mika.
I like you no matter what!
I like you too.
Oh no...
Thrust it in me more.
Make yourself feel good with my pussy.
I'm about to...!
Not...not my wings!
So you feel aroused here too.
No...
Don't...
Don't lick it like that!
It's squeezing me really tight again.
I'm gonna go crazy again.
Are you about to cum again?
That's because both my womb and
tail are being stimulated like that.
And I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum too.
Cum inside me!
Do it like you're really impregnating me!
I'm cumming!
In the end, I should thank the curse
for making my love bloom like this,
but instead of getting my curse removed...
It seems that it felt too good
that it won't turn back to normal anymore.
Or something.
Please take responsibility for this, okay?
Kazuya-kun!
Seems my love issues won't get completely solved just yet.
We can still...
It's okay, we can just do it again!
Little Devil Girlfriend
So this is the rumored cursed DVD.
Sorry Kana, can you watch it for us instead?
It's only you we can count on for this.
A DVD that curses the one who watches it?
How foolish.
It's just a rumor, right?
We're supposed to watch it and tell senpai what we think.
So please, Kana-sama.
My mistress Kana, I beg of you!
Guess it can't be helped.
I'm going to watch it for you two then.
What is this?
There's nothing on the screen.
Thank goodness.
My worry was just wasted.
Oh, so Onee-chan also watches porn when alone.
Mai, since when did you...?
I'm home.
Hey, can you lend that to me too?
Huh?
Is it something intense?
You can't have this!
This is still too much for you.
It's not for kids.
Besides, you need to be as mature
as I am before you can watch this.
Ehh?
As her elder sister, I just can't tell her that I was scared of this DVD.
My body is already matured enough, you know?
Mine is bigger than yours.
Here, look.
You talk too much Mai.
Meanie!
Jeez, here body is the only thing that's
actually matured about her.
Hey, what's this?
This feels like...
No!
Onee-chan?!
Mai, my body feels hot.
I'm getting really tingly down there.
I think I'm starting to lose it.
Jeez, what a troublemaker.
You just put a vibrator inside there, didn't you?
You pervert big sis!
Onee-chan?
No!
Mai, actually...
I was watching a DVD, the one that's rumored
to curse you when you watch it.
And then, I just felt all tingly down there.
And this is the result.
So this is what a dick looks like.
It's the first time I've seen a real one.
It looks a bit more monstrous than what I've heard though.
Mai...
Do you think I should go the hospital right now?
So it becomes like this.
Hey, are you listening Mai?
Okay! Leave it to me!
I'm on your side in this.
I'll do anything just for you.
Leave it...to me?
M-Mai!
It feels so hot and stiff.
Hey, Mai...
Stop that...
It's already this big, are you getting horny or something?
That's not it.
Oh, but it's soft here.
Feels like a marshmallow.
Stop, not there...
Oh no, whats is this?
My part down there...
Its really getting aroused.
It feels good.
No, don't.
Stop doing that.
It's coming out!
Is this, cum?
It feels good.
What is this?
It's still coming out.
It feels all slimy, and it smells weird.
Mai...
Eh!?
Onee-chan, this is...?
It felt really great to cum earlier.
That's why... let me do it more with your breasts.
Onee-chan, you're acting weird.
Onee-chan!
But my dick is itching to do it!
I just can't stop!
This feels gross.
It's the first time I've felt like this.
I can feel it twitching at each moment.
Dick's sure are awesome.
I'm cumming again.
Mai, your breasts feel too good, that I can't stop cumming!
Suck it.
Your mouth feels good too.
Here, take some more.
No way, she just came earlier.
It's getting stiff again.
I can't breathe.
There it is again, I can't stop it.
Mai, I'm going to cum inside your mouth.
No...!
Onee-chan, let's stop this already.
Jeez, that's not good.
You have to drink it all.
Here.
Onee-chan.
I'm sitting on top of you right now.
In that case, I'll just have to teach you everything using my body.
Th-that's...
Don't.
Even if you say that, your pussy is all wet already.
You were aroused by my tit fuck earlier, right?
No, that's not true...
Oh no, what am I going to do?
It feels too good to be fondled by Onee-chan.
Even though we're both girls.
Now then, we need to teach your body a lesson.
Onee-chan...
Oh you...
You're so wet.
I'm going to insert this for you.
Let's make this feel good for both of us.
No, don't put it in.
You're now inside me!
What's this?
It's really squeezing me tight.
Now I'm getting really horny too.
This is my first time and yet,
I'm being violated by her dick.
You're cute... just too cute.
I'm going to make your cute pussy feel good.
I'm going to lose it if you keep doing it that intensely.
That's alright.
Just go wild.
I'm about to get crazy too.
I'm going to cum lots inside so don't worry.
No...
You can't cum inside.
Onee-chan, please.
I can't listen to that request, Mai.
Onee-chan!
It's coming out, it's coming out.
Cum is being poured inside me.
Again?
You're going to make me cum again, Mai.
Your pussy squeezes me tighter as I lick your ears.
You're sensitive here just like me.
We really are sisters.
No...
I don't want this anymore.
Stop.
My insides are already filled with your cum.
I'm sorry, it just feels too good to be
squeezed by your pussy like this.
My dick just can't stop cumming.
No, Onee-chan!
I never knew...
That having a dick could feel this great.
More, I want to cum some more!
Amazing, she just came earlier,
and yet she's still drilling inside my pussy like this.
I can't keep up anymore.
Let me go already.
Onee-chan.
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum while having sex with you, Onee-chan!
Mai, your pussy is twitching.
You're getting all horny now, right?
Your dick is amazing.
I'm going to cum again.
I'm going to pour lots of cum into your womb again.
Onee-chan...!
Wow, I’m fine now!
I guess the trick was to keep on making it cum.
My pussy's all clean now!
Mai, look!
I'm back to normal.
Mai, did you just...
That was just unfair.
You're the only one who had fun earlier.
Even I...
...﻿also wanted to cum like this.
Now I'm the one who's going to cum lots inside your pussy.
No!
So, in order to lift the curse,
you have to have sex.
No way.
We're going to do it now, right?