Come with me.
The service shall start soon.
Now then,
shall I put in more effort this time?
The forgotten phantom fox
Ginko, there, that's good...
Mister, this is what you love, is it not?
No matter how great or poor my customers are,
men will always be men.
Ginko...
This stupefied expression...
You crave to release It already, do you not?
Here, hurry and ejaculate.
For I shall take it all in.
Lots of it is coming out.
H-Hey, let me rest for a bit.
But, this one is still holding its vigor.
You are one strange prostitute, Ginko.
I've been frequenting this 'red-light' district for quite some time,
but you're still as youthful as ever.
It's almost as if you're a being from another realm.
Such words might make me feel embarrassed.
What is it that you require of me?
Ginko...!
That feels good, as well.
I'm tingling all over.
Here, I want you to pleasure me as well.
Your hot thing is penetrating me.
Yes, and you're wrapping around me really well, too.
If you want,
I can wrap it even tighter for you.
It seems to have gotten even bigger.
My insides are now being stirred intensely by it.
G-Ginko...
Look, my breasts are now completely aroused, as well.
Well then,
I shall take good care of you tonight, mister.
Leave it to me, I'm the one who shall
show you how great my cum is.
Amazing...
Mister, I am about to reach my climax,
and also lose myself along the way.
Here, I'm going to cum.
I'm going to let it all out inside you.
Cum then.
Please cum.
It's trying to suck me in.
It's squeezing my dick to the tip.
Lots of your hot and sticky stuff is dripping out.
This is weird, Ginko.
I know we just finished earlier,
but my dick won't stop pushing.
I am happy that you desire for me this much.
Please, do it more.
Just let it all out wherever you want to.
It's wrapping tightly around it again.
I feel the same way, I am about to cum, as well.
Please, mister, do it with me...
Oh yes... that feels good...
It feels good...
People become enthralled,
and the desire that is both ugly and beautiful surfaces.
Such is the norm at the red light district of Yoshibara.
In this place, anyone's heart can be easily manipulated.
It is indeed a fine place for one such as I.
Each customer is easily captivated by my charm,
and then I receive their essence.
No one gets hurt, and we part ways as soon as it ends.
That's the game I frequently take part in here.
Huh? What is this scent?
I shall visit again sometime.
Feel free to look at my goods again.
Wait, you over there.
Is there something you need from me?
Why now of all time?
No... You seem to bear a resemblance to someone I know.
I just thought you might...
H-Hey, are you Ginko?
Why are you here?
You...
I thought you'd already forgotten about me.
Is it okay for me to set foot in this place?
Do not mind.
For you are already acquainted with me.
I see.
I never thought you'd become a traveling peddler.
I've been wandering around, while in
search of new places to do business.
But that is only part of what I really want to do.
I was actually looking for you, Ginko.
What foolishness are you talking about?
I ran away exactly because I needed to be separated from you.
Then all I did was meaningless!
But I'm really surprised.
I never thought that you would become a courtesan.
Do you hate me now?
No, you just seemed quite different, so I was hesitant for bit,
but you really didn't change.
His scent is so nostalgic.
I'm glad that we met again, Ginko.
No, I can't hold back any longer.
In any case, I'll just have to... just for this occasion...
How many years has it been since we first met?
During that rainy night,
you saved me,
and became the very first human that I
as an Ayakashi, had ever set eyes on.
You were still an innocent boy back then,
wrapping your warm arms around me and making me feel safe.
Even after I revealed my identity as an Ayakashi,
you still treated me like a family member.
During those peaceful times when I lived with you,
I eventually developed feeling... for you.
However, I knew that humans and Ayakashi
just weren't meant to live together.
I, who feeds on the essences of humans
might someday lose myself to instinct,
and eventually devour you!
A long time has passed since we parted ways.
But this nostalgic scent, is something that I could never forget.
That tickles.
No, not there...
This is strange.
My nipples are already hard.
Maybe my instincts as an Ayakashi are going wild.
Wagging your tail like that...
You really seem like a dog.
I'm a fox, you fool.
Then, how are you here?
No, that part is...
My body feels really hot.
The sensation is completely different than
when I do it with my other customers.
It feels as if I'm going to melt inside at anytime.
Look, it's starting to overflow.
His fingers are stirring up me wet pussy.
I'm not supposed to be this slutty, but...
It's just suddenly like this.
That was quite the vigorous reaction.
Do you usually flirt with your male customers like this?
Don't take me too lightly.
It's because it's you, that's why I...
Ginko.
Even you, are already aroused, you know.
Hey...
See, you're already this hard.
This is payback for what you did.
I'm going to make you feel so good that you'll go to heaven.
Ginko, you...!
What is it?
Could this be the first time you're experiencing this?
Rubbing my nipples onto this tip feels very great, does it not?
I shall put everything I've learned to the test with you.
So? Does it feel good?
This is his scent, his taste...
I do not hate it one single bit.
My body is getting even more aroused.
That's good...
I'm about to cum.
His thing is twitching, and is getting hotter.
Just release it anytime you want to.
I shall take it all.
This is his cum... hot, sticky and has a very strong smell.
S-Sorry, I've even soiled your face.
Do not worry.
But, cumming outside so much is such a waste.
You tease me quite well.
This time, I'll get you to cum every drop in me.
Hey, Ginko.
It's still very lively after cumming like that.
I admire its strong vitality.
It's going straight inside me.
I'm about to cum just by having it inside me.
My body is completely aroused, and is quite sensitive already.
It's so tight.
I'm going to move.
Wait, Ginko...!
It's too late now.
It's already filled my insides.
And it's making its way even deeper inside.
You want to cum more, right?
That's true, but this sensation is just too intense!
He's getting really aroused with my body.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
My insides are starting to get even wetter.
Oh no, I'm...!
Me too, I'm going to...
I'm going to cum!
Ginko...
There, can you feel it?
My insides are pulsating.
It wants your dick so much that it just won't stop.
Ginko, could you...
actually be...
Do not worry, for I will not devour you.
I'm not an Ayakashi right now.
I'm all yours at the moment.
I am simply a whore you can play with any way you want.
Ginko...
Right now, I am simply another female
that wants to frolic with you.
Do you understand?
Alright, here I go.
This is amazing.
Your insides are pushing me hard.
If you say that, then I'm going to play with you real hard, Ginko.
Yes, that's right.
Right now, everything in me is yours.
Oh yes,
just mess with me however you want.
Play with my body more.
My body is starting to lose it.
Whenever I say something obscene, my body
starts to get excited and move on its own.
Gi-Ginko, your insides are sucking me really hard.
That's good, just cum whenever you want to.
I'm going to squeeze every last bit of your cum inside me.
Ginko!
It's coming...!
We seem to have forgotten the passage of time after that,
and continued to make love with each other.
He poured all of his cum into me,
leaving no part of my body untouched.
I'm, l'm about to...
Oh yeah, I remember she loved it when I touched her tail.
No, my tail... my tail...
I see, so your tail is very sensitive.
No, don't...!
If you keep on rubbing it like that I'll...
Stop...!
It's coming out!
Looks like this slutty fox needs some disciplining.
Oh no, oh no, please let it be...
I'm going to go crazy if this continues.
Let's, let's just do it normally...
I'll have you make me cum as well.
No, this is...
I just came so I...
But, this feels good for you, right?
It feels good.
It feels good...
So please fuck me more.
Make a complete mess of me.
Amazing.
You really do tease me well.
I never intended to expose my self to you like this.
Now you've seen how shameful I can be.
Ginko, I don't care if you're an Ayakashi.
Because I love you!
You are...
You're getting even rougher now.
It's pushing even deeper inside.
Ginko...!
I'm about to cum!
Me too, I'm going to cum too.
Let's, let's...
Cum together!
I'm cumming!
Hey, Ginko.
Won't you come home with me?
You're the only one,
who can make a fool out of a phantom fox like this.
So, that's a no?
Well...
I don't think it'd be that bad.
Ginko.
This will be the first... and last time, that
I shall fall in love with someone.
Ginko!
She couldn't have...
Done it again...
In the end, you are still but a human.
Just think of this as a one time merriment,
and start treading on your own path.
I am an Ayakashi.
I shall be a phantom fox, no matter what.