Sorry for having you carry those.
What are you gonna do with these?
Repairing our clotheshorse.
It'd be pretty costly to hire someone to do it, right?
Ah, I see.
She's the manager of the apartment I live in.
Loving the complex left behind her uncle filled with memories,
it looks like she decided to succeed him young.
Opening♥Closure
Yuuichi, if you don't mind, why don't you join me for dinner?
As a reward for helping me today, that is.
I can, seriously?!
Yay!
Ouch.
Are you alright?
Ah, ...yeah.
You're unexpectedly clumsy, eh?
Don't laugh at me so much...
These childlike expressions she sometimes shows are ever so cute.
I was completely in love with her.
Opening♥Closure
Delicious!
I'll join you as soon as I get done washing off this sweat.
Please go ahead with the food.
Sure!
It'd have been nice if she could join me too.
This can't be, a rat?!
Manager?
No!
Sorry for hurting you, Yuuichi.
Ah, no.
I'm sorry too.
That place of hers I only caught a glimpse of a moment ago is right infront of my eyes!
Uhm Yuiichi, that is...
This is, uhm...
Could that be because of me?
Well, about it being your fault, or rather, that happened because it's you.
Is that true?
I wouldn't get like this if it wasn't you.
Me too.
These days, when I see your face, my heartbeat gets faster.
And you're always helping me with something or other too.
I wondered if that was simply out of goodwill.
But I'm more that 5 years older than you, so...
That doesn't matter at all!
Since I love you!
I won't do?
You'll have to properly take responsibility for making my heart race.
Manager!
Ever since the first time I saw you, I...
Kanako.
Kanako, that's my name.
I've always longed for your boobs, Kanako!
Don't, Yuiichi.
With a cute face like that, and to think that your tits are so large...
It's unfair!
Even if you tell me that...
Nothing's gonna come out even if you suck it like that.
Can I take off your underwear?
Y-Yeah.
I'm so wet there that it's making strings.
He only teased my boobs and I ended up like this...
So this is your pussy.
I beg you, don't look at it so closely!
It's so embarrassing!
I can't get enough of this.
It's sticking to my fingers so lovingly.
Just putting in my fingers feels so good!
Yuiichi...
I'm making such a perverted sound...
My insides are being churned up.
I ...can't hold back any longer.
Sure, that's fine.
Put it in.
Huh? It won't go in.
Calm down.
It's a bit below.
Yeah, there.
Oh crap!
Eh?
Sorry for cumming so soon.
Nah, it's alright.
Your thing's still so hard.
Like this, do it once more.
S-Sure.
Yuuichi, you're being rough.
Sorry, but I can't stop my hips anymore!
That's okay.
Move as you want to!
Make yourself feel good even more with me!
Kanako, I love you!
Kanako!
The semen from before is sticking to my insides.
This is the first time I've ever felt like this.
Ah, don't!
If you do my tits too, I'm gonna end up perverted.
That's fine.
I want to see your perverted sides too.
Amazing, it's hitting my deepest parts.
It already feels like I'm gonna break!
You're squeezing me so hard!
This is turning me all perverted!
Let me show you.
My embarrassing, shameful spots. All of them!
Kanako, if you go that far, I'm gonna...
Me too!
I'm gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum!
Let's do it together, please!
Cum loads, I'll be sure to accept it all!
Kanako...
Yuuichi...
This is the first time I've ever used someone's arms as pillows.
This somehow feels so nice.
I don't even care if I die now!
The truth is, I've been in love with you for a long time.
For a long time?
When would that be?
I've forgotten already.
Drama Club
Alright!
Next up is the 8th page of the scenario,
the scene where the little fox gets caught in the trap!
A-Alright.
You damn fox cub!
I'm gonna punish you with interest for everything till now!
Hey, wait!
There's nothing like that in the scenario.
This is ad-lib.
Don't mind the small stuff.
Huh?!
Princess Fox
It hurts.
You don't have to tie me up so seriously, no?
That won't do at all!
Now, like that, try saying "Sorry for all the pranks I've pulled till now."
Eh?
I don't want to.
If you don't, I'm going to take off your panties, Himeno.
I-I got it.
Sorry for all the pranks I've pulled till now
I'll do anything, so please forgive me.
Ugh, Himeno!
Idiot! Why are you hugging me?!
It's just practice for the play!
You mean to say that with a face that's basically begging for it?
Don't strip me, no!
You can't look!
Don't stroke my breasts!
Don't touch me there!
I used to think you were still a kid,
but recently, you've grown up quite a bit.
I'm not a kid.
Don't make light of me like that!
Oh, is that so?
Let me subject you to adult terms then.
Eh?
Why does adult equate sex?!
Don't, you idiot!
Don't rub me with that thing.
It's embarrassing.
But this place of yours is so wet already, Himeno.
Eh? You really mean to put that in?
You're an adult, so that should be obvious, right?
Right, here we go then.
My thing's inside your important place, Himeno.
Right about here as of now, I guess.
S-Stop, don't push it in more.
Don't grind against me.
There's no way we can stop here, you know that, right?
Bear with it already.
Then, at least untie the rope.
I promise I won't run away.
Amazing! Your hot thing's grinding in me!
Just as I thought, your loli pussy is so tight!
Don't call it a loli pussy!
Since this is all your fault, Brother!
Brother! Brother!
H-Himeno! Himeno!
Why so hard all on a sudden?!
Don't, not so hard!
It's hitting my insides!
More, call me by 'Brother' more!
Idiot, I can't...
Hurry up!
Brother, you're so rough!
If you do it like that, I'm gonna...
I can't anymore, Himeno!
I'm gonna cum inside you!
This can't be happning, not inside!
You're gonna knock me up.
Don't cum inside!
A lot of your stuff is coming out.
I'm gonna get pregnant with your baby.
Geez, you're mean!
I told you to stop so many times.
W-Well, it's been so long since you called me by 'Brother," so...
Hey, do it again, just once.
You idiot.
B-Brother...
From Kanako's parents, we got travel coupons.
So, we went on a hot spring trip with just the two of us.
Yuuichi, look!
That's a pretty great inn, eh?
I know, right? It's great, huh?
Kanako.
Opening♥Closure
Wait, why are you here?
Oh my, so cold.
It doesn't cost anything to show me your boyfriend's face at least, does it?
Uhm, what might the relation between you two be?
It didn't have to be like this, does it?!
Sorry, Yuuichi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kanako's mom, Yurie.
Thank you for always taking care of my daughter.
Eh?!
Mom?! Not sister?
Oh my, it looks like that?
Geez, you sure know how to flatter.
Eh? No, I'm being serious.
You're so young and beautiful, so I thought...
Yuuichi, why are you getting so lovey dovey with mom?
Here we go Yuuichi, say "Ah."
Eh?!
You don't have to get shy!
Uhm, okay.
Hey Mom!
You're troubling him.
Oh my. I'm not, am I?
Uhm, well, nope.
You're the boyfriend of my cute daughter.
It makes me want to serve you, somehow.
Or is it that you wanted to be the one feeding him?
That's not it, but...
Ah, you've got rice in your face!
Geez, mom!
Once we're rested up a bit, let's head into the bath, together!
Is it really okay, for me to be here too?
This place is reserved, and we've got towels too.
Yurie's really bold, hmm.
Hey Yuichi, can you give me a shoulder rub?
Uh, sure!
What's her problem?
She's been going "Yuuichi this, Yuuichi that" for a while.
He's my boyfriend!
But, I don't want to seem so jealous.
Geez!
Just like that, you're good.
Try a bit lower too.
Like this?
Oh my.
Sorry, it wasn't on purpose!
It's fine, don't worry.
She seems to have fallen asleep already as well.
Eh?
It's fine to leave her alone.
She's just crashed from being drunk.
She can't control her alcohol, but did it anyway.
Even then...
Rather than that Yuuichi,
there's something serious we need to talk about.
Hey, do you really love her?
Y-Yes!
Of-course!
Thinking of marrying her or something along the line?
If we can, I'd want to.
Uhm, they're hitting me.
Indeed they are.
For a harmonious married live, your bodies must be compatible!
This is bad!
Let me confirm whether you have what it takes to make her go crazy!
Oh my, it got like this just from seeing me naked?
That's because you're so beautiful, Yurie.
I couldn't hold back.
That's not good.
To think you got close to women while hiding such a weapon!
I'm going to confiscate it.
This can't be right.
You're Kanako's mom, Yurie.
So, doing something like this is...
You're holding back due to her, eh?
So cute!
Then, how about this?
Yurie...
My breasts are soft and feel nice, right?
They're larger than Kanako's, even.
This is bad, I can't!
Your dick's so hot, it's pulsating!
You're gonna cum?
You're about to cum, right?
You can't yet.
It gets serious from here.
Wait, that is...
This is only a lesson.
There's no need for you to worry.
It's so big!
Yuuichi, it feels so good!
You're filling me up!
So tight!
I'm cumming already!
You can't!
Not yet, you'll have to hold back!
But!
More, mess up more insides with the tip of your dick more.
Move your hips up and down, like this.
Like that, yeah.
You're good, and your dick's shaped really nicely as well.
You'll be able to make her happy too!
It's impossible to hold back anymore!
You've done well to hold back this far, I'm about to cum too!
It's fine, cum to your heart's content!
I'm cumming while being cummed inside!
Yurie...
A lot of it came out.
I got inseminated by my daughter's boyfriend.
Mom, give me Yuuichi back, right now!
Oh my, you're awake already?
This isn't, uhm...
Yuuichi's my boyfriend, you know.
Don't just take him.
Kanako?!
You sure you want to do that? Mommy's gonna see it all, you know.
That's fine, it's not really embarrassing.
I'll let you watch us having sex too.
Ugh, wait!
The only one allowed to use your dick is me, Yuuichi.
I'll make you cum with my pussy!
Kanako...
So, don't just look at my mom, look at me too!
Cute, you're too cute!
Damn it!
There's no way I can be calm after you show me something like this!
Don't, I'm gonna cum already!
I'm supposed to be the one making you come today.
I'm gonna caress your insides.
I keep telling you, don't!
This can't be...
And, on the shallow part inside you, I'm going to caress like this!
Don't Yuuichi, don't do that.
I'm going to cum, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
That was amazing.
To think Kanako'd actually squirt while cumming...
That was pretty embarrassing, Kanako.
Weren't you supposed to make him cum?
Well...
Sorry, Yuuuichi.
It doesn't seem like she can move her hips anymore.
So, cum all you want in your pace using this!
No, don't...
Sorry, but I can't hold back anymore.
This can't be...
You just put it in and I'm already feeling it so much.
Don't, I'm gonna cum again!
Hold yourself back, Kanako.
It wouldn't be fair on Yuuichi if it was just you who cummed.
That place of mine is already sloppy wet and driving me crazy!
Mommy will keep you company, so work a bit harder!
Clench your pussy.
This is amazing, the tightness is out of this world.
I can feel your penis becoming hot and start pulsating.
Yuuichi, does it feel good?
Yes!
I'm gonna cum already!
That's fine, cum!
Cum loads!
It's coming out.
His hot stuff is coming out.
Kanako?
It's fine, she just fainted from feeling too good.
You too seem snugly compatible too, body wise.
Really?
Well then.
Shall I have you do it to me once more too?
Eh?
It's aching from seeing you two.
Yuuichi, please?
After that, Yurie squeezed me dry.
Ugh, my head hurts.
Kanako was hungover and didn't seem to remember anything at all from last night.
Mom seems to be shining today.
It looks like that? Nothing's really up though.
Right, Yuuichi?
I-Indeed.
Koiito Kinenbi The Animation
Koiito Kinenbi Memorial episode: 2
is meant to come out in 2013, Spring