Waku-FAPsubs
Credits: Naoya/Fomite
Love Thread Memorial Day THE ANIMATION Memorial 2 『Unexpected Holy Night☆』
This should be the last house.
As expected of myself. I'm so efficient.
I'll end this quick.
Nyaa~!
S-Santa?
Unexpected Holy Night☆
T-This must be a Christmas present from God.
I can't be wrong!
A-Alrighty, I'll start with the boobs first.
Great stuff. I'm touching real breasts.
The nipples will actually erect.
W-W-What about the vagina?
It's got a nice color to it.
The inside is becoming wet and warm.
Don't tell me she's feeling horny?
I can't stand it anymore!
Santa! Here I come!
Why are there surges of pain inside me?
Are you awake, Santa?
What is this?
Why am I... being...
Because, you are the present, aren't you, Santa?
So I accepted it right away.
W-What are you talking about?
You got it wrong. I'm not a present!
Hey, stop moving like that!
Thank you so much, Santa!
I feel great!
I'll feel troubled if you thank me.
I didn't mean for it that way.
Receiving such a present, I'm so glad to be alive!
Seriously, stop weeping and thrusting at the same time.
Calm down a little and listen to me.
No, please don't.
Santa! I'm gonna come!
Don't cum!
No, how could you cum inside.
If you do that..
I'll get pregnant.
I'm really sorry.
Because Santa is way too cute.
I accidentally...
What the hell... I'm going back after giving you your present.
Oh? A card.
To Aisha.
The presents are finished.
So that makes the last present yourself.
Be his girlfriend.
From Mom, with love.
WHAT!?
Erm, where's my present?
There's no way I agree to it!
Love Thread Memorial Day.
Yahoo, Onee-chan!
Welcome, Anna. Long time no see.
Nice to meet you.
Onii~chan~
P-Pleasure's is mine.
I heard a lot about you from Mom.
She said the two of you are really compatible.
Isn't it about time you start making plans for wedding?
Well, we haven't even...
Right? Yuuichi-kun?
Yeah.
Both of you are so slow.
Are you already at the stage of fatigue?
I-It's nothing like that, right? Yuuichi-kun.
O-Of course not.
Looks like I'd better start doing something.
To Tie♥and To Open Little Devil☆Anna
The reason why couples have quarrels...
Is definitely that, right.
Hey, Yuuichi-san.
Are you having sex with Onee-chan?
She's really serious when it comes to stuff like that.
You must be holding it for a long time?
Well, quite...
Well, why don't you first do-it-with-me?
Anna-chan, are you really alright?
Yeah, it's fine.
I'm also about that age already.
I'm also rather interested in stuff like this.
Your here has become so wet.
T-That's because...
Seriously, don't make me say embarrassing stuff when I'm like that!
Sorry.
M-My..
Oh no. Yuuichi-san is really good.
Is he also doing stuff like that to Onee-chan?
No, I can't bear it anymore.
H-Hey, Yuuichi-san. That's enough.
Come in quick.
It's itchy down there, I can't stand it.
Here I go, Anna-chan.
Amazing. It's huge!
Are you alright?
What do you think? Does it feel good inside me?
Yeah, it's really tight. Feels fucking good.
I see. That's good.
What's this?
It's reaching all the way inside.
It's so hard, I'm gonna start making noises.
Shit. This just feels too good.
Yuuichi-san's penis feels so good.
Could it be that you're easily sensitive?
No, stop saying weird stuff.
It's not like that, I..
I'm not such a lewd person.
My there, my deeper region.
I'm feeling waves of it.
If it's so tight on me,
I'm gonna cum!
Anna-chan?
You wanna cum inside, right?
I don't mind if it's Yuuichi-san.
I can't do something like that.
But if it feels this good, I can't just stop midway.
Impressive. Your penis is gradually, getting warmer and bigger.
Anna-chan. I'm really gonna cum.
I'm fine. Please go ahead.
Empty everything inside me.
I'm not wearing a condom or anything.
It's fine, even without protection.
I'm gonna cum really, really soon.
What's this!
It's hot. Your penis is throbbing, it's going crazy inside!
S-So this is an internal ejaculation?
Amazing.
I don't think something like that will really happen.
Am I perhaps, having a sexual discontent?
Ka-Kanako-san!
Welcome back, Yuuichi-kun.
Well, you know...
I think I have to discuss something with you.
Eh?
Oh, on second thought, it's really nothing.
Yuuichi-kun.
Love Thread Memorial Day
It's almost a year since Aisha arrived at my home.
Time really flies!
Why do I feel the turn of events is a bit fast.
What!
Merry Christmas, Nee-sama.
S-Sasha?
This is a present from Mom.
Holy Night Happy Bell.
Wow, erotic!
Seriously, Mom.
What's with this sort of clothing?
Mom says she wants to see her grandson soon.
She tells you to use this to seduce him!
I see now!
A sure-win attire for procreation.
If that's the case...
Hey, wait...
It's a piece of cake!
Wait!
What are you gonna do with me?
I'm not mentally prepared for it.
If Nee-sama is unwilling,
Mom says I could take her place.
I see, I see.
Aisha doesn't want to bear my child.
Then I only have to do it with Sasha-chan.
Nii-sama.
Eh.
That's..
If Nee-sama is reluctant,
I can bear a child in your place.
No way.
It's still too early for you.
That's not true.
I feel embarrassed if Nii-sama does it with me. But it still feels good.
Ah...
Can you split open your cunt, Sasha-chan?
No... this...
shouldn't be allowed.
Tight!
Does it hurt, Sasha-chan?
I'm fine.
Your warm penis is moving in and out, I 'm  feeling weird.
Nii-sama, I want it more.
I'm becoming such a slut.
If Nii-sama feels good,
I feel good too.
I'll keep doing my best until Nii-sama feels satisfied.
Sasha looks to be feeling really good.
I'm gonna cum, Sasha-chan!
Nii-sama!
It felt great.
Erm...
If you still haven't had enough, I...
You can also hug me, if you want.
Aisha!
You're finally prepared!
It feels great inside you, Aisha.
You're already so wet.
No, don't say that.
That's not true, I'm just...
You're so vigorous all of a sudden.
Let's make a bunch of healthy kids!
No, it's embarrassing.
Sasha is watching too.
How could I actually...
Nee-sama, you seem to be feeling good.
Aisha.
I'm on the verge of coming.
Can I really trust you?
Yes.
I love you, Aisha.
Make sure they count.
I'm cuming!
Lots of fuzzling stuff are filling inside me.
Incredible.
It's not over. This is just the start!
What?
Nii-sama, unload more of your stuff inside me.
Nii-sama!
I only came just now, yet...
I.. I'm about to...
Love Thread Memorial Day.
Yuuichi-kun, what's wrong with you?
Don't tell me he's dating other girls.
So he wants to break up with me.
No way.
Yuuichi-kun isn't such a person.
But I still feel really uneasy, Yuuichi-kun.
I get your point.
But it's still hard to tell even if that's the case.
I know right.
Why don't you just go to his room now and ask him.
Pondering over it won't solve anything.
Now?
It'll be fine.
Together we'll send him flying if he strays.
Anna.
Yuuichi-kun, are you awake
K-Kanako-san?
I'm sorry for barging in so late.
You know...
Can we sleep together today?
Eh?
We can't?
No.
Erm, Kanako-san.
Did something happen?
You seem to want to tell me something, lately.
So I started thinking a lot about various things.
Huh?
Could it be you found another girlfriend
and perhaps you want to break up with me?
How can that sort of thing be possible!
Yuuichi-kun?
No way.
I've been trying to give this to you.
But I couldn't find the words to say every single time.
But I...
I'll never do anything that will hurt you.
Yuuichi-kun!
I'm sorry for suspecting you.
I'm really sorry!
Kanako-san.
It's alright.
I love you the best, Yuuichi-kun.
Yuuichi's...
Hey...
Let's do it.
My glans, no....
It feels really good.
Yuuichi-kun's penis is throbbing here and there, it's adorable.
I-I have to try harder for him.
I must do my best!
That's!
Yuuichi-kun.
No.
I'm really sensitive there.
Yuuichi-kun.
I can't stand it anymore.
Come in, please.
In all the way.
Incredible.
This...
This position... is dirty.
You're so tight there, Kanako-san.
That's because, it's been a long time since we last did it. So...
Oh no! I can't!
I'm going to... cum!
I can't anymore!
I feel it coming in.
Sorry.
I came on my own.
I made you feel too good, that's why.
I feel kind of happy.
Anyway, I'm going to clean this up.
Kanako-san!
My waist seems to be coming off.
If you lick on the urethra.
I'm going to...
It's fine.
Love me however you wish today.
Yuuichi-kun!
I-I love it.
There's lots of semen still inside. It's kind of lewd.
I can still be more of a slut.
As long as Yuuichi-kun wants it,
I can be even more lewd.
No, my breast.
Amazing. It's getting hard.
No, don't!
Hey, let's...
Let's cum together.
I'm climaxing soon.
I almost there too.
Yuuichi-kun.
I love you.
Kanako-san.
Please marry me!
No!
At a time like this, you're so cunning.
I.. I'm... cuming.
I'm going to cum.
Cuming!
Go ahead.
Cum all of it inside of me.
There's so much of it.
Seriously,Yuuichi-kun.
That's too sudden.
There's no way I could have given you a proper reply at that sort of time.
I-I'm sorry.
But, thank you.
I accept your proposal.
K-Kanako-san.
Yuuichi-san,you look really nervous.
Are you alright?
I'm fine, Anna-chan.
Onee-chan! Yuuichi-san is here!
How do I look, Yuuichi-kun?
Gorgeous.
Thanks.
There's still a bit of time.
The both of you can wait here.
I'm call you both when everything's prepared.
I see.
We still have some time.
Hey, Yuuichi-kun.
Are we really gonna do it here?
It's only now that kanako-san's in a wedding dress.
Please.
I can't hold it in any longer.
Geez... it can't be helped.
Your breasts seemed to have gotten bigger recently, Kanako-san.
You're sucking it everyday, that's why.
Oh dear, the penis has become so hard.
I'm also starting to feel strange myself.
Yu-Yuuichi-kun.
You're so rough all of a sudden.
Kanako-san in wedding dress is too seductive.
No way, that sort of thing..
You're already so wet inside.
You must be really horny, right?
No, don't say that.
The thought of having sex at a place like this
makes me feel more excited than usual.
It's so deep inside.
Your hot and piping penis.
It's touching the tip of the womb.
My dick is melting inside your womb.
I'm cuming, Kanako-san.
The source of babies, I'm releasing them!
Babies.
Yuuichi-kun and my baby.
I have more feeling than usual.
Kanako-san. Get pregnant with my semen.
Now, with you moving inside of me...
I'm going to climax! I'm cuming!
Your semen is comng in spurts.
My insides.. are burning.
S-Seriously..
I even said the wedding ceremony is about to begin.
What do they think they're doing?!
I'll surely give you happiness, Kanako.
I love you, my dear.