Ren'ichi-kun...
Will you keep the fact that we went to the pool
yesterday a secret from Nanase-chan?
Will you, please?
Sanae...
Amagi-kun? Hey, Amagi-kun.
Sorry, what?
Sanae's in love with you.
But she can be a bit insecure and shy,
so if you don’t be clear with her...
Sanae...
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: MrMew |TS & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Ayanami-
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Afterschool Love Club
Etude of Love
Episode 2:     . . .  Because Love Has No Logic
Rinko-chan, your mom seems very strict.
Hm?
Jeez. Rinko-chan, what's going on?
How was your date today?
I just received a call from your teacher.
It appears you cut class!
Would you like seconds?
Jeez, I was just getting to the good part.
Rinko-chan,
you don't need to hang out with
this jerk if you don't want to.
Misawa?
Misawa-san...
When did I drift off? Sorry about that.
Sis, can I go home-soon?
Se-n-pa-i.
This feels pretty nice, doesn't it?
Sitting across from each other
like this and talking every day.
You really think it's that nice?
Of course I do!
I'm so happy I joined the club!
You do look happy.
I am!
Lots of nice things have happened!
I got to be friends with Kanami-san,
and I also got to meet Shiina-senpai.
Kanami? You mean the ko-gal?
Yes.
Even though she's in the same class as me,
we've never talked. I was scared of her.
Scared?
Well, I guess she's just kind of
intimidating. Hard to talk to.
She is a lot different from you.
That's right.
I always thought there was
something different about her.
The way she looks, the way she
dresses the way she thinks.
But her outward appearance and dress
is the same as yours, isn't it?
Huh?
But you see, when I finally talked to her,
we actually had a great time!
I thought today we’d visit a place
that Kanami really likes.
That Kanami likes?
In that case, it probably doesn't serve food.
Senpai, you mustn't judge
on outward appearances.
I guess you're right about that.
Then what is it?
"Oh dear, I burned the gratin!"
You mean something like that?
W-Were you trying to imitate me just now?
No, I didn't mean to...
Ah! Don't tell me...
So when I messed up dinner last
night, you weren't stalking me?
No, well, I just thought that it would be funny
if Kanami said something like that.
Senpai, it was just your imagination then!
Of course it was. You don't really think
I'd stalk you at your house, do you?
No, but...
Senpai!
Sanae.
Ren'ichi-kun...
I've been looking for you.
What a nice fragrance.
Really?
You can judge a good tea by its fragrance.
You're pretty knowledgeable, aren't you?
We drink lots of different kinds of tea at home.
Listen...
You're avoiding me, aren't you?
We went to the pool on Sunday.
You shouldn't hide that from Nanase-chan.
I think you're right.
So I thought I'd tell her about it, but...
Should I tell her, then?
Wait. Don't do that, Ren'ichi-kun.
I want to be the one to tell her.
Well, I guess so...
Yeah, you're right.
It's okay. I'm a little scared,
so please hold me tight.
And if....
we can see love in our future,
then let's smile more.
Bye, Senpai!
Huh? You re leaving already
You are my angel.
Yeah. I thought I'd go home with Shiina today.
With Shiina?
Yes!
Because she's an old friend of Sanae.
I guess it makes me jealous, you know?
I had some friends when I was small,
but I don't see them anymore.
Well, I guess it might make a person jealous.
It's unusual to stay friends for so long.
That's true, isn't it?
That's why I envy Sanae and Shiina
for staying friends for so long.
And so...
I get to hang out with her and talk now too!
Talk about what?
Oh! That's a...
se-c-r-et!
It's a secret between girls.
Is it just me, or does that sound kinda nasty?
What? That’s not it at all!
Aren't you being nasty, Senpai, for thinking that?
Well...
Ah, I thought so. You're a beast.
Hey, hey! I'm not a beast. Not at all.
Just a joke! A joke!
Anyways, Senpai, see you tomorrow!
What do you mean by that?
Kotaro doesn't have enough experience,
so I thought I'd take him out for some.
I never said that.
You're just jumping to conclusions, Takeaki.
But you shouldn't say things like that either!
You'll embarrass yourself in front of Misawa-san!
You're not listening.
I don't need to worry about that anymore.
How dare you! Why didn't you tell me?
Anyway, I'm uncomfortable that you're taking
him to such a seedy place for "experience".
You're both still in high school, you know?
You bet we are.
You don't need to be so rude about it.
Please, Ren'ichi-kun, try to talk him out of it.
Takeaki-san, Mizuho-san says
she hates that sort of thing.
You probably should stop.
What the hell, man!
You're making me look like the bad guy!
I don't know about that.
If Mizuho-san weren't here, you would've
jumped at the opportunity to come with us!
I'm right, aren't I?
Judging by your past behavior...
But that's not what I...
You really think I'd "jump at the
opportunity" to go there?
Enough!
Cut it out!
Stop even considering whether you're going there!
You can say that all you want,
but it's our own choice.
And we have our reasons.
Anyways, just drop it for today.
I don't really like this, but whatever.
Don't worry. I won't go there.
I'll be good.
But, if I could, I'd want to be even
better friends with you, Senpai.
And that... I guess is just me being selfish.
By the way, Nanase, did Sanae tell you anything?
Sanae-senpai, you mean?
Not really. She hasn't told me anything.
Is it sort of a secret?
No, not really.
Nanase, listen, what kinds of things do
you usually talk about with Sanae?
Good question. Usually we talk about cooking.
She knows a lot about it.
I see.
Yes.
I don't really understand tennis.
And we talk about our problems a lot too.
Problems? You mean like studying and college?
Or do you...
We do talk about that,
but lately it's been about you and me.
However, she's been acting weird a lot lately.
Sanae?
That's right.
I wonder if she's just not interested in romance.
I mean, whenever I start talking about it.
she suddenly seems disinterested.
Oh, right.
Or rather than not being interested in romance...
she's not interested in you.
That's how it seems.
Not interested in me?
Senpai.
Did you say something to her
recently that might've upset her?
Huh?
Ah-ha! You just thought of
something, didn't you!?
Not really. Nothing comes to mind.
Something still doesn't make sense.
Ah-ha! Could it be...
that Sanae-senpai is in love with you?
That can't be true, can it?
Because she's known that I loved you
even before she even joined the club!
I still haven't told her anything.
But I think you should tell her soon.
Yes. I agree,
so I promised that I'd meet up with her tomorrow.
Is there time for us to go on a date?
I'm going to talk to Nanase-chan in the morning.
Do I really look that depressed?
Yeah. Like something's troubling you,
or like you're about to cry.
I talked to her about the pool,
and then I wanted to tell her the rest of it.
That I wanted to date you.
But... before I was able to say
that, she told me something.
What did she say?
She said...
She asked me what I intended to
do by going on a date with you.
"You don't really want to date him, do you?”
I see.
So you couldn't tell her.
Yeah.
In the end, we left things that way.
Ren'ichi-kun...
Nanase-chan is very important to me,
as important to me as you are.
You're always thinking about her, aren't you?
And I wanted to root for her romance with you.
Even now?
Yeah, but...
But?
Ren'ichi-kun, don't you want
to date Nanase-chan?
I want... to date you, Sanae.
I’m serious.
Sanae!
Let's go some vhere where we can be alone.
I love you, Sanae.
I love you too.
I love you so much!
Misawa-san...
Huh? When did I drift off? Sorry.
Can we go home now, Sis?
Would you like seconds?
Did I disturb you?
Misawa-san, thanks.
Are things going well with Kotaro?
Guess so.
I guess it's kinda embarrassing
to be facing you like this.
Oh?
But yesterday we faced each other
even more closely, didn't we?
B-But...
We don't need to be ashamed.
We did it because we love each other.
I know that.
I thought I knew that, but...
But...
Are you having fun walking with me like this?
Yeah. As long as you're with someone
you love, everything you do is fun.
You're having fun too, right?
Yes.
I love just being with you, Ren'ichi-kun.
I thought so. I believe in myself.
What’s wrong all of a sudden?
My first love will be mine!
So... I guess you already know about it...
but right now, I’m dating Sanae.
Still, ever since I first saw you,
I felt we were fated to be together.
Fated, huh?
Yes. Fate brought us together.
When we met, I felt a lightning bolt!
Senpai, have you heard of stories where
first love never comes to fruit?
Yeah, I've heard of them.
Senpai, how do you feel about them?
I'm not sure.
I don't believe in them.
Even if it's fate?
If it's fate that will keep us apart,
I don't want to believe in it!
I see.
I still can't... give up on you, Senpai!
I'm only saying this for your sake, Ren'ichi-kun.
Were you being serious when you said that?
I don't really get it, but consider how I feel.
How you feel?
It's just too much.
S-So... does that mean you're
considering how I feel?
Do you understand how I'd feel
if you dated another girl?
Because you love me?
Why?
Sanae, you just wanted to test me, right?
That's why you said something
that would repel me.
That’s right, isn't it?
Sorry.
Sorry for testing you.
I'm not mad at you.
Really?
I don't like being tested, but I understand
why you felt like you had to do it.
How much time has passed since we came here?
I don't know.
What were we talking about?
I don't know that either.
You don't know anything, do you?
Neither do you, Ren'ichi-kun.
Yeah. I wonder why.
Probably because it was something pointless.
Sanae...
What?
Will you come with me to my room?
Your room?
Yeah.
I want to make love to you.
Okay?
Yeah.
Ren'ichi-kun?
I was scared.
Because it’s your first time?
No, not that.
Listen, Ren'ichi-kun.
Ever since you kissed me,
I've been very happy.
And I wonder if it's okay for me to be this happy.
So... so I was worried that maybe
this happiness would fall apart.
That I'd wake up from the dream.
That's why you were scared?
Are you still scared?
No. I'm okay now.
Just a little nervous, though.
Sanae...
So this... isn't a dream, right?
If it were a dream, I don't think
we could be like this.
So soft.
Just as I thought you'd be.
I'm... so happy I can be with you like this.
Did you imagine it before?
Many times. Many times.
Right now, how are you feeling?
Happy.
Very happy.
Is that so.
That's good.
D-Don't!
Don't tell me that. I won't stop anyway.
Sanae, you're very pretty down here.
It’s wet and sparkling.
Ren'ichi-kun! Ren'ichi-kun...
Sanae...
Ren'ichi-kun...
Come to me.
Sanae, does it hurt?
I'm fine.
Never mind that. I can feel you.
It makes me happy.
I’ll try moving a little.
Sanae, I feel wonderful.
How about you?
Me too.
It's feeling... better... I think.
I think I'm cumming... Sanae!
That's okay.
Let's cum...
together.
This time, I'll make you feel good too.
Make me feel good? Sanae...
You don't need to push yourself.
I'm not pushing myself.
I want to do it.
Cut it out.
Right here? You like that?
Sanae... just a few minutes ago, you...
Because I love you.
Because I love you a lot.
Ren'ichi-kun, don't move, okay?
Leave everything to me.
Ren'ichi-kun!
I think... I'm gonna cum right away.
Ren'ichi-kun, you're getting hotter inside of me.
I can feel it.
I can cum, right?
No, not yet!
I want more! I want you to feel more!
Sanae!
But if you move that much, I'll...
Yes. It feels so great.
Sanae, it's no good. Hurry!
Wait. I...
Right now, I feel wonderful.
I want to stay like this forever.
So...
Okay, I get it. I’ll hold back until you say so.
Ren'ichi-kun!
I love you. I love you.
I love you so much!
It feels like it's been a very long time.
You're right.
A lot happened between us.
Up until now, it was just an etude.
An etude, a practice song.
What we were doing up until
now was an etude of love.
An etude of love?
Yes, but our practice ends today.
Senpai!
Huh? Nanase, you look hyper today.
Yes!
I'm sad that the club is ending, but I thought
I'd party hard today to celebrate!
I see.
I'm going ahead of you, okay?
I'm meeting up with Karumi at the train station!
Afterschool Love Club
Yay!
Hey, guys!
Congratulations!
Now! It's our turn!
We practiced really hard.
Everyone listen!
ii no choppiri kowai keredo
It's okay I'm a little bit scared,
tsuyoku daite ne
so please hold me tight.
moshi
And if...
koi no mirai mietara,
we can see love in our future,
motto egao ni narou
let's smile more.
I have so many things to thank you for.
You are my angel
You are my angel.
nani kyua tsuketa totan
The instant it seems I've found a cure,
mune ga zawameku
my heart flutters with anxiety.
kyoukasho ja wakaranai
It seems that there is a world
sekai ga aru no
that cannot be explained in textbooks.
otona ni naritakunai
I don't want to grow up,
demo kodomo janai
but I'm not a child either.
yume miru onna no ko wa
Girls with dreams in their hearts
abunai angel
are dangerous angels.
dame yo hakkiri taido kimete
No, you don't Show me strongly how you feel.
demo yasashiku ne
But still be gentle, okay?
moshi
And if
honki de koi shitai nara
You really are serious about love,
motto hadaka ni narou
then let's be naked more.
You are my angel
You are my angel.
mamoritai no
I want to cherish.
pyua na kimochi
these pure feelings.
kirei na me de
Through your pretty eyes,
yume o misete
please show me your dreams.
hakkiri taido kimete
Show me strongly how you feel.
demo yasashiku ne
but still be gently, okay?
moshi
And if
honki de koi shitai nara
you really are serious about love,
motto hadaka ni narou
then let's be naked more.
choppiri kowai keredo
I'm a little bit scared,
tsuyoku daite ne
so please hold me tight.
moshi
And if
koi no mirai mietara
we can see love in our future,
motto egao ni narou
Then let's smile more.
You are my angel
You are my angel.