Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: MrMew |TS & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Ayanami-
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Afterschool Love Club
Etude of Love
Episode I: Love Needs no Motive...
Good afternoon! Welcome to Starry Sky!
Oh, Takeaki-kun.
You were going to start coming today?
Yeah, yeah, that's right!
And Misawa-san, there's
something I want to ask you...
Senpai! Over here!
Ren'ichi-senpai!
What should I do about it?
I'm a little too busy, you know.
It'll be fine.
I got your boss's permission.
Oh, Take-chan.
Oh, hi.
So anyway, that's the scoop.
Misawa, I hope you'll help me out!
I'll think about it.
Good afternoon!
Even so, I envy you, Sanae-senpai.
I haven't even had a chance to
talk to Ren'ichi-senpai yet.
But you know, Nanase-chan, if you hadn't
talked me into coming with you,
I don't think I'd be able to have a relaxed
conversation like this right now.
Well then, folks! Should we begin?
Kazumi, Kotaro and the others are over there.
So you’re saying that all the players are here?
For now at least. But we're still not there yet.
This is the Love Notebook I was telling you about.
So, Mr. Manager, I’ll leave the next
four weeks in your hands.
"Manager"?
It's not a big deal, really.
The club notes. Then albums for the list of rules.
List of rules?
Yeah. Like when a boy approaches two girls.
Make sure you investigate first,
so no one gets offended.
I’m counting on you!
I'm busy with my other club,
and I have business with Kazumi and Kotaro.
When you say "Manager", does that mean I can't
have my photo taken with Ren'ichi-senpai?
No, that's not true at all.
If you want, Nanase-chan
you can be with Ren'ichi.
If ya don’t do that, that means during the next
four weeks, this guy'll be the only lonely one.
Then you don't need to worry!
Leave everything to me.
Kazumi-senpai and Takeaki-senpai...
So, Ren'ichi-senpai,
how do you fit into this?
Kazumi and Takeaki are childhood friends.
I've known them since junior high.
Kotaro too.
I guess we were a group of friends.
Kotaro-senpai... is he that guy over there?
Yup.
The girl with him is Hinako-san.
She's Kotaro's big sister, and
she's a grade ahead of us.
She's mature for her age, and she always seems
to be getting Kotaro out of trouble.
It's just that lately, Kotaro's been
getting into more trouble.
Oh? Hey, Senpai!
Kazumi-senpai and Takeaki-senpai...
are they datin?
I don't think so.
Then, what about you and Kazumi-senpai?
Just friends, I guess.
Oh, really? Thank goodness!
Why?
Because... Because... if that's not the case, then...
Never mind.
Well then, Senpai!
What is your dream type of girl?
I haven't really thought about that much.
Like, for example, if you ask
me or my dream type...
It's Sanae-senpai!
Sanae?
Yes!
Why?
I mean, she's good at cooking.
And even though I'm a girl, I'm still
charmed by her girlishness.
Though I guess it’s kind of rude of
me to say this because I'm a girl.
But anyway, I really think
she's a wonderful person.
I guess you could say I envy her,
But I know I'd be a poor imitation
if I tried to be like her.
I see.
This is making me kinda depressed.
For real. Why do we have to get
photographed in our swimsuits?
Whaddaya say, Ren'ichi?
More nice girls joined up, right?
I guess you could call this one of my talents.
Feels like I’m in a daytime variety show.
So how's the thing with Kotaro going?
Tomorrow, first thing.
His two-shot photo with Misawa-san, right?
Better prepare for it.
I am Misawa-san's underclassman's...
underclassman.
Oh, I get it!
I really am grateful you joined the Love Club!
As the president, I'm very pleased.
Oh my.
I don't recall you thanking me
when I joined the club.
Oh, didn't I?
You're not wearing a uniform.
Are we supposed to change
before we come here?
I go to a school that doesn't require uniforms.
I've always hated uniforms anyway.
Ayumu-sensei needs to be able
to express her individuality.
You've started a band too, right?
Not yet! We don't have enough members.
That's right.
Are there any good people in this club?
Hey, hey! What about me?
Sorry.
I've decided all the band members should be girls.
What a shame.
So which instrument do you play in the band?
Keyboards!
I would've liked to be the vocalist, though.
I'm really good at singing.
Oh, really? That's awesome!
She's kidding. Even she knows
she's totally tone-deaf.
Kazumi, I can see right down your throat.
Why you!
So Misawa is on board.
That means we can do a two-shot photo together.
Anyways Ren'ichi, be sure
to walk Hinako-san home.
Why me again?
We're counting on you.
Senpai! Are we going home late today?
Not today.
By the way, what do you think of this uniform?
What do you mean?
What I mean is,
it brings out my chest really well, right?
Y-Yes, it does.
Right?
Hey, boys really like this sort of thing, don't they?
Um...
What? Kotaro-kun, are you shy on this subject?
No, it's just that... not here.
I don't want to discuss it here.
So you are being shy.
Kotaro-kun, you're really cute sometimes.
D-Don't make fun of me!
I'm not making fun of you.
I'm complimenting you.
You're unspoiled and cute.
Hey, listen, Ren'ichi-kun, I think
that it would be a lot of fun
if everyone in the Love Club went cycling.
Hey, Ren'ichi-kun, don't you agree?
Oh, Hinako-san, you must be thirsty.
I'm gonna go buy some juice or something.
Thanks!
Oh, welcome.
Ren’ichi-kun, hello.
Sanae, I thought today wasn't...
May I sit down?
Yeah, of course you can.
Are you waiting for someone?
No. I've got tennis practice after this.
I see.
Yeah. I was going to skip the club today,
but I saw you in here, so I stopped by.
Oh...
That girl who joined the club the other
day, Shiina, is your best friend, right?
That's right! We're old friends.
I hear she does gymnastics.
Yup.
And you play tennis.
That's right. When Shiina joined a sports
club, I decided to join one as well.
It's because Nanase-chan isn't here, right?
I mean, usually you have a
difficult time talking to me.
Well, that's probably true, but...
Nanase isn't coming today.
Yeah, I heard.
She's going out with her family, isn't she?
Yeah.
And that's why you're here by yourself in the club.
That's not true!
I'm sorry.
No, you don't have to apologize.
Sanai, don't you feel bored not having
a date or anything to do on a Sunday?
I guess so. Ren'ichi-kun, wanna
go play tennis with me?
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Actually, ever since I saw you on Monday,
I've wanted to be in a picture with you.
Really?
Of course. But this last week has been
pretty hectic, so I couldn't ask you.
And you're the manager too.
We have a lot more members too.
That's true.
Ren'ichi-kun, Takeaki and Kazumi-chan
invited you to join the club, right?
Yup. They forced me to.
Forced?
That's right.
How can I explain it?
I’m living alone.
I know.
And so, it's a pain for me to make
my own meals and stuff.
I think I get it.
And so I got a free coupon to eat at Starry Sky.
What do you mean?
Oh, that's right, Sanae, you didn't know.
The owner of Starry Sky is Takeaki's grandfather.
Oh, I had no idea!
So that's why the Love Club meets there.
Hey, Ren'ichi-kun.
What?
I've been meaning to talk to you for a while,
so I'm glad I joined the Love Club.
Seems like it's what we both wanted.
You're right. I'd better thank Nanase-chan
for inviting me to join the club.
I worked all day yesterday. It really wiped me out.
Your parents really make you work
hard on Sundays, don't they?
No helping it.
That's the way it's always been.
In any case, I've been pretty lonely here.
Lonely?
Yup. After all, I wasn't able to see you.
Hey, how are you feeling, Kotaro-kun?
How am I...
Jeez, don't beat around the bush.
Kotaro-kun, you missed me, didn't you?
Yes.
I thought so.
Yup.
Well then, I get off work soon.
Kotaro-kun.
Is this where Takeaki always
locks up the club notes?
Yeah. I guess so.
How gross.
Kazumi, you're in the way.
W-Wait a minute!
Don't worry. I'll change right away.
But the sign says "No Trespassing"!
Never mind that.
But we shouldn't be doing this!
What is it, Kotaru-kun?
Are you nervous about this?
O-Of course I'm...
Despite that, you're really excited.
Amazing. Your heart is racing, Kotaru-kun.
Here, compare it to mine.
I can't feel it.
Then try touching me harder.
Well?
I can't feel it, but...
But?
Um, it's soft.
Pervert! I was only asking
you to feel my heartbeat.
U-Um... I'm sorry!
Hey, how were my boobs? How did they feel?
Misawa-san!
I mean, Kotaro-kun, you're just so cute.
That was really embarrassing.
You didn't think things would
progress so quickly?
Speaking of that, Ren'ichi, things are
going well with Nanase-chan, right?
Wait just a minute!
Nanase and I aren't like that!
You don't need to get all defensive and deny it.
No one will be jealous.
Listen, you!
And what about you?
Huh? Me?
I'm not involved, I guess.
But you're a member of the Love Club.
But listen. Actually, I was asked
to be the lead vocalist in a band.
You mean Ayumu's band?
So you know about it.
Oh, it's Takeaki.
What's up?
Weren't you walking home with Ayumu?
She says she likes someone else.
Someone in the Love Club?
It's you, Ren'ichi.
Me?
Yeah.
Ren'ichi? Did you take a two-shot with Ayumu?
No, I didn't.
Something's fishy.
I haven't got a clue.
That's not what I meant.
Either way, I don't wanna see your face today!
Hey, hey, Takeaki!
Senpai, what kinds of things do you like?
That was just a convenient lie, wasn't it?
How can you say that?
It's none of your business, Kazumi!
It is my business!
Ren’ichi and Takeaki are my friends!
I think you're being pushy.
I think you're being dishonest!
Hey, Ren'ichi!
Kazumi, why are you so pissed off about this?
You're acting weird.
Now I get it, Kazumi.
You just don't want me to steal
Ren'ichi-kun away from you.
Thats why you're so pissed off.
D-Don't be preposterous!
You wanna fight?
Aren't you the one who wants to fight?
You've been saying horrible things to me all day!
Oh, shut up, shut up!
What the hell, you tone-deaf bitch!
You're just in a crappy band anyway.
Hey! Now that's going too far.
You're horrible. You're horrible, Kazumi.
How could you say something so cruel?!
Hey! Kazumi!
Kazumi! You wait here.
I'm okay now.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Kazumi really went too far.
But it was my fault.
I’m sure that when she called you tone-deaf,
she was just reaching for an insult.
I think Kazumi should apologize to you.
I'm happy you think that way, but...
If you make her do that, she'll just hate me more.
I don't care about that.
You don't?
Kazumi was in the wrong.
I'll make her apologize.
But...
Just because she's my friend doesn't mean
I'm gonna let her get away with anything.
Ren'ichi-kun...
Besides, if I can't speak frankly to her about
this, I'm not much of a friend, am I?
Hey, Ren'ichi-kun...
I wonder if Kazumi and I can stay friends.
Ren'ichi-kun?
What is it, Ren'ichi?
You got a problem?
Wasn't your complaint supposed to be
only about the purpose of the club?
Yeah, that's true.
Still, I can't forgive her for rejecting Takeaki.
Yeah, but that was just a little fight.
Even so, it pisses me off!
Ayumu looked like she was going to cry.
Ren'ichi, you're taking her side?
Just let her cry!
That bitch!
I'm not taking sides.
Then what are you trying to say to me?
I think you're just saying
things to sabotage Ayumu.
And what if I am?
Kazumi, I was being sarcastic.
But she's talking trash about me too.
As for that, I can see why a person would do
that if they have a problem with someone.
But what you're talking about
is just simple animosity.
Isn't that all?
You have no logical reason for it.
Takeaki and her "crappy band."
Why are those two things related?
You're right, but...
Can't you be a little optimistic for a change?
I know you're mad about Takeaki,
but aren't you doing the same
thing back to Ayumu?
You're insulting her, and she can’t push back.
Isn't that right, Kazumi?
Well, I...
Ren'ichi-kun?
Ren'ichi-kun!
Sanae!
You're still here?
I haven't talked to you at all since Sunday.
You were really busy this week, weren't you?
Sanae.
This Sunday, let's go on a date.
Ren'ichi-kun, let's take a break, okay?
We really swam a lot.
After a while, I felt like the waves
were pulling my body.
Swimming uses every muscle in the body.
You're right. Sure feels like it.
Shiina comes to this sports club a lot.
Shiina? You mean your old friend?
Yeah.
Hey, Sanae.
What, Ren'ichi?
That swimsuit looks good on you.
Really?
Yes, it really does.
You've got good fashion sense.
Thanks.
Listen, this is the first time I've worn it.
So I guess that means you're wearing it for me.
I'm flattered.
Go ahead and be egocentric like that!
Oh, did I make you mad?
Yeah, but I guess it's okay.
Meeting you like this...
What do you mean?
I mean, I guess it's a good thing we're
going on a date on Sunday.
Won't you ask Nanase-chan out?
That doesn't have anything to do with you.
You don't need to think about it.
But come tomorrow, you'll
see Nanase-chan again.
Stop that!
Today is our date, just the two of us.
Don't talk about other girls.
Sorry.
Kotaro-kun, you know some pretty nice places.
What a relief.
Misawa-san, I always see you
eating delicious-looking food.
I was worried you wouldn't like this place.
I really had lots of fun today.
Thanks, Kotaro-kun.
Y-You're welcome.
So... now it's my turn to entertain you.
Hotel.
We're going, right?
Hey, did that feel good?
Y-Yes! Very much so!
Really?
Then let's try licking this area next.
B-But if you lick that...
What?
I'll...
It's okay.
Yeah.
You're just nervous.
I hear your heart thumping.
Kotaro-kun... lick me too.
O-Okay!
Yes, yes.
Like you're searching down there.
You're really good.
Yes. Put your tongue in.
Wow. Somethings flowing out.
That's because you're good at it.
It's because... it's you, Misawa-san.
You say such flattering things.
Then let me make you feel even better.
Not all the way down!
Well?
N-No!
It feels too good!
You feel it here too?
Don't do that, Misawa-san!
It's boring in this position.
I can't see your expression.
Kotaro-kun.
It's about time, right?
Kotaro-kun, I guess you like it. How cute.
Th-That's because... you're so warm.
Kotaro-kun, move more.
Move harder!
Feel my boobs too.
Match up with my rhythm.
Yes. Very nice. Very nice.
Misawa-san! I'm gonna cum!
No, not yet.
It’s too soon for that.
But I can't... control it.
Then lets take a little break.
Just a bit longer. Let me have more fun.
This much should be okay, right?
I-I feel... really good, but...
kind of anxious.
You wanna cum?
In that case, I guess you can start moving.
Yes!
It's about time... for me too.
M-Misawa-san, can I cum like this?
Yes. Yes, you can.
What's wrong, Kotaro-kun?
Are you tired?
No, I just...
I just wondered if it's okay
that things were so easy.
Easy?
I mean, we had sex... so suddenly.
You didn't like it?
That's not true at all!
Misawa-san, it was amazing.
Then that’s fine.
Don't think about it too hard.
Love doesn't have to be that complicated.
If both people have fun, that's all that matters.
Senpai!
Hi.
Ren'ichi-kun, I have a favor to ask.
What?
Will you keep the fact that we went to the pool
yesterday a secret from Nanase-chan?
Will you, please?
Sanae...
ii no choppiri kowai keredo
It's okay I'm a little bit scared,
tsuyoku daite ne
so please hold me tight.
moshi
And if...
koi no mirai mietara
we can see love in our future,
motto egao ni narou
let's smile more.
You are my angel
You are my angel!
nani kyua tsuketa totan
The instant it seems I've found a cure,
mune ga zawameku
my heart flutters with anxiety.
kyoukasho ja wakaranai
It seems that there is a world
sekai ga aru no
that cannot be explained in textbooks.
otona ni naritakunai
I don't want to grow up,
demo kodomo janai
but I'm not a child either.
yume miru onna no ko wa
Girls with dreams in their hearts
abunai angel
are dangerous angels.
dame yo hakkiri taido kimete
No, you don't Show me strongly how you feel.
demo yasashiku ne
But still be gentle, okay?
moshi
And if
honki de koi shitai nara
You really are serious about love,
motto hadaka ni narou
then let's be naked more.
You are my angel
You are my angel.
mamoritai no
I want to cherish.
pyua na kimochi
these pure feelings.
kirei na me de
Through your pretty eyes,
yume o misete
please show me your dreams.
And now we have a marvelous
announcement from Starry Sky.
Houkago Ren'ai Club's second episode,
"...Because Love Has No Logic,"
is currently in production for a summer release,
hakkiri taido kimete
Show me strongly how you feel.
Please look forward to seeing vhere Ren'ichi
-kun's and the others' romances will go.
demo yasashiku ne
but still be gently, okay?
And now, let's continue with Ayumu's
and Kazumi's ending them song.
moshi
And if
honki de koi shitai nara
you really are serious about love,
motto hadaka ni narou
then let's be naked more.
choppiri kowai keredo
I'm a little bit scared,
tsuyoku daite ne
so please hold me tight.
moshi
And if
koi no mirai mietara
we can see love in our future,
motto egao ni narou
Then let's smile more.
You are my angel
You are my angel.