Hey Yuu, you did not take your medication.
That's not good.
You need to follow what the doctor tells you.
You said you would go buy it.
You said that if I properly took my shots and medicine,
you'd buy me those cream puffs.
I have them right here.
Let's eat them together with your brother.
Kaname, come over here.
That's not it!
This is not what I wanted!
The one you bought before looked a lot yummier!
I don't want this anymore...
I hate you! Go away!
Ma'am, here are the procedures for the next medication.
Yes, okay.
A terrible illness.
She was never allowed outside and had to
always take medicine and get injections.
No one tried to understand her.
No one was on her side.
But I'll stay with her.
Onii-chan.
I bought them for you.
It's only one though, since my allowance isn't that big.
It's this one, right?
Thank you.
Yay!
I'm still a kid right now, so I may not be able to do much.
But I'm going to be a knight when I grow up.
I'll get stronger, become knighted,
and I'll continue to protect you.
Okay.
Nii-san.
Nii-san, wake up already Nii-san.
Y-Yuu?
Good morning, Nii-san.
As long as I'm here, I'm not going to let you be late.
Y-Yeah.
I was almost late again and you just moved in.
Thanks for earlier, Yuu.
No, I'm just happy to be useful to you as your sister.
But if you're really that grateful...
Give me a reward then.
Wha-What kind?
The usual kind.
I'm happy.
Nii-san, I want things to stay like this forever.
I won't lose, never!
An opening!
Point!
Duel over!
Amazing! Yuu won against Shia!
Everyone, everthing okay with your training?
Yuu
Akari
Mana
Shia
Kaname
Oh, I see you're conducting a mock tournament.
a date with Kaname
Yes, and it was Fujimori who got to the finals.
So it was Yuu, eh?
Yes, it seems that she is a lot more into training than usual.
And what's the meaning of that "date with Kaname" over there?
Oh, I'm the one who thought of that.
I was thinking that the winner gets to have a date with Kaname.
In the red corner,
Fujimori Kaname.
In the white corner,
Fujimori Yuu.
Ready...
Set...
Fight!
Yuu's already pushing herself just to keep up.
I guess that has to do with the huge
difference between their strength.
Yuu had always been using hit and dodge tactics before,
but what is this?
Her reflexes are far different from when we fought.
The fight is over.
I lost.
Point! Winner, Fujimori Yuu.
Nii-san!
Kaname, you had a tough oppenent.
You finally got me there.
That's because I'm the one closest to you.
I'm the one who knows you the best.
Guess I'll just have to try harder next time.
Besides, I really...
I really wanted to have that date with you.
Alright, let's do it.
There sure are a lot of couples here.
I'm sure they also see us as a couple.
Well Yuu's cute and a nice girl.
Anyone would love to have her as a girlfriend.
I love you.
I love you!
I can't hold myself back anymore.
Maria...
Onii-san.
I love you.
Yuu...
Maria, we've been living very closely together
ever since we lost our parents.
Which is why you are mistaken.
The world is big and wide.
I'm sure you'll find the one who's really dear to you.
Maria, I'd like to introduce you to someone.
Someone who is dear to me.
We're getting married soon.
And I would like you to be happy for me as well.
Pleased to meet you Maria-san.
Yuu? Yuu?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Please don't mind me.
They said it was a remarkable achievement!
Huh, where's Yuu?
Oh, she seems to be not feeling well.
She has been in her room ever since she came home.
Nii-san...
No...
You can't be with someone else...
I just don't want to.
I don't want you to choose anyone but me.
A letter?
Nii-san, I'm sorry for writing to you so suddenly.
We usually don't mind imposing on each other,
but this time I did not have the courage to say it,
and simply wrote this letter.
I have something important to speak with you about.
Nii-san, I will be waiting on top of the school building after school.
I can no longer stop, nor can I go back.
Yuu.
Yuu!
It's raining, what are you doing?
You'll catch a cold again!
Yuu...
I have been holding it in.
I thought that as long as you're happy...
But I can't hold it any longer!
I just can't bear the thought of you being with another woman!
I love you already!
Not as a sibling, but as a sweetheart!
Yuu, do you remember?
That I said I'd be a knight and protect you!
It hasn't changed a bit.
No, my desire has grown even stronger.
And after hearing your feelings, I finally understand.
That I'm also lost without you.
I love you.
Yuu...
Nii-san.
Nii-san, I have a request.
Please share with me the experience that I'll never forget.
Yuu...
Nii-san, your chest feels warm.
Nii-san, please be gentle with me.
I know.
Sorry, I did not need to say that, did I?
Because you are always so nice to me.
If we continue, our clothes might get messy, so...
Okay.
This is embarrassing.
I don't have breasts like Kaori...
You shouldn't think about somebody else now.
I'm sorry.
For me, you're my number one.
I'm now all over your petite breasts.
No, if you play with both of my breasts like that...
I won't be able to hold on.
Yuu, can you raise your hips?
Yes.
You're wet already.
I'm sorry, I just felt good when you were fondling me.
And I just got like this.
Yuu, spread your legs.
Yes...
This is embarrassing.
Your insides are squeezing me very hard.
Nii-san, no...
I might get even wetter.
Sorry, I'm not going let you be the
only one who feels embarrassed.
Nii-san...
I've already become like this.
Wow.
It became like this because of me?
Yeah. Can you take them off for me?
Okay.
Nii-san?!
When I tried to finger you, I just realized,
that I'm about to enter this hole.
Nii-san, but can I really take this big thing in?
I'm not really sure now.
It's okay.
Just leave it to me.
Nii-san, I'm about to die from embarrassment.
You don't need to be, it looks very beautiful, you know.
It feels a little strange.
It feels hot down here.
No, don't!
Just thinking that you're the one licking down there, I'm already...!
No need to hold back.
Yuu!
Oh no, his tongue feels so good that my mind's going blank.
I love you...
I love you very much.
You sure squirted a lot.
Now, we're going ahead to the next step.
Nii-san...
I'm sorry Yuu, but can you help me?
It's in here.
This is where you put it in.
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
Are you alright, Nii-san?
I'm just barely in but it feels great already.
That's good.
Nii-san, don't worry about me and just keep moving.
Nii-san!
Yuu!
I'm already cumming right after I put it in!
Hot... Something hot is entering inside me!
Huh?
Nii-san, you're still stiff.
I'm sorry, you are so erotic and cute
that I just can't stop after cumming once.
It really feels fulfilling to do it with someone you truly love.
Sex feels really great, doesn't it?
My mind and my body, are being filled by him.
My feelings of affection are just overflowing.
I love him.
I love you, Nii-san!
You're cute, Yuu.
I love you too.
My breasts, you're sucking on my breasts again.
It's okay.
Just let it all out.
Yuu!
Yes... Yes...
Nii-san, I'll give you everything.
Everything.
Please take all of it.
But I don't want to cum alone.
I want you to join me too.
Please squirt it all out inside me!
I understand, Yuu!
Nii-san!
This is amazing.
I feel like I'm totally connected with you.
Wow.
Oh wow!
Huh? Yuu, are you there?
That's strange.
I just heard someone in here.
Must be your imagination.
She said she'd be out with her brother.
You're right.
Anyway, maybe Yuu likes Fujimori after all.
It's probably not just familial love.
You think so too?
But they're siblings, wouldn't she hit a wall sooner or later?
Well, that goes for both of them.
No matter how cute Yuu is, and no matter
how much she really loves her brother,
it is unfortunate that they just can't stay together.
A terrible whim of fate you might say.
If they can't be together,
Your insides...
we should at least be at Yuu's side.
You're right.
It's okay, Nii-san.
My insides are made for you to cum inside.
Well, see you tomorrow, Mana.
Okay Shia, see you tomorrow.
It feels good, it feels really good Nii-san.
It feels so good that I...
Nii-san, Nii-san, Nii-san!
Yuu, Yuu, Yuu!
Let it all out!
Give me your hot thing!
Yuu, are you alright?
Hang in there, Yuu!
Nii-san, you're deep inside me.
And lots of your hot thing is flowing inside me.
It feels hot, it's flowing inside me.
I'm happy.
Oh no! I wanted to take it all.
I don't want to leave a single drop, but it's overflowing...
Being held by Nii-san like this...
I'm very happy.
My heart feels like it's melting.
I want to be by your side and protect you.
Winner, Fujimori Yuu!
Is it...
Is it okay to stay like this?
I...
You have already thoroughly thought this out, right?
Yes.
I will not abandon my feelings for her,
or my dream to become a knight.
Then, I'm going to have to give you a few conditions.
There will be a special training curriculum for modern knights.
I want you to take it, and complete all of the tasks that they give.
It might take you around a year or so to complete the curriculum.
If you really want to be happy together,
then you won't let this become an issue.
Become a fine knight.
Yes.
As for you my little lady, you must continue
your activities as a squire without him.
And carry your feelings for him until the very end.
Yes.
Well, I had originally intended for Kaori to take it,
but now I need to make preparations to get you into it.
You'll most likely leave the day after tomorrow.
Get plenty of rest and prepare yourselves for tomorrow.
Understood!
We'll be separated from each other for a while.
I'm sorry Yuu,
you'll be lonely for a while.
I'm okay.
No matter how far away you are, I'll always feel connected to you.
Nii-san.
Yuu.
Nii-san, that part is okay, but...
Please touch me here.
Wait, please wait Nii-san.
Yuu, we're doing it here?
It's okay, Nii-san, this place is about to
close so nobody is coming today.
I love you, Nii-san.
Please do it with me a lot today.
I understand, Yuu.
But first I want to watch you play with yourself.
Li-Like this?
A bit more intense.
Nii-san.
You're cute, Yuu.
It looks like they're stiff already.
Oh no, Nii-san.
Your breasts are very cute.
Oh no, Nii-san...
My beloved Nii-san is...
If you play with my nipples like that...
Yuu!
I'm happy.
Nii-san, is completely filling my insides again.
I can't believe it, I can see everything.
I wonder how that big thing could ever fit inside me.
I know what he'll do next.
He's about to let loose, hold my legs up, and thrust rapidly.
Yuu, sorry, I can't control my hips anymore.
Nii-san!
It's getting bigger inside.
He's about to cum.
Nii-san.
The way he rubs it hard inside me,
is a sign that he's about to cum.
The only thing on my mind as he does this, is him.
I can't think of anything else.
I'm sure that my womb is longing to have his cum.
Yuu, I'm cumming...
Yuu!
Me too,
I want to cum with him too!
Nii-san, please cum deep inside me.
Please cum with me.
It's overflowing.
It looks like it feels very good for him.
I'm happy.
You came a lot, Nii-san.
Nii-san that's...
Are we going to do it there?
No, it's embarrassing there.
Can you give me all of you?
Nii-san...
Yes.
I'm going to give everything to you.
It feels amazing to be penetrated in my ass.
No, don't look inside.
Please don't expose my insides.
His thick thing is entering me from behind.
It's stirring everything inside.
I'm sorry, I can't hold myself back any longer.
Nii-san, I, I...
I'm about to cum while you're making love to me from behind.
I'm sorry, Nii-san.
Sorry, I'm your sister and yet I'm this horny!
It's hot, it feels hot!
Your hot cum is seeping deep inside me.
My insides are being filled by Nii-san's hot thing.
Nii-san, the tip is opening and closing.
Tha-That's...
You already came a lot and that still wasn't enough, right?
What a cute dick.
I'm going to let you cum again in my mouth, okay?
If my...
If my beloved Yuu is going to do that...
I won't be able to hold it in!
Yuu!
Nii-san, let's continue this when we get home, okay?
I wonder what Kaname is doing?
I'm sure she is doing her best.
Because there is someone that is waiting for her.
Nii-san!
Nii-san.
Yuu...
I've missed you.
Nii-san, you truly are the only knight for me!
Congratulations!
Yuu!
Kaname!
She looks so pretty!
I'm really glad, that I was able to live
my entire life with you up to now.
And we're still going to be together from now on.
And we'll be even more happier, Yuu.
Yes.
Congratulations!
Koi Kishi, Purely Kiss.
May you be happy together!