Are you okay?
I'm coming for you now!
I'm going to get you out of here.
Get away!
You'll be in danger too.
No, those knights on TV would never leave anyone to...
You guys held out well.
It's alright now.
It was a knight who saved us.
A modern-day knight.
I've decided.
I'll become a knight.
I promise you.
That I will become a knight,
one that will uphold justice and righteousness
more than any other.
I promise too.
I will become a knight that will protect
everyone more than anyone can.
Let's meet here again someday.
Okay.
Kaname, take the rear!
Okay, I got this Elcia!
Damn...
That was splendid.
Your swordplay is wild as always.
Don't say that.
I'm satisfied as long as I can keep your back safe.
You seem way too relaxed for this.
My bad then.
My heart was about to burst.
Kaname...
A matchmaking session?
Wait, wait, wait!
How did you guys know?
The school principal told us about it earlier.
That old man!
Why worry about it?
It's not like you need to keep it a secret or something.
Nii-san, I didn't know about it until now!
Hey hey what kind of person is she?
You better have an explanation for this!
Hey wait!
You already have me and you're still looking for someone else, Nii-san?
Cia!
Cia?
Elcia-san...
Hey, this is a two-man night patrol.
If you keep that distance, we won't be able to operate properly.
Besides, it's hard to talk when you're that far-
Found two suspicious people.
Hey let's go.
Going in pursuit.
Hey Cia, don't go on your own!
We need to contact Commander Kaori first!
Cia!
What's wrong with you?!
I won't let you get away.
Oh, I see that one cute little knight seems
to have wandered into a thieves den.
Damn.
I'm completely surrounded.
And Kaname, the one who should be guarding my rear, isn't here.
What's wrong?
it'd be boring if you don't resist a bit.
But I guess scared little girls can also be
entertaining in many different ways.
Who the hell are you?
You bastard!
That fierce and wild left handed wield.
Some idiot has wandered in alone again.
These knights sure are fools.
I'm not alone!
Because there's another really strong knight over there!
Amazing my body just suddenly...
It just suddenly became able to move freely.
A knight squad is coming!
Damn it!
Run away!
Cia!
Are you alright?
You didn't have to come.
Stupid.
I was really worried back there.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
I thought I could fight by myself.
But I realized that I can't use my skills when you're not there.
Then let's just continue doing our best together.
But... but...
Free of thoughts, free of emotions!
One mind, no distractions!
Erase mindless thoughts!
Cia!
I knew you'd be here.
Mind as clear as a mirror!
Wait, wait, wait!
Ouch...
That surprised me.
Y-You just appeared so suddenly, so I...
Cia, there's something that I need to tell you.
I on the other hand, haven't got anything to say.
Why don't you go discuss this with your matchmaking partner?
Cia!
I declined the matchmaking session.
And theres only one reason why.
Because I'm already in love with someone.
I won't try to hide it anymore.
The one that I love is you, Cia!
K-Kaname?
Cia, please tell me bluntly.
I want to know your honest feelings.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I wasn't sure when...
No... it was probably ever since we first met.
That I've always been...
Kaname, I love you too.
Cia, I'm sorry that I wasn't able to tell you sooner.
You sure took your time.
But I also did the same.
Kaname, don't.
My mind feels clouded.
Don't be too pushy.
My heart won't be able to catch up.
It's unfair that you always take the initiative.
I also want to...
I want both of us to do it to each other.
Your tongue... I feel like I'm going to melt.
Kaname?
I want to know more about you.
Please don't stare too much.
It's embarrassing.
Wat are you saying? You look beautiful.
Oh no, he's only touching me there,
but I'm already getting this aroused.
Don't grasp it too tightly.
No...
No licking there...
It feels hot.
The longer you keep doing it, the hotter it gets.
I've never felt like this before.
I don't know what to do.
Cia, you don't have to hold back.
E-Even if you say that...
Stop, please...
I'm already going to...!
Did you cum, Cia?
Cum?
I see, so this is how it feels to cum.
It's all because of you.
You kept touching me like that...
If my body gets used to it...
Kaname? Where are you touching me?
No! It's sweaty and dirty, down there!
There's nothing dirty about you?
No, I really can't...
But this part says it feels amazing.
D-Don't... you're making that sound.
I-I'm going to cum again.
Wait, Kaname.
Kaname...
Cia, I'm sorry.
I don't think I can hold it in much longer.
Okay.
I also want to give my everything to you.
Cia...
A little lower...
Kaname...
Are you okay, Cia?
I'm okay.
Besides, it's hard for you not to push further, right?
But...
I said it already.
I'm ready to accept everything from you.
Cia...
Cia, it's all the way in.
I'm really happy.
I was able to give my first time to my beloved.
Cia!
Kaname...
Your insides are soft and tender, it feels great!
You're such a liar.
No need to pretend that it feels me.
I want to do it until the end.
Even if it's painful for you?
You're about to leave your mark in me, right?
I want this moment to be etched forever.
Cia, I love you!
Cia!
I can feel it.
I know exactly where you are inside me.
I know how deep it is within me.
Please, hit my very insides.
The sensation inside me...
You're the only one who will remember it as long as we live.
Cia!
Kaname!
I love you!
Cia!
You just kissed me without warning.
It feels better than earlier.
I can feel something other than pain now.
What could this be?
I can sense his feelings.
His true desire for me.
I'm...
I'm about to...!
Cia, me too.
I'm also at my limit!
I want it.
The semen that will flow from you to me,
pour it all into me and leave no trace of it behind.
Kaname.
Give me warmth with your dear thoughts.
Cia!
It feels hot.
It's here.
It's flowing.
I'm cum!
My cum, it won't stop flowing inside you.
It's hot.
If this continues, I'll really burn.
Cia, I'm sorry.
I don't think I can stop it.
It's alright.
Please don't be upset about It.
I want us to stay connected this way for awhile.
Kaname.
Cia!
It really is a good day.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey Cia... woah!
Now this is...
She really looks amazing the more I see her.
We need to spread our wings and enjoy ourselves once in awhile.
Kaname, what are you looking at?
Sorry my eyes just wandered off unconsciously...
Well that's okay.
You mistook me for a boy before anyway.
I'm going to make you fully recognize that I'm not.
But even if I was just a kind back then, I can't believe that I mistook you for a boy.
How about now?
I'm a woman no matter how you look at it.
I'm at a loss for words.
Good then.
Young Kaname needs to reflect on his own mistake.
Cia, what is this?
I-If you've got something to say then say it.
Quite a unique room, I guess.
A lot of people say that.
This is my hobby.
People usually find it strange though.
It doesn't really cause trouble or harm.
Besides, there isn't really any reason for
me not to love collecting stuffed toys.
Yeah, that's right.
There isn't any single reason.
And that crock is?
This one?
It's name is Portos.
Kaname here, say "ah".
Cia, I think that s really embarrassing.
I-It's okay.
Other couples are also doing it.
Come on.
There, I cleaned you up.
Kaname and I are now sweethearts.
At least that's what I thought during those times.
Kaname is still the usual lucky pervert.
Oh no, I'm exposed!
His timing also couldn't be worse.
Oh no, I'm exposed.
It's so bad that even I'm surprised about it.
I'm not really troubled by it though.
Yep.
I'm not troubled one bit.
It's not really the actual problem, but...
I'm going to sleep early tonight.
It's my date with Kaname tomorrow after all.
First we'll go here, then we'll go there next...
Lastly, we're probably going to do it again.
Oh, Cia!
Everyone!
But I think those flavored sticks are more tasty!
Well, they are quite delicious.
Putting that aside, Elcia-san's breasts
sure look healthy and well rounded.
R-Realy?
They're really amazing they even float!
So Nii-san was taken away by these voluptuous breasts.
Hey Yuu!
But, it feels really comfy when I lay my head here.
I think I might want a big sister like you.
Yuu...
I also want a big sister like you!
It feels really soft.
Don't play with my breasts!
Does Kaname like bigger breasts?
I think he does like them.
He fondles my breasts a lot whenever we do it.
But if that's true, then how about Kaori-san?
I've never seen breasts that are as great as hers.
But Kaname wouldn't just do it with her, would he?
Gotcha!
Kaname...
After that, I began avoiding Kaname.
And those tough days simply continued.
The scenery here hasn't changed since that time.
The sea, the town...
Kaname.
Cia.
I never thought you'd be here too.
This is where it started, and it's an important place for us.
Where it started... but we soon lost sight of our goal.
Cia, do you still remember what happened that day?
Of course.
I clearly remember.
Are you okay?
I'm coming for you now!
I'm going to get you out of here.
These scars are from that time, when you tried to protect me.
Cia, Kaori-san was drunk during that time...
I wonder why?
I'm the one who knows best that you
are not that kind of person, and yet...
Our goal is still far ahead.
But I want to reach it with you, Cia.
Yes, together forever, Kaname.
For it to grow this big...
So you've been holding it in until now.
Okay I'll take responsibility for this.
And release it for you.
But, no matter how many times I look at
it, I still can't get used to this colossus.
It's yours though so I don't mind.
Hey!
It's going wild like an untrained horse!
I don't know what it will do once I take my hands off it.
It feels good.
Good grief.
I'll be the one to take this, only I can take this thing's carnal desires.
I'm ready, to take anything from it.
It's unfair for you to do ail the work.
Huh?
Kaname?
What? No way...!
I'll be tasting this.
You don't need to...
It's somewhat sour, but easy to lick.
I'm the one who should be doing it.
There's no need for you to do it.
then I'm going to keep up with this until the end.
Cia, you've become quite daring now.
Idiot and why do you think I became like this?
You're the one responsible for this, remember?
Cia, I'm about to...!
It's okay I don't mind, just release it whenever you want to.
I'm cumming!
For us knights to be doing this lewd thing.
Even knights are humans.
They're also males and females.
That's true, but...
Your thing here is moving as if it really enjoys it.
Kind of like a small version of you.
I'm cumming again!
I'm sorry Cia.
What are you doing Kaname?
I'm going to use a condom.
We've already prepared for this, right?
You don't want to make me pregnant?
I want physical proof of our love.
I understand.
Cia!
It's tight.
It's pushing inside and opening my pussy.
Cia!
Yes!
You're getting really wild now.
I can't help it.
There's no woman that would not like to
be penetrated by the man she loves.
Even more so if that man is my first love, I just can't resist it.
Wow...
Kaname, your cumming deeply inside me.
With our thoughts, together.
It feels hot.
So hot that I also feel like cumming as well.
I need to take responsibility for turning you into this beast.
Cia!
You're breathing so hard.
And it's piercing through my delicate parts.
I give you my everything.
Cia, it's wrapping around me just right.
As if I'd know...
And whose fault is it?
You're the one who formed its shape with your
cock, while thrusting wildly inside me.
Kaname...?
Oh no, I'm about to be marked.
I'll be marked with the pleasure of a woman.
I'm going to bear it.
It's going to be etched in me.
Kaname, I'm...
Me too, I'm going to... So just hold on a little more!
I'd try if I still could!
Cia!
If this continues, I'm going to cum first.
I don't want to do it alone.
Cia!
My womb is getting filled with your semen.
It feels like it passing through me.
My head feels light.
I feel like I'm going to lose it.
Kaname.
If this continues, I'll...
What are you doing?
Stop that's dirty.
Then I'll clean It.
Kaname.
Cia...
Oh no...
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum again.
I don't know how many times we've done it already.
I wonder why I became this lewd.
If it's just with me, then I don't care if you're lewd.
Of course, I will never show this side to anyone else, only to you!
Cia, I'm about to...!
Kaname, you can't!
It's full already,
Anything more, and it will overflow!
I said it's full already.
I'm sorry Kaname.
My body's already worn out.
Let this be our last union.
Okay I'm going to release every last drop of it in you!
Kaname...
I'm a knight, and yet I've become a lewd woman.
I, Elcia Harvens, ask to be forgiven for this.
I want to...
I want to climax with you.
I want to have it.
I want you to let your semen flow Into me,
so that I'll be impregnated.
Kaname...!
I'm about to...
Are you about to cum, Cia?
That's right.
I'm cumming.
I'm happy to cum because of you.
I'm cumming because of you!
Kaname.
Together, forever...
I love you, Kaname.
Me too, Cia.
I love you.
It'd be tough for my old self if she knew about this.
She'd most likely cut me in two.
Don't worry.
When that happens, I'm going to protect you from her.
It's all because you forced me to learn the pleasures of a woman.
We found our goals again after meeting at that memorable place.
After that, we both passed the knight exam with flying colors.
But all of that was just but a starting point.
For us to do it while I'm cooking...
Where are your table manners?
I just couldn't resist since you're dressed like that!
I just didn't have anything to wear earlier.
I just agreed to your suggestion.
Then let's just leave it at that.
Oh no, I'm going to feel horny.
I can't believe that my body now can't live
without getting a taste of your cum.
Cia, me too, I also need to indulge in your milk.
Kaname, don't...
That's not just yours anymore.
But you're getting aroused from it, right?
It's exactly because I'm getting aroused too much!
And don't make me say it you jerk!
I should sometimes do this to you too.
Here, say "ah."
Cia, thank you for everything.
For being an honorable knight and for always
being willing to take my seed within you.
Idiot, we have each other don't we?
You've also accepted me, and if it's not you I won't desire to do it.
Then let's do it together Cia.
Let's cum together.
Geez, you sure can cum a lot.
Our child must have been surprised.
I want that child to learn, not just from you, but also from me.
And what would you do if our child grew to be as perverted as you?
But you also like that side of me, right?
Only for you, I already told you that.
Don't feel conceited.
An emergency signal?
Something happened already?
Kaname, we'll skip our meal for now.
Okay!
We are a bound by a vow.
It's a bond that surpasses all other things.
As proper knights, we're now one step close
into fulfilling our childhood dreams.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm fine.
Mothers are strong.
And now, we made a new promise.
That we'll both live on to protect each other.
Kaname!
What?
You forgot something.
Now, let's go!
Someones waiting for us!
Nii-san...
Wait for me, okay?