Yuu, you haven't taken your medicine!
You have to listen to what the doctor says now.
You said you'd buy it.
Huh?
You said you'd you buy cream puffs if I take
the medicine and the shots for a week.
Like I said, I have.
Let's eat together with onii-chan.
Kaname, over here.
No! This isn't it!
Yuu...
I want the ones you bought last time!
The ones that are pretty and cute!
I don't want this anymore! I don't care!
Go away!
Ma'am, about the future plans...
Yes. Um...
A tough sickness. Always trapped inside,
With the painful injections and bitter drugs.
No one would understand Yuu.
No one was there to support her.
But I will always be...
there for Yuu!
Onii-chan!
I bought it!
I could only get one with the pocket money I have but,
this is it, right?
Oh, thank you!
Yay!
I’m just a kid now, so there’s not much I can do.
But when I grow up I'll become a knight!
I'll become strong knight, and always protect you, Yuu!
Okay.
Nii-san...
Nii-san, Nii-san... Please wake up, Nii-san.
Yuu?
Good morning, Nii-san.
As long as your sister I am here, I won't let you be late.
Shiromiya Academy
I was at the point of being late for the first day.
Thanks a lot, Yuu.
My pleasure. To help her brother is all
that a younger sister could wish for.
But if you want to thank me, please give me a reward.
Eh, what?
Like the usual.
I'm so happy!
Nii-san... to be honest, I really wish
that this will last forever...
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
I won't lose!
No way!
A chance!
One point! End of match!
Amazing! Yuu actually beat Shia!
Hey, you guys working hard with practice?
Oh, you're doing it in the form of a tournament today!
Yes, sir. Fujimori is the seed.
So it's Yuu who made it to the finals.
Yes, she seems to be really at it today.
But what's with that "date with Kaname"
at the top of the brackets?
Oh, I thought of that!
You'll get a date with Kaname
for winning the tournament!
On the red side, Fujimori Kaname!
On the white side, Fujimori Yuu!
Ensemble, salut, aller!
Yuu already has her hands full just dodging!
As expected there’s too much difference
in strength between them.
Well, Yuu does fight through dodging
and looking for chances.
But what is this?
Her reaction is even faster than
when she was fighting me.
Looks like we have a winner.
My lost.
One point! The winner, Fujimori Yuu!
Nii-san!
Kaname, looks like that wasn't
the right opponent for you.
I finally got one point taken from you.
It's because I've always been looking
at the closest distance.
I know the most about Nii-san.
looks like I have to work hard, too.
Beside, I want to...
I wanted to have a date with Nii-san.
Well, let's go.
Woah, there are so many couples around here.
I'm sure we look like a couple, too.
Eh? Well, I guess Yuu is cute and... a good kid...
If a girt like this was my girlfriend...
I love you! I love you!
I can't hold back anymore!
Maria!
Nii-san, I love you.
Yuu...
Maria, it's been just the two of us ever
since our parents passed away.
So, you see, you could just be misunderstanding.
The world is very large.
The person truly precious to Maria is out
there, and you'll find him one day.
Maria, I want to introduce someone to you.
She's the person precious to me.
Our wedding will be held in the village,
I and really hope you can come, too.
Nice to meet you, Maria!
Yuu?
Yuu? Are you okay?
I'm okay, Nii-san. Please don't worry about it.
Credit Belongs to the New Knight Group!
Tada!
They say it's all thanks to us!
Wuh? Ware's Yuu?
I think Yuu hasn’t been well.
She's been resting in her room ever since we got back.
Nii-san...
You can't...
Not with someone else...
You can't!
No... you just can't...
Not with someone that’s not me...
A letter?
Nii-san. I apologize for writing to you so suddenly.
Although we've always been free around each
other because we grew up together,
just this time? I couldn't bring the courage,
and decided to write instead.
I have something very important to say.
Nii-san, I’ll be waiting for you
at the roof after school today.
I can't go back or stop anymore.
Yuu?
Yuu! What are you doing standing in the rain!
You'll catch a cold again.
Yuu...
I always thought I should hold back.
I thought that as long as Nii-san is happy...
But I can't anymore!
I can't stand Nii-san being together with someone else!
I've fallen in love with Nii-san!
Not just as an elder brother, but as a lover!
Yuu! Do you remember?
I said that I'd become a knight, and protect you, Yuu!
Those feelings haven't changed, even now.
In fact, they've become stronger!
I finally understand now after hearing your feelings!
It has to be Yuu for me, too!
I love you, Yuu.
Yuu...
Nii-san...
Nii-san, please do me a favour...
And give me a memory that I'll never forget.
Yuu.
Nii-san's arms are so warm to be in...
Nii-san, please be gentle.
Okay, Yuu.
I'm sorry. It’s not something I needed to say, is it?
Nii-san has always been so gentle to me.
If this goes on, the clothes will be all wrinkled, so...
This is embarrassing...
I don't have a great chest like Kaori-san...
Let's not talk about anyone else at a time like this.
I'm sorry!
For me, Yuu is always the best!
I can't stop looking at your lovely boobs!
Don’t! You can't do that.
If you tease both my boobs at the same time...
I won't be able to hold it!
Yuu, can you raise your hips?
Yes...
You’re soaked...
I'm sorry. I'm so happy Nii-san is touching my body...
So happy, my body can’t help be honest about it...
Yuu, spread your legs.
Yes... this is embarrassing...
Amazing... Yuu's insides are squeezing
so much it could hurt...
Nii-san don't... my face is burning
in embarrassment already...
Sorry for making you feel awkward, Yuu.
Nii-san...
Mine is... like this, too.
Wow... Nii-san is like this... thinking of me?
Yeah. Yuu, could you take it off?
Yes...
Nii-san!
When you squeezed on my finger
just now, I was imagining...
I was thinking "I'm about to go in here"...
Nii-san... but, it's so large...
Will it fit inside properly?
To be honest, I'm worried.
It's fine. Leave it all to me.
Nii-san...
I’m so embarrassed I think I could die...
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
You're very pretty here, Yuu!
It feels really strange somehow!
Yuu is so hot down here...
Don't, you can't!
Just thinking that Nii-san is licking me is... I can’t...
You don't have to hold back, Yuu!
No... Nii-san's tongue feels so
good, my mind is going blank!
Love you... Nii-san... I love you...
What a flood. Well then, just like this...
Nii-san...
Yuu... I'm sorry, can you lend a hand?
Nii-san, it's here.
The entrance is here.
Yuu... are you okay?
Yes, I'm alright.
How are you, Nii-san?
It's just the tip inside, but it feels incredibly good!
I'm so glad to hear that.
Nii-san, please come inside me.
Nii-san!
Yuu!
I'm cumming from just going inside!
It's hot! Hot stuff is coming inside!
Huh? Nii-san, you're still completely hard.
Sorry, Yuu is just so sexy and cute...
I don't think I can calm down from just cumming once!
To be connected with the one you love...
It really fills your heart up.
I didn't think sex would be this amazing...
Both my body and my mind is filled up with Nii-san...
There's just so much of  "I love you" inside...
Love you! I love you, Nii-san!
You're so cute, Yuu... I love you, too!
My chest again... Nii-san's mouth is on my chest!
It's fine. Cum as much as you want.
Yuu!
Yes, yes!
I'll give all of me... to Nii-san!
I'll give everything, so please take it all!
But I don't want, I don't want to cum alone!
Please be with me, Nii-san!
Please cum lots inside me!
I get it.
Yuu!
Nii-san!
Amazing...
Right now... I'm in touch with the
world only through Nii-san...
Amazing... amazing!
Huh?
Yuu? Are you there?
That's strange... I thought I heard her voice just now...
You must have misheard.
The brother and sister said they'd be out tonight.
I guess.
Speaking about it, do you think that
Yuu does have a crush on Fujimori?
If doesn't seem to just be love as a family.
You think so too, right?
But it's sad, that there's no way you can
get past the obstacle of being siblings.
They are brother and sister, after all.
No matter how lovely Yuu is, how successful
she is, or how much she loves Kaname,
it's sad, but siblings simply can't be with each other.
Fate is cruel, I guess we could say...
They are destined to never be together...
I want to cum...
I want to let it out inside Yuu!
but at the very least, we should be here for Yuu.
You're right, we should.
It's fine, Nii-san.
My insides are only for you, Nii-san.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow, Mana.
Nii-san, yes!
I can't hold back anymore, Nii-san!
It feels too good, I...
Yuu! Yuu! Yuu!
Nii-san! Nii-san! Nii-san!
Please give it to me! Please give me your hot stuff!
Yuu, are you alright?
Pull yourself together, Yuu!
Yuu!
Nii-san... I...
Nii-san's is... connected deep inside...
And so much hot stuff is flowing inside...
It's hot! Nii-san is all inside me...
I'm so happy...
No! I wanted to take it all...
I didn't want to leave out even a single
drop, but it's overflowing...
Being with Nii-san... I'm so happy...
My heart is melting...
I want to always be by your side, and protect you, Nii-san.
One point! The winner, Fujimori Yuu!
Am I, really fine with this?
You've thought it through, right?
Yes! I will not give up on my feelings for
Yuu or my dreams of becoming a knight!
Then, I'll have to set out some conditions.
There will soon be a special training program
for the Holy Knights starting.
You have to join that and complete all the courses.
For someone who hasn't become a Holy
Knight, it might take you a year
or even longer to do that.
If you really want to be happy together, then
Kaname should not complain about this,
and grow up into a knight!
Yes!
For the lady, you have to keep up your
work even without Kaname around,
and keep those feelings even though you are separated.
Yes.
Alright then.
Well, we were going to send Kaori in the first
place, so there will be some time to prepare.
We'll probably leave the day after tomorrow.
Rest well, and prepare for your trip tomorrow, Kaname.
Yes!
I'll be separated from Nii-san for a while, I guess.
I’m sorry about it, Yuu.
I have to leave you all alone for a while.
It's fine.
Right now, no matter how far we are separated,
I can feel that our hearts are connected.
Nii-san...
Yuu...
Nii-san... that's good too, but... um...
Please touch the front.
Wait! Please wait, Nii-san!
Yuu... here?
It's fine, Nii-san.
They're closed today, no one will come.
I love you, Nii-san.
Please do lots and lots of naughty things today.
Alright.
Well, to start, I really want to see
Yuu doing naughty things herself.
Like this?
Rougher.
Nii-san!
You’re cute, Yuu.
They're swelling and hard, aren't they?
No, Nii-san...
Yuu's boobs are really cute, too!
If the Nii-san I love so much is
licking my nipples like that, I...
Yuu!
I'm so happy...
Nii-san’s is fitting perfectly all the way inside me again...
It's hard to believe even looking
at where we're connected...
How does something so large fit inside me?
I know everything about Nii-san.
Soon, Nii-san will be unable to hold back, he'll
raise my legs and start being really rough.
I'm sorry, my hips won't stop anymore!
Nii-san!
He's getting larger inside me...
You're about to cum, right?
Nii-san!
This... rubbing insanely inside me, it's
the proof that Nii-san's at this limit!
When he does this, my mind will be so full
of Nii-san, I can't think of anything else!
It has to be because my womb is yearning
and waiting for Nii-san's sperm!
Yuu! I'm cumming, Yuu!
I want to cum! I want to cum with Nii-san!
Nii-san, inside! Please let it out inside!
Together with me...
It's overflowing!
Nii-san really looks like he feels
good when he ejaculates...
I'm so happy...
He came so much...Nii-san...
Nii-san, that place... could it be, we're doing it?
No, Nii-san that's too embarrassing!
Can I have all of you, Yuu?
Nii-san... yes... I'll give all of myself to Nii-san.
It's amazing, we're connect through my butt...
Nii-san, don't... don't look inside, don't peek inside!
Nii-san's thick thing is going inside my butt...
My insides are being stirred up
by what Nii-san uses to pee...
I'm sorry, I can't anymore, Nii-san!
I... I'm... being loved by Nii-san, I'm
coming even from my butt hole!
I'm sorry Nii-san!
Even though I’m your sister! I'm sorry for being so lewd!
It's hot! It's hot!
Nii-san's hot sperm is soaking deep into me...
My inside are filled by Nii-san's hot stuff...
Nii-san... the mouth is pulsing here...
That's...
You came so much and yet that's still not enough, huh?
It's such a cute penis.
I'll let you cum one more time with my mouth.
If Yuu... if the Yuu that I love so much
does that, I can't hold back anymore!
Yuu!
Nii-san, when you come back, let's continue this.
yume no naka kimi to sugoshite kita toki kioku ga
Memories of the time I spend with in my dreams
afurete mirai wo egaite yuku
Overflow, and paint a picture of the future
ayamachi sae itoshku omou
Even the mistakes we've made, are full of love
kakegae no nai takaramono dato
and are irreplaceable treasure to me.
dakara kitto aruki tsudukete yukeru
So I definitely can keep walking forward,
kimito naraba
if it’s with you.
Tooku ni ukanderu yume ni mukatte bokutachi wa
Us, moving towards those dreams hovering afar.
eien wo dakishime te wo nobasu itsudatte
Holding tight on to the forever, and reach out our hands, always.
I wonder how Kaname is doing.
He's definitely working hard.
Because there's someone waiting for him.
kono kokoro ga motometeru yume yadoru jounetsu wo
This heart, seeks and yearns, the passion where the dream lies.
futari naraba kiito itsuka
If It's the two of us, then for sure one day,
tadoritsukeru yo kagayaku bashou e
we will reach, that place shining bright.
hitotsu hitsotu taisetsu na koto tsunaide yuke tara
if we can connect, all the important thing one by one.
sekai datte kaerareru hazu dato
We'll able o change, even the world.
Nii-san!
Nii-san! Nii-san!
Nii-san...
Yuu... I missed you.
Like I thought, Nii-san is definitely the knight for me!
Congratulations!
Go Kaname!
She's so pretty!
I'm really, really happy to have lived
together with Nii-san all this time.
Even from now, we'll still always be together.
You'll be even happier, Yuu.
Yes.
Congratulations!
Knights of Love
Purely Kiss
Happily eve after!