Are you okay?
I'll head over right now!
I'll get you out right away.
Leave me and run, or you'll be in danger as well.
No. If it's the knights of justice I saw
on TV, they would never abandon...
Well done! Everything's alright now.
It was a knight that saved us.
Knights of the modern era.
I've decided. I'm going to become a knight.
I pledge to you here,
that I will become a knight that fulfills
justice better than all other!
I pledge, too.
I'll become a knight that protects
more people than anyone else!
Let's meet here someday again!
I'm leaving my back to you, Kaname!
Leave it to me, Elcia!
Damn it!
Well done, but your swordsmanship is coarse as usual.
C'mon, don't say that.
I'm happy as long as I can protect Cia's back.
You're being a little too comfortable, Kaname.
Ah, my bad.
My heart feels like it's going to explode, Kaname.
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset, Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
What?
Wait, wait, wait!
How do you know?
The president was talking about it earlier.
That old man...
Why not? It's not like it's something you have to hide.
Nii-san, how did I not hear of this?
Hey, hey, so what kind of person is she?
Please explain this!
C'mon tell me!
Wait up, please!
What is the meaning of this, Nii-san?
Ah, Cia!
Cia?
Elcia-san...
Um, it's a paired patrol so,
um, it works less well if you're too far away...
And it's hard to talk, too.
Suspicious people discovered.
We need to pursuit.
Hey Cia! Don't chase after them on your own!
We should contact the leader Kaori-san first!
Hey Cia! What happened to you!?
Cia!
Like I'd let you run away!
Oh?
For a cute knight to come right into
the HQs of a theft group, huh?
This is bad. I've been completely surrounded.
And right now, I don't have Kaname
to protect my backside.
What's wrong?
It won't be fun if you don't resist a little.
Well there are ways to enjoy a scared little girl as well.
Who the fuck are you!?
You bastard!
That rough, left-handed sword.
Damn it! Go! Take care of him!
Coming in alone again like that,
knights are all stupid aren't you?
I'm not alone!
There's another powerful knight right there!
Amazing... My body is suddenly free to move.
The knights are coming in groups!
Shit!
Run!
Cia! Are you okay?
You didn't have to come, you know...
You idiot! I was really... really worried about you.
Sorry... I'm sorry.
I was thinking that... I'd had to be able to fight alone.
But I ended up realizing that,
without you, I'm unable to put forth my strengths.
Then it'd be fine if we always hold out together, right?
But...
No sense, and no thoughts!
With undivided attention!
And a completely clear mind!
Cia! As expected you were here.
Like a clear mirror and still waters!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!!
Ouch... Ah that was quite scary.
It's Kaname's bad for suddenly appearing in...
front of me.
Cia, there's something I want to tell you.
There's nothing you can get from me.
Why don't you ask someone like
your marriage meeting partner?
Cia...
I declined the marriage meeting.
There just one reason.
I have a girl I like.
I can't lie anymore.
I like you, Cia!
K-kaname...
Please don't lie to me either, Cia.
Answer with all honesty, please!
I don't know...
I don't know.
Since when... No,
it was probably since we first met, I've always... always...
Kaname...
I like you, too.
Cia...
Sorry for not telling you earlier.
You're really late, you know. But I
guess that's true for both of us.
Kaname, no... My feelings are overflowing...
Don't be in such a hurry.
I'm going to lose myself...
It's unfair for you to do all you want...
I want to... touch Kaname, too.
I want us to both be... loving each other...
It's like...
I'm getting a burn from your tongue...
Kaname?
I want to know more about you, Cia.
Don't look too much...
It's embarrassing...
What are you talking about? They're beautiful.
No... I'm just being touched and yet...
I'm feeling it too much...
Don't grab them like that...
That's...
not somewhere you should lick...
It's hot...
Whenever Kaname touches me, it keeps getting hotter...
This is the first time I've been like
this... I don't know what to do...
Cia, you don't have to hold back.
Even if you say that...
Kaname... Kaname! K-kaname, I, I'm already...
Did you cum, Cia?
Cum? I see, so this is what is called "cumming"...
It's Kaname's fault, alright?
Being attacked over and over again... this is as if...
Kaname, where are you touching?
No! I'm sweating from practice, it's dirty!
There's nothing dirty about Cia!
No... it's really...
Really? Even though Cia is saying
she feels good down here.
Don't! Don't make such kind of noises...
I'll... I'll cum again...
Wait, Kaname...
K-Kaname...
Cia... Sorry, I don't think I can hold back anymore.
Me, too... I want to give you everything.
Cia...
A bit lower...
Kaname...
Are you okay, Cia?
I'm fine. More importantly if you
don't come deeper inside...
It'd be painful for you, right?
But...
I already said it, right? That I want to take all of you.
Cia!
Cia, it's all in!
I'm a very lucky person...
To give my first time to my first love...
Cia!
Kaname!
Cia's insides... are soft... and it feels really good!
Don't lie, Kaname... You're holding back...
I want you to feel it lots as well...
Even though you look like you really hurt...
You'll engrave it deep inside me, right?
So this moment
never vanishes in my life!
Cia, I love you!
Cia! Cia!
I can tell... where Kaname is right now...
How deep you are going into me... I can tell!
Feel me too, Kaname!
Please! Hit deep inside me!
The sensation of me... that only you will know...
Burn it in your memory for the rest of your life...
I love you, Cia!
Kaname! Love you!
Kaname!
Cia!
This is...
Kaname, it's going deeper that before...
Something other than pain...
It's good! What is this? It feels good!
K-kaname's feelings are being conveyed...
That you want me so much...
I'm... already...
Cia, me too.
I'm already...
I want it! From inside Kaname's body to inside mine,
the sperm that your body produces...
Pour it all into me through your phallus!
Kaname! All of it...
Warm my insides with your feelings!
Cia!
It's hot! It came... It's coming...
Cumming...
I can't stop cumming inside Cia...
Hot...
It's hot... If this goes on, I'm really going to get burned...
Sorry Cia, looks like it's not gonna stop for a while.
It's fine. More importantly don't take it out.
I want to keep being... connected with you...
Kaname...
Cia...
Ah! That must be it.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, Cia... uh!
This... If you look again, she has an amazing body.
It's good to relax once in a while, huh.
Kaname? Where are you looking.
S-sorry! I couldn't help but...
Oh well. Kaname did mistake me
for a guy in that past before.
I'll make you re-recognize me here.
However, although we were kids... for me
to make a mistake on Elcia's gender...
How's this? No matter how you
look at it, I'm a woman, right?
There's not a single thing to complain about.
Good. The Kaname in the past should
be reflecting on himself.
Cia, this is...
If, if there's something you want to say, blurt it out.
It's a very unique room...
That's a very common way to put it.
This is my hobby.
People often think it's strange, but...
There's nothing wrong or bad about it.
For starters, there's no reason why
I can't collect stuffed dolls, right?
That's right, there would never be.
By the way that alligator...
Ah, this child? He's called Porthos!
Kaname! Here, say ah...
C-Cia! This might be a little too embarrassing...
It-it's fine! Other couples are doing it, too.
Here...
I took it off properly...
Me and Kaname are a couple.
I still thought so at this time.
Kaname is still...
a lucky pervert...
So you saw...
Or should I say he does things
at surprisingly horrible times...
I'm not worried about such things!
Yeah! Not worried at all!
The problem is not that, but...
Let's sleep early today!
I have a date with Kaname tomorrow, after all!
We should go there, and then there...
I wonder if we'll end up doing it again at the end...
Ah, Cia!
Everyone!
But the Umaibo is the best I think!
Yeah, that's certainly tasty.
By the way, Elcia-san's breasts
are very plump and beautiful.
R-Really?
It's amazing! Your boobs float on water!
I wonder if Nii-san became a captive of this bust as well...
Yuu!
But it's true that if you do this...
you can really calm down...
If it's a sister in law like Elcia-san, I might want one.
Yuu?
I want a sister like Cia as well!
So soft!
My chest is not a toy!
I wonder if Kaname likes larger breasts as expected...
That must be the case, since
when we're doing it he...
But then, what about Kaori-san?
I've never seen such amazing breasts anywhere else.
I don't suppose Kaname is going after Kaori-san as well...
C'mon!
Kaname...
From then on,
I started avoiding Kaname.
It was... a time of nothing but pain.
The view here hasn't changed at all from back then.
The town and the sea you can see from here...
Kaname...
Cia...
I didn't think that Kaname would come here as well.
Because this is the important place
when our connection started.
It's a great thing that it started but...
Before I knew it, I lost sight of the goal.
Cia, do you remember what happened on that day?
Of course. I remember.
Are you okay?
I'll head over right now!
I'll get you out right away.
The scar on your right hand,
is from trying to help me at that time.
Cia, about what happened before...
That was because Kaori-san was drunk and...
You don't have to say it.
I wonder why I was upset... Kaname's not
the kind of person to do such things.
I should know that the best.
Although the goal is still very far away,
Please walk all the way with me, Cia.
We'll always be together, Kaname.
For it to become this big...
You've really been holding back, haven't you?
Very well then.
I'll take responsibility and release it for you.
But you really can't get used to the grotesqueness
no matter how many times you look at this.
I don't mind since it's Kaname's but...
Hey!
It's twitching around like some kind of monster...
I don't know what it's gonna do
if I don't hold it still like this.
It feels good!
Geez, I'll take responsibility so you
don't direct your desires to others...
It's hard, and really salty...
I can't let Cia do everything, can I?
Kaname?
No way!
I'm going to have a taste.
There's no such need...
It's a little sour, but surprisingly easy to drink.
I'm doing it right now.
There's no need for you to do anything...
If you're gonna be so stubborn,
I'll keep going until your waist gives away!
Cia's become really daring.
You idiot!
Who do you think made be become so?
It was you that made me such a sloppy woman!
Cia! I'm going to...
It's fine! Let it out!
Let it out inside my mouth!
It's coming out!
Knights like us are doing such disgraceful things...
Knights are humans as well...
And we're man and woman!
That's true but...
Kaname's is moving around trying to get its way with me.
It's like a small you.
Again!
Sorry, Cia.
There.
What are you doing, Kaname?
I thought I'd put on a rubber.
We've already confirmed on each
other's determination, right?
Don't you have enough dare to make me pregnant?
I want... a fruit of love.
I get it. Cia!
It's tight inside...
you're spreading me...
Cia!
It's good!
You're really lewd right now!
I can't help it! There's no woman that wouldn't feel it,
From being penetrated by a man she loves!
Let alone that man being her first love!
Amazing!
Kaname is...
bursting his feelings... deep inside me...
It's so hot... It feels like I can cum from just this...
I've got to take responsibility till the very
end, for turning you into a monster...
Cia!
Everything is... being broken...
My precious place is being hit and crushed...
Make me yours!
Cia's insides are sucking tightly!
Shut up! Who's fault is that!
Who's the one rampaging inside while
turning it into his own shape!?
K-Kaname...
I'll, I'll be engraved... the pleasures of being a woman...
Even though I'm a knight, why?
Even though I'm a knight...
Ka-Kaname... I'm... I'm going to...
Me too! So please, just a bit more!
It's not like I can't resist it right now...
Cia!
Kaname, Kaname, if this goes on I'll end up...
Hurry up! Please! I don't want to be alone! Not alone!
Cia!
My womb is filled with your seed...
Something is... Tingling inside my head
I think I'm gonna pass away...
Kaname...
If you keep going like this...
No! What are you doing?
Stop it, Kaname, it's dirty!
Then I'll make it clean.
Kaname, Kaname!
Cia!
No more! I'll cum again... I'll cum!
I can't... think straight anymore...
Why have I... become such a... disgraceful woman...
It's in front of me...
so being disgraceful is fine!
Of course! Such... such a slutty appearance...
can be only in front of you!
Cia, I'm gonna...
You can't! Kaname, it's already full!
Any more is... No!
Even though I said no more will fit...
Sorry, Kaname, my body is falling apart.
This is the last...
Okay. With this, I'll pour all the sperm I made, inside Cia!
Kaname! Even though I'm a knight,
I've become such a disgraceful woman for you!
Thank me! Elcia Harvence!
Hurry, together! I want to head
towards an orgasm with you!
I want it! Kaname's sperm in my womb!
If it's you then I don't mind if you break it!
I'm prepared!
Kaname!
I'm... going to...
Are you going to cum, Cia?
Yes! I'm cumming... Kaname is making me cum again!
I'm happy! To cum from Kaname...
Kaname!
Kaname... Always...
I really like you,
Kaname.
Me too, Cia.
I love you.
Such acts... It'd be trouble if the past me found out.
I'll be chopped into pieces for sure.
Don't worry.
If that happens, the me right now will protect you.
'Cause you forced me to learn
the happiness of a woman.
We reconfirmed our goals at the
place of memories for us.
After that, we both passed the test to become Paladins.
However, that was but another new beginning.
To demand such things while I'm
cooking is a breach of manners!
If you're dressed like that, there's no way I could resist!
I just didn't have anything to wear!
I wasn't responding to your request or anything!
Let's just leave it at that.
No, I confess!
If I don't get a taste of your seed regularly,
my body tingles...
Cia!
Me too. If I don't drink your milk regularly...
You can't! Kaname! That's not just for you!
C'mon, what's the real reason?
Because I feel too much from it!
Don't make me say that you idiot!
Once in a while I should feed Cia as well...
Here, say ah...
Cia, thanks for everything!
While walking on the same path
and being a prideful knight,
taking care of my frenzy and calming
me down every day like this!
Like I said, that's true for me as well.
I go crazy, too. I want Kaname's so bad...
I can't wait anymore...
Then together! Let's cum together!
Geez, you really shot out so much...
The baby inside is probably really surprised as well.
I want it to not only know Cia, but me too!
Well?
What would happen if the baby was
raised by a pervert like you?
But Cia likes it, don't you?
That's only because it's you.
You haughty person.
Emergency contact!?
Did some kind of incident happen?
Kaname, we're leaving in five minutes!
I get it!
We have pledged to each other.
And that is a bond stronger than any other between us.
Right now, we have walked towards the promise
when we were young, by becoming Paladins.
Is your body alright?
I'm fine, Kaname. Mothers are strong.
And now, we have taken new oaths.
An oath to protect each other and live on together.
Kaname!
What's wrong?
You forgot something.
C'mon, let's go!
Someone is waiting for us!
Nii-san...
Please wait for me.