Kouta-sama, I love you.
Kouta... I love you.
I love you.
I love, I love you, Kouta...
Kouta!
I have to clean the garden so early this morning, huh.
What a pain.
Oh, Kouta?
You can't become a good Shinto priest if you slack off like that.
Quit it already.
I already said that I'm not inheriting this shrine, you know.
I just want to live a normal life.
*stare*
What is it?
I thought you were going to start your speech about
becoming a government employee again.
It seems I've been found out.
We've been together for a long time.
Of course I'll know what you're thinking right away.
True.
Anyway, Tomo-chan told me to call
you since breakfast's already done.
Come as soon as you're done there, okay?
Gotcha.
Good morning, onii-chan.
Huh, where's onee-chan?
Beats me.
Here I am!
My, my, is everyone doing alright?
Who is she?
Well, I'd like to introduce her to you all.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Kudou Mai.
I've left my rural home to become Kouta's fiancée
and inherit the Nikomori shrine with him.
Everyone, though I'm still inexperienced,
I hope to get along well with all of you.
Have we ever had a breakfast this awkward before?
Mio!
Motoka!
Mai, pass the soy sauce, please.
Here, Erina-sama.
Thanks!
Alright, I think it's time to start our copulation
sessions as soon as possible.
Are you okay with that, Mai-Mai?
I'm okay with that.
I've been training for a long time, just
for this very day and purpose.
I'm going to school.
What in the world is going on?
Kouta-sama.
Kouta-sama!
Oh, yes?
Are you all right, Kouta-sama?
Oh yeah, Mai and I are about to do it for the first time.
Kouta-sam...
Kouta-sama, please don't think I'm a lecherous woman.
Mai!
Kouta-sama!
Have we ever had a breakfast this awkward before?
Oh yeah, how was yesterday?
Did Kouta do his job well?
Yes, Kouta-san guided me very gently.
I actually lost control somewhere along the way.
Mai-san, we're in the middle of breakfast right now!
So saying that in front of everyone is just...
My relationship with everyone is important,
which is why I don't think keeping secrets is any good.
Yup, yup.
So... Kouta really did naughty things with Mai-san.
She even stopped using that honorific with him.
Indeed, I believe that it's the wife's
duty to obey her husbands words,
though I still think that "Kouta-sama" is still better.
W-W-Wife...?!
No, I definitely won't allow you to be Kouta's wife!
Because I'm going to be his wife!
What the hell?!
Kouta.
Nono's nude body...
Jeez, what's wrong with you, Kouta?
I-I'm sorry.
Kouta, you see...
I may have said those things earlier,
but I think I really need to say this beforehand.
Kouta... I love you.
Me too...
Yay!
Well, I kinda had a feeling that was the case.
Childhood friends really do think alike.
Kouta...
...let's make a baby.
Yes! I really love you, Kouta.
Nono...
I'm a god!
What?
Ahem.
You may all find it hard to believe, but
I'm actually the god of this shrine.
Well, technically, I, Okazaki Erina, am
the current vessel of that god.
So the actual reason why I brought Mai-Mai here is,
for world peace!
That's actually a bit too much.
The plan is to successfully purify the miasma surrounding
this shrine and the neighboring areas.
Which is why the daughters of each
of the Kudou family's generations,
are trained since childhood in order to
maintain this land's spiritual power.
I-I see.
Just what are you doing agreeing with her?
And so Mai-Mai will be training for her future engagement.
Yes, my heart shall be prepared for it.
I-I'm doing it too.
I guess it's going to turn out this way, huh.
Oh well.
There's actually no strict requirements on the bride's side.
I know this will sound like a pain, Kouta,
but it's inevitable that your own indecisiveness led to this.
What exactly do we need to do to train?
To put it bluntly... just have lots of sex.
Normal sex won't do by the way.
You need to carefully plan out a nice, gooey
performance, or else it won't be effective.
Gooey?
That's really...
I'll do my best!
I'll work hard!
I'll... do my best.
Kouta-san, please take a good look at my body.
I'm sorry, if you don't want this...
It's not that I don't want to,
but this is embarrassing.
Your breasts look really beautiful.
Mai, are you getting aroused?
To be aroused while exposed like this...
I'm not that lewd a woman.
I got this, I got this!
So please, just calm down.
My apologies for being so shameful.
Breasts sure are sensitive.
I can no longer...
Are you really satisfied with just the breasts?
Kouta-san...
You have other pleasurable spots, right?
Are you trying to muffle your moans?
No, it's just that such lewd voices shouldn't be...
Shouldn't be let out.
I don't think so.
I really want to hear your voice more.
D-Don't...
I won't be able to control my moans.
Come on, let me listen to them.
I-If that's what you really want, then I'll...
Alright, here we go.
So hot.
It's still quite tight.
I'm sorry, it seems that I haven't gotten used to this yet.
I think it's okay to get used to it bit by bit.
Yes, I'll do my best.
What, a sixty-nine?
...I want to try it.
Do I straddle like this?
I'm totally exposed like this!
Amazing, all I can see is your pussy.
Please don't say embarrassing things like that.
Getting aroused?
I'm not.
Really now?
I'll open your pussy like this if you say that.
Stop...!
I'm already asking you to stop, you know.
Embarrassed?
Yeah, I feel so embarrassed that I just want to die.
I can really see your lewd pussy from here.
Hey, try licking mine too.
O-Okay.
I'm going to pleasure you in a moment, sir.
Oh yeah, Nono,
try writing something with your ass.
What's that for?
Let me know what you want to do most with your ass.
Jeez, just this once, okay?
Please lick it, don't tease me any more!
I feel so embarrassed that I'm about to cum,
so please lick my pussy.
Lick it already.
No, not my clit!
Okay, inside this time.
No, no, stop. Don't stir my insides now, please!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Oh no...
Don't suck it like that.
You just saw me pee.
P-Please, go ahead then.
Well then...
I feel surprisingly nervous.
To be robbed of freedom in this manner.
I don't think it's that serious, though.
Kouta-san, you're too rash!
K-Kouta-san...!
Not... there...
Feeling quite horny now?
Please don't stop, Kouta-san.
No, there it is again...
Kouta-san!
Not there... please, I really don't want it there.
You can't do that there!
It's dirty, it's dirty in there!
There's nothing dirty about you.
Kouta-san!
No... no...
Please, you really can't...
You really can't do it down there.
I see you actually love anal.
P-Please don't say such ridiculous things.
That's not where you're supposed to caress me.
That's not where you make babies...
Even if you say that, with this obviously aroused ass...
Stop, stop...!
Please don't!
Stop!
You mustn't do it, and yet...
I never imagined things would go this way.
Please Kouta... let me... let me be already...
I guess it really is strange to do it in the classroom.
Yeah, it is.
Am I really going to play with myself here?
Yeah, I'm super serious, and I really want to see it.
Th-Then... I'm doing it.
Just a bit...
You're so slutty.
No I'm not.
No? But you're masturbating while sitting
on your boyfriend right now.
I'm not that slutty.
I'm not...
Your dick.
Quite erotic, don't you agree?
Use it like a sex toy, Nono.
Such vulgar words.
Oh no... but I think I'm getting more aroused now.
Do you love dicks, Nono?
Yeah, but I just yours.
I'm imagining you fucking me right now.
How do you usually masturbate?
Well...
I usually do it in front of a mirror.
It makes my heart race, as if you're actually watching me do it.
I see.
Do you have my face in mind when you do it?
I only look at my own pussy.
Oh no...
You're really slutty, Nono.
Where are you touching yourself right now?
I'm touching my clit.
I'm rubbing it a lot.
I'm so lewd. I'm such a shameful girl, right?
Your dick is already very wet, Kouta,
and I'm rubbing it on me right now.
Rubbing it, rubbing it, rubbing it on me.
So you love rubbing your own love juices on my dick.
No, that's not true.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum!
Oh no, I'm cumming!
Look at what's happening upfront already.
This is all your fault, Kouta-san.
I haven't even done anything to it yet.
Those juices mean it's raring to go.
I'm really such a...
I'm really such a lewd woman now.
Kouta-san.
I can't wait any longer.
Here I go then, Mai.
Here it comes!
Your dick is going inside me!
Your insides feel really hot.
So hot, that I feel like I'm about to melt.
Your pussy is indeed very lewd.
I can feel it even more by the way it reacts.
So dirty.
Yes, my pussy is very lewd and slutty.
It's so vulgar that I want to get fucked more.
I'm going to cum while being fucked hard.
I want to feel this pleasure more and more!
It's coming out, it's coming out.
Now I have to pleasure you even more.
In my ass?
S-Stop... you mustn't!
I think it'll be fine.
You can't!
That's not even where you make babies anyway!
Exactly.
You feel more aroused in here, right?
That's not true!
Don't, stop!
Please don't!
We can totally do this.
With you, I'm sure.
I'm sure that we can do it!
My ass, my ass...!
Getting the hang of it yet?
Not my ass.
I mustn't feel any more pleasure in my ass!
So you do feel pleasure.
No, please... my ass feels good.
So you feel more pleasure in the hole
that's not meant to make babies.
That means you simply want the more pleasurable option.
I'm... I'm...
I'm not that...
That's why, we simply need to pleasure ourselves more... right?
Please.
Yes, please do it...
With your dick, in my ass...
Please teach me more lewd things with my ass and your dick!
Alright, good girl, Mai.
So hot...
My ass feels hot.
My ass, my ass feels great.
I can feel it, I can totally feel it in my ass!
I'm cumming!
I really... love this.
I love anal sex.
Hey, Nono.
You're practically exclusively mine now, right?
Huh? E-Exclusively yours?
You're never getting any other guy's dick
but mine, for the rest of your life.
Y-Yeah, that's already the plan, though.
I want to hear you say it.
Come on, turn your body that way.
Eh? You mean in front of the camera?
In front of the gods as well.
Eh?!
You'll do anything for my dick, right?
Well, yeah, but we already know that, so...
Isn't that enough?
I guess it is enough,
but I still want to hear you say it.
That you're my personal pussy.
Your dick and no one else's...
You mean I'll become your dick's personal hole?
Whoa, that phrase was really erotic.
I don't really know.
That's what you wanted to hear, right?
Then you do know.
But, saying that here is...
Here it comes again!
No, you can't just push it in one spot.
I'm being penetrated deeply.
There, I love it in that spot.
Stir it... it feels so good at the entrance of my pussy.
Oh, cumming now?
Yeah, I'm about to, because your dick just feels too good.
Come on, say more of those erotic words.
No, I'm really about to cum!
Why did you stop?
No, no, let my hands go.
I'm going to move by myself.
Th-That's the spot!
Come on, say it.
Oh no...
Jeez, I just have to say lewd words, right?
I'll do it, I'll do it already, so please just keep fucking me.
In front of the camera, okay?
You're definitely a sadist.
So this is part of my wife training as well?
No, this isn't part of that.
I just want you to be my personal pussy.
I said I'm already yours, didn't I?
Say that my dick is the only dick that
you'll want for the rest of your life.
For the rest of my life?
Okay, I get it, I get it already!
That's the only thing I need to do, right?
You can also say that you're going to be my pussyhole.
Or be my pussy slave.
Or be Mr. Kouta's exclusive pussy.
Wait, wait, stop!
I can't think anymore, my mind's completely muddled.
Can you say it?
Yeah, so...
Can I just say that I want to become your comfort hole?
That's my Nono! I knew you could do it well.
You're absolutely not complimenting me!
I get, I promise already!
I'm going to be Kouta's personal pussy.
Not just his wife,
because I'll be his cum-loving wife pussy.
Do you swear that to the gods?
Yes, yes, I will.
I swear to the gods, that I'll always let Kouta make love to me.
Alright, I'm going to fuck you hard for the rest of my life as well!
My pussy feels great!
I'm going to cum!
My wife pussy is about to...
...about to cum!
It's been a while since you two started your wife training.
How's it going, by the way?
I'm enjoying my current life with him quite well.
I got to enjoy some wet and wild sex
with him in the classroom, though.
And I enjoyed having anal sex with him!
I enjoyed his dick so much that I... that I...
That I actually peed!
Wow, you two sure are amazing.
You've completely blown away my initial expectations.
In a good way, of course.
No, well... I guess.
I kind of want you two to keep that
up, though, so I'm counting on it!
Yes.
I love onii-chan too!
I also want to...
...have babies with him!
Then... me too!
Looks like my life is no longer going back to normal...
...I hope.