Kouta-sama, I love you!
Kouta, I love you! I love you so much!
I love you! I love you! I love you!
Kouta!
Why do I have to clean the yard
this early in the morning?
What a pain.
Huh? Kouta?
You'll never become a
good priest if you don't clean.
Oh, please. I've already told you so many times
that I'm not taking over this shrine.
I just want to live a normal life.
Stare...
What?
I just thought maybe you'd start talking
about working for the government again.
You read me like a book...
Of course! We've always been together,
so I can always tell what you're thinking!
That's true.
Well, breakfast is ready, so you should
come as soon as you're done cleaning.
Got it.
Good morning, onii-chan.
Huh? Where's onee-chan?
No clue.
I'm back! How have you all been,
ladies and gentlemen?!
Huh?
Who's that?
Let me introduce you all to her.
My name is Kudou Mai. Nice to meet you all.
I have come here to help Kouta-sama take
over this Komuri shrine, by making a child.
I'm inexperienced,
but I hope everyone will treat me well.
What?!
Koinaka!
First Love x Cream Pie Sexual Life in the Small Countryside
I don't think this room has
ever been this tense before.
Mio!
Hmph.
Motoka?
Mai, pass the soy sauce, please.
Here you go, Erina-sama.
Thanks!
We'll be commencing the baby-making tonight, okay?
Huh?!
Is that okay with you, Mai Mai?
That is perfectly fine.
I have been training in anticipation of this day.
Huh?!
I'm going to school!
What the heck's going on?
Kouta-sama? Kouta-sama?
Uh, yeah?
Are you alright, Kouta-sama?
Yeah...
That's right, I'm going to have my first time with Mai...
Kouta-sama...
Kouta-sama, please don't think of me as some lewd woman.
M-Mai!
Kouta-sama!
I'll say it again... I don't think this room
has ever been this tense before.
Oh yeah, how'd it go last night?
Did Kouta do it right?
Yes, Kouta-san was very gentle.
It felt like I was the one who
was going to lose my mind.
Mai-san, please, not at the table...
well, not in front of everyone!
Everyone here is special to you,
so I don't think keeping secrets would be good.
Yep, yep.
Kouta, um, you did dirty stuff with Mai-san, huh?
She's already calling you "Kouta-san" instead of "Kouta-sama".
Yes, as his wife, I must obey his wishes,
so I thought it would be fine.
W-W-W-Wife?!
No! You can't be his wife! You can't!
I'm the one who's going to be his wife!
What'd you say?!
Kouta?
This is what Nono looks like naked?!
Geez, what's the matter, Kouta?
S-Sorry.
So, Kouta, um, you know?
I kinda already said it earlier,
but I think I should say it again.
Y-Yeah...
I love you, Kouta.
I love you too.
Yay! I guess you already knew, huh?
Since we're childhood friends,
then we're probably just on the same wavelength.
Let's make a baby together, okay?
Nono!
Yay! I love you, Kouta!
I am God!
Huh?
It might be difficult to believe,
but I am the God that is worshiped at this shrine!
Well, to be precise, I'm currently
inhabiting Okazaki Erina's body.
Right...
The reason I brought Mai Mai here is simple...
World peace!
It's a little exaggeration, but this shrine
is used to disperse the area's evil energy.
That is why all women of the Kudou clan
train from a young age to help the priest.
Oh, I see...
You really buy that story?
With that said, I'd like to begin
Mai Mai's training to become a bride.
Yes! I've already prepared my heart!
I'll do it too!
Well, I kinda saw that coming.
Sure. Not like there are any restrictions
on who can join in on the training.
This might suck for you, but it's
your fault for being so indecisive, Kouta.
What will we be doing during the training?
Put bluntly, you two will be having a lot of sex.
Not just the, vanilla kind, though.
If you don't do some really perverted play,
then it'll have no effect.
Perverted play? That's probably...
I'll do my best!
Me too!
I'll give it my all...
Kouta-san, please violate my body as you wish.
If this isn't what you want, I'm sorry.
I-I never said that...
It's just embarrassing.
Your boobs are just so pretty, I couldn't help myself.
Are you getting turned on, Mai?
I wouldn't get excited just from being
looked at! I'm not that kind of woman!
You need to calm down,
you're not even speaking properly!
Y-Yes! I will. This is beyond embarrassing...
Your breasts are sensitive, huh?
I can't take this...
Light groping just isn't enough for you, right?
You're so mean!
It's not my fault that you're getting
even more turned on from this.
You're trying to keep your voice down?
I can not allow myself to let out such
an obscene voic... I don't want you to hear it!
It's not obscene at all.
I want to hear more of your voice.
No! I really won't be able to hold my voice in!
I want you to let me hear it.
If you say so, Kouta-san, then...
I think it's about time.
It's so hot!
It's still kind of tight.
I'm sorry. It seems I'm still nervous.
I think it's fine if we get used to this little by little.
O-Okay. I will do my best.
What? 69?
Okay, let's try it.
So I get on you like this?
Wait, can't you see everything like this?
Wow, I can't see anything but pussy.
Don't be weird!
Does it turn you on?
It doesn't!
Really? If you keep saying that,
I'll spread your pussy wide open.
No, don't! Geez, even though I told you not to...
Embarrassed?
I'm so embarrassed I could die.
I can see every last detail of your pussy, Nono.
Hey, come on, suck my dick.
Y-Yeah.
I'll make you feel good right now, okay?
Oh right, Nono, let's play the butt game.
Huh? What does that even mean?
I want you to write out what you
want me to do with your butt.
Just this once, okay?
I want you to lick my pussy.
Don't tease me so much!
It's so embarrassing,
but I want to cum! Please, lick my pussy.
Lick it!
No, not my clitoris! Not my clitoris!
Look, now I'm inside you.
Wait, no! Stop moving your finger inside me like that!
I'm gonna cum! Gonna cum! Gonna cum! Gonna cum!
No, don't suck me like that!
You saw me pee...
All right then, go ahead.
Okay, then.
You're much more nervous than I thought you'd be.
To think that you're taking away my body's freedom...
I'm not going that far.
Kouta-san, that was so sudden!
Kouta-san, no... Not there!
Looks like you're already starting to get turned on.
K-K-Kouta-san, don't stop!
Ah... I'm gonna...
Kouta-san... Not there! You can't!
Anywhere but there!
Th-That's a really dirty place!
There are no dirty places on your body, Mai.
K-Kouta-san... No...
Oh my God, no, I...
You really like having your
butt played with, don't you, Mai?
That's not true at all...
That's not a place you're supposed to do it with...
You can't make babies from there!
You say that, but your face looks so happy.
No!
Please, stop!
I didn't think you'd like it this much...
You're so mean, I told you to stop.
Doing it in the classroom really
gets your heart racing, doesn't it?
Yeah, it does.
Am I really going to masturbate here?
Yeah, I really want to see you masturbating here.
F-Fine... I guess I'll do it, then...
Just a little...
Nono, you're really dirty.
No I'm not!
Oh yeah, not at all.
You're just masturbating on your boyfriend's lap.
I'm not too perverted.
I'm really not perverted.
Your dick...
It's erotic, isn't it? Use your juices on it.
You use such vulgar words.
Oh no, I think it's kind of turning me on.
Nono, do you like dicks?
Yeah, but only yours.
I'm imagining you doing me.
How do you usually do it?
I usually do it in front of a mirror, because it's
like you're watching me, so I get really excited.
Oh, really? Do you just look
at your face or your entire body?
I just look at my pussy.
Oh no!
Nono, you're so dirty.
Where are you touching right now?
My clitoris. I'm rubbing it a lot.
I'm dirty. I'm a really embarrassing girl, aren't I?
Your dick is really wet.
It's so slimy.
I'm going to rub your dick against me.
You like rubbing my pre-cum against your pussy, don't you?
No, that's not it!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
No, I'm gonna cum!
The reason I get like this every
night is your fault, Kouta-san.
I haven't even done anything yet,
but you're so wet already.
I've really become...
Such a dirty woman.
Kouta-san! I've been at my limit for a while now!
Then here I go, Mai!
It's going in! Kouta-san...
Kouta-san's dick is going inside me!
Mai, your insides are so hot!
They're so hot and wet!
Your pussy is so dirty.
Getting fucked like this makes
you even hornier, doesn't it?
How unbecoming of you!
Yes, my pussy is dirty!
It's lewd and indecent!
More! I want more!
I want to cum while you're making me happy!
I want a lot of your pleasure inside of me!
It's coming out! It's coming out!
I think I need to have more fun with you.
My butt? No, not there. You can't!
It'll be fine, don't worry.
No, it won't! You can't even make a baby there!
That's even more of a reason to.
You like anal more, don't you?
That's not tru... Wait, don't!
You can't do that!
I can, don't worry! If it's with you, I can do it!
It's in my butt!
Looks like you're in the mood now.
No, my butt...
I can't let my butt feel any better than this...
So you admit that it feels good?
Oh no, my butt feels so good...
You're more turned on when we do it
somewhere babies won't come from, huh?
Doesn't that mean you're looking for pleasure,
rather than to mate?
No, that's not true... That's not tru...
Let's feel even better, okay?
Please, more! More... more of your dick!
Do more dirty things to me with your dick!
Good girl, Mai!
My butt... my butt feels so good! It's so hot!
It feels so weird!
No, something's coming. I feel weird!
I'm cumming!
I love you! I love you!
I love you, Kouta-san.
Hey, Nono.
You're my woman, right, Nono?
Huh? Y-Your woman?
You won't put anything else other than
my dick in your pussy, right? You won't?
Y-Yeah, that's what I was planning to do, why?
I just wanted to hear you say it.
Okay, now face that way.
H-Huh? You mean, towards the camera?
Yep, and in front of God.
You'll do anything for my dick, right?
Y-Yeah, but were already doing it,
do you really need me to say it?
It's fine, but I still want to hear you say it.
I want to hear what your pussy has to say.
If I can only have your dick,
would that make me a retainer to your dick?
Oh, that phrasing is great. It's very hot.
I don't understand you...
You wanted me to say that, right?
Yeah, you know it.
But out here, I...
It's in me again!
You can't just keep hitting the same spot!
Oh my God, it feels so good. It's digging into me!
This is too amazing! You're stirring me up!
The upper part of my pussy feels so good!
Hm? Are you gonna cum?
Yeah, I'm gonna cum!
Your dick just feels too amazing!
Nono, talk dirty to me more.
No, no, I'm gonna cum!
Why did you stop?
No, stop! Let go of your hands.
I'll move by myself...
Yeah, that's good! Just like that!
Okay, now cum!
No, I...
I just need to talk dirty, right?
I'll do it. I'll do it,
so just keep moving your dick, okay?
Say it to the camera, though. Okay?
You're such a sadist, Kouta.
Is this a part of the bridal training?
No, this has nothing to do with that.
I just wanted to make your pussy my own.
I'm telling you, it already is.
Swear that you'll only ever put
my dick in it for the rest of your life.
Rest of my life...
Okay, okay, I get it already!
Is that all you want me to say?
Maybe you could also say "dick hole"
instead of pussy, or something.
Or maybe say you're my pussy slave.
Or maybe say that your pussy
is for Kouta's use only!
No, no, stop!
This is bad, I can't even think of anything right now.
Can you say it?
Yeah, okay, here it goes. "My pussy is your
personal masturbation tool", is that good?
That's it, Nono! You really are talented!
Is that even a compliment?
I get it already! I swear, okay?!
I swear that my pussy will be
for Kouta, and only Kouta's, use.
This will be his wife's pussy. This pussy will
become overjoyed whenever it receives his semen.
Swear to God?
Yeah. Yes, I swear!
I swear to God that this pussy will be
for Kouta's use for the rest of my life.
All right, I'll fuck you really hard,
for the rest of your life!
My pussy feels so good!
Ah, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
Your wife's pussy is...
Cumming!
It's only been a short while since we started,
but how has your training been?
I have been enjoying intercourse with Kouta-san.
Huh? I've already done it with his
slimy dick in the classroom, though.
Well, I had anal sex with him.
My pussy felt so good once
that I... I peed on him!
You two are amazing!
You've exceeded my expectations...
In a good way...
Oh, well, it was nothing...
Well, just carry on like that, okay? Thanks!
Okay.
I... I also love onii-chan!
I'm going to make babies with him too!
What?!
Okay then, I guess me too!
I don't think there's a chance of my
life going back to how it was, ever...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч