Brought to you by KonoHentai
and Shounen-Anime
Kyou-chan
Congratulations on finding a job.
Though, who would have thought you would become a Sensei at my school.
You can say 'Sensei', but I'm just the Sensei for the School Infirmary.
But... are you really okay with this, Aya?
Geez, quit asking me over and over.
Ah... sorry.
We may be separated by age, but doing something like this with a childhood friend you know so well is kind of...
embarrassing isn't it.
It is.
Move your hand.
Kyou-chan you pervert!
We can't have sex like this, right?
Uwah! You said sex!
Kyou-chan that's ero!
Sorry for being 'ero'.
Okay, just a little bit though.
Ah... you're already this wet.
Dummy... the neighbors are going to hear.
So... sorry,
but my voice is coming out.
I never thought Kyou-chan's fingers would make me feel this good.
You're all drenched.
Aya...
See?
You're making it noisy.
No.
You're so cute, Aya.
Kyou-chan!
Aya... Ayaa!
Kyou-chan... Kyou-chaaan!
Put it in...  I can't...
wait...
anymore!
Aya!
Shounen-Anime Presents
Kojin Jugyou
Kyou-chan, you're too rough!
Aya, I can't believe I'm in this kind of relationship with you!
It's no use... you're too tight!
Cumiming!
It's so hot!
That hurt, you know.
Sorry.
I wasn't composed enough to worry about you.
Could it be, that was Kyou-chan's first time?
Yeah.
Hey, did you save your virginity for me?
Dummy, there's no way I would have done that right?
Wanna do it one more time?
School Infirmary
Physical Exam Notification
Sensei! There's some trouble!
Sonoda-san said her stomach was hurting all of a sudden.
Ah, okay take her to that bed.
Leave the rest to me and get back to your classroom.
Please take care of her.
My tummy hurts!
I'm giving birth to Kyou-chan's baby!
You're quite something.
I'm not helping you skip class.
That's mean! I'm not skipping!
Then what are you doing?
Um, you see...
Something like the School Nurse and Girl Student's, Naughty Extracurricular Lesson.
Are you a fool?
Be a good girl and get some sleep.
I've got work to do.
Hey, hey!
I told you I have work to do, right?
Knock it off already.
I'll stop if you have sex with me.
I'm not in that kind of mood right now.
Even though you're like this? You've never have been honest with yourself.
It's starting to feel good for me too.
Come on... Kyou-chan.
Alright, but only once okay?
Yeah! Just one shot, right?
It's okay, Kyou-chan.
My stockings...
tear them.
Okay.
Getting excited?
Dummy.
What the, you're already soaked aren't you.
How about it Aya?
If you want it, give me some cute begging.
Okay, give it to me.
Kyou-chan.
Your dick,
give it to me!
A...Ayaaa!
Dummy, don't be so loud!
That's because Kyou-chan, you're so big.
You're really just too sensitive, Aya.
Kyou-chan.
Hmm?
I wanna be on top.
Okay.
You're tired from work, aren't you Kyou-chan?
I'll do the moving.
Kyou-chan, does it feel good?
Not bad,
but if you don't move with more intensity, you'll never make a middle aged guy like me cum.
No.
Your voice is too loud!
We better quiet your mouth.
More... stab me with your dick Kyou-chan!
I'll do it, so hurry up and come!
So good....  I'm gonna come, I'm gonna come!
I'M COMIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIING!
Say, Kyou-chan...
One more time...
I said one time only, didn't I?
Besides, that was the last rubber.
If that's all, then it'll be fine.
We can recycle it like this, right?
O... oy, Aya!
You know...
Sonoda-san! They said you collapsed during class!?
Ah, Itou-sensei
How is she feeling?
W... well, she's already past the difficult part.
She seems to be coming to the infirmary a lot lately.
As her Homeroom Teacher, it's worrying me sick.
Don't tell me she's faking being ill?
No way, she wouldn't do...
My, she's sweating so much and her face is red too.
She really does look ill doesn't she?
Don't get in my way, you old hag!
I pray that for the rest of your life you never get married!
Never get married! Never get married!
NEVER GET MARRIED!
I got away from the wedding ceremony.
There's no men either.
Ah, my body's so hot I just can't help it!
But... for a frustrated... older woman's... sex drive...
This just... isn't enough!
An erect penis just isn't enough to satisfy me!
Use that manly arm and fuck me with it!
This thickness... this hardness... is so good!
It's so good, so good!
Yes!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm come....
Wh... what do I do!
Ah... no way, it won't come out!
If this stays inside, I'm gonna get looser and looser.
I'll never be able to be fucked by a regular size penis again!
It'll be something like that,
for sure.
No, I'm pretty sure Itou-sensei wouldn't do something like that.
What, you got a thing for that woman?
That's not it.
You really are a jealous person aren't you?
That just shows how much I love you!
Aren't you happy?
I'm happy, but you know...
Ah! I'm gonna run off ahead.
A... Aya!?
Kojin Jugyou
Welcome home!
Would you like to go in the bath first,
or perhaps
you'd... like... me?
Dinner!
There's none!
So lets have sex!
But I'm hungry.
Some exercise will make the food taste better!
Right?
I'm no match for you.
Nobody's gonna get in our way here, so we can do it nice and slow!
Kyou-chan.
No more...
Put it in!
What?
No way, geez.
Pervert.
Say it.
Pl... please,
I want you to plunge your dick into me down there.
Alright then, I'll put on a rubber.
Okay, I'll put it on for you,
Huh, what was that sound just now?
Condom failed.
Eh?
It tore!
That was the last one...
It's alright, if we just do it raw!
I'll go buy some.
What's with you!?
You think pregnacy is a bother so you're just running away?
Coward!
What the!?
I'm fine with whatever Kyou-chan does to me!
I....
I want to feel Kyou-chan inside me directly!
I...
'I' what!?
Because I love you,
and because I treasure you more than anything, I thought we should do things right.
Wh... what?
Ca.. calm down!
I'm gonna go buy some rubbers right now, so just hold on bit!
No way!
I... if you do it like that all of a sudden...
Wa.. wait! I'm... gonna cum!
Let's do it in here next, okay?
I'm sure it'll feel really good.
Are you really okay with this?
Why are you saying that now?
Sorry.
I want Kyou-chan's raw dick in one hard thrust!
You got it, one hard thrust!
Wow, it's twitching so much! Your dick is so hot and throbbing!
You too, you have so many...
I couldn't tell when I was wearing a rubber, I can't believe there's so many creases and folds.
Ah, this is bad, my hips are moving on their own!
Ah, Aya! I love you, Aya!
Kyou-chan!
So good... so good... it feels so good!
So... good... so good... I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come!
Gonna cum!
Shit, is this okay!?
I'm gonna shoot it all into you!
Shoot it! Come as hard as you can!
In my womb,
Kyou-chan, your semen,
SHOOT IT ALL OUT!!
Geez, you came too much!
Kyou-chan.
Yes!
Kyou-chaaaaan!
It's... so good!
It feels so good!
No... don't...
I'm gonna come, I'm gonna come!
Why are you dressed up like that?
I thought you'd be sick of the naked apron.
It surprises even me that I can still fit into my old School Uniform.
Ah, I see.
Kyou-chan, it'll be ready soon so wait a little bit, okay?
Oh YEAH!
Kyou-chan!
Kyou-chan.
AYAAAAAA!!
Geez, silly Kyou-chan,
That was dangerous, I could have stabbed you, you know!
Geez, now I'm the one that's gonna get stabbed!
Aya!
Kyou-chan.
Do you wanna fuck me while I'm in my Sailor Uniform?
I... wanna fuck you!
Can't be helped I guess.
Well then, take your dark lustrous and dangerous weapon, then stab me with it.
It's so thick!
Aya! You feel too damn good!
It's so good! Kyou-chan, your dick is so good!
Aya! Aya!
You're squeezing down on me so tight!
Kyou-chan!
I'm gonna come!
Kyou-chaaaaaan!
So good.... good... good... good!
Good... so good!
Aya!!
I'm gonna come, Kyou-chan!
Kyou-chan!
Kyou-chaaaaaaaaaaaan!
Kyou-chan, I wonder if we'll be okay with me being so bad at cooking?
Yeah.
In exchange, I'll get a lot better at sex!
This was a Free Fansub/Translation brought to you by KonoHentai and Shounen-Anime
If you paid for this translation, then you were ripped off.
If you enjoyed this show, then please help support the creators by purchasing the original DVD.
© 2007 Kino Hitoshi/Core Magazine/Pink Pineapple
Kino Hitoshi is the original creator of the manga this anime was based on.