No Trespassing
I'm a master of the moving private room...
I got addicted to this
job in my last town.
I can't forget those
great days hunting girls.
No, stop it!
Please...
No...
No!
Stop resisting or your
precious pussy will get hurt.
It's a nice view.
Your pink lips are quivering.
This is so embarrassing,
please don't look at it!
Embarrassed? Then why
is your pussy so wet?
No!
Stop it, please!
Her name was Yukiko Muroi.
It was her fate that she
rode my taxi with her boss.
Now suck my dick.
Please don't make me do this.
Do you want me to disclose
your affair with your boss?
Suck harder!
Okay, that's better.
You're doing good...
N-No!
I don't want it.
No!
You filthy bitch!
You must enjoy sucking
your boss's dick, huh?
Please don't push so hard!
What made things even
worse for her was that...
...her younger sister
also got into my taxi.
Thank you so much.
She was pretty, and went
to a famous private college.
But her luck ran out...
when the conversation with
her sugar daddy was recorded.
Now, you sisters show me your asses!
Blackmailing her with the
tape worked out just fine.
She had a sugar daddy, but she
actually hadn't had sex with him yet.
She turned out to be a virgin.
It hurts!
Yukiko!
Hitomi!
Hitomi liked her sister
so much, she became...
...one of my collection.
Are you blackmailing me?
You shouldn't have left such
an important thing behind.
Fine.
If you promise not to hurt Natsumi,
you can do anything you want to me.
She was a famous model,
Katsumi Housho.
It was her fault, leaving behind a picture
of her having sex with her girlfriend...
...Natsuko Takamizawa, a daughter
from an upper class family.
You both look great.
But I assume neither of you
has experienced sex with men.
No, stop it!
Don't do it so hard!
It feels good...
Natsuko!
Don't worry, I'll do you next.
Oh no!
You beast!
You lesbians, I'll make you
unable to live without men.
No, please, I beg you.
Man, a virgin's pussy is really tight.
No!
Since I'm such a generous man, I
share my hunted girls with my buddies.
Don't put it in!
Pull it out, please!
So I have a lot of good
memories from my last town.
An abandoned school building...
I can expect a lot of fun in this town.
No Trespassing
This building will be demolished soon.
Not in Service
Great, I will use this
building until it's demolished.
I hope there are a lot of
pretty ladies in this town.
There are a lot of girls in
uniforms around the station.
There must be many
all-girl colleges in town.
What a pretty lady she is!
She's a student of Seika College...
...which is famous for its
refinement and has a long tradition.
What?
Rena, come quickly or I'll leave you.
Wait for me, Sena!
Don't be mean.
Hmm, gorgeous twin
sisters, Rena and Sena.
I'll keep that in mind.
I wonder if their privates are
as identical as their faces...
Well, that's all for my
market research for today.
I already picked the targets...
I'm looking forward to hunting them.
What?
Could you go to Kotobuki town?
Kotobuki town?
Yes.
She looks so lovely and gracious.
Hello.
Yes, at the archery room at Seika
College after school tomorrow.
What about getting
together around 3:30 PM?
That's right.
In the locker room, yes.
Seika College...
In the locker room of the archery room...
That's good to know.
Why do I always say "yes"?
Sorry?
Excuse me.
You look exhausted, are you okay?
Can you tell?
Yes, I have a lot of experience
with customers in this taxi.
I see.
I guess I'm trying to do
something beyond my ability.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean...
So, are you going to go shopping
in Kotobuki town to relax?
No, I just like being in the crowd...
So you can take your
mind off things, huh?
Yes.
Wait a second.
Sometimes, doing something
really wild can be refreshing.
Well, thank you.
It seems that she can't
stand pressure from others.
She looks so helpless.
It should be fun to follow her.
She seems really nervous.
What's going on?
What is she trying to do?
Let me prepare the camera just in case.
The driver told me that I
should do something wild...
Then, I can relax...
How could I expect this?
This is great, Miss Satsuki...
Who would've thought that
an honor student like her...
...would be shoplifting.
I'll teach you how to pay for
the crime you're committing.
This is a great source for blackmail.
My next target is this
lovely girl, Satsuki.
Now that I know her schedule,
her future is decided.
Archery Club
Today's game depends on you.
Good luck!
Don't put pressure on me, besides,
it's just a practice game anyway.
How could you say that?
Whether it's practice or
not, we're going to win!
Okay
I'll do my best.
You should be more
careful, Miss Satsuki...
You have to be on guard even
while talking to your friends.
Hmm?
What's the matter, Satsuki?
I feel like someone is peeping at us.
Stop it, that's not funny!
You're right, sorry.
Maybe because I'm nervous.
Yeah, it must be so.
Actually, Miss Satsuki's
sixth sense is quite keen.
What a find, indeed!
It looks like she needs a ride.
It was worth staking out.
Could you go to Junasan?
Yes, Miss.
You were great today, you must be tired.
Thanks.
But not as good as you were.
I envy you. I wish I could be like you.
You're a straight A
student and a great athlete.
You're exaggerating, I'm not that great.
It doesn't matter, you
make me feel miserable.
By the way, I've always
wanted to ask you this...
Do you have boyfriend?
What?
Come on, you can tell me!
No, I don't have a boyfriend.
Really? So what do you do to relax?
Oh, I know, what about this?
Cigarette?
No, I don't smoke.
I'll give you one, give it a try.
You might like it.
That's not a smart move.
Even under peer pressure,
you shouldn't smoke.
Thanks for opening the window.
Smoke your cigarette now, Satsuki.
Okay...
Well.
I think it's the time to
use my hidden camera now.
This is so bitter!
I'm glad that I had a CCD
camera installed inside the car.
Here is Junasan.
Thank you.
Sorry, dessert is on me, okay?
Pictures of the honor
student smoking a cigarette...
I'm sure these will come in handy.
I think I have enough sources
to blackmail my target.
Now I just wait for my chance
near Miss Satsuki's house...
Hmm?
It's Miss Satsuki.
Could you go to Satellite Hotel?
Yes, Miss.
I'm in a bit of hurry.
I'll do my best.
Please hold on tight.
Thank you.
Yes, hello?
Oh, Father.
Yes, I'm taking a taxi.
Yes, I have the
envelope from your study.
No, I didn't look inside.
I see, she's bringing the
documents for her father.
But why doesn't her father want
his daughter to look at them?
I warned you before...
to hold on tight.
What happened?
No, nothing, I'm fine.
I asked the driver to drive fast.
She's so kind...
She's covering my backside...
Oh no, I dropped them on the ﬂoor.
Please make sure you pick them all up...
I'm too busy driving,
and concentrating on...
keeping the one sheet
that ﬂew under my foot.
Thank you so much.
You're very welcome.
Sorry for my reckless driving.
Well, let me take a look
at the sheet you left here.
The list of the clients
of the father's company...
This must be confidential
company information.
I've waited for you.
Thank you for using my taxi.
Have you waited for me?
Actually, I have something I
want to show you, Miss Satsuki.
How do you know my name?
This is...
I printed out frames from the video...
but they look pretty nice, don't they?
How did you...
And take a look at this one, too.
No...
This is some kind of mistake.
I think you have enough money.
You like the rush you get, don't you?
No!
That's not true, I just
wasn't myself on that day.
It's not a good excuse, Miss.
Oh, I've got this one, too.
Even though under peer pressure, you
shouldn't have smoked a cigarette.
I didn't want to do
that, but my friend was...
No, you shouldn't put
the blame on your friend.
And I've got something
more scandalous, Miss.
T-This is...
my father's document...
How did you get this?
Oh no...
Was it when you hit the brakes?
Yes, you're right, Miss.
Everything went as planned.
This is horrible! Who are you?
All the things you've seen are
copies, I have the originals.
Do you know what I mean?
A-Are you blackmailing me?
What do you want?
Money?
No, that's not what I want.
What I want is ownership
of you, Miss Satsuki.
No...
If you don't want to,
that's fine with me.
I'll just make these things public.
If you do that...
I'm sure this will be a big scandal
for you and the people around you.
Fine, I'll do anything you want.
You can have me, but promise
that you'll burn them all.
That's fine with me. I promise.
Now call your family, and tell
them you won't be home for a while.
Mother? This is Satsuki.
I forgot to tell you
that I have archery camp.
I won't be home for a while.
Thank you.
Talk to you later.
Is this fine?
A boot camp, huh? It's not so
far from what we'll be doing.
Yes, that's fine.
Here we are.
What's this place?
This is my home and the
place I store my collection.
Your collection?
Yes, you're a Bambi I've hunted.
I can treat you however I want.
No, stop.
Don't trouble me, Miss. You no
longer have the right to resist me.
No, stop it.
You look so good with a collar on, Miss.
Take this off!
Please let me go, I don't want
to stay here another second.
I can't let you go yet.
I just hunted you down, I
haven't even tasted you yet...
I can't breathe...
This is a good view, Miss.
Please don't...
No, not there!
Please stop it!
Didn't I tell you that
I haven't tasted you yet?
This school building
is old but well built.
Feel free to cry and
scream, no one will hear you.
No, I won't cry.
I see, you're a big girl.
It makes things more interesting.
You make me want to
make you cry and scream.
What are you going to do?
Don't be afraid, I won't hurt you.
Actually, it's quite the opposite.
You really are a big girl.
Usually girls beg for me to stop.
It's also strange that...
your pussy is getting wet
under these circumstances.
That's not true.
Is that so?
Let me find out...
What are you doing?
No, don't look!
Please don't look!
But I ought to find out the truth.
No!
See? It's wet.
So wet that it's
dripping from my fingers.
No, that's not true!
That's not true!
If you say so, it may be my mistake.
Let me look at your pussy closer.
No, don't make me do this.
I can see your pussy
closely from this position.
Please don't look, I'm begging you!
What's that?
This is a special ointment
for making you relax.
No!
I wonder how long you can stand this.
What's the matter, Miss?
N-Nothing.
You shouldn't try to hold it,
it's not good for your health.
What's that?
No, please stop it.
Please don't put it in!
But Miss, I can't help it.
Your body is being honest.
No.
It's going in deeper and deeper.
It seems like you're feeling good, too.
No, I'm not!
No.
Look at this, you're all wet.
No, it's dirty.
Don't lick there!
Yeah, let me hear you scream.
Please forgive me.
Forgive you? I'm not punishing you.
I'm just making feel you good,
that's why your pussy is so wet.
It doesn't make me feel good at all.
Well then...
I'll make you feel better.
No...
Stop it!
No!
It is my task to give you pleasure.
I'm putting it in...
It hurts.
It hurts!
You're hurting me!
Your pussy is so tight! It feels
like it's chewing on my dick.
It hurts!
It hurts.
But you're feeling good, aren't you?
Your nipples are already so hard.
No!
Don't grab them so hard!
What are you talking about?
It's your pussy that's
squeezing my dick so tight.
This is great!
You're breaking me.
Oh, Miss I'm coming inside your pussy
I'll fill it!
No!
My pussy and my butt are so hot.
You're doing good for
your first time, Miss.
Please someone help me...
No!
Do you understand where
you stand now, Miss?
You don't have to worry
about frivolous things.
Until I'll see you again, take care.
Well.
Let me start the hunt again.
These twin sisters
will be my next target.
They'll be a good
addition to my collection.