This city is filed with taxis.
A taxi is like a moving private room.
No, stop it, Hirohito.
No.
Your husband is gone now.
We don't have to worry
about him anymore.
Whatever you say whatever you do, you
can keep it secret inside of a taxi.
People have that kind of
illusion when they use taxis.
Come on...
I can't wait for it anymore.
Not here, no.
No...
Everything went as we planned.
Nobody's in our way now.
In this place, people easily
open up their mind...
...and say things they could
never say to other people.
We're on the way to his
memorial service now.
This feels so good.
In this place people even have sex.
They totally forget that there's a man
who overhears all of their conversations.
Thank you for riding.
Oh well...
Since I've already set
my mind on my next target...
...I'll let you guys go.
Sex Taxi Victim 3
A Hunted Swimmer: Misaki
Misaki Manabe.
It's your time to be hunted
as part of my collection.
Oh, she's just finished
her club activity.
What a coincidence. She
must have read my mind.
Please get in.
Can you go downtown to near Ginjo
Station?
Yes, Miss.
Hello. This is Misaki.
Oh, Tani.
Yes, I know.
Yes, but I...
The swimming trials as tomorrow, but...
I know I can't beat her.
If I lose tomorrow, I'll be off the
regular team and will never return to it.
I already made up my mind.
No, I don't mean that...
Yes.
Thank you for saying so...
What?
Well, if she doesn't get a good
score, I can be a member of the team.
Yes.
What? No way.
I'll talk about that,
when we meet later.
Yes.
Hmm, I smell something fishy...
Interesting.
We're downtown.
Where shall I pull over?
Yes, over there.
One more person will hop in there.
Yes, Miss.
What are you looking at?
Ah, no, I didn't mean to.
Here comes your friend.
Hey.
Thank you for coming.
I know you're busy.
That's OK.
Can you go around the castle
ruin and come back here?
Yes.
I really appreciate
what you've done for me.
Cheer up, Misaki.
I know you're a talented swimmer.
Your record has got better and better.
But I can't beat that new girl.
I told you.
Before the trials, in the
locker room, you should...
No, I can't do such a thing.
Come on. You have no choice.
Hey, after the trials, why
don't we do some extra training together?
You know, we have to beat other
rivals until the final trials.
You mean you'll give me extra training?
Of course, I'll do
anything for you, Misaki.
Thank you so much.
"I'll do anything for you", huh?
It's too obvious that
he just wants her body.
But things are getting
more interesting for me.
A trick for her rival before the trials
and the extra training after the trials.
Miss Satsuki, have you
gotten used to this life?
Let me get out of
here right now, please!
You still have an attitude, don't you?
Haven't you done enough of
this? Now please let me go.
I don't think I can do that.
It's totally up to me
whether you can go or not.
Let me go!
Then, you'd better lose
your attitude toward me.
It's not good for your health,
if you don't eat enough food.
I have to punish you for
trying to escape from me.
What are you going to do?
Stop it.
I put a lot of love drug on the dildo.
You're going to be
horny all night tonight.
Soon you'll be begging me to fuck you.
Be my pretty slave.
It's hot, it's burning inside me.
Pull it out!
I'll come back later to
see how you are doing.
Gym Storage Room
How're you doing, both of you?
I can't stand it here
anymore. Let us go home!
Hm, you look like you're feeling down.
What's the matter?
Anyone would be depressed
after the things you did to us!
That's not a good thing to hear.
Why don't we go out
today to change the mood?
Go outside?
Yeah, let's go for a little drive.
But before that...
What's this?
You have to wear these clothes.
Now what are you gonna
do to us in this place?
To meet some new people.
People who are
interested in meeting you.
Here they come.
Welcome all.
Who are you?
Who the hell are you guys?
Huh, what cuties they are!
W-What do you want?
Come here.
No.
S-Sena!
Get off me!
Wow it's amazing. They
really do look alike.
No, don't touch me!
No!
So, how do you like them?
They're some hot looking
chicks. Can we really fuck them?
Of course.
No, stop it!
Stop it!
Guys, let's get started!
No!
Stop it!
Sena!
No.
No, I don't want it...
Please stop it!
No, don't touch me.
Get off me!
Huh, they speak too much.
Shut them up.
That's right, put your dicks
deep into their throats.
Sena, keep moving your hands!
Don't forget fucking them.
How are they?
Don't they have the tightest pussies?
Release your come inside their pussies.
Huh, what animals they are!
Both must have well stuffed bellies.
Hmm? Too exhausted to speak?
Then sleep tight.
I'll come back to see
how you guys are doing.
Huh, really?
Then, he goes something like...
What happened next?
Locker Room
Before the trials, in the
locker room, you should...
Oh, here comes Misaki.
This is perfect timing.
What is she doing?
I bet that's the swim suit of her rival.
I captured the crucial moments!
Misaki, go for it!
You can do it!
Go!
Go, Misaki!
Yeah! Misaki!
She doesn't like the result, huh.
Let's go!
Go! Go!
You can do it!
You're almost there!
Oh, no!
A-ha! I got it.
It seems that Misaki's
rival fell into her trap.
But it was careless of her
to let me know her plan.
Misaki.
Tani.
Did you wait long?
Here comes the string-puller.
The planned accident worked so well.
But I regret what I did.
Don't worry, nobody knows about this.
Do you really think so?
They have no clue that
someone is watching them.
Oh no, Tani.
Don't worry, nobody's here.
I don't think you call that training.
Tani.
Oh no.
Not there...
I made sure that everybody left here.
But...
You're so pretty, Misaki.
No, not there...
No, Tani, please...
It's not a big deal.
Let's have fun a little.
Oh no.
Let me capture the
second crucial moment.
Wait, Tani.
I think someone's here.
No way.
Tani, I want to have sex with
you after the trials are finished.
So please wait a little longer.
Misaki...
I got it, I won't do anything today.
Thank you.
Let me change my clothes.
I'll wait for you at the gate.
Yes.
I have two sources to
blackmail you so far.
If I can get one more source...
Three strikes, and you'll be mine.
Here comes Tani.
Let me get you in my taxi immediately
I've waited for this moment.
I have company Can you
wait here for a while?
Yes.
Thank you for waiting, Tani.
Hey, hop in, I'll take you home.
Thank you.
Can you go to Kotobuki-city?
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Tani.
That's OK, never mind.
Do you think they'll
think it was an accident?
You worry too much.
But...
...I don't think this will
work at the final trials.
OK. So we'll make sure the
newcomer will never be selected.
That sounds impossible...
At the final trials, the coach has
the power to make the final decision.
But the coach doesn't like my
performance.
But what if the coach and the new
girl have a scandalous affair?
But there's no such affair...
Yeah, but what will happen if they were
together in front of a sleazy motel?
We'll make up any reason to have
them to meet in front of the motel.
But...
I'll ask the coach to come thee.
You'll ask her to come.
The meeting place will
be in front of the motel.
Yeah, got it?
We'll take picture of the
crucial moment.
But will it work out?
Why don't we give it a shot?
If it doesn't work,
we'll find another way.
Y-Yes...
Huh, they think like I do.
But I don't care whether
you guys will succeed or not.
The conversation you
just had is enough for me.
It'll be at 7 o'clock tomorrow.
So it's about the time...
Huh, she's on time as they planned.
Can you go to Motel
Alley in Kaminari city?
Yes.
Hi Tani?
Yes, I asked her to come there.
But I kind of feel bad.
I asked the coach to come, too.
Maybe he's had feelings for her.
I really don't feel good about this,
I think we should cancel this plan.
Don't be chicken.
With the pictures, we can
have the coach fired...
...and she'll never be
selected as a team member.
No, Tani, let's cancel this plan.
What the matter with you?
I'll meet you later, don't be late. Bye.
Tani, wait!
What's this place?
Congratulations on your success
trapping your rival, Misaki.
What?
What are you talking about?
I have something to show you.
And I have more.
What do you want?
I want you to be part of my collection.
Are you nuts?
Pervert!
I suppose you will be deep in
trouble, if I disclose these pictures.
Yeah, right. Only in your dreams.
I'm not kidding.
To help you understand the situation
here, these pictures are just copies.
I keep the originals.
At the final trials, the coach has the
power to make the final decision.
But the coach doesn't like my
performance.
But what if the coach and the new
girl have a scandalous affair?
But there's no such affair...
Yeah. But what will happen if they were
together in front of a sleazy motel?
So what do you want?
As I told you. I want you
to be part of my collection.
Would you call your family to tell
them you won't be home for a while?
Or do you want me to
disclose these pictures?
I-I understand.
You'll stay here.
What is this place?
I'm worried that you might
get away from me.
If you're scared,
get me out of here!
Who's the one who's scared?
Huh, say it again!
That's OK.
I'll teach you how you to have now!
You're sick! What are
you going to do to me?
No, stop it.
Don't touch me!
It makes you feel good to be
touched by fingers, doesn't it?
No, stop it!
Don't touch there!
Where's "there"?
Oh, for instance, do you
mean this cute red clit?
No.
Huh, what happened to the tomboy?
Why don't you resist me some more?
Get away from me!
See, your pussy is getting wet.
I'll rub your clit down more...
...until it's sore.
No, no.
Stop.
You couldn't hold it, huh?
I-I'm...
It must be damn good that you peed here.
No, it's not.
Stop it.
Oh, no need to lie to me.
Look. You wet all over
the chairs and the floor.
No, it's not true!
Oh yeah?
So why is your pussy having a spasm?
No!
Don't lick there!
No, not there...
This is delicious, Misaki.
Especially since your
clit has a great flavor.
Don't say that!
Stop it!
No!
Don't touch it anymore!
I see. I know what you mean.
Then, let's do the next step.
Stop! Don't come near me.
You still want to resist me?
Go ahead.
But the more you resist,
the more you feel despair.
No, no!
Oh, that's not good.
Swallow my dick deep into your throat.
Lick it all over with your tongue.
Yeah, that's it. It's getting better.
It's so warm inside of your mouth.
I like it, so I forgive you.
I can't take it anymore! No!
I see.
Then, I'll give you what you want most.
No!
This is tighter than I thought.
I thought Tani already
made your pussy loose...
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!
Does it happen to be your fist time?
Don't move.
Stop it!
Pull it out!
Yeah, I'd like to pull this out
but your pussy is stuck around my dick.
So I can't.
Don't push hard!
Don't push!
Well, I'm coming now.
Do you want me to come inside
or outside of your pussy?
Not inside!
Outside!
I see. Then, I'll come
inside of your pussy.
No.
I'll never forgive you for this.
I'll tear you into pieces.
Go ahead.
Suit yourself, if you can.
Rest yourself until
your next time comes.
Damn you!
Well, let me start hunting now.
The next target is a cheerleader, Yuki.