This city is filled with taxis.
A taxi is like a moving private room.
This is just a first-aid
treatment for your upset stomach.
So stay still.
Whatever you say, whatever you do, you
can keep it secret inside of a taxi.
People have those kind of
fantasies when they use taxis.
You don't need to go to see a doctor.
Soon you'll get better and return
to practice with the others.
Coach.
I...
Your pussy smells damn
good and is soaking wet.
People open up easily inside of a taxi.
I feel strange.
If you have my dick inside of you,
your stomachache will be gone.
I've always wanted to
be like this with you...
Sometimes people even
have sex inside of taxis.
They completely forget about the
man sitting right in front of them.
I'm coming!
Thank you for riding.
One two, one two, one two...
My targets are Rena and
her twin sister, Sena.
I smell something scandalous is
going on with this tennis club.
Sex Taxi, Victim 2, Hunting
for the twins: Rena and Sena
Until the Uchiyama sisters get out of
class, I'll have a look at my collection.
Laboratory
Have you been a good girl, Satsuki?
Are you going to do
you-know-what to me again?
Have I ever done anything to hurt you?
All I teach you is how to feel pleasure.
Don't come near me.
Go away!
The more you refuse, the
more I want to come closer.
No!
Why are you doing this to me?
Because you're so pretty
I want to get you dirty.
Look, your pussy is getting wet again.
You're so nasty!
Let's see which one of us nasty.
See, your pussy is wet and quivering.
Please don't look at me!
You look like you want something.
No...
Stop it.
Don't touch there.
My fingers are already wet...
Let me take a look inside that pussy.
It hurts! Don't put
your fingers in there.
You must be feeling good though...
...because the inside of
your pussy is soaked.
No, don't say such a thing.
I'm not feeling good!
Despite what you say, your pussy
is sucking my fingers right in.
You want me to stir the
inside of your pussy?
It's time for your fucking.
What are you doing?
No, stop it!
No...
It hurts.
It's too hard.
It tightening around my dick.
What a tight pussy you have!
No, you're gonna break me!
I'm letting it all go
into your pussy, Miss!
No!
It's inside of my body...
No...
That wasn't so bad, was it, Miss?
Please somebody help me...
No!
Well, let me go back to hunting now.
Oh, here comes Rena and Sena.
Good, I didn't even
have to look for them.
Can you go to Ginjo Station?
Yes, Miss.
The girl from class B
you told me about before?
Oh, the one with longish
hair and a pierced left ear?
Yes, she said she didn't like me.
I see. Rena is the quiet type,
so other girls pick on her.
She speaks behind my back,
and does mean things to me.
Are you serious?
I thought she was acting
strange in front of me.
Today she hid my gym pants.
So I had to wear shorts...
She's pretty and gentle. No wonder
some girls are envious of her.
How could she do that to Rena?
I won't forgive that bitch!
Here we are.
She's getting off here for a minute.
Sena?
Just wait for me outside.
It'll be just a minute.
Okay...
Can you close the door?
Is this okay?
Thank you.
Hello, it's me, Sena.
Can you see me tomorrow?
Meet me at the park next to
campus during lunch bleak tomorrow.
Anyhow, I'll see you tomorrow.
I see Sena is a woman of action.
Does that have something
to do with Rena's story?
Well...
Are you getting off?
Can you open the door?
Yes.
Rena, hop in, let's change the plan.
How come?
Come in quickly.
What's wrong?
Have you kept anything from me
besides that story you just told me?
What?
I know you have.
Like, a boyfriend...
It seems Rena has mole problems.
A boyfriend? No way.
I can tell you've been keeping
something from me. Spill it, Rena.
Don't be mean, Sena.
You must keep this secret, okay?
Actually, a boy told me
that he has a crush on me.
I knew it!
But I haven't answered him yet.
Today I'm supposed to meet him
behind Junasan at 7:00, then...
Hmm...
Junasan
If what she said is true, Rena must
be here with her boyfriend candidate...
I'm just asking you
why you're doing this.
Well, because I like Rena...
Don't call her "Rena,"
like you know her!
That's Sena.
Don't yell at me.
First of all, why is
her younger sister here?
She's too nice to say no, and I don't
want you taking advantage of her.
That's not what I want to do.
Anyway, Rena will never go out with you.
I won't give you permission, okay?
Why do I need permission from you?
You have no right!
Oh, I got it...
I guess it's picture time.
Shut the hell up!
I won't let Rena go out with anybody!
What's the problem with you?
Wait a minute, are
you in love with your...
This is my first source for blackmail.
Now I can see the whole picture.
Sena loves Rena, not with
sisterly love but as a woman.
A forbidden love, eh?
This will be a tasty
source for blackmail...
But I'll need a couple more sources before
I add both twins to my collection.
Wait for me.
Why did you dress me like this
and bring me to the archery room?
What are you going to do?
As I expected, you're brave in uniform.
That's very good.
What are you doing?
I love to see a brave woman lose
her power to resist gradually...
That's the essence of destruction.
How do you feel about being
raped in the archery room?
No. Stop it!
For you, this could be
the nightmare of reality.
But for me, this is nothing but fun.
Stay still or you'll get hurt.
Why are you doing this to me?
The reason is simple.
I want to destroy you. That's all.
Open your legs.
Oh, your pussy is pink and looks
so soft. It must be delicious.
Don't say such an embarrassing thing.
Please don't look...
Please!
It seems that your body is being honest.
You must be getting excited, huh?
No, that's not true!
Well, let me check it out.
No!
Would you like it if your
pussy became a target?
How would you like a
bow inside your pussy?
No, no, no!
What kind of girl are you?
Getting excited by putting
such a thing into your pussy...
No, that's not true!
I'm not that kind of...
What are you saying?
Your wet pussy has a bow inside.
Stop it!
Why are you doing this to me?
Oh, I get it. Instead of
the bow, you want my arrow.
Please forgive me.
You should learn to say
what you really want.
So how's this?
Your pussy and clit are red and hard.
You must want me really bad.
No, stop it!
You're going to break me!
Your pussy is so warm.
Your soft pussy is sucking my dick.
No, pull it out!
Pull it out, please!
Your wet pussy feels so good.
Now, let me fuck you hard.
No, I don't want it!
Please don't do it so hard!
Please, no!
What do you mean?
Your pussy is so wet and you feel good.
Your pussy is pushing away my dick.
Maybe I toyed with your pussy too much.
No, I can't take this any more!
If your pussy is getting a little
tired, I could use your back door...
Not any more...
You reached your limit, haven't you?
Then, I will save the back
door for your next punishment.
Feel desperate for my come.
I think I've broken your
will to escape from me by now.
Now, I can concentrate on
the hunt for my next target.
Soon it'll be lunch break.
I know everything
about this college now.
Sena's volleyball club
is going running outside...
...as Rena's tennis
club returns to school.
Sena's friend that she called
yesterday will show up soon.
The one talking to Sena must
be the person who bullies Rena.
Do you think I'll
believe such an excuse?
That's Sena, I'm not
surprised by her short temper
Wait a second, I really
didn't do anything!
Shut up! Your friends
told me it really happened.
There's no way you can
convince me that you didn't.
I'm sorry.
It's too late!
It's your bad luck
you picked my sister!
What a tomboy she is!
I don't think Rena
knows this side of Sena.
I bet she'll give me
more good material today.
So how are you gonna pay for this?
Here comes my chance.
No!
But even if this is for your beloved Rena,
I don't think violence is a good idea.
Though it works fine for me...
Sena looks down today. Did they
have a quarrel or something?
You were called to the adviser’s office.
What did your adviser tell you?
It sounds like it's not a quarrel.
Hmm, some stuff about me.
Because I don't behave like
you, they have a problem with me.
No way! You're a good student.
No one should have a problem with you.
Thanks.
Stop crying
I'm glad you think so.
Yeah...
But my adviser will come to our
house after school to check up on me.
That's so unfair.
That means they didn't
trust you from the start.
What can I do? I have
to deal for a while.
Oh, it sounds like she got
a warning from the school.
Sena.
What?
I have to stay on campus
late for practice today.
Oh, is that so?
I'll be back by nine.
Okay, I see.
I can't ignore Rena's words
that she'll stay on campus late.
It was a heart-warming moment
when Rena cheered up Sena...
...but I just can't forget
Rena's face in the mirror.
She had looked as if her loved
one had been hurt by someone.
I shouldn't take my eyes off Rena today.
That's Rena.
She looks very determined,
it's unusual for her.
I'm glad that I brought
high-quality camera.
What do you know about Sena?
I won't forgive anybody
who tries to hurt Sena!
What a surprise!
She's taking such bold
action for Sena's sake!
My Sena is different from what
you think. Totally different!
How could I miss this precious moment?
My Sena, she said...
It sounds like she
loves Sena as a woman.
Mom, Dad, take good care of yourselves.
Don't worry about us,
we'll manage everything.
Ciao!
Bye bye!
Your parents have just
left for an overseas trip?
Who are you?
Too bad you don't remember
me, but I know you very well.
Oh yeah, you're the
taxi driver from before.
What can we do for you?
Could you take a look at these pictures?
Is this Sena?
No way! You're a good student.
Is this you, Rena?
You don't want me to make
these pictures public, do you?
I think both of you
understand the situation.
Don't treat Rena roughly!
You should know that you aren't
in any position to order me around.
Sena!
What's that look?
Don't annoy me!
Stop it, please!
Don't hurt Sena.
I'll do anything you want.
Please, I beg you.
R-Rena.
Rena, you're very kind.
Okay, I'll fuck you both together.
Sena, take off Rena's panties.
How could I?
Didn't you hear me?
I said "Take them off!"
No!
I'm sorry, Rena.
Are you happy now?
Please let Rena go!
It's nice and pink, is
Sena's as pretty as yours?
Don't look at me!
Look at her pussy, Rena's
pussy is getting wet.
I think she's feeling good.
Stop it!
I don't wanna hear
such a disgusting thing!
Let us go now!
Obey my orders!
Put your finger into Rena's wet pussy.
No.
Hurry UP!
You'll never know what will
happen if you disobey my orders.
I'm sorry, Rena.
N-No...
Rena,
Please don't do that...
You're doing fine.
Now Sena, take off your panties now.
That's right. If you're a good
girl, we both can have fun.
Now, get on top of Rena.
And eat her pussy,
lick it from the bottom.
Don't stop your hand, move your finger.
Oh no...
Rena, do the same to Sena.
No, Rena...
Oh, no.
You girls both love it, don't you?
Rena!
The raving nymphomaniac
twins need more discipline.
No.
Doesn't it feel good?
Isn't it great to lose your virginity
while your sister is looking at you?
You're tearing me up!
Rena, don't stop licking her clit.
Y-Yes...
S-Sena.
No!
Help me!
Rena!
S-Sena.
You're next.
No, stop it!
Please, I beg you!
I didn't know that there was a
difference between twin pussies.
Don't do it so hard!
Rena has a pussy with
an abrasive surface.
Pull it out!
Sena's pussy was mole slick...
But Rena has a good pussy, too.
Stop it, please!
You reached your limit? But
I haven't given it to you yet.
W-What?
My Sperm!
No!
I've held it for a long
time, I can't stop my come...
Something's coming into me.
It's hot.
No...
Why us?
No, stop it...
Don't do this to us any more.
Two twins at once...
There's no greater happiness
than this unbelievable pleasure.
You were delicious, both of you.
See you later.
Well, it's time to go back to hunting.