This city is filed with taxis.
A taxi is like a moving private room.
If I keep my mouth shut, this
will stay as an internal matter.
He hasn't gotten promoted yet, has he?
Whatever you say whatever you do, you
can keep it secret inside of a taxi.
People have that kind of
illusion when they use taxis.
This is the price you should pay
I'm also frustrated with
getting moved to this town.
Yeah, that's good.
No, please don't go there.
Please.
It won't take long.
I need some stress relief
after chasing that pervert.
In this place people
easily open up their mind...
...and say things they
could never say to other people.
We're on duty now, aren't we?
This is a part of your duty.
And this is for your own good.
In this place people even have sex.
No...
We shouldn't...
This is so good.
This is good, so good.
They totally forget that there's a man
who overhears all of their conversations.
Sex Taxi, Victim 4
A Hunted Cheerleader: Yuki
Yuki Natsume.
What a cute cheerleader!
Even her pictures cheer me up.
It's time to hunt you.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, Leiho!
Yuki is the swan among the ducks.
They're practicing so hand that nobody
notices I'm taking pictures of them.
Huh, this stain must be...
Even though she has cramps,
she looks cheerful and alive.
That's my girl, Yuki.
She's a big girl, isn't she?
This is such a precious shot.
Good I made it.
Can you go downtown in Kaminari-city?
Yes, Miss.
She looks like she is feeling down.
What's on your mind, Yuki?
We're in downtown.
Are you getting off here?
That's him!
He wears a black hat and a black jacket.
Are you supposed to meet him?
Um...
Please pick him up.
Yes, Miss.
You found me easily?
You wear a black hat and a black jacket.
I guess not many men
wear clothes like this.
They seem to be total strangers.
Well, this is what we talked about.
Yeah, that's right.
What is she giving him?
I'm so curious.
Wow, this is great!
Anyway, what surprises me is that...
...such a pretty girl like you can
sell this stuff on the internet.
Hmm, I smell something fishy here.
I suppose I should prepare my camera.
Wow!
The camera angle of this
picture is really good.
How did you shoot this?
I set the timer for the
camera in a locker...
Hmm, I see.
He's embarrassingly excited.
In contrast to him,
Yuki looks like she's in pain.
She doesn't look like a girl
who can do this kind of business.
Well, I have to go now.
Oh yeah.
It's a deal.
Is this okay?
I suppose I should get my camera ready.
That's not very nice, Yuki...
You're not supposed to take pictures of
your fellow cheerleaders and sell them.
Well, for me this is just what I wanted.
So can I buy some more?
Yes, use the internet
auction site again.
Can you go to Kaminari-city?
Yes.
What are you doing, Yuki?
I know you want some
money you can spend.
But this is not what a good
cheerleader is supposed to do.
You got a phone call, Yuki.
Hello.
I'm in a taxi now.
What?
But we have plenty of
time before the clue date...
The clue date?
Plenty of time?
She looks so upset.
So he'll come by tomorrow evening?
Back home?
Around 7?
Okay.
I'll get back home as quickly as I can.
No, Mom, I won't let you
handle this by yourself.
OK.
Huh, tomorrow at 7?
Who will show up at your home?
It seems her family has a problem.
Thank you for riding.
This is her home.
Now I know where she lives.
Oh, wow, that pervert left
a little present for me.
Nothing is better than
this to comer my target.
Well, tomorrow I'll check out Yuki.
Until then I'll take care of
my precious collection.
It's best to take care
of them frequently.
No, stop it!
What are you gonna do?
You must be lonely after
being by yourself all the time.
I'll introduce you to the other girls.
Now, hurry up!
Move!
Don't pull me so hand!
Here he comes again...
Who's she?
Are you OK?
Her name is Satsuki Shiina.
These are twin sisters,
Rena and Sena Uchiyama.
You've been doing brutal
things to other girls too?
Huh, "brutal" is a
strong word, isn't it?
Well, I guess you can describe
the situation in that way
I can't believe this.
You're some kind of a
monster, not a human being.
I didn't introduce you guys
to have this conversation.
No, you'll rape us again?
I'll take you guys
out to have fun today.
Hey!
This is our home?
That's right.
Since your parents are abroad now...
...we'll have a welcoming
party for Satsuki here.
If you don't obey me, you know
what will happen to you, right?
No!
Well, Rena and Sena.
Both of you, make Satsuki feel good.
Otherwise...
What do you want me to do?
Don't you forget that I have
scandalous secrets about all of you.
Sena, give Miss Satsuki pleasure.
No, please stop it.
I'm sorry.
Forgive us.
No.
No...
No, I can't believe you
are doing this to me.
Please stop it.
That's right, Sena.
Lick her tits all over.
Don't forget to nibble
the nipples sometimes.
No, don't nibble.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
Hey, Rena, get busy.
Open her pussy wide and show me her
clit. Then, lick and suck it well.
Y-Yes.
No!
How do you like being toyed with
by women's soft tongues and hands?
Don't you feel damn good?
It must be have been good enough to
make you come.
Rena, stick your ass up in
the air and open your legs!
Stick your asses higher, both of you!
Ouch.
Satsuki's pussy is so wet, too.
This is so embarrassing.
Please don't say such a thing!
What a great view it is!
Three pussies are
inviting me to fuck them.
I shouldn't waste this chance.
No.
Please stop it now.
Oh, all of your pussies ale so hot.
How do you like my finger, huh?
Please don't move your finger!
No, no! Don't use two fingers!
Rena and Sena must have
their G-spot in the same spot.
What about Miss Satsuki?
It hurts.
No, please, I'm scared.
Oh your pussy is as tight as usual.
Can you tell?
A naughty noise and smell
are coming from your pussy.
Don't move, don't...
You're asking me the impossible.
It's you who wet my dick all
over and made it move easily.
You're breaking me!
Breaking me...
No!
R-Rena!
You guys make me feel so good.
I should share this
great moment with others!
Shut up!
What do you want?
What's that?
An outdoor fuck also should be fun.
Miss, why don't you
move your ass harder?
Rena, rub your pussy
down with Sena's knee.
Oh, it's rubbing against my knee.
Rena's wet pussy is moving on my knee!
Sena!
Don't move so hard.
There're people looking at us!
Stop it. They are looking at us!
Rena and Sena already came.
You should be coming, too, Satsuki!
Everyone is looking...
Don't move so hard!
Having an audience makes
you feel hot, doesn't it?
How's this?
Do you like this?
I'm coming!
You went so wild, Miss.
What happened to the two of them?
They went to bed in their room.
They were so satisfied that
they couldn't say a word.
Well, I got enough rest.
I'll check out Yuki at 7.
Until then I'll drive around the town.
I should find the next target.
Oh?
I must have seen him somewhere before...
Oh, he's the cop from yesterday.
I guess that's his colleague.
Are they assigned to this city?
That doesn't sound good to me.
I still have things to do in this city.
Before I get these things
done, I can't get busted.
Especially, I don't want to
get busted by that bastard.
Hm, I guess I should check out Yuki.
Let's see what kind
of things will happen.
Of course, she'll never notice me.
Hm, is it Yuki?
Standing in front of her
house, looking worried.
It seems like she's waiting for someone.
Let's see what's going on.
Well, well, here comes
a suspicious looking man.
Hey, you're the daughter
of Natsume, aren't you?
My parents are not home now.
Don't lie to me.
Here, I have the interest.
Take this for now.
Huh, it looks like her family
is in hock to some loan shark.
This isn't enough.
We'll return the rest of money soon.
But my dad is a victim.
Please don't threaten
my parents anymore.
What's that?
It's your
dad's fault for co-signing.
But that's all we have for today
I got it.
She was selling the pictures
to pay off her father's debt.
Please take this money
and leave us for today.
This is not child's play.
Maybe I'll just take
you back to the office.
Stop it. Leave me alone.
Don't resist me.
You have no right to complain to me
as long as I have your loan agreement!
No, get off me!
Wait!
Hey,
You...
I'll keep the loan agreement.
This is better for all of us.
Please come in, I'll take you home.
I called 911, so the bad guy is
just being taken to the police now.
So, please feel free to hop in.
Run all you want, but I'll
get you sooner or later.
I already got three
sources to blackmail you.
I'll come back to pick you up tomorrow.
Well, let me resume my
hunting as I planned.
Good morning, Yuki.
Please hop in, I have
something to show you...
...such as the pictures of you
selling the pictures of your friends.
Please drive, I don't want
the neighbors to see us!
Finally you understand your situation.
That cop is working hard this morning.
But I'll never get busted by that cop.
When did you get this stuff?
Are you trying to blackmail me?
When?
Don't you remember that you used
my taxi to do your naughty business?
I guess nobody usually
remembers a taxi driver huh?
What do you want?
And I also have this.
That's me!
Those are just copies.
You know what I mean?
Shame on you!
Well, I also keep this for your sake.
Is that the loan agreement?
Those nasty loan
sharks must be so upset.
Without this agreement, they cannot
threaten your parents anymore.
How did you get that?
I've always watched out for you, Yuki.
What are you gonna do with it?
Well, what shall I do with this?
I can either return this to the
original owner or just throw this away.
It's totally up to me.
So what do you want me to do?
Why don't you call your parents?
And tell them not to worry about you
if you're away from home for a while.
OK.
Why do I have to wear this?
Why?
Because you look great in this costume.
Where are we?
There was a reason
why I blindfolded you.
I'm sure you'll like this place.
How long do you want me to stay here?
It's totally up to you.
Now, let me see under your cute skirt.
What? No!
Don't give me trouble.
Here, you must show me
what's under your skirt.
You, pervert.
Oh, that is a compliment to me.
So, please touch your pussy
I will watch from here.
No, no way!
If you don't, I'll rub your
pussy down until it bleeds.
No, no, no.
I understand, I'll touch it by myself.
Please...
Don't make me do this...
Okay then, to give me a good view...
...sit down there and open
your legs wide toward me.
I see that's how you masturbate.
No, I've never done this before.
Don't lie.
You can't stop moving your fingers.
That's not...
I suppose I have to reward you for that.
Oh, your pussy is already soaking wet.
Your wet pussy is reflecting the lights.
No.
I'll skip foreplay and
get right down to business.
No!
It hurts!
Oh, so you're a virgin as I expected.
It hurts.
Your pussy is so tight!
I'll break it in.
Yeah, that's good, Yuki.
I'm going to come pretty soon.
Yeah, that's it.
It hurts!
Blood from losing virginity.
What kind of color will it be
after I mix it with my come?
You're an animal!
Nothing is better than a virgin.
Why must I go through
this horrible thing?
Hm, I also wonder why.
Well, think it over by yourself.
You have plenty of time to do that.
Well, I'll go back to hunting.
Oh, here she comes, pretty Nanami.
I'm glad that you're finally
riding my taxi.