Kyou-chan, congrats on the job.
But it's kinda odd that you're going
to be a doctor at my school.
I may be a "doctor", but only in the infirmary.
Still, are you sure you're okay with this, Aya?
Stop being so nosy.
Sorry.
Even though we're years apart,
it does seem a little awkward doing
this with someone I grew up with.
Oh, stop.
Well, move it.
Kyou-chan, you perv.
If you keep your hand there, we can't have sex.
Whoa, you said "sex" Kyou-chan, you're gross.
Well pardon me for being gross.
Okay. Just for a bit then.
Y-You're already so wet.
S-Stupid! They'll hear us next door.
S-Sorry. But I can't help screaming.
I didn't think it would feel that great
just to have your fingers inside me.
You're soaking wet, Aya.
See?
I don't wanna be... wet.
You're so cute, Aya.
Kyou-chan!
Aya. Aya!
Kyou-chan. Kyou-chan!
Put it in.
I...
can't... hold back anymore.
Aya!
Kojin Jugyou.
Schoolgirl ready for a private lesson!
Lesson 1: Starlet.
Lesson.1 「Starlet」
Kyou-chan! That's too hard!
Aya, I dreamed of the day that we would become one.
It's no use. It's too much!
I'm cumming!
It's hot.
That hurt.
Sorry.
I wasn't in a position to notice.
Was that your first time too?
Yeah.
Oh! So you saved your virginity for me?
Moron. You think I'd do that?
Let's do it again.
Infirmary
Doctor! It's an emergency!
Sonoda-san's stomach suddenly started hurting.
Ah, then she can use that bed.
I'll handle things from here. You go back to class.
Thank you very much.
My tummy hurts.
I'm gonna have your baby!
You silly girl.
I don't condone skipping class.
How cruel. I'm not skipping.
Then why are you here?
Um, let's see...
For an "inappropriate private lesson with the school doctor".
Idiot.
Just take a nap. I've got work to do.
Hey, easy!
I told you. I have work.
Stop it.
I'll stop after we fool around!
I'm not in the mood right now.
But you are in the mood.
Kyou-chan, you never were good
at telling people how you feel.
I'm feeling really good now as well.
Kyou-chan.
Oh well, fine. Just this once.
Yup!
Just once.
That's great, Kyou-chan.
My stockings...
Rip them apart.
O-Okay.
Does that turn you on?
Stupid.
Wow, you're already so wet.
Well Aya, if you want it, then ask me sweetly.
I want it, Kyou-chan.
Your cock...
I want it!
Aya!
Stupid, don't scream!
But Kyou-chan, you're so big.
You're just too sensitive, Aya.
Kyou-chan.
I wanna be on top.
Sure.
You're tired from work, right? Let me move for you.
Kyou-chan? Is this good?
Pretty good.
But you need to move faster,
or this won't do it for an older guy like me.
Okay!
Hey, you're too loud! Cover your mouth!
More!
Kyou-chan, push your cock in deeper!
I'll do that. Just hurry!
Yes...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Hey, Kyou-chan...
One more time?
We agreed, just once.
And besides, I'm out of condoms.
Don't worry about that.
We can recycle that one.
Hey, Aya.
Listen, you...
I heard Sonoda-san fainted in class.
Ah, Itoh-sensei.
How is she feeling?
Well, she's sleeping it off now.
She's been coming to the infirmary a lot lately.
I can't help worrying about her health.
I hope she's not faking it.
She would never fake it.
Oh, dear.
She's red and sweaty.
She really does look sick.
Stop getting in my way, you nosy bitch!
God, make sure Itoh-sensei
never gets married, never gets married, never gets married...
With no man in my life...
I must find a way to satisfy my body.
The sexual desires of an older woman...
can never be satisfied by normal means!
I can't be satisfied by a normal cock anymore.
Get me going with your muscled arm!
This thickness... This firmness is amazing!
Yes! Yes!
Yes...
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming. I'm cumming...
Wh-What should I do?
Oh no, I can't get it out.
If it stays in much longer, I'll get even looser.
I'll never be able to put a normal sized cock in there again!
And that's what she does. I'm sure of it.
I don't think Itoh-sensei would do that.
Oh? So you're taking her side?
No, I'm not.
You really are the jealous type, aren't you?
That's only because I love you so much!
Doesn't that make you happy?
It does make me happy.
Oh, I'm going ahead of you, okay?
Aya?
Kojin Jugyou.
Welcome home.
Would you like to take a bath first?
Or...
do-you-want-me?
Food.
Okay.
After we have sex.
But I'm really hungry.
Food tastes better after a workout.
Right?
I can't keep up with you.
No one will bother us here, so we can take our time.
Kyou-chan...
Jeez...
No, put it in.
Put what in?
Oh, come on, you perv.
Tell me.
Please...
Put your dick... in my pussy.
Okay. Let me just put a condom on.
Let me put it on for you.
What was that noise?
Condom failure.
It broke!
That was my last one.
That's okay. We can do without.
I'll go buy some more.
What the hell!?
You're just using fear of pregnancy as an excuse!
You coward!
What did you say?
As long as I'm with you, I don't care what you do to me!
But I...
I want to feel as much of you as possible inside of me!
"But I" what?
I love you.
I care about your safety, so I want to put that first.
What is it?
Hey, calm down.
I'm gonna go buy some condoms, so just wait for me.
No way.
Hey, you, not so sudden.
Wait, I'm cumming!
Please, put it in here next.
I'm sure it'll feel really good.
Are you sure?
You're trying to back out now?
Sorry.
Thrust your naked dick in there in one go.
Okay. In one go then.
Wow!
My insides are throbbing.
Your dick is sending warmth through my whole body!
You're really warm yourself.
I had no idea when I was wearing a condom.
But you're so soft and warm!
Oh, no, my pelvis is moving on its own.
A-Aya! I love you, Aya!
Kyou-chan!
Yes! Yes!
This feels great!
Yes! I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Okay, are you ready?
I'm cumming inside of you!
Yes! Inside of me! As hard as you can!
I want your semen in my womb!
That was too much.
Kyou-chan...
Kyou-chan!
Yes...
This feels great.
Oh, no.
No...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Why are you dressed like that?
I wanted to do that naked apron fantasy thing.
Though I'm surprised I can still fit into my old school uniform.
I-I see.
Kyou-chan, breakfast will be ready soon, so sit tight.
Kyou-chan.
Kyou-chan!
Aya!
Kyou-chan, you almost lost it there.
Jeez. Now you're gonna make me lose it.
Aya!
Kyou-chan.
Does seeing me in a sailor uniform
make you want to fuck me?
I wanna fuck you!
Can't be helped.
Take your thick, hard weapon and thrust it into me.
How is it?
Aya, you feel too good!
Yes! Kyou-chan, your dick... I love it!
Aya. Aya! You're making me crazy.
Kyou-chan...
I'm cumming.
Kyou-chan!
Yes. Yes. Yes!
Aya!
I'm cumming!
Kyou-chan...
Kyou-chan!
Kyou-chan, are you dissatisfied because I'm a bad cook?
No.
In exchange, I can get better at sex.
To Be Continues...