There's a taxi that runs
freely throughout the city.
The taxi itself seems to
be in a secret dimension.
Plus no matter what people
do or say in the taxi...
...it never gets leaked to the outside.
People harbor such fantasies
as they get in this taxi...
I'll be late for my rehearsal.
We don't get to see
each other that much.
When can I see you again?
The media is really onto me.
If the fans find out, my
popularity will decline.
They can easily reveal secrets they
normally wouldn't tell others...
It's a place where people
can have love affairs.
I'm coming, I'm coming!
They forget the fact that the taxi
driver is listening to everything they do.
Thank you very much.
Kyoko, I didn't know your lover
was a vocalist for a popular band.
Sex Taxi 5 - Nurse Hunting: Nanami
I'm sorry for calling you
on such a short notice.
I'm calling you about the loan...
Yes, I just need about 20 million yen.
I don't know how to thank you.
But then your bank's reputation will...
Okay, I'll see you at
Junmai hotel as usual.
Yes, I'll be waiting.
I see.
So you're going to use
your beautiful body.
You have a lover but you sell your
body to your sponsor. That's not nice...
Here we are.
Thank you.
Hey mister. Can I sit
up front next time?
What?
Sure.
Yay!
Promise?
I hate dealing with kids.
Oh yeah...
I almost forgot something important.
Today's target is an angel in white...
A nurse named Nanami.
Please enter.
Excuse me, but are you the
one who wanted to see me?
That's right.
I'd like you to take
a look at something.
What?
Take a look inside the
envelope placed next to you.
This one?
This is...
You visit this elderly man often
to give him some medication.
You were secretly
taking pictures of me?
A nurse who is kind to an elderly
man with no one to depend on.
It's such a heart-warming story.
But we have a problem
with this medicine.
I slammed on the breaks when you
were in this taxi a while ago.
That's when you lost these.
You shouldn't forget
such expensive medicine.
What do you want from me?
I want you to listen to this tape.
Doctor, this is a lot...
I put in about a 2
weeks' worth this time.
And how is the progress?
Is it going well?
Well, it's about that...
It's not good to deceive people.
Is that what you want to say?
You know there's no turning back.
But it's not fair to take
advantage of an elderly man.
That's why he makes a great target.
If we can get his house and property,
you and I can have a great future.
Stop!
Stop! Please stop it!
The doctor has nothing to do with this.
You were having fun with him in the car
parked at the hospital parking lot, right?
What?
Take a look at the other photo.
No!
If this gets out to the
public, you and your doctor...
Are both finished in
the medical profession.
Stop! Please don't!
Then you can call the hospital
for leave of absence right?
Where are we going?
Look what we have here.
This detective has been
sniffing around town lately.
It's getting harder to
hunt for women in this town.
Nurse's office
What are you going to do?
Probably what you're
thinking of right now.
Then you're gonna let me go?
It looks like you're
not so bright, Nanami.
Stop!
This is what I'm going to do.
Just like I thought.
Your tits are wonderful.
They're so big and beautiful.
No!
Your tits are amazing.
I'm gonna have lots of fun with them.
Oh my, your nipples are hard.
It's amazing that you can
feel good by hot-dogging.
It's not like that.
I'm embarrassed, that's why.
You're embarrassed but
you're feeling good?
Maybe you're a masochist?
That can't be...
There's no need to be embarrassed.
I want you to make love
to my cock even harder.
Yes, that's it.
Get your tits closer, and
keep moving it up and down.
Lick my cock like you're
wrapping your tongue around it.
Yes, that's it. You're doing very well.
Your tits and tongue are
wrapping around my cock.
This is much more than I expected.
I'm suffocating!
I'm gonna climax!
It's hot...
Sorry about that.
It's just that your mouth
and tits were so amazing.
No, I don't want anymore.
Please!
You're getting so wet Nanami.
No, it's embarrassing.
Don't look at it!
Now look at this cunt of yours.
It looks like it's going to burst.
Now I'll stick my fingers deep inside.
No, I can't...
I can't take it anymore.
Now, let's get this started.
No!
It's really tight inside you Nanami.
It's inside me.
Your slimy cunt is
tightening up on my cock.
That's not true!
It hurts...
It's deep inside...
I can feel it!
It's good?
It feels good, right?
I can't believe you enjoy getting
raped. What a slutty nurse you are.
You're one naughty lady.
Please let me go.
Stop tormenting me.
Do it harder...
No...
I'll climax...
I'm gonna climax too.
I'll release plenty of it inside.
It's flowing inside...
So hot...
I just released it but,
it's still coming out.
So hot...
Your body has something
that excites the men, Nanami.
But I'm surprised that
you were such a slut.
Please let me go.
Nope.
You're too good to let go.
A woman who enjoys getting
raped is too important to let go.
That sluttiness of yours...
I'll use that effectively from now on.
Abandoned school will be
demolished. Please do not enter.
Now everyone, please enjoy the show.
Are you sure about this?
Please.
We're the only ones
inside this movie theater.
That's great.
I'm a very kind man.
This is to improve my
collection, it's part of my hobby.
Here we go!
This is amazing!
I said come here!
No, stop it!
Stop it!
Amazing...
Helping out others
sure makes me feel good.
Time to check out.
Just as I thought, Kyoko is coming out.
Take me to Takatobi airport.
Unfortunately, we're not going there.
What? Are you crazy?
I don't know about that.
But I'm sure you'll figure
out who's crazy or not...
After you look at that
envelope right next to you.
What are you talking about?
Looks like you were really enjoying it.
You were secretly
taking pictures of me?
Your lover is a popular
rock singer right?
What are you planning to do?
I'd like to take you to my suite.
Are you kidding me?
None of the banks will give me a loan.
Yes, about 20 million yen.
What?
But you're always helping me out.
I don't feel like
asking you for more help.
I dubbed the original tape.
There's plenty more in the original.
But then your bank's reputation will...
Stop it! Turn it off!
Okay, I'll see you at
Junmai hotel as usual.
Stop it!
The media is really onto me.
If the fans find out, my
popularity will decline.
Then I'll see you after your
concert. I'll be waiting at the hotel.
Do you know the
situation you're in now?
If this tape goes public, what would
happen to your kind executive director?
Plus your superstar lover might
lose his popularity as well.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to be part of my collection.
What did you say?
You can refuse if you want to.
I'm sure the media would
love to hear a scandal.
Wait a minute. Don't
ruin his reputation!
I don't care what happens to me!
I see that we
understand each other now.
Why don't you call the store
to get a leave of absence?
Fine.
Well well, it's that detective again.
He's really serious about his job.
Yes, just for a while.
I want to see you.
It's sad to see lovers
break up, isn't it?
OK, here we are.
This is an abandoned school...
Now, let me enjoy that
ripe body of yours.
Stay away from me!
Oh? I thought you agreed to do this.
I changed my mind!
You're so full of energy.
Ones that struggle a
lot have a weak heart.
Am I right?
Get your face away from me.
Pervert!
You can struggle all you want now.
This is part of the fun as well.
Your tits look real nice.
Your nipples are pink and cute.
Stop touching me!
Let's see how you are down here.
Stop it, stop it!
You pervert!
You're a stylish woman.
If you're a graceful Japanese woman...
...you're not supposed
to wear any underwear.
Stop looking!
No...no!
You're getting so wet.
With your pretty cunt
underneath these soft hairs...
How many men have you entertained?
Stop saying that.
You're experienced, yet your
pussy's still very pretty...
Your juices are flowing out.
Stop saying dirty things.
You're so annoying.
You want me to stick it in real quick?
Stop it!
Then how about a present?
Despite its size, this vibrator
creates very intense vibrations.
I'll stick it in deeper.
Don't stick that thing inside!
No!
You're complaining a lot, but
you're feeling it, aren't you?
Look at all the juice
that's flowing out.
No!
Don't look at it!
I think this should keep you quiet.
Now suck it all the way. Do
it like you do your lover.
Looks like this vibrator
isn't giving you enough.
That's not true.
You want the real thing, right?
Liar!
Why don't you beg for the real thing?
The real thing...
I can't hear you.
Say it so I can hear you loud and clear.
Please give me the real
thing. I'm begging you...
Here's the real thing.
Well?
The real thing feels
so much better, right?
Yes, it feels so good.
It's getting entangled...
The juice from inside
is sticky and hot...
I can't take it anymore.
Liar.
Do I make you feel
better than your lover?
Yes.
What do you guys usually do?
You probably enjoy having a
vibrator up the ass too, right?
No, I don't do that stuff.
You lying bitch!
Take that!
No!
Amazing... I can't...
I'm coming...
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
I'll climax!
You have a killer body.
I might become addicted to this one.
Are you okay, Rena?
Yes, we're finally getting out, right?
We were able to escape
due to team work.
No.
If you didn't encourage
me, I would've given up.
Now let's hurry.
Before he finds out.
Okay.
I don't care if I get arrested.
But before the elderly man becomes
disabled from the medicine...
...I have to hand myself over to
the police and save that man's life.
I'm sorry, doctor.
Now, let's go hunt some fresh meat.
Yay! This is great!
Thanks for letting me sit up front.
We made a promise so...
You're a good person.
You remembered our promise.
I don't know if I'm a good person.
But a promise is a promise.
Hey, it's a crane truck.
Are they doing construction around
here?
Didn't you know?
They're going to demolish
that abandoned school.
Oh, it's today?
I forgot about that.
Hey, it's a police car!
Wait a minute.
I believe that was Renna and Senna.
I wonder when they escaped...
Hey mister.
Are you listening?
Can you let me sit up front from now
on?
Is that okay?
Please say it's okay.
I can't let you do that.
Why?
I have to leave this town today.
Why? Why?
I don't think I'll ever
drive a taxi here again.
No, you're lying!
It's true.
And you will never see me again.
Tell me why.
I have lots of reasons.
But I'm certain of one thing, I'm
not the kind of person you think I am.
No, it's not fair.
I like riding in your taxi.
You'll understand when
you become an adult.
Now, this is the end of the road.
Take care.
Fine.
But don't forget about me.
Farewell.
Goodbye Ai.
You'll forget about me in no time.
And I'll forget about you
and hunt for my next target.
According to the local authorities...
...as they were about to
demolish the abandoned school...
...they found several
missing women confined inside.
They are looking into this as a
case of kidnapping by some pervert...
...and the police are confident
that it's only a matter of time...
...until the suspect is caught.
I think I'll head to a new
location and begin hunting again.