It must be difficult for you to pay for school tuition
and everything after losing your parents.
Do things just get too painful for you sometimes?
It is very difficult, but not painful at all.
Lots of people help me out,
and all of my elders are very nice to me.
I'm very grateful to them.
I hope that everyone continues to
treat me well and respect me.
Good for you.
You're that girl who was just on TV, aren't you?
Makes me proud to be your viewer.
I wish my boss could see this.
The CEO of the Kojin Group.
Well, here I come.
I came so suddenly.
This sort of play is difficult for older guys like me.
Yes. I'm supported by everyone's love,
and I live every day to the fullest.
I guess you do.
My "love" opens up this hole and fills it with my seed.
And it makes her so fulfilled.
Nee-san... Nee-san!
Kojin Jugyou.
Schoolgirl ready for a private lesson!
Lesson.2 「The Secret Aquarium」
Lesson 2: The Secret Aquarium
Wow, would you look at the time. Going home early again?
She's probably got another TV interview or something.
Nevertheless, Ningyo-chan sure is cute!
I wanna hear her squeal just for me.
Yeah, like that'll happen.
At 01:00 pm, we have a recording session with KSM Radio.
I don't care about that.
Do I have work tonight?
Yes.
Someone from Mega Bank.
Is he a first timer?
Yes.
Here is his photograph.
Let me see.
Looks like a normal guy.
What do you think, Takashi?
What do I think?
I don't care.
Me either.
All I care about is tonight.
Will I be forced to watch again?
Like I said, I don't care how long you've been doing this!
I'm not gonna give you guys a loan on those terms.
- Listen, mister...
The mansion we live in has a room for show.
And on the other side of a magic mirror, there's a secret room.
My job is to watch the clients and make
sure things don't get too out of hand.
In an emergency, I can leap out and save my sister.
That's right. I'm always forced to watch from here.
The company president will be here shortly.
If you would just be patient...
Huh?
No way, man. I'm leaving. Get my car.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That outfit... I bought the same thing for my daughter.
Papa!
I am the company president, Kuonji Ningyo.
Thank you for visiting our home today.
Oh, well...
Um, I'm sorry, but I don't intend to go through with this.
Um, crap, I'm getting hard.
Down, you stupid dick!
I don't mind.
Tell me, your wife is pregnant, isn't she?
Yeah.
So is your sex life somewhat lacking?
That is no concern of yours...
If you don't mind, I can try to help you in her place.
What's that noise?
Well, I wonder?
S-Stop playing dumb. It's here!
You dirty old man.
See? There is nothing here.
I-It's inside! You've got a vibrator up there!
Take it out. Take it out and show it to me!
Very well. I'll take it out.
Don't vibrate so much!
Dammit!
Let's get one thing straight. You seduced me.
I'm just returning the favor.
Shit. Don't be so rough!
Wh-What the hell?
You came with just one thrust?
That must not be very satisfying.
You can have more fun if you wish.
What was that?
You...
Shit!
Who are you, bitch? You're unreal, you know that?
Amazing... This is too amazing.
You...
You're irresistible!
Son of a bitch!
That dirty old man's semen is invading my sister!
I've never felt it this deep before!
You're a really bad girl, you know.
I guess I need to teach you a lesson with this!
With a body like yours, I'm sure you could
enslave both men and women!
Nee-san! Nee-san! Nee-san!
How do you like it? My rugged dick?
My hole is getting torn up!
Wow!
If you're that rough...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna pee myself!
Now you feel it! Did you learn your lesson?
Don't! Not so deep!
I'm gonna pee!
Oh, no!
Good.
Let's see the "company president" piss on me!
Don't do it, Nee-san! Don't let that
bastard have your holy water!
Nee-san!
She pisses while she fucks? What a bitch.
Take that!
I-I'm cumming!
Nee-san!
That was intense.
Here.
See?
I've got more for you.
Drink it, Ningyo!
Hey, you. I'll give you a loan.
Thank you very much, sir.
Let us retire to a different room to discuss this.
I'll come again later, Ningyo!
I trust you'll show me a good time!
Nee-san.
It's over now. Everything's okay.
All I can do is rub my sobbing sister's back.
Kojin Jugyou.
Why'd you call me here?
Lunch period is almost over.
Today we get to spend the whole day in school.
I don't wanna waste time doing boring things.
I treasure the time during the day when
I'm allowed to be a normal girl.
But at night...
Takashi?
Nee-san...
I can't...
take it anymore.
I can't stand seeing you like that anymore.
So, take this.
Take this and kill me.
Very well.
How do you want me to kill you?
Right here.
One stab through the heart.
Nee-san...
As I predicted, the brother broke first.
It's good that I thought to put a bug in Ningyo-sama's clothes.
I don't mind, Ningyo-sama. I will take care of the cleanup.
Do as Takashi-sama wishes.
I understand.
The heart, right?
Nee-san!
What you're doing is wrong.
My mom and dad died.
And yet you try to make me even more miserable?
If you're really doing this for me,
then promise that you'll never hurt me like this again!
I promise.
I know this has been much more painful for you than for me.
I think my period is starting.
I know that, but I can't stop myself.
I wanna have sex with you right away. I can't stand it.
Me too.
I wanna have sex with you, too, Takashi.
Hey, Takashi...
Hurry up.
Nee-san!
It's right here, Takashi.
You put your dick in here.
Come in little by little.
Oh, it's in a great spot right now!
This is your pussy. It feels really good.
It's all the way... It's all the way inside.
Not so fast.
Wow! Your dick is wonderful!
I love it!
Nee-san, I'm gonna...
You're gonna cum already?
Yeah.
Go ahead. I'll take it for you.
Nee-san!
I came.
I feel it flowing.
So much of your...
Your semen spilled out.
This is amazing. It's so squishy.
Let Onee-chan clean it off for you.
Oh, dear. Takashi, you silly...
Your dick is all hard again.
Nee-san!
Nee-san... You didn't have to...
It's all right, Takashi, because it's you.
You can do it one more time, right?
Please, put it in again.
I can do it forever!
Disgusting.
That boy is corrupting Ningyo-sama!
An interview for me instead of my sister? That's unusual.
And what a strange location.
Takashi-sama.
Whenever I see you and Ningyo-sama so deeply bonded...
Do you have any idea how my troubled my heart is?
Iwakura-san?
I always wondered why it was you by her side and not me.
Do you have any idea how messed
up my mind has become?
Feel the wrath of my pain. Starting with your manhood.
Stop it, Iwakura!
Nee-san!
He hasn't used it enough yet.
Ningyo-sama!
Iwakura, I knew all along.
I knew you had a bug in my clothes.
But I'll bet you didn't know...
that I'd done the same thing to you.
Takashi!
You mustn't, Ningyo-sama!
I will stop you with force if I must!
I cannot shoot her.
I knew I could never shoot her under any circumstances.
What a cruel fate.
But please, do not worry.
I will be the one who loves you most in the afterlife.
Nee-san?
Takashi? Takashi!
You're so mean! You wouldn't wake up!
Nee-san, where am I?
It doesn't look like a hospital.
It's our new home.
Our new home?
Nee-san, what happened to our old house?
I quit and dissolved the company.
I also sold all the other houses in
our estate so we could live here.
Nee-san, are you okay with that?
As long as I have you, I don't need anything else.
Me too. As long as I have you, I don't need anything else.
Nee-san, not there.
Takashi, you still don't know how I feel here.
It's in.
The inside of your butt is really tight and hot.
Takashi! My other hole... dig around in it!
Okay, Nee-san.
Takashi. This feels great!
I'm cumming.
It just feels too good back there. I'm gonna cum!
Me too, Nee-san!
I'm cumming!
Hey, Takashi.
I want more.
Either hole, please.
Nee-san.
Nee-san. Nee-san!
T-T-Takashi!
Takashi, make me live. Put your life deep into me.
Put your dick all the way inside
of me. Put it inside my womb!
Nee-san!
I...
Let it flow! Fill my insides with lots of semen!
All the way inside my womb! Drown it with your semen!
Takashi!
Nee-san, I'm cumming!
Takashi.
Nee-san.
Everything begins how.
Our new life begins.
Takashi...
I love you.