Sweet Dreams
I was treated nicely 1
I'll pour my heart into this
For the senpai that I adore
Oh, my bittersweet feelings.
Because it's Valentines!
Thanks!
I wonder if he'll be happy to take my homemade chocolate.
Hey.
Maybe, I'll just let myself be swept away by him.
I said hey.
But, my heart isn't quite prepared yet...
Hey listen to me.
Oh, Akira-nee-san.
You!
My insides...
The chocolate that I've poured my passion into!
Hiromi.
How terrible of you!
What did you just do?
Why did you do that?!
You're creeping me out.
What are you doing humming happily early in the morning?
And what the hell is with this outfit?
Stop!
Stop nee-san!
scream
No
Please no!
Please stop being mean to me.
Why are you always doing this to your cute little sister?
What sister are you talking about?
You're a guy for heaven's sake!
You're even weaning panties.
Jeez, he's helplessly perverted.
Hey, don't make that dirty thing stand up.
Take that, and that!
No, Akira nee-san stop!
If you keep doing that, it will...
Hey pervert, don't you dare try to
squirt that dirty thing on my foot.
You're a guy,
and you're dressing like this?!
Look, I'm pretty soiled now thanks to your cum.
But, but you just kept at it Nee-san...
Oh, so it's my fault, eh?
Let's see, a guy dressed up as a girl,
and having a boner While dressed like that,
even squirting out his dirty cum everywhere.
All of that is my fault, huh?
No, I'm not a pervert!
Just because I'm a boy...
just because it has to be a girl...
That's not what this age of freedom is all about!
Dressing up like this, and even liking a guy,
are all my own decisions to make!
Even if you try to throw difficult terms at me,
perverts will still remain perverts.
It's just creepy.
That's your own cam.
A pervert like you will never be liked by anyone.
There's no guy that would be pleased to receive
valentine chocolates from another guy!
That's not true!
Yamaguchi-senpai is...!
Hmph, we'll see about that.
Nee-san you idiot!
Hiromi, you...!
You plan on defying me?
But, if you're calling me a pervert,
then you're also a pervert!
Teasing me ever since we were kids...
While you were actually aroused the whole time you were doing it!
You're the one who wets her pussy by rubbing
cum that I just squirted onto you!
What? What the hell are you trying to say to me?!
Hey, stop!
Even you...
Look, even you are...!
Idiot, stop that!
It went straight in.
And it's wet all the way inside.
Hiromi, you...!
Pull it out right now.
While I'm still in the mood to forgive you.
No, stop pushing, stop pushing it inside!
Stop pushing it inside already!
You, you...!
Oh no, oh no...
I said you can't.
I already told you to stop.
But you're still... stop, stop it!
These big breasts, these big cow breasts...
I really...
I really wanted to have breasts like these.
I'm going to cover these slutty breasts in chocolate!
It feels slimy and gross.
Your insides are twitching.
So you came, you just came, eh?
You came while being fucked by this perverted dick.
Your breasts are also covered in chocolate.
See Nee-san, someone perverted, violent
and totally uncute like you,
won't also be liked by anyone!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
It's flowing inside.
In the end, the only thing that keeps us as ourselves,
is the fact that we only have each other.
That's Why we know each other so well.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for cumming inside.
Akira-nee-san, this is...?
Just forget about it.
I mean, well...
It's still one day ahead, and it's not exactly handmade, but...
Nee-san...!
Then, next time I'll give you my very special white chocolate!
The chief
hostess'
fantasy
This inn has been open for a long time.
The place gives a fresh experience of old traditions,
with an aura of relaxation and rejuvenation.
The dishes are made with utmost
preparation and perfection, and...
Welcome to our inn.
Please, make yourselves at home.
This is the young chief hostess, Yoshino Ayaka.
There are quite a number of customers who
are actually visiting just to see her.
This place sure is wonderful no matter how many times I visit.
It's amazing that you take care of everything
with those delicate arms.
Oh my, your compliments are too much for me to take sir.
Oops, my hand slipped.
My my, mister.
That person is at it, as always.
That totally glued look.
He doesn't even try to hide it.
How about we get a taste of the chief hostess herself next.
Please, take a bite.
Look, it looks firm and it's beautifully pink.
How about the lower part?
This reddish thing is soft, tender.
And if I try to open it a bit...
There...
The sight of it is enough to excite me!
This frail body doesn't really look that tasty.
Please don't eat me.
Okay then, how shall I get on with this?
Look, this wet matsutake mushroom is already this big.
I think it'd go well with our expert cook chief hostess.
Let's see how far this mushroom can go inside your mouth.
Please don't say that.
No...
It stinks.
The smell stimulates my nose.
Its wetness, and the strong smell...
It reeks of something worse than raw fish.
I'm sure lots of women spilled their tears from this thing.
Well, how's the taste?
Your tongue is making me crazy.
And your mouth is even...!
You suck it like you're never going to let go!
It's going deep inside!
What? Am I really that slutty to you?
Being violated by this old man deeply like this...
I just can't resist him!
Your pussy is making sloppy sounds.
How about me squirting lots of my
cum on that slutty face of yours.
Oh no, he's about to cum.
Chief.
Chief?
Oh my, I was spacing out there.
Someone's calling you at the kitchen.
Stupid! How many times do I have
to tell you before you remember?
Just quit the job if you're not really into it!
What's wrong, Tate-san?
I can hear your voice even from afar.
Oh, Chief.
I'm sorry.
Jeez, it's just these two aren't doing the job well again.
And it's proof that they are not really into what they're doing.
But that's really no reason for you to raise your hand, right?
I'll just ask them properly, okay?
Well, if the Chief says so...
Hey, we're not yet finished!
Our cooks really are strict, even than before.
They're probably just too hard on the kids.
Yes, they really are too hard.
So hard, that it looks really scary.
But it looks really burly.
I know, everyone here is looking out for me,
but sometimes, the passionate stares
that I feel when I turn my back
are just full of wild, carnal and primal instincts.
But we can't because I already have a husband
that was wed to me by family tradition.
I have to be everyone's elder sister.
Chief, for a long time we have...
Elder sister...
You can't, you can't do this!
We heard it from your husband.
That your expression becomes completely different at night.
Your husband is already pretty old, I bet
he can no longer satisfy you well.
No, this is terrible.
We are going to satisfy you in place of your husband.
Ah, if those thick and strong fingers keep on fondling me, oh no...
No, please no...
Chief, your underarms...
No, not there!
Chief, it looks very wet already.
For you to look very horny like this.
I can't even imagine it from the kimono you usually wear.
No, please not there.
I haven't let anyone in there but my husband.
I'm married...
And yet I'm totally exposed to those
who are younger than my husband.
This is really embarrassing.
Your hips and your pussy are starting to hold me really tight.
Chief, chief.
Chief!?
C-Chief?
Are you alright?
spaced out
Chief!
I'm sorry about that.
Oh yes! I'm going to go and see those kids.
Her presence just rejuvenates me.
Damn, I'm really pissed off.
Why do I have to be hit like that?
I'm going to quit working here.
I want them to witness the gap at I'll make.
We'll take on the Chief, and then do her.
What?!
Those guys treat the Chief like some kind of idol, right?
I bet I could really piss them off if I fuck her.
But the Chief is a really nice person.
I don't like that.
W-well, I don't really have anything against her.
We'll take on the Chief, and then do her.
So you came here to be raped by us, Chief.
No, stop this foolishness!
Look here granny, I'm going to let it all out on you!
Stop, I can still forgive you now!
Chiefs boobs... big boobs...
To be raped by really young boys...
Shaking your big tits like that every day in front of us...
You were inviting us to do it, right?
Right? Right?
See, you aren't even wearing undies!
What a pervert!
No way, I was not seducing you.
There's just no way I'd...
I'm violated, and my insides are forcefully being opened.
They're still kids!
But they can already reach into my womb!
I just inserted it in, and it's already very wet.
I knew from the beginning that you wanted it.
No way, I'm really getting aroused from this.
It's too intense.
This is too intense.
Chief, your expression is becoming perverted.
Your face tells me that it can't get enough of my dick.
She really does...
She really does have that perverted expression.
And I want it so bad too!
My perverted face is exposed as he continues
to fuck me from behind...
I haven't even shown this expression to my husband yet!
Oh no, oh no...!
Oh no, oh no, oh no...!
We can't do this...!
Something like this simply won't end with
just doing it once with these kids.
Having unprotected sex, and being cummed
inside many times already.
This won't be good for me...
I'm going to get pregnant with some kid.
I'm going to cum while being impregnated!
Ayaka, what are you doing?
What was that sound for?
You're not thinking of something weird again, are you?
D-dear!
M-master!
Here now, I'll be the one to talk to those two.
So just go back in there already, okay?
Don't let them worry too much.
I think, he's still my number one.