I have been treated nicely - 02
Yui's Shrine
Hey, not like that Yui-chan, you have to suck it properly.
The night is still very young, so you can't be tired yet.
Yui-chan, it's gripping me quite nicely.
No...
Oh, how's this?
My dick feels great, right?
No, no...!
Your body is saying the exact opposite, though.
What?
You're such a lewd young woman.
The way I fondle your breasts also feels nice, right?
Here, here.
So this is the result after just one week.
Well, we've been at it almost every night, so that's to be expected.
Seems your body has already remembered the sensation.
You don't even have hair down there,
and yet you look so mature already.
Now, concentrate on sucking my dick.
Yeah, just who do you think allows you to have this shrine, eh?
I'm cumming.
Me too, I'm about to cum.
It's coming out.
I'm about to pour it all into Yui-chan!
No, no...!
Lots of it came out.
Your pussy's twitching after it was cummed inside.
How sweet...
Hey Ran, switch with me already, will you?
I'm itching for it badly now.
Can't you wait a bit more, Kanekahino?
N-No!
Look, your insides are already filled with my cum.
That's a lot of cum inside.
It's not even comparable to the first night.
It's my turn now.
No time to waste now.
Just put your hips up already.
If you keep that up, you won't be able
to catch up with your mother.
Mom. I want to meet you, mom!
Mom!
The fleshy sensation is really great.
You even have your beautiful nipples hard now.
Oh, does it feel good for you now, Yui-chan?
Just be honest.
Say that you love being fucked by these old men's big dicks.
Here, here.
Aren't you going to say that your pussy
feels good when rammed by our dicks?
See, it clearly feels pleasure whenever I thrust into it.
Just say it already.
You're still as passionate as ever.
Start thinking about your age already.
Oh yeah, I kinda forgot as I was fucking this wonderful thing.
But I just can't help it, you know!
With this, it would seem as if both you and
your Mom bear some kind of curse.
So in a way, your wish did come true.
Everybody also loved fucking her like this.
Where is she? Where's my mother?
Your beautiful mom? Well, listen up...
In order to pay for your priest father's debts,
she started serving us, with her pussy as payment for all of it.
It only took three days before she finally gave in.
Of course, at first she resisted.
But on the last day, her body finally learned to grip our dicks well.
Now she's just another prostitute.
At that time, I was still slapping her ass real good.
With her lovely hips sticking out, she was completely
fucked in both her pussy and ass.
She's the type that doesn't care whether you cum inside or not.
It's like every second she was awake, she was either
sucking a dick or getting fucked by one.
Soon, you'll also be hanging around your
sex customers as if it was a normal thing.
Just please us, and you'll soon be following
in your mother's footsteps.
Your mom started since you were a small child.
Everybody around her was like an animal,
continuously fucking her non-stop.
Every male in the village surrounded and violated her.
The most miserable part was when even some
of the kids started messing with her,
she continued to call out your name, even
fainted from the pleasure.
Please not Yui, please don't let Yui fall victim to the same fate...
Her pretty face considerably changed
expressions as the boys fucked her.
It was a lovely sight to behold.
This strong dick that's now inside of you is all thanks to her.
Hey Kanekashino, don't complain if your back
suddenly starts to ache from pushing.
I'm going to make you like your mom, a woman who
loves getting fucked deep inside her womb!
Your youthful womb is starting let its egg fertilize.
Getting stirred up like this is already bad enough, and yet...
Mom also tried to resist this... thing...
See? The sensation from the tip of my
dick rubbing inside feels great, right?
Save me, mother.
Please, save me!
Oh, I remember your mom looking the same as you.
All the while getting fucked deeply inside.
Oh yes! I'm about to cum! I'm going to die!
Something like that.
P-Please, leave me alone already.
This feels... good?
Did it feel this good for mom?
My mind's about to break.
I'm going crazy...
I can't go back anymore...
Oh yes...!
That's right, try saying it like I taught you.
Say, "Mister, I love your dick, it feels great."
Mister, I love your dick, it feels great.
It feels great!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming lots!
With this cum, it looks like you've paid the interest already.
After that, in this shrine I...
Continue to offer my body to everyone who comes by.
Welcome... to Yui’s Shrine.
Huh?
It seems you are a virgin.
And your condition looks far worse than imagined.
Umm... why is that even...?
You'll have to be hospitalized as early as tonight.
We still need to check up on this further.
That can't be...
Even if you suddenly say that...
Please inform all of your family members and
related personnel at work beforehand.
Why?
This is most likely a result of me being too busy to take
the company's regular physical examinations.
Now that I'm 26, I tried for the first time to take one, but...
I never thought that it would lead to an immediate hospitalization.
From high school, to college, even as I work...
I was just too busy doing things.
Going out with women?
The busy life I chose didn't even give
me the opportunity to meet them.
Isshin-san, I'm coming in!
Excuse me.
How are you feeling?
I-I'm sorry, I'm really sorry!
A real deal klutz!
It's the first time I've ever seen one.
A-Are you all right?
I'm sorry, I'm really clumsy...
Isshin-san, you're quite the nice guy.
Now I'm relieved.
Eh?
Actually, I've never taken care of a
patient diagnosed with virginity.
I imagined you'd be a bit more... scary, I guess.
Why did I have to...?
I'll be the one in charge of taking care of you while you're in here.
I'm Fujita Yukari.
I'm still quite new here, but I hope we get along well.
Let's get started right away with a few check ups.
Please lie down straight.
Oh, okay.
First, we'll measure your blood pressure.
Blood pressure...
Umm, which arm is needed?
No, that's wrong, Isshin-san.
Just lie down and relax.
Wait, hey...!
W-What are you doing?
What am I doing?
It'll be over quick.
So just stay still.
Even if you say that, this is just...
You don't have to be that embarrassed.
Even I'll feel embarrassed if you keep that up.
Don't think too much!
I think not looking was the right choice.
It's being touched by a woman...
This is the first time my dick has been held like this.
And even by a very cute girl.
This situation is just...!
In all 26 years of my life...
This is the very first time I've felt so embarrassed and yet so happy.
I never thought this would happen.
Umm... Isshin-san?
Could I have made you nervous?
Or maybe this really is a symptom of your virginity?
Well, I am nervous, but...
It doesn't seem to be getting aroused.
You're going to measure my blood pressure, right?
Yes.
That's why it needs to get stiff, or else I can't do it.
What kind of joke is that?
Umm... is it okay for me to ask?
Has it gotten aroused when you try to masturbate lately?
Well, yeah I guess.
How many times per week do you masturbate?
How do you do it, and what materials do you use?
Have you gone to any sex service establishments at least once?
Oh my goodness.
For it to be treated like some kind of illness is...
Is being a virgin really that bad?
Is not having any experience going out with women that bad?
Isshin-san, you'll be just fine!
Virginity  isn't something that you can't cure,
no, I'm certain that it can be cured!
That's not really helping...
You're not the one to blame.
It's all due to your virginity.
Umm...
I'll take full responsibility to help you completely recover.
That's why, there's no need to be embarrassed.
Please feel good, I'll make it enough to compensate
for all the years you've suffered.
Look Isshin-san, isn't it amazing?
It's already becoming this lively...
Your tongue, it's rubbing against the back,
and the sensation as it gets sucked on...
Isshin-san, I...
Can I be the one to cure your virginity?
I don't think that's the issue here...
It's as if I'm in a dream.
The fact that I'm with a wonderful person
like you is all that's on my mind.
Consider this a special treat from me.
Amazing, it's really soft.
I never thought that women felt this soft...
No, I'm sensitive there!
Your boobs, they're...
My nipples, please don't pinch them!
My fingers... they're going in!
And it's wet...
Please, don't go in too deeply...
Can I really do this?
There, that's the spot.
It feels warm.
Congratulations.
Now your virginity has been cured!
Thank you very much.
W-Well? How does it feel inside?
It feels warm, and wet...
My mind's about to burst from this sensation.
Isshin-san, Isshin-san!
It's okay, just keep on moving!
I'm about to cum!
It just feels too good!
Cum... inside me!
Amazing, lots came out.
And it's still not stopping.
Can I continue like this?
Yeah.
Well, nothing really changed after that, but...
My steps feel a lot lighter.
And the blue skies look a lot clearer now.