I have been treated nicely - 03
Please summarize all of our current progress
on distributable handouts.
We have Insufficient backing.
B-But that would require negotiation between our intel sponsors.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm saying that the support from our
data results is being neglected.
That's enough, you two.
Let's reconvene on Friday morning.
We'll make it by the end of the week.
If that's what you want, boss...
Okay then.
Kura'ta-san, would that be alright with you?
Yes.
Kurata Chie.
It's been one year since she was transferred to this branch.
As you witnessed earlier,
she has no problem saying what's on her mind
and motivating her fellow co-workers.
Add the fact that she is also quite aloof,
and it's not surprising why she still
hasn't assimilated into the group.
There are even rumors that she actually caused troubled
at HQ, which is why she was transferred here.
That is why I've been careful when dealing with her, but...
Boss Shirai, how about a drink or two?
Oh, thanks for the offer but I can't.
You're now living alone, right, boss?
Oh, I remember you're living with your daughter.
No, she's at my ex-wife's place now.
I already have an appointment for this evening.
I'll just have to take up on your offer some other time.
I'm home.
W-Welcome back.
U-Umm... I just finished buying ingredients, so I haven't really...
Oh, I don't really mind.
Why don't we just prepare it together.
I guess I could say the events that
took place just kind, of happened.
A few months after she started working here,
some important business matter went unreported to her
and because of that, an error that wouldn't
usually happen broke out.
Adapting to the situation, she simply
worked hard to make up for it,
but her expression after the incident was just
too stiff, and became unbearable to look at.
True, the solitude that she experienced was due to her attitude.
But I'm also responsible for just standing
by without doing anything.
When the problem was finally solved, it was
on that fateful night, in the late hours.
This was when I finally realized after seeing her shaking fingers.
I had just relieved her of the burden that
had been on her shoulders for so long.
I-I actually wasn't able to do things right...
I know this very well, but...
Men are very weak when it comes to women's tears.
The tears streaming down her face, her closed lips,
and her broken, tender, sobbing.
I just couldn't stand by and watch any longer.
I waited for her to calm herself down.
And listened to every word she had to say.
The next morning, we became one.
Before, when I was still your age,
I actually hated the way some women had romantic relationships
with their considerably older superiors.
Now that I'm one of those older superiors,
I finally understand.
There's no way I'd just let them be with younger men.
I don't plan on losing the competition.
Okay then, what are we going to have for dinner ton...
Oh, now this is something.
I figured I wanted you to take care of me tonight.
I'll work hand to meet your expectations.
I'm...
Now, don't hide it, and expose everything.
It's okay to get hornier.
You're already like this.
It's become like that because you were caressing it, Shirai-san.
Here, try to relax your legs.
But this feels embarrassing.
Oh no, I'm starting to feel weak.
No, no, not now...
Sorry, can I take a moment to answer the phone?
Hello?
It's been a long time, Dad!
Can you listen for a bit?
Okay.
Oh, I see.
Dad, what's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I'm listening.
Wait, are you with someone right now?
Oh, so it's a woman.
No...
I see.
Did I disturb you?
Way to go, Dad!
Oh, I can keep this a secret from Mom.
Its been a while since I was really entertained.
I'll hang up now then.
Sorry about this.
I'm expecting something big at my
university admission party, okay?
Good night.
For a moment, you sure were mischievous.
If you can't wait any longer, then try inserting it on your own.
Shirai-san, it's big, it's big.
Good, that's wonderful.
Just keep going.
Lower your butt slowly.
My hips are feeling tingly.
My butt is...
My insides feel like they're being stirred.
I'm going to cum quickly if this continues.
Oh no, I think I'm going to cum a lot.
I'm going to cum again.
Sh-Shirai-san, are you going to cum soon?
I want to cum together.
Oh wow, oh wow...
What do you want me to do?
Release it, release it.
From her point of view,
I must be at an age similar to her father.
But, when we're having sex like this,
it doesn't feel like it matters at all.
I even forget my rusting stamina,
and simply drown myself in pleasure.
I'll be going on ahead.
Looks like she's toned down her behavior a bit these days.
She looks cute when she's a lot more sociable.
Even jealousy, which I haven't experienced for such a long time...
My oh my, this is perplexing.
These are second hand DVDs I bought at some shop.
As I try to play the contents of one of the discs...
Miss, you look quite nervous.
Adult videos today aren't that special anymore, you know.
U-Umm...
It's okay even if your face is completely exposed.
People won't find out that it's you.
I can see so clearly, that my eyes can't help
but remained fixed on the screen.
The woman Who is in this Video...
And her voice...
This is...
Youta, I'm coming in!
Hey, answer me, will you?
Are you still fiddling with your computer?
Weren't you about to leave already?
That's why I thought of vacuuming things up beforehand.
I can clean my room on my own.
Just go already, jeez.
Okay then, I'll leave the house to you.
I'm going!
A mother and her son living together.
It's something that everyone is usually used to seeing.
The familiar sight of my mom's face.
I never thought it would be possible.
I wanted to see if I was just seeing things.
Now now, Miss, how long are you going
to stay embarrassed like this?
Miss, how old are you again?
T-Twenty-eight.
You don't look like you have a child.
U-Umm... about my child...
Boy, you sure have some huge tits.
Bounce, bounce.
This is my mother when she was still quite young.
The Mother I've Never Know
My mother in the video looks a lot younger than today.
Hence, this video must have been taken a long time ago.
That's right, this happened around ten years ago.
I heard she's already a mother at this age.
Well, we are doing an adult video about young mothers.
She's got a nice body so it ain't bad, right?
U-Umm... we're doing it right here?
This erotic body of yours is just too much to handle, right?
Now's a good time to stop playing the video.
I'm sure that it's just someone else that happened to look like her.
Stop watching already!
Miss, your nipples are starting to get big.
Are you getting horny?
No need to hold back, just moan when you want to.
This one's starting to make sloshing sounds.
Her pussy's already wet.
Okay, let's insert a dick there.
No please...
I'm going to cum outside, so I can put it in raw, right?
Whoa, this is great, your insides are wrapping
around me quite nicely, miss.
Feels good without a condom, right?
Here, I'm going to keep fucking you like crazy.
Miss, your face looks erotic.
Stop this already.
With my dick all the way in now? I don't think so.
It feels really good.
You're quite the sex fiend.
Oh no, I think I'm going to cum already.
Wait, that's not what we...
I'm cumming!
Stop!
You're holding me really tight, so I just had to cum inside.
No way...
This is terrible.
You said you were going to cum outside.
In the end, I kept watching... on, and on, and on.
I actually fapped about eight times.
After I came to my senses,
I realized that I was now in a condition
where I couldn't quell my urges.
I'm home.
Hey, Youta, what's with that expression?
Are you alright?
That night, I wasn't able to look directly into Mom's face.
There area lot of other adult videos where my Mom appeared in.
For a very short time ten years ago,
she seemed to have worked as an adult video actress.
Even though she's an actress, it was an underground business.
If not for this bizarre coincidence, I
probably wouldn't have realized.
Nothing will realty change for us now even if I know her secret.
Aren't you pushing yourself too hard by working
while studying at the university?
You always look tired to me.
Because it's all in the past now.
My beautiful, kind, and strict mother...
I want to go on a trip with you, Youta.
Now, Youta, hold on tightly to my hand.
What? I don't intend to lose to you yet, Youta!
You won't fool me with your tears, Mister.
Why can't you just say that you're sorry?
Have you brushed your teeth already?
I'll check to see if you actually did.
Youta, I bought too much at that limited-time sale.
Hold half of these for me, will you?
Youta, there it is, there's your name!
Congratulations on passing!
I love all of your dicks.
I'm sorry for being such a slut.
Please, don't come to my home.
The neighbors will hear you if you moan loudly.
I remember this kitchen...
This is the apartment that we lived in before.
I never noticed that some guys were actually visiting the place.
I beg of you, please leave already.
I don't want my son to know about this.
If you want me to go home, then you'll
have to make me cum quickly.
We should at least do it in a room.
Cum already, please.
He's going to come home soon.
Then straddle me and plead to me.
I can clearly see it entering you.
The view's really nice.
This looks great as always.
Your husband sure was an idiot.
Leaving a gorgeous lady like you.
No, that's not true.
Please, don't just talk about him.
He might have thought the kid was a burden.
No, I strongly believe,
that I can be a proper mother for him.
I want to be the proper mother for him.
She could have left too and stopped being a mother.
She could have thrown away her responsibilities
as a mother, and yet...!
And yet, she stayed by my side.
Oh, seems you're finally at it, eh.
Satisfy me, satisfy me more!
No, I'm starting to moan.
Apologize to your son.
Say you're sorry for being such a slutty mother!
No, no...
I can cum inside you anytime,
so keep gripping me tightly with that pussy.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Youta...
Don't apologize.
There's nothing for you to apologize!
Mom!
Youta, you want seconds?
Oh, yes, please.
You don’t look well these past days, are you alright?
You never tell me how you feel.
I saw her.
I won't know if you don't say it.
I'm glad I saw it.
You too mom, I want you to stay well.
Huh? Huh? Oh my, what is this about?
What's wrong all of a sudden?
That's why I too,
want to at least be a good son for her.