Licking the penis just like that.
Do you know?
To let Mishiro-kun feel good.
I specially practiced it.
S-Sorry.
Let it to me, Mishiro-kun.
I love you.
I really love you, Mishiro-kun.
Mishiro-kun.
It's all right now.
She..
That person told me those few words.
It wasn't long.
It was the start of the happiest moments of my life.
Lying on the rock hard bed, I understood everything.
The moment I reopen my eyes once more.
The fact that I was engulfed really happened.
I'm sorry.
If only I'd made it earlier.
Perhaps half of your soul wouldn't have been taken away.
Who... am I?
Your memories...
Maybe losing your memories is part of your desire.
You can call me Kazamidori.
You're Mishiro-kun.
Your soul is merely being taken away. It has yet to disappear.
Your soul and memories will surely return to you.
That creature will no doubt appear before you again.
She kept her promise.
She always stayed by my side from then on.
Taught me many things.
She is my everything.
She filled the void in my soul.
Those were happy periods where my heart healed.
But when the Aragami appeared before me once again
She died protecting me.
I'm Tsuina Mishiro.
A pleasure to meet everyone.
Impossible. There's no way it could be her!
She's already dead.
Before my very eyes.
I bet you couldn't understand the lessons having joined midway through.
Do you want me to lend you my notes for a look?
It must be boring being by yourself.
Should I introduce you?
We can start with the guys.
I'll show you around the school.
You'll need it.
You've to take into consideration your campus life from now on.
Why are you in a daze?
Did you recall some painful memories?
It's normal.
It must be that.
He was bullied previously before he moved. Those fellows sure are mean!
Is it true?
That's fine.
Why are you so uncooperative.
I was walking on the road before they attacked me suddenly.
This city is not as scary as you think.
I'll keep you company when I don't have club activities. Matane~!
Now what?
Go home.
Hey.
You've yet to even ask me a single question.
Not even my name.
Are you really so uninterested in me.
At least attempt to deny it!
You're Yuki, right?
Are you not?
Y-Yes.
Yuigahama Yuki.
Do you have anything else?
I'm going to be frank. Using this kind of attitude won't get you anywhere.
If I don't do anything for you,
my heart becomes hazy and won't go away.
D-Don't get me wrong! By doing anything, I don't mean kissing or the sort.
No lewd intentions.
Don't you feel anything?
Not even a bit?
I get it, seriously...
What's that? Monsters?
You can see them?
What do you mean?
Look out!
Yuki is able to see [Kotowari].
Are you kidding me?
That's!
Reishin!
[Kotowari] are fragments of the soul.
Only those whose soul are destroyed can see them.
The only exception are those with deficient soul, that being me.
What are those?
Do you know the [Kotowari]?
What's that?
Those monsters?
You see them as monsters?
My family are devout Shintos.
So I can see ghosts.
So sorry, Mishiro-kun.
See you tomorrow.
I'll make a move.
You blockhead!
What motives do you harbor coming to see me?
Leave. Scram at once!
Wait! Please listen to what I've to say. Please.
Granny!
That Reishin is a family heirloom.
An auntie who looked after her when she was young passed it onto her.
Even though she can't remember her very clearly.
That is Yuki's explanation.
Having that sort of reaction after hearing the name Kazamidori.
This place must be connected to Kazamidori-san.
Yuki? No.
I just said goodbye to her.
Kazamidori-san! Kazamidori-san!
She can't be alive.
Kazamidori-san is dead.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Stop! Please stop! Don't snatch away this power from me.
This is all that I have. I won't have anything else otherwise.
I need this power! I've to take it back.
You can't, uncle.
You won't be able to convey your feelings properly to your wife with such a method.
Using power of the reishin.
Yuki is able to touch that fellow's heart.
I don't know what she's able to see, though.
Go! Get rid of them!
That was close.
W-Who are you?
Hello there.
What a beautiful night sky, isn't it?
The people over there informed me you were harassed by a hoodlum.
Are you all right, Yuki-san?
You're from Granny's...
Leave the rest to us.
That person merely wanted to be accepted by others.
But no one realizes.
I know very well, the person who made a mistake is in the wrong.
Granny is the person behind it.
Mishiro-kun.
She's different.
That's a [Kotowari].
Stop running!
Tsuina Mishiro.
It's your fault I'm dead.
Killed by the thing attracted to your abominable left hand.
If only you were dead.
Damn it! Damn it!
Why would you do something so cruel?
Attacking Mishiro-kun.
What were you thinking?
Answer me, Granny!
Sorry. I'm so sorry, Mishiro-kun.
Kotowari - Fragments of Your Overflowing Heart
I've also become rather nosy.
The two of you are always together. How far have you progressed?
Anyways, be sure to enjoy what youth is all about. You two.
Seems like we've worried Kiyomi.
You're pretty close to her.
We talk almost anything, even those which might worry you.
What are you saying?
I even have dreams, it's pitch black, and the cries of a baby.
That's enough. Don't force yourself to remember.
If only Mishiro-kun is always by my side.
I'm fine now.
I didn't do anything.
I feel energize after talking to you, Mishiro-kun.
So please stay by my side from now on.
I'm even more energetic with that. Let's go!
How did the cardinal die?
She...
Granny.
What's this...
The cardinal protected you, and you met Yuki while at her sanatorium.
It's considered a miracle for you to be involved in this matter with her.
She wasn't able to see [Kotowari] before meeting you.
But you're able to see the cardinal now.
You should somewhat understand the nature of the treatment the cardinal gave you.
The cardinal filled the void of your soul using her own life.
Kazamidori-san's soul exists within my body.
Because she gave her soul to me...
Kazamidori-san was unable to fight satisfactorily.
Furthermore...
Her soul also exists inside Yuki.
Your heart was transplanted when you were very young.
It belongs to the cardinal.
The day Mishiro-kun transferred to our school.
My heart skipped a beat.
If there are remnants of auntie's memories within my heart..
That's enough!
You should have realized it now.
You killed the cardinal.
Your left arm is able to move
because your deficient soul still exists somewhere.
[Kotowari] are the overflowed fragments of your soul.
Which means?
Fragments of Mishiro-kun's soul
is alive inside the body of the aragami?
No! Only those who breed [Kotowari] can see them.
Who do you think the aragami belongs to?
That's..
...my [Kotowari].
That monster is me.
Did you have a fight with Yuki?
She's really depressed.
It's not a quarrel, right?
Yuki is also rather worried now.
The meeting is at four in the afternoon.
Take a shower and get ready.
I can't forgive myself.
For causing Kazamidori-san her death.
We're both dependant on auntie's life.
Isn't it?
You said you can't forgive yourself.
It's the same for me.
The reason I'm able to feel so happy now
is all because of her.
I'm only thinking of becoming one with you, Yuki.
Yuki.
Mishiro-kun.
Why! Why did it appear again?!
You are me.
Why did you kill her?
Why did you kill her!
You are actually me.
Is it no use even if I beg you?
Then, I have no use for you!
Get lost!
You.
Are you prepared to sacrifice your left arm to kill that [Kotowari]?
I'm prepared!
The cardinal gave me these letters.
Your past is written in it.
I've made contact with the boy burdened with the [Kotowari] we discussed before.
The boy is the old lady's grandson.
He was taken in by the old lady after his parents died.
The old lady used to perform abortions.
Her hands became unable to move.
She thought about it
but still decided to adopt the boy.
She wanted to make use of the boy's slender hands.
In order to reverse her own calamity and earn her livelihood.
The true nature of the boy's [Kotowari] was revealed.
The [Kotowari] is the boy's consciousness of sin.
He engulfed countless babies.
He said he killed the souls himself.
The boy came into contact with life.
He felt death within his palms.
I persistently urged her to stop.
The old lady refused to listen.
The worst case scenario has to be delivered.
The boy continue suffering.
He drove out his memories together with his soul
in order to protect himself from the terrifying [Kotowari].
That [Kotowari] is still alive.
I wanted to trace the origins of the aragami, and eliminate his sin.
I resolve myself into doing that.
What should I do, Kazamidori-san?
Kazamidori-san!
I...
Let's go.
You should get going.
Kazamidori-san!
Hurry and bring her...
No, don't.
Don't fight with only vengeance.
Don't doubt auntie's words.
That boy...
That boy is a fragment of your soul.
Only you can accept him.
You said to accept him?
What is it shielding?
Auntie's [Kotowari] got attacked
because it's stomach was attacked by her.
In order to get me back.
Weak point...
I'll distract it.
Aim for its stomach, Mishiro-kun!
Don't hurt Yuki!
Stop taking things away from me.
Those are!
I beg of you.
Mishiro-kun?
Please.
I've taken many lives.
I don't care what I become.
So I beg of you.
To send this feeling of life that remains in my hands
and the pitiful souls
back to their mothers.
It was always protecting them.
Unable to be born.
The many lives.
As well as the precious soul of my beloved gentle person.
Did you return them?
You've to continue living even with the burden of sin.
I am your sin.
Thank you.
Take that~
Stop that.
Mishiro-kun! Mishiro-kun!
I'm coming...
There are still times you're so spoiled.
There's no helping that, Mishiro-kun.