Waku-subs            Credits: Naoya/Fomite
Kotowari - Kimi no Kokoro no Koboreta Kakera
Reason - Fragments of Your Overflowing Heart:  Mystery Arc of the Nonsensical Detective Minamo & Mute Beauty Hatsuka
Her name is Kunashi Hatsuka.
She's no longer able to speak as a result of an incident.
I want to do something for her.
This fellow is Sanshishi.
The [Kotowari] following Hatsuka-chan.
She treats me like a fool.
We always quarrel and don't get along well.
Hey, Cabbage!
Do you know what's a Karasumi?
Karasumi?
Well, I've heard of it.
But haven't tasted it before.
What do you think it tastes like?
The size is around the same as Tarako.
I'd think the taste is somewhat similar?
Am I wrong?
It's not an issue of right or wrong.
That's a bad habit of yours.
You should admit it if you don't know.
You shouldn't try to predict or guess.
That's true.
What are you laughing about?
Well..
I'm just used to being lectured by you.
I don't want to waste my breath on a novice like you.
Sorry for being a novice.
Speaking which, aren't you also the same?
You absolutely love predicting and guessing.
Sanshishi.
I'm not an insect like you.
What are you doing, Hatsuka?
Didn't I already say I don't want it?
You're talking about patting your head, right?
So you like to be patted?
Excuse me.
I've no plans to establish such good relations with you yet.
Hmph, same here!
Just what I wanted.
You're looking for something?
Yeah!
If it's that big...
I heard all about it.
My beloved boss, Mishiro-kun.
You're playing detective again today?
Tsuburaya Minamo.
She's crazy about an ongoing TV drama serial.
So she's play acting like no tomorrow.
She sticks around me for some reason.
Hmph.
What's she up to?
Play acting? What's that.
You can rest assured and leave this case to me.
How did you manage to get that detective hat?
We've managed to solve quite a number of tough cases up till now.
The world may not know it, but you should be very clear.
Sorry you got the wrong person.
What a tragic affair.
As someone who understands me the most
If even you stop believing me...
The case this time is similar to previous ones.
The nature of the incident is the same.
Anyway, you're gonna be caught in it eventually.
Minamon.
All the credit will be yours for this case, at least we got that scene settled.
So in your mind, I'm Watson?
You do know Watson is the only person who could understand the famed detective.
You and him are worlds apart.
I don't get it at all.
The passion needed to solve this case.
I know justice exist somewhere inside your heart.
But your passion is not there yet.
Passion eh?
It's true I don't have that.
I do it as I have no other choice
That won't do!
You're an ally of justice!
I even said so yesterday.
I'm no ally of justice.
Cracking this case.
Justice to prevail.
Your lack of passion is due to inadequate thinking on your part.
Like I said-
But worry not.
I'll make up for your shortcomings.
Let's go!
First off we gather information.
Evidence is more often than not always at the site of crime.
Searching for something?
Sorry.
I regret to say
I'm unable to assist you in any way.
Thanks for your cooperation!
Tsuina...
Hey, have you tried the nikuniku burger?
Ah, Yuki and Kiyomi.
-I haven't tried yet.
Mishiroki!
No, this is...
Die once!
I'm hungry.
She's tired of it.
I'm sure she's tired of it.
Your brain won't work with an empty stomach.
It's the opposite.
Your brain becomes more alert when you're hungry.
You can't use common sense on a genius.
Who can take my place to subdue this fellow..
Hey! Where are you going?
Did you smell a trace? Famed detective.
This!
It's really cute.
Look, the accessory with flower.
It's so gaudy.
You don't know how to appreciate it at all, Mishiro-chin.
Such a design makes it easy to match clothes.
Buy it, then.
I won't.
I was only looking.
Minamon.
Just buy it if you really want it!
I said I'm only looking.
Stop making it difficult for me!
I don't.. have money.
Huh?
I got it!
Which one?
I'll buy it for you, pick one.
Mishiro-chin.
It's a gift for a girl yet you use such an attitude.
What are you thinking...
I'll buy it for you.
But I can only give it to you as a present next time.
Why!
We're still in the midst of investigation.
Famed detective.
I'll give it to you if you cooperate properly.
You're bargaining..
So you want to bargain?
It's shameless to be talking about conditions with me.
Forget it then.
I can accept such general provocation.
Hey, wait.
Do you have business with me?
Yeah, I have matters that's why I stopped you.
Matters?
What's your relation with Yuki?
Huh?
So it's about girls.
He's jealous I'm on good terms with Yuki.
So he's trying to get back at me.
It won't be so simple the next time if you don't check that arrogance of yours.
Thank you for worrying about me.
Mishiro-san.
Her face..
is totally like in the drama re-airing yesterday evening.
I'll hold tight not not let go of you, Mishiro-san.
Not for anyone else.
Just to become a pillar of support for you, Mishiro-san.
Where have I heard these lines before?
I'm alright.
I'm so small down there.
But I want you to take me at once.
Minamon.
It-It's fine.
Just like that.
Mishiro-san.
Minamon.
It's Ok.
You went in all the way so quickly.
I was merely taken aback.
Mishiro-san.
Does it feel good inside me?
Minamon.
More.. please.
You can do it anyway you like.
Don't worry about me.
Minamon... I...
I got it...
Mishiro-san, your sturdy penis.
It's throbbing inside me.
I'm so happy.
Mishiro-san.
Minamon.
Minamon.. Minamon...
Mishiro-san.
Mishiro-san! Mishiro-san!
Come.
It's all coming in.
Splurge after splurge, Mishiro-san...
It's so warm inside me.
It's not over yet.
Because your dick hasn't fully unloaded everything.
Remain like that...
Sorry, Minamon.
I was so rough...
It was wonderful.
I was also stunned.
To think joining ourselves together would be such a gentle and blissful thing.
Surely the reason has to be you, Mishiro-san.
Thank you.
Mishiro-san.
Minamon.
I'm expanding.
I'm actually expanding so much.
It's even my first time.
Because you wanted to, so I...
Mishiro-san!
I... I...
I love you, Minamon.
Minamon...
I love you!
Mishiro-san.
It's drawing and pushing me.
Down there.
The place where you are connected to me lovingly.
It feels great.
Your face...
Please let me see your face, Mishiro-san.
Mishiro-san! Mishiro-san!
Your penis..
it's about to go off.
It's throbbing deep inside me going off.
Minamon.
Come, Mishiro-san.
Your semen.
Let my deepest regions feel the gush of your semen.
Your penis will explode if this carries on.
Minamon!
Mishiro-san!
Minamon! Minamon! Minamon!
Mishiro-san! Mishiro-san!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
No...
Your penis is incredible, Mishiro-san.
It's still moving.
You're really gentle, that's why.
Then I'll become even more gentle.
Kotowari - Kimi no Kokoro no Koboreta Kakera.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to find your missing item.
Forget it!
But Hatsuka will be at a disadvantage if I'm unable to use my powers.
Really?
I'd wanted to protect Hatsuka-chan.
But I'm still helpless as it is?
What are you doing during lesson time?
I'm unable to banish humans as of now.
So Sashishi was the reason why no one came to the roof before?
You're Tsuina-kun the transfer student, I presume?
Yes.
Playing truant isn't a small matter to be taken likely.
But I might as well use this opportunity to have a talk with you two.
Kunashi-san doesn't seem have have settled into class.
But she's making an effort to blend it.
She also started learning proactively.
I thought things are finally starting to look good.
But she's started to change ever since hanging around you.
I'm not forbidding a boy-girl relationship.
You also don't seem to have many friends.
So I'm giving a word of caution if you're really dating.
You can't be together all the time.
Please open your eyes to the world outside.
Hatsuka-chan.
Any chattering can wait till later- Wait!
Why did you run?
Are you a scaredy-cat?
That's why you're always running away when you encounter situations like that.
What!
You don't want that cabbage to hear all those stuff?
You want me to back off...
I'm always going according to your wishes...
Hey, Sanshishi!
That's not really nice, Hatsuka-chan!
I think we should stop?
Hatsuka-chan.
No! I'm sorry.
Love-
You
Hatsuka-chan.
It's fine. You're sexy.
I'm gonna start touching you.
Could you spread your legs a bit more?
Does it feel good?
Good..
Is it really alright?
I'm putting it in.
We are one now, Hatsuka-chan.
Let's see it through, ok?
But are you sure?
It's gonna hurt more.
I understand.
Hatsuka-chan.
Are you feeling it?
Hatsuka-chan!
I'm almost there. Let's come together.
I'm coming inside!
You don't have to do that, Hatsuka-chan.
Sex is about feeling good together.
Hatsukoi-chan!