Did you know
that cocks can be sucked like this?
I thought of doing something to make your feel good
so I did some studying.
Sorry.
I'm going to move, okay Mishiro-kun?
I love you, Mishiro-kun.
I love you very much.
Mishiro-kun.
It's alright.
Those were the first words that she said to me.
Fleetingly short,
but it was the start of the most joyful part of my life.
As I lay on that hard bed, I understood.
That the next time I woke up,
I would learn of the fact that I was "eaten".
Forgive me.
If I had arrived sooner, I could have
saved at least half of your soul.
Who, am I?
So your memories are...
It seems that the cause of your memory loss,
is you yourself.
My name is Kazamidori.
You are Mishiro-kun.
Your soul, which was taken from you, is not yet lost.
I'll bring back the memories of your soul.
Because someday "it" will once again appear before you.
She then kept her promise.
Since then, she was always by my side,
and taught me lots of things.
She was my everything.
She filled the void made by my lost soul.
It was a tranquil and peaceful time.
But...
The Aragami that once again appeared,
took her life as she tried to protect me.
I'm Tsuina Mishiro.
Nice to meet you all.
It just can't be.
She just can't be her.
She's gone already.
Died right before my eyes.
You're not familiar with the current
lessons at the moment, right?
Shall I lend you my notes then?
Its boring to just space out by yourself, you know?
Shall I introduce you?
We could start with a few guys.
I'll show you around the school.
You'll need it, right?
Considering your school life here from how on.
Why are you spacing out?
Remembered something bad from before?
It's normal for me.
Could it be that he was being bullied before he moved here?
My, how scandalous!
Is that so?
Let's just put it that way.
Why aren't you answering me directly?
I got smacked in the face as I was walking in the streets.
This town isn't that violent, you know?
I'll go with you next time when I don't have club activities.
Bye bye!
What are you going to do now?
I'm going home.
Hey, you haven't even asked me a question or two yet!
Not even my name.
You're absolutely not uninterested in me, aren't you?
Hey, at least try to deny the last part!
You're Yuki, right?
Aren't you?
You're right, I'm Yuigahama Yuki.
Still need something from me?
Just so you know, that attitude won't work on me.
Something just needs to happen between you and me.
Or else this fuzzy feeling in my heart won't go away.
Huh?
I don't mean that!
I don't mean I'd like a kiss or something.
I don't mean it in a lewd way.
You're just...
Don't you feel anything?
Nothing at all?
Fine then! Geez.
What are those?
Monsters?
You can see them?
But they're plainly there...
Look out!
She can see a Kotowari?
No way, that's...!
The Reishin!
A Kotowari is a fragment of one's soul.
Normally, it's only seen by the life
form or entity that it came from,
but there are exceptions, such as those with damaged souls
and those who are roughly connected
to them in some way such as myself.
What was that?
Do you know what a Kotowari is?
What?
Is that what those monsters are called?
You thought it was a monster?
My family is a Shinto household,
maybe that's why I can see those monsters.
Sorry Mishiro-kun.
See you tomorrow.
See you then.
Wretched one.
Why did you come to this place?!
Leave at once!
Drive him out!
Please wait!
I have something to ask of you!
Grandma!
The Reishin
was something that was passed down within Yuki's family.
It was actually her aunt, the one that
took care of her, who inherited it.
Though, there's nothing much that
she remembers about her.
That was how Yuki explained it to me.
When I simply spoke the name of Kazamidori...
So this place is connected to her.
Yuki?
No.
I just bade goodbye to her earlier.
Kazamidori-san!
She can't be alive.
She's already dead.
I saw it with my very own eyes!
Stop!
Please stop!
Don't rob me of this power!
This is the only thing that I have!
Everything will then be lost to me!
I need this power, and I need to retrieve something back!
You can't do that mister!
This method won't help you reach out to your wife and kids.
Yuki was able to touch his heart using the Reishin.
I don't know exactly what she saw though.
Do it!
Kill them all!
Well, that was quite a risk.
Who are you?
Hello there.
What a nice night sky we have here.
There was a report made from your house that
you were being assaulted by some hoodlum.
Are you alright, Yuki-san?
You're from Grandma's...
Please leave the remaining task to me.
That person, simply wanted to be accepted.
But no one ever noticed him.
I knew.
I understand that it was wrong of him to have
done that bad thing in the first place, but...
The one who took over that was Grandma, right?
Mishiro-kun!
No, that's a Kotowari!
I won't let you get away!
Tsuina Mishiro.
It is your fault that I died.
I was devoured by the abomination that you held.
You should have been the one who died.
Damn.
Damn!
Why are you capable of doing such a terrible thing?
Driving down Mishiro-kun like that...
What were you thinking?!
Answer me, Grandma!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mishiro-kun.
Kotowari ~The spilled fragments of the heart~
Now I feel like meddling between you two.
I was wondering how far the two of you had progress
since you're always together.
Anyway, try to put a plug on that youth of yours!
Could it be that we made Kiyomi worried?
So you consult Kiyomi on a variety of things.
I talk about everything with her,
and I thought I might be bothering you enough already.
What are you talking about?
I still see those dreams.
It's completely pitch black.
I can hear children crying.
It's okay.
No need to force yourself to remember.
I hope you can be by my side forever.
Okay, now I feel better.
I didn't do anything though.
I feel better when I am with you and talking about things.
So, please stay by my side from now on.
That way I will feel a lot better.
Let's go!
How did she die?
She was...
Aunty was...
What's this?
She protected you, and allowed you meet
Yuki because of her prudence, correct?
The fact that both you and Yuki are here now,
is already considered a miracle.
She was incapable of seeing Kotowari before you came.
However Yuki, you can see her now.
You were also lighted with the treatment
that was given to him by her.
She gave up her life in order to compensate
for the damage done to your soul.
So inside of me, part of Kazamidori-san's soul is...
Then, she wasn't able to fight at her
full strength because of that?
Yuki also has a fragment of her soul.
That heart of yours was transplanted
to you when you were young.
It was hers.
The day when Mishiro came to the household,
I felt a certain throb in my heart.
So, if part of aunty's feelings remained in this heart...
Stop this!
You must have realized it already.
You are the one who killed her!
The reason why that left hand still moves
is because your damaged soul is still somewhere within you.
A Kotowari is a fragment of a disintegrated soul.
Then that means...
A fragment of Mishiro-kun's soul
is still living inside the Aragami?
No!
A Kotowari cannot be seen except by the one
who owns the soul where it came from!
Where do you think the Aragami came from?
That would be... my own Kotowari.
That was me.
You're feeling awkward towards Yuki at the moment, right?
She really feels down.
But you two did not have an argument, right?
She's really worried about you.
You're to meet her at four in the afternoon,
so you'd better take a bath and prepare.
I can't forgive myself.
For driving Kazamidori-san to her death...
Both of us hold parts of Aunty's soul, right?
Yeah.
That's right.
You say you can't forgive yourself,
and I also feel the same.
The reason why I can feel joy at this moment
is all because of her.
I can only think of being one with you right now.
Yuki...
Mishiro-kun.
Why?
Why did you come out?!
You are me!
Why did you kill...
Why did you kill her?
You are supposed to be me.
Won't any of my prayers be answered?
Then I don't need you.
Be gone!
You there.
Are you prepared to kill that Kotowari
at the cost of losing your arm?
I am.
These are letters passed on to me by her.
Your past is written there.
I was I finally able to establish contact with
the boy that is tainted by his Kotowari.
He was the grandchild of an old lady.
He was taken in after the unfortunate death of his parents.
The old lady carried out abortion for a living.
Her hands did not waver as she did her job.
She contemplated on it for while,
but in the end he took the boy in.
Then thought of using the small hands of the boy.
She taught him the techniques
that were passed down to her,
in order to keep the household.
I now know the identity of the boy's Kotowari.
It was the consciousness of his sins.
He considered the countless infants
that passed through his hands,
as souls that he himself had murdered.
He touched those souls, and felt
the stain of death within them.
I implored the old lady to stop what they were doing,
but the old lady simply would not listen.
I had yet to tell the worst thing that could come out of this.
The boy continued to be pained by it
and by attempting to pull out the fragment
of his soul that contained those memories
a frightening Kotowari came into existence.
That Kotowari is still alive as I speak.
I must find the Aragami's whereabouts
and erase his sins.
That is what my heart wants.
What should I do, Kazamidori-san?
Kazamidori-san.
I...
Let's go.
Hurry now then.
Kazamidori-san!
Save this girl, quick!
No!
Don't fight it using your hatred!
Trust the words of Aunty.
That thing...
That thing is a fragment of one's soul.
You're the only one who can accept it.
Accept it?
Is it protecting something?
The reason why Aunty's Kotowari was attacked by it
was because she attacked its belly.
She wanted to get me back.
A weak point.
I'll try to restrain it.
Target the belly, understood Mishiro-kun?
Don't you dare hurt Yuki!
Don't snatch anything from me anymore!
Those are...!
Please, I beg of you.
Mishiro-kun.
I beg of you.
Many lives were lost by my own hands.
I don't care what happens to me.
That's why, please...
Remain with me, the sensation within my hands.
May all these poor souls,
be lifted to where my mother is!
You were protecting it, right?
The lives of all those unborn children,
and the tender heart of the man I love the most.
So you went out to return those.
You will live, to continue carrying those sins.
Because your sins, are my own.
Thank you.
There!
Stop that!
Mishiro-kun.
Mishiro-kun!
I'm going to cum.
So you can also act spoiled sometimes.
You're really helpless, Mishiro-kun.