This girl is Kunashi Hatsuka.
She is unable to speak due to a certain incident,
and I want to help her somehow.
This one is Sanshishi,
an entity that is always with her.
She always treats me like an idiot.
We'd even bicker constantly with one another.
Hey, Tamanashi.
Do you know what a karasumi is?
TL Note: Karasumi (or bottarga) is salted and dried mullet roe.
Karasumi?
Well, I'm familiar with it,
but I've yet to taste one.
How do you think it will taste?
It looks somewhat like a cod roe,
so I guess it'd also probably taste the same.
Am I wrong?
Don't end it with a question.
There you go with your bad habit again.
If you don't know, then you don't.
It's okay to speculate and theorize, but you also
have to realize your ignorance about it.
Well, I guess you're right.
What are you laughing for?
Oh, it's just that I've become used
to being lectured by you already.
I'll always feel like doing it if I'm around
someone as inexperienced as you!
Sorry that I'm inexperienced then!
But you're in the same boat too, right?
You also love to speculate and theorize, Sanshishi.
I'm not as ignorant as you, though.
What is it, Hatsuka?
I already said that I don't want that!
You want me to pat her?
You yourself like to be patted, huh?
Sorry,
but I don't plan on getting along with Sanshishi that much.
My thoughts exactly!
I share your opinion on that!
You're searching for something?
That's right.
Something that big...
I heard all the details,
my beloved assistant, Mishiro-kun.
Are you playing detective today?
She's Tsuburaya Minamo.
She loves watching popular shows on TV,
and usually tries to imitate what she sees in them.
I'm always getting pushed around by her.
Who is this person?
Playing detective you say?
You can leave this case to me.
And where did she get that hunting cap?
With all of the countless cases that I have already solved,
you of all people should have more
faith in my investigative skills.
Sorry.
I mistook you for someone else.
How sorrowful.
For someone who understands me best of all,
you sure are quick to doubt my abilities.
The case a hand is quite similar
in nature to the last one since
the essence of both cases overlap with each other.
That means:
"The last one to take action is you, Minamo!"
"This case is all yours!"
Those should be the next set of dialogues.
Are you imagining me as Watson-kun in your head?
Do you know the difference between you and
the famed detective's best friend, Watson?
I have absolutely no idea.
It's the passion that's needed to solve a case.
I know that there's justice in your heart,
but passion is what you lack.
Passion, eh?
It's true that I don't have passion.
I'm just doing it because I have to.
Are you okay with that?!
You're an ally of justice remember?
I already said it yesterday.
I'm no ally of justice.
The one that would solve this case is justice.
It seems that preparation is what you really lack.
I said...!
But do not fret.
I'll compensate for what you lack.
Now, then.
Okay, let's go.
Let's start by collecting info.
Evidences are always present at the crime scene!
You're looking for something?
I'm sorry, but I don't think I can be of help to you.
Thank you for your cooperation.
That was intentional...
Have you eaten at Nikuniku Burger?
I haven't.
– I wonder what's in there?
– Yukito Kiyomi...
Mishiro-chin!
No, this is...!
Die, you scum!!
I am a bit hungry.
She's already losing interest.
I'm absolutely sure.
An empty stomach can dull our ability to think!
It's the opposite.
Hunger can clear your mind.
The world's common knowledge
isn't applicable to geniuses.
Won't she go home already?
Hey, where are you going?
Have you sniffed out a part of our
case in here, oh great detective?
This one!
This one looks really cute!
The one with the flower pattern.
It looks really gaudy.
You don't understand at all.
This design will go along perfectly with my taste in clothes.
Why don't you buy it then?
I won't.
I'm just lookin'.
Minamo, if you're buying something, buy it already!
I said I'm just going to look!
Don't cause trouble for me here!
I don't have money...
What?
Fine, fine!
Which is it?
I'm going to buy it for you, so choose whatever you like.
Mishiro-chin!
You're going to buy a girl a present,
and yet you're trying pick a fight with me.
I'm buying it,
but I'm going to give it as a present later.
Why?
We're still in the middle of our investigation,
are we not, oh great detective?
Help me with this properly, and
then I'll give it you as a present.
A trade?
So now you're using a trade as a condition?
It's despicable of you to bait me with some prize!
Shall we stop this now then?
I'm going to take that provocation then!
Hey, wait up.
Do you need something from me?
Yeah, we stopped you because
we want something from you.
Something that you want?
What's your relationship with Yukito?
Huh?
It's about a girl, huh?
They're unable to tolerate the fact that I'm close to Yukito,
so they’re probably going to settle things off right now.
If you ever get that cocky again,
you won't end up with just that.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Mishiro-san.
That pose is the same from the scene in the
drama series that was re-aired yesterday.
I'm going to stick with you, and I'm never
going to let you go, Mishiro-san.
I want to support you, Mishiro-san, and no one else.
I've heard those lines before...
I'm fine.
It's small down there, but I want to
wrap myself tightly around you.
Minamo...
It's okay. Stay that way.
Minamo?
I'm okay...
It's just that you came all the way in too quickly,
so my hips reflexed.
Mishiro-san...
Does it feel good?
To be inside me...
Minamo...
Keep doing it.
I-I'm fine with it no matter how you do it.
I'm okay, so go ahead.
Minamo, I'm...!
I know. Your sturdy cock is...
It's inside me,
and it's throbbing so hard.
Mishiro-san...
Minamo!
Mishiro-san!
– Minamo! Minamo!
– Mishiro-san!
Mishiro-san...
Mishiro-san, please cum.
It's coming out...
Your thing is twitching inside me.
It's hot.
We're not done yet.
Your thing is still pumping in me,
so let's stay like this a bit longer...
I'm sorry for being rough, Minamo.
It was really wonderful.
I was also surprised.
I never thought that connecting like
that would bring such happiness.
I'm sure that it's because it is you, Mishiro-san.
Thank you.
Mishiro-san...
Minamo!
It's opening up.
It's opening up lewdly.
It was just my first time, and yet it's
already addicted to your cock.
Mishiro-san...
Mishiro-san, I...
I love you, Minamo...
I love you!
Mishiro-san, that part of me...
You are making love to my pussy so passionately...
It feels so good!
Please show me your face, Mishiro-san.
Mishiro-san...
Mishiro-san!
Your cock is hard inside me.
It's shaking up my insides roughly.
Minamo!
Release it in me, Mishiro-san. Your cum...
Make my innermost parts feel it.
If this continues, your cock will be molded into my pussy.
Minamo!
Mishiro-san!
Mishiro-san...
Cum in me.
It's great...
Mishiro-san...
Your cock is amazing.
It's still lively inside.
It's because you're gentle to it.
Then, I'll be more gentle!
Logic ~The spilled fragments of your heart~
I'm sorry!
I can't find that thing that you're looking for.
Leave it be.
However, since I am unable to use my powers,
this will adversely effect Hatsuka.
Is that so...
I planned to protect Hatsuka-chan, but...
So I failed then?
You two!
What are you doing while classes are going on?
I haven been using my powers to keep
prying people at bay, until now.
So no one came to the roof earlier because of Sanshishi?
You are the transfer student Tsuina-kun, I presume?
Yes.
I'll hold you responsible for ditching class,
but I guess this is a good opportunity for this.
I need to talk to you about something.
Kunashi-san seems to be unable
to it in with the rest of the class,
so everyone's trying to make her blend in.
I thought it was a good thing because her
grades have also improved as a result,
but she's changed after she started hanging out with you.
I'm not saying that I'm against boys and girls socializing,
since you're also the type that doesn't
have that many friends.
But let me say it anyway.
Both of you must not get cooped up in your own world.
Lay your eyes beyond and towards the outside world.
Hatsuka-chan.
You can talk with each other anytime after...
Wait there!
Why did you run away?
You're a coward, Hatsuka.
That's why you're still running away from that thing.
What's with that?
Are you going to just lose it all and
never hear anything about it?
You're telling me... to disappear?
I was only following your will.
Hey, Sanshishi!
Hatsuka-chan...
This is no good.
Wanna stop?
Hatsuka-chan...
No, well... I-I'm sorry.
I love you...
Hatsuka-chan.
Don't worry. You look sexy.
Then, I'm going to touch it now.
Can you raise your legs?
Does it feel good?
Are you really okay with this?
Well then, here I go.
We're now one, Hatsuka-chan.
Are we going to go all the way?
But is that okay?
It will hurt a lot more.
Okay, then.
Hatsuka-chan...
Are you getting horny?
Hatsuka-chan!
Hatsuka-chan...
Just a little more... Let's cum together.
I'm going to cum inside.
Hatsuka-chan, you don't need to do that.
Sex is somethin that is done to
make both partners feel good.
Hatsuka-chan...
Logic ~The spilled fragments of your heart~
The Nonsensical Detective Minamo and Lovely
Mute Girl's Hatsuka's Mystery Chapter.
How was it?
Did you enjoy watching it?
Oh, oh, that's great!
– Well then, till next time...
– Wrong!
There's still the next preview, right?
Oh, yeah, right.
Geez, that's just so you.
Well then, once again.
Next Time!