This is how it's done... sucking a dick, I mean. Did you know that?
I wanted to be able to show Nishiro my feelings, so I studied hard.
Sorry!
I can do it, Nishiro.
I love you, Nishiro, I really love you!
Nishiro...!
It'll be all right now.
Those were the first words that person spoke to me.
Such a short phrase...
That was the start of my happiest times.
Lying painfully in a hard bed...
I understood everything.
The next time I opened my eyes,
I realized that something had been eaten.
I'm sorry. If I had been there a little sooner...
but half of your soul was taken...
Who... am I?
Your memory...
...It could be that you've lost your memories because that is what you wished for.
My name is Kazamidori.
You are Nishiro.
Your soul that was stolen is still not lost.
Your soul and your memories - I'll definitely return them to you.
Because that thing will definitely appear before you again.
She kept her promise.
After that she was always with me, and taught me a lot of things.
She was my everything. She filled the missing part of my soul.
It was a carefree and happy time.
But when that spirit appeared for a second time, she died protecting me.
I'm Tsuina Nishiro.
Nice to meet you all.
Impossible. It can't be her. She died right before my eyes!
You don't understand the material, right? Want to review my notes?
It's boring by yourself, right? Shall I introduce you? I know boys too!
Hey, we'll show you around. That's important, right? Think about your student life from here on!
What are you spacing out about?
Huh?
What, were you remembering something painful?
Just normal stuff.
Hey, I bet it's that he had someone special before he moved! That's totally it!
Is that true?
Let's go with that.
Why are you dodging the question?
If you go down a dark path, you're gonna get hit.
It wasn't that dark of a path, you know.
I'll hang out with you again when I don't have club activities. Cya!
What'll we do now?
I'm going home.
You know, you haven't asked me a single question.
Not even my name! Are you not interested in me at all?
Hey, spit it out!
Yuki, right?
It is Yuki, isn't it?
Yeah... Yuinahama Yuki.
What, is there something else?
I'll say this now, but it's pointless to ask with that kind of attitude! I...
My heart is telling me that you and I have to have something together.
...Huh?
Wait, not like that! By "something" I don't mean a kiss or whatever! I didn't mean anything perverted!
Do you really not feel anything here? Not at all?
Fine, whatever!
What are those? Monsters?
You can see them?
I can see them, but what...
Watch out!
Yuki can see the Kotowari?
No way! That's...
a Drive?!
Kotowari are fragments of souls.
They're only visible to the very spectre that broke that soul.
Someone with a damaged soul or someone who has a strong connection to them is the only exception, like me.
What was that back there?
Have you heard of "Kotowari"?
What do you mean? Is that a ghost?
Did you think those were ghosts?
I live at a Shinto shrine... maybe that's why I can see ghosts and that kind of thing.
I'm sorry, Nishiro. See you tomorrow.
Later.
I can't believe this!
What do you mean by showing your face in front of me?
Keep this kind of thing outside!
Please wait! There's something I want to ask of you!
Grandmother!
That Drive was handed down through Yuki's family.
She inherited it from her real grandmother who took care of her in her childhood.
She didn't remember her grandmother at all...
That was Yuki's explanation.
Just as I was recalling Kazamidori's name, I knew that place was connected to her.
Yuki? No... I just parted ways with her a minute ago.
Kazamidori!
She couldn't be here. She died!
I saw it myself, didn't I?
Stop! Please stop!
Please don't take this power away from me! This is all I have...
I'll have nothing!
I need this power! I have to be able to use it...!
It's no good, mister! You can't reach your wife or your mother like this!
With the Drive's power, Yuki can reach this man's heart.
I don't know what she saw there, but...
Do it! Attack them!
Geez... that was close, huh?
Who... who are you?
Hello there. Lovely sky tonight, isn't it? Well...
That gentleman was bothering you two, right?  We saw that and had to step in.
Are you safe, Miss Yuki?
You're... from grandmother's place...
Please leave the disposal to us.
That person just wanted to be recognized...
But, nobody would notice him.
I can understand that. To say that he was bad because he made a mistake...
The person behind all that was my grandmother.
Nishiro!
No. That's...
a Kotowari!
Running away?!
Tsuina Nishiro. It's because of you that I died.
I was devoured by a disgusting thing that came from you.
It'd be better if you died.
Damn... Damn...
How can you do something so awful? Hurting Nishiro like that...
What are you thinking?
Answer me, grandmother!
Sorry...
I'm sorry, Nishiro.
The Shards Torn From Your Soul
I'm starting to want to try too!
You two are always clinging to each other, I've been wondering how far it'd go!
Anyway, make sure you're living out your youth properly!
I wonder if we made her worry.
You talk to Kiyomi about a lot of things, huh?
We talk about pretty much everything. I was wondering if I'd worried you too.
What are you talking about?
I still have that dream.
It's dark, and I hear a baby crying...
It's fine. Don't worry about it too much.
It'd be nice if you would always stay by my side.
I feel better now.
I didn't do anything.
Just talking to you makes me feel better.
So... please stay with me.
Now I think I feel even better.
Let's go!
How did Tsuki die?
She was...
Grandmother was... ah!
What is this...?
Tsuki was protecting this bug, coddling and sheltering this meek thing who met Yuki, right?
The fact that this thing and Yuki are both here itself is like fate!
Until this bug was here you could see Kotowari.
But, Yuki, this bug can see Tsuki right now!
The soul that Tsuki gave him too was given for a reason.
In order to repair the piece of soul he lost, she used her own life.
Kazamidori's soul is inside of me?
Then, the fact that she couldn't fight fully was because I had part of her soul...?
And her soul is inside of Yuki, too.
This bug's heart was transplanted when you were a child.
It's Tsuki's.
That day when Nishiro arrived, I felt something in my chest.
If that was the thoughts... of my grandmother...
Stop already!
You've probably noticed, right, you bug?
You're the one who killed her!
The reason that left hand can move is because the part of your soul that was fractured is living somewhere!
After all, Kotowari are pieces of damaged souls.
So then...
the piece of Nishiro's soul is living inside of that spirit?
No! The only people who can see a Kotowari is the person who lost a piece of their soul.
So what does that make that thing?
That is...
my Kotowari.
That thing was me!
Things have gotten strained between you and Yuki, right? She's really clammed up!
It's not like you fought or anything, right? Yuki is still really worried.
We're meeting up today, so take a bath and get over there, okay?
I can't forgive myself!
I caused Kazamidori to die...
Both of us are here because of my grandmother's own life.
That's true, isn't it?
You said you can't forgive yourself, but I'm the same.
Because the fact that I can feel this happiness is because of my grandmother...
I can't think about anything but being together with you anymore.
Yuki...
Nishiro...
Why... why would you appear?
You're part of me!
Why did you kill...
Why did you kill her?!
You're supposed to be mine!
But even if I try and will you to do something, it's useless?
In that case... I don't need you!
Just disappear!
You insect.
Even with this left hand, do you think you can kill that Kotowari?
I do!
This is a letter that Tsuki sent with me.
Your past is all here.
As we discussed previously, I was able to make contact with the child who is responsible for the Kotowari.
He was taken in from his parents by an old woman.
The old woman was withdrawn.
She cannot move her hands.
She thought to take care of the boy and use him to repair her hands.
I understand the true form of the boy's Kotowari. It's the awareness of his sins.
The woman who took care of him had him take the souls himself...
He could feel the lives and pull them into his hands.
I tried to ask her to stop repeatedly, but the old woman would not listen.
I knew this could only come to grief.
The boy's despair continued, and so he cast away the memories of these souls,
which lead to something truly frightful.
From the bottom of my heart, I hope that I can cleanse this boy's sins.
What should I do? Kazamidori...
Kazamidori! I...!
Let's go.
You better hurry.
Kazamidori!
Quickly, this girl-!
Stop! Don't fight just out of hatred!
Don't waste what my grandmother did. That child...
that child is a piece of a soul. Nishiro, you're the only one who can stop it!
I have to stop it?
Is it different somehow?
Grandmother's Kotowari was attacked by that child because she attacked its tummy.
To get me back...
Weakness...
I'll restrain it! I'm counting on you, Nishiro!
Don't you hurt Yuki! Don't take anything else from me-!
That's...!
I'm asking you, please!
Nishiro...?
Please!
I stole away many lives.
Somehow, I can't seem to care.
So, I'm asking you!
What's left in these hands,
the feeling of those poor souls...
Please let them go to their mother!
You were always protecting them, huh?
The many lives that couldn't be born...
The precious heart of the kind person I love...
Were you saying this from the beginning? I'll forgive these sins and live properly now.
Because... your sins are mine too.
Thank you!
How's this?
Hey, cut it out!
Nishiro... Nishiro! Ah, I... I'm gonna-!
That spot really does get me going.
I can't help it with you, Nishiro!