Yay!
Your neighbor?
So, is it really him?
Your hand writing is so messy.
You're such a moron.
Live hard-on...
Hey...
Dummy...
You're really into it!
Uncensored?
Really?
Okay!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, this room.
Let's begin. Let's begin.
Very good, Hiroyuki.
Don't mention my name!
Oh, sorry, sorry.
It's okay!
Just show off your
well hung meat stick.
Hey, Mitsugu, you're so fucked up.
You're not a woman.
Okay!
I'm not a woman, I'm an artist.
Hey, now take off your underwear.
Moemi and Reina are waiting
to see your boy in front of the TV.
What?
Are you going to
show it to somebody?
Don't worry, I'm just kidding.
Oh!
It's small.
Just wait and see.
It's not hard yet.
Make it hard.
Shut up.
I can't make it hard so quickly.
I see.
That makes sense.
Do you want to see my breasts?
Ah, stop that!
That doesn't help!
Hmph, you're so picky.
Okay. I'll give you a blow job.
Oh!
I'll do it by myself.
It's like a comedy show.
It's fun.
Oh, you're not circumcised.
Sorry, Moemi, he's not hard yet.
Oh!
When it gets hard, it'll be fine.
Now you're bragging!
So show it to me.
Your $100 cock power.
Oh, shut up.
Now it's getting there!
Here is revealed the pink dick!
Are you totally an asshole?
Hey, how did you like it?
Yeah, it was cool.
You want to see the real thing?
Is that possible?
Oh!
Well...
It was just a simple start.
A video camera
Mitsugu bought one day...
Maybe I expected it from the beginning.
Somewhere in my mind...
There was also a part of me
getting excited about this play.
It's okay!
Oh? But...
I already called him.
You better think about it,
this is a once in a lifetime chance.
It's live anyway.
Well said!
I knew you were reasonable.
The way you talk.
Well...
Here he comes.
What? Hey, wait!
Hey, hey, give it up.
Hey, Hiroyuki, we waited for you.
Hello.
H-Hello.
Hi.
Hey, hey.
Here, here.
Come on in.
Stop!
By now, the smart
Hiroyuki could have figured it out.
This is Reina and Moemi.
Oh, hiya.
Anyway, I want you to show it to us.
Your dick.
What?
You, are you insane?
Hey, you got that right!
Don't be a sissy.
We're not strangers.
Did you show them the video?
Correct, correct!
Whoa, shit!
Hold it!
Oh, no!
Don't worry about it.
We all know your dick's
front and back, and each vein.
Then you don't have to see it anymore.
No, you know what we want.
Take a good look.
Here, such pretty girls and
they're happy to look at your live cock.
You won't have this
kind of opportunity again.
Well...
Be nice, Hiroyuki.
Don't you want to show it?
Just display your meat
stick in front of this pretty face.
Maybe these sisters will
do something good for you.
Won't you, Moemi?
What? Well, I don't know...
Moemi here looks innocent, but she
has the biggest interest in your dick.
Hiroyuki, ever get a blow job?
If you're nice, she'll do it for you.
Really, Moemi?
Uh, well, I don't know.
It's okay.
Hiroyuki, show it to her.
Hold it, Hiroyuki.
O-Oh!
It's half way there, you pervert.
Hey you, shooting again?
Yes.
I found something.
Look, look!
His balls are moving.
Balls...
What are you doing,
moving by yourself?
I don't know...
Can his dick move, too?
Dick...
Do it.
Yeah! Exactly!
That's not how you should ask...
You're great!
The best neighbor I could have.
Reina, touch him and make it harder.
What, touch it?
Sorry, this girl is scary.
Hey, it's getting harder!
How can it be hard so soon?
As you can see, he's my horny boy.
What a rude thing to call him.
This horny boy has a secret!
When he gets frustrated,
he transforms into jerk off boy!
You'll see white
stuff shooting from there.
Anybody want to see it?
Then, anybody want to shoot it?
Okay, Moemi!
Hey, I haven't said anything.
Okay, okay.
Don't say anything.
It's pretty easy, so just try.
I don't mean that.
I tried once and it was okay.
It's really hard and I was impressed.
Oh?
Well, Miss Moemi, just try once.
What?
Uh...
Is it okay?
Uh... Y-Yeah.
Oh...
It's really hot, your meat stick.
How do you feel, Moemi?
Oh...
It's kinda cool.
Give him a lick.
What?
My sweet hieghboor
is doing this just for us.
You cold hearted woman.
But...
M-Moemi, please.
Hey, now we have a couple.
She's going down on him!
This is quite an angle but...
Maybe try and shoot this angle?
Oh, a point of view shot?
So, the smart girl
makes a clever comment.
What the hell?
I can't shoot by myself, so
Hiroyuki why don't you take over?
No, Hiroyuki, are you really shooting?
Oh!
Is it good?
You go, girl! Woo hoo!
Is this okay?
What should I do?
Hey Moemi, how about under there?
Under there?
There, the balls.
Well...
Oh!
How's it feel?
Touch it.
Really, there are two balls.
Lick them, lick them.
Those balls...
What?
You mean here?
What's the problem, you
were giving head already!
It's totally okay, right Hiroyuki?
Y-Yeah.
Cool, it's getting bigger!
Can you feel it Hiroyuki?
It feels great!
Hear that, Moemi?
He likes it the way you do it.
Aren't you happy, Moemi?
Oh!
Oh, sorry.
Huh?
What?
It's sticky, oh no!
You came on my head?
No!
It's dripping on my face!
Oh, good, good, Moemi.
Very pretty.
Now, take off your panties.
Well... okay.
Now, we're going down.
What are her private parts like?
Oh, her slit is so visible?
What, you shaved?
Very good, so good, super good!
You're so outdated.
Even though I'm a
woman, I'm turned on.
I feel it!
See, this is her pussy.
Reina, zoom in!
Let's open it.
It has a very pretty curtain on the edge.
How about the other side?
Let's flip it.
I see you take good care of it.
No sign of scum!
Stop it, Mitsugu!
Let's get closer now.
Oh, what's this?
Your clit still has skin on it.
Was it alwas like this?
Huh? What's that?
Oh my, she doesn't know.
Then it's a special presentation...
It's Moemi's "skin off her clit" show!
Ready?
Go!
Well, we're live for this program.
We have here pretty,
innocent Moemi, and her pretty clit.
Let's take the audience to
the unexplored world of mystery.
This is so pretty!
It's like a slice of fruit!
It's like a piece of jewelry!
Oh, I just made an artistic comment.
That's how pretty her clitoris is.
Oh, it's getting fat!
It's a pretty girl's hard on!
But, it's still got skin on.
It's phimosis.
Moemi's dick!
I'll give you a blow gob, Moemi.
Oh!
No, you're licking it.
Because it may hurt when it's skinned.
Is Reina's skinned?
Yeah, it's skinned.
Show me, show me.
Have a good look, Moemi.
Good, it's skinned.
You're excited.
You look so uptight, so
do whatever you need to.
You're so outdated.
Look Moemi, you can be like that.
Is there anything good about that?
Yes, of course.
If you have skin on,
boys won't like you.
Really?
It's true.
If it's temporary, that's okay.
How about mine?
Well... Yours is... maybe temporary.
See, it's skinned.
Moemi, try it yourself.
It feels like the shape is different.
What are you talking about?
That's normal, you know.
Pinch the skin like that, and
you can masturbate like a guy.
No, you don't need to do that!
She's moaning a lot!
I'll give you some more.
What?
You're so hard, Moemi!
It's great.
Pretty girl's big hard-on!
We want to see her shoot
her come, but that's too much.
I can't be jelious.
No!
Oh, it's a surprise!
This is the legendary
female come shooting?
I've never seen this before!
This is such precious
footage, I'm touched.
Live from an
unknown place in the city...
That's all the time we have today.
Good-bye.
Actually, I don't want it so intense.
Just a little soft touch is enough.
That was too much.
You must be kidding!
You're so weird!
I prefer the soft way, too.
You're just a pervert.
Okay, I won't give you a copy now.
No, I didn't mean that.
I just made an honest comment.
Reina.
What?
We're all done with shooting indoors.
Sneaky shooting is outdated!
We've got to start shooting outdoors!
Shooting outdoors?
You're a moron, a real moron!
So, in the line nobody recognized us...
So, what is your plan?
You're on a roll, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You have no guts, Moemi.
Because...
That's why I'm doing it with you.
O...
...kay.
We'll go on three.
Next stop is Onko, Onko.
Okay, I'm ready!
Ready and go!
Good, you look perfect.
Uh...
Let's go, shoot and run!
What?
Moemi, hurry!
Oh!
No, hey!
Oh! Hold it, I can't stop.
No, wait for me!
Oh, what do I do?
Ready?
Here I go!
Hey, h-hold it...
Okay!
It's coming.
M-Mitsugu!
She's peeing backwards!
No!
Go around!
Is this good?
Get over here!
Over here?
Almost.
That shot!
Good!
You look so sexy, Moemi!
Let's begin!
Yes, go ahead!
Shit!
Somebody's
coming, somebody's here!
Moemi!
What? But!
What are we going to do?
Run, run away!
But, it's still going!
Hey, wait!
Reina! Mitsugu!
Don't leave me here!
Oh, no!