What is a girl like you doing at a store like this?
Hey, cut it out!
- No! Don't rape me!
- Rikuro!
Is that your woman? Do something about her!
You don't have to tell me that!
Calm down. You're the quiet Miki-chan, right?
I want you to find my missing brother.
With the clothes I'm wearing now, it's
impossible for me to do it alone.
But if it's the great detective Annerose-san,
she'd definitely be able to find him for me.
That's what the brown-skinned girl told me.
Brown-skinned?
Ah, it must be Aishu-san.
Anyway, it must've been quite a feat getting
here all by yourself in this scary town.
Japan's largest abandoned city, Amidahara.
This place is also known as the Dark City.
Humans and residents from the underworld
live together in a slum district.
Currently, criminals and killers are increasing
day and night in this lawless district.
Rikuro-san? Tachibana Rikuro-san? Are you listening?
A-Ah, yeah. I'm listening Miki-chan.
Is there something wrong with my chest?
No, it's just been a while since I met a human girl.
I'm so happy that I was staring without thinking.
Leave this to me. I will definitely find your brother for you.
T-Thanks.
What are you blushing for, you stupid human!
Ouch...
Michiko, what the hell do you think you're doing!?
I finished shopping already. I'm going home.
Well, I'll ask Annerose-san for you.
Let's meet here tomorrow.
Stop dawdling, you stupid human!
KOUTETSU NO MAJO ANNEROSE
The Witch's Servant: Witchslave
What's with that cocky attitude!?
Who the hell do you think you are?
I'm Mitchiko-sama. Do you have a problem with it?
You're supposed to be Annerose-san's maid.
Don't order me around.
You're facing a real demon.
Don't talk to me like you would a normal human.
Damn. Your face is cute but your personality is just horrible.
I'll tell you this while I'm at it.
W-What is it?
It looks like you get along well with Annerose.
But she belongs only to me.
You're in the way.
I'll have you die here.
Wai...
Michiko-san?
I'll say that the stupid human was done in
by miasma and brutally burned and eaten.
I-It's not a joke anymore!
I'm serious. Die, you stupid human!
Hey doggies, it's dinner time.
Thanks for saving me!
I owe you...
You are mine.
You will became one of my undeads.
So you've awaken.
This thing has already been up though.
A-Aishu-san. Y-You... When did you...
When did you get erect, you mean?
T-That's not what I...
You're so health . When our bod was oin back
to normal, this was standing up the entire time.
As expected of a delicacy that Anne noticed.
N-Now that you mention it, you were the one that told Miki.
Ah, you mean that girl with the machine gun.
I'm glad that you guys got to meet.
Aishu-san, why are you doing this?
I was thinking about this since before... about you.
You're a little cute but why did Annerose choose
an ordinary student with no redeeming qualities?
I'll have you tell me your secret.
There's really no secret.
Keep this a secret from your master.
Looks like you've been holding it in.
S-Sorry.
I'm fond of licking the penises of guys I like.
Aishu-san!
It smells and your smegma is so sticky. I love it!
Nice eyes. Let me peek into your future.
F-Future?
Is this your first time getting head?
I-It's my first time.
I see. You can move more intensely.
It's okay to use my mouth and throat. Go deep inside me.
A-All the way inside?
Get it deep inside. Make my throat go crazy.
Give it to me. My throat.
- Aishu-san.
- Give it to me!
Aishu-san!
More. Give me more. Make my throat crazy!
I'm sure Anne will do this to you in the future.
She'll make a contract with you and
let you use her mouth anytime.
Annerose-san will?
Its flavor is so deep and delicious.
This is?
This is your private world.
I touched just a little bit of your inner power. It's incredible.
It's covered with sperm and life energy.
My inner power?
Your soul was stolen by the witch making you immortal.
But that doesn't happen to everyone.
You had the power since the beginning.
Thanks to purity of your power, you
were able to become immortal.
Me?
Even if you're one of Annerose's undead, Michiko went too far.
I'll help you be able to live with that demon.
Use this.
This?
When that girl is sleeping, try blowing it.
I've returned.
Ri-kun.
Someone like you with a slave standing, just where were you?
Annerose-san.
Because Ri-kun was so slow, I had to make dinner.
Michiko cut me up into pieces.
Again? But you were able to come back quite quickly.
Aishu-san picked me up.
Aishu?
Aishu and I have had a bad relationship ever since we were kids.
She loves getting involved with other people's troubles, someone
that enjoys it from the bottom of her heart. A perverted sadist.
It's best if you don't get too involved with her.
I-I understand.
I'm going to sleep. Because of Ri-kun, I drank too much.
I'm sleeping too.
I'll leave the cleaning to the stupid human.
If it's not cleaned properly, I won't let you off.
Shut up!
I know Annerose-san said it like that, but
I can't forgive that bitch, Michiko.
W-What was that?
W-What is this? I can't get it off me!
This is Aishu-san's magical power?
It was you? You did this to me?
Nice look, Michiko-kun.
Shut up!
Hurry and get this off me!
No way.
Try to remember what you've put me through up till now.
What kind?
Like cutting off your head when we first met,
putting things in your food and drink...
What else was there?
You cut me up ruthlessly with an axe today.
That's right. I wanted to make your body suffer.
I even scattered your body parts.
You're really persistent you stupid human.
I guess this means you have no intention
of reflecting on your actions then.
W-What do you think you're doing!?
Hey, if you're not careful, you might hurt yourself.
I-It's cold!
Hey!
Why are you cutting my clothes!?
Stop!
Here, it's done.
W-What do you mean it's done?
Don't look at me, you stupid human!
This is the end of your tough act, Michiko.
Stop it.
T-That... Don't touch it.
The fact that you're responding like this...
I'm sure you masturbate. You erotic demon!
T-That...
If you're not honest, I'll do this!
I-I don't... masturbate.
You're still not being honest. Then how about this?
S-Stop!
You're really getting wet. How about this then?
S-Stop...
I'll cum...
I'll cum from the hands of a stupid human!
Then cum! Cum while getting your clitoris and cunt played with.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Michiko. There's something coming out of your cunt.
Don't look!
Don't come out. Don't look at me.
It's flooding out of your pussy.
This wet Michiko is so cute.
I-It's not like that. I won't forgive you.
Here, look at this.
Y-You're going to use that...
Yup. I'll make Michiko go crazy.
It's time for your punishment.
I'm putting it in.
Michiko's pussy is filled with my penis!
Huh, you're a virgin?
I won't forgive you.
I got it.
I'll take responsibility and mold your virgin
pussy into the shape of my dick!
Suck my fingers.
Wow. A lewd noise is coming from down there.
Michiko can feel my dick inside her.
I-It hurts, but feels so good!
Let's get along with each other just for now.
Become mine for now!
Don't keep thrusting it in me.
You'll break me.
If you keep doing this to me, I'll become
the woman of a mere human!
I'm cumming. I'll cum inside you!
Don't! Don't make me the woman
of a human. Don't cum inside me!
No!!
You came so deep inside me!
That was really good.
Are you okay, Michiko?
I'll kill you.
I guess you haven't become my woman yet.
Let's make a truce for today, okay?
Is it okay if I punish you again?
J-Just do want you want.
I just need to punish you a little more before
you become the perfect sex slave.
I-It's morning!?
A-Annerose-san... I gotta go.
She always sleeps in such scandalous outfits.
I can't believe this is the Steel Witch that shook Amidahara.
I always manage to hold it in but I can't hold back today.
B-B-But if she wakes up...
She has an awfully low blood pressure,
I'm sure everything will be okay.
Show courage, Tachibana Rikuro. You're a guy right!?
Wow.
It's so soft.
It's Annerose-san who provokes me every day. It's her fault.
Annerose-san can feel it? I'm so glad I'v alive.
T-These are...
Annerose-san's breasts that I can only see in my dreams.
I can't hold it in anymore. I-I'll do it!
C-Can it be that Annerose-san is awake?
She's actually awake and accepting me?
A-Annerose-san's nipples are sticking up!
She can feel my penis.
Wow, Annerose-san's breasts...
They're so soft and hot...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Wow, I came all over Annerose-san's face.
Here, Annerose-san. Drink all of my sperm.
I guess it's not enough then. I got it.
Here.
It's here right, Annerose-san?
Then I'll do this for you.
I'll let you cum, Annerose-san, with my finger!
Annerose-san, cum with your pussy!
I knew it. Just my finger is not enough.
I won't satisfy Annerose-san with just my finger.
Then, I'll put it in, Annerose-san.
M-My penis is inside Annerose-san's pussy.
I'll thrust it in deep inside you.
What? Ri-kun?
Annerose-san. This is just a dream. Go back to sleep.
A dream?
No way! Annerose-san is also a virgin?
Wow, I'm Annerose-san's first man!
- I'll let you feel it some more.
- Ri-kun...
What are you...
Annerose-san, Annerose-san!
I can't hold it in anymore! I'm cumming!
I'll cum inside you and fill you up!
Inside is okay, isn't it? Isn't it?
Annerose!!
Wow.
What should I do? I let out too much!
Are there tissues?
Ri-kun, you're heavy.
T-This is...
Just what did you do to me?
For a slave, how dare you attack your master!
You better be prepared!
N-No. Well...
Well, that's the punishment you were Expecting.
Annerose-san...
I found you, Annerose.
Ri-kun. For someone with a slave standing,
do you realize what you've done to me?
But that's because Annerose-san is so attractive.
Did it feel good doing it with me?
Of course! Thanks for letting  me do it with you last time.
Hey, you stupid human. You also came all over me.
Ri-kun, what do you mean?
Well... a lot of things happened.
Do you want to die for real?
Stupid human. Go to hell!
Next time: Annerose's second episode.
See you next time!
Who the hell are you?