W-Who are you?
Miki-chan?
I am pleased to make your acquaintance.
My name is Barde Barde.
You're the sorcerer that recently came to Amidahara?
What we desire is the philosopher's stone,
which is inside that woman's heart.
Damn, if you do that Aish-san will...!
She will die for our grand plan.
What did you say?
Now, hand it over to me.
Give me the philisopher's stone!
You sure planned far ahead, didn't you?
All for our grand plan,
and I shall accomplish it in a few moments.
But Anne is still here.
I think nothing of that woman.
If she interferes, then I'll just eliminate her.
Will it really go according to your plan?
It will.
Now, let’s finish this.
This is the end,
so I'll savor this while I can.
Aish-san!
A poison from some lame sorcerer would never...
No way...
Cumming while being caressed like this...
I don't want to cum, and yet my body is cumming on its own!
There's more aphrodisiac for you over there.
You came while this boy penetrated your womb, yes?
Then I'll just have to penetrate your womb again.
Don't compare this vile thing to Rikurou's dick!
I wonder how long you'll be able to hold on to that thought.
This isn't real, this can't feel good.
My pussy is going to break!
I'm going to break!
Here's your beloved cum.
Enjoy it to the fullest.
This can't be...
I'm cumming!
Just like a prostitute, I'm sure you've noticed it well.
That right there is a special type of cum.
A powerful aphrodisiac, quite fitting for your final moments.
A cum aphrodisiac...?
As long as Its effect lasts,
even if I rip off one of your limbs, you'll
only be able to feel pleasure.
You're going to suffer all the way.
My womb is going to burst...
What is this...? It feels sticky...
It's starting to feel good.
My womb...
Looks like the preparations are complete.
Aish-san!
That amount would have normally made someone insane,
but at the very least, you can no longer resist.
Your heart,
the source of your power,
the philosopher's stone.
It shall be mine!
Stop!
It feels good.
It feels too good.
I'm going crazy...!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
That's right, just cum.
It's driving straight toward your heart as it eats away your flesh.
Die while cumming.
You bitch!
My pussy, my womb,
it's still going through,
it's violating me all the way inside...
It feels good...
I've never felt this kind of pleasure before...
This is the end.
Do you have any last words?
Remember this!
Of course I will.
I'll remember the slutty witch who died
while drowning in her carnal desires.
Die, Aishwarya Ray!
Oh, so this is the philosopher's stone.
Aish-san!
Clean the mess up.
What in the world is this?
I see, you are the vessel that person is seeking.
Fleuretty!
How do you know my name in the demon realm?
So you are Barde Barde.
Hmph, I have no time to waste with witches.
My loyal servants!
Capture Fleuretty!
That Miki,
so she was an agent of that sorcerer after all?
Then... I don't have to hold back!
You're just a puppet.
Don't underestimate me!
Michiko, behind you!
Fleuretty, I demand you come to my side!
Michiko!
I even captured the vessel.
Now the gates to the demon realm shall soon open!
So your plan was to link Amidahara and the demon realm?
Chaos and strife that is even worse than now,
and the never-ending madness between demons and humans
I shall be the creator of that new world.
Thanks to you all,
the key to that gate, the philosopher's stone,
and the vessel is now in my hands.
As thanks,
I shall now grant you a peaceful death.
Watch out!
I'm disappointed to see a witch of Amidahara like this.
Die!
Wait just a moment, Barde-sama.
After the incident with Barde,
I woke up, alone.
I was thrown away somewhere in Amidahara.
Ever since that day,
Annerose never showed up again.
Michiko's whereabouts is also unknown.
I don't have the slightest idea of where to look.
Annerose-san, Michiko...
Where are you two?
What a splendid view, Fleuretty.
Doing all this to me...
Don't ever think I'm going to give you a quick death!
So you can still talk impudently.
Now then, it's time for your orgasm.
What is this?
This is really lame, you hear me!
The aphrodisiac that oozes out of it will just keep on flowing,
and will keep pouring into you.
This thing is...!
It's pushing in...
It's entering my ass!
Something weird is rotating inside my ass!
Well? How does it feel to be penetrated in the ass for the first time?
What is this...
Oh no...
Something weird is in my ass...
No, please, not my ass...!
You're such a prideful demon.
My torture seems to have actually made you cum.
Shut up, I didn't cum at all!
I didn't cum in my ass!
There it is again.
I'm going to cum again.
I just can't stop cumming.
I mustn't cum, and yet...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming again...!
I can't stop it...
I can't stop the pleasure in my ass!
That voice, it's Michiko's...
Barde Barde, I'll never forgive you!
Hey, can you hear me, Annerose?
Her cries sound quite cute.
I'm referring to your servant.
Now then, do you want to cry too?
No...
Okay.
I'll make you cry soon.
This is good, Annerose.
With this, you'll be able to have sex, with both your pussy and ass.
My oh my, can't talk?
I'm sure you're just feeling thirsty with your throat being dry.
Oh yes, I'll let you have a taste of my special cum juice.
It tastes raw!
Well?
How's my cum juice?
Tastes great, right?
It's so good that you'll crave it forever.
Of course it's not!
Looks like you want some more.
Here, drink it all up.
Drink it until you love it.
I can't breathe.
I'm going to drown.
I'm going to drown in cum!
Drinking lots like that...
Has its taste seeped into you now?
It keeps pouring inside.
Lots of cum is just pouring inside me.
It's seeping inside me!
Oh no, I'm going to cum while being violated in both holes!
I'm cumming!
Oh my, you're such a slut.
You came just by drinking cum?
You pervert.
What an unsightly display.
Here, let me look at your face.
That looks wonderful, Annerose.
I've never seen any other woman with such a fitting expression.
Remember this...
I'm definitely going to kill you.
That's, you can't be...
No, if you insert that in my pussy now I'll...
Now something's also rotating inside my pussy.
Don't stir my pussy like that!
Now, you want some cum, right?
This thing can actually cum.
It can cum fresh swine cum!
I'll kill you.
I'll definitely kill you!
Take its cum!
It's cumming, it's cumming inside me!
I'm cumming, after taking in this swine cum!
I'm cumming~!
T-This is...
A demon species that loves females.
A Tororo.
You're such a...!
I just thought you'd want a real dick already.
What did you say?
No need to thank me.
I'll be satisfied as long as I can see you get completely raped
with that stupefied expression of yours.
Mayfeng!
You...! Let me go!
You should be grateful.
See? It looks like he's taken a liking for you.
No way...
He can't be...
Rip off her insides!
It won't fit...
That big thing just won't...
My pussy,
it's being torn open!
No, don't move.
My pussy will turn inside out.
It'll turn inside out!
This very tight sensation...
No, no, no!
It just won't fit inside my womb!
It's going to break!
It's going to break if you push it further!
My pussy is widening up.
It's opening up to the shape of his dick.
It'll never go back to normal!
No!
If I... if my pussy molds into the shape of his dick...
My pussy will become his,
it'll turn into a hole just for him!
What?
It's getting even bigger inside?
It's about to happen.
What is?
What... you say?
Tell me!
He'll cum, of course.
He's about to cum all of your beloved cum.
Good for you.
No, pull it out!
If I get cummed inside with this, I'll...!
I wonder what will happen.
Mama Annerose.
No, no, no!
I don't want to become a monster's mother!
Save me please!
Please don't let this monster cum inside me!
No...
It's cumming...
Lots of cum is going inside.
Lots of this monster's cum is pouring into me.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
When Tororo's cum,
they usually stay like that and keep going for hours.
He isn't finished?
Stop, stop this right now!
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming as a monster cums inside of me!
I'm cumming!
No, stop him from pouring his cum.
Stop him from impregnating me...
I'm still cumming...
I'm cumming while being impregnated.
It's still pumping inside me.
I just can't stop cumming!
I'm Annerose's servant.
If she dies, I too, will die.
If I'm alive, then she's still alive.
I'll definitely find you.
Just wait for me, Annerose-san.
More, more please...
Pour more of your monster cum inside.
Make me pregnant with it.