Amidahara,
a lawless area where demons and humans coexist.
I, Tachibana Rikurou, was reborn
and given a new life as the servant
of the Steel Witch, Annerose.
We, who are currently assisting Miki-chan
in finding her lost brother,
were eventually led to Amidahara's seer,
the Crimson Queen, Aish.
The match is over!
Here comes the main event!
Here comes the woman who is about to
get a taste of Aish-sama's punishment!
N-No way am I going to let myself
be humiliated by the likes of you!
That's Mayfeng!
The White Snake, Mayfeng, of the Nine Dragons clan!
Please watch closely!
Look at the face of the woman who was raped 24/7!
What a lovely expression, Mayfeng.
I never thought I would be able to pick up such
a wonderful servant, how lucky of me.
W-Who is it?
I think I will enjoy this.
Stop...
It feels warm inside.
What are you going to do with me?
No!
I'm exposed to everyone!
It's coming out! It's coming out!
Stop!
Annerose-san?
Here they come.
Just who are these people?
Rikurou-san, save me!
It hurts...
I-I can't breathe...
Rikurou-san?
I thought I was gonna die.
But you're a zombie now, right?
We're now separated from Annerose and the others.
And we took a great fall.
I think this is actually a good thing.
There was a proposal before to build
a geofront underneath Amidahara.
All underground districts are connected to it.
In other words, it will lead us to the Crimson Building.
What I'm saying, is that we can go directly to Aish-san's place.
The one that will tell us about your brother.
Oh yes, that's right!
Rikurou-san, this’is...
Umm, well...
A sexual reaction... I guess...
Sorry, it's bad taste to be having this kind
of reaction at a time like this, right?
So this means you're aroused right now, right?
Wait, Miki-chan, what are you...?
You're always protecting me,
so I want to repay you.
So it's this big.
A-Amazing.
I never thought it'd look this way.
What is this clear liquid?
It means that it's feeling good... somewhat...
So it's pleasurable for you, right?
I'll try to do my best,
so please, give in to the pleasure.
Rikurou.san, it's been twitching for a while already.
It means that you're doing well, Miki-chan.
I want to feel more pleasure too!
That means...
I'll do anything that you want to do.
Miki-chan.
I'm putting it in,
so that I can feel more pleasure from you...
I'm inserting your dick inside my pussy.
I just gave my virginity to him!
Please look at how I'll shake my hips.
Make yourself feel lots of pleasure, okay?
I'll move too.
It's piercing me, pushing deep inside.
Your thing is now as aroused as my dick.
It's embarrassing,
but I want to feel pleasure with you!
Rikurou-san, something good is welling up inside me!
It feels very good!
Me too, I can cum, right?
Please do, cum inside my pussy.
I'm sure it'd feel good inside me.
Your fluids are spurting inside, and it feels good!
My insides are...
It feels good!
It feels good inside!
I-If you grip me tightly like that, I'll cum again...!
I can feel that it's making you feel good.
I can feel your dick twitching wildly inside me.
It's still hard.
So I was fucked hard by this stiff dick, huh?
It's still twitching.
Are you going to cum again?
Miki-chan, i-if you keep doing that, I'll cum again.
Please show it to me.
This time do it front of me.
Cum like how you did inside my pussy, Rikurou-san!
I'm cumming!
O-Oh wow...
It squirted it all out!
So you poured all of this thick cum inside me, right?
I-I'm cumming again!
It's so lively.
I think the cum is going to be stuck on me for a long time.
This is Rikurou-san's flavor.
It tastes a bit bitter, but it's full of happiness.
I feel like my mind's going blank as you spray me with your cum.
We're here.
This is the Crimson Building.
Why only me?
Why won't you let Miki-chan meet you?
She's my client, you know.
You didn't ask Anne how I do my divinations?
I-I didn't...
By uniting ourselves as one.
Mixing both of our love juices all the way.
I remember the time when my throat was worked too much.
Besides, this guy is pretty eager as well.
So you're aroused because of me, eh?
I'm happy.
Aish-san!
You can fondle them harder if you want.
Here, I'll let you rub them until they become distorted.
That's right, if you want to make me horny,
then do it harder.
Try to make my nipples hard.
It's not stiffening yet, Rikurou-kun.
It's being sucked upwards?
The way you hardened my nipples like this made me speechless.
We're going to have sex, right?
Let me guess,
are you trying to make me your woman?
I'm about to try.
Wait, that's my ass!
It's in so deep!
It feels good...
But, I'm not about to fall for this just yet.
We're just getting started, Aish-san!
My clit?
But this is still not enough.
Your level of experience is far below mine.
I don't intend to end this so soon.
Just inserting your finger in this position won't...
Your fingers... and my pussy...?
Stop fingering me like that!
Oh yes...
Oh yes!
It feels so good.
I'm going to cum,
while getting my pussy stirred up!
And all the while getting penetrated in my ass!
Feel pleasure with my dick,
and become my woman!
Your cum!
You're cumming inside me!
My insides are getting stirred up by your dick!
I'm cumming as your dick cums inside me.
I've just been turned into your woman.
Don't move while I'm cumming!
My fingers aren't enough for your huge pussy.
Please don't say huge pussy.
More fingers are in my...!
It's going to tear apart!
It won't tear apart with just four fingers.
Look, it's even sucking it pleasurably.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming out of my ass and pussy!
I'm going to make you cum some more!
No, I'm cumming again...
How much do you plan on making me cum?
Until you completely submit to me as my woman!
It's still cumming...
My insides are getting filled with your cum.
And I'm still cumming with it!
Oh no, oh no...
Don't make me cum...
I'm going to lose control of my pussy.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
For someone to make me cum this much...
Now we can start my divination.
I'm not through yet.
Didn't I say it already?
That I'm going to make you fall for me,
and make you my woman.
It's too deep!
It's directly violating my womb!
I'm being violated by this giant dick!
It's widening my very insides, I'm...!
Now, be my woman!
I'm already your woman now!
I've been cumming a lot since earlier!
Your huge dick feels so good!
Then have a taste of my reward, a full shot of my own cum!
I'm cummimg...
I'm cumming!
I've been utterly defeated.
You've made me cum pathetically.
You're going to take responsibility
for turning me into your woman.
Are you ready to listen to whatever I say from now on?
As long as I can have sex with your huge dick.
I'll even happily drink your piss if you want me to.
My body won't move?
What did you do to me?
I didn't do anything.
You fell into my trap, slutty witch.
W-Who are you?
Miki-chan?
I am pleased to make your acquaintance.
My name is Barde Barde.
You're the sorcerer that recently came to Amidahara?
What a pitiful sight.
I never thought that you were actually
the rumored Crimson Queen.
You were filled with his cum, which
was laced with a paralyzing agent.
I never thought that this would work out so well.
When did you...?
Through my servant of course.
Servant?
He refers to the girl named Miki.
Miki-chan?
That girl is nothing but our puppet.
What we desire is the philosopher's stone,
which is inside that woman's heart.
Damn, if you do that Aish-san will...!
She shall die for our grand plan.
What did you say?
Now, hand it over to me.
Give me the philisopher's stone!
Your methods sure are meandering.
It's all for our grand plan,
and it shall be fulfilled very shortly.
But Anne is still out there.
That woman is of no threat to us.
I shall simply eliminate her once she tries to interfere.
Will it really be that easy?
It will.
Now then, shall we put an end to this?
This is the end.
I'm going to enjoy this bit by bit.