This is a lawless district where humans and
demons from the underworld live together.
I, Tachibana Rikuro, was about to be sold by slave traders.
But I was saved by Annerose who is feared as the Steel Witch.
I had become her servant.
Being unable to resist my master's
breasts and sexy body in bed,
I had taken her virginity.
A special relationship between us awaits...
An erotic lovey-dovey life between master and servant.
Riku.
Yes!
You made a mess of the sheets with
your massive load of sperm.
You better change.
You've got to control yourself.
Good grief!
And here I was thinking I've become a special man for her...
I'm being treated like a little brother
who can't control his sexual urges.
Oops!
Out of my way, stupid human!
This is Michiko, Annerose-san's maid.
I took her virginity as well, but she still behaves like this.
What are you looking at?
The White Snake from Nine Dragons...
Lee Mayfeng!
Annerose's arch-nemesis!
You're still ugly and wearing black,
Annerose, the Iron Mold.
It's still better than hiding a dirty mind behind white cloth,
Mayfeng, the Mud Snake.
Shut up and hand over the crazy machine gun girl!
A machine gun girl?
She can't be talking about...
I see.
The Nine Dragons' men must've gotten injured at the bar.
You mean the girl named Miki who Riku was talking about?
The one who wants me to find her
missing brother in Amidahara?
So you guys are here to punish the balloon-breasted girl, huh?
So that's what it's all about.
That explains a lot about the strange presence at my house.
Hello...
Miki-chan!
We promised to meet up at the bar!
The brown-skinned girl told me this is the safest place.
Aish-san, again?
You were more likely to become a
hedgehog with Mayfeng's knives though.
Give me the girl, or I shall consider you my
organization's enemies and kill you all.
Although, I'd prefer killing you all now anyway.
Try it if you can, Mud Snake.
Don't call me by the name, Iron Mold!
Annerose!
Let's go. Riku! Michiko!
nasubeki mono to toki to sadane sameru made no yume to kodoku
Achievers whose destinies were judged by time,
you will dream of loneliness until you wake up.
nasubeki mono wa migi te ni ari soredake ga shinjitsu
Achievers are on the right hand. That alone is the truth.
sashi nobeta hidari te ga ima mata chi ni somaru
The left hand facing it will now be dyed in blood again.
kono sekai wa kodoku dakara mata dakera no na wo yobu
Because this world is lonely, you will call someone's name again.
tsunagaru no wa kegareta te to kotoba dake nanoni
Even though only tainted hands and words are accessible.
kakageru no wa migite ni aru shinjitsu to tukinu yume
Holding up is the truth and unfettered dream in the right hand.
sore wa imada mienu kotae wo kasaneta
That piled up the answers that can not be seen yet.
Koutetsu no Majo Annerose
The Witch in Distress: Witchlose
Are you okay? Riku? Michiko?
Where are the other two?
They've gone somewhere...
They expect me to take care of this girl all by myself, huh?
Be quick and let's go!
Please don't abandon me!
You got us separated from Annerose!
That's not my fault, stupid maid.
What are you saying, stupid human!
You're looking good, Steel Witch.
Just like that. If you stay quiet, I will give you a treat
I will crush your insolent eyes for you.
Actually, it'd be more fun to sting down here.
You've got a disgusting taste.
Trust me. These will make you feel good.
You will enjoy it.
These will go in even deeper.
All right, it's done! You are poisoned!
Now you, tomboy witch, are done!
Wh-What did you do to me?
I injected some estrus poison into your body.
Your nerve of sexual pleasure is going
to make you horny and out of control.
Soon you're going to be begging for cocks.
If you don't kill me now, you'll regret it later!
Good, good! I like seeing you acting tough.
Let me hear more! Go on!
The poison won't...
My, my. You're pushing yourself.
Hey, guys. Help her out!
Now, let's crush Annerose-chan in the name of justice!
Stop...
Don't touch me with your dirty hands!
Let go of me!
It's taking effect!
Your boobs are getting excited and growing bigger!
Damn it!
Well, well, well. What's this?
Don't tell me you're getting wet?
Is all the hard rubbing getting you off?
I-I am not...
You're looking good.
You look just like a bitch in heat
No... This is not me.
My efforts were well rewarded.
You're a fool to not realize that you're just a fucking whore.
So I developed this estrus poison meant especially for you!
I just added three more!
These piercings suit the whore very well.
It can't be...
I-I don't feel any pain... but instead...
If you cum, say that you're cumming, you fucking whore!
You snake!
Now that we are done preparing,
it's time for the main course.
What do you mean...
Come on, raise her ass more.
Spread her legs.
No... Don't!
My goodness. I did use the estrus poison,
but you are incredibly wet, Annerose.
Don't look!
Let me take a closer look...
...at how your pussy interacts with a penis during sex.
Amazing! Your cunt is responding very well!
My... My pussy is being spread so wide...
I know you're feeling so good that you can barely hold it in.
Just be honest with yourself.
Shut up!
It's you who's not shutting up.
Splashing your love juice around like that...
You're such a nympho!
I will get you for this.
I'm definitely going to kill you!
Look, look! You're going to cum soon!
Your pussy is gushing as his cock thrusts against it.
Your pussy... is cumming!
I'm cumming!
I feel the hot stuff flowing inside me.
Inside my pussy...
You've cum inside me... I won't forgive...
Looks like you're loving the sperm.
You weren't satisfied with him cumming inside you,
but you came just from semen flowing out.
Who said that you can cover it?
The fuckfest we've prepared for you is just getting started.
Have you forgotten about that other place, Princess?
The hole that can be penetrated by the cocks you love...
Th-That...
M-My ass?
Th-That's not the right hole!
This is wrong!!
It's not wrong.
Like I said, whores like you have another pleasure hole.
My, my, my...
The sperm inside you is spilling out. What a waste.
Don't use my hair!
Let go of my boobs!
My ass hurts!
Even a whore feels pain, huh?
I guess I have no choice...
What are you going to do?
This is special estrus lotion that's very effective.
You know about my power, don't you?
I can make an endless amount of the
potion that whores love so much.
Now, I'll go ahead and...
Stop!
...rub the lotion into this whore's pussy.
That is my pussy! Not my ass, but my pussy!
That's right.
The pussy that belongs to the nympho
witch who's taking it up the ass.
Don't move your fingers inside me!
The lotion's being rubbed inside me!
I'm going to loosen up your damn pussy with an orgasm!
Sh-She's touching...
She's touching parts of my pussy with
the guy's penis inside of me!
My ass... My ass!
Oh, no. You squirted your cunt juice all over.
What a dirty climax.
She seems to be ready.
Come on, feel your orgasm more!
Go crazy with pleasure, you witch whore!
My assshole... My pussy...
Go crazy, you perverted whore!
Feel your orgasm with dirty anal sex!
I'm going to cum through anal sex if you move it like that!
Like I said, just cum already!
With that damn asshole, you whore!
No!
This bitch is cumming!
She's cumming with her ass filled with cock!
Stop it. I'm going to die!
Stop! Stop! Stop...
So it's that good, huh?
To have your pussy be fondled with a woman's fingers,
while your ass is being penetrated by a man's cock.
Come on, come on...
Tell me that your ass feels good!
Or else I'll give you more estrus poison!
I don't want any more of that!
Then say it.
Say that you love getting your ass fucked!
My ass feels great.
I love getting it in the ass!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from the force of ejaculation in my ass!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Wow... This is really grotesque.
A whore's climax is outstanding!
You are wonderful, Annerose.
I think I'm starting to like you.
I can't take this anymore... Please stop this now...
Come on, guys. The witch whore is craving more cocks!
Be sure to satisfy her sexual desire.
I'm... I'm going to die.
Good work, Annerose.
You did a great job.
Just kill me already.
I'm so proud of myself.
Annerose-san!
You're too late.
D-Don't look...
It's just what it looks like.
My men will be arriving with horses and dogs,
so just wait for a bit.
How dare you do such a thing to Annerose-san!
Ow...
Riku, pain is a hindrance.
It's the mechanism that tells you the limit of humans.
If death is the limit of pain,
then what about the undead?
To be able to transcend the limit...
That is what it means to be undead.
To transcend the limit of pain...
Wh-What is going on?
I am the undead...
I transcend the limits of human pain as
well as the limits of my former self.
In order to protect the person I love...
The true undead.
Hall of Magic
I have removed the poison from Lady Anne.
So Annerose-san will be okay?
Go and feed her this soup.
How are you doing, Annerose-san?
W-Who are you?
So... In other words, Annerose-san,
you're saying that you become like
this on the night of new moon.
That's right.
That is all because the magic power
of Kongou-yasha gets weak.
No wonder you couldn't stand up to Mayfeng...
My appearance my have changed,
but I can't believe you forgot your own master. Goodness.
But why has the way you talk changed as well?
Th-That's, well...
It's because I feel like it.
That's it?
Is it because you're adapting to my taste?
What are you talking about!?
I've been like this from the start.
This is a special soup that Noi-san made for you.
Here. Say "Ahh!"
You're treating me like a child.
Hot!
This is too hot to eat!
Check the temperature before feeding me!
S-Sorry... Then...
You're a cocky servant for stealing a kiss from your master.
I want some more! Hurry up!
Oh, okay. As you wish.
Don't tangle your tongue with mine!
I want to have sex with you.
You're okay with that, right?
Why would I want to do that with my servant!?
Would you change your mind if I kissed you more?
My tongue is getting sucked.
Could you suck on my tongue this time?
Don't be foolish! Why should I?
You're doing well, Annerose-san.
Don't look down on me...
What are you doing all of a sudden?
You're going to have sex with me, Annerose-san.
Right here, right now.
Have sex with a servant...
Wh-What are you...
How did you get it so big?
You beast!
A man and a woman shall now engage in sexual intercourse.
H-Hold on, Riku...
I-It's really tight inside of you, Annerose-san.
It's being stretched.
My pussy is being forced open...
You beast!
Huh? I thought Annerose-san's hymen was...
Got a problem with that?
Every time my body turns small,
it regenerates itself.
Are you serious!?
What's up with that face?
I get to break through your hymen once a month, huh?
I-I won't allow you to...
Hey! My hymen just got broken!
Don't move so roughly!
Annerose-san's hymen is mine and mine alone, okay?
I-It's going to go through...
It's knocking on the door...
Th-The penis is going to penetrate my womb!
It's getting there!
Riku's penis is entering into my womb.
I'm going to cum inside you, Annerose-san.
I'm going to fill your womb with my sperm.
You think I would allow a servant to do that?
He's going to cum inside me,
and my womb will get filled with his sperm!
Please let your pussy be mine and mine alone!
It's moving inside me...
Deeply into my womb...
The hot sperm...
The hot sperm is making me... It's making me...
I'm cumming!
I just came...
D-Don't move it.
I still want to have sex.
Please remember the feel of my sperm in your womb!
What are you saying...
If I remember the feel of sperm, I... I...
You look very cute tonight, Annerose-san.
You're just a servant. Don't get cocky.
Your belly is swollen.
I will help you there.
Wh-What are you going to do?
N-No...
The flowing sperm is rubbing my innermost parts!
I'm cumming...
I'm cummin from the sperm flowing out of me!
Now please clean my penis.
I will get you for this once I return to my regular form.
First of all, let's ask Aish if she knows where Miki's brother is.
Good morning. I overslept!
You're late, stupid human!
You need to be punished severely!
Lady Anne, about the mysterious sorcerer who recently
showed up in Amidahara called Barde Barde...
Do you know anything?
No.
I have a bad feeling about him.
Don't worry, Grandma.
I'll keep an eye out for him while looking for this girl's brother.
Barde Barde...
My desire, the Philosopher's Stone, is in that building.
nasubeki mono to toki to sadame sameru made no yume to kodoku
Achievers whose destinies were judged by time,
you will dream of loneliness until you wake up.
nasubeki mono wa migi te ni ari soredake ga shinjitsu
Achievers are on the right hand. That alone is the truth.
sashi nobeta hidari te ga ima mata chi ni somaru
The left hand facing it will now be dyed in blood again.
kono sekai wa kodoku dakara mata dareka no na wo yobu
Because this world is lonely, you will call someone's name again.
tsunagaru no wa kegareta te to kotoba dake nanoni
Even though only tainted hands and words are accessible.
kakageru no wa migite ni aru shinjitsu to tukinu yume
Holding up is the truth and unfettered dream in the right hand.
sore wa imada mienu kotae wo kasaneta
That piled up the answers that can not be seen yet.
Next Episode Preview
Riku, with that looney face of yours, I would
never have expected you to be a pedophile.
Huh?
Hey, what are you grinning about, stupid human!
Because I get to take Annerose-san's virginity once a month.
This is going to be great!
You enjoyed it that much, huh?
That's right!
Go to hell! Stupid human!
Yeah! Yeah!
Why are you guys here?