Good! This feels so good!
Hey, I don't really like this position.
Okay, how about you do it for me, then?
Geez.
By the way, does he know about you coming here?
What does it matter to you?
He's busy with exams anyway,
so it's not like he has the time to check.
You're the one who forced me
to have sex with you, anyway!
I don't understand why you even care about my boyfriend.
I guess you wouldn't.
I've just been so happy that you come here, Risa-chan.
Does that mean you've fallen for me?
Huh?! Keep dreaming.
I hate being at home with my parents.
This is just payment for letting me stay here.
Risa-chan, you're quite impulsive, aren't you?
Oh, could you suck the tip while doing that?
I can't do something that hard.
You can. Now, hold it between your boobs, like this.
Oh, geez.
Like this?
Yeah, yeah, you're so good!
Being praised for this doesn't make me happy at all!
It actually kind of pisses me off.
Risa-chan, swallow it.
No, stop pushing down my head! I can't breathe!
Oh, it's overflowing.
The phone? Who could that be?
Sorry, excuse me for just a minute, Risa-chan.
Hello, who is it?
Oh, it's been a while. What's the matter?
So bitter.
Oh, Risa-chan? Yeah, she's here at my place.
W-Why did you tell?!
You're talking to my parents, right?
Oh, no worries. I'll take her to you right now.
Okay, bye.
There's no point in running away if they know where I am.
It's better for your parents if they
at least know where you ran off to.
Sorry if I inconvenienced you.
She left without saying a word.
Well, Risa-chan is at that age.
It's probably better if you're not too rough on her.
It wouldn't be good for her if we're too lenient.
We need to discipline her before it's too late.
When you have your own child one day, you'll understand.
Speaking of which, do you still
have no intention of getting married?
You're not getting any younger.
You can't live by yourself forever.
Well, I guess there is a girl I'm interested in.
I think my boobs are getting bigger.
What's happening to my body?
It's getting lewder and lewder.
Oh, wow. You dress like this when you're at home?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Don't come into my room without asking!
This is such a cute room.
It smells really sweet too.
Why are you still here?
Oh, your dad asked me to stay the night.
I've been drinking and he wanted
to thank me for taking care of his daughter.
Did I ask you?
This photo brings back memories!
Stop touching things without asking!
You were so small back then, but now you're so...
You've gotten so big.
Stop that! Not here! My parents are in the next room!
I can't sleep anywhere but in my own bed.
I'd be happy if you kept me company.
Why don't you just go home, then?
Oh? Your ass is sensitive too, Risa-chan?
It's just ticklish!
How about we try using this hole for a change?
It's my first time trying it too.
Huh?! Why would I want to?! You pervert!
What are you doing?!
Young girls really are bounder!
Stop! You idiot!
It doesn't hurt, does it?
I'm not saying it hurts, I'm saying I don't like it!
That might have hurt a little.
Next time you do that, I'm gonna hit you!
Huh? Risa-chan, you're not wearing panties?
I'm at home. Why does it matter?
Sto...
Maybe you're not wearing any
because you were waiting for me?
No, it's just hot...
It'd be really uncomfortable.
No, not so rough! No! No! No!
Oh, you came, didn't you, Risa-chan?
You don't have to point that out.
I'm drenched now. I need to change my pants.
Risa-chan, wait a second.
Huh? What are you gonna do with those?
I'll buy you new ones later, okay?
Huh?! No, stop! I don't want this!
Don't move, or I might accidentally cut you.
There, all done.
Don't hide it! Just move your hand.
You pervert!
This is perfect! It looks so dirty.
You're satisfied now, right? Leave already!
I don't think that was enough.
Wai...
No, don't. You can't!
You'd rather take it to the end, right? Risa-chan.
Oh, sorry. You're just so wet that I slid right in.
This can't be... I hate you, you're so stupid.
Just like usual, your mouth and body
aren't being honest with each other.
That makes you cute, though.
Is that supposed to make me happy?!
I never wanted it to be like this,
but I can't resist anymore!
Stop ticking them like that!
I just showered, but I'm getting dirty again.
Hey, don't kiss me!
Does my breath stink or something?
That's not the problem!
I just don't want to!
So, sex is okay, but kissing isn't?
Kissing and sex aren't the same things!
Oh, so you'll only kiss your boyfriend?
You care about those things, huh, Risa-chan?
What's it matter to you?! Can you just shut...
Risa?
Y-Yeah?
What time do you think it is?
Haven't I told you not to be on your phone at night?
Sorry, I'll hang up soon.
S-Stop, she'll find out!
You need to wake up early to see
your uncle off. Don't sleep in, okay?
Y-Yeah, okay!
Aren't you finished yet?
Wait, he's twitching inside me.
Is he going to let his cum out inside my pussy?!
No, don...
Go to bed soon, okay?
W-What are you doing?!
Just cumming inside without saying anything!
Sorry, your mom came, so I was in a bit of a panic.
Sorry.
This is it, okay?
Huh? I still have so much left inside me.
Just do it by yourself!
By myself? Hmm. Then, I want to watch
you masturbate. Can you do that?
Huh?! Why would I? No!
For just a while is fine!
Why should I? No.
Please, Risa-chan. I'll buy you a gift later,
and keep this a secret from your friends.
Seriously, knock it off. Fine, just for a little...
Why don't you be a little more rough?
This is embarrassing.
Why don't you just stop watching me?
Your face is way too close.
Do you masturbate a lot, Risa-chan?
No, not really. Maybe once a week.
Recently, I've actually been doing it every day.
What's going on? Masturbating while
he watches is turning me on even more!
It feels so weird.
There's so much love juice coming out.
You're soaked!
I've always been like that,
but I think it's been getting wetter more easily.
I wonder if it's because you
have sex with me all the time.
S-Stop! Don't play with my asshole!
It was twitching, so I couldn't help myself.
No, seriously, stop! Take your finger out!
Risa-chan, which hole feels better?
The one I'm touching or the one you are?
How am I supposed to know?! Does it matter?!
Come on, don't you want my dick again, Risa-chan?
It's cooler out here than it is inside, right?
Are you crazy?! We can't do it out here, we'll be seen!
It's the middle of the night,
so nobody will be around. Don't worry.
We can't...
You're even tighter than before!
Does being outside turn you on?
Just hurry up and finish!
This is bad! This is bad, bad, bad!
I'm really turned on right now!
The embarrassment is turning me on!
Oh yeah, your parents are right over there.
That's right, and if they find out, we'll be in real trouble!
Their lights are off, so I'm sure they're asleep.
They'll stay asleep as long as you're quiet.
You...
I bet they'd never think that their daughter
would be having sex so close to them.
I doubt they'd guess she's having sex
with someone they know, either.
If they find out, I'm done for.
I'd be kicked out of the house as well.
I thought you didn't like living here.
Wouldn't that be good?
That's...
If that happens, what would you
say to becoming my daughter?
I'll take good care of you.
Just stop talking already, they'll hear us.
Kids like you really have it easy.
He just came, how is his dick getting even bigger?
Risa-chan, I'm about to cum inside, is that okay?
You'd do it even if I said no, wouldn't you?
Yeah, but I just wanted to check.
It'd feel better for you if I said you could, right?
What are you even saying?
If you don't tell me I can cum, I won't stop.
You're so annoying! If you want to, just do it!
You can cum whenever and wherever!
No! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Oops, that wasn't everything.
Sorry I got your shorts dirty, Risa-chan.
Huh? Why are you taking them off?
We still have some more time before the sun comes up.
What?! You're not done yet?
I'm gonna do my best!
You don't have to! Let go of me!
Huh, did he leave already?
Yeah, he said he had work to do, so he left.
By the way, what's wrong with Risa?
She's still asleep.
She was on the phone with someone
until late last night. Christ, what is she doing?
Maybe we should be a little harder on her?
Maybe. It'll be too late if something happens to her.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч