This is...
I'm going crazy...
No...
Sensei will see me like this...
And yet...
Why?
He will definitely see this...
No, I can feel it.
At this rate...
Please push your cock inside more.
I should have dealt with you more carefully.
It is you.
You are the cause of everything.
What was that just now...?
Thats should never be...
Everything's suppose to be over already.
Yukino shouldn't be...
She's already getting back to her life again.
So where did that...?
Damn.
These dreams should already be...
Yukino, I'm going to protect you.
This was probably a long-abandoned house.
Maybe the suspect will come back to finish what he started.
Not sure about that,
but eventually found it to be completely deserted.
Geez, oversleeping again, eh?
I always have to come and take care of things for him.
Now then,
how am I going to wake him up today?
A sweet scent...
Was she, Yukino-san?
The one that Sensei said that he would take care of.
During his last job, her house burned down.
She's quite pretty.
Does he like those types?
Sensei, it's morning already.
It's time to work!
These breasts sure have lots stuffed in.
Stop it!
It's becoming quite noisy around here.
I never thought that this cute girl would be the reason.
Sensei, please save me!
I said stop!
What is it?
Oh? Momoka-san.
And Mushizou-san.
Did you do something wrong again?
He's really quite the mischievous type.
He makes good food though.
Sorry about that Miss Yukino.
My hands just move on their own.
Oh yes, the meat that you gave me yesterday.
Kyousuke-san also really enjoyed it!
Kyousuke-san?
Well, he's still sleeping,
but there's none left now.
Well, that type is also quite tasty. I think I'll be able
to prepare something new and different soon,
I'll bring some over once it's done!
That'd be great.
Momoko-san, I'm going to wake up Kyousuke-san.
She's one meat-filled female
You don't usually like to do this right?
But if you don't do it every now and then,
you'll be receiving less...
How is it?
This request isn't that difficult.
You can't do that Sensei!
You have a responsibility to keep it a secret.
So you can't just let somebody else see...
Momoko-kun.
Yukino may just be in my custody right now
but she's already like a daughter to me.
Please don't treat her like an outsider.
I'm sorry.
Well, you're part of the family too.
Just like how a wif-  I mean a mother is part of a family.
You no-good bum!
Anyway, I'm going to accept this one.
You better be use to how we do it now.
Oh yeah!
This is my first real job as a detective's assistant!
I'm going to do my best!
Thanks for the soup.
The meat also tasted great.
What kind of meat was that?
It's a secret.
Drop by and have a meal again sometime.
Well then,
Sensei, see you to morrow!
You'll have to say it clearly.
Keeping it vague will just make things harsher.
Oh, I forgot my passcase!
Your cock, it's becoming really stiff.
Your cock is really great.
My pussy, feels really full with your cock...
Your cock, it's entering deep within me.
It's stirring up my insides.
I love it.
Your cock feels great.
It's even piercing my womb.
Sensei, why...?
Like a daughter?
That's unfair.
You said she's like your daughter.
Thrust inside.
Thrust inside me until I break.
Drill into me.
Push your cock inside my pussy.
Wow.
It's pushing so hard,
it feels like my womb is about to burst.
Yukino-san...
Her expression...
Sensei's also doing it passionately.
I'm going to wake Kousuke-san.
She's really...
Quite a terrible man, isn't he?
Do you want to be noticed?
Stop, stop it.
Let me go.
Do you want to be smacked again?
I can smell that bittersweet scent even up here.
It's reeks of a female.
His arm...?
No! What are you doing?
I said stop it!
This guy is trying get my breasts.
This is the worst.
Your nipples are getting hard, so what are you trying to say?
No way, I don't like this one bit.
And yet my body is...!
These breasts sure are big.
Are they filled with milk?
It's insides also looks delicious.
It won't secrete, there's no milk in it!
He's just fondling my breasts.
It feels gross, and yet...
No, no, stop! I don't want this!
This can't be.
No one has touched me there yet,
but this guy is...
No, I'm sensitive there!
No...
It feels gross.
But this guy is...
I'm going to cum.
This is gross.
And I don't want this...
But why am I getting aroused?
Too bad huh?
For your man to be taken away from you.
You pervert!
Shut up.
I'm not a pervert.
His fingers, are going inside me.
No way This is...
Oh no, my voice is...
Your cock is going wild inside my pussy.
You can go all the way if you want.
I'm going to make you become satisfied with my pussy.
Come with me to the other room.
I'm going to let you have an even better view of it.
You want to see your man right?
Your cock...
It feels too good.
My pussy, is becoming sloppy with your cock.
It reeks of a female's scent, and it's dripping wet.
It looks even sluttier than an animal in its mating season.
I hate it, but...
No way it's even bigger than Sensei's.
That's...
My butt is being played with, but...
This butt is getting quite filthy now,
you perverted animal.
Oh no, I'm going to cum from my butt.
You don't seem to be satisfied yet.
So you want this after all?
No...
Anything but that...
That just won't...
No, no...!
What's this?
What is he doing to me?
My body feels hot.
Insert it already.
No, don't.
You absolutely can't.
My virginity's about to be taken away by this..
Stop fretting.
Then how about this?
No way.
I can't hold on with this.
No, I'm...
I'm going to cum again.
This is...
I can't go on any longer.
You want it right?
Be straight with me already.
Say "please mate with me".
Sensei, I'm sorry.
I'm...
Please...
I can't hear you...
You have to speak clearly when you plea.
I want to, copulate with you.
Please insert this dark and thick cock into my pussy!
So this is how I lose my virginity.
I lost it to this guy...
It's entering me...
It's filling me deep inside.
It's rubbing really hard inside my pussy.
It feels good to have my insides get rubbed and stirred up.
This is one fine female cow.
I'm going to impregnate you as a reward.
No, you can't do that.
I don't want to be pregnant.
Then shall I stop now?
I was just requested to do this anyway.
If I don't get away, I'll really be Impregnated.
I can't... I mustn't do this.
But I can't stop it anymore!
I can't stop it!
I'm going to fill your inside completely.
You can't.
You really can't do that!
It's coming!
It's pouring inside me.
I'm going to get pregnant from this.
Kyousuke-san.
That was amazing.
Your thing is getting smaller.
I'll have to get it up again.
Our copulation isn't over yet.
That big thing is going inside me again....?
I don't want it, and yet it feels good.
Becoming like this after just one night.
You really are a big pervert.
Your cock.
I want your cock.
Here.
I can't...
Take it any...
It's really wide.
Not only was I able to test this medicine,
but I even found a good medium for it.
What's this...
Your cum is...
I'm cumming again!
Jeez, what a dirty sex pig.
No...
It's rubbing really hard inside my pussy.
I can't stop it!
Your cum is...
I was toyed with by that guy.
It felt gross, but...
This is my first real job as a detective's assistant!
This is...
This isn't possible...
It hurts.
Sensei, I'm really sorry.
I don't feel well.
So I really can't.
That can't be helped.
Let's just meet up when you get better.
There's still lots of time.
I'm going to get well soon and get there as soon as I can.
At that time.
At that time...
Please give me a pat on the head okay?
Okay.
I'll pat you for as long as you want to.
Well then, Sensei...
Get well soon.
I wonder how you are going to face him.
It hurts!
Sensei, I...
Don't resist too much.
I'm going to get your breasts bigger as a reward.
It hurts, it hurts!
It hurts!
I'm going to break!
There's still the other one.
That won't...!
Pull it out!
We've received some fresh meat again from our neighbor.
So, I decided to make a kidney pie.
My mother was good at making this.
It's my first time tasting this, but it's really good.
It's not just all kidneys either, it's also
made up of breast and uterine meat.
So one can savor the taste while chewing it.
We're also going to have home-made sausages tonight.
Next in line is some more meat, blood and even smoked meat!
This pure-meat diet is just...
I wonder if our neighbor's getting too much meat.
Oh yes, our neighbor also said about getting some fresh milk.
I see. But we're getting some pretty much every day.
Maybe I should stop by their place to say hello.
No, you don't need to do that.
Besides, it might still be too early for that.
Too early?
You have work again today right?
Just leave the menial work to me and
just do your best on your job okay?
I've been leaving it all to you,
but I'll be sure to do it too when I have the time.
What's this?
I can't, move...
Stop...
Don't come near.
I'm sending you to heaven.
No...!
Your existence ends here.
Unless that person thinks otherwise.
What?
Why?
Why am I peeing?
I...
No way, no way...
This can't be...
Stop.
No.
Don't look.
It's coming.
It's coming out.
I'm...
I'm...!
It's a sort of an anesthetic.
Your body feels too weak right?
Though pleasurable sensations remain intact.
I'm, excreting...!
Cumming while pooping,
what a pervert!
He just saw me pee and poop.
But... it felt good...