So like, they're all like "break up with your boyfriend
or find a way to get your grades up".
Like, I can't even go out to have any fun anymore.
They're being way too controlling.
So that's why you ran away from home?
Yep. For real, you're a life saver.
All my friends live with their parents
and I didn't have any money or place to go.
You looked so grown up,
it took me a while to realize it was you, Risa-chan.
How many years has it been?
Hm... we haven't seen each other
since Grandpa's funeral, so about six years?
It's really been that long?
Hey, so have you been living
by yourself all this time, Uncle?
Yeah, I do all my work from home,
so I don't really have many opportunities to meet people.
That sounds rough.
Yeah, I guess. Oh, it's already gotten this late?
Risa-chan, you're tired, aren't you?
I still have some work I need to get done,
so you can use my bed to sleep.
Thank you!
Aw man, if only my parents were as nice as he is.
You can stay here as long as you like, Risa-chan.
Uncle?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Th-This isn't... Risa-chan...
Those are my panties!
Wait, did you take them off of me?!
Are you for real?!
No, this is a misunderstanding.
I-It was just in the heat of the moment.
No, don't touch me! You fucking pervert!
Geez, you used to be so much more
subservient and docile when you were little.
Wh-What are you...
I'm sad that you've become a delinquent
who would run away from home!
I need to punish you in your parents's stead.
No, stop! Don't come near me!
What are you doing?!
I couldn't tell because your uniform was covering them,
but you've developed quite well!
Th-This can't be real.
Is he really going to go all the way?!
Risa-chan, your body's the only
adult thing about you, isn't it?
No, stop sucking it like that!
Cross! Way gross!
So what about down here? Let your Uncle see.
It's glistening like a gem, it's so beautiful!
I haven't seen a real pussy in a while.
I never thought that my niece's would be the next I saw!
No, stop it! Don't spread it
open like that, you pervert!
You're already getting tighter.
I guess younger girls are more sensitive.
No, there's no way that's happening.
That would never happen to me!
Or maybe it's because of your
boyfriend doing this all the time?
Shut up! Don't talk about my boyfriend now!
Stop! Slow down! Don't be so rough!
Oh dear, what's the matter?
You're so rigid and stiff. Did you cum?
Look at how big your clitoris has gotten.
You look like you're having trouble breathing,
so how about I take off the tape for you?
But you can't scream, okay? You wouldn't want
anyone to see you like this, would you?
Please, untie me. I wanna go home!
Hm, well this is quite the pickle. You see, your Uncle
over here has been hard for quite some time now.
I need you to help me out.
Fuck that! Just use a towel or underwear or something!
That's a shame. I guess I'll just
have you stay over a bit longer.
Ilf you do that, my parents will...
You think they'll really look for you?
Of course they will!
And they'll catch you red-handed!
What do you think will happen after that?
On top of running away from home,
you would also be causing more
trouble by involving the police.
Their supervision of you would be
even stricter after they found out.
N-No...
If you follow my instructions,
I'll let you go home come morning.
What'll it be?
Wear... okay?
Wear a condom, okay?
Yeah, of course.
Oh man, this is the best!
I've been using my right hand for so long
that I'd forgotten what a real woman was like.
I'm so glad you came here, Risa-chan!
If I knew you were a huge fucking pervert,
I never would've come here!
I think I'm on the nicer side.
If you stayed with a guy you didn't know,
they would've been much rougher.
Fuck off!
Just hold it together.
Hold on. It'll all be over soon.
You keep verbally rejecting me,
but you're making my dick so wet.
What the hell are you saying?
You make me sick!
So, tell me. Between me and your boyfriend, who's better?
Wh-What the hell are you asking me?
You fucking pervert!
You really do have a foul mouth.
No, stop! That hurts!
So, you're into this kind of thing, Risa-chan?
Your pussy's squeezing my dick like crazy!
No, it's not! Just hurry up and end this!
Oh no! You were squeezing me so tightly,
I couldn't hold it in anymore!
It's over. Now I can...
Okay, time for round two.
B-But, you just...
I never said it'd be just the once, did I?
You're kidding...
Hey, please let me rest a little.
Hm? What did you say?
Whatever. Just take it out for a second. I need a break!
Oh, a pee break? Okay, let's go together.
Huh? Why the hell should we?
Just go with it. I'll help you out.
What are you doing? No... Stop!
It's not good to hold it in.
If he keeps doing it like that,
I'm really going to pee! It's gonna happen!
Oh, it really came out! There's so much of it.
I guess you were really holding back.
No, stop! Don't look! Don't look at me!
After looking at you, I became even harder!
Let's go back to the room and continue.
You pervert!
Why? Why is he still so hard
after cumming so much?
Hey, what's the matter, Risa-chan?
You've stopped moving.
You're satisfied, aren't you?
Let me go home already!
Oh, it's already morning, is it?
Well then, I guess I'll have you
finish me off with your mouth.
This is really the last thing, okay?
Of course. After I cum, we're done.
This is it. All I have to do is make him
cum once and then I can go home!
No, not like that!
You have to go deeper otherwise
I won't be able to cum!
No, I can't breathe! Stop!
I'm going to cum soon,
so don't move your face away, Risa-chan!
Mom
We're just getting to the good part!
It's from your mom.
Looks like she was worried, so she called you.
Hey, that's my phone! Don't touch it!
Hello? What is it?
It doesn't matter where I am, does it?
Stop!
If you don't talk to her normally,
your mom's going to find out.
Nothing's wrong.
I just kinda dropped my phone.
Please, stop!
I can't hold back my voice!
I know. I'll come home today.
Okay, I'll see you later.
So, was your mom angry?
What the hell?!
You said that you'd finish with my mouth!
Now, now. I think after this, I'll be satisfied.
I've been so lonely, you see.
Why should I care?!
If you ever want to run away
from home again, come here.
I'll let you stay here as much as you like, okay?
Who in their right mind would do that?
Looks like you hate me quite a bit now.
It's a shame. Our bodies are so compatible.
Hey, wait. Where's your condom?! Where is it?!
Oh, sorry. I never put it
back on after the blowjob.
No! I told you to put one on
if we're doing this, didn't I?!
Take it out! Take it out right now!
Sorry to break it to you, but your Uncle
here is just about ready to cum!
No, stop! You can't!
You can't do this raw!
I'm going to cum now, Risa-chan!
No, please! Don't cum inside!
Don't!
This can't be... He's cumming inside me!
Cumming inside sure is different.
It feels so much better!
I might have overdone it just a little bit though.
Sorry about that.
Risa-chan. I'll drop you off at the station, okay?
Fuck off, you piece of shit.
Risa, where the heck were you last night?!
Your father's calling you. Come down here!
I'll be down later!
Risa!
Why... How did it end up like this?!
Last night was a blast.
I'll take good care of your panties,
so feel free to stop by anytime!
What a scumbag...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fyurie
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч