My nipples...
What are you going to do to my nipples?
Seems they've grown well.
My breasts...?
Why are they secreting milk?
This dick...
Feels great...
It's thick too...
My wet pussy's being stirred hard.
It's been months since you were confined in the mansion.
It looks like you're now ready to be offered to our Master.
She's amazing.
With her around, maybe we won't need that maiden anymore.
Keeping at it with her until it can possess her again, I see.
We'll have to impregnate her before she notices.
What?
I bet it'll feel good, once that huge thing pierces me.
No way...
Something that big just won't fit!
My pussy will...!
No, you can't!
Oh w-wow, it's reverberating throughout my entire body.
This is amazing.
It's just perfect.
Now the only thing left is to impregnate her with the seed.
This is too big...
My insides are about to burst.
It feels...
My pussy, oh yes...!
Oh no, my pussy is getting completely filled with this beast's cum!
This just feels so good!
We still have to fill her up.
It tingles, it tingles...!
And it's shaking.
What is this?
Feels good, right?
I'm currently molding these gargantuan breasts to our liking.
It feels good.
My breasts feel great.
It's almost done.
I never thought that there would be someone
else other than the maiden
who could properly take in the seed.
My nipples, and my pussy feel numb.
This is strange...
This is crazy!
My pussy's getting filled with cum again.
The baby's going to drown in cum!
Too much cum... oh no...!
My baby's going to drown... with this much cum...
So this is what that person can do.
Original Animation
Kowaku no Toki
The restless girls investigation
The fleeting and denched
scar of seduction
What's wrong, Kyousuke-san?
No, it's nothing.
I thought I just heard something strange.
Hey, let's walk by the park.
So there's a park here, eh?
Well, it's been a refuge for many of the homeless folks.
Oh, I see.
So there are flowers here.
What a rare one.
Hey, Kyousuke-,san.
These are...
Kyousuke-san, you're a pervert.
No one's really here?
Yep, no one comes here often.
Kyousuke-san, your hands...
It's making my pussy feel hot.
Your thing is already...
It's embarrassing doing it here,
and yet it's still getting really wet.
Please, I want your big dick inside me.
Even if we're exposed here,
I can simply be more daring... for you.
Kyousuke-san, this already feels so good!
It fits perfectly inside me.
It's embarrassing doing it outside, and yet...
My breasts...
I'm going crazy from your touch.
My body is really starting to lose it.
Kyousuke-san, amazing.
Your hard and stiff dick is making my mind go blank.
Do it more.
I want lots of it inside me.
Your sticky cum...
It's filling me up inside.
Your smell, it's seeping into me.
This is...
It's about to be born!
Here, let me give you a hand.
No...
It feels good.
You're feeling horny with this?
I may have drugged you so that you'd feel ecstasy,
BUT you're really something else.
I'm giving birth!
It's coming out, and it feels good!
It's going to be pulled all the way out.
And I'm being forced to feel pleasure inch by inch.
Am I simply going to be impregnated again after this?
Our neighbor gave some to me again.
I see, so this delicious meat is...
Well then, Kyousuke-san,
I'm heading out for awhile.
So just rest easy, okay?
Got it. You're going to meet a friend, right?
Enjoy yourself.
Okay.
I'm going.
Take care.
Man, I'm still in the red this months.
Not that I've gotten any investigation requests lately.
Momoko-kun should really be fine by herself this time.
Huh? Momoko...
Request given
to Momoko
Comlete!!
Momoko, who was she again?
Huh? Momo... ko...?
What is this?
This is strange.
I felt this earlier too.
Oh yeah!
I brought Yukino-san, and Ai...
Ai was supposed to be there too!
When did Ai...
And for that matter, Momoko too...
The dream I had before.
Was that not Yukino, but Momoko instead?
Mushizou, what's the meaning of this?
I never asked you to do this!
What are you going to do now?
Ruriko, it's the end for you now.
You've done your job.
It's now time to give it all away.
You should have died.
Then those other girls would have...
Ruriko?
Isn't that Yukino-san's mother?
But that fire incident should have killed her already....
What's going on?
Dammit...
Where is she now?
Momoko-kun...
Yukino-san also didn't come back after that.
How many times do I plan on allowing the same things to happen?
Yukino-san, Ai, Momoko-kun...
Yeah, they said a woman is letting them do it with her there.
I really love it!
So our emergency rations are 'packed' with a woman now?
Why don't I try it out for a bit?
This is really good.
There's lots of dicks...
Please, let me drink more semen!
This thick cum...
It's going to fill me inside, and make me pregnant again.
Oh yes, it feels good.
Give me more!
Do it to me more please!
You just gave birth, and you can take this many dicks already!
No way...
She was impregnated...?
So you finally noticed... Sensei.
Sen...sei...
No, no, no...
Please stop!
Wow, she started gripping me tighter.
No...!
What is it that you don't like about this?
You're actually happy to be exposed in
front of your beloved Sensei, right?
Sensei...
That's not...
I'm not really...
These dicks... no...
Sensei, don't look!
Don't look!
So you finally remember.
Sensei, you're the root cause of all of this.
Ruriko, Yukino, and even Ai.
Even this horny cow.
If you hadn't existed...
No way, all of this is my fault?
This power is...?
Please...
Sensei, don't look.
I don't want you to see this!
M-Momoko...
Momoko!
So you found out, eh?
Are you actually Ruriko-san?
Let me go!
I have to save Momoko!
I can't do that, and besides this body is mine.
I'll live on as the maiden.
I'm not letting that woman take my place.
And you're going to be at my side.
Mushizou is no longer capable.
Huh?
What was I...?
This isn't right, I'm...
Kyousuke-san.
Breakfast is ready.
We're having sauced hamburgers today.
Oh, thank you.
Wait, I'm forgetting something really important.
I feel like I forgot something.
If you forgot about it, then it's not that important.
So you just have to keep it forgotten.
How sweet of you.
I actually took off your limbs because they were in the way.
Can we take off her arms already?
We're done with this horny cow as well.
Let's just offer up all of her innards.
But first, let's enjoy this till the very end.
How about we start with this opening here?
The sensation is really something.
And being able to rub it in like this is fantastic.
Now then, to prepare something special for our neighbor.
That's quite generous of you, Master.
The one before was the younger sister, right?
Well, I can't really tell the difference
between their bodies anymore.
Can't deny that!
Man, I'm really loving this.
I'm really fine, Kyousuke-san.
Why don't you just save it for tomorrow?
It'd be too late by then.
Even if it's our neighbor, I still have to properly tell them off.
Hey, you're being too loud.
You're being rude to the other neighbors, so please keep it down.
Sensei, perfect timing, or perhaps I should say otherwise.
We're about to go for the last course.
Did your assistant taste well?
I see.
This delicious meat is...
Oh, you want to do it too?
Can’t be helped.
I can let you have her.
We're about to be finished with her anyway.
We're going to let you have the last serving.
Let her rest in peace.
Momoko...
I'm sorry, Sensei...
Momoko, it’s alright.
You've suffered a lot.
I have this power, and yet,
I'm already...!
What is this?
It's the master's curse!
T-This guy is...
Let me go, Mushizou!
I can't just let you go, you know.
Not when I've finally found a replacement.
You're not the maiden anymore, Ruriko.
No, stop!
Stop!
Mother...?
Let's go, Kyousuke-san.