How much longer will it go on for?
How much longer will this
messed up relationship of ours go on for?
Come on, move your hips more.
In this position,
he can see all of my embarrassing parts.
Excellent.
I can reach deep inside you like this.
No... If you go that deep...
That's good, Kasumi. Grip me tighter!
I'm going to cum!
Please, end this already!
I-I'm about to...
Look at all this dirty juice you let out.
It's going to stain the futon.
I'm sorry.
I'll be sure to wash it later.
Well then, I guess I'll head to bed.
You should do the same.
W-Wait...
The parent-child meeting at school is next week, so...
Oh, right. Of course I'll go.
So, um...
Something the matter?
No, nothing.
Don't forget, okay?
Stepdad
Dad...
Broken Girl
So, how are my daughter's grades?
Great! Nanakura-san is really giving it her all.
Her ranking on the latest test was really good.
Oh, really?
That's a relief.
I'm working most of the time,
so I don't really have the opportunity
to look over her studies.
Ever since my wife and I separated,
it's just been me and Kasumi.
I leave all the duties of the house to her.
She's my pride and joy.
Is that right? You're a good kid, Nanakura.
College Prefere
Please list your preferred colleges below
Rank number
College name
1st choise
Tokio Literature university
2st choise
Aoyama Academy
3st choise
Tama All-Girls university
So your first choice is Tokyo Literature University?
You meet all their requirements, so as long as you
keep up the good work, getting in shouldn't be a problem.
Tokyo?
Oh, she didn't tell you?
N-No...
Nanakura,
you haven't discussed your plans
for the future with your father yet?
I'm sorry.
I think one more year of good performance
should seal the deal for the university,
so be sure to talk this over with your father, okay?
Yes.
Why aren't you choosing a local school, Kasumi?!
How could you go behind my back
and apply to a school in Tokyo?
What the hell are you thinking?!
I'm sorry...
I tried to talk to you about it, but...
Are you...
Are you going to betray me too?!
Just like your mother did?!
Is that it?!
No... I'm not...
Dad, stop! Not here!
I'm begging you Kasumi,
don't leave me! I need you!
The reason I couldn't talk to him about my plans
for college was because I knew he'd be against them.
I knew it. Dad really can't let go of me.
Dad...
Ever since the day that my mother
ran off with another man,
my once gentle father drowned himself in alcohol.
And then, one night...
Stepdad
Dad?
Dad, no! Stop!
Please, let me go!
Kasumi, tell me, where did I go wrong?
D-Dad?
No matter how much I think about it, I just don't know!
What did I do wrong, Kasumi?
After that, I lost any courage
I had to tell him to stop.
Kasumi, your pussy is so wet
and it tastes so good!
No, don't tick that!
Kasumi, your Dad's been so lonely
and he's almost at his breaking point.
I thought that if I denied him,
he would break tonight.
That's why I...
Kasumi, your insides
are so warm... it feels so good!
It hurts! It really hurts!
I'm being raped!
I'm being raped by my dad!
He's stirring up my insides! It... isn't right!
Kasumi.
Kasumi! Kasumi! Kasumi! Kasumi!
That night, Dad violated my body multiple times.
Taking my first time in the process.
I know more about you than anyone, Kasumi.
Every night after that,
my Dad had sex with me.
Amazing, they're already this hard.
It feels good, doesn't it?
My body has already started
to react the way he wants it to.
Look, you're already geting soaked.
I'm the only one who
can make you feel good.
No. Dad already knows all of my soft spots.
I guess I really was wrong...
Dad's going to lick you clean, okay?
What should I do?
I'm doing something I shouldn't in school!
Oh no, I'm going to cum!
You came already?
You're so sensitive, Kasumi.
I-I'm sorry.
Now, stick your ass this way.
U-Um...
Can we do this at home?
Don't worry, it'll all be over soon.
B-But, if someone comes...
You're graduating next year anyway.
This'll make for a great school memory, don't you think?
There was nothing I could do.
Since it went this far, I...
It's been so long since I've done it raw.
This is definitely the best!
Wait, Dad, you're not wearing a condom?
Yeah, I forgot to bring one.
No, you're kidding!
Don't you think it'd be weird for a parent
to bring one of those to a school?
Dad's dick is so big and hot.
It's rubbing me so hard!
Does it feel good to be fucked raw, Kasumi?
Yeah... it's so slippery and warm.
Is that so?
Then I guess, every now and then,
I won't put one on.
Just what am I doing?
I know that I don't want to do this,
but I can't help but do
what Dad tells me to do.
My body likes doing this!
Kasumi, let's talk about
your plans for the future again.
Okay...
Don't worry about school fees or anything.
I'll give you everything I have.
Dad...
However, you can't go anywhere far from me. Okay?
But...
Okay?!
Yes...
Okay. Good girl.
No, Dad, don't be so rough or else I'll...
Even after you graduate,
you'll always be with me!
Let's do lots of fun things from now on, okay?
I really can't resist him.
At this rate, I'll just become his possession.
Come on, Kasumi,
tighten your asshole and squeeze Dad tighter.
Yes...
Good, just like that! Very good!
I know I shouldn't be doing this,
but I'm even more turned on than usual!
What should I do?
I'm getting dirtier and dirtier!
No, it's going so deep inside me!
It's hitting my womb!
How about it?
This spot feels good, right? Dad knows!
Dad, please.
Don't do any more of that!
I'm going to lose it!
Someone's still here?
I'm going to cum inside you soon.
I'm going to pour all of my cum inside you, okay?
But if you do that...
It's fine. You won't get pregnant
after just one time.
So lower your body more.
He's going to cum.
He's going to cum inside of me!
But I can't stop him. I'm going to cum too.
I'm at my limit!
I came a lot today, just like usual.
Amazing. His hot stuff is flooding into me.
We can't be a normal family anymore.
Please clean Dad's dick, Kasumi.
Yes...
Just like that. You're really good at sucking.
What a dirty smell.
This was inside of me?
His dick is getting even bigger.
Is he getting aroused?
What should I do?
I'm starting to feel really weird.
You can stop.
I'm going to cum again at this rate.
Let's pick up later at home, okay, Kasumi?
Yes, Dad.
Nanakura?
Sensei?
What are you doing over there?
Wh-Why are you...
Th-This isn't what it looks like! This is...
What the hell did you do to her?!
After that day,
I was never touched by my father again.
What did you need to speak to me about?
Did your father do something to you again?
No...
If anything happens, tell me. I'll help you out.
Sensei, I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
H-Hey!
This just won't stop throbbing.
Could you touch it for me, Sensei?
Nanakura?
Stains are rather hard to get out,
and the one left in my mind never did disappear.
So once again, I began to lead my body
down another immoral path.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fyurie
encoder: bakaproxy