Do you like sex?
Yukino… wants Kyousuke-san to feel good.
It’s soaking wet, right?
Yeah…
Will you fill me up?
Will you fill me up with cum from your big cock?
This feels good~
I hope you like my taste; I cleaned myself for you.
Kyousuke-san, it feels really good!
Give me more!
No... he’ll notice.
Y-Yukino-san…
Stop it…
Make me feel even better.
Bring me to rapture!
I’m sorry, Kyousuke-san.
Please…
Kyousuke-san?
Kyousuke-san? Are you okay?
Wake up! Kyousuke-san!
Tsk. You useless girl.
Kowaku no
Toki
W
Nii-chan?
Nii-chan!
Onii-chan!
Yes!
Onii-chan, how much longer are you going to sleep?
We finally got a chance to be together.
This is boring!
Ai-chan. Sorry about that.
I apologize!
Geez...
Then after we eat, will you hang out with me?
Yeah, sure.
Really?
Then I’ll forgive you.
I’m home.
Welcome back.
Dinner is almost ready.
Yay!
It's nothing; I just felt some Déjà vu, that's all.
What do you mean by that?
Nothing.
It's just my imagination.
I’m going to keep Ai-chan company after this.
Oh my.
Ai is still young, so you shouldn't be too rough with her.
Wh-What are you suggesting?!
Are you failing on purpose just so you can be punished?
Hey.
You need to please us with those ridiculously huge tits of yours.
It stinks!
He didn't bathe on purpose.
The reason why he's allowing himself to get injured is because he wants to give me the opportunity to escape.
He really is trying to save me.
And I must save him too.
No matter what horrible things are done to me.
Suck it deeper.
I can’t breathe.
Please cum quickly and be satisfied!
If this continues…
Hey, this one too.
What? What are you doing?
You’ve been raised by drinking semen, so how can you not know?
N-No… No…
Not like this...
They’re waiting for me to cry.
If I desire this, if I ask for them for more, then they...
They’ll continue doing this to me forever.
This is the policy that's been set.
But even so, I was able to meet and talk with him.
It made me truly happy. I felt that I was saved.
This old man is worried about you.
Are you thinking about HIM even while you’re doing this?
You naughty girl!
We’ll make it so you that you only crave dirty, old men.
You need to satisfy us more, you stupid slut!
You pissed yourself while cumming again? You bitch!
I have to do this... For Onee-chan’s sake.
Onii-chan!
Um, sorry, Ai-chan.
I’m going to the bathroom.
I ate too much.
His dick... Was hard.
My feelings are irrelevant.
Onee-chan loves him.
So... I must not fail.
Ai-chan, are you asleep?
You’ll be violated if you remain asleep.
Ai-chan, you're still not awake?
Nii-chan’s semen is in my mouth…
It has the same taste… as normal semen…
Nii-chan… he’s kissing my pussy.
He’s licking my pussy!
Nii-chan is tweaking it!
What a naughty girl you are, Ai-chan.
No… I’m getting turned on! I'm getting wet!
There's no way that Ai-chan can still be asleep.
This is your punishment.
Nii-chan’s dick is going inside me…
Onii-chan... What’re you...?
You’re tight.
It hurts!
He’s… almost all the way in...
Nii-chan…
Didn't I tell you? This is your punishment.
Onii-chan!
Don’t!
Ai-chan.
This feels great!
Ai-chan… Ai-chan…
I thought he cared about me… but I was betrayed.
It hurts!
Nii-chan’s dick...
Is this okay?
Nii-chan is... turned on...
Fucking me… makes him happy.
No... Onii-chan, don’t...
No... Onii-chan’s eyes don't show my reflection!
Onii-chan!
It’s coming!
His semen is spilling out inside me!
Ai-chan...
What did I…?
I’m sorry!
I… wasn’t…
It’s fine.
I don’t mind… if it’s you.
I’m fine, really.
You can go.
I... I understand.
This is… for the best.
Wh-What’s this?
So you’re awake?
It’s too early to be dozing off.
No!
Pee comes out from that hole…
No…
My… my body is so hot.
He’s doing something horrible to me, but I’m still looking forward to it.
This smell…
This is morning semen.
From humans.
No… I’m sorry!
I’ll be a good girl, I promise!
Please!
Please let me go!
I can’t let you go.
I prepared this just for you. Enjoy.
No… it’s going inside…
No…
Don’t…
Jesus, it's a bitch filling up the tank.
I'm getting full; my bladder is going to burst!
Oh no! I can’t take any more!
No…
Incredible! I can't contain myself!
It’s so painful!
I can’t hold back!
No! No!
I’ll explode!
Oh no! I want to pee!
I'm gonna… I'm gonna!
I'm looking forward to taking this out.
No… I can’t.
If he takes it out… I’ll…
Don’t!
No!
While you’re cumming, I’ll cum inside you!
No! The cum-pee is coming out!
No… no…
This can’t be...
If this keeps up, I’ll cum...
I’ll cum!
Onii-chan, I’m embarrassed to be out here like this.
Don’t worry, Ai. No one is watching.
It looks like she’s not bothered with yesterday's incident.
Now, I'll make her mine.
Onii-chan, let’s go to the lake.
Going out, Princess?
What the hell is your problem?
Onii-chan, stop it! Please!
Ai! But he-!
Just stop it!
Shit!
Why did Ai tolerate that jerk?
Why did she choose him over me?
Onii-chan…
He's aroused after seeing me in my swimsuit.
Well... Um…
I know what he’s thinking. He wants me.
Onii-chan?
Even though I’m so young.
You look good in anything, don’t you, Ai-chan?
Onii-chan… my boobs…
You don’t like it, Ai-chan?
We’ll be seen!
Don’t worry.
No one’s watching.
Onii-chan... don’t…
I can’t move…
Wha- Don’t pull so hard!
Do you want to pee?
No, not at all!
Onii-chan…
He wants me to wet myself?
Right here? Right now?
No...
I have to do it. I have to do what he wants… and pee…
No… no…
Ai, you’re hopeless.
But… you… but...!
No buts!
Onii-chan!
It’s your fault for not holding back.
S-Sorry.
Onii-chan…
You’re selfish, undisciplined and you need to be punished.
I can’t breathe… I can’t breathe, Onii-chan!
He’s happy.
He’s enjoying this.
Doing these horrible things to me… he looks exactly like those other men.
Onii-chan…
Onii-chan!
No…
Not out here…
Onii-chan… no…
Onii-chan, how could you?
It’s fine.
Let’s give them a show.
Onii-chan, no, I don’t want to be seen!
No...
You’re swirling around inside… your dick is opening me up!
Ai.
You’re saying such perverted things.
It's not like that; it's not!
No!
Not so… rough… my pussy… will break…
Your dick is… thrusting… so deep… opening me up.
It’s so deep…
People can see us!
Everyone will see my pussy getting wrecked!
Oniii-chan is so hard… filling up my insides...
Very good, Ai!
More! More!
Onii-chan, no! I can’t hold back!
I’m losing my mind!
Onii-chan… my pussy feels good…
No!
Your cum is… spilling out…
So much perverted juice went inside me…
Oh, did I fall asleep?
I still have time.
Ai-chan.
Huh?
Shit!
Where did she run off to?
Ai!
Dammit. Ruriko was coming back late today – I could have had my way with her.
Shit!
Study
What’s this room for?
Ruriko
Ouch… What’s this?
Ai and Ruriko… my head…
Yukino…?
Yukino-san!
It’s barely started.
What’s this?
Yukino-san? Yukino-san...
I can’t anymore…
How much longer will this continue?
Are you already finished? How boring.
What happened to your usual spunk?
Maybe this will restore your energy.
No… why? No way… Kyousuke-san…
I didn’t kill him; I only knocked him unconscious.
With this girl. She’s really a pro.
Ai… No way!
Yukino… Onee-chan…
He’s fucked both you and your mom and probably many others, for all we know.
That can't be! Mom?
No…
Are you shocked that your beloved prince has his way with both Ruriko and Ai?
How tight! I can’t stand this!
No! Stop it…
You’re so wet. You’re even squeezing me tighter than your sister.
No… no…
Please don't…
S-Stop it…
No...
Please... Don't do this...
Let’s make the sisters show twisted, insane faces!
No… no…
Your darling prince is awakening.
No… No!
Don’t… don’t…
Yukino-san?
A-Ai?
Why?
I can’t move.
The drugs that I gave you were potent.
You won’t be moving any time soon.
Just sit back and enjoy watching the slut sisters get fucked.
No, don’t watch!
Kyousuke-san… no more…
Don’t look…
Sisters? That can't be...
It looks like your prince is all that you can see.
How do you feel about your little sister stealing him?
No...
Why is my body so…?
Shit!
Choose one: either your prince, or your sister.
I’ll let you choose which one to save.
No. Stop it!
I can’t… I can’t…
Nii-chan is watching me… but I’m…
Don’t fuck with me!
Impossible!
How can you move?
I’ll k-kill you!
You bitch-
Girls, run away!
Mom!
Wh-What’s happening?
My master is angry!
Kyousuke-san… please… take care of my daughters!
Mom…
Kyousuke-san…
Just as mom said, Ai did entrance Kyousuke.
Having lost her spiritual powers, my mom was probably frustrated, being unable to do anything.
But, in the end, mom came and save us.
We, the sisters who lost everything, were accepted by Kyousuke.
Even so, we still needed more time for our wounds to heal and recover.
And the one who gave us a home to convalesce in was Kyousuke.
We are extremely grateful, however…
However...
Don't worry, Onee-chan!
I know he likes this.
But… um… it’s much too embarrassing.
Oh, Onee-chan, just go in!
Onii-chan!
Geez, Ai!
Kyousuke-san. Don’t look at me like that!
It’s embarrassing!
By the way, Kyousuke-san...
I heard you took "good care” of Ai back there.
I’d like to hear ALL about it.