Don’t...
This doesn't seem to be enough for your body.
Not inside...
How dirty, dammit.
Your nasty juices are all the way inside.
Your uterus is all swollen.
Not in there!
Don't put your fingers in there...
You’re turned on by having your organs massaged from the inside?
What a perverted priestess you are.
No... That’s not true...
Not there...
It’s all whirling around...
Why...?
Was it really that good?
Then I suppose it's about time I gave you this.
N-No...
Don’t...
You’re the same as always.
Yes... Harder...
No...
You’re so excited, you fucking whore.
Looks like my fingers aren’t enough for you.
Don’t... Any further would...
I think this much should be fine for you.
You’re so cruel...
My body is... Moving on its own...
Your uterus is big as always.
Looks like ANYTHING will fit in there.
Get wet all the way inside your uterus.
If you’re not drugged enough, the ceremony won’t work.
Got it?
No... Don’t...
Stop it...
It changes any pain into pleasure.
What a handy little drug.
It’s going... Inside... My uterus...
Don’t... No...
This much then?
You’ve sucked up so much inside.
If you suck up more, it’s AWESOME.
No... No more...
My insides are...
Looks like it’s got you inside.
No... Stop...
I’m scared.
You’re a fucking cow who loves being fisted.
Good. You’re all ok.
I brought you a friend.
Awesome.
Something so long will fit in?
No... No way... Please, stop it.
Chew on this.
Even though you're drugged, I’m surprised that you’re so aroused on your first ceremony.
I’ve got high hopes for ya.
Oh no...
No...
You’re pissing yourself.
Shit, how dirty.
Who’s gonna clean up that mess?
I'm sorry...
I wonder what your prince would think of his cow pissing herself.
Shit. Not again.
It was a little different today,
but she was like that?
What the... It smells like an animal.
What the hell was that?
Was it a bull?
It also looked human.
Shit! You think I’m sticking around here?
Damn it! The directions were bullshit! I’m lost!
That can’t be true...
That he would...
He’s coming closer.
Mother?
Such a big cock. I want it!
Your cock... So big...
It’s so wonderful!
It’s ok.
Come further in... Come all the way inside my uterus!
Yes...
It's whirling around... Inside my uterus...
Oh... Yes...
I love your cock, Bull!
It’s so thick and hard, but it’s so soft too.
I’m cumming... I’ll cum... So you can cum too.
You can't hold back, can you?
Squirt it out!
Fill me with your bull seed!
I want your semen! Make me pregnant with it!
Inside of me!
So many possible babies!
Fill me full!
Fill my uterus with your seed!
No!
Don’t take it out!
Wait!
Don’t!
It’s leaving my uterus!
Original Animation
Time of Rapture
Cool Pregnant Belly • Yukino
~Thick Holes Overflowing with Shame~
Shit.
I got lost in the middle of nowhere, and I lost my reception... Dammit!
Ow...
Where am I?
Looks like people live here.
I can't use my cell, so I’d better borrow something here.
Hello! Anyone here?
Maybe no one’s home...
Hey!
Um, do you live here?
Can I use your phone...
Do you have business here?
No, well, I just got lost, and I was wondering if I could use your phone.
If you reverse your direction on the path that got you here, you’ll get back.
And we have no telephone here.
Goodbye.
Wait!
Owww...
Um... You noticed my foot was there when you slammed the door just now, didn’t you?
No.
Hey... I got lost BECAUSE I couldn't get back by the path I came from.
Can I at least borrow a socket to recharge my phone's battery?
Just leave, please!
This is not the sort of place for a person like you to come to.
Don't say something like that.
H-Hey... Have we met?
That’s an old pickup line.
That’s not what I was trying...
Yukino-san, is that a guest?
N-No. Um...
Um, I’m Mibuu Kyousuke.
I'm actually supposed to be a detective.
But I’m embarrassed to admit that I’m lost.
May I at least borrow the phone?
Oh dear, is that what happened?
I am Hongo Yuriko, the mistress of this house.
And this is my daughter-
Yukino.
Nice to meet you.
I’m sorry, but we have no telephone here.
This place is rather isolated... And we have no servants here today...
Would you like to at least stay here for the night?
Is that okay?
Mother!
We can't offer you much, but don’t hesitate to make yourself at home.
Please?
Then I guess I’ll take you up on your offer.
Why did he actually come here?
I ate too much.
I’m safe for now, but I’d better call someone.
What the... I’m sleepy...
What’s this?
Something moving inside my uterus?
Looks like it’s finally coming out.
Coming out?
Am I going to have a baby?
My hips are throbbing.
Looks like your uterus has opened up a lot too.
What?
Something’s... Coming out...
Hey! What’s...
It’s moving...
A baby...
The legs... They're straining...
This feels so good.
Having a baby... Feels this good?
Pull it out.
It’s coming out.
Something so big... It’s coming out.
I’m cumming!
Giving birth... Feels so good.
What the hell was that just now?
Besides, was that...
Yukino-san?
That’s right! The girl in my dreams, she looks exactly like Yukino-san!
But...
It's so healthy, isn't it, Kyousuke-san, your...
Your dick... It’s throbbing...
Like a baby... It’s overflowing...
It’s okay... Cum whenever you want.
Cum, please.
You’ll feel better. Cum.
So delicious.
What’s happening?
I can’t stop ejaculating.
That man finally came here.
Not knowing anything...
Please leave soon.
If you don’t...
Do you have business with me?
Did I scare you?
Sorry.
I wasn't scared!
If you don’t have business with me, would you please go?
Cut it out and leave, please.
This isn’t the place for people like you.
Hurry!
Yeah, about that...
I was told me I could stay longer, so I...
Why?!
You really should leave!
It’s best for you!
You’re probably right.
But I need to talk to you.
To me?
You might not believe it, but...
What you've mentioned, it's... Normal.
Normal?
But if nothing’s been said then it’s still okay.
You need to forget what you saw and leave.
That’s not what I mean. A pretty girl just like you was in trouble...
So I thought...
A pretty girl WAS in trouble.
She looked just like you.
My dreams always come true.
And if that girl turns out to be you...
Then I want to save you.
Mr 'Unknown Detective'...
Even if you’re right, what exactly can you do about it?
If that’s my fate, then I must be bound to it.
Thank you.
But please leave.
Hey, Yukino.
This guy, eh?
Mushizo, do you have business with me?
What?
What a slutty bitch you are.
What are you doing? Hey!
Stop it.
Stop it, Mr Detective.
Releasing her whorish juices already.
N-No...
You bastard!
No!
Time to stop playing house.
Time to come with me.
... Yes.
Thanks for saying I’m pretty.
Shit. Who would leave when looked at like that?
I spoke with him.
He said he wanted to save me... And I was so happy I could cry.
I only met him in my dreams until now...
But just as he wishes to save me, I must be the one to save him.
Even if my wish is to be with him,
it’s impossible.
So at least...
For the sexy-you... This should do the trick.
Lucky you.
Be grateful!
I am.
Want it in your tits?
How much longer can the thrill continue?
No.
I’m scared.
Someone help...
O-Ow.
Looks like it’ll go in further.
For the slutty Yukino-tan, this suits ya perfectly.
No... Why?
What gross juice you’re spewing out.
Why?
Why is my body happy about this?
What about here?
Next up...
No...
Good.
Don’t...
I don’t like it... But it feels like I'm going to cum...
It’s getting more intense.
Look at all that slutty juice coming out.
You are your mother’s girl after all.
It's so frustrating... So frustrating...
No... Don’t...
Don’t...
Stop...
Don’t! Not again. Not again!
It’s all flowing out.
Looks like you’d prefer this.
This tingling is awesome!
No...
Don’t... It’s piercing me...
Stop... No...
I’m cum... Cumming...
I can’t stand it!
Her spasms are getting me harder and harder!
It stings!
I’ll cum...
I’ll cum!
Our sperm is great. Drink it all up.
If not, you’ll be punished!
Delicious semen... So much...
It’s stopped.
Is it over?
Is that all?
Then it’s punishment time.
No way. I thought we were finished.
Don’t... Not that... I’ll die!
I can’t stand that face.
Your poker face is wobbling.
You okay with that?
No!
Well then, are ya ready?
No... Help me...
Don't be worn out already.
My uterus... It'll break!
Shit, I suppose there's no helping it.
No... No way!
Don’t!
Don’t watch me poop...
Hey, she’s shitting herself.
No. Don’t look. Don’t look!
Don’t watch!
She’s getting all excited while shitting.
What a fucking slut.
Awesome!
It’s still coming out.
No... Being watched like this?
I can’t take it.
I’m done.
We need to have fun with the next part, too.
You have no time to rest. You need more punishment.
Okay.
Shit!
What the hell is that?
Yukino-san...
Good evening.
May I come in?
Let’s feel good together.