No... No!
N-No... No!
Wait, I'm still...
Don't!
No! I-It hurts!
No way! It hurts!
You were still a virgin despite being a female ninja.
This is interesting.
O-Ouch! It hurts!
S-Stop this!
I-It's reaching deep inside me... No!
Ouch! Stop moving!
No! Please stop moving!
Stop, stop!
Even though this is my first time...
Don't worry, the pain will soon stop!
No... No!
Huh... Huh, what?
My belly just felt numb!
How is it? That's the spiritual power of the ogres!
S-Spiritual power of ogres?
Hey, look at that! Your body keeps getting hotter
as their meat sticks penetrate you!
This can't be... It feels good...
No, don't do that!
S-Stop rubbing them! No way, no!
There's no way you hate this when
your nipples got that hard already!
Wh-Why?
Even though they forcibly keep
scraping inside me, why?
I'm moaning... I don't get it but this is amazing!
This feels far from when I do it by myself!
Am I... responding to this pleasure?!
You can't stop craving more and more, right?
A-Amazing! This is amazing!
I'll end up addicted to this!
Keep thrusting it more in my pussy!
I want to feel good a lot! I want lots and lots of it!
Very, well then! I'll make you come.
Take all of it inside your body!
No, No!
His cock is getting bigger!
No way, no! Something is coming deep inside!
No—!
You are our decoy.
You'll be our hostage when those
ninja folks sneak in here later!!
Nee... Nee-sama...
Botan-neesama... F-Forgive me...
I-I'm...
Kunoichi Botan
Female Ninja Botan
Episode One
I-Intruder... Intruder alert!
I'm already detected...
Ninja Arts: Shadow Clones!
You use quite an intriguing technique, female ninja.
This is bad! Did I just walk into an ambush?
Botan-neesama! Forgive me!
I'm... I'm already done for!
Yasuzu!
No, no!
Please forget about me and run away by yourself!
No!
How about it? Do you want to fornicate as well, huh?
You, fiend!
You fell for it!
What's with their strength?
No, I can't move an inch!
Even ninjas like you can't overcome the strength of demi-ogres!
Demi-ogres? These people?
So you at least have heard about them,
humans dwelt on by spirits of ogres!
Their intellect sharply falls
but their physical strength and stamina
soar way beyond humans!
They literally are human-shaped brutes!
How can he possibly control these demi-ogres?!
Is your name Botan?
Now that I have a better look,
you have quite a nice body.
It's such a waste that you became a ninja.
Fine! If you're planning to rape me
then rape me as much as you please!
I won't yield to someone like you so easily!
I wonder how long will that facade of yours last.
Wh-What are these? Huh, what?!
Those are my adorable demon slugs.
Those things love women so much!
S-Stop! Stop sucking me!
They'll give you an unbearable
pleasure when you get used to them!
Don't mess with me! This feels
nothing but disgusting for me!
What the hell are they doing?!
My body suddenly feels hot!
This can't be, no way!
Are these slugs doing something to my body?!
I'm starting to feel strange!
N-No!
Stop! Stop entering inside me!
Th-This is bad! If this goes on, I'm...
That's great! Keep it up!
Keep playing with my demon slugs!
By the way, do you want to know
what happened to your clones?
Huh?!
O-Ouch!
No... No!
N-No! Stop that, stop!
S-Stop messing my clones up!
It looks like they are enjoying themselves though.
Alright, you guys are gonna
accompany those two next!
W-Wow! This is supposed to just be a clone,
but she's actually wet inside...
Isn't this one just like a real human!
This feels so good! Female ninjas
sure are on another level!
Her tightness down here is
totally unlike other women!
Oh... I'm gonna come!
Even though my clones are
being violated recklessly,
they're making such indecent faces.
They're feeling good.
I-It started to feel good for them!
No...
Sh-She's squeezing me so
tightly! Isn't this one hell of a slut
N-No... Stop saying weird things!
Wh-What should I do?
After watching them, even I will...
Even I'm gonna end up feeling strange!
No, I shouldn't!
H-Her mouth feels good too! I can't get
enough of the way she uses her tongue!
Good, you're doing good! Try harder
to not hit me with your teeth!
No, you can't do that!
How does it feel to watch your
own self sexually aroused?
Come on, isn't it about time? Don't you
want to get stirred up inside as well?
Huh?!
No way, not there!
I knew it! I had a hunch that
it's your first time in this hole!
No, it hurts!
No way, putting it in my ass...
Pull it off my ass!
Your clones have already tried it, you know!
Stop! No, stop!
You might act with disdain on sex,
but your body is craving for a meat stick!
There you go, watch your clones as well!
Wow!
Both cocks are rubbing against
each other inside! It feels great!
I never felt this good before!
Both cocks are hitting each other!
Feels good, so good!
A-Amazing!
I'm begging you... More...
I want it deeper in both my ass and pussy...
More, do it even a lot more!
Punish this filthy female ninja even a lot more!
Stop! You can't, you can't do that!
You two shouldn't feel good from all these!
I have a mission as a female ninja!
No, you can't!
Wow! Good, good! it feels great!
Okay, I'm coming! I'm gonna shoot a lot inside you!
Please do so! Come, please come!
Shoot it inside me!
Make a mess of my pussy as you wish!
She's clamping me down there!
You won't really think that she's just a clone!
I can't take it anymore! I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
Spray me! Spray me with your piping hot semen!
Make my pussy... make my pussy come!
They both look like they're in ecstasy.
How about it? Do you want to come as well, huh?
Even me too...
No! Th-That's not true, not at all!
I don't want to come! There's no way
I'd want to come from my ass,
but those slugs made my body...
Hey, won't it be alright?
I'll see to it myself that you'll come a lot!
No! Stop! Don't do it so roughly!
No, I'm coming! You're making me come!
No! No, you can't!
You can't! No!
No! No! No!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Feels good... Good...
We still haven't had enough!
Just when I thought there will be three of them...
It can't be helped, then.
Shall I make you take care
of all these remaining men?
This can't be real, no!
No way, this isn't over yet?
No... No—!
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization