Stop...
Stop!
No!
Make it stop!
No, I'm coming! I'm coming again!
I'm gonna come!
Coming! I'm coming!
I-I came! I-I came already!
I-I'm begging you!
M-Make it stop!
There's no way we'll stop even if you say that.
N-No way!
Stop it from thrusting!
Coming, it's coming! No, no!
I'll keep on coming if this goes on!
Hey, hurry up and come from
the wooden pole already!
I-I'm... I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
Somebody help me!
Botan-neesama—!
Y-Yasuzu!
Wh-What are you doing to Yasuzu!
Even the so-called female ninjas end up
as mere girls after going through this.
Alright, isn't it's about time for you to squeal?!
How about it? Under whose orders
have you infiltrated my mansion?!
That's one thing I can't disclose!
You should answer me quickly
for your own body's sake!
Damn you! I won't always be able
to hold myself back just like this!
No... No more!
Y-You'll tear me apart!
You'll tear me apart!
Help me, Botan-neesama!
Help me—!
Yasuzu!
I-I'm begging you... You can
do anything with me!
But not Yasuzu... Don't do
cruel things on her anymore!
Are you telling me what to do
when you're nothing but a bitch?!
Take this, you female ninja!
Impudent, take this!
Th-this is bad! I have to do something!
If this goes on, both of us will be killed!
Kunoichi Botan
Female Ninja Botan
Episode Two
Yasuzu, are you alright?
Y-Yes...
But if they continue violating me,
I think it'll drive me crazy...
Our bodies are being corrupted by
the spiritual power of the ogres.
I'm near my limit as well.
Why can the merchant in this mansion
utilize the spiritual power of the ogres?
He most likely managed to get hold of the
legendary secret concoction, kichoumu.
Kichoumu?
In any case, we need to get out of here first!
Ninja Arts: Shadow Clones!
Huh?
N-Nee-sama!
Th-This is the most that I can do now.
The kichoumu should be hidden
somewhere here in this mansion!
If we get our hands on it, we'll be able
to bring our bodies back to normal.
We might even be able to match
the strength of the demi-ogres!
It should be here...
N-Nee-sama, could that be this thing?
Kichoumu
Kichoumu!
I'm sure that this is it! Good job
on finding this, Yasuzu!
The fact that you knew about the kichoumu
lead you both into my trap!
Where are you? Where are you hiding?!
What is this?!
This kichoumu is my trump card.
Of course, I'd always have it with me.
My body is getting numb!
Nee-sama, I'm...
I can't go on...
Shit! How did this happen?!
You see, this is a trap purposely made
to catch intruders like you.
That's too bad for both of you.
You, bastard... I failed...
Worry not, I won't kill you yet.
You both still need to provide
plenty of entertainment!
I'm fully exposed...
The crowd can see my shameful state!
No... It's digging in!
My pussy is nibbling on the wedge
as it pushes in between the lips!
What should I do?
Come on, tell everyone who's watching
about what you did right now.
W-We are female ninjas.
We were ordered to sneak into a mansion here.
We killed several people.
We were captured
and then we were raped over and over.
O-Our bodies were
corrupted with the spiritual power of the ogres.
Even when we're tortured like this, and even if this should hurt...
My body feels hot
and I can't help it from throbbing.
I'm begging every one of you.
Punish us vulgar and filthy women...
Please exact punishment on us!
Please violate us!
Until we regret what we did and until we wish to die...
Rape us, rape us please!
As you all see, this is a public
execution of these two criminals.
Enjoy them both to your heart's content!
I-It feels good! Good!
What, isn't your pussy already
soaking wet from the start?
Did sitting on the wooden horse really feel good?
Yes! When my pussy gets violated,
I feel strangely good.
Hey, hey hey! Then that wouldn't
count as a punishment, right?
The hell with that! Just let us have a go!
Forgive me! Keep on punishing me more!
You can violate my body any way you want!
I'm tired of waiting!
Don't shove it inside!
A crowd is forming around me!
Wow! It feels great!
Hey, come on, female ninja!
Squeeze your pussy tighter!
Aren't you looking forward to this?
I understand. I-I'll tighten it up!
I'll tighten up my pussy!
H-How's this?
You're doing great! That's so good, good!
I will do my best!
That's so good, that's good!
Then, can I use this one as well?
Th-That's my...
They're rubbing together! Both cocks
are rubbing against each other inside me!
I never felt like this before.
M-My insides are getting messed up!
T-Tighten up your pussy!
Oh, incredible! You're squeezing tightly inside!
It feels good! They're rubbing together!
Wow, great! Th-This one is amazing!
She's a real perverted girl!
You're doing great!
As expected from a female
ninja's tongue technique!
Both of my mouth and pussy...
My pussy feels good too!
Their dicks are getting hotter! They're also twitching!
I can feel it, I'm feeling so good!
His cock grew bigger!
He's gonna come. He'll shoot lots of his gooey semen into my pussy.
I'm yearning for it!
My pussy throbs from craving semen!
I'm coming! Coming... I'm gonna come!
No, don't hump that hard on me!
But it feels good, so good!
No! Don't... Don't thrust it that hard into me!
No, don't!
Stop thrusting up on me that much!
You're reaching deep inside me! So deep, so deep!
So deep, so deep! S-So... So deep!
No... I'm coming!
More... Come plenty more times!
Do that and the spiritual power of the ogres
will corrupt your bodies even faster!
And in the end, you will lose your sanity!
No, please!
I-I'm begging you!
Let me have a rest!
Idiot! What the hell are you talking about?
Isn't your pussy enjoying this so much?
Doing something like this... You're cruel!
I'll end up being stretched loose!
Stop lying! You're moaning with
pleasure while getting your ass raped!
Who's gonna get stretch where?
No! Th-That hurts!
It really hurts!
Shut up with that blabbering! Here you go!
I'm coming, coming, coming!
No, stop! If you do it intensely like that,
I'm coming again!
You'll make me come from my pussy!
It's okay! Come with both your ass and pussy!
I can't take it anymore, I'm gonna come!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
No, don't do it that hard!
No! My ass hurts... It hurts!
She's getting more and more sensitive.
I'm already...
You're breaking me, you're breaking me!
My belly already hurts!
To think that it feels this good...
My breasts are getting kneaded again!
It feels so good!
I-I'm coming—!
I'm sorry, Yasuzu.
I wasn't able to save you.
I-I'm sorry that things turned out this way.
Me too... for sneaking in alone and getting caught...
And getting you in trouble...
I'm sorry...
I'm...
Yasuzu!
We're not done yet!
No! No more!
Stop, Yasuzu is...
You're not done yet as well!
Here you go, here you go!
S-Stop!
I'm already full of semen inside!
Looking good! You both look like pregnant!
I can't take it anymore, no!
But it feels good!
I can't take it anymore! No! Stop!
Both my pussy and ass are full of semen!
So hot! It feels hot!
Any more of this and I'll die!
I'll really die!
No, stop!
What are you even saying now?
This is supposed to be an execution!
Stop! I can't take this much!
Please, I really can't anymore! I'm gonna die!
Here, come on! We're far from getting done!
You'll both be violated until everyone's satisfied!
You are murderers! You're indecent sluts!
Nobody will weep for you even if you both die!
After that, we were both tortured and raped
by countless men until we dropped dead.
Everyone, I'm sorry for us being incompetent.
And so, this is our punishment.
But since I'm gonna die in the end,
I wanted to at least die feeling good.
Mission       Failed
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization