I can see our future getting
tainted in the "Cuntry".
This country... And even the whole
nation is already doomed!
No—!
Kuroinu
Kedakaki Seijo wa Hakudaku ni Somaru
A Shocking Tragedy: What Captivated The Pure and Adorable Young Princess is the Genital with a Black Gleam Chapter
Black Dogs
Noble and Holy Women Tainted Milky White
A Shocking Tragedy
What Captivated The Pure
and Adorable Young Princess
is the Genital with a Black Gleam Chapter
On that day...
At that moment,
I fell in love.
No, that's not right.
If the defense here comes under heavy clash,
they won't have any choice but to go around here.
That's brilliant, Alicia-neesama!
Let's rethink our strategy.
All this time...
I had my eyes on you for all this time!
From that moment, onwards...
I badly wanted to push the princess down and hump her!
I wanted to make her scream!
I wanted to grab those delicate hips
and shove my cock into that still developing ass!
Stop!
Pervert!
Traitor!
I've always been looking at it, but you
sure have a wonderful butt, princess!
S-Stop this, Beardsley.
Do you understand what you're doing right now?
There is nothing to be afraid of, princess!
No!
Princess.. princess!
You're doing great! That feels fantastic!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Finally, I finally did it with the princess...
With that princess...
Th-This should be enough, right?
I won't resist!
Finally... Finally, I...
Untie me!
Beardsley, take these off!
Shut up.
I'm about to make you a slave to my cock!
What are you up to?
S-Stop!
I'm still not done with this one down here!
Here on this silky smooth, nibbling
and still bald childish pussy of yours!
Now, I'm about to
make you unable to live without cock.
You will become a slave to my huge cock!
Fall in love with me!
Stop, Beardsley!
P-Put that filthy thing away!
What are you saying?
This is something that will become
the most important thing for you!
C-Come back to your senses, Beardsley!
Ho-ah!
N-No—!
N-No!
Pull it out!
Oh, it's so deep! I'm going in so deep!
P-Pull it out!
S-Stop!
Coming... I'm coming!
Don't shoot it inside me!
I-I can't get enough of this!
That princess who always presents herself
as noble and valiant...
has now been poured with cock juice by me!
Okay, stop right there...
Bastard!
You idiot, what are we gonna
do if you knocked her up?
The princess will still lend her body after this.
Th-This is my woman!
A-Are you gonna betray me on our deal?
Aren't you the one who betrayed someone?
Stop, don't touch my woman!
Aren't there a lot of other girls out there?
You don't have to worry.
We'll just clean her up and
have a talk for a short while.
W-Wait! Hold it right there!
Give my woman back!
Black Dogs: Noble and Holy
Women Tainted Milky White
She's doing great!
Come on... Say something, princess.
I'll never give in!
Come on, relax.
I'm gonna clean the part which that man sullied.
Stop!
Even if you do as you please to our bodies,
I and Celestine-sama will never ever submit to you!
Did you hear that, Miss Goddess?
Will that suffering lamb be fine
even if you don't guide her to the truth?
She's still resisting.
Just as expected from a princess,
she haven't even touched herself.
Despite that, aren't you too sensitive?
Your nipples already got this hard.
Here you go!
Come on, I'll make you feel
even better if you'll speak up.
You know a secret passageway
in that fortress, right?
I can't, just stop!
Hey...
Be honest and let yourself feel good, princess.
Wh-Who would even feel good from this?
Prim...
Oh-ho... Your nipples got so hard...
Come on!
Come!
Where am I...
What just happened to me...
This is a dream.
Celestine-sama will never do that...
You should focus here instead of
worrying about others, princess.
Does my cock feel that good?
My cock is having a good time inside you as well!
Y-You, this is—
Just as expected from a royal-blooded girl.
She has a body well-suited for conceiving a progeny.
Well, it can't be anything but slutty!
This is such a nice body!
It finally gained a taste for cocks!
You're wrong!
No way...
S-Something like this...
will never break me down!
Prim... Prim is...
Hey, princess...
Don't you want to protect that girl in the fortress?
Then, how about telling where the
secret passage is only to me?
Who the hell would?!
I have no interest in that girl.
I just want to have an upper hand for prestige.
While the Black Dogs troupe
are occupying this fortress,
you should just listen to me.
When we go over the next fortress, I can let
the women go and you can do what you want.
Or do you want that girl to serve
as a sex slave with you too?
Even that goddess you believed in couldn't
help but shake her hips over a man!
You're incredible! Vult-sama, Vult-sama!
Shoot it out, shoot it out! Vult-sama!
Please give me a lot of your thick semen!
You have to promise...
...that you won't lay your hands on Prim!
Didn't I tell you?
I have no interest in that girl at the fortress.
You don't have to worry.
If you'll tell me where the secret
passage to the fortress is,
I'll guarantee your safety.
So you should just let yourself loose for now.
I can't take it anymore!
That's good, princess!
You poor thing...
That man soiled you with his semen.
I'll wash up your insides instead.
Hey, princess. Now it's your turn to clean mine.
Just as expected from a princess,
even the way you lick is dignified.
Come on, get on it!
Alright! That's enough, everyone.
We're going to the next fortress!
Alright, let's go!
Well then, we should also go.
My... My woman...
I'll make sure to save her.
I'll definitely...
This one will take a while before it falls.
Where's the boss?
Nah, never saw him since yesterday.
He might have found a lovely woman
and having it off somewhere?
You numbskull! The boss
will kill you if he hears that!
This is awesome!
So there really is such a passageway.
Come on, you can go first.
Will it be alright?
It's alright, now go.
Prim!
Do it already, or I'll shove an enema up in your ass!
N-No—!
What? You're already here, boss.
Yeah! You're late, Hicks.
You still have a long way to go.
Just as expected from you, boss!
You always work flawlessly.
Prim...
Huh?
N-No way...
N-Nee-sama...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization