No! Why are you doing this?
Taking the virginity of my student feels quite good.
I'll be sure to give you extra credit!
I-It hurts!
My insides are being violated by your hard thing!
To have my first time be with.
A horrible person like you!
It's humiliating and disgusting!
I have no intention of stopping.
J-Just do whatever you want!
In exchange, you need to keep your end of the bargain!
Sensei!
Oh, Nomiya?
Come on, no one's around. You can just call me Nanako.
I've gone from being the tutor to your teacher, so forget it.
St-St-Stop!!
As expected of Mr. Uehara.
Even after I hit you with full force, you haven't got a scratch!
Narukawa-san?
It's fine if you're being playful, but do not
forget your place as a student.
Am I clear?
Yes, I apologize.
The Principal's scary.
I'm more afraid of the person who jumped me.
I only did it because it's you.
Actually, I have a little favor to ask.
Oh, the bell! I'll ask you later.
Just can't stay still, can she.
Your cock is the best!
Thank you for fucking this indecent pussy of mine!
I apologize for my impudence earlier.
I'm sorry for being so strict in front of them.
Save your excuses.
In exchange, I'll have you fully satisfy me.
I prepared this school...
In order to satisfy you, master!
There's a lot you don't want to be made public after all.
I'll be doing as I please from now on.
That makes me so happy!
Please enjoy this to the fullest!
I definitely... won't!
Don't worry. Being a guy with a healthy sex drive, I'll be
sure to subjugate the rest of my targets just as well.
Black Classroom • Cheeky Leotard/Mahiru ~ Drilling
a Large Rod into An Unyielding Asshole
Sensei! I have a favor to ask...
My adviser is out today...
Could you stand in for her?
It's pretty important, so... please?
I've got no choice if that's how it is, but...
It's not my area of expertise, so I can only handle the basics.
It'll be fine if it's you!
Oh, it's Sensei.
What's he doing?
Nanako?
Don't overdo it. You're our ace after all!
Sensei, please watch Mahiru closely so that
she doesn't push herself too hard, okay?
Wai... what are you saying?
See you later, Mahiru.
Sensei, good work today.
Thanks for helping me out.
Now that I look more closely, you've got quite the body.
You could've gotten a scholarship for this
body alone, regardless of your grades.
Sensei, I know you're probably trying
to compliment me, but...
That could be taken as sexual harassment.
Oh, sorry. I said that without thinking.
No worries, I know you said that
without any ulterior motive.
Just as I heard...
Sensei, you're pretty good.
Your advice was on point.
I didn't really notice that myself.
I'm a scholarship student, so I've got
to deliver results after all.
This time, everything seems to be going well!
Hm? What's the matter, Sensei?
This might be a little strange for a
hard worker like you, but...
Could you just patiently hear me out?
Y-Yeah.
Truth is, you might not be able to enter
any competitions at this rate.
I've heard some things.
There are rumors going around that you've
been engaging in indecent activities.
Wai... Rumors about me? Huh? Indecent?
Huh?!
If there are any problem students within the club,
all of its members bear a collective responsibility.
Wait! I haven't done anything indecent!
This is horrible... why is that kind of lie even...
Yeah, that's a pretty bad lie.
Sensei, you believe me, right?
Yeah well, right now it's a lie, but...
Huh? Sensei? What?
What's the matter?
We're going to make that rumor real.
What are you doing? That hurt!
If this is a joke, it's not funny!
Hey! Let go! Let go of me!
The way you're moving this big ass of yours...
you trying to invite me in?
As if! You're acting really strange!
You egocentric teacher! Pervert!
No! Don't look!
Don't hide it!
Yelling while violating a girl? You're the worst!
I can't get enough of this ass.
It makes me wanna hurry up and jam my cock into it!
That's disgusting! You demon! Beast!
Pervert! Let go of me!!
Keep your struggles to a minimum.
That hurt!
What are you doing? I said no! Stop it!
What a great view.
I told you, it hurts!
Don't be so rough!
You're the biggest scum I've ever met!
You're gonna give your virginity to this scum.
Who would do that?
Let go! Let go of me, you!
Do you want to be hit again?
Well, if you don't want to lose your virginity,
I'll have to make do with this.
Wait! Where are yo... No! It hurts!
It feels disgusting!
Hey! What are you trying to do?
That won't fit!
No!!
Looks like it opened up a bit.
No!! Not in my butt!
No! It's gross! I'm telling you, it won't go in!
Don't go any further! It won't it!
You're going to break my asshole!
What a great feeling. This hole is the best!
No! This can't b... Why my ass?
It's gonna break! My ass!
No! Not my breasts!
Don't look! My ass...
It's starting to throb!
Oh? You're feeling it? You've got
potential to be an ass slave.
Stop! Don't rub my breasts!
Let me enjoy this while I can.
No more! I'm losing it... Stop!
It hurts so much, I could die!
This is better than I thought.
It's coming out! It's reaching into my stomach!
This is...
My butt feels weird.
It feels disgusting.
You really do have a great body.
I must get some of this too.
Huh?
You said you wouldn't take my virginity!
Your ass was a different story.
My first... why?
It hurts! No! Why? Stop!
Good. Scream more! Every time you do, you get tighter!
No! It hurts! Don't hold on to me! No! No!
My insides are ripping apart!
It hurts!
Stop! I don't want this!
Yeah, let's end this with my semen in your pussy.
No! If you do that, I'll get pregnant! Don't!
No, you'll take it all in!
No! No!!
You really came inside!
No! No! No!!
It's going into my stomach!
I'm going to get pregnant!
I don't want to get pregnant!
No! There's so much semen inside my stomach...
No way! Senpai and sensei are...
Why did you rape her, sensei?
Doesn't look like there's morning practice.
No! If you cum inside, my stomach's
gonna overflow! Stop!!
My ass again?
It's going to split open! No!
Please let me go!
What should I do? I can't tell anyone about this.
Hm? That was Nanako, right?
Die, you!
Hey, why did you dodge that?
You...
Do you understand the situation you're in?
I know!
I was raped... and won't be able to enter the competition.
I can't show my face in front of them.
I thought you were a good teacher!
Did you tell anyone about yesterday?
How could I?
So who says you can't enter?
But, yesterday, you said...
I've no intention of letting yesterday's events go public.
You can enter the competition.
So I can still enter the competition?
Phew.
See? I am a good teacher.
Y-Yeah.
Yeah right! After you did all those horrible things to me!
Is your ass alright?
If you don't take care of it, there'll be problems.
Use the medicine I gave you yesterday.
Whose fault do you think that is? You...
If you go any further, I'll tell everyone.
I get it already.
Hmph! Idiot! Idiot! Pervert! Devil!
Y... You again?
You...
You don't learn, do you? What about the competition?
I want to enter, but...
I definitely won't forgive you!
You!!
Wai... Again? You demon! Devil!
Stop it!
Wait! You idiot!
We're only just beginning.
The fun starts now.
Wai... Stop!
It hurts! Stop!
It hurts! It hurts!
You'll get wet soon enough.
What a perverted body.
No! I don't want...
Don't do that! Stop!!
Do you really hate it?
Of course I do!
Whatever you're doing just feels disgusting!
Again! In my butt! Stop!
Idiot! Scum! I told you, I don't want this!
Mahiru, your insides seem pretty happy.
Sh-Shut up!
Don't say such dumb things!
No matter how many times you do it,
it won't make me feel happy! Idiot!
Let's ask your body.
No! Sto...
Don't put it...
What's this? My body is...
The stick that's going in your ass is all lubed up
from your wet pussy. Get it?
Stop saying weird things! Just hurry up and take it out!
No! Stop! You pervert!
I can't wait till you make a lewd face again.
Screw you! I won't do that!
No way! Don't cum! No, don't! Stop! Hey, stop!
No! You came! You came inside again!
Even though I told you not to!
Shit! He came inside me again. That bastard.
He really...
Principal!
Um, this is...
You'll catch a cold if you stay dressed like that.
Hurry up and get changed.
Principal... I... I...
I've been... by Uehara-sensei...
He's done a lot to me...
Oh my, you were that happy?
You were taken care of so well by Master.
Huh?
Ah, I'm so jealous.
When I was your age, I was already Master's personal asshole.
Pr-Principal?
Puberty and Sexual Behavior
Th-This is...
I told you not to, didn't I?
Looks like you need some severe punishment.
I've seen this from my friends, but this
isn't something that goes in the butt!
Narukawa!
1. The best option when you are being
pressured to choose your sexual stance.
This is enough isn't it? I don't know the answer.
I can't think!
What a good face you're making.
In this situation, you can see...
Your body fluids are spewing out.
Why is my body getting so hot?
Does it feel so good that you're losing your balance?
As if...
Oh no! I need to pee!
Are you at your limit? Don't you want to
enter the competition?
I won't let you!
Good job. Go let it out in the toilet.
Yes!
Huh? What? Wait!
No! Don't look! Don't look!
Oh? It's coming out nicely.
The smell isn't too strong either,
thanks to your healthy genes.
No! Stop! Stop!
No! Why is it still going?
You're so loud! I'm gonna have to shut
that mouth of yours!
What are you going to do?
Are you going to kill me?
Hey, hey. Who do you think I am?
You're a pervert, right? A demon, right? A devil, right?
Wai... Class is starting soon!
What are you thinking? You pervert!
The girl who lost her virginity during club
activities is the one to care about class?
I didn't! I was forced to!
I was forced to by the pervert standing in front of me!
You're still talking back to me, huh?
That's part of your charm though.
Now suck it.
Alright already.
You're gonna say that if I don't, you'll tell everyone, right?
Good girl.
Hurry up. You're too young to be doing "stare-play"
I get it, okay?
Wai... Sto...
This is gross!
No! It smells!
This guy make you a woman.
How rude of you.
Squeeze it tight with your entire mouth.
Use it in place of your pussy, okay?
No!
If you don't drink it all, I'll punish you.
Can't breathe!
Next, Narukawa! Come on, hurry up.
You're kidding, right?
No, please! Sensei, stop!
It'll be fine as long as you let it out every day.
It's some medicine to alleviate the whole process.
No, no, no! I'll definitely...
Mahiru, what's going on? You let out a weird
voice just now. Is something wrong?
Is she okay?
I'm fi... Sorry.
I just hit something...
No! I can't hold it in anymore!
That guy! Is he just going to stand there and watch?
Is he planning on watching me poop
out here? Is he serious?
Pooping in front of everyone... that's...
But I'm wearing a diaper...
Mahiru? Hey, you alright?
No, no! At this rate, I'll...
Yeah, just a second, I'll get...
No! At this rate, I'll... a place like this!
No!!!
It's over. Everyone's seeing this pervert...
While he's laughing at me.
Hey, Mahiru? What's the matter?
Hey!
H-Huh? They didn't notice?
Is it because of the diaper?
Thank god!
Looks like you're not feeling well.
I'll take her to the nurse's office, so
this'll be a self-study period.
That was a great show.
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
After shitting that much, your asshole
should be all clear now.
Again with my ass!
Stop!
Stop it!
Don't move your dick like that!
Give my butt a break!
I really don't want this!
Even though your ass is gripping me so tight?
That's not true!
My ass doesn't want it!
No!!
Your ass says differently!
No! What is this? My ass is tingling.
You can't cum inside there!
This place feels good huh, Mahiru?
No, it doesn't. It doesn't feel...
It doesn't!!
From a pervert like you...
It doesn't feel good at...
My butt is...
My body is... my body is... what is this?
My ass is going to... it's!
Right there! It feels good!
You're going to cum soon.
You're going to cum while getting fucked in the ass.
No! Stop!
I don't want to! I'm scared! No!
Just cum.
I'll let you truly revel in the glory of my semen.
I don't know! It feels like it's pumping in!
It's not stopping!
I'm going to go crazy!
Did you just cum from your ass?
Quite the pervert, aren't you?
But Mahiru, we're not done yet.
Now it's throbbing inside my pussy.
No! If your dick keeps hitting me
this deep, I'll lose it!
Looks like you're on course to cum
from both your ass and pussy.
I'm going to lose it again!
Your dick! No more!
My butt can't take it anymore!
Show me your perverted side!
No!! Both my pussy and butt are...
They're cumming from your semen!
I'm going to go crazy off this!
Translator: Hikarucon
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Punk4real