W-Wait! Can you listen to what I have to say...
I am Alicia Arcturus.
From this day onwards, the Order of
Holy Iris is taking command in here.
Kuroinu
Kedakaki Seijo wa Hakudaku ni Somaru
A Horrifying Orgy: Feasting on a Pure Princess Knight's Silky White Skin Demands Courage at the Tip of the Sword Chapter
Black Dogs
Noble and Holy Women Tainted Milky White
A Horrifying Orgy
Feasting on a Pure Princess Knight's
Silky White Skin Demands
Courage at the Tip of the Sword Chapter
What's the matter, Prim?
Nothing...
Beardsley, stop the carriage!
Be careful on the steps.
Yes, Alicia-neesama.
If I remember correctly...
There should be a spring here nearby.
I thought that it's a perfect place
if you wanted to take a break.
I'll just wait here for you.
Alright, then. Let's go with that.
It should be fine around here.
It's alright now, Prim.
It's been a while since we spent time like this.
Is that why you seem to be
more mature in my eyes now?
N-No way...
Alicia-neesama...
Are you feeling better now?
Nee-sama...
Hmm?
Nee-sama! What does...
What does it mean to love someone?
Huh?
Why can't one hold their audacity back
whenever they're with that person?
Loved one, hun...
Together with this sword, my fate is
to protect the way of life of the nation.
I wish for nothing else.
In this continent exists a land larger than others, Eostia.
In this land divided by a long conflict
is a white goddess who can see the future.
The conflict's end is now imminent
thanks to Celestine-sama's guidance.
Or so it should be...
Black Dogs: Noble and Holy
Women Tainted Milky White
Oh no...
I didn't realize that I dozed off...
Just what on earth is happening here?!
Beardsley!
This is...
What's the meaning of this?
What's happening here?
Why is the "Black Dogs" troupe in here?
Don't you dare hit it
with your teeth, come on!
Scoundrels, just where did you come from?!
Stop right there!
Stop this at once!
Oh, my... Hello there, princess.
You've been quite late,
so we already helped ourselves.
Stop! All of you—
On no! No way!
I'd rather not become a traitor.
Hey there...
We'll end up with a pile of corpses
if you try to resist, princess.
Or if you're willing to at least get yourself
disgraced, we'll let all our women captives go away.
Shall we go to heaven?
You'll all witness the birth
of the nation of "Cuntry".
Be good girls, alright?
We'll take good care of you all.
Hey goddess, Princess Alicia is being insolent!
Celestine-sama!
Even if she's someone revered as a goddess...
She becomes like this when stripped naked.
Behold this indecent body!
It's been yearning for the
moment of its copulation.
No... Stop that, you two!
Celestine-sama!
I'll be right there—
No!
Stop! You're filthy!
You should just accept it.
So that you'll have the best
kiss, get pregnant and survive!
Have some shame, Beardsley!
This is your important share of burden, princess!
What are you saying?!
Alright then, I won't hold back and take you now.
You're the one who should have
some shame instead, princess!
Let go of me!
No! Any more than this and...
No, don't!
Stop! Get away from Celestine-sama!
Come on!
Here! Here, get pregnant!
You too!
I... I can see it...
I can see our future getting
tainted in the "Cuntry".
This country... And even the whole
nation are already doomed!
No—!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization