I... must atone for my sins for getting us into this war.
Citizens, who followed me for long...
If I can ease your pain, even for a little bit...
Please...
Fuck me.
Kuroinu: Kedakaki Seijo wa Hakudaku ni Somaru
Vault led the massive demon army, Kuroinu, to establish the Sex Empire.
It was an appalling idea of turning all women into sex toys for men.
This is practically the deciding battle.
Once we defeat Claudia, the Holy Knight...
The Goddess will be stripped of her forces.
Why...
Why?
Why would you...
Why did you betray us?
General Glave...
or should I say, Father?
Claudia.
Bear my child.
What did you just say?
This is an order.
Bear my child.
No!
Do you have any idea what you just said?
I would rather bite off my tongue and die!
I'm Claus's wife!
Then that impotent son of mine is no longer useful to us.
You're taking my husband as a hostage?
It's your duty to pass on the magnificent blood of the prestigious Laventine Clan
when you married into this family.
It is also my duty.
No... don't, father!
You're not going anywhere!
You will bear my child!
You belong to me!
N-No!
Your body belongs to me!
No!
Take a good look!
My cock is deep inside you!
As a mentor and as a father-in-law,
He raised me to become a holy knight with tough love.
What drove him to this madness?
Take a look.
You don't care what happens to your husband?
I can't...
Look, or I'll release inside!
I've swallowed up my father's cock.
Father! What are you...
Make sure you don't miss the moment when I release inside you!
That's not what you promised!
You said you wouldn't if I looked...
It's finally time!
It's time for me to release my seeds into your uterus!
No!
Pull it out!
Pull it out, please!
Anywhere but inside!
You'll bear my child.
I'll release a lot inside to make sure you get pregnant!
No!
Father!
Don't do this! Please!
I'm going to have sperm of someone other than Claus released inside me?
No!
No, no, no!
He's releasing a lot inside me...
My father-in-law's seed!
H-how could this happen...
I allowed someone other than Claus to release sperm inside me.
His father, of all people!
Please forgive me, honey.
Did you think it'll be over this quickly?
Have a look!
What's my dick like?
Is it soft now?
Say it!
If you don't...
I-It's hard.
Father's...
Father's cock is still hard!
I'll give you enough pleasure to forget about my son!
If I can endure this... then...
How can I be moaning?
I'm getting turned on by making love with him?
I can't believe his penis goes so deep!
No!
As I thought, you didn't know the true joy of being a woman even though you were married.
I'll teach you the true joy of being a woman!
No!
Please! Please stop, Father!
I don't want to get turned on by his penis.
No... why am I...
I'll release again.
I'll release a crapload inside you!
Anything but that!
If he releases any more inside me...
I can't take it anymore!
You're a holy knight protecting the Goddess.
Look at what a slut you've turned into.
You've turned someone on...
H-Honey?
I...
No...
Let's have my son see the moment you get impregnated.
N-No!
I can tell.
Your uterus is getting closer.
I can feel it in the tip of my cock!
Honey...
Please don't look.
Now you'll truly become mine!
I don't belong to you!
Can you say it to his face?
He's right.
Considering my current situation in front of him...
How can I possibly tell him to believe me?
Something is happening to me.
Something is coming.
I'm going to come.
I don't want to, but I'm going to come!
Oh no, I'm going to come.
He's watching...
I don't want to, but...
Keep your eyes fixed!
Your wife is about to be impregnated with a new member of the Laventine Clan!
Don't look!
Don't look at me while I'm having an orgasm and getting impregnated!
No!
Pull out your dick!
Pull it out! Don't release inside!
I don't want want to be impregnated!
Don't impregnate me!
Don't pour your cum inside my pussy!
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming again!
It's all over.
You'll become a product in the Sex Empire starting now.
I don't care what happens to me.
But...
I need you to continue being the Goddess to them.
As the high-elf goddess worshiped by the people.
That way, you'll have more value as a product.
Those hairs, ass, and tits of yours.
All men will swarm around you for them.
You deserve to become the ultimate symbol of the Sex Empire.
Hey, apparently we can buy those princesses as long as we pay for it.
Really?
I wonder how much they cost?
Promise me.
If I can stop myself from having an orgasm in this show,
you'll release Princess Origa.
All right, I'll consider it.
But how longer can you suppress your true nature from the whip after so long?
Although, maybe it's not enough to satisfy a true masochist slave like you.
No...
I'm no longer a slave.
I have to endure this... I have to...
for Princess Origa.
A-Am I... reminiscing?
I thought I had forgotten my disgraceful past.
Well? It's the smell of you favorite thing in the world.
Oh, no...
It stinks, and my nose feels like it's about to be pulled off...
but I want to smell more!
Looks like you don't really dislike this.
As expected of masochist slave whore.
I'm a... masochist whore.
W-What's this?
No...
I'm Princess Origa's knight.
I'm no longer a sex slave!
My entire body is turning into pussies.
Yes, I'm nothing but pussy holes!
Looks like you enjoyed that.
The more you feel pain, the more pleasure you get.
After all, that's how you've been trained.
Kuroinu: Kedakaki Seijo wa Hakudaku ni Somaru
95!
Anyone else?
100!
We have 120!
Anyone paying more?
150!
155!
My body... my body is burning.
My pussy isn't supposed to be allowed to be used humans,
but I'm in a good mood today.
Come on now, stick your boner in my pussy hard enough to mess it up.
Man, the aphrodisiac worked like charm!
We paid good money to get you.
We'll fuck your brain out even if you didn't tell us to!
Whoa, she's coming just from me sticking it in!
The one down there isn't enough to satisfy you, is it?
She came from giving a blowjob.
We have a whore princess here!
Pervert princess!
I'll let you come as many times as you want!
I'm coming!
My tits... I'm going to come.
You pervert whore princess!
I'll release right inside!
The Black Elf Princess is nothing more than a slutty dark-elf now.
Cocks... more cocks...
Everyone, we have surrendered to the Kuroinu Demonic Army.
We have lost.
It's all my fault for not having enough power to protect you.
I truly apologize.
This kingdom will enter a hard era as the Sex Empire.
I...
I... must atone for my sins for getting us into this war.
Everyone, please endure through this era with me.
We'll get through this.
Well then, it's showtime.
The legend of the glorious Kuroinu Demonic Army begins here.
By red devirginization of the White Goddess!
How does it feel to become a true woman?
In front of so many, too.
Don't worry.
You'll feel good soon enough.
Don't you still have something to say to the civilians?
Our demonic army isn't very patient!
Goddess!
Please look at the true form of the Goddess that has been defeated.
Starting today, women will live only to give pleasure to men.
There is no exception.
Goddesses will pleasure others too.
The atonement of the Goddess should be shared equally to everyone.
Citizens who followed me for long...
If I can ease your pain, even for a little bit...
Please...
Fuck me.
Lady Celestine!
Is this what it feels like to be inside Lady Celestine?!
I can't believe I'm sticking my dick inside the Goddess!
Lady Celestine.
Use your hands.
Just gripping it accomplishes nothing.
At least give him a handjob.
Stroke it!
Is this fast enough?
Lady Celestine is stroking my dick!
This is like a dream!
Lady Celestine, I'm going to...
M-Me too!
Goddess, please do me with your breasts!
A-Am I doing it right?
It's so nice and soft!
Celestine, what does a lowly sex toy like you have between your breasts?
I-It's a man's...
What was that? I couldn't hear you.
C-Cock!
It's a cock!
It's a really hot and big cock!
It's sucking in so hard and feels so good!
I'm going to...
Doesn't it feel great making men feel good with your body?
Y-Yes.
That is the role of women in this country.
And that is what you truly desire inside as well.
My breasts...
No!
It feels good...
Cocks feel good!
I'm coming! I'm releasing breast milk!
Cocks...
Thick cocks...
I can't get enough of the silky hair!
I can't get enough of these tits!
Her big ass wants more!
Cocks...
Thick all the way...
Hard and big cocks...
Dirty cocks...
I love cocks.
I love all kinds of cocks.
Cocks...
Cocks! Cocks! Cocks! Cocks! Cocks!
Cocks! Cocks! Cocks!
Well, I guess we're done.
It's a decent country now.
But... my battle has yet to end.
Not as long as there are things to take by force!
I, Celestine Lukures, the inheritor of Goddess Laurendeau's soul...
declare the establishment of the Sex Empire.