Hey, you got the wrong hole.
I thought you were gonna break her hymen right away!
What's with this asshole?
My lord...
This is the result of the declaration of a sex empire by Vault, the general of the Kuroinu Demonic Army.
We gotta kill them now, huh?
It's decided, huh?
These fools should die by my axe, huh?
Take that!
Vault, this has to be a joke, right?
His invasion has become nearly unstoppable.
Vault...
Kaguya x Luu, Luu x Maia / Insects wriggling in the soft skin, night of the deranged beasts
This is a pretty rude greeting for a reunion.
You've become a fine woman since the last time I saw you few years ago.
Well, thanks.
I didn't expect us to become enemies.
You've always been popular among the soldiers.
They all wanted to rape that fine body of yours.
Do you expect me to say I'm honored about that?
You're in charge of pleasuring my soldiers.
Have fun with them.
They might rip my pussy apart.
There's a special performance later.
Look forward to it.
Do you remember me?
I do. You, and everyone else.
You always flaunt that lewd body of yours, so I had trouble holding myself back!
Whoo! Maia's pussy is up for public display!
What an amazing pair of tits.
It looks nicer than I expected!
Ow!
Damn, it feels so tight because I haven't had sex for so long.
This is tighter than I expected!
I'm being raped now, right?
By my former comrades,
in front of everyone.
I can't believe someone like him is doing what he wants with my pussy.
You can actually make cute sounds.
Shut up.
I can't last much longer when it's so tight.
I'm gonna release soon.
What? Release?
Wait a minute!
Why are you acting like an innocent maiden now, Maia?
Not inside me!
Wait!
If you move too much, your semen will be released from your dick!
You'll release it! Pull it out! Now!
You released inside...
You released so much cum in my pussy...
We've only just started.
I expected as much.
Here!
It hurts when he moves so much.
He's gonna rip my pussy apart.
Inside again... this is not good.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Geez, don't feel good when you're getting raped.
Stupid body of mine!
They released inside me again...
Lots of hot semen.
Hey! Let me rest for a bit!
Wait... please...
No!
I can't take it anymore!
How many times do you guys have to release inside?
I don't want any kids.
You're like that already after only nine?
No way...
You're all sticky now.
Any one of us could've impregnated you already.
It hurts...
Why is this dick so big?
Your pussy is tightening in joy.
No way!
I don't want him to think I'm a lewd woman.
You're so stubborn!
You'll be a nice whore for us.
N-Not there...
Stop stirring around in my womb.
If you keep this up, I...
No... if you keep wriggling like that, I'll go crazy!
Amazing...
Something is coming.
Something amazing.
This sensation...
Does this mean I'm cumming?
I'm going to cum?
Even though I'm being raped?
I've never came before,
but now Vault's cock is raping me, and I...
No!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
He's releasing so much!
He's ejaculating inside me!
This is terrible.
I'm going to be pregnant.
I'm gonna have Vault's baby.
I love him.
When I was still a new recruit,
I screwed up, and I thought I was done for...
You weren't like this back then.
The person I fell in love with wasn't...
When I was still a new recruit,
I screwed up, and I thought I was done for...
I fell in love with him.
What's this?
It's a magic item.
Isn't it convenient?
You weren't like this back then.
Not bad.
So this is your true feeling.
The person I fell in love with wasn't...
Stop it!
No!
The person I fell in love...
Don't!
The person I...
N-No!
Love. Love. Love. Love.
Who would've thought Maia of all people was so affectionate!
You wanted to use her affection to crush her, right?
You're so evil, general!
D-Don't touch me!
This is a nightmare you'll never wake up from.
No!
You've turned me into a laughing stock.
Isn't that enough?
Not yet.
I'll rape you until you hit rock bottom.
You can't resist me.
I hate you!
You still love me, don't you?
You're the worst.
Good answer.
It's a tragedy of the woman who fell for the worst man ever!
He's doing something so awful knowing how I felt about him.
I resent him.
I hate him.
I absolutely hate him!
If only I can hate him from the bottom of my heart...
No!
Stop!
It's over.
Let your lust take over, Maia!
No!
I don't wanna cum, but I'm going to!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming and cumming, yet...
I'm still cumming!
His cock is filling me up with its milk inside me,
but I can't stop cumming!
Good for you, Maia.
You probably got pregnant from the beloved general!
Now, say it.
Say that you're our sex toy starting today.
I-I'm...
I'm the shared restroom for everyone.
I'm the pussy toilet for semen ejaculation.
No!
You inferior creatures are even lower than human!
How dare you mess up my castle!
Idiot! Scum!
Die! Die! Die!
You were defeated.
So I can do whatever I want to you.
Why?
I'm tiny compared to humans.
Sex empire is just absurd.
I thought we should give it a try.
Almost all Half-Links are born female,
but they're supposedly capable of mating with any race.
I've never seen one before.
Actually, it's impossible!
It won't go in!
No way!
S-Stop...
Seriously, stop!
I-It hurts.
It hurts so much!
Pull it out... pull it out!
This is what a loser looks like.
Do you get it now?
This is what happens to those who resist me in this land.
Looks like we can expect a healthy baby.
No!
I'll get pregnant!
Not inside!
No, no, no!
You managed to satisfy Tororo?
That's an impressive slut pussy.
Don't waste your energy on crying.
Don't...
It's so painful.
Why is this happening to me?
As expected of a Half-Link.
She's built to last.
Where did you find this thing?
I'll die! Seriously!
There's no way...
Stop...
Someone, hel-?
It doesn't hurt?
Not only that...
It's starting to feel inside,
even though it's so thick.
How?
My body is already fucked up.
I never knew huge cocks felt so good.
Humans can't please me like this.
Is this bliss?
Are you going to cum?
Are you going to release semen?
Come, fill me up inside with semen!
She's done.
My pussy is all messed up.
But this feels amazing.
Delightful.
Kuroinu: Kedakaki Seijo wa Hakudaku ni Somaru
My job is to pleasure cocks.
Give it to me.
Give me your cocks.
In my pussy hole.
Princess!
Princess Alicia!
I'm fucking Princess Alicia!
Princess, Princess!
Your dick feels so good!
Release inside me!
It feels so good in my mouth.
My mouth is so filthy.
My whole body feels so sensitive when someone kisses me.
My pussy is tightening up against the cock.
My pussy and mouth-pussy are cumming!
I'll endure this,
but Prim is still young.
I can't let this happen to her.
H-Here I come.
You dirty pigs!
I'll let your masochist cock that enjoys abuse to cum today.
How does it feel to be fucked by Princess Prim?
Release your sticky penis milk like a fountain while wrapped by sticky juice!
Come on!
I can do this just fine.
I don't want my sister to keep treating me like a child!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming now!
While getting semen released in my ass!
This ecstasy is unending!
Watch out for the shrine maiden.
Watch out for the asshole devoted to God.
So this is the shrine maiden from the Far East.
I've never seen one before.
That's a strange underwear.
Her ass is nice and round too!
I can't hold it anymore!
I'll open her right up!
A little piece of paper isn't going to stop me!
Huh?
What?
You cannot convert me, as my heart is devoted to God.
I've heard that shrine maidens in Far East has strange powers.
I see what they mean.
But how will you fare against them?
My lord...
My lord, please give me strength to endure this shame.
What's the matter?
Do you surrender?
Are you done with devoting yourself to this so-called God of yours?
A-Absolutely not...
My asshole for God is defiled,
and my purity was lost.
I'm no longer qualified to be a shrine maiden.
I thought only God could make me feel good,
yet these monsters are giving me pleasure.
Is it possible for anyone to make my body feel good?
Your body is honest.
No!
Please, let me go!
You're not a shrine maiden anymore.
You're just two fuck holes!
N-No!
My ass and pussy are gonna split open!
No!
If you keep this up...
Hot fluid is flowing into my ass and pussy...
A-Amazing.
It feels... so good!
T-This is not happening.
That's your true nature.
It means your holes are dirty holes that cum no matter who sticks it in.
You're no big deal.
You just didn't know the joy of being a woman.
Please forgive me, God.
It's been 5 years, Kaguya.
You were behind all this?
What?
Miss Kaguya?
Our shrine maiden!
I'm glad you're all safe.
I'm sorry you had to sacrifice yourself for us.
It's all right.
We shall endure whatever pain they inflict upon us.
With the pride of shrine maidens.
Yes.
Miss Kaguya?
What's the matter?
My asshole...
Is this what they were after?
It's so hot...
My whole body is throbbing.
I want someone to stir me up inside like crazy.
What am I thinking?
Someone, please hurry and give me...
I want it.
Someone, please stick a c-cock inside me!
Miss Kaguya?
You, over there.
Me?
Please stop...
Your dick is so hard!
It's so hot!
Your cock feels so good when it rubs against me!
I've never felt so good before!
Miss Kaguya...
Is this a nightmare?
What a dirty whore.
Shut up! This is...
What am I doing in front of everyone?
It's wrong, but I can't stop myself.
This feeling of becoming one with someone else...
A man's cock is so wonderful.
I've never felt so happy before.
Ah! Fuck me harder with your dick!
Mess up my pussy with your cock!
Did you like my cock that much?
Do you love my cock?
I love it.
I love cocks.
I can't get enough cocks!
So fuck me harder!
Stir me up inside!
P-Please...
More cocks...
Cocks...
I love cocks.
I love nothing more than cocks.
N-No...
My body belongs only to God.
I don't need any other cocks.
I don't need...
I don't need cocks.
Not cocks.
I don't need...
Cocks.
Cocks!
Cocks! Cocks! Cocks! Cocks!
She finally lost it.
Miss Kaguya...
Please stop.
I'm gonna...
I can't hold it!
R-Release it!
Release it!
Release lots of penis milk for me!
Semen... feels so good.
More.
Please release more here too!
Release more!
Release all your semen in my asshole!
How could this be happening?
Not only did I offer my asshole for God,
I even said something like that,
and I'm all excited...
Stop me.
Someone stop me!
What the hell?
I can't pull it out!
You're not getting away.
You'll release to the last drop.
Until you die.
How blasphemous?
A shrine maiden devoted to got seduced these filthy men,
and offered her holy buttock to them.
I have no more respect for you.
You are no longer qualified to lead us.
I have succumbed to lust.
H-How did this happen...
Along with aphrodisiac, I injected you with the egg of the insect.
Wh-What are you up to, Mi-
I abandoned that name.
A woman who devoted her body to God would make an ideal womb.
I abandoned the Far East and joined this army of mercenaries to obtain your body.
You'll give birth to the ultimate insect, and I shall...
surpass God!
No!
Nice to meet you, my cute baby.
Only two castles left.
All women in this land
will become products used to serve men.
Even if they were holy knights or reincarnation of goddesses!