Hey, hey!
Where are you inserting your dick?
Didn't you say you were going to rip open her virginity?
What's with her ass?
My Lord...
Volt, leader of mercenary group, Kuro Inu,
declared a nation-wide sex service law...
No choice but to finish this off, right?
There's no other option, right?
You all just have to fall down to my axe, right?
This is just an insane joke of yours, right Volt?
The advancement of their invasion
was already so deep that direct conflict was now inevitable.
Volt?
The Worm that Squiggle in their Soft Skin
The Sight of the Wild and bad beasts Chapter.
Kuro Inu
Dark Beast
~The Holy Women Tainted in White~
Kaguya X Ruru X Maia
Isn't this a bit too rough for a reunion?
It's been years.
You've grown into a fine woman.
Thanks, I guess.
I never thought that we'd become bitter enemies like this.
You've always been popular with the group's soldiers before.
Many have wanted to rape that body of yours.
Oh, what an honor.
Is that what you wanted me to say?
You're going to become the source of "comfort" for my soldiers.
Can you attend to them properly?
I think my insides are going to get rubbed till it hurts.
I've also prepared a small form of entertainment for you.
You might want to look forward to it.
Eh?
Do you remember me?
I do.
Not just you, but everyone as well.
You constantly showed off that curvy body of yours,
I always loved looking at it.
Oh wow, Maia has her pussy completely exposed.
She's got great tits too.
Quite a nice color you have there.
It's been a long time since I last had one, so it feels a bit tight.
She tastes a lot better than I thought!
I'm being raped, right?
By my former comrade, and in front of all of them.
For my pussy to be just used like this by this man...
Is that a sweet voice you just let out?
Shut up.
Though, I don't think I can hold long if it's this tight.
I'm going to cum soon.
Eh? Cum...?
Just hold on right there!
Why are you acting all innocent and pure, Maia?
You can't cum inside my pussy...
Wait...!
You're going to cum inside?
If you keep moving like that,
your dick will let out all the sperm inside...
It's going to come out...
It's going to come out!
Pull your dick out!
I said pull it out!
You moron...
Cumming inside like that...
Letting out all your cum inside my pussy like that...
We're just getting started.
Well that's surpris-
There!
Wait, It's going to hurt if he pushes so intensely like that.
My pussy is going to break.
Inside again...?
This is getting really bad now.
It's starting to feel less painful...
Damn, I mustn't get aroused while being raped.
My stupid body...
H-He came inside again.
There's lots of cum inside me already.
Let me rest for a little bit.
Wait, I beg of you please!
No!
I can't continue anymore!
Just how much do you guys plan on cumming inside me?
I'm the one getting worried about becoming pregnant here.
Giving up already after taking on just nine guys?
He can't be...
It's all wet and sticky.
It wouldn't be surprising if you were
impregnated by one of these men.
It hurts...
Why is this dick so... huge?
Your pussy seems to be wrapping around me happily.
No way...
I don't want to be thought of as a pervert
especially not by this guy.
Still acting tough, eh?
You're going to become a fine prostitute.
Wait.. Not there...
His dick is rubbing up to my womb!
I-If this continues, I'll...
Oh no...
I'll go crazy if you twist and turn like that.
Oh wow...
Something is coming...
Something big is coming...!
This feeling...
Could it be that I'm about to cum?
Am I really going to cum?
Am I going to cum, while being raped?
I've yet to experience it,
and yet I'm going to cum from being raped by Volt.
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm cumming,
I'm really cumming.
I'm really cumming!
I'm cumming while he’s cumming inside of me!
W-What should I do?
I'm going to become pregnant,
with Volt's child.
I love you.
When I was still a novice,
I messed up once, and thought I was about to die.
But you weren't this kind of man, were you?
You, whom I've grown to love...
When I was still a novice,
I messed up once, and thought I was about to die.
But I love him.
What's this?
It's a magical item.
Quite convenient, isn't it?
You weren't this kind of man, were you?
Not bad.
Is this what's truly on your mind?
You, whom I've grown to love...
Stop this.
Stop!
You, whom I've grown to love...
Stop it already!
You, whom I've...
N-No!
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you...
No.
No!
Man, I never thought that Miss Maia here
was really that pure and innocent.
And our leader here just used it to bring her down to her knees.
Our captain sure is nasty.
Don't touch me!
This is reality, one that you'll never wake up from.
No!
Y-You've already made fun of me...
You've had enough already, right?
Not yet.
I'm going to violate you until you go straight down.
You cannot defy me.
I-I hate you!
You still love me, right?
You're the worst!
That's nice to hear!
This is the tragedy of a woman who fell
in love with the worst man possible!
He just tossed my feelings aside,
and keeps on doing this terrible thing...
I abhor you.
I hate you.
I absolutely hate you!
I hate this, I hate this, I hate this, I hate this...
I hate this...
I hate this,
because whenever I try to look deep within myself,
I'm absolutely...
No! Not that!
Time to finish this.
Cum all you want, Maia!
No, no!
I don't want to cum, and yet...!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming.
I'm coming!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm still cumming!
I can't stop cumiming while he's cumming inside me!
Ain't that great, Maia?
The captain whom you love, you're
now pregnant with his child, right?
Now, admit it.
That you're our property from now on.
I-I'm...
I'm...
I'm everyone's sex tool.
A sex tool meant for pouring cum into.
No!
You filthy...!
You're all just inferior mutts!
How dare you totally mess up my own fortress!
Idiot! Trash!
Die, die, die!
You lost.
Which is why I will deal with you exactly as I want.
What's with that?
I'm small compared to other humans.
Punishing me like this is like...
I'd like to test something.
Halflings are known to bear only female offsprings.
And they're able to cross breed with other species well.
I-It's my first time seeing this...
Anyway,
You can't, you just can't!
It won't fit!
I said it won't fit!
S-Stop, I mean it.
Stop it...
It hurts...
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts...
Remove it,
remove it I said!
Such is the fate of the loser!
Understood?
This is what happens when you try to defy me!
Seems like you're going to give birth to a healthy child.
No!
I'm about to be bear someone else's child!
No, no, no!
You've just satisfied Tororo here.
That's some strong beastly pussy you've got there.
Is that how you'll use your strength in this situation?
Stop...
I-I can't breathe.
Why do I have to experience this?
As expected of a halfling.
You're quite strong.
Where did you get this guy?
I'm going to die.
I'm going to die!
That definitely won't fit!
No...
Someone, save...
It doesn't hurt?
Moreover...
It somehow feels good...
Even though it's already something this big.
Why?
My body...
It's gone crazy.
I never knew very big dicks like these
could feel this great inside me.
You won't be able to taste something like this in a human.
I somehow feel very happy.
Ah, are you about to cum?
Are you going to let it out already?
Cum.
Cum lots inside me!
It's completed.
Every bit of me has gone crazy now.
But, I still can't get enough of this.
This is the best.
Kuro Inu - The High Holy Women Tainted in White.
My job is... to service your cocks.
Now, come to me,
with your cocks.
Put them inside my pussy.
Princess!
Princess Alicia!
It's really her!
Princess!
Princess! Princess!
These cocks feel great!
Let it all out.
Pour it all inside me!
My mouth feels good.
How obscene my mouth is.
As they violate me,
my entire body becomes sensitive.
My pussy is gripping these cocks tight.
I'm cumming,
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
With my mouth, and with my pussy...
I’m cumming!
I shall endure it.
Because Prim is still too young.
I can't let her do this.
Well, then, here I go.
You perverted pig!
That masochist dick of yours that gets
more aroused the more it's punished,
I'm going to especially make you cum my way.
That thick, stinky, and almost yellowish cum
milk that I'm trying to squeeze out.
Release it out like a water fountain!
Come on!
So l can do it after all.
I don't want Onee-sama to treat me like a child anymore.
I'm coming!
I am cumming! I am cumming!
And I'm being cummed inside my ass too!
And I can't stop it!
Be careful with that shrine maiden.
Her ass, is something that was offered to the gods.
So this is what a shrine maiden from the East looks like.
It's the first time I've seen one.
That's quite a strange body.
Her butt also looks very tender.
I can't get enough of this!
I'm going to pierce you through!
I'm going to do it in one thrus-
Huh?
You are incapable of taking away the heart that I gave to the gods.
I heard that the Eastern Shrine Maiden
had mysterious powers, but..
I see.
But how about these guys?
My Lord...
My Lord,
please give me the strength to muster this taint.
What's wrong?
Giving up already?
Seems the days of your servitude to your god are now over.
T-That's not true.
My ass, which was offered to the gods
and my purity were taken from me.
I no longer have the right to be a shrine maiden.
Until now,
I thought that it was only god who could perfectly stimulate me.
For me to feel aroused with these monsters...
But could it be that everyone experiences this normally?
Your body does not lie.
No!
Please...
Please let me be already!
You're no longer a shrine maiden.
You're just a meat hole now.
No, no!
My ass, my part down there, is getting ripped apart.
No!
If you continue that...
My ass and my pussy are now bathed in searing heat.
A-Amazing...
I-It feels... It feels good.
T-This is...
This can't be.
That shows who the real you is.
Which means that your hole,
is nothing but a lewd hole that would make
you easily cum when pierced enough.
Unimpressive.
This is what happens to someone who never knew
about the pleasures of being a woman.
My lord, please forgive me...
It's been five years, Kaguya.
So this was all your plan.
What are you...?
Kaguya-sama!
Head shrine maiden!
You are all safe.
My deepest apologies!
For our sake, you...
It is alright.
Let us endure whatever tribulations that may lay ahead.
Hold onto your pride as a shrine maiden.
Ok.
Kaguya-sama?
Is there something wrong?
M-My ass...
S-So this is what they want?
It feels hot.
My body's starting to feel all tingly.
I want to be stirred up.
I want something to penetrate it straight though.
W-What am I thinking?
S-Somebody, hurry...
Get that thing...
I want it.
Somebody, please put your dick inside me.
Kaguya-sama?!
You there.
M-Me?
Please stop...
His cock is hard!
It feels really hot.
It feels good to have it rubbed inside me.
It's the first time I've felt this good.
Kaguya-sama...
Am I in some nightmare?
What a slutty bitch.
Silence!
This is...
What am I doing in front of everyone?
It is something I should never do,
but I just can't control myself.
This sensation of being one with someone...
Men's dicks are wonderful.
I never felt so happy in my entire life.
Do it more.
Thrust your dick into me!
Mess up my pussy more!
You really like it that much?
Do you like my dick?
I love it.
I love dicks.
I can't help but love them!
Thrust it inside more.
Stir it inside more.
P-Please, more.
Give me more of your dick!
Dicks...
I love dicks.
I really love dicks.
I love them.
N-No, that's not true!
My body exists to serve my Lord.
Anything other than my Lord's dick is...!
These dicks...
I don't need...
Dicks, dicks.
Dicks!
Dicks, dicks, dicks, dicks!
She's totally lost it, huh?
Kaguya-sama...
Stop this already.
I'm... I'm about to cum!
It's coming out!
Let it out!
Let it out, let it out, let it out!
Pour lots of your cum milk inside me!
Cum... Cum feels great.
I want you to cum more in here.
More, just cum some more!
Release all of your cum inside my ass!
How terrible.
This is something that I offered to the gods.
I even told them to put it in, and was aroused by it.
Someone, stop this.
Somebody stop me!
What is this, I can't pull it out!
I won't let you go.
You’re going to have to let out every last drop.
Until you die, okay?
What a terrible thing this is.
A shrine maiden who has dedicated herself to the gods,
seduced these men into making love with her,
and even allowed them into her ass.
This is a scornful act.
You no longer have the right be our leader.
I wasn't able to stop it.
My carnal desires...
W-What is this?
I injected into your ass,
the egg of an insect.
W-What are you planning to do Mi-
That is a name I no longer use.
That body, which was chosen by the gods,
will be the perfect breeding vessel.
In order to claim you as my own,
I left the Eastern Lands,
and entered as a mercenary here.
You are going to give birth to the best insects.
And then,
I shall overcome the gods!
Hello there, my cute offspring.
There are only two fortresses remaining.
All of the women here,
will become prostitutes to serve men.
Regardless of whether they're blessed knights,
or even a reincarnation of a goddess.