No... why?!
Why did it become like this?
My student's virgin pussy is really something.
Today's activity will be all about penetration.
I-It hurts!
This thick thing is drilling my insides!
I never thought that my first time would be taken away,
by a terrible teacher such as you.
It feels so dirty and humiliating.
I don't intend to stop, though.
Th-Then do whatever you want to.
In exchange,
you'll have to do what you promised!
Sensei!
Hey... oh, it's you, Nomiya.
Jeez, nobody's around, so you can
just call me Nanako, you know.
As your tutor, I'm also considered your teacher here.
So just give up on that.
Stop, stop, stop!
Whew, that's a male teacher for you.
I already pushed with all my strength,
but you didn't even flinch at all.
Narukawa-san.
I appreciate the sentiment,
but I hope you're not forgetting the school's rules and policies.
Understood?
I understand!
Sorry for causing trouble.
The principal sure is scary.
Suddenly pushing me like that, you're the scary one, you know.
I'm not doing it with just anyone.
Anyway, I have something to ask you.
Already?
Well, I'll just talk about it later.
She looks like she's always in a hurry.
Your big dick is the best.
I'm very happy that,
you've given my lewd pussy the chance to be fucked.
Please forgive me for earlier.
I needed to...
...act strict in front of everyone.
No excuses.
I'll just enjoy myself in the same manner.
I wanted to make you happy, Master.
So I prepared this school.
We've eliminated all unstable variables, anyway.
I'll do whatever I want from this point on.
I'm happy.
Please enjoy yourself as you see fit.
You definitely...
Must...!
Don't worry.
I'm a guy, so I can instantly deter anyone
who tries to snoop around.
Sensei, I have a request!
Our advisor's out with the flu.
I want you to stand in for a while.
It's already the season.
Please?
I guess it can't be helped if your advisor isn't around.
but it's not particularly my specialty.
So I can only manage very simple stuff.
It's okay, it's okay!
If it's you, of course.
It's sensei.
I wonder what he's up to?
Nanako!
Don't overexert yourself.
You're our ace after all.
Sensei, please watch over her overtime training,
so that she doesn't exhaust herself, okay?
Hey, what are you trying to say?
See you later, Mahiru.
Thank you for today, sensei.
I'm glad that you accepted the job for me.
Looking at it again now, I realized
you have such a nice constitution.
Which explains a lot about why you were chosen and
accepted for the school's scholarship program.
Sensei, I know you're trying to compliment me,
but that just reeks of sexual harassment, you know.
Oh, sorry.
I just said what was on my mind.
I know that you didn't mean anything weird.
She's as my data says.
Sensei, you really are amazing.
The way you guided us earlier was totally spot on.
Really?
I'm not really aware of it myself, though.
Well, I'm under scholarship,
so I have to give them results.
Besides, I think we can go quite far this time.
Oh, what's the matter?
Sensei?
This may be unfortunate for you, and your efforts,
but can you calmly listen to what I have to say?
A-Alright.
To tell you the truth,
if things go on like this, our school might not be able
to participate in the regionals because of you.
Word got out, you see.
There are rumors that you, Narukawa Mahiru
are involved in some kind of obscene activity.
Wha... huh?
Becuase of me...?
Obscene activity?
Huh?!
For the club involved with the student in question,
not only would that person be affected,
but all of its members would also held responsible.
Just wait!
I'm not involved in those kinds of things!
How terrible.
Why did those rumors...
It is indeed a terrible lie.
Sensei, you do believe in me, right?
Yeah, it's still a rumor for now.
Huh, sensei? What are you...?
What's wrong?
But it might become truth after a short while.
Wh-What are you trying to do?
It hurts!
I can't accept this even if its a joke!
Hey, let go!
I said let me go!
Moving your fleshy butt like that...
Are you trying to seduce me?
Stop joking around!
You're acting very weird!
You about-to-be-molester teacher!
Pervert!
No, don't look!
Stop hiding it!
Threatening a girl in a loud voice... you're the worst.
This is really one fine ass.
Makes me want to fuck it right away.
That's just creepy.
You demon! Beast!
Pervert!
Let me go!
Don't resist too much now.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
I said I don't like this, stop!
What a great view.
I already said it hurts.
Stop being violent with me!
You really are the worst, you trash!
And you're about to give up your virginity to that same trash.
Just who in their right mind would
give up their virginity to you?!
Let me go, let me go already!
Do you want me to hit you some more?
Well, if you don't want your virginity,
then I'll just have to help myself over here.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
No, not there...
No, don't, it hurts...
It feels gross.
No way, no, what are you going to do?
That won't fit!
No...
Looks like it's opening up a bit after loosening it earlier.
No, don't push it in my ass, it hurts...!
This is gross.
I said it won't fit!
Stop! It won't go in any further,
and it'll rip my ass apart if you do!
That felt really great.
This is simply the best ass I could have.
No way, it can't go in any further, please...
No way...
No...
Not my breasts... don't look...
And my ass, too...
What? My ass' insides are...
They feel all tingly.
Oh, so you can feel it.
That you have potential as my anal sex slave.
I don't understand any of that.
Please, stop already...
Just let me enjoy this great sensation, okay?
This is getting weird... stop...
It hurts so much I think I'm going to die.
You're a lot more compatible for sex than I originally thought.
It's coming out...
Pumping inside me.
It's flowing completely inside!
Could this be...
This is really weird...
And it feels gross.
You really do have a nice constitution.
I shall take your first time in here as well.
Eh, eh?!
Hey, what are you doing?
You said you wouldn't take my virginity!
Fucking your ass was just a separate round.
My first time... Why...?
It hurts, you know.
Pull It out.
Please stop this already.
Good. Your insides are trying to squeeze me even more.
I want you to cry and scream more, Mahiru!
No...
It hurts...
Stop pushing inside.
No, no!
My insides are getting torn apart.
It hurts!
Stop this, please!
I don't want this anymore.
I'm about to.
Because I'll be finishing this with a good load of cum in you.
But, I'll get pregnant!
No, you definitely mustn't!
Please don't cum inside me!
It's no use,
You'll be taking It all.
No!!
Oh no, you really came inside me!
No, no, no!
It's seeping inside me.
I'm going to get pregnant.
I don't want to be pregnant.
No...
Your cum is building up inside.
It's filling me deep inside.
No way...
Senpai and sensei are...
Why did he rape her?
Sensei...
She didn't come for morning practice, huh.
No, it'll get really full if you cum any further!
Please stop this already.
My ass again...
No, not my ass, don't keep fucking my ass!
Please let me be!
What should I do?
I can't just tell this to anyone.
Was that Nanako?
You...! Die!
Hey, what are you dodging my attack for?
Do you understand where you're standing?
I do.
I got raped, and never got to the competition.
don't have anything to show to everyone,
and I though you were a nice teacher...
Did you tell anyone about what happened yesterday?
Of course I can't do that!
And what about not getting into the competition?
That's because yesterday you...
I don't have any intentions of letting anyone know about it,
so-you shouldn't have any problems in participating.
Th-Then, I can join the competition?
Wh-Whew.
See? I'm still the good teacher that you always knew.
Y-Yeah.
Wait! You still did something terrible
to me, so that's not true anymore!
Hmph.
Is your ass alright?
It'll get worse if you don't treat it soon,
so use the medicine properly.
And just who made it that way, huh?!
I'll let everyone know if you keep acting like this.
I get it already.
Stupid, idiot!
Pervert, demon!
Hey...!
You again...
You...!
You never seem to learn.
Are sure you're going to be okay in the competition?
I hate not being able to participate,
but I'll never forgive you for this!
You...!
Hey, not again?!
You demon... devil!
I said stop!
Wait, you idiot!
We're just getting started.
The fun that is.
S-Stop!
It hurts, no, don't! It hurts!
It hurts!
It'll get really wet soon enough.
This body is slutty anyway.
That's not true!
Please don't...
Don't move it, don't!
Do you really hate it?
Of course!
Anything feels gross if you're the one doing it.
My ass again...?
Stop it already!
Stupid!
I said I don't want it!
You insides feel really good with it.
Shut up!
Don't you ever say that to me!
I'm not going to feel the least bit good with any of this!
Stupid!
Then ask your body then.
Stop...
It wont go any deeper.
What's this? My body's...
Can you feel it?
With all of these slutty juices of yours,
the club just easily slid inside.
Don't say such weird things.
Stop this! Pull it out already!
You can't do this...
Stop!
You pervert!
I'm looking forward to your sloppy expression.
Stop joking around!
I won't ever do that!
Again? This can't be!
Stop! Don't cum!
Stop! Hey, I said stop!
No. no...
It's pouring out!
It's pumping inside me again!
I already said that you can't!
Darn, you came inside again.
He's really such a...
Ms. Principal!
Th-This is...
You'll catch a Cold if you stay like that.
Hurry up and change.
Ms. Principal...
I'm...
Actually, Orihara-sensei just...
He did lots of things to me.
My oh my, so you were that happy about it.
Having sensei take real good care of you like that.
Eh?
That makes me quite jealous.
When I was still a student, he basically
treated me like a sex slave.
Huh... Ms. Principal?
Then this is...
I've already told you many times.
Looks like you need to be punished for quite a while.
I already learned about this thing from a friend,
but this isn't something that you insert in somebody's ass!
Narukawa.
This is enough already, right?
I don't know. I can't even think clearly!
What a nice expression.
In this situation...
and it's even exposed!
Your love juices are overflowing.
Why?
Why is my body getting really aroused with this?
Is your body starting to feel weak due to pleasure?
Of course not!
Oh no, I'm going to pee!
At your limit already?
Is it alright for you not to participate?
I won't let that happen!
You endured it well.
Take it off in the restroom.
I did it!
Eh? W-Wait...
Don't! Stop looking!
Oh, it's coming out rather vigorously.
The smell also isn't that strong, looks
like you're quite healthy there.
No, stop, stop!
Oh, please, no, why are you even here?
You're too noisy!
I'm going to have that mouth shut itself up.
What are you going to do?
Are going to try to cover my mouth and suffocate me?
Hey now, who do you think I am?
A pervert, right?
A demon, right?
You're the devil, right?!
H-Hey!
Classes are about to start.
What are you thinking, you pervert!
You just lost your virginity to some 'affair' that happened
during afterschool club activity hours.
So what are you trying to say?
That's definitely not true!
I was forced to do it!
Completely forced,
right in front of my eyes,
by some pervert!
Your tongue is as sharp as always.
Though, that's what makes you attractive.
Suck it.
I get it already.
You'll just try to expose it if I don't anyway.
Good girl.
Hurry up.
You're still too early to do tease plays.
I know, I know!
Hey, stop that!
This feels gross.
No, it's quite dirty.
It's the very thing that made you into a woman,
So that's just rude.
You pleasure the dick by rubbing it with your mouth like this,
as if it's a pussy.
I'm going to add more penalties if you try to spill it.
I can't breathe.
Next ,Narukawa.
Come on now.
No way.
No, no!
Sense, please stop this!
It's okay, even in the case that you do spill it.
That drug is quite potent, you know.
Oh no, oh no, I really can't do this!
Ow, ow!
What's wrong, Mahiru?
Letting out a weird voice like that.
Is something wrong?
I'm alright.
I-I'm sorry.
I think I just hit myself a bit down there.
Oh no, I can't hold it in much longer.
He's just going to watch me like this?
He really wants me to take a dump here?
For real?
I definitely can't take a dump in front of everyone!
But, I just can't hold this thing in.
Mahiru, are you alright?
No, no, I really mustn't!
Yeahf wait a sec, I'm just going to go dow-
I mustn't and yet...
And yet, I'm about to...
I'm about to take a dump...
No!!
It's all over.
Everyone will now think I'm a pervert,
all the while being laughed at by him.
Hey, Mahiru, what's really wrong?
Hey!
Huh?
They haven't noticed yet?
Is it because of the diaper?
Mommy....!
Looks like she doesn't feel well.
I'm going to take her to the infirmary
so just continue the lesson from here.
That was really entertaining.
I'm very sorry...
Forgive me already.
You released quite a lot, so I think it's quite clean now.
It's in my ass again.
Stop...
Stop!
Stop rubbing it inside me.
Let my ass be already!
I don't want any of this anymore!
Even though your ass is trying to
suck and squeeze me in deeper?
That's not true!
I don't want it in my ass!
Don't...!
Your ass says otherwise, though.
What are you doing?
My ass now feels all tingly!
Don't push it in upwards!
But it feels good at this point, right, Mahiru?
No, I'm not... It doesn't feel good for me at all...!
I'm...!
It doesn't feel good...
... with a pervert...!
My asshole is...!
And my body is already feeling this...
What in the world is this?
I don't want it in my ass, and yet...
But you still keep on fucking me there.
You're going to cum shortly afterward.
And it's your first time cumming with your ass.
Stop!
Oh no, I'm starting to...!
I'm scared... no...!
Just cum all the way.
Savor the taste of your orgasm as your ass gets fucked.
I don't understand.
I can't stop twitching.
My head is starting to lose it.
Your first orgasm is during anal sex?
How perverted of you, Mahiru.
But, we're not done yet.
Now it's my pussy that's getting rubbed.
No, if that dick goes deep in me again...
I don't know what will happen next!
Looks like it's going to be a two-combo
ass pussy cumming session.
I'm going to start feeling strange all over again.
Stop... not your dick, please...
And stop playing with my ass, too...!
Show me how a pervert cums!
No... not in my ass and pussy!
He's cumming inside me again!
I'm going crazy as this pervert cums in me!