Damn you!
Is it not enough that you escaped?
Will you betray us too?
What are you doing to me?
How shameless can you be?!
Do you think I will forgive this treatment?
You are the real pigs here!
Degenerates!
Die!
Die, everyone!
Oh, please.
You seem just fine to me.
It seems you've gotten really good at deriding others.
You really don't seem to understand your own position, though.
You know, they've always wanted to rape you.
Thanks for fulfilling their wish in a moment.
All right now, enjoy yourselves!
She's your reward!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's not for you to decide that—
Let me go!
I'll remind you how different we are from humans.
Stop! Stop!
Black Dog
The Noble Holy Saint Is Smeared in the Seed of the Loin
Olga, Kuroe and the Black Fort, Collapse Chapter
This world consists of one giant continent:
The continent Austia.
In the outlands of the north live grotesque creatures,
and ever since they first lived on this continent,
they have been creatures of evil that all other life hates.
These monsters have endangered their lives,
defiled their bodies, taken their livestock,
and rejoiced in it.
However, the century-long battle is changing.
Some hundreds of years ago, at the border of the outlands,
a powerful fortress called the Black Fort was erected in a flash.
In the periphery of the fortress, the once fertile land
was turned to a wasteland by powerful black magic overnight.
There is no day nor night in their land,
and the sky always looks like it is drenched in blood.
The atmosphere is filled with marsh gas,
and the land is so barren no plant will grow in it.
All fresh water has turned into poisonous, murky swamps.
There is a rumor that a single, beautiful dark elf,
rules in the fortress erected in this desolate land.
Because of her, this land came to be called "the land of the black queen".
Stop it!
How dare you humiliate me like this?
What are you doing?
Don't look!
Stop it!
Just let me go!
Now then, ogres, do it.
Stop it!
Do you really want to put that fat thing in?
It's too fat.
It's so fat in there.
I can't breathe.
M— My queen...
Stand up.
Get out.
They can do whatever they want to me.
I'm nothing more than a slave...
My mouth...
The ogre's dirty penis... fills me up.
My mind is going blank.
He's going to come!
I can feel it!
Why?
Don't!
Don't come!
Don't come inside me!
Not inside!
Don't!
I'm going to break!
No!
Don't!
If he comes, I will...
I will...
If he comes inside, I will...
I can't take it.
I'm coming!
Just don't come!
Please forgive me, my queen.
Forgive me...
My head is spinning...
They're coming!
It's inside me...
They are coming inside my pussy...
The semen sliding down my throat...
It's delicious.
I can't have enough of it.
The black magic of the queen gave all the evil beings that visited her kingdom vast power.
The monsters took advantage of their power and attacked.
A call went out through the land to unite against them.
The ones they attacked elected to enter an alliance with them,
and built seven fortresses in the marches.
There was a reason they rushed it.
The high elves saw their goddess reborn.
The high elf girl that she reincarnated into, pronounced holy by the church,
predicted the fortress and the coming crisis sooner than anyone.
Answering to the call of the elves, warriors from every nation assembled.
With the full support of the church behind them, they quickly forged an alliance.
The seven countries backing them quickly followed into their alliance.
In the long battle that followed, mercenaries were used in gradually growing number.
They were simple crooks who lived by the day with the money they received and only looked for enjoyment.
However, the mercenaries that used to be no more than disorderly gangs
were united and organized under the leadership of a certain man.
His name was Bolt.
Bolt, my master...
Can I get my own reward?
Didn't you hear what my aide said?
We have brought her to be raped as you requested.
No. I want more.
I want more cum.
It seems I am no longer welcome elsewhere.
There's something I've been dying to know.
I wonder if a dark elf can get pregnant from a human.
I would never submit to a rotten bunch of stupid worms like you.
I'm taking this back.
What am I reading?!
Alicia, my sister...
I'm sorry I got angry, Prim.
But... I can never forgive this!
Now then, that was a huge failure, wasn't it, Queen?
This is my last defense.
You...
It looks like a spell of sorts.
I see.
It must be a spell against pregnancy.
I cast an inviolable, holy barrier on my body.
I won't let you do as you please.
Very well.
I will have fun breaking that spell!
Get it on, boys!
The girl we captured is hot as fuck and a virgin!
Get the dark elf queen!
Nice dressup.
You might be a queen,
but this gets them excited nicely.
Man, I can't stop.
I might come any second.
Is she trembling?
I thought the dark elf queen was a slut.
What with the spell earlier, do you think this'll work out?
Then we just have to try and find out.
Now then!
I want to start sucking on it so nice it smells.
I can't stop!
Captain!
Please check out if she's still a virgin!
Let's see...
They can't see it...
Humans should never see it...
My power is waning...
At this rate...
She looks like a perfect virgin down here.
This makes me laugh.
Let's get going then.
Prepare yourself, Queen.
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm up in your womb.
Now matter how my body is defiled,
as long as I have my last spell,
your sperm will not reach my uterus.
Captain, can we do her too?
Can we suck her tits?
Whatever floats your boat!
Do it!
This is boring.
I want more.
Look here!
Don't!
That thing is dirty!
You're making a whore out of me.
I won't let you do this!
I won't!
What's that?
Calm down, Lady.
You don't look like you hate it.
Don't the women all like to be violated?
Put some more effort into this, guys!
Don't just tease her, do some real shit!
Grab her brown skin!
You guys too!
Don't hold back!
Do whatever you want!
The Queen's pussy is so great!
Hurry up!
Don't rush me!
Wait for your turn!
She's sucking good.
Now, don't get greedy.
All right! My turn!
Make way!
No rush!
She's not going to vanish.
Top, down, anything!
Do it!
That's our Captain right there.
Now me.
How long will this continue?
How long will they keep up this cruel game?
You seem to've liked it in the end, Queen.
Now matter how often you do this to me, I will be proud.
I wonder how much longer you'll say that.
That's the Queen for you!
Although she just had her hymen broken, she's welcoming my cock already.
Stop joking.
I'd never be like that.
That's the last of your confidence.
The preparations are complete.
Now then, let's shoot for real.
Don't! Don't come inside!
My womb should never receive the seed of tainted beings like you!
Well that's a shame.
I will put all I can into such a splendid womb!
You are worthless!
I can't endure this!
You better appreciate this!
I will make sure you get every last drop with both your holes!
Don't!
Don't bite, now.
Why am I being violated here?
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Take my seed!
Come, you guys!
Stop! Stop!
They're coming...
He's filling my womb with his dirty seed.
I think I came ten times alone!