No! Please, stop! Why are you doing this?
Because I wanna fuck you.
What's that supposed to mean?
No, please don't! I'll never forgive you!
No!
Well, there goes your virginity.
Now you're a woman, ojou-sama.
No! Why?!
Your pussy and tits are in a league of their own.
Yup, that's a Kusonoki family's lady. High quality, all around.
I will never forgive you! Never!
I'll turn you into a woman who can't live without my cock.
I've been seeing nothing but nightmares
since that guy violated me.
Will I really be able to endure this?
But if I use this, I'll...
Was I lied to? There are students who get
better grades from his tutoring, though.
I don't know what to think.
My grades really improved after
he pointed out what I was doing wrong!
I'm usually not good with guys,
but he was so nice and charming that we got along.
He's completely different behind that mask,
though. Even so, he's only human.
If I just keep enduring it...
Hey, Kusonoki-san?
Yes?
Why do I need to stay behind in my swimsuit?
What do you want from me?
You know what I want.
Have you forgotten what you said?
Your tits look bigger when you're wearing that.
The boys probably want to nail them.
My breasts aren't for those perverted purposes.
You're being disgusting! Don't look at me!
Your pussy's one thing, but your tits and asshole
are all so erotic. It's impossible not to look.
I'll teach those cow tits of yours some new tricks.
C-Cow? That's so mean...
So this is how big they are? Very nice.
What are you doing?! Leave them alone!
If you want sex, just do that instead!
This is a tit fuck.
You're still as resistant as before, huh?
That's because you were playing with it nonstop, so...
That just means I have to play with these a bit more then.
No! Don't rub that against me!
This is what turned you into a woman. Don't be so rude.
Well, if you won t do this, then I guess
I can ask you to do something else.
I won't let you do that!
That's the spirit. If you use your mouth,
you'll make me cum faster.
Huh? My mouth?
He wants me to put this disgusting
thing in my mouth? How?!
This is how you do it.
He's making me go this far?!
Stop!
Don't you want me to hurry up and cum?
He's enjoying this, isn't he?
He's not a human being!
You're scum! Making me do this, against my will!
That's right, I'm the scum you gave your body to.
No! It's getting harder! No, don't squeeze my breasts!
No! Please, stop!
I don't want you to use my breasts anymore! No!
Please, stop, I beg you! At this rate, I'll...
What's this?
This fisnt semen, is it? Breast milk?
No! No, it's not! It's not breast milk!
Well, you were a virgin just a few days ago.
Well then...
No! You want to violate me in this position again?!
Of course. We're gonna keep going until I'm satisfied.
It hurts! Sense's dick is going inside me again!
Yeah, it feels good. I'm gonna have tons of fun with this.
I'm being raped again!
Your dick is rampaging around
inside of me... my insides hurt!
No!
Please, stop! You can have sex with me,
but don't touch my breasts!
I need to check if that was actually breast milk or not.
It wasn't breast milk! I'm not pregnant,
so there's no way it was breast milk!
Good point.
No! If he keeps doing this, my breasts are gonna...
You're really wet. It must feel really good for you.
No, it doesn't! You're doing horrible things to me, so...
You get turned on when I do horrible things to you?
Weird taste, for a rich girl.
No, that's not what I meant! I...
Your dirty tits feel like they'll burst.
Is something going to come out soon?
Please, stop! Even if you squeeze them that hard,
nothing will come out of them!
You're rubbing my pussy so hard,
I... You can't keep doing that!
I can't hold it back anymore!
It's coming out! It's gonna come out!
It came out! My breast milk's coming out!
You're squeezing it out of my breasts!
Don't look! Stop!
Why is this happening? No!
No! I didn't want to let it out!
I didn't want to let anyone know about this!
Tell me, why is breast milk coming out?
There's no reason to hide it anymore.
For a wgile now, every time my breasts
get too stimulated, breast milk comes out.
Sometimes I'd have to go to the bathroom
to let some out because it gets painful.
I didn't want anyone to know that my body does this!
That's why I told you not to touch them!
Why? Why is it getting even bigger inside of me?
Well, now that we know,
how about you focus on making me feel good?
No, don't! Right now I... You can't right now!
If you're that sensitive after letting it out,
that means you can feel even better.
It's going deep inside me again!
It's like your hard thing is digging inside of me!
You know what you need to do to satisfy me, right?
No, you don't mean... You can't cum inside! You can't!
Sorry, I'm going to.
No, please, I beg you! Don't do it!
Stop going so deep inside me!
You can say you hate it as much as you want,
but your body is being honest.
No, that's not true! This doesn't fedl good!
I'm not getting turned on at all!
No! Please take it out! If you cum inside me, I...
No, stop cumming! Stop!
Stop shooting your cum inside me!
It's going inside me! Your semen is flowing into me! No!
It's filling me up! My insides are full of cum!
I didn't want anyone to know
about my breasts... You're too cruel!
Well, now that your secret's out,
I'm going to help you squeeze out all of that milk.
N-No, please don't!
This is my only option. Sensei isn't human, he's a beast!
With this, I'll...
Gym Teacher's Office
Well? What is it? You had something
you wanted to talk to me about, right?
Yes, that's right. I have something I need your advice on.
I understand why you're scared,
but you should calm down a little.
How about something to drink?
I-I'll prepare it. You can just sit down, sensei.
This is a very underhanded trick,
but for a beast like him...
In twenty minutes, she should be here.
Sorry for the wait.
Excuse me.
Headmistress?
Why is she here already?
Is the talk you wanted to have
about your relationship with him?
Y-Yes! About that... Um...
I know you're in front of the headmaster,
but you should calm down.
O-Okay.
Kusonoki-san, something's bothering you, bright?
You can talk to me about anything.
Y-Yes, so...
Um, that is... huh? My breasts are...
It's already starting to work? That was quick.
Effect?
The drug you put in my drink.
Kuosonoki-san, you mustn't be putting
strange drugs into my master's drink.
You wanted me to assault you while under
the drug's effect so Sayaka could walk in on it?
That's good thinking, for a rich girl.
Up until you asked Sayaka, that is.
I'll have to re-teach you a lesson I think you've forgotten.
Health
Education
If anyone sees me like this during class,
my secret will get out!
My breasts are super sensitive due to the drug.
I want to squeeze them. I want to masturbate!
No, that's not true!
However you try to twist it,
that's obviously masturbation.
You feel good when you squeeze
the milk out from your tits.
I never thought it was masturbation.
To think I've been doing somethin like that...
If this keeps up, my breasts will...
If you even try to touch yourself,
I'll let everyone know how perverted you are.
That is known as the REM phase of sleep.
We'll have a quiz on this,
so try to note this down in ten minutes.
He told me not to touch them,
but now he's touching them?!
What was I just trying to do?
Was I really trying to let him touch me?
I know this is bad, but I just keep
getting more and more sensitive!
I want to touch them!
I want to squeeze my milk out!
I'm getting so turned on,
my pussy feels hot. I don't think I can resist!
He'll expose me to the entire class
if I play with them, though!
I know this is wrong, but maybe I can ask
him to rub them for me... No, I can't!
Looks like she's at her limit.
You don't look good, Kusonoki.
You should take a break in the nurse's office.
I'll send someone with you...
No, I'll be okay by myself.
Where...
Sensei?
Sayaka brought you here.
You need to be punished for
leaving in the middle of class.
No! It's inside me! My pussy's filled with your dick!
It keeps hitting me so deep inside!
Please, stop! You're even rubbing
my boobs so roughly, I can't hold back!
Don't, then. Let the pleasure take over.
I shouldn't, but whenever you rub them,
it feels like they'll let out so much milk!
I never feel this good when I do it alone,
so why does it feel good with you?!
It just means that we're sexually compatible.
You're the perfect sex slave for me.
Slave?!
You're squeezing my breasts and moving
your cock inside me! It's too much!
If you become my slave,
I'll rub them for you as much as you want.
If I become your slave you'll squeeze my boobs for me? No!
Even if you squeeze my breasts so erotically,
I'll never become your slave!
Squeezing milk out of a High School Girl~
Lesson on disgracing your slutty childhood friend
The face he was making was different than the one I know.
The sensei I loved was kind.
That couldn't have been him, right? I need to find out!
Sensei! I have something I need to ask you.
What is it?
A little while ago did you and Narukawa-san... Um...
Did you two do something in the gym?
Oh, you saw that?
I didn't get a good look, but you two were practicing, right?
Maybe doing some coordinated gymnastics?
I was raping her. It was her first time,
so it must've hurt a lot.
She even cried.
Rape?! What are you saying?!
Did I never tell you the reason why I came to this school?!
What... What are you doing, sensei?!
What reason are you talki...
I cam here to rape high school girls,
and make them my slaves.
Sensei, that's not funny. I just wanted to talk to you.
I've already decided who my slaves will be,
and you, Nanako, are one of them.
Sensei, your hand is... No, stop, sensei!
You can't touch my breasts!
They feel good in my hand.
You're completely different from when you were a kid.
No, sensei, stop! Why are you doing this?!
What's wrong with you?!
Didn't you hear me? I'm going to make you my slave.
Your everything will be mine.
This can't be happening! Sensei even took my first kiss!
You just kissed someone you like, aren't you happy?
You're doing this even though you know
how I feel about you? You're horrible!
Your feelings are irrelevant.
I'm doing this because I want to.
Sensei, stop! Please, go back to the kind
person you are! You're being weird!
This is who I really am.
The sensei you fell in love with is just an illusion.
No! Don't move your hand! Sensei, don't rub it! No!
This is where the fun starts.
The fun?
Sensei, no! Something hot is rubbing
against me! This can't be... Stop!
I'm gonna take your virginity and your first kiss, Nanako.
No! It's going in!
Your hot thing is going inside me! No!
Of course it is, I'm gonna fuck you.
You can't! I don't want to have sex with you like this!
You stopped...
Crying? Looks like you're still a kid.
I'm going to turn you into an adult now.
Ow! It hurts so much!
How does it feel to be a woman, Nanako?
This is what a cock feels like.
It's inside me... It's going deeper and deeper.
It hurts! It really hurts!
I lost my virginity!
I'm really being raped by you!
We're just getting started.
Ow! Stop! Sensei, please stop! No!
I don't think I can stop myself if you keep
letting out those sweet cries of agony.
Make this more fun for me.
No! Stop doing these horrible things! This isn't right!
You know, ever since I became
a private tutor, I've raped a ton of girls.
That can't be true!
You're a good person! You'd never do that!
I'll break the fake image you have
of me by cumming deep inside you.
Inside?! No! You can't do that!
Please, I'm begging you, stop!
We're no longer childhood friends,
you're just my slave. You'll drink from my cock.
No, don't do it! You can't do that! No!
Something hot is flowing into me!
Your dick is swelling inside of me!
Were not done yet.
No, stop! Don't rape me anymore! It's so deep! No! No!
I used to let you sit on my lap when we were little,
but now there's a dick as well.
No, stop! Stop saying that! It's too cruel!
Look at my cock disappearing into your pussy.
Get used to it, this will be regular.
You're horrible!
It's going inside me! Something so thick is violating me!
Does your own shameful pussy surprise you?
Are you going to cum inside me again?
Stop! You'll get me pregna...
It's going inside me again, no!
I'm going to get pregnant! I'm going to have a baby!
I told you to stop, but you're still cumming inside me.
Sensei, you're the worst!
I trusted you! How could you be such a terrible person?!
I was finally able to show you my true self.
I'm glad to see that you enjoyed yourself, Master.
Headmistress? Why are... Master?!
Sayaka's one of the girls I raped and made
into my slave back when I was a private tutor.
I am Master's cockslave, so anything you
try to do at this point is meaningless.
You're lying. This is just too much!
He raped me. I didn't think he was that
kind of person, but all this time, I've...
If you get naked in the pool,
I'll think about taking that out of you.
Sensei, you can't be serious!
I can't do this right now! Please, take it out!
I thought you were gonna reform me.
If you don't get a move on it, it'll be too late.
I love you, sensei!
Huh?
Didn't I make it clear that the person
you fell in love with was just an illusion?
When we were kids, you took really
good care of me. That was the real you!
I never thought for a second that was fake.
I believe the sensei I love will return!
No, I'll change you back into how you used to be!
Do whatever you want, though,
I'm not going to stop training you as a slave.
No, where do you think you're touching?! Sensei, stop!
You can't!
If I can't, then why aren't you resisting?
It might be stupid, but being held by the person
I've loved for so long makes me happy!
At this rate, you're going to become
my slave before you reform me.
That's not true! I'll never give up!
Why is he suddenly making it stronger?!
He told me to hurry,
but how am I supposed to get naked here?!
I need to hurry up or else everyone will see me.
Nanako, what's wrong?
Why are you taking off your swimsuit?
The string just kinda got loose.
No, if he makes it this strong, I'm gonna cum!
What's the matter, does your stomach hurt?
Should I call the teacher for you?
N-No, I'm fine. I'll be fine...
No way, I...
Nanako! Are you okay?
We're in the middle of class.
Why do I have to be dressed like this?
What do you want?
Can't you guess?
Something to do with sex again?
More precisely, punishment for disobeying my orders.
You're kidding! That's all because you made it too strong!
After you did that to me all I could
feel was shame and disgrace.
You're saying that after cumming
in front of all of your friends?
You're so mean, sensei.
You knew what would happen
if you came here, but you did anyway.
I can only assume that you want it.
That's not true! I thought that if I didn't come,
you'd do something even worse to me, so...
Let's see if that's true or not.
You can save your surprise for later.
Use your huge tits to service me.
Use my breasts to service you?
What am I supposed to do?
Give me a tit fuck.
Tit fu... Huh?! That's way too embarrassing!
You want to do something worse than that, then?
Fine, I'll do it. I ll do it. This is so embarrassing.
Just do it already, then.
If you don't hurry up, class will start.
I know, its just that it's embarrassing
taking my clothes off in front of you.
Want me to help?
No, I'll do it myself! I don't need your help, geez.
Sandwich my dick in between them.
Oh God, your dick is in between my...
Wow, it's...
What's the matter?
It's... This is the first time I've seen a cock this closely.
It's the first time I'm feeling it too...
What do you think of it?
What do I think? It's so hard, hot and stiff.
I didn't know it looked this scary!
It has such a strong smell, too!
It smells really strongly of you, sensei!
That's because your tits are so amazing.
You've really grown, Nanako.
Don't say that! Sensei, you jerk!
I'm hugging your dick.
I'm doing something really dirty right now.
The smell from your cock is getting even stronger, too.
Keep it up. I'm gonna cum soon.
Something hot's coming out of your dick!
This is amazing. The smell from
your dick is so strong. It's covering me!
Your dick's thrashing around while it's cumming!
The smell is so strong!
W-Wait, your dick is still big, sensei!
You're right. Now that the tit fuck is over,
I guess I'll use your pussy next.
Wow, I haven't even touched your pussy yet,
so how come you're this wet?
I got really turned on making you feel good.
I love you, so I can't' help it!
I don't think this has anything to do with love.
You're just a dirty pervert.
I'll prove that to you right now.
That's not true! I'm not a dirty pervert!
Sensei's dick is inside me again! I'm being raped again!
No, don't move your dick! Don't thrust it so deep inside me!
It feels good even though you're being raped,
doesn't it? What a pervert.
I'm not! I love you just as much
as I can't help getting turned on!
Getting turned on from being raped makes you a pervert.
I'm not a pervert! It's gonna come out!
Stop moving! No, it's gonna come out!
I'm peeing!
What's this, pee? Feeling so good from
it that you pee, you really are a pervert.
I can't help getting turned on after being
covered in the smell of your cock!
So smells turn you on?
I never thought you were that kind of slut.
Stop being so mean! I just like how
the person I love smells! That's normal!
Say what you want,
but your body proves that you're a pervert.
No, stop moving inside of me! You're making me go crazy!
My body feels weird!
I'm not a pervert! Even if I'm turned on, I'm not a pervert!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч