Please enter your name
Please enter
Nezu Kimihiko
Kussetsu
the transience worn on the body
karisome wo minimatoi
masquerade that continues to dance
odori tsuzukeru masquerade
sinful pleasures
tsumibukaki kairakuni
fingertips that invite puzzling masturbation
sasoi nazo meku yubisaki
gradually learning about perversion and love
tousaku no ai to shiri tsutsu
unescapable memories of hands
nogarerarenai kioku no te
your smiling persona
persona no oku de hohoemu anata
reflects in the mirror of my honest face
kagami ni utsuru sugao no watashi
Things that take the shape of people are called dolls.
They are replicas of humans. Imitations without hearts.
But are the living dolls happy?
Would they be happier to be just dolls?
Episode 2
Why do I find playing with dolls fun?
I was hated by everyone around for a while.
The only one who treats me normally is Kouda Masashi.
I hated the cheerful and well liked Masashi.
He looks like a guy living in a picturesque happy
family. I hate the pitiful look in his eyes.
I swore I'll rob him ot everything precious to him... and everything he loves.
And now I've chosen my next target to be Masashi's sister, Yuna.
I haven't said anything about Misato and Kana to Masashi.
Kouda
I could only think that Masashi keeps his problems to himself...
...and tries too hard to solve them on his own.
She is the next target: Kouda Yuna.
She may be Masashi's sister, but they're not related by blood.
They're the same age.
But because they grew up together, she calls
him "brother" and completely trusts him.
I'll rob her of that trust and sever that sibling bond.
I'm just waiting for a chance.
I bought new one.
Huh?
Oh, mom and my sister. The quality looks great.
Ten years ago, Kouda Kayoko married Masashi's father and brouth her daughter.
She's not Masashi's real mother.
Kouda Naoko is Masashi's sister in-law.
She teaches piano in this house.
Is this what you wanted to show me?
No.
I wanted to watch this on your big screen TV.
What's this?
"The astro seeker" unaired-episode 92. English
dubbed with Cantonese subtitles.
You're a maniac as usual.
I went through a lot of trouble finding it.
You put a lot of work into these kinds of things.
Like collecting figures. I'm impressed.
I got the feeling that there was a bitterness in Musashi's words.
Let me sneak into the enemy base.
Can you do it, lieutenant?
No prob, Captain.
Who was she again? Um...
She's the chief pilot, Lieutenant Commander Yuu Laia.
Don't you think Yuu Laia and Naoko look similar?
Eh? You think so?
That's it!
Drop your weapon!
I envy you.
Naoko and Yuna. Living with two girls your age.
Idiot. They're siblings.
All right now. Tell me the code number of the fleet!
No. Nobody tells but God!
But since you're not related by blood, I think it's all right.
Well... Let's see how long you can resist!
What are you talking about?
With Yuna.
What are you saying?
It wouldn't be strange if you wanted to. Don't you want to?
Stop it!
Yuna is my precious little sister.
I apologize. I'm sorry.
That's okay. As long as you understand.
That mature, adult attitude just pissed me off.
Can I come in brother?
Sure.
Hello.
Ishikawa Tamaki is Yuna's classmate.
I know a lot about dolls and figures so I've talked to her a bit.
But it was obvious her real purpose was Masashi.
Well... Tamaki has a favour to ask you.
A favour?
Since you're here. I was wondering if it's all right to ask.
Go ahead and ask Kimihiko.
Even thought she just wanted to ask something,
she made Yuna ask Masashi for her.
Maybe she don't like talking to me directly.
But that's just stupid.
What's up?
Well, my doll "Rina" broke so I was wondering if you could fix her.
At that moment, I saw a way to entrap Yuna. I can use Tamaki.
Allright. No problem.
Really? Thank you.
That's great isn't it Tamaki?
Yeah.
Can you fix her?
Yes, I can fix her in no time.
Really? I'm so happy.
Nezu-senpai. Would you like some sugar?
Eh? No, I don't need any.
I see.
I mean, one teaspoon, no, two please.
Okay.
I'm really glad, you're so nice.
I thought you were moody.
Unlike Masashi, you don't talk as much.
You like Masashi too?
Umm... that's...
Masashi likes you too...
Thai's a lie. Masashi and Kirishima are...
He can't hurt anyone...
If you confess, he can't reject you.
But.
Masashi told me, "I want a doll just like Tamaki".
Give him a special doll modelled after yourself.
If you do, you might sway his feelings.
I can make that doll.
Okay, can you take off your clothes?
I have to measure your three sizes.
B-But.
I can't make a doll without the proportions.
Okay.
Stretch out your arms.
Stand straight, shoulders up.
Are you done?
Okay, thanks.
Now take off your bra and panties.
I can't...
This doll has to be exactly like you. It has to be a perfect replica.
There's no point making a doll layered in clothing
if the body isn't exactly like you, right?
But, there's no way... I can do that...
You don't want to turn away from Masashi do you?
You don't want to make him yours do you?
Hurry and take the picture. This is embarassng.
I love you.
No, you can't do this. No!
No, it's coming out...
What's coming out?
My pee...
Let it out.
No... I can't...
I can't hold it.
Preparations complete.
I never thought you'd call me.
Why do you hate Masashi?
Why do you ask?
Probably because you interest me.
I can't trust him.
He doesn't wear a mask. No skeletons in the closet.
I can't trust a guy like him.
He has to be a guy with secrets like me.
I can't take it. I want to break him. I want to
rob him of everything. Destroy everything.
All you have is your ego.
Dumbass.
I'll take on that role.
Huh?
If you rob everything importance to him. He'll only have me.
Cooperate with me? I want to make Masashi mine.
What did you have to tell me?
I didn't know if I should tell you this.
The way Masashi feels towards Naoko...
It's a special kind of love... like the kind between a man and a woman.
I think he plans to continue to hide it but...
I found out. I'm a woman after all.
No way...
If that was all...
If that was all, I'd keep this a secret.
His feelings towards his sister...
But...
But?
To satisfy his one sided love... Yuna, he might...
That can't be... It's a lie.
I'm not positive either.
But the truth is I love him. I know that.
It can't be true.
You're the only one to satisfy his desire since you're
not related by blood. So I want you to be carelul.
I think you have to be the most careful, but...
Um, I have to go now...
How was that? I did my part... next is yours.
Thanks.
Would you like me inside you now?
I'm going to come.
Please let Tamaki go first.
Are you sure?
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
That's the doll you modelled for.
I... don't need it anymore.
I... with you.
Tamaki.
Tamaki. I have a favour to ask.
I got to invite Yuna.
To step up the final stage of my plan.
If it's this crowded, I should have just driven.
It'd be just as crowded finding a parking spot.
It'd be a useless waste of time.
Tamaki, are you okay?
Do feel sick?
This guy's a molestor.
Now all arangements have been complete.
All that's left are the finishing touches.
No... I'm coming... I'm coming.
You're ready? Go...
Please take care of Yuna.
Leave it to me.
Masashi... How could he...
Mother.
Please don't condemn Masashi.
It's better not to get too agitated.
I can't believe that he'd do such a thing.
Masashi substituted his desires for you onto Tamaki.
A sister not related by blood is still a sister.
His rationale was overtaken by his desire.
Did you know about that?
I knew. I was your brother's friend for a long time.
You're at fault too.
You called Masashi brother and played the younger
sister even though you're the same age.
You chose to be a doll.
You were too sweet and relied on him.
That's not...
You made him puzzled and tormented.
Stop it!
To save him, you have to stop being his pet doll.
You can save him. Only you can save him.
How?
You have to demonstrate to him on your own that you are not his doll anymore.
To my brother? On my own...
Brother, look at me.
I'm not your sweet, innocent Yuna anymore.
I can do things on myself...
...and this is how Masashi lost Yuna.
Only one more step to complete the world I desire.
I'm coming... coming!
Me too. I'm coming.
Please... together.
Where do you want me to come?
You're not a doll. You can choose yourself.
Inside... it's ok so come inside.
Ok... inside!
I'm coming! Coming!
You don't need to do that.
I want to thank you for taking me to ecstacy.