Kussetsu
Please enter your name
Please enter
Nezu Kimihiko
Episode 3
And I lost my way...
I've been hated by people around for a long time.
The only one who treats me normally is Kouda Masashi.
But I hated the cheerful and well liked Masashi.
I swore I'll rob him of everything precious to him... and everything he loves.
Why do you hate Masashi?
I can't believe in him.
He doesn't wear a mask. He doesn't have any skeletons in his closet.
I can't trust a person like him. He has to be an ugly person like me!
I can't take it.
I want to break him.
I want to see him robbed of whoever he loves.
I robbed him of Takahashi Kana who going to confess to him.
I took Ishikawa Tamaki who was attracted to him.
And his sister-in-law Kouda Yuna.
Brother, look at me.
I'm not your sweet, innocent Yuna anymore.
I can do things on myself...
Kimihiko.
You... what's the meaning of this?
W-Why...
Revenge.
Revenge?
Because you're hypocrite.
Me?
You've always took pity on me...
Acting all superiour.
- What are you talking about?
- Everybody detested me and looked down on me and yet act all superior.
What is this... what are you saying?
What did I do to you?
And what does it have to do with Yuna?
Go ahead and pretend you don't know.
Judgment will soon be passed.
My revenge is almost complete.
My next target is Masashi's in-law mother Kayoko.
And his real elder sister Naoko.
That's enough! Stop it!
I just brought a copy.
The original source is in a safe place.
You know what that means, right?
If you contact the police, this video-tape will be distributed.
That's so cruel. What grudge do you have...
You wouldn't understand if I told you. So there's no need for me to tell you.
- That's...
- What's important is...
What I want to do and what you think you should do...
How much do you want?
No money.
What I want is, you.
You just need to be a woman.
Just enjoy a young man's body without thinking too seriously.
That's something I...
My husband...
Masashi's father... Your husband has gone to Italy for a half year.
Aren't you getting horny?
Kimihiko...
I've been attracted to you for a while.
I dreamed of having sex with you.
No... this is... embarassing.
I want teach you... that sex isn't just between husband and wife.
It's a fun activity.
That's...
See, you're wet all ready.
I'm going in.
No, don't!
Is it that good? To make you pant so heavily.
Kouda Masaharu
It's your husband.
Interesting... talk with him.
I can't...
Hello.
Kayoko? It's me.
Dear...
Is everything okay?
Yes, nothing to worry about.
Good.
I called to ask you something.
Our client, Mr. Carlos, will be
coming to Japan next month.
So could you show him...
Kayoko?
Yes, I understand.
Great, I'll fax a detailed schedule
when everything's decided.
Okay.
Thanks, please take care of him.
Bye now.
Well? How does you it feel getting fucked in
your ass with talkling with your husband?
It feels so good!
I'm going to come! I'm coming.
Kimihiko... you...
Were you watching?
You were peeping weren't you? Watching your mother's lewd side.
Wait!
Why did you watch without saying anything?
Do you want this?
Stop it you filthy animal!
I know all ready. That you collect vibrators.
You like them, don't you? A man's hard dick.
No! I hate them.
But you have so many.
I'd hated penises.
Hate?
Men are men only because they have these things.
I wanted to protect my family by becoming a man.
Since my mother died, I supported Masashi
in place of my father who is never home.
So I had to be firm.
Penis envy eh?
While wishing that you were man, giving up on escaping being a woman.
So you hate the symbol of a man, the penis.
But... on the other hand, you want it.
But whether or not you have this... It's the
difference between a man and a woman.
Men and woman different.
Then why don't you try it?
If your sexuality is in conflict. Then the only thing
you can do is stick a foreign object in you.
If you're a man, you should be able to play the piano properly until ejaculation.
You're this wet...
Go ahead and play.
I wonder how long you can keep it up.
What's wrong? Are you getting turned on?
That's not...
You don't hate this.
You're taking it in.
Open your mind.
That's it. That's good.
Ah... that feels good.
No... I'm...
I'm home.
Masashi has lost his sisters and mother.
Surely his mind has begun break.
At last the time has come to trap last trophy.
If you rob Masashi of everything dear to him, he will be all mine.
Kirishima Misato...
At that time, we may have known about this.
The roof of the school? Why there?
I don't want any to hear.
No one should be there on the day off.
Kana, what's the matter?
Nothing. Then be there at 3:30.
Hello?
It's me.
Kimihiko.
Shall we have frank conversation? You must have something to ask me, right?
I used Kana to set a trap.
The plan goes like this: Kana invites Misato and I invite Masashi at the same time.
But Masashi and Kana meets first. Kana will
sway Masashi. Then Misato will come.
Then I will rape Misato in front of Masashi.
That will be the last of my revenge.
Kana, why are you here?
I can't give up on you.
I love you, Masashi.
Hold me. I know that you have Misato.
But I can't erase my feelings for you.
Kana.
Nezu.
You're late. The show has begun.
What?
Kana... Stop it.
Misato! Kimihiko!
What is this?
Kimihiko... you?
Sorry. I know I shouldn't be doing this but...
But I just couldn't give up.
She's getting revenge on you Kirishima.
That's it, isn't it, Kimihiko? This is part of your plan, isn't it?
I understand.
Exactly. We're going to have now.
I'm going to get a good taste of you.
Stop! She has nothing to do with this!
Stop it.
I won't run away even if you do this.
What?
You said it didn't you? "You and I are the same".
Yeah.
I realized how Masashi is so powerless.
And that you're much more interesting.
Tight... you're pussy feels nice and tight.
Masashi's... Masashi's penis filling my pussy. It feels so good.
Even in this situation, you've got an erection and fucking Kana's brains out.
You're a dirty beast. Recognize yourself as a lewd human!
I'm almost done.
No... fuck me more, harder!
Okay.
This is so good. I'm so hot.
Well? Ready to come?
I'm ready. I'm coming.
Okay, let's go together. Ready?
I'm ready, fill my pussy with your cum!
Okay, here it comes!
This time, I should have completely broken Masashi's mind.
My revenge is complete.
And after a while, Masashi disappeared.
But one day, I got a letter from him.
I know that my unconscious acts and weakness
caused you great pain and embarassement.
You made me realize that...
Because of you, I've exorcised my carnal desires and threw away my want.
Thank you. I will surely conquer my weaknesses inside me.
P.S. Please take care of my mother, sisters ant Yuna.
Masashi was not mentally destroyed. He threw away all his desires.
There's nothing left to rob him of.
My revenge had no meaning.
I couldn't even get him to recognize his weakness.
I just made him recognize his sins.
I was tormented by the feeling of defeat.
All you have is your ego.
You big idiot.
the transience worn on the body
karisomewo minimatoi
masquerade that continues to dance
odori tsuzukeru masquerade
sinful pleasures
tsumibukaki kairakuni
fingertips that invite puzzling masturbation
sasoi nazomeku yubisaki
gradually learning about perversion and love
tousakuno aito shiritsutsu
unescapable memories of hands
nogare rarenai kiokuno te
your smiling persona
persona no okude hohoemu anata
reflects in the mirror of my honest face
kagamini utsuru sugaono watashi
on the stage of the palm
te no hira no stage de
the marionette continues to sing
utai tuzukeru marionette
discomforting buddhist precepts
fujiyuu na kairitsu no
the lure hidden in the darkness
yami ni hisonda yuuwaku
the trap of desire that no one notices
yokubou no wana ga itsushika
when the nectar can't escape
nogarerarenai mitsu no toki
your smiling persona
persona no oku de hohoemu anata
reflects in the mirror of my honest face
kagami ni utsuru sugao no watashi