Please enter your name
Please enter
Nezu Kimihiko
Why do people hide their true nature?
Is it their real self? Or only a virtual image?
Can people turn lies into truth?
I've been hated by people around for a long time.
I don't know why.
I've just lived my life as I thought I should.
The only one who treats me normally is Kouda Masashi.
But he is the person I despise the most in this world.
I hate him because he and I are the complete opposite.
I hated the cheerful and well liked Masashi.
He looks like a guy living in a picturesque happy
family. I hate the pitiful look in his eyes.
His attitude seems hypocritical to me.
He acts like he doesn't discriminate against me.
I will make him recognize his own hypocracy. His true self.
I swore revenge.
I swore I'll rob him of everything precious to him... and everything he loves.
It's all your own fault.
You'll get everything the way you want.
You big idiot.
Episode 1
How should I proceed first?
I'm going to confess to Masashi.
I just don't want to...
Give up on him.
I have to tell him straight up, don't I?
But... he might not be able to accept me as more than a friend.
Kana, I know you can do it.
Can I?
I'll go with you, if you're afraid.
We're friends, aren't we?
Thanks a lot, Misato!
She's wearing a mask...
Now's my chance.
So who is it?
Kirishima Misato or Takahashi Kana?
Who do you really like?
I like both of them.
I don't want to hurt either of them.
"I don't want to hurt either"...
That excuse disgusts me.
I put my plan in motion.
Do you like Masashi?
Do you want to make him yours?
Well?
Do you like Masashi?
Do you want to make him yours?
Well?
Do you like Masashi?
Do you want to make him yours?
Well?
I'll help you out
Do you like Masashi?
Do you want to make him yours?
Well?
I'll help you out
Really?
Do you like Masashi?
Do you want to make him yours?
Well?
I'll help you out
Really?
You're true feeling have come out eh?
Do you like Masashi?
Do you want to make him yours?
Well?
I'll help you out
Really?
You're true feeling have come out eh?
Actually, Masashi isn't
thinking just about you.
I'll help you out
Really?
You're true feeling have come out eh?
Actually, Masashi isn't
thinking just about you.
I'll help you out
Really?
You're true feeling have come out eh?
Actually, Masashi isn't
thinking just about you.
But I think if you told Masashi
I'll help you out
Really?
You're true feeling have come out eh?
Actually, Masashi isn't
thinking just about you.
But I think if you told Masashi
you loved him then everything
I'll help you out
Really?
You're true feeling have come out eh?
Actually, Masashi isn't
thinking just about you.
But I think if you told Masashi
you loved him then everything
would fall into place.
But
But...
What about Kana?
Take her with you when you confess.
But...
What about Kana?
Take her with you when you confess.
Make her see Masashi choose you.
But...
What about Kana?
Take her with you when you confess.
Make her see Masashi choose you.
Then she'd be forced to give up because of your friendship.
But...
What about Kana?
Take her with you when you confess.
Make her see Masashi choose you.
Then she'd be forced to give up because of your friendship.
Right?
I know that if it's for the sake of making Masashi
hers, she'll trample on her friends feelings.
Masashi's late.
What should I do if he stands me up?
Don't worry.
My heart feels like it's going to explode.
I'll go call him.
Kana.
Kimihiko?
Masashi's not coming.
I love you...
Do you... love me...? Masashi?
Of course, I love you.
But...
Kana!
Masashi...
Misato, what are you doing here?
Don't misunderstand! This is...
Misunderstand?
No... I mean...
Sorry... I knew I shouldn't have done this because of Kana.
But I just didn't want to give up.
And I thought that Kana might be angry...
Because you shouldn't sacrificed your own feelings.
That's right, you shouldn't sacrifice your own feelings for me.
Kana...
Sorry.
That vas a worthless excuse wasn't it? Not wanting to hurt either...
That was only the first step towards my revent.
I was grateful at the attitude that Misato showed Kana.
It was a clearly calculated excuse.
with Kana's attitude, all she could do was find a way to escape.
But there was a fire pent up inside Kana...
While she knew there were people at the bus
stop, she purposely opens her drapes.
I knew that insider her there was a desire to be watched.
I thought I should make her my obediant servant.
In order to help get revenge on Masashi.
There isn't anyone else you can ask?
To drive you.
Masashi said he was busy.
Thanks.
Kirishima was using you.
Remove a rival and monopolize Masashi.
That's...
She trampled over your feelings to get Masashi.
Stop it!
She made a fool of you.
Shut up!
What's wrong?
You don't look good.
You had better stop the car.
It aches doesn't it?
It aches there doesn't it?
Aphrodisiac.
It's called Zokunyubiac.
Don't fight it.
Kimihiko?
It's okay, just relax.
Don't worry, the windows are tinted.
Release yourself.
That's it. There's nothing to be afraid of.
Don't stifle your emotions.
Just say yes to what you want.
I can feel you in me.
That's... good...
How is it? Are you tetting aroused?
Does it feel good?
Feels great.
You want more?
More! More!!
You came all by yourself. Finish me off too.
Okay.
*Log of their previous conversation
That's the proof that you betrayed your friend to get Masashi.
You'd be in trouble if it got out wouldn't you?
Is that a threat?
Exactly.
What are you trying to do?
Isn't it obvious?
Stop it.
Aren't you tired?
Your father's a famous local politician.
Your mother's belongs to volunteer clubs.
You're justified in your worthless appearance.
You've been bound by your parents.
You try your best to act as your ideal self and get into that act.
What would you understand?
I understand.
You'll do anything to get what you want.
Including methods that wouldn't muddy your ideal own image.
If your true self was exposed, it'd be the end of you.
Let me rape you.
You're smart.
You're getting wet.
No!
Look. Daddy's little girl is excited and wet.
This is photographic evidence that you're rapist.
You bitch.
I'll expose your sexual assault.
What's so funny?
No one will believe you.
Get out.
You're the same as me.
It was nothing to get impatient about. Because
our relationship was just beginning.
You obeyed my command?
Yes.
Please... take it off.
Please.
What's wrong?
I want you to put it in me.
Don't open it so wide. It's embarassing.
Don't be so violent.
You're getting really turned on, aren't you?
Don't say that.
So wet...
It just slides in.
You're twitching.
Moving in and out...
Well? Does it feel good?
You... even if a stranger might see you, you're still so excited.
Do you want to show off that much?
Say it.
I want to show... I want people to see me! Look
at me. Getting fucked here... I'm so horny.
Look at how dirty I am...
Come on, you're dirtier than this...
Please... fuck me deeper.
Kana.
Do it! Do it! I... I...
I'm almost finished...
I can't hold it anymore...
Are you ready?
- Do it!
- Come...
And now...
I've chosen my next target to be Masashi's sister, Yuna.