Aw... Can't get down?
Poor kitty...
Hey, could you close your eyes for a while?
Till I say you can open them again. No peeking!
Why?
You can open your eyes now. Here.
Awesome! How did you do that?
It's a secret.
Okay...
Thanks!
Good morning, Kawakami!
Good morning...
Let's get going.
School! We're going to be late.
Kuttskukiboshi
- Stars Intertwined -
As thou becometh father to thy son,
swearest thou an oath unto the world beyond...
Aaya Saitou transferred to our class this spring.
And for the next passage... Saitou.
To me, her voice is more beautiful than any other sound in the world.
And the wind exists...
to put a sigh through her hair...
...but this protein known as haemoglobin, found in red blood cells...
Just her presence was more important than anything else in the world.
Kawakami...
Kawakami!
Were you listening?
And your face is pretty red.
Is something wrong?
Uh, no. Nothing...
That blush in her cheeks, that right there is the haemoglobin.
Now you'll all remember!
Well, then, everyone stay focused and disciplined over the summer break!
Class dismissed!
Stand.
Bow.
Call me if there's something you don't understand.
Thank you!
Only for the parts I know, okay?
Got it. Bye-bye!
Let's do our usual thing today.
Follow me!
Had enough already?
Yeah... I can't take any more...
It moved! A new record!
I really think your powers are getting stronger!
Saitou... You treat me like a guinea pig or something.
Exper—
When you had that traffic accident a year ago, did anything else change?
Oh... Back then...
By the time I woke up at the hospital,
I was already like this, somehow...
Okay.
It must have been the shock that brought out your powers.
Do you have other powers, like predicting the future?
Umm... I'm just able to move objects without touching them, but...
— Can we stop now?
— No way.
I want to make those powers a secret between us.
Hey... Follow me.
No way!
That was close...
I don't know why, but this tree didn't burn down even in the air raids.
That's why I think there's a great well of energy sleeping in here.
Let's receive some of its energy.
You try it.
As long as I keep this secret, I have no choice but to do what she says.
But...
Actually, there's another secret that she doesn't know about.
The fact that ever since we met...
I've been in love with everything about Aaya Saitou.
Saitou?
Oh, my god!
What am I doing?
The school during summer vacation is somehow... otherworldly.
The empty morning campus seems almost like our own private castle.
I couldn't find one to my liking, so I made it myself.
What, a puzzle ring?
No, this isn't a puzzle you can solve.
Wow... You're so clever.
I thought that maybe you'd be able to separate these with your powers.
Really? I'm not too sure.
In other words, you're still experimenting with me.
— It's two different matters!
— Okay, I get it!
I can't do it, after all. Things like these are impossible.
Or is it... possible?
Sometimes, it happens before you've realized.
I want you to try at this every day.
And if you can see the future, tell me immediately!
Sure. But seeing into the future is...
Your nails are so pretty.
Aaya, you're wearing mascara?
Yeah... Does it look weird...?
It's gorgeous!
You look really cute in anything.
Thanks! But even if you flatter me—
I have it.
And I also brought eyelash curlers.
Kiichan, you should put some on, too! I'll do it for you!
Yes, please.
Couldn't you foresee this?
I can't. You talk too mu—
Even though you knew it was coming?
Aaya... You haven't been wearing underwear this whole time?
Isn't it hot?
I'm sweating...
It feels great!
Kiichan, come in!
Yup.
Hey, are you sure this is a good idea?
Well, our school doesn't have a swimming club.
But if anyone comes...
They won't! Because this is our secret private bath time!
Aaya... You're kinda... horny, aren't you?
Yeah, I am!
We did so many dirty things today that I'm worn out!
Aaya! It would be embarrassing if someone heard that!
It just tempts me more when you get all embarrassed.
Let's buy ice cream over there!
What flavor would you like?
I want it to taste like your —
Geez, you pervert!
What's gonna happen to us from now on, I wonder...
Sorry, we don't have to talk about it.
It seems that I love you so much...
that I wilted.
Aaya...
Let's make lots of love again tomorrow.
Yeah.
Kiichan's thigh flavor...
From: Saitou, Aaya
Sorry! (>o<)> I'm feeling a bit unwell 2day, so no experiments~ ^.^
omg, r u @ skul already? I'm so sorry!! oh but I'm not srsly sick,
so dun worry >_<; I'll def go 2moro ok? <3333
Sorry!
Come in.
Thanks.
Is coffee all right?
Oh, no, no. Sick people need to sleep.
Uh... I'm not actually... sick...
My flow is kind of... heavy today.
Are you all right?
Yup, I'm okay.
In any case, you should lie down.
Yes, nurse!
You sure have a lot of instruments here.
They're my brother's.
— Wow... So you have a brother.
— He seldom comes home, though.
Did you manage to separate that?
These stars, right?
No...
But anyway, here. This is for you.
I recommend this.
I've been listening to this since junior high...
— Perhaps you know it?
— Yeah.
Really? I guess you would.
— I'm back.
— Welcome back!
— Your friend?
— Kawakami, my classmate.
Sorry to disturb you.
How are you?
Um...
Huh?
What... Seriously?
Yeah.
Your grandfather's a foreigner, so...
A half of a halfie... What do you call that?
A "quarter".
And your brother is going overseas after the summer break?
Yeah... He's going somewhere in Australia...
Stop!
One, two.
One, two!
Someone might find out!
Sorry...
There are only the two of us in our family,,
so I was planning to go with him.
I've answered question 4.
That's my girl!
You were planning to go with him, but...
I'm not going to go.
I'm so happy it was Aaya who found out about my secret powers.
Oh, hello? It's me.
I'm staying at my friend's place tonight, so I'll get home tomorrow.
It's still impossible to separate that, after all.
I'm sure it's just because you're not trying hard enough.
Well, then I'll try harder.
All right, I'll see you tomorrow at school.
I'll text you.
Yeah.
Maybe she's not home yet...
There's no choice!
Excuse me.
Kiichan!
Wait!
They're separated...
They separated...
And the more we wish with our fingers interlocked,
the more our wish comes true
If we can stay the way we are now,
it doesn't matter if we disappear
Because those intertwined stars in that sky
will watch over us