Hello.
Saitou speaking.
The new semester starts tomorrow.
When I heard the news of my brother's death,
I decided that I should use the remainder of the holiday to redeem myself.
I need to make up for the wrong I committed against her.
If only this nightmare were my only punishment.
That was just my stupid, selfish fantasy.
Kuttskukiboshi
- Stars Intertwined -
Part Two
The strong, large-scale hurricane 11 appears to be approaching the Kanto coast.
Expect a large storm on the last weekend of summer vacation.
She hasn't come...
She brought it...
What's this?
Location of your phone: PE shed
My phone's in the PE shed?
Where is it?
Huh? What happened?
Oh, no! Hey...
What?! What's going—
Why? What do you want...?
Stop...
Stop it!
Water.
You're not eating?
I'll have some.
Umm... I think my hands are swollen.
It's done!
It should still work, even though I altered the shape.
This looks better.
This will make Kiichan want to carry it with her everyday.
Maybe...
Is this weird?
Anyway, I won't tell her where I got it.
That was...
Yeah, I've been at a friend's house.
Yeah.
She invited me to come study with her.
Oh...
I know.
My parents are pissed.
It's been several days.
Can you open that for me?
Oh, right.
What's wrong?
I forgot the combination.
Hey...
I wanted to ask you...
What were you doing with your brother that time?
You still haven't told me anything.
What? Nothing much.
Do you hate me now?
Just because of that?
"Just that"?!
Hey.
It's hot...
I saw before that the door to the pool changing rooms wasn't locked.
When you're done, you don't need to close the door.
By the way, don't get me wrong.
I was only with you because you found out about my powers.
But I'm through with all this.
Bye.
What have I been wanting to do this whole week?
I'm just a guinea pig in an experiment.
But... if I wanted to, I could always escape.
Oh, well... I'm just really angry right now.
Incoming call: City General Hospital
You're so tan!
I went to the beach four times!
That's too much!
Oh, crap! The teacher's here!
All right, get to your seats! Homeroom is starting.
Kawakami!
I marked you as absent since you weren't at the opening ceremony.
But I'll just mark you as late now.
So come on in.
Wonder if it's 'cause of Saitou.
It's the first day of a new semester, and Kawakami's late, and Saitou's absent.
Let's start homeroom then!
Aaya didn't come to school.
I wanted to ask how she felt,
but I couldn't bring myself to text or call her.
Maybe it's 'cause I'm scared that she wouldn't reply.
I want to forget everything,
and believe that maybe Saitou Aaya never existed in the first place.
But... I can't think that way.
My thoughts are only of her.
And with that, I'll be collecting the summer break assignments now.
Bring them in order of roll call.
— Assignment?
— Oh, no!
I totally forgot...
No...
Thank you.
Get home safely.
Let's do it again, for the last time.
Wait! My bag!
What the...? You're not wearing anyth—
There's no need to be embarrassed.
Just make your move.
That's it...
Hey... Why don't you have panties on, either?
I didn't feel like it.
Your... finger...
Isn't this wrong?
Let me have yours.
What are you—
This is wrong!
This is wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
Stop that.
You seem even further gone than me.
We could've gone in when there was more water in the tub.
Next, we'll do it in here.
There's no point anymore.
I mean, it's already...
Anyway, I'm not even carrying it around now.
I don't even know where it is.
That doesn't matter anymore.
It's just...
I'm leaving Japan tomorrow.
In other words, the experiment is finished.
I'll keep your secret.
So let's make love tonight.
As many times as we can.
Let's begin.
This is...
Are you the patient's sister?
...a hospital?
We've had a look at the results,
and unfortunately, there's been no improvement.
This is partially due to the absence of cognitive symptoms that delayed diagnosis.
And because it's so close to the spinal chord,
surgical removal of the tumor will be extremely difficult.
Saitou-san.
Yes.
I am very sorry to say this,
but the probability of success is extremely low.
Please be prepared for the worst.
However, we will do our best.
Apparently, the surgery can be done this month,
and then, the doctor said that you'll definitely get better!
No, I have no hope.
I just know it!
Don't give up!
Believe in yourself!
I can't really help, but I'm praying that it'll be a success.
Praying won't change a thing.
In Operation
But...
At least... before the end...
I want to make love with you before I die.
It's always been on my mind.
You're not just a sister to me anymore.
What are you... talking about?
I...
No!
Sorry! There's something wrong with me.
Forget it... I wasn't being serious.
I'm going to have the operation.
Even if I don't do anything...
So the reason why you've never dated anyone was...
Okay.
You can do whatever you want.
I wanna do whatever I can to help.
It'd be great if you could lock up before you leave.
I know.
I can lock up for you.
You don't need to tell me that.
But...
Why?
Why...?
Why...?!
Why did you just disappear?
Why didn't you explain everything to me?
Your brother died... Didn't he?
And...
And he manipulated his own little sister like that.
Kiichan, did you see my memories?
That was too selfish!
What was that?!
I'm sorry I didn't tell you...
But no matter what the reason was...
There's no changing the fact that I betrayed you.
It's unforgivable.
That's right. It is unforgivable.
If you disappear again without telling me,
I really will kill you.
Without tell—
I'll do it.
We'll do more things together.
The empress
We'll fill each other with memories.
And then...
I'll make you mine.
she stands all alone
Even if I have to force you with my powers.
with her forlorn
Because no matter how you touch my body,
I get excited because I love you so much.
blue jewels
Maybe I'm just a pervert.
By your side,
What about you?
No matter what happens, I'll still like everything about you.
I tremble
I love you.
Just hold me
This is so messed up.
and my vanished courage
But... I'm glad.
I love you, too!
There are many people
Aaya...
searching for answers to this world
I forgot to lock the door.
but of you, I know nothing
Well, let's go.
Okay!
If only I could
Aaya!
Wh-What should we do?!
I would leave time behind
The sea!
and cry a yell that turns all ages to history
If only I could
with the same passion
I want to see the beautiful sea!
I'll transform my naked figure
into your only girlfriend
I think I really have lost it.
It doesn't matter. It's done its job.
Infectiously
Where did you get that?
I bought it online.
When separated by a supernatural force ==>
Your wish will come true in a new world
an aurora in a bottle
I see... You got it online...
But... I'm glad I gave it a chance,
So exquisite
because I was able to meet you.
And incredible things have happened! Look!
A floating treasure
It's so beautiful.
Yeah, but where are we?
The universe
roars a giant avalanche
Maybe it's a distant planet...
I don't care where we are.
As long as you're with me.
but I will not disappear
Hey, Aaya.
I've seen the future.
We'll be together forever.
If we could
I'd like you and I
to share a kiss that would annihilate all reason
If I could
I would give flight to this passion
as though they are ripples
I want to believe in these newborn feelings