The Case of Mr. H.Y.
The Academic Staff (59)
and Miyamoto Sana
Mr. Principal.
Should I let you see down here as well?
The Case of Mr. S.T.
The Salaryman (52)
and Kogure Chika
How is it, uncle?
Am I not good at giving a massage?
So it feels good when I do this.
Uncle, you're sucking on my breast!
If you do any more than this, I'm...
Just from my breast... I'm gonna
come just from my breast...
I love cuddling!
More, more!
The Case of Mr. K.N.
The Academic Staff (51)
and Tazawa Anko
Sensei, what are you doing?
Are you giving me extra lessons alone
so you can to get a good look at my body?
Sensei, not my tits!
They feel good!
Suck them more!
I'm gonna be your woman.
The six of us got to know each other online only by chance.
We went to a hot spring resort in N prefecture for an orgy.
Well,
we're about to start a fun celebration.
My name is Miyamoto Sana.
I'm Kogure Chika!
Tazawa Anko!
squishy
The Busty High School Girls are all squishy and are
having a kinky sex with middle-aged men's dicks.
The Busty High School Girls are all squishy
The middle-aged men's dicks are shared with everyone!
and are having a kinky sex with middle-aged men's dicks.
Mr. Principal,
please feel good even a lot more!
You came a lot, huh?
Oh no...
Uncle, you're being reckless!
You'll break me down!
You'll break me down, you'll break me down!
Wow, it feels good...
It feels good!
No...
No! I can't take it anymore!
I'm coming... I-I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
Sensei, more!
Hurry up... Make me come!
Suck my tits a lot!
This feels good...
It feels good!
My tits and down there as well...
They're both feeling good!
I came!
Wait!
I just came...
Stop that!
I'm still highly sensitive...
I said wait!
I'll end up coming again!
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming...
I'm coming—!
Tazawa-san...
...and Kogure-san too, they're amazing!
Miyamoto-kun...
Hmm?
The main event is about to begin.
I get to have all of these
incredible cocks by myself!
More... More!
I want even more!
It's our turn to serve the middle-aged men next.
Uncle, does it feel good?
I wonder which one of you
can hold back the longest...
The winner will get to have all three of us
at the same time as a reward!
I'm going to make you feel good
a lot using my mouth, okay?
You almost had it, sensei!
Congratulations, Mr. Principal!
Get a good taste of my pussy, alright?
Does this feel good, Mr. Principal?
Your cock is swelling like crazy!
Could it be that you're about to come?
You don't have to hold it in.
We're going to do it even a lot more!
This is terrific!
Seriously, I'll get addicted to this!
Your dick... Oh, your dick is amazing!
It feels good! Your thick cock feels good!
Mister, more... I want more!
Mister, you're hitting me deep inside!
It's pounding deep into my womb!
Mister... Your cock is so deep!
Mister, I like your cock!
I love it!
More, more... Dick!
Please...
Take care of our pussies
from today onwards!
Please train our pussies!
Squishy... Squishy every day!
Uncle... Uncle...
More! More!
It's going inside me!
Mr. Principal, your cock is so intense!
Your middle-aged cock broke me down!
Sensei...
Sensei, I want your sperm inside me...
Shoot all of it inside me!
So deep!
Middle-aged men are the best!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization