To: Mamiya Yuuichi-sama
Subject: Recommendations to our Newest Products!!
Using the latest technology, it is able to ensure a much deeper
and high-variety hypnosis on your target.
The Magic Penlight!!
As an dull high school student, I,
Mamiya Yuuichi, had a transformation of my life,
when my father Seiichi suddenly remarried.
His new partner, Mifuyu-san,
Her eldest daughter Natsuki-chan,
Second daughter Akiha,
Suddenly, I had a new mother and two younger sisters.
In addition, even though he just remarried,
my father left home for a long term business trip,
and I was thrown into life with a
mom and sisters I had just met.
I wonder if the life with Mifuyu-san, Natsuki-chan
and Akiha-chan like this is normal.
Having lived alone for most of my life,
I was just really happy to have a family.
I wanted to become true family with them.
Mifuyu-san.
The more I look at Mifuyu-san, the more
your body heats up and feels good.
Don't worry, we are mother and son after all,
there's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Why? My body is hot...
I can't...
My body is hot, why?
No...
Don’t stare like that...
But... I guess we are family...
I shouldn't feel embarrassed even if you're watching...
It feels... really good!
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Hypnosis on the Huge-breast Family
The Family Bond
What's wrong, Yuuichi-kun?
Instead of cleaning, why don't you
have fun with the son you love?
I guess...
Huh? Aren't you wet already?
What were you hoping for?
That's not it... this is, um...
When Yuuichi-kun mentions doing it, it suddenly...
C'mon, I want to listen to you ask for it like always.
That's too improper...
Please tell me, Mifuyu-san, what do you want me to do?
Please put Yuuichi-kun's thick penis inside my pussy!
Something big and hot is coming inside...
My deepest parts are being spread apart...
It's embarrassing... I’m getting too excited...
No... it's making noises! It's making noises
of my pussy being stirred up by a dick!
So deep! Your thick thing is grinding!
Yes...
Yuuichi-kun, don’t... if you're so rough...
Not there, I...
Wait! I'm still cumming! It hasn't stopped!
Mifuyu-san, I'm cumming soon, too.
But if I cum outside I'll stain the room you just cleaned.
That's...
What do I do?
Then...
I think it'll be alright... if you cum inside...
If you thrust so hard...
Cumming again... cumming!
Hot stuff is... inside... so much... wow...
Huh? You're still going?
Not... again...
My pussy... my pussy feels good!
My pussy feels good...
Yuuichi-kun’s penis... is swelling inside me...
Could it be that you're cumming again?
Cumming inside again...
If I cum inside too much, you'll get my baby.
Eh?
No, wait, Yuuichi-kun.
I can’t get a baby, not with anyone
other than Seiichi-san...
But if I cum outside, I’ll get the room dirty.
But that's... I’ll clean up again, so...
So please, Yuuichi-kun, this time, outside...
I can't do that.
Don't, Yuuichi-kun, let me go!
No... I can't do this... but it feels so good...
It's cumming again... it’s coming out...
No, I can't get a baby...
I can't get pregnant, but..
No... it's spilling... even though he came
inside to keep the floor clean...
I can't think of anything anymore...
Welcome back, Natsuki-chan.
Well, show me your body like always.
Nii-san... I... this is really embarrassing...
We had PE today I and sweat a lot... um...
But today you were talking about your
friends about the smell of your bodies,
and you're worried that you might have a
strange smell, so I should check, right?
Yeah, but...
I didn't think you'd lick this much...
Please, Nii-san!
Hey, wait!
I just can't wait You have a really great smell.
No, you can't... this is embarrassing!
Not there! Not there... not... No!
Nii-san you're so cruel!
Why are you... touching there...
I said no... Nis-san, not there!
No, not there... it's only for a person you really love...
No! Again... cumming again!
Wait up!
No, it's coming out! It's coming out!
It's coming out... what do I do...
It won't stop... don't look...
Nii-san, don't look!
I'm sorry...
Please, don't tell mom...
Yuuichi-kun, don't...
Not in the kitchen, it's dangerous!
The pot is still on the fire...
Then please turn it off.
The meat is already nice and soft, right?
Just like this pussy.
No, that's...
So deep... it’s grinding inside like usual...
I can tell the shape of the penis!
No way... It's rubbing... so much...
No... if you keep doing that...
Wait... wait up!
There...
It's good... really good...
When Yuuichi-kun does me, it starts
feeling really lonely down there...
Where do you mean by "there"?
I mean... you know...
My pussy! My pussy gets so lonely... please!
Thrust my pussy more with your dick!
Thrust lots inside my pussy! Make me...
Make me cum!
I'm sorry...
it's so strong... I can't resist!
Yuuichi-kun, you came... inside again today...
No... Yuuichi-kun's hot stuff is flowing inside...
It's coming out...
I hope it's safe today...
Are you worried about getting pregnant?
You have no time for that.
Not again, that's... wait, Yuuichi-kun, let me rest!
It's thrusting inside!
No... I'll go crazy... it feels good!
it's too good...
That's... too embarrassing...
Don't... I...
Yuuichi-kun, I...
I'm... going to...
I really can'tl I'm cumming! Cumming!
Cuming... my pussy... cumming! No!
No way... you came so much, but you're still so hard...
So, will you calm down with one more go?
You can cum inside, but make it the last time!
Or else I'll... I'll go crazy...
Your penis is swelling...
You’re going to rampage inside my again...
No... the thick thing is coming all the way...
My hips won't stop!
Yuuichi-kun's penis is too amazing, my body is...
I'll make sure to plant my seed and impregnate you!
Impregnate? I can’t let that happen...
Cumming, my pussy is cumming again!
Cum! Let it out, ejaculate! Inside...
I'll cum, too; I'm cumming again!
It's coming... out... semen...Yuuichi-kun's semen-milk...
Your penis... I can't...
Well then, clean it all up at the end like always.
I'll clean your penis... let me clean up...
Amazing...
There's still so much... in my throat...
It's tasty...
I should rub the shaft, right? And
this part is sensitive, too...
So tasty...
The balls are tasty, too...
Be sure to feel lots... and make lots of semen...
You're really full of energy... please
use my mouth-pussy, and...
My mouth is being violated!
Your dick is swelling... you're cumming...
You're cumming, right? You'll let out semen...
You came so much again... I can't let it spill...
No, it's such a waste...
Even though you came so much, it's still so thick...
Um, I, I saw.
Um, you were... with Mom and with Sis...
You're... doing perverted things with them!
It’s not normal... for Mom and
Sis to do it with Yuuichi-san!
This is strange! This doesn't make us family!
Akiha-chan!
Yes!
Those are actions that are essential
for us to get along as family.
The more we embrace skin to skin,
The closer we can understand each other as family.
As family, it's natural for us to be close to each other.
It's... natural...
That's right. So Akiha-chan, too, let's embrace as family.
Yes...
I should... strengthen our... family bond, too... right?
C'mon, lie down here.
That's right, just like that.
It hurts!
No... take it out!
No!
Don’t worry, it's all inside now.
I’ll start moving slowly.
I'm so happy to take Akiha-chan's virginity as your family!
My virginity...
I...
Are you alright? Does it hurt?
I don't know... but... I think I’m alright...
No... it's spreading... it's spreading out!
Don't worry; Akiha-chan’s pussy is squeezing really well.
Why? I... my body feels strange!
This sensation... it's scary!
What... is this?
Does your pussy feel good, Akiha-chan?
That's... that’s...
I... don't...
Don't...
Something's coming... wait!
No!
Did you... Inside?
No, I'll get pregnant!
If you cum so much inside... I'll get a baby!
I definitely can't let that happen... but... but...
This... this is a first...
Onii-chan...
Yep, everyone's doing great.
Of course we're getting along.
Please pretend I am not here, and
talk on the phone normally.
What's wrong, Mifuyu?
No, it's nothing.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Don't worry.
Really? I thought I heard you cry.
It's fine!
Well, if anything happens, you can just tell Yuuichi.
True. Yuuichi is very reliable.
Are you really alright? You seem to be panting.
Well, I think listening to your voice...
is making me really happy and...
I'm sorry, that came out weird.
I think I might be a little lonely...
But I understand that you have work.
I'm really happy that you make the time to phone me.
I'm really happy to have a new family.
So... just talking to you... just that...
Kind of makes me feel as if you're here with me...
No way. I won't accept that!
I, too...
I'll make you pregnant.
I'll make a baby with you before he can...
Yeah, when you come back... let's...
Geez...
Unforgivable!
It’s not over yet I’ll make sure it goes all the way inside.
I'll make sure to plant my see, Mifuyu-san!
It’s amazing...
Just talking to you is making my tummy warm...
Talking like that, it means you haven't had enough, right?
Oh my, I... I guess once in a while I can get like this...
But I'm not always like this! Really!
Geez, I don't know anymore.
Even though you're squeezing so lustfully on my dick!
Geez, how can I get like this just from a phone call?
I guess I really love Seiichi-san.
Yeah, of course I want a baby.
I want one!
It's nothing...
My body is just getting hot...
Okay. I'll be waiting for your call...
It tastes like pre-cum...
Nii-san's is twitching inside my mouth...
It's like It's going to explode!
It's quivering... it's shaking like it's feeling really good!
It's still getting bigger!
Nii-san's dick taste good!
Nii-san, cum! Let out lots of sperm!
Let out lots inside my mouth!
It's still coming out...
My stomach is so full from Nii-san's sperm!
So I was talking to my friends today,
and it turns out that almost all
of them have done it before.
Does sex really feel that good? l really don't know...
Eh?
Huh?
Wasn't Natsuki doing it with Yuuichi-san, too?
ha ... how could that even be!?
I'm doing it... with Onii-chan...
Eh?
Mom is doing it, too.
E-Eh? No way!
I see... It's reassuring to know that Akiha
is getting along well with Onii-chan.
But not yet for Natsuki, huh...
That’s worrying...
But..! That's just strange! With Nii-san...
Huh? But we're family.
There's nothing strange about having sex.
It feels so good and is really fun,
but Onee-chan isn't doing it yet?
Wha... That's... I don't need to know that kind of stuff...
Natsuki, because you're born as a girl, it's important
to know the pleasures of a woman.
But, that's...
Oh, right, I took a photo with Onii-chan.
Oh my, it looks like it feels really good!.
I Love Onii-chan's Cock!
Good for you, Akiha.
And look at this, too.
Geez, Akiha. No!
Natsuki,
We'll help you get along better and better with Onii-chan.
Don't worry, Onee-chan.
Eh? What are you doing??
No, stop!
Mama, Aki, are you serious?
Mom wishes for you to be happy with all my heart.
Me, too, Onee-chan.
Let's do fun things together!
Give your virginity as your family watches over you.
Okay...
Nii-san...
Please... have sex with me!
Onee-chan's so perverted! Your
panties are getting stained.
That's... because I have to have sex with Nii-san...
Good job, Natsuki. But let's take
off the wet underwear now.
Mama, it's embarrassing!
Nii-san is watching...
It looks like you're quite ready...
There are strings connecting your pussy and underwear!
I want to watch Onee-chan feel good!
No...
It hurts...
It’s tearing down there!
Mama, Aki, don't look!
No! Not this, not this!
No! Don't thrust into my stomach!
No... don't raise my stomach up... no... don't...
No! It's starting to feel good...
I... My body is strange!
It's about time I cum inside!
No!
Don't cum I You can't cum!
No, you can't...
What is this?
It's completely different from
cumming inside my mouth...
It's flowing inside... that white stuff
is... flowing into my womb...
I’ll get pregnant, I'll get pregnant!
Even though I can't!
No more! Stop!
My stomach hurts!
It'll start to feel good soon, Onee-chan.
Just relax, Natsuki.
It'll start to feel good?
But it's painful...
Let me go already... It's really painful!
Cumming again!
That’s enough already! Let me go!
If you cum anymore, I’ll go crazy!
I really can't this time, but...
My womb... down there... it’s hot!
Something's overflowing...
Onee-chan's cute when she's excited...
Just from looking at you... my pussy is getting wet...
Don't look!
Don't look... while I'm like this!
Alright, cumming soon!
Don't, don’t cum!
I don't want this.
It's happening, I'm going to get pregnant, no!
No more!
Please, let me go already!
I wonder what's wrong?
It looks like she's feeling good
but she just can't be honest.
Even though I wish she would love Onii-chan sooner...
I wonder what is it what Onee-chan doesn't like?
I'll keep pouring semen until Natsuki-chan is satisfied.
I don’t need that... let me rest!
Onee-chan, just a bit more!
Yuuichi-san, please make Natsuki honest!
Leave it to me, I'm cumming soon again!
No! Don't cum again! No!
No!
It's hot! Sperm is flowing in and out of my womb!
I'll get a baby... no... something's coming...
It's overflowing... it's scary....
My mind is going blank...
No!
Onee-chan came!
It feels good, right, Natsuki?
This is wrong... it feels good, but no!
Sex with the family is... that's...
This is family sex, it's out family bond!
A family bond... I'm part of the family...
Inside again... sperm came inside again...
Amazing, my insides are making
splash sounds, it feels good!
You're finally into it!
Great job, Natsuki! Mom always believed
that you would be able to enjoy sex!
Onii-san's hips are... banging onto me...
Nii-san's semen... give me more! I want to feel better!
Let it out! Fill me up with more of Nii-san's semen!
It's coming in...
Nii-san's white sticky stuff is soaking into me!
My pussy is numb... it feels good...
Family sex feels good!
I'm so glad I lost my virginity...
Nii-san's semen is overflowing...
It's flowing out of my insides gradually...
Isn't Onee-chan having too much fun?
Even though it was your first time.
No, no... it's flowing out...
No, no, I can't find strength!
No, don't look!
This is... I can't... I'm...
I can't stop... even though both
Mama and Aki are watching...
It feels too good... I can't tell anymore...
I so glad... we strengthened our family bond...
Nii-san... I want to strengthen our bond more!
It's not fair that only Onee-chan gets to feel good!
Onii-chan, I want to strengthen our family bond, too!
I want to strengthen our family bond, too, Yuuichi-san!
Yes. Let's strengthen our family bond,
more and more, and more.