The six of us got to know each other online only by chance.
We went to a hot spring resort in N prefecture for an orgy.
Well then, shall we have some self-introductions first?
My name is Miyamoto Sana.
I'm Kogure Chika!
Tazawa Anko!
squishy
The Busty High School Girls are all squishy and are
having a kinky sex with middle-aged men's dicks.
The Busty High School Girls are all squishy
I wonder how I can seduce him?
and are having a kinky sex with middle-aged men's dicks.
The Case of Mr. H.Y.
The Academic Staff (59)
and Miyamoto Sana
If I remember correctly,
aren't you the student council
vice president, Miyamoto-kun?
Principal's Office
I want to consult you about
something today, Mr. Principal.
Principal's Office
Umm... Before that, sensei...
Haven't you been ogling at
my body for a while now?
No... That's not it, Miyamoto-kun.
Y-You see, this is...
Should I let you see down here as well?
Y-You shouldn't act sloppily like that!
Isn't your underwear showing?
It looked like you wanted to see so I did it.
Should I close my legs?
O-O-Of course.
C-Come on, let's go back to what
you want to consult me about.
Understood.
I've been busy with student council activities
and I've been missing my gymnastics training.
But...
Joining in both was my own choice
so I don't want to neglect either one of them...
That's right! Excuse me for a second.
My body already got rigid due to lack of practice.
My hip joints are all stiff now.
May I trouble you a little and
help me do some stretching?
Huh? Wh-What should I do?
Press around my inner thighs with your finger.
W-Will it be fine?
Please do so.
Sensei, hurry up!
I-Is it around here?
Not there, move it more to the left!
Left?
Yeah, you went over it.
Move it a little more to the right.
Wh-When you said right...
R-Right here?
There, right there.
Sensei, you're being gentle...
Your finger alone
might not be enough for me.
I need something thicker than a
finger... Something hard and hot...
Sensei, don't you have one like that with you?
And then, please recklessly thrust it
and keep rubbing it rapidly inside me!
Sensei...
That feels good!
P-Please, I'm already...
I'm coming! It feels good!
I'm coming—!
After that, I forgot both the time and my position.
I kept banging her.
Of course, I held myself back from doing creampies.
But needless to say, it is the best sex I had in my life.
Mr. Principal!
Amazing!
Shoot it out! Please shoot it out!
Shoot me lots of it!
Sensei...
The Case of Mr. S.T.
The Salaryman (52)
and Kogure Chika
It was at that time when my niece Chika-chan
was giving me a massage.
Heave-ho!
Chika-chan, you're good at this!
Aren't I?
I've been wanting to give you
a massage for a while now!
Oh, but should I really be taking off my clothes?
Don't you feel creeped out by my body?
Ehh... There's no way I'll think of you that way.
I knew you since I was little.
You're astounding and reliable.
That makes me happy...
Hi-ya!
This is dangerous!
Ch-Chika-chan's butt crack is exactly over my crotch!
Heave-ho, heave-ho!
Th-This is bad! I'm feeling pleasure...
Huh?
Ahh... Did your dick get big?
No... Y-You see, this is...
Uncle, you perv...
S-Sorry...
Does it feel good when I do this?
Uncle, your dick is hitting me down there.
It feels so hot!
It's hard...
Uncle, do you want to have sex with me?
I can't be wanting to have sex
with a girl as old as my own child!
But it is my fault that your dick became like this
I'm fine if it'll only be the tip.
Uncle, your dick got all twitchy.
I'll feel sorry for it if we leave it like that.
If you'll only put the tip inside a little bit...
Will you make do with that much?
Ch-Chika-chan!
Uncle, I'll massage your dick as well!
How is it? Are you feeling good?
The tip is nibbling inside me!
You got bigger!
Ch-Chika-chan!
You went all the way deep inside!
Even though you said that you can't!
Let's go all the way from here, okay?
Gosh... Uncle, you perv!
Uncle, you're sucking on my breast!
I feel weird, I'm starting to feel weird!
If you do any more than this, I'm...
Just from my breast... I'm gonna
come just from my breast...
After that, just as anyone would guess...
I kept pounding the pussy of a girl
that I treated like my own daughter.
In the end,
I'm nothing but a stud after all.
I love cuddling!
More, more!
Uncle, your cock feels good!
Uncle, I love you a lot!
The Case of Mr. K.N.
The Academic Staff (51)
and Tazawa Anko
Sensei, what are you doing
in front someone else's butt?
You put your face close to my ass,
and then you intently stare while gasping.
Are you giving me extra lessons alone
so you can to get a good look at my body?
Y-You're wrong!
Sensei, you've always been
habitually looking at my body.
You were pretty obvious about it.
Th-That's because you always act so defenseless!
Hey, sensei!
Do you want to do it with me for real?
I'm fine with doing it if you can meet my condition.
C-Condition?
If your dick has a size
way bigger than anything I ever saw,
then you can do as you wish to my body.
Look, it's suffocating in your pants!
I'll take it out for you!
Hey, wait!
Wow! What's this, sensei? Isn't this so huge?
I might end up having sex with you!
Here, look! Want me to lick your penis?
I'm gonna roll my tongue like this.
Today's extra lessons will be a long one.
Sensei's cock... Such a huge cock!
Sensei, does this feel good?
Thanks for the meal!
I want this huge cock inside me next, okay?
I had the sex that I even dream about
with my huge-busted student.
I pleasured that far well-developed body despite her age.
As I dominate her body,
it felt like I reached heaven.
Sensei, you're incredible!
It feels good when you suck on my tits!
More... More!
It's reaching my deepest parts!
I'm gonna be your woman.
So I want you to spray me a lot!
I never had anything like this before!
I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
You're the best, sensei...
The six of us got to know each other online only by chance.
We went to a hot spring resort in N prefecture for an orgy.
Well,
we're about to start a fun celebration.
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization