Nice weather, isn't it, Morishita-kun?
Shirakawa-sensei is as beautiful as ever.
So I, um, have something to tell you...
You see, I...
Is she going to confess to me?!
I got married.
I've been dating this guy for a while
Shirakawa Miwa
In charge of : Modern Japanese
She is a teaching assistant for Public
Relation and now newly married. She
wants children with her husband, but she
has so far been left unsatisfied by him.
and we finally submitted
the paperwork for marriage.
We haven't decided on a date for the official
ceremony yet, but on paper, we're legally married...
Hypnotizing Busty, Married Female Teachers
Creating Sex Addicts With a Cell Phone App!
#1 Kyoko and Miwa
Hypnosis App
Installation Complete
OFF
Sheesh! Morishita-kun, are you listening?
Oh, yeah. Congratulations.
Hypnosis App.
Give your target a command.
ON
What the heck is this?
A prank at a time like this?
S-Sensei?
Yes?
This isn't a prank... is it?
W-We're married, aren't we, Miwa?
What possessed you to say that
all of a sudden? Of course we are...
Miwa!
We're at school right now!
Regardless of that, it's normal for a married
couple to play around like this, isn't it?
You do have a point...
Wataru-kun, you're already so hard!
You're already dripping wet too, aren't you?
Oh, wow. It's gotten so big!
Your dick is so hot!
Miwa, it feels too good! I'm gonna...
No, you can't!
I want it inside me.
Give me your dick.
Miwa...
It's entering me!
Oh my god, it's so big!
This is amazing!
Your insides are convulsing like crazy!
No! My boobs are really sensitive!
You're already this wet after
just giving me a handjob...
You dirty girl.
I can't help it. When I really want
to do it with the person I like,
my body just reacts like this!
I'm going to cum inside you now, okay?
Your dick is so intense!
Cum inside me! Give me your newlywed cum!
Here I go! Take it all in!
It's going so deep inside!
It's making me tingle all over!
I really want a child.
I can't believe I've gotten into this kind
of relationship with Shirakawa-sensei.
Hypnosis App
Give your target a command.
ON
I can do anything with this app.
Student Guidance Room
Morishita-kun?
Your attitude in class is horrible.
It looked like you were playing around
with your phone on some app or something.
Tsukishima Kyoko
In charge of : Math
Teacher in charge of Public
Relations. Married. She's only
had sex with her husband.
Since her husband is very
fickle with sex, she's never
been satisfied.
It doesn't seem like you understand
what position you're in at all.
– I'm telling you this for the sake of your future.
– Even the teacher that everyone fears, Kyoko-sensei...
– Why won't you focus in class?
– With this hypnosis app, I can...
Hey, are you listening?!
Seriously, from now on, just...
Hypnosis App.
Sensei, do you think that I'm a burden to the school?
Yes.
No matter what I do,
there's no change from you.
Don't you think you're part of the problem?
I... do...
If you bring those huge knockers into class,
of course I'm going to get distracted!
I'm in puberty, after all.
Okay, I understand.
How's this?
It's perfect, sensei!
And now, If you'll excuse me...
So you're weak when it comes to pleasure, huh?
Th-That's not...
How does it feel to have your nipples sucked on?
It feels great!
It makes my pussy tingle.
Then let's get into the main course
the pussy of this slutty married woman.
You're wrapping around me so tightly!
You're not used to this?
I only started having sex after I got married!
You're such a pure woman.
When was the last time
you and your husband had sex?
Just this morning!
How's my dick feel compared to his?
It's a lot better than my husband's!
It'll feel even better when I cum inside you!
Wait, you can't. You can't cum inside me.
This is all so that you can become a better teacher.
You'll let me cum inside you, won't you?
You're right.
Okay then, cum all you want into your teacher's pussy!
Here I go, Kyoko!
Okay, gather around everyone.
Today we will be observing
Tsukishima-sensei's mouth work,
that is, her fellatio, first hand.
Fellatio is when you caress a penis, right?
It is an act that provides a different type
of arousal than regular sexual activities.
In it, one can directly feel the desire to service the man.
Shirakawa-sensei, "penis" is a bit
hard to wrap my mind around.
Could you use "cock" instead?
Oh, is that so?
My apologies.
So, after getting the c-cock wet,
you swallow it like this.
When you do this yourself, do it like Tsukishima-sensei,
using your tongue to find sensitive spots.
Taking in the majority of the cock
like she's doing is called "deep throating".
Oh, I can't hold it in!
Some males, like Morishita-kun, will move your head
by themselves when they're about to cum.
That kind of rough play makes me jealous.
Sensei, I'm cumming!
And after he's done cumming, you open your mouth...
Let him see the cum and then thank him.
Thank you very much!
Master, your cock worked very hard today.
There isn't a single person in this school
who isn't under my hypnotism.
They'll all listen to whatever I tell them to do.
Master, please be sure to shove your big,
hard cock inside me, okay?
Please spray me with your hot cum!
I wonder if they'll let me get them pregnant.
Please look at our pussies.
They want your cock so badly!
They're totally drenched!
Master, my pussy has even hotter liquids
coming out! It's just waiting for your cock!
It's ready for you.
In that case, I guess the first one will be...
Oh, Master!
Master, this is amazing!
Your cock is making my slutty pussy make
such dirty noises! It can't get enough of it!
Your cock is so intense!
Thank you, Master! Thank you so much!
Wow, your cock is almost hitting my womb! It's so close!
I'm so jealous.
Please let me have my turn soon, okay?
No, not my nipples!
My nipples and pussy feel so good!
Are you ready to get pregnant?
Yes, I'm ready to be impregnated.
Please pump your baby juices
into this slutty slave of yours!
Kyoko, I'm gonna...
It's coming! It's coming!
I can feel your cum filling up my womb!
I'm definitely going to get pregnant!
Please unload your baby-making
fluids deep into my pussy!
Your cock is inside me!
How does my pussy feel?
It wants to get pregnant so badly! It's soaking wet!
If you really want to get pregnant,
you'll have to beg more than that!
Get it deep inside me! If you shoot all of it
right in there, I'll definitely get pregnant!
Please! Your hot, sticky semen! I want it!
If you get pregnant, you'll have to tell
everyone at school, won't you?
Yes, I will! I promise to become your cum dumpster
in front of all my beloved students!
Please give me your semen!
I can feel something amazing coming!
I'm cumming!
Wow, there's so much...
It tastes so good...
Hypnosis App.
Today, we will be introducing our husband Morishita
Wataru's sock, which he used to make us pregnant.
His cock is so big and hard, and he
gives it to us no matter where we are.
It's truly amazing.
He cums so much for us, too.
Our Master's cocks tip quivers at
even our slightest touch. It's so cute!
Is your cock at its limit?
It's because you're doing it
in front of all these students.
Are you about to cum?
Please cum all over these dirty sluts.
Let's have your cum come out to say hello.
I'm cumming!
Wow, I feel like I'm going to get pregnant again!
Semen...
Nobody can oppose me in this school.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fuyrie
quality control: fyurie