We're holding physicals today.
We need to see if Ikenoue-kun's ejaculation is healthy or not.
Kichijoji Arisa
Fukinaga Koharu
Kamizumi Rio
Kamizumi-san?
Huh? I have to?
Fukunaga-san?
Y-Yes! I'll do my best.
It's so hard. It's so full of energy.
We'll see if you can cum or not.
It's getting even bigger!
Does it feel good being rubbed like this?
It's getting kind of slippery.
It's getting super hot too.
Hey, Koharu, you're making your nipples touch mine!
No, I'm not doing it on purpose!
Ikenoue-kun's dick has been twitching tor a while now...
It came out!
There's so much healthy cum.
It's just overflowing.
So whose boobs felt better?
Let me see... If I had to choose one, I
guess I'd go with Koharu's huge tits.
Hey, that's not fair!
As a reward, I'll cum right in your pussy for you.
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
You're already this wet after barely doing anything?
You really have a dirty pussy, Koharu.
Your dick... Let my dirty pussy drink its cum!
There's so much baby milk inside me now.
Young, Big Titty Girls MC Academy
# 2 Fall of the Empress
What, you need something from me at this time of night?
I-I need your cum!
Hurry and give me your cum!
Without my cum, her body gets
so hot and turned on with no end.
It was just a simple order under hypnosis,
but it looks like it's paying off big.
If you want something, isn't it common
sense for you to bow your head and beg?
Are you telling me to grovel?
Yeah, cum is pretty valuable after all.
You'll let me drink your cum as long as I grovel, right?
P-Please.
I want the thick cum from your huge dick.
I can't stop the throbbing. I want it so bad.
P-Please grace me with your sacred cum!
Guess I got no choice.
Your dick...
Pardon me.
Cum! Cum!
Hurry! Cum!
Hurry!
Don't worry, with the way you're sucking, I'll...
If you like it that much, I'll give you a second helping.
Arisa, your blowjobs are the best!
That doesn't matter, just...
More!
You came from just that? Looks like we got
another helplessly perverted girl on our hands.
You understand, don't you?
When I get control of my body
again I'll make sure you pay for this.
I've been mind controlling all of you this entire time.
But when you see my face,
you'll gain awareness that I've been mind controlling you,
but you won't be able to move your bodies.
No! What's going on?!
It's getting noisy in here.
This is an important demonstration of semen
extraction, so stand there and watch silently.
I'm going to make Ikenoue-kun cum with my boobs.
Wh-Why are you doing such a dirty thing...
M-My body won't move!
Wh-What did he do to us?!
What's dirty about this?
For making a male cum, it's natural to use not only
your pussy, but your boobs and mouth as well.
This isn't right! Come to your senses, Kuga-san!
Even boobs can act as a magnificent pussy.
A boob job can be just as effective as a pussy.
Yuriko, give them a good look at your blowjob!
Ikenoue-kun, what are you doing?
Understood. Then please allow me to use my mouth.
Why does she look so happy?
Maybe they're both crazy.
They're messed up.
We've got some harsh comments.
I guess seeing a member of the disciplinary
committee sucking a guy's dick like this
would throw anyone off though.
This dick...
She's doing it like that? She makes it look so tasty though.
Everyone's getting into the mood
thanks to your blowjob, Yuriko!
People on the disciplinary committee
just are a cut above the rest, huh?
You're about ready to cum and let me swallow your cum, right?
Don't hold back. Just let me drink your dick milk!
So good.
Yuriko, you really are the best!
I think you were a pretty good example for them.
I'm being covered in cum.
He came. He really did.
Kuga-san really took it like that.
And she actually looks so happy.
Do you understand now?
If you can take in cum like this, you
can fulfill both your mind and body.
Don't forget your grace as a lady
like myself when doing it though.
We still have time, how about we show them
how to get cum right into their wombs too.
You want my pussy? You don't even have to ask.
I'll drink your cum with my aroused pussy.
No wonder you're called the slut of the disciplinary committee.
You're just too dirty!
It seems that your dick is ready to go!
Your pussy is drenched! You have the best pussy, Yuriko!
Of course. This isn't something you
need to be praising me about now.
R-Right there... It's rubbing against my insides...
It's coming in so deep!
I can feel your huge dick getting close to my womb!
Your huge dick makes my pussy feel so good!
I can't get enough!
It feels so good when you thrust your dick into me!
Having sex like this with your dick
rubbing me so hard feels so good!
You need to try more and fuck my pussy harder!
Yes! That's it! Hit me deep inside!
Twist me and mix me up inside!
I'll make my pussy tighter and squeeze out all that cum for you!
Your dick is so deep!
It's going so deep, it's making my pussy go crazy!
The way it's rubbing me inside...
I love it!
I'm about to...
That's right. You want to cum, right?
That's fine. Let it all out.
Let it out in my womb. Shoot it out into my fertile slutty pussy!
Your cum is shooting out inside me!
It's the cum you've been waiting for!
Get a good taste of it with your womb!
It's coming inside me!
There's so much cum flowing into my aroused pussy!
My pussy is cumming. It's climaxing from your cum.
No! If we don't plug it up, it's going to come out.
What a waste.
You're pretty greedy, huh? How about another go?
Okay. Leave it to me. I'll take it all.
Kichijoji-san?
Do you recognize this music box?
Why do you have that?!
My body won't move!
Stay away from me!
No!!
You lowlife!
I can't believe you're this low! You're worse than trash!
Yeah and you love having sex with this trash.
Are you serious?
You won't get away with doing this!
Well this isn't our first time, you know?
So loosen up a bit.
You're gonna love it soon anyway.
No! That's disgusting! If you go any farther, I won't forgive you!
It's still kinda tight.
I might need to loosen you up again.
No! Take it out!
Don't worry. I'm gonna make myself feel
good and take my cum out inside you!
Stop spouting nonsense...
Once it feels good you can moan as loudly as you want!
I refuse!
Your mouth might say no, but your pussy
is being pretty honest about what it wants.
That's just a natural biological reaction!
Don't interpret it with your warped mind...
I'll make you regret doing this!
Oh that's scary. Then I guess I gotta
take this chance to get you pregnant.
Huh? Wait! Please don't cum inside me!
I'll never forgive you!
You can't cum inside me!
No! Please!
You say that, but your pussy is gripping me
hard, getting ready to take my cum inside.
No, it's not!
There's no way...
No! No!
I don't want it inside, but... it feels good!
No!
It's inside me!
I'm gonna get pregnant. I'm gonna have a baby!
Come on take a look at your face after cumming!
Don't you look happy, Arisa?
No! I... You're a horrible person.
No! Keep that hot stuff away from me.
– I'm gonna cum!
– You gotta say what exactly is cumming!
No... My pussy's gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!
It's getting tighter. Your greedy pussy is
getting so many rewards out of my dick.
Isn't that enough?
You've already cummed so much!
I'm gonna go crazy...
Please let me go.
Stop your dick! Don't cum again!
I'm gonna let your womb drink lots of
my cum so you can get pregnant, okay?
N-No...
It feels too good...
So much... in my pussy...
Good morning everyone.
I'm the new Headmaster, Ikenoue.
I'd like all of you to grow into wonderful
ladies, as well as become my slaves,
who will be willing to take in my cum at any time or any place.
Don't be deceived!
This man is brainwashing you with a vile method!
There's no way that scum like him could be our headmaster!
Oh my, what seems to be the matter, Kichijoji-san?
This isn't like you.
Well then everyone, watch closely as the more
experienced girls show you how a slave should act.
No! Stop!
Stop it right now, Yuriko!
No!
There's something wrong with all of you!
Don't worry Arisa.
He'll help you know the pleasure of being a woman.
The headmaster's dick is so hard.
No! Stop!
This is messed up!
You'll feel even better if you give in.
Arisa, your pussy is crying tears of joy.
No! Stop! I'm gonna...
I love... cum...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч