Kyonyuu Dosukebe Gakuen
( Busty Naughty Academy )
The Unstoppable Hip Shaking of Virgin Women
Volume Two: Aim for the Harem Ending!
He might be even cuter than us.
Let's stop this now.
Delete it already.
Even though you're just a boy...
Even though you're just a boy!
Hoah!
You are not a cute girl!
Th-That hurts, Rune-chan!
You should be gentle.
You're the one to talk!
I'm gonna console him.
H-Huh—?!
Wanna see my tits?
W-Wow...
You're reacting on Tama's breasts, dammit!
I'll show you that mine is better.
Here you go, here you go! Don't they feel good?
Shou-kun, you're amazing down there!
Here you go.
You're good at this, Shou-kun!
Her tits feel incredible to grope!
Shou-kun, suck them!
Oh, you're just like a baby!
You like being treated this way, huh?
Rune-chan!
You're squealing like a girl!
I'm starting to get in the mood now!
Shou-kun, lick my groin.
Shou-kun, you have a knack for this!
That's good, Shou-kun—!
I'm gonna rub you more down here, okay?
It's like you're weeping pre-cum
in pleasure down here!
Let's stop this already!
Shou-kun, no slacking!
That's good, Shou-kun!
Try to squirt it between my breasts!
I'm gonna watch it too!
Shou-kun, you're so cute!
I'm gonna come too!
Even though you're an effeminate soy boy,
you're reeking of an incredibly hunky scent!
Shou-kun, your juice is amazing!
What's wrong, Tama?
I'm so in the mood right now!
H-Huh—?!
Oh, it moved!
I wonder if it wants to go inside me...
Tama-chan, let's stop it here. Okay?
No, I'm already horny!
Horny... No way...
Let's have sex, Shou-kun!
I think it's a little bit tight...
Tama-chan, you don't have to force yourself...
Hey, are you serious?
Gosh... Everyone looks down
on me like that all the time!
This is no big deal for me...
D-Doesn't it hurt?
It's hitting against my important place!
I'll graduate from being a virgin
when you come a lot inside me, right?
I knew that it's gonna turn out like this...
You're a nice guy so you're
gonna help me on this, right?
Have sex with me, okay?
Make yourself feel good a lot inside me, okay?
Your dick is getting wild inside me!
Tama-chan, you're moving too much!
My body is starting to feel hotter!
I don't think that I can stop my hips!
Having sex so easily like that...
Shou-kun, isn't sex fun?
I'll end up coming inside you
if you keep doing it that much!
Well, you're a boy... Of course,
you want to come inside me!
Shou-kun, here comes your semen!
It feels so thick and hot...
So this is how semen feels like...
I got coerced into sex again.
Do it with me too.
R-Rune-chan?
I'll give you my virginity.
Y-You're asking for the impossible!
I can't do this anymore...
Huh? Then how do you explain that?
Th-This is just a physiological
response, not a will for...
I'll spread this around.
N-No way...
Shouta... Man up and come here.
Do it already!
Here you go. It's gonna be
easier when I do this, right?
So this is how being penetrated by a cock feels!
Are you alright?
Push the whole thing deep inside!
S-Stop that!
You look hurt, so...
Don't mind that and push it inside me already!
R-Rune-chan?
Make sure to come inside me and
make me graduate from virginity!
Do I really have to do that?
Isn't that obvious?
My insides are getting molded up into your shape!
Are you trying to be gentle on
me because it's my first time?
That's because...
Stop doing unnecessary stuff!
I'll stroke you a lot using my pussy,
so you should come already!
My mind is going blank!
My hips won't stop!
A weird feeling is welling up
inside me as I move my hips!
R-Rune-chan, you're being too reckless!
Can you feel it? It's my womb, you know!
Your womb?
How is it? It feels very good, right?
Are you alright?
Stop looking at me!
You look very cute right now, Rune-chan!
Don't go thrusting in my pussy
while saying stuff like that!
Rune-chan, could it be...
I-It's not like I'm feeling good from
your cock or anything, okay?
W-We can't do it like this!
It's just my first time having sex...
You're pulling me up and directly pouring it inside!
Aren't you glad that you got to have sex with me?
You moaned like crazy as well, Rune-chan.
Th-There's no way that I'll get so
absorbed having sex with you, Shouta.
That's right... I'm sorry.
Come on, let's go home when Tama wakes up.
I can't understand how a girl's mind works...
What's the matter?
I was just a little tired.
This will recharge you.
Thanks.
You look pale. Are you alright?
I've been through a lot...
Shou-chan, what do you want me to do?
Shou-chan, you're so cute but
you have such a thick semen!
Keep thrusting a lot and come plenty inside me!
Make yourself feel good a lot inside me, okay?
Shouta... Man up and come here.
It looks like Nao-chan is different
from the other three girls.
Nao-chan, why did you come here to my house...
Nao-chan...
Oh, you're awake.
What are you doing?!
Preparation for sex.
It should only be done with a loved one!
Even though you did it with the other three?
You won't do it with me?
I want to have sex.
You should take a better care of yourself.
I understand.
Huh?! Wait...
Don't you like my breasts?
But...
Try putting it between them.
It feels so soft!
I can tell how hot your dick is right now.
It's like you're having sex with my breasts.
Your dick is swelling up.
It's alright, splatter it within my breasts!
Wow, it's like my tits are being impregnated!
You can lick them.
You're lapping the entrance!
So you want to do this as well, Shouta-kun.
It's arching backwards in my mouth.
Shouta-kun is getting into this
now. Then, I should do the same.
I'll do this and stimulate all of them!
Nao-chan—!
I can tell how much you're feeling good right now!
Try stimulating the beanlike
protrusion at the far end.
That's a woman's weak point.
Make sure to remember that, okay?
I'm about to come again!
It's alright, shoot out a lot!
Thanks for the meal!
I'm about to have sex for the first time.
It makes me feel so excited.
Here we go.
Huh, wait for a sec...
You're hitting my hymen.
I can tell how your male genital
is being stimulated inside me!
Nao-chan...
You're pushing up against my cervix!
Stop moving already! I'll end up coming!
This can't be called sex
unless you ejaculate, right?
This is kind of tough... I wonder if I'm doing it right?
You're doing it now, so isn't that enough already?
Nao-chan, don't do that!
When a man says "don't",
he means "more". Am I right?
Where did you learn something like that?!
Your dick goes in and out.
Doesn't sex feel wonderful?
I think I can understand now why
everyone is smitten with it!
Your dick is throbbing! It's alright...
Shoot a lot of it deep inside me!
Shouta-kun, you're coming!
This might be bad... My feminine
instincts are being triggered!
The sex was a success... Thank you...
I graduated from virginity all thanks to you.
Y-Yeah...
I'll depend on you from today onwards.
I want to try different things.
Huh?
I wonder how we should do it next time...
I got coerced into sex again.
Even though I want to do it with someone I love...
Oh, I should just fall in love with someone in the club.
But if it turned out that all of them love me,
I wonder if it'll be okay even if
I'm unable to choose one?
So, which one will you go after?
Reika-chan, who's headstrong
but gets bewildered in sex...
Nao-chan, who's usually
composed but reckless in sex...
Tama-chan, who looks cute at a first glance but has an abnormally high sex drive...
Rune-chan, who becomes docile in sex...
Every one of them is adorable...
I'm at a loss on which one to go after.
You're cheeky, considering how
you snivel like a baby in sex.
That's right, I'm cheeky...
R-Reika-chan!
Haven't you gone quite far
with that fantasy of yours?
Shou-kun, let's play!
Don't get cocky just because I let you do it once.
Were you planning to have all of us
in the palm of your hand?
That's...
That's not true at all...
I'll forgive you, then.
Thank you.
Did you really think that I will?
I-I'm sorry!
You...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization