Sex is an important type of skinship for our family.
Ever since Yuuichi-kun became a new part of our family...
Me, my daughter, Natsuki,
And my other daughter, Akiha...
And now even my little sister Haruka...
We're all so much closer to each other now.
But out of nowhere, people have started gossiping about us.
And so, Yuuichi-kun took his pen light
and put them under his suggestion.
For Nanae-san, he made it so that her breasts
and mouth became as sensitive as her pussy.
And now lit looks like she's head
over heels for him from the pleasure.
And then for our neighbor, Yachiyo-san, he made
it so that she practiced child making with him.
It was so that she could take the lead and
motivate her husband to have sex with her.
Yachiyo-san is the type of person who gives everything
her all, so she just kept cumming and cumming.
But I think you came too much in her, onii-chan.
This is the house.
But now, we have the Chairman of the City
Committee, Ruiko-san knocking on our door.
I wonder what Yuuichi-kun will do about this.
Big titted big family hypnotism
I can't stop having sex with my family, so
good, that there's no end to the cumming
#2 Getting my hands on all the women in the town!
So to be frank, I've heard numerous salacious rumors
about you and your family from residents in the area.
If this continues any longer, I'll
be forced to take you to court.
Excuse me, miss Chairman...
Yes?
Look closely at the light.
You are one of the elite women of this town.
Even when it comes to sex, you are top tier.
I'm an elite?
So why don't you prove that to me
by giving me a little lesson in sex?
Alright then.
This is just part of my job as the
Chairman of the City Council.
This is...
What do you plan on doing by having me in this position?
You want this, don't you, Ruiko-san?
Look how happy you're getting right here.
Stop... moving your finger inside me there.
I-If you keep being that rough...
I-I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum with my ass!
My asshole feels so good!
I'm gonna cum!
Is this your first time doing anal?
Looks like you're feeling it pretty good.
This is exactly what I expected from
the elite Chairman of the City Council.
No! Don't move!
I-It's rubbing...
And I-It's shoving against me so hard!
Come on, let's give the neighbors a little peek.
No...
We can't...
Please, nobody notice!
Don't look!
Nobody look!
My ass... My ass is...
It feels so good!
I-It's driving me crazy!
I'm losing my mind!
I feel so weak, I can't move my body!
I'm gonna cum!
This is so intense... I'm gonna cum!
Don't fuck me any harder than this.
I... I can't...
I'm gonna...
No!
No!!
That was a great lesson.
This is why you're the Chairman of the City Council.
Even your asshole was top tier.
I look forward to more of these lessons.
We were able to get them off our backs this
time, but what if this happens again, nii-san?
Apparently rumors about us are
spreading outside this neighborhood too.
Well, now that it's come to this,
I guess I'll have to go all out.
And saying that, Yuuichi-kun made his way
around town, putting people underthis suggestion.
And then he planned a special event in the Spring festival.
This is so embarrassing...
This Happi doesn't hide my nipples at all.
This is amazing. Everyone's watching!
Everyone can see how my the cloth is riding up my ass!!
In order to give a boost to the prosperity of this town, the
ladies standing on this stage tonight, including myself,
will be performing a sex ritual with the deity of prosperity.
Why am I involved in this?
Having sex in front of people...
I'm a mother of three!
What should I do if my classmates see me?
B-But we need to do our best for the sake of our family.
Okay, lord deity...
The festival won't end until you've
satisfied the women on this stage.
I'm just rubbing it with my boobs, but...
It feels so... It feels so good!
Our boobs and mouths are basically our pussy now.
Oh no, I can't get enough!
More... I want your dick to screw me more!
Me too!
I want it too!
I want your dick!
Please lord deity, you should cum too.
We'll cum with our boob-pussies too!
We're cumming!
What's going on?
My boobs are tingling so much!
I put your boobs under a special suggestion, Nanae-san.
I'm not pregnant, but I'm...
I'm letting out so much milk, I can't stop!
I'm cumming!
You're going to milk me dry!
Lord deity, please come deep inside me!
Please fill me with your seed in front of all these people!
It's so hot... It's so hot!
I'm cumming!!
Th-That's good.
Harder... Do me harder!
Today, I want you to make sure
that you make my pussy cum!
I'm going to become an elite at sex too!
Come on, just a little more.
After I cum, I'll let you cum with me!
Nii-san, I can't believe you're this
hard with all these people watching.
B-But I think I'm turned on even more than usual!
I'm going to cum in front of all
these people from his tongue!
Me too... I can't stop my hips from moving!
His dick's so hot... It's so hot!
Oh, lord deity!
This is amazing... You're so intense!
Your huge dick is rubbing against both of us!
It feels too good... I'm starting to feel weird!
Together... Let's cum together!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!!
My ass...
My asshole, it's... It's gonna break!
It's gonna break!
You say that, but look how wet your pussy's getting.
Nee-san?! That's...
If this keeps up, I'm gonna...
My ass... I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
No, I can't anymore.
My pussy and my ass... everything is...
No...
No!!
You're gonna get me pregnant!
Is that such a bad thing?
I might be pregnant with nii-san's child too.
I think it'd be great to have a bigger family.
Do your best, Mom!
I...
I want your child, Yuuichi-kun!
Please... together!
Let's cum together!
All women who wanted to be blessed by
the lord deity joined him in sexual harmony.
May the town be blessed with great prosperity.
Now, lord deity...
Please give us your blessings!
The festival's only just getting started...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч