Shiratori Academy.
The girls that attend there are what
society labels as "high-class ladies".
Wow, the bear is pregnant!
Hey, you're over doing it,
Though that's only from the outside, just as you can see.
Ladies Club
So the rumor that this club was established
for them to be able to play with boys was true.
Ladies Club
Ah-ah... It's your fault, Tama!
That's because he makes a very cute
moan when I play with his dick.
We have to find a replacement for him immediately.
Hey, do we really have to
hurry ourselves and find one?
Of course!
What will we do if people find out that
we're virgins despite toying with boys?
Huh, virgins?
Welcome to the Ladies Club
Kyonyuu Dosukebe Gakuen
( Busty Naughty Academy )
The Unstoppable Hip Shaking of Virgin Women
Volume One: The Secret of the Ladies Club
Umm...
So, you heard it...
If you meant stuff up to the "virgins" part...
I-I'm sorry, I won't tell anyone about it!
I-I wonder what will happen to me...
Ladies Club Application Form
Prove to us that you'll keep our secret.
What will happen if I don't?
Good job!
Welcome to the Ladies Club, Higashi Shouta-kun.
I'm Umesawa Rune. Nice to meet you!
Kusuda Nao.
Shinohara Tamaki, you can just call me Tama.
I'm Segawa Reika, the club president.
We address each other by first names
in this club. My regards, Shouta.
Huh? It's pretty normal unlike how I thought...
Ladies Club
So, can I go now?
Whoa! Wh-What's up?
It's our club activity.
Huh?
Sex.
If we want to continue...
We will finish what we were doing to you instead.
These girls aren't normal!
This is bad, I'm in danger!
Then, shall we begin?
Let me go back already.
It's a rule for male members to follow our orders.
That's coercion.
I'm gonna pull it out now.
Wait, stop!
It's much bigger than I thought.
It might get even better if it gets fully erected.
Should we try making it big?
I'll show you this today as a special occasion.
This is amazing!
I'm taking a picture.
Welcome to the Ladies Club
Will these look good on Instagram?
Stop playing with it!
We ran out of time.
S-Stop that...
You really are such a cutie!
This is so mean!
To think that someone this cute is actually a boy.
Oh my, you're aroused.
I'm just nervous!
You're just like a girl!
You're so cute but you got such a nasty dick.
Shou-chan, what do you want me to do?
I'm gonna lick your girly dick, Shouta!
You're so adorable, Shou-chan!
Stop calling me that!
You're the female Shou-chan whenever
you wear that and do lewd things with us.
No, stop!
No can do! I won't stop until you come.
Maybe deeper...
My dick will turn weird!
That's such a cute wailing!
How should I squeeze it next?
It feels like your dick is about to burst!
So these two made lots of semen!
You're gonna come while
looking all messed up like this!
I'm gonna observe your lewd face, Shou-chan!
You're a good girl, Shou-chan!
His semen is gushing out!
I'm going to suck the tip dry as well!
Shou-chan, you're so cute but
you have such a thick semen!
I can finally relax!
I welcomed myself inside.
Hey, you're being too loud!
Wh-Why?!
I went out of my way just to
come here. Be more grateful!
Th-That hurts!
So, why did you come here?
Hoah—!
We're going to have sex!
We can't, even if you're just playing around.
I'll be done before you count
all the stains in the ceiling!
You should only do it with someone you love.
Looks like this one down here says otherwise.
Just shut up and lend me your dick!
Th-Then, I'm putting it in.
You don't have to force yourself...
This is nothing to me!
Can you feel it? That's my hymen.
A-Alright already!
Have a good taste of my hymen!
I don't want to lose my virginity
just from being played with!
So you've been protecting it?
Then, I'll let you off since I feel sorry for you.
Thank goodness...
Just kidding.
I lied.
My first time...
I popped your cherry, Shouta!
Th-Then, we're done.
Huh?! We're doing this until you come!
You make such a feminine voice!
You're so huge.
Just moving around is difficult for me!
Isn't that enough?!
Come deep inside my pussy, then
I'll graduate from being a virgin!
You're reaching up to the entrance of my womb!
I'll start to do it harder now!
Keep thrusting a lot and come plenty inside me!
I don't want to give you a creampie!
I'll definitely make you do so...
My womb is opening up from
being repeatedly poked on!
Your dick is convulsing! You're close, huh?
I now graduated from my virginity with this.
For me to lose my virginity from being reverse-raped...
She's a beauty when she's all quiet.
I should let him see my manly side to make her behave!
Alright, I'm doing this!
Shouta...
I'm still safe.
Sh-Shouta?! What are you doing?
Penetrating a sleeping woman...
Just how preposterous can you get!
I'm not letting you have your way anymore!
So you want me to submit by
making me climax before you do...
I'll show you that I'm a man as well!
Give me your best shot, Shou-chan!
I don't care if you exert yourself some effort!
You're desperate... You won't end up
coming spontaneously, right?
Tell me honestly when you're coming!
I'll make you come so loud that you'll
lose that discriminatory attitude!
My pussy is getting all soppy inside!
I feel hot!
Are you done already, manly Shou-chan?
Not yet...
That's it, keep moving!
Beg for it...
Hah! You got quite full of yourself.
Th-This guy... Are you trying to make me angry?
If you won't say so, then I'm not gonna put it in!
Don't you want to come inside me?
Do you want me to?
N-Not really...
Y-You're stubborn. Do you want
me to think that you're strong?
Not confident on making me come?
What a pathetic dick you have there.
It's also good to do it this way, isn't it?
You have a long way to go.
If you have something to say, then I'll do it harder!
Hey, aren't you using cheap tricks now?
You're sadly mistaken if you think
I'm gonna come from this!
Aren't you doing great?
I won't let you off until you come first!
You'll lose if you don't keep it up!
Hurry up and make yourself climax in defeat!
E-Even though it's just you!
Alright, I won't be a toy for
the Ladies Club anymore!
I have to wrap things up with this.
Reika-chan, clean this up for me.
That's enough.
I have to clean it up again!
No, stop! I just came so I'm highly sensitive!
Stop rubbing me anymore!
It got dirty again!
It's not getting cleaned up, huh?
I'm cleaning it the wrong way, huh?
I'm going to clean it up until you empty your balls!
I'm sorry!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization