Training my slaves really tires me out.
Hm?
Excuse me.
Kagurazaka Yui
In charge of: Social Studies
Teacher-in-training
She's been put into a class a trainee. She
is the niece of the principal and has thus
far lived a very sheltered life. Her aunt,
the principal, has already set an arranged
marriage for her. She has no experience with
men and holds an idealized view of romance.
Do you need some help?
Oh, really? You'll be starting
here tomorrow as a trainee?
Principal's Office.
This is the Principal's office.
Thank you for helping me out.
You're late!
Daimon Naoko
In charge of: The School
She is the head of the academy and is married.
She is very prideful and values academic results
over everything. She's only had sexual relations
with her husband. However, she and her husband
have not engaged in such activities in several years.
I-I'm so sorry, Aunt Daimon.
Aunt? How the hell are these two
polar opposites related to each other?!
Yui, you should steer clear of garbage like him.
All men are filthy and vile.
Hypnosis App.
Aunt Daimon?
Creating Sex Addicts With a Cell Phone App!
Hypnotizing Busty, Married Female Teachers
#2 Naoko and Yui
Principal's Office.
Sucking the dicks of the men at this school until they're
clean is an important job when working at this school.
Aunt Daimon, Morishita-kun...
What's going on?
You have to make sure you go deep.
Look, Kagurazaka-sensei's in shock.
You need to make sure that you show her how
a blowjob is done as the principal, okay?
She's taking it in so deep...
She really looks like she's enjoying it...
It's about that time. I'm gonna pack your mouth
full with the cum you love so much.
Make sure to drink it all.
I can't believe she was able to take a man's dick
that deep inside of her. She's so amazing.
So how about it? Do you feel like
having a turn sucking my dick?
Hypnosis App.
Yes, I do. I've wanted to gobble up
your dick since we met.
I didn't even have to order you to suck my dick.
You must have really wanted it.
I've been raised in a very sheltered environment.
So even just the smell of your dick drives me crazy.
If you have the time to talk,
you have time to suck harder.
Aunt Daimon, you're so unfair. How could you not
have told me about this amazing thing until now?!
You were too young at the time.
That's not fair.
I'm being trained to be a teacher now...
This is something I should be learning.
You two are really showing off
what it means to be an educator.
I'm so touched that I think
I'm going to cum soon.
Wait, are you going to defile Yui
with your disgusting cum?
You can't do that. Here, cum on me!
Please give me your dick milk.
I'm cumming!
So this is what makes babies?
I'm so happy!
I can't believe I'm having sex with a kid.
Hey, stop! Yui's watching!
You're saying that now?
This is all for your cute niece's education though.
So this is sex?
It's so wonderful.
Yui, you're too young for this.
You're not even married yet!
So that means that she's a virgin, huh?
Oh boy, that makes me so happy. Do you mind me
taking her virginity before she gets married?
No, you can't!
Yui is engaged!
Your dick is so hard!
Do you really wanna keep this baby-making
sex all to yourself that much?
Oh my god! If she gets a taste of this
amazing cock too, she'll become a slut!
Okay, I'm gonna have a taste
of your niece's pussy now.
O-Okay...
Morishita-kun, you can have my first time if you'd like.
It's coming... It's coming inside me!
It's so good! Your cock is so hot!
I don't care if you're my fiancé or someone I just met!
I just want to have sex with you!
You're so tight, Yui-san.
Do you know just how pleasurable sex can get?
Yes! I can feel your dick pulsing inside me
while it strokes the sides of my pussy!
It feels so good!
I can feel it bulging and throbbing inside of me!
It makes me feel like I need to pee.
Please pour your cum into my womb!
Something amazing's coming!
Let's cum together.
Please connect to a power source.
Hypnosis App.
Huh? Why am I having sex?!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Yui, I'm cumming!
Principal's Office.
Hey, you two. Homeroom's starting.
Please get dressed and return to your normal lives.
As you wish.
Nurse's Office.
I wonder why ever since yesterday, my body's felt like
it's been on fire. I know I need to work hard,
but sometimes I just start having these
really realistic and erotic fantasies.
And then... when I look at Morishita-kun,
my heart starts beating faster than usual.
Sensei?
M-Morishita-kun?
Are you feeling okay?
Y-Yes...
I'm guessing you've just been having
trouble getting used to being a teacher.
Morishita-kun...
I don't mind lending an ear
if you need someone to talk to.
Okay...
So actually, since yesterday,
I've been feeling really weird...
I've never really talked with men before, but...
After meeting yesterday with you, Morishita-kun,
no, Wataru-kun, my heart just won't stop throbbing.
Sensei...
I know we've just met,
but I think I've fallen in love with you.
Or so I think.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Call me Yui.
Yui, ever since I met you,
I haven't been able to get you out of my head.
I'm glad. So, listen...
I want to feel good with you.
Yui, you're so dirty.
No way! I can't believe I'm doing this with a student!
You're nipples are so hard. You're such a slut.
Oh god, my nipples are so tingly!
You're gonna rip them off!
No!
Being touched by the person you like...
really feels amazing, doesn't it?
Oh, your dick. I need to make sure you
let all of its milk out into my mouth.
Your dick is starting to twitch!
Your mouth is great and all, but I think
I want in on some of my lover's tits as well.
You like boobs so much!
Your dick is getting so excited!
You're like a little boy, it's so cute.
This is totally amazing.
Your boobs are so smooth, Yui!
Your dick keeps hitting the peaks
of my boobs, it's making them tingle.
Look at how much pre-cum you're letting out,
it's like you're peeing on me.
Let me try some.
You're taking it in so deep!
It's so tasty!
I'm so happy I became a teacher
and met you, Wataru-kun!
I'm at my limit!
Blow your load and fill my mouth with your sticky semen!
Shoot it into me!
Next is this hole, Wataru-kun.
It's a fresh, new, adult pussy.
Come on, hurry!
Let's have some great sex together.
Yeah. Here I come.
It's coming in!
I can feel it coming towards my baby room!
I'll squeeze your dick now and stroke it
with my pussy to let it know that it's a good boy.
What a good boy.
Let's make sure that you give me a lot
of that hot and steamy baby milk, okay?
Are you telling me to give you all of the cum I have?
Yeah, it's fine. I'm your lover, so give me all of it.
I can feel your dick getting bigger.
Your baby... I want your baby so badly, Wataru-kun!
Just like that, cum!
I'll definitely get pregnant!
There's so much cum!
I'm definitely getting pregnant.
Well, good luck.
I hope the baby comes out healthy.
Yeah, it will...
The support period for the Hyphosis App has expired.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fyurie
quality control: fyurie