To:  Mr. Mamiya Yuuichi
Subject:  Guide to your Recommended Product!!
Using the latest techniques, our partners
have created a more reliable, deep,
and robust hypnosis tool,
The Magic Penlight!!
I'm Mamiya Yuuichi, in the dull study year before taking entrance exams.
My life recently underwent an upheaval.
My father, Seiichi, suddenly married again.
His new wife is Mifuyu.
Her eldest daughter is Natsuki.
The younger daughter is Akiha.
Suddenly I found myself with a mother and two little sisters.
Furthermore, even though he'd just remarried,
Father left the house to work overseas.
I was unavoidably made part of my mother and two sisters' lives.
As one would expect, my relations with Mifuyu, Natsuki, and Akiha grew strained.
Until now, I'd mostly lived on my own,
but suddenly having a family, I was happy.
I wanted to become a real family with them.
Mifuyu...
Mifuyu, when you look at me,
your body will grow hot and you'll feel pleasure.
It's alright, since we're family,
it's not embarrassing at all.
W-why?
My body's so hot...  oh no...
Why's my body so hot?
I mustn't...
D-don't stare at me like that...
But, we're family, huh...
Being looked at isn't embarrassing.
It feels super good...
Busty Family Hypnosis
「Family Bonds」
What is it, Yuuichi?
Rather than cleaning, why not feel good with your beloved son?
Yeah, okay.
Huh?  You're already wet, aren't you.
Were you hoping for something like this?
I, I wasn't.
This is, uh...  since you said we should do it...  all of a sudden.
Come on.  I want to hear you beg for it like you always do.
Th-that's so shameful...
Please tell me, Mifuyu...  What do you want to do?
Put your big dick in my pussy.
Your big, hot thing's going inside...
You're spreading me so deep.
It's embarrassing...  my heart's pounding so hard.
Oh no...
I can hear your cock stirring up my pussy.
Your thick thing's reaching so deep.
Yuuichi, you're so rough...  not there...
I'm...
Wait, I'm not done cumming...
Mifuyu, I'm about to cum, too.
It'd be a shame if I came outside right after you were cleaning, huh.
Y-you're right...
What should I do?
I think it'll be fine if you cum inside me...
If you do me that hard...
I'll c-cum again!
Amazing, cumming so hard...  I can feel it hitting me inside...
You're going to keep going?
Wait, if you...
My pussy, my pussy feels good!
My pussy feels good!
Your cock's swelling inside me!
Are you going to going to cum again?  Inside me like this?
If I cum inside you again, you'll probably get pregnant.
Hey, Yuuichi, you can't get me pregnant.
I can't have anyone but Seiichi's child!
But if I cum outside it'll be a mess.
But I can just clean it again, okay Yuuichi?
So please cum outside.
No way.
Yuuichi, please pull it out!
It's so bad, but it feels so good.
You're still cumming, it's still coming out.
No, not a baby, I can't get pregnant...
N-no...  I mustn't get pregnant, even though he came inside...
Jeez...  I can't think straight...
Welcome home, Natsuki.
Ah, do you want to show me your body like usual?
B-brother, I, I'm embarrassed after all.
Today I got really sweaty during PE.
So...
But, you said you were worried
about how you smell, so
you asked me to examine you.
I did, but...
I didn't think you'd lick me this much...
Please, please wait a minute!
I won't wait, since you smell so lovely.
D-don't, it's embarrassing!
S-stop it!  Not there...
I absolutely don't like it!
You're awful!
Touching me there...
I told you not to, even though I said not to...
Not there...  That's really only for the person I love...
No!  I'll, I'll cum again!  Wait a minute...
Don't, it'll come out, it'll come out...
It's coming out, no, what should I do...
Don't touch it, don't look, Yuuichi, don't look...
I'm sorry, please...  don't tell Mama...
Yuuichi, doing this in the kitchen's dangerous...
There's a fire under the pot...
Then turn off the stove.
You want the meat more raw, don't you?  Like this pussy.
That's...
Thick, are you going to cum inside like usual?
The shape of your cock's super hot.
Rubbing me, there...
If you keep doing me like that, wait, hold on...
There is...
It feels super good...  Whenever you have sex with me there it feels incredible...
And where is "there"?
That is, you know, my pussy.
When you do my pussy so eagerly...
Please, thrust your cock into my pussy more!
Fuck my pussy a lot, make me c-c-cum.
I'm sorry, this is too strong, I can't hold on!
Yuuichi, you're cumming in me again today, no...
Your hot stuff's coming inside me, you're cumming...
I, I wonder if today's okay...
Are you worried about getting pregnant?
You don't have the time to be thinking about that!
Again, this...  Wait, Yuuichi, let me wait a minute!
I'll cum!  No, I'm getting weird, it feels good!
It feels too good!
This is so embarrassing.  Oh no, I'm already, Yuuichi, I'm already, already!
No, seriously, no, cumming again, I'll cum, I'm cumming, pussy, cumming, no...!
No, you came that much and your penis is still this hard...
Can you cum again?
Inside is fine, if you just cum again, otherwise, I...
I'll go crazy.
Your penis is swelling, are you going to stick it in me again?
Oh no, it's so thick, it'll never fit!
Your dick's too amazing, my body's moving on it's own.
I'll be sure to breed you and get you pregnant!
You, you can't do that...
My pussy's cumming again!
Cum, shoot it in me!  I'm cumming again, I'm cumming!
You're cumming...  semen...  you're filling me with your semen...
Dick...  no more...
Okay, now that we're done, clean me up like usual.
I'll totally clean your dick, I'll clean it for you...
Amazing.  Your semen's clinging to my throat.  Delicious.
The taste is spreading through my mouth, even though I'm so sensitive right now
it's amazing.  And your balls are delicious, too, they make me feel so good.
The feel full of cum.
You're really energetic, huh.  Do me in my mouth.
You're raping my mouth.
Your cock's swelling even though you just came, give me your cum.
It's going in my mouth, even now you're cumming too much.
Oh no, what a waste.
You came so much and it's so thick...
Uhm, I saw you...
Uh, you and Mom and Natsuki doing those sexual things.
You shouldn't be doing those kinds of things!
It's strange, that's not how families are supposed to be.
Akiha!
Yes?
Those are things we need to do to get along as a family.
In the case of cleaning Natsuki's skin, that was something she asked me to do.
Since we're family, it's only natural to wash her like that.
It's only...  natural...
Right.  So since we're family, I'll help bond with you the same way.
Okay.
I also, uh, think it's better to strengthen our family bonds.
Look, come here.  Right, just like that.
Ouch, n-no.
It's alright, it's already totally in.
Now I'll take it slow.
As part of your family, it makes me happy to take your virginity.
Virginity...
Are you alright?  Does it hurt?
It does hurt, but I'm probably alright.
You're spreading me...
It's alright, I'll seriously do your pussy.
Why?  My body's feeling kinda weird.
I'm starting to feel it.
What is this?
Does your pussy feel good, Akiha?
It, that is, I...
Something's coming, wait!
No way, inside?!
No, I'll get pregnant!
If you cum in me this much, I'll get pregnant!
Even though I absolutely shouldn't be doing this
I...!
This is...  the first time...
Yuuichi...
Yes, everyone's well.
Of course everyone's getting along well.
I'm not here, continue the phone call and ignore everything I do.
What is it, Mifuyu?
Oh, it's nothing...
What, did something happen?
No, it's nothing in particular, you don't need to worry.
I see, I thought I heard something.
I'm alright.
If anything happens, you should call for Yuuichi.
Y-you're right.  I can really rely on Yuuichi, huh.
Are you alright?  It sounds like you're breathing pretty heavily.
It's because when I hear your voice my body feels good and I get turned on.
I'm sorry, I said something weird.
I guess I'm a little lonely after all.
But I know you're busy with work
just hearing you on the phone makes me glad.
I've got a new family, I'm completely satisfied.
That's why, I'm starting to get turned on just from talking to you, probably.
No.  I can't accept that.  Since it's me!
I'll fuck you good.
I'll give you a baby first, while you two are apart.
Right, when you come home, we'll...  oh you.
I'm cumming!
I'm not done.  I'll shoot it all deep inside you.
I'll definitely knock you up, Mifuyu!
It's strange.  Just from talking to you it's like I'm getting hot inside.
It's not enough if you just say that on your own.
Oh come on, since I'm...
already in the mood right now.
Don't just talk to me like that.  Come on.
This slutty...
It's like she's doing it to please my cock!
I can't believe myself, getting in the mood from just a phonecall.
I really am in love with you, after all.
Of course, I want a baby.
It's nothing, my body's just really hot...
Yes.  I'll be waiting.
I can taste your precum.
You're twitching in my mouth.
Your cock which was born from a different mother.
It's overflowing.  Your cock's leaking like it feels really good.
It's still getting bigger.
This cock's good, it's delicious!
Let it out, let out a lot of cum.
Let out a ton of cum in my mouth!
Can't breathe...  still coming out...
My tummy's totally full of your cum!
Today I was talking to my friends
and they'd mostly all done it before.
Does sex feel all that good?
I have no idea.
Natsuki, you haven't done it with Yuuichi yet?
Wha?  There's no way I would, right?
I've been doing it with Yuuichi...
Wha?
Mom's been doing it too.
Eh?  No way!
Yeah, I have.
I was relieved because Akiha was getting along with Yuuichi, but...
but you haven't yet, huh.
I'm a little worried...
B-but isn't that weird!  Doing it with Yuuichi...
Ara, we're family.  It's not weird to have sex within the family.
Even though it feels that good and is so much fun...  You still haven't done it?
What?  I, I just didn't know!
Natuski, it's important for a woman to know a woman's pleasure.
B-but, that's...
That's right, I even have a picture with Yuuichi.
Ara ara, that looks like it feels really good.
Good for you, Akiha.
Look at this one, too.
Jeez, come on, Akiha...
Natsuki, we'll help you get much much closer with Yuuichi.
Yeah, it's alright, Natsuki.
What're you doing, no, stop it!
Mama, Aki, this is seriously...
Mom seriously wants you to be happy.
Me too, Natsuki.
Let's have fun together.
You're going to give me your virgnity while our family watches.
Yuuichi, I want you to...  fuck me...
Your panties are totally soaked, Natsuki.
That's because I have to fuck Yuuichi...
That's really good, Natsuki.
But let's take off your wet panties.
Mama, it's embarrassing.
Yuuichi's watching...
It looks like you're already ready, your panties and crotch are sticking to each other.
I want to hurry and see where Natsuki feels good.
It hurts!
You're spreading me down there!
Mama, Aki, don't look!
N-no.  Don't do that!  Don't do that!
Don't pound into me!
You're pushing me up inside, don't!
It feels good, but my body feels weird!
I'm about to cum inside.
N-no!  Don't cum inside!  Don't do it!  Even though you mustn't...
Wha-  What is this?
It's totally different from when he cums in my mouth!
It's coming inside me!  That white stuff's going into my womb!
I'll get pregnant.  I'll get pregnant!
Even though I absolutely shouldn't!
No!  Stop it already!  You're cumming inside so much!
You'll feel good soon, Natsuki.
Just let go, Natsuki.
It's starting to feel good!
But, it hurts!  Let me go!  It really hurts!
I'm going to cum again!
Isn't that enough!  Gimme a break!
At this rate, if you cum inside, I'll go crazy!
Even though it hurts, I'm getting hot down there!
I can feel something dripping out!
Natsuki's cute when she's feeling it.
I'm jealous.  Just watching is making me so wet.
It hurts!  I don't want to cum like this!
I'm about to cum!
Please, don't cum, please don't!
I'll get pregnant!  No!
I'm begging you, please let me go!
I wonder why she's being like this.  It looks like she feels good...
I wonder why she won't calm down?
I want Natsuki to love Yuuichi, I wonder why she's crying.
Don't worry, I'll keep cumming in Natsuki until she's satisfied.
I don't need you to do that, take it easy!
Natsuki, hang on a little longer.
Yuuichi, I'll help you with Natsuki.
Leave it to me, I'm about to cum!
I don't want you to!
Hot!  Your cum's filling my womb!
I'll get pregnant, oh no.
Something's coming!
Something's coming!  I'm scared!  Everything's going white!
Natsuki came!
That felt good, right Natsuki?
You're wrong!  It felt good, but
having sex with family is...
This is family sex!  It's our family bond!
Family bond?
I'm family, too...
You let your cum out inside me!
Amazing, my insides are all stirred up.  It feels good!
You managed to feel it!
Very good, Natsuki!  Mom knew you could do it.
That you could have fun having sex.
Yuuichi's hips are still moving!
Give me more of your cum.  I want to feel even better!
Let it out!  Fill my womb with a fresh batch of your sperm!
It's going in!  Yuuichi's lewd white cum's filling my womb!
My pussy's going numb!  It feels good!  Family sex feels great!
I'm glad I lost my virginity...
Yuuichi's cum's flowing out.
My womb's slowly emptying.
Natsuki had too much fun, didn't she?  Since it's her first time.
Oh no, it's coming out.  No...
I can't stop it!
Don't look!
Oh no, not this!  What'll become of me...
Don't touch it!  Even though Aki and Mama are watching...
It feels too good
I don't know any more...
I'm glad we deepened our family bonds.
Yuuichi, from now on, I want to deepen our bonds even more!
It's not fair to just pleasure Natsuki.  Yuuichi, I want to deepen our bonds, too!
I want to deepen our family's bonds, too, Yuuichi!
Yes.  Let's deepen our family bonds more and more.
These fansubs are brought to you by Lv1Translations.
Thanks to hikiko123 for the raw.
All translation, typesetting, timing, and editing was done by Lv1Translator.
I apologize for any and all errors.  Typesetting is hard!
I hope you enjoyed this animation!  Be sure to also check out the visual novel which is excellent!