Several Summers Ago
Nee-san!
What are you doing!?
"What" you ask?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm sneaking in to make love with you.
Nee-san, are you drunk?
No, I'm not!
I just can't help but want this
thing of my brother's tonight.
But we can't do such things, we're siblings!
Even if you say that,
we're only step brother and sister, so it's completely fine!
You're a virgin anyways, right?
Onee-chan can teach not only schoolwork
but also how good it is,
to have sex.
Just stop!
Don't worry! I won’t hurt, so...
It's hot...
My brother's penis...
Although you're resisting It's so... hot...
and really... big!
My brother's penis is... reaching deep inside...
It's getting harder... amazing!
My brother is looking at me...
Yes... more... look more at Onee-chan perverted side!
It feels really good!
Every time it hits inside Onee-chan I can feel it twitching!
You feel good, too, right?
It's so much better... than doing it alone!
Nee-san...
My brother's penis is swelling up...
You want to cum, right? It's fine.
Whenever you want...
It's your first time, so you can cum
when... and wherever you want!
Lots... give lots of sperm to Onee-chan!
It's hot...
So much hot stuff is inside...
All the way to my womb... it's flowing inside...
It felt great...
Onee-chan...
came from being creampied...
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Busty Try!
Intensive Boob Grabbing Lessons
Lesson Start!
Today
Huh? Is Nee-san back?
Nee-san, you should always take
the keys when going out,
didn't I tell you that before?
Ouch...
Oh, I'm sorry!
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm okay.
Huh, this uniform... the one from Nee-san's school...
Good day to you, um, I...
I'm Kobayakawa Ayano, I'm from Shindo-Sensei’s class...
Oh, as I thought from Nee-san's...
Could, could it be that...
You're the younger brother she’s so proud of?
Well, I am Shindo Mio's younger brother.
Um...
I wanted Shindo-Sensei to help me with studying so...
Nee-san's not back home yet, though.
Do you want to wait in the living room for now?
What did you want Nee-san to help you with?
Um...
Oh, once again, I am Kobayakawa Ayano.
Please just call me Ayano!
So, Kobayakawa-san, right?
Just Ayano is alright!
By the way, if there's something
you need help with studying,
I think I should be able to teach you.
Really? Please do!
Well, let's start.
Yes, Sensei...
So, first off...
Um...
Actually, the reason I came here today is not for studying,
I actually have a favour to ask of Sensei!
Me?
Yes. I...
I want to have boobs like Shindo-Sensei.
I'm desperate about it!
I asked Shindo-Sensei at school
She told me that thanks to her brother
rubbing them, her chest grows.
Ha??
So... so...
Please rub my boobs, too!
Wait, put on your clothes!
I can't! I've already made my decision
and came all the way here!
I...
As expected, my boobs are small, aren't they?
Am I doomed to be laughed at for being flat-chested?
Sensei...
No, you're boobs are certainly big enough...
I can't! I can't let it go on like this...
I get it. Please keep it a secret from Nee-san.
Of course!
Please, Sensei!
Um... please don't make such strange sounds...
But... I can't help but letting my voice out...
And also... I think that if I try to let out sexy
voices, it will help my boobs get larger...
This is... how to rub boobs to make them larger...
Somehow... It's starting to feel weird...
Like my body is heating up from inside...
I see. You excite it with heat so it grows...
Then, you've got to excite it some more...
My breath is getting warmer...
No...
My nipples, too...
My body is twitching...
Are you alright? Does it hurt?
It doesn't... hurt.
If anything, it feels good.
My body is tingling.
Is this... the feeling of my boobs getting larger?
More... please be rougher!
Please rub my boobs more roughly!
They'll break! But... it feels good!
Um... are you alright?
Oh! How unmannered of me... I couldn't help
but feel good and almost lost myself...
H-how are my boobs?
Hmm... they don't seemed to have changed much.
I was hoping for instant effects...
Probably not so quickly...
More...
Other secrets to getting larger breasts...
What Shindo-Sensei did with her brother was... sex...
Oh! That's the secret...
Sensei! While we're at this please
make me a grown woman.
Please!
While we're at this?
It's not something simply done!
You have to do those kinds of things
with the person you love...
Then I will fall in love with Sensei.
I like you! Please have sex with me.
Please take my first time!
Even if you just force it onto me right away...
No? I really think that it would be okay if it's with Sensei!
You're really alright with this?
Yes. I don't mind.
If it's for my boobs!
I'll be as gentle as I can,
but if it hurts, tell me.
Yes, please...
It's hot, Sensei...
Ayano's is wet, too.
So you were getting turned on from
having your boobs rubbed.
No... don't look there, it’s embarrassing!
Then, here I go.
Yes.
It's coming in!
The hot thing... a hot thing is coming inside!
It's inside...
No... it's painful!
Sorry. I'll hold back until you're used to it.
Yes.
It's alright. Please go in all at once!
No...
Deep inside... it went all the way inside!
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm alright...
So... please do as Sensei wishes.
Sensei's is rubbing inside me...
I'm so full inside from Sensei's...
It's heating up all the way inside!
It's going deep in, then out, it’s rubbing...
It's hitting deep inside!
Sensei's is thrusting... so hard...
The stimulation is echoing... and
making me twitch inside!
It feels good!
More... please be rougher, Sensei!
I want you to mess up my insides!
It's really... really good!
No! No... it feels so good I'll go crazy!
My mind is... going to break!
Sex... it's so painful... so pleasureable...
my mind is going blank!
I can't hold back anymore!
Something... something is coming.
This is bad... I'm also...
I'm going to cum! I'll cum!
Inside... hot stuff is pouring inside...
You came lots, Sensei...
I can't... anymore...
It’s this late already. I have to go home!
Sensei, can I come to ask for help with studying again?
Yeah...
So tired...
Hello, Shindo-Sensei!
Welcome back!
Oh, it's Ayano! What's up?
N-nothing really! I happened to come nearby,
so I stopped over and g-got Sensei to...
I mean, I got your brother to help me have...
I mean, help me with my studying!
Excuse me, good bye!
Oh alright, bye...
Kobayakawa
The Next Day
Sorry for disturbing.
Please wait upstairs inside my room.
I'll be right there with something to drink.
She's asking me to help her with
studying after yesterday...
I wonder what's up.
No!
I'm so sorry!
Who are you!? And what are you doing!?
Pervert! Poyeur! Glasses' Theif!
No, I'm none of those!
The last one doesn't even make sensei!
I'm Ayano’s Tutor!
Don't lie! Ayano doesn't have a boyfriend!
Not a boyfriend! Listen to what I say!
No! Stay away from me, you voyeur!
Huh, Sensei?
What are you doing?
Someone's in your room...
Oh, Rin-chan you were here!
Ayano! Who is this guy?
This is my bust-up Sensei.
No, I mean, level-up!
Yeah, he the tutor helping me with getting
to a higher level with my studies.
Um, I have no idea what's going on...
Oh, sorry, Sensei.
She's my childhood friend who lives nearby, Rin-chan.
We go to different schools, but we're best friends
and have known each other for very long.
I was going to have a pajama party tonight,
but I didn't think she'd be here so fast.
I see... a pajama party with your best friend...
What's with that face? Don’t look this way, okay?
Geez, do what you want.
Well for now, let's start studying.
Alright.
Sensei, um, Rin-chan is asleep.
Yeah... she is.
Um... can I ask you for help today, too?
But, right here?
Rin-chan is asleep, so it's fine.
Please!
As I thought...
Sensei... please keep on giving me...
lessons... to help me bust-up...
Bust-up?
The Next Day
Coming!
Who is it?
Hey, why are you so slow at coming to the door?
Y-you're the girl from yesterday...
I'm Rin. Kiyosato Rin.
But that's irrelevant Excuse me for a while.
U-Um... so what are you here for today?
Uh...
The same for me...
I'm saying that I want you to do the
same to me as you did to Ayano!
What are you talking about?
It's useless to play dumb!
I know what you guys did yesterday!
I'm close friends with Ayano but also rivals!
So my... please rub my boobs!
I won't lose to Ayano on bust size!
Wait...
Hurry...
Touch them... directly...
They're getting hotter...
With this... I won't lose to Ayano.
It feels good...
You're fingers are sinking in...
I thought you'd be more gentle...
Was that too rough?
I just hurt a bit.
Hurry and continue! They haven't gotten larger yet!
Never mind. I’d only be the same as Ayano with this.
Ayano wouldn't go this far, would she?
So hot...
So men get this hot...
My chest is getting even hotter than when
you rub them with your hands...
This feels good...
Something slippery is coming out of the tip...
Wow... it's getting harder and hotter...
I... I can't hold back anymore!
Hey, this... put it inside me!
So hot...
Mine is tingling already, too...
That's it, I'm putting it in!
Sensei's penis...
I want it. I want sex!
Your thick thing is coming inside!
Are you okay?
This is nothing.
With this... I'm one step ahead of Ayano!
It might feel good...
You penis is so hard and big!
Deep inside... it feels good inside! You're hitting inside!
You’re rubbing my pussy... you're
rubbing all sorts of places!
I won't lose just because she's my best friend!
It feels good!
More! Thrust more!
Your penis... it's swelling up!
I'm... almost...
Just like this... inside!
It's no good, I can't hold back!
It's hot... hot stuff is...
So much inside...
So much inside my pussy...
I'm so full from Sensei's semen... amazing...
With this...
Will they get bigger than Ayano's?
Sensei, let me tell you!
My bust grew by two centimeters!
Uhh... good for you...
Yes!
So I thought we could do something different today.
And I got you to come!
Sensei, please come over here.
Well here I go.
How is it, Sensei? Does it feel good?
I'm able to do this now because they got larger?
It feels good, Ayano.
So much juice is coming out of the tip!
It's so slippery... it feels good!
My boobs are heating up... I think
they're getting larger again...
Ayano, if you rub that fast, I...
What is it? I'm busy right now.
Sensei, if I like the juice coming out of
the tip, will my boobs get even larger?
Huh?
If you do that now...
Incredible...
There's so much of Sensei's!
It's tasty...!
With this... they’ll get larger again, right?
My dear younger brother...
Good morning!
How's is going as a tutor?
They're heavy!
How does the weight of Onee-san's boobs feel?
Please just let go... it’s hot!
C'mon, don't be so heartless.
Please stop!
This time I'll be the one helping my
younger brother with studying.
I got my brother's penis!
How are Onee-chan's boobs? Good right?
It's so big and so hot!
It's getting harder...
My brother's penis is happy!
You're happy from Onee-chan's boobs, right?
What is it? You're thrusting your hips right at me,
do you want more?
Geez, I guess it can't be helped.
Let me use my mouth, too.
Like I thought it's hot!
So much tasty juice is coming out...
It's the smell of my brother's stinky penis...
The taste is getting thicker and thicker...
It's different from sex...
But this has its own good feeling, right?
Yes!
Your penis is swelling...
You want to cum, right?
It's alright! Spray it on Onee-chan wherever you want!
Cum as much as you want!
So much sperm came out!
My brother's sperm is so hot, and it's like milk!
So tasty...
Oh my, how sloppy you’re looking.
Sensei, are you alright?
Ayano?
Shindo-Sensei said that you were
in trouble, so I rushed over!
What's that?
Hello you two!
Just stay like that...
Shindo-Sensei!
Don't worry about me.
More importantly...
I've got to check how much larger you've
gotten from my brother's tutoring.
Did you think I didn't know anything?
I know everything about my brother!
Okay, my younger brother!
Can you give her the lesson as usual?
Of course, to Onee-chan, too.
Shindo-Sensei... it's embarrassing...
Don't worry... Just let out your voice as usual.
That's... that's not the problem!
Okay, Ayano... Come over here.
Younger brother, put it in for her like usual.
No...
Sensei's is...
Even though you're saying no you're still getting excited.
You're nipples are hard.
See?
No, Sensei... don't pinch my nipples!
You’re all prepared.
No...
Sensei's penis is... inside...
Geez brother you’re such a cheater...
No, this is...
It's tight... it's hard...
It's full... it's all the way in!
Please don't push anymore!
Really? You can take it deeper, right?
It's hitting the entrance of my womb!
Sensei's penis... it's rubbing so much!
Shindo-Sensei, you can't rub my boobs so hard!
But I have to say, Ayano’s boobs really got bigger!
Oh, this sensation on the hand...
Sensei, Shindo-Sensei... it feels
so good my mind's gone blank!
I can't anymore...
I'll go crazy!
It's fine! Cum, Ayano!
Go on and feel good from it!
Looks like you came.
Geez, look at what you did to my student.
This time you’ll put it in me, okay?
Yes...
It's hot, hot and... so big!
You got excited from Ayano's pussy, right?
You can feel free to enjoy Onee-chan all the way inside...
My brother's penis is... twitching inside!
It's echoing into my womb!
Mess up my pussy! More!
Your penis is swelling!
Sensei...
Sensei is having sex with Shindo-Sensei!
Ayano... don't worry!
I'll make sure you... feel good again...
I... I'm going to cum again soon!
Me, too... I think I’ll cum...
Together...
Nee-san... I'm almost... cumming, too!
It's fine! Let out as much as you want.
Give us lots!
Shindo-Sensei... I'm cumming, too!
I'm cumming for the second time!
Cumming, cumming...
I'm cumming, I’m losing it!
It feels good!
Inside... it's flowing inside!
Sensei's sperm... I can feel it!
So much is... coming out!
My brother's sperm... overflowing...
My pussy, too... it's overflowing...
Intensive (Boob Grabbing) Lessons During the Summer