For our family, sex is...
our important form of skinship.
Since Yuuichi-kun became
a new member of our family,
I, my daughters Natsuki
and Akiha,
together with my younger sister Haruka,
have all deepened our familial bonds.
However, it seems that there were rumors
spreading around before I even noticed.
And so, Yuuichi-kun used his light pen
to hypnotize into the neighbor wives minds.
Nanae-san from across the street
had been given a hypnotic suggestion so
both her tits and mouth will feel like her pussy.
It seemed that she got intoxicated from the pleasure.
Yachiyo-san from next door received a "baby-making lesson" suggestion,
so she will be able to take initiative on sex.
She's a very diligent woman,
and it looked like she came over and over again.
However, Nii-chan. You creamed her pussy too much!
Here it is.
But Ruiko-san, the neighborhood association president
comes snooping in our home.
I wonder what Yuuichi-kun
is planning to do about her.
Kyonyuu Daikazoku Saimin
Large Breast Big Family Hypnosis
I can't stop having sex with the whole family
I'll have my way on every woman in the whole town!
And for that reason,
everyone on the neighborhood is
talking about these indecent rumors.
Since the issue seems to get worse,
I just have to fix it from where it all started.
Hey, Miss President...
What?
Here, look at this light properly.
You are an elite in the eyes of
everyone as well as yourself.
May it be about even having sex,
you are nothing short of an elite.
I-I am an elite...
Then, prove it by giving this lowly bumpkin
a sexual education.
I understand.
This is also my duty as the president.
T-This is...
What are you planning to do,
making me do something like this?
You actually want it. Right, Ruiko-san?
You're loving it much down here.
Don't... poke me there...
If you keep doing it hard...
I... I'm gonna come from my ass!
My asshole is squeezing tight!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
Is this your first time to use your asshole?
You're enjoying it already.
As expected of the elite president.
No! Stop moving!
You're mixing me up inside!
You're messing my deepest parts!
Here, let's our neighbors watch you!
Don't!
Don't do this!
Please don't notice me! Don't look here!
Don't look here, everyone!
N-Not my ass!
I-I beg you!
It's driving me crazy...
I'm losing my mind!
You're humping my hips...
I'm losing my strength...
I'm coming... I'm gonna come!
I'm gonna come intensely!
If you keep on thrusting...
I-I'm... already...
I can't... anymore...
Don't... Don't!
What a wonderful guidance!
As expected from miss president.
Your asshole was elite level as well.
I'll be counting on you again.
Things kind of worked out this time,
but will it continue to go well, Nii-san?
It's not just nearby, the rumors already
have spread all around the neighborhood.
Alright then, now that it came to this,
I'll have to resort to more drastic measures.
After that, Yuuichi-kun started
to put suggestions into every person in the town.
He arranged a certain special event
together with the neighborhood association's festival.
This is embarrassing.
My nipples can be seen through this coat.
Wow, everyone's looking here.
My loincloth is digging in my butt,
and all of my neighbors see it!
Tonight, we're changing attires for the last stage event.
We, the shrine maidens
will be copulating with the Sacred Medium.
H-How did thing turn out like this?
To have sex in front of everyone...
Even though I already have three kids...
Wow...
What should I do if my classmates see me?
But I have to do my best in this for our family's sake.
Here we are, our Sacred Medium.
Until all of us shrine maidens are satisfied sexually,
the festival will never end.
Even though we're only pressing our tits together,
it feels very very good!
That's because our tits and mouth
have already become pussies!
Oh no, I can't hold myself back!
I want to rub this dick more!
I want it too!
I want this dick!
Please come as well, o Sacred Medium.
We're also gonna come with our tit-pussies!
I'm coming!
W-What's happening?
My tits feels fuzzy!
I tried putting a special suggestion on your tits.
I don't even have a baby...
What's this? My breast milk won't stop flowing...
I'm coming... I'm getting milked!
O Sacred Medium, please come inside me!
Please pour your seed into
my pussy in front of everyone!
So hot! It's so hot!
It's pouring in me!
That's it. More... Do it harder!
How is it? Do it precisely as I say
and try making my pussy climax!
That is how much an elite level should be at least.
There... you're almost there.
I'm gonna come too.
I'll let you come with me!
Nii-san... Everyone's watching us,
yet your dick is this hard!
I'm feeling it more than usual!
I'm gonna come in front of everyone
while having my pussy licked!
Me too... My body is moving on its own!
Your dick is hot! It's so hot!
Sacred Medium!
Amazing... You're doing it so hard!
Your dick is rubbing us while being
sandwiched between both our pussies!
It feels so good, It's making me feel weird!
Together... I'm coming together with everyone!
My pussy... I'm coming... Coming...
I'm coming!
So hot!
My ass... My asshole is tearing apart!
You're breaking it!
You're talking like that...
But you're pussy is dripping wet!
Nee-san... That's my...
If you both keep doing this, I'm...
My ass... I'm gonna come from my ass!
I can't... Take it anymore...
My pussy, my asshole... Both of them...
No...
No!
I-I'm really gonna get pregnant!
What's wrong with that?
I might also get pregnant with Nii-san's child.
I'm looking forward on our family growing bigger.
Do your best as well, mom.
I'm fine with it, since it will be Yuuichi-kun's child!
Please, let's do it together!
Let's come together!
Every women who wanted to be a shrine maiden
began copulating with our Sacred Medium.
May the town be blessed with children
from our festival's closing event.
Now then, our Sacred Medium!
Please grant us with your blessing!
The festival has only just began!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization