Ikenoue, you were just staring at Koharu's huge tits, weren't you?
Kamiizumi Rio
Is that true, Ikenoue-kun?
Fukunaga Koharu
No!
What's the matter, Ikenoue-kun?
Kichijoji Arisa
It sounds like you're causing quite the ruckus.
Were you leering at Fukunaga-san with an inappropriate intent?
Kichijoji Arisa
That's quite the problem.
Th-That's not...
It's easy to tell when you're lying.
Look at this hard proof we have right here!
Stop!
Are you actually hard right now?
You're a huge pervert, aren't you?
This is probably a reward to a total masochist like you.
Isn't it?
You get excited from having a girl step on your dick, don't you?
Stop it...
Are you serious?
Did you just cum from that?
I didn't think you'd actually cum.
How filthy.
Young, Big Titty Girls MC Academy
#1 Prelude to Domination
This is the Private School, Oukyo Academy. It
used to be a pure and fair girls only school.
As the first male student to ever step foot in this academy
due to the new policy enacted by the new headmaster.
I immediately felt what it was like to
be the only guy in this entire school.
My bittersweet expectations for my new
school life were crushed and destroyed.
I had no choice but to endure every
day of being looked at with scorn
like I was some kind of monster by the girls surrounding me.
I'd like it if you didn't dirty my hands with such a vile task.
My apologies, headmaster, but I wanted
to speak with you as soon as possible.
Kichijoji-san and Kuga-san?
You don't have to call me headmaster when we're alone, Yuriko.
Well, we are in the headmaster's office.
Did she just say, headmaster?
How's the plan shaping up?
It's going well.
Ikenoue Takumi has become the target of everyone's frustrations
and not one of them is catching onto why.
That means that the mind control is working, right?
Yes.
He's also feeling stress,
but he no longer has any way to fight back.
I guess that means that we'll need
this to work a little more for us.
Yes.
Thanks to the magic inside this music
box, as long as we have its music...
Indeed. I never thought we'd be
able to do mass hypnosis like this.
It's unpleasant to have that filthy man here,
but he's doing a good job as our slave.
Slave? Mass hypnosis?
Well then, I'll see you tomorrow.
This really has that kind of power?
What are you doing?
This is surprising.
You, a student, have broken into the headmaster's office.
What for?
I heard everything!
I know about your plan!
You're using mass hypnosis on everyone and
using me like a sacrifice to focus their hate on.
And what are you gonna do about it?
This isn't something that concerns trash like you.
At any rate, hurry up and return that to me!
It's do or die!
Stop that!
I-Is the hypnosis working?
U-Uh, from now on, you'll obey me like it's second nature to you.
You'll never disobey me no matter what I say.
Yes. I will never disobey anything you say, Ikenoue Takumi.
Don't make this more troublesome than it needs to be.
Give it back already!
Ask nicer!
Answer me with "yes" and stand right there.
Yes!
So the hypnosis worked?
How long are you gonna make me wait?
This is why I hate talentless people like you.
Shut up. You can't disobey me!
Kichijoji-san, take off your uniform and show me your boobs.
Alright.
You want me to show you my breasts, right?
What are you staring at?
You're staring so lewdly even though you're just trash.
Men really are wretched lifeforms.
But you're standing there so you
can show them to me, aren't you?
How about you take off your bra and
show me what they really look like?
They're so pretty and naughty, Kichijoji-san.
They're not naughty.
Think so? You must touch them all the time.
Not all the time.
Just every now and then.
So that means you masturbate every now and then?
Yes, I play with my breasts and masturbate.
Hey, now's a good time. Show me how you do it.
O-Okay.
It feels good.
This feels...
I'm gonna...
That scream right now... did you just cum, Kichijoji-san?
Can't you tell by looking?
I just came.
I can't tell by looking at your face.
Show me what's under your skirt.
You kept condemning me for being so lascivious,
but you're not too different, are you?
You're right.
You want more, don't you?
I'll show you the ropes, so do exactly as I say.
Take off your skirt and straddle me.
What are you doing?!
What am I doing? Getting ready to help you masturbate.
When you masturbate, you use a vibrator, don't you?
Don't you know that?
I know what a vibrator is.
Why are you acting all high and mighty?
I just need to put it in me, right?
Oh, so you really were a virgin.
How's it feel, Kichijoji-san? Have you ever had sex with a man?
What are you...
Don't be stupid!
Why would I ever have sex with a filthy man?
I see. So, tell me, how does your
pussy feel right now, Kichijoji-san?
I-It's tight!
The vibrator's so big and hard!
It's rubbing against me!
It feels really good!
My pussy's starting to get really hot!
My pussy's getting so hot from the vibrator rubbing against me,
I feel like something's going to overflow from inside me!
You made so much fun of me, but yet here you are
enjoying yourself with a vibrator in your pussy?
Yes! Masturbating with a vibrator feels so good!
Enjoy this with your dirty pussy as much as you
want until you get so tired you can't stand anymore.
My pussy feels so good!
Let go!
Who said you could touch them?!
Forget that. Ignore me and just focus on your pussy!
Look, you like having your boobs rubbed like this, don't you?!
This is amazing. My boobs feel so good!
My pussy's getting even hotter than before!
Looks like you're completely hooked on this now.
You like it here, don't you?
This doesn't feel...
I'm sure you know this already,
but when you're masturbating with a vibrator,
you gotta ask it to shoot its seed inside you.
I know.
Please cum inside me!
Put your seed inside me!
What is this?
I'm cumming!!
I-I've never felt this before.
There's something hot and raw trickling down my pussy.
All of you distinguished ladies will desire to consume
the cum of a man to better improve yourselves.
Please exert the best effort you can to
ready your body for the intake of cum.
Come on, stay still.
Here we go.
I'll squeeze out your precious cum for you.
Oh wow. "Precious cum", huh?
Looks tike the mind control's working perfectly.
Come on, how's this?
You're already so hard and I've barely even touched you.
Your dick is such a simpleton.
That feels good.
I know, right?
I like your honesty.
Take this.
How's this feel?
This doesn't happen too often, so
how about you use your mouth?
I think more cum would come out that way.
Shut up! I know that already!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Look, it's twitching! I know you can't hold back anymore.
Hurry up and cum already.
Shoot your cum out already...
It stinks.
See, aren't my boobs the best?
Stop standing around and stick it inside me already.
I thought you were pretty tight, but I didn't
know you were a virgin, Kamiizumi-san.
Shut up!
What's the matter with this being my first time?
You idiot! You're being too rough!
You're becoming a good girl.
Are you actually a masochist, Kamiizumi-san?
Huh? What nonsense are you...
Yeah, I bet the rougher it is, the more you like it.
Listen, can you hear the sloshing sound of your pussy?
You're being too rough!
Don't worry, I'll cum soon.
After that, you'll be a full-fledged woman, Kamiizumi-san!
My...
What is this?
My pussy is starting to twitch and it feels so good!
Don't spank me!
You're just a peasant. This is your
only chance to act high and mighty.
Right there... No!
Your dick feels good when I do this, doesn't it?
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum in your virgin pussy!
Stop taking your time and cum in me already!
Cum in me! Shoot your thick, hot cum inside me!
Give it all to me!
No! It feels too good! I can't even stand.
How was that? Piece of cake.
Ikenoue-kun? You sure do like to take your time.
Come up to the front already!
Today is self-study where we learn how to extract cum, right?
Today, Kichijoji-san is offering her
pussy, so hurry up and get ready!
You're already wet, huh?
I haven't even done anything and you're like this.
You're quite the pervert, aren't you, Kichijoji-san?
Wh-What are you blabbering on about?
Just hurry up and insert your dick already!
Oh, right.
Alright then, I'll be sure to thoroughly use your onahole pussy.
Oops, that might have been too rough.
But your pussy just ate it up.
So I guess I was right, it's been waiting for my dick.
N-No, that's not...
No need to be embarrassed.
I'm praising your onahole pussy.
Come on! Come on!
Be quiet!
J-Just hurry up and focus on ejaculating!
It's too deep! It's so deep!
It's so hard! I feel like you're digging into me.
Your dick's...
How's it feel? Is your dirty pussy feeling good?
It feels fine. If you cum inside me, I'll
forgive your impudence towards me.
Oh, so that's how you beg, huh?
But you gotta ask me to cum inside you. Come on! Do it!
You're being even more demanding?
Well, I don't have to cum inside you.
I'll just find someone else who wants to be cummed in.
W-Wait!
Please!
Please... in my, in Kichijoji Arisa's, dirty pussy,
pump it full with your cum, your special dick milk.
Plant your seed in my womb!
Please, hurry! Cum!
Here comes the semen milk!
My onahole pussy is cumming!
Wow. Arisa, you should look at your face.
It's so embarrassing.
Wow. I never knew that she could look like that.
Don't... Don't look at me.
Not here...
Look at it dribbling out.
It's gonna go to waste, so whoever's faster can drink it.
Say that quicker!
Th-This...
I can't resist this.
Koharu, you'll regain your consciousness and get raped by me.
Wait! Wait!! No!!
This isn't right!
I thought you were a really nice person!
That hurts.
We've already had sex so many
times, have you already forgotten.
What are you saying?! No!
Looks like your eyes aren't the only thing crying right now.
No!!
Don't look!
It looks like your pussy wants my dick, Koharu.
It's already drenched. Do you really want
to keep pretending you don't want this?
No! I'm not like that! I'm not perverted like that!
You think so?
Let's see what answer I'll get from downstairs.
No! Anything but that!
It's coming inside!
What a dirty pussy!
For all the talk of not wanting it, your pussy
just swallowed me whole like it was nothing.
No! Don't say that!
No! This can't be real.
It doesn't feel good!
This doesn't feel good!
Your words say one thing, but your
moans are telling a different story.
There's no way that I'd feel good from being raped...
I guess I've got no choice.
Your body seems to really want my dick,
so I'll have to answer its desire.
No!
Every time it goes in, it echoes throughout my body!
Can you hear the nice moans you're making now?
That's not...
No! I can't stop moaning!
I'll shoot my cum out inside you, Koharu.
N-No! Don't cum inside me!
I'm cumming!!
I guess I just hurt your innocence, so
let's put you back under the hypnosis.
You're... so horrible.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
softsub: торрент иваниваныч