You're kidding, right?
I have a hard time believing that.
I mean, aren't they all related?
I-I live next door to them,
and I'm absolutely positive I heard moaning.
This is so wrong! Even though I'm your mother, I'm...
I'm...
I'm getting so turned on by your dick!
Nearby-Neighbor's Wife
Ouzora Nanae
Sometimes, the mother's sister
joins in on the action as well.
Oh my God, this is so amazing!
He's pounding you so hard... I bet it feels good!
You look like you're having fun too, Haruka.
You enjoy rough sex just as much as me, right?
Your pussy is sopping wet...
You're so horny right now, aren't you?
Don't say it out loud...
City Council Chairwoman
Okabe Ruiko
There's no way something like that
could possibly be happening, right?
Look, Haruka!
My pussy's engulfing my son's cock!
Here it comes! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Next-Door-Neighbor's Wife
Narumi Yachiyo
Do you think her daughters join in too?
Hey, pay attention to me too!
Just look at how fucking wet I am...
My pussy is gonna overflow!
Hey, no fair!
I want him to mess my pussy up!
My pussy is so hot...
Hurry up and jam your cock into me!
I can feel it pulsing inside me!
You're about to cum inside me!
N-No!
Cum! Cum!
Give me your thick spunk!
Fill your sister's cunt with your cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My brother's dick is inside me!
It feels so fucking good!
You're messing me up so badly...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming so much!
I'm gonna lose my mind if you keep
fucking me so rough and deep!
I'm cumming again!
No more... This is too much!
No more!
Big Hypnosis, Big Families, Bigger Tits
I Can't Stop Fucking My Family and Cumming Nonstop
Big Hypnosis, Big Families, Bigger Tits.
#1 Big Tits in the Neighborhood
Um... There's been some gossip going around lately...
That, uh, you and your family...
do certain "things" together.
We don't do anything out of the ordinary.
To us, sex is simple bonding.
The best way to get closer as a family
is to get closer with your bodies.
Wouldn't you agree?
You need to learn how to better
please your husband, Ms. Nanae.
Yes...
Amazing! How is this possible?
You're already so hard!
I can tell you're really enjoying this by your face.
What a dirty little boy.
Your tits and mouth are now as sensitive as your pussy.
Pussy...
Pussy!
I'm starting to feel strange...
What's going on?
Careful now. If you're too loud, you'll be
the one who they gossip about next.
I-I know, but my tits...
My tit-pussy feels so good!
Ms. Nanae?
I'm going to mess up your mouth-pussy next, okay?
Please use my mouth-pussy to feel good, Yuuichi.
What's going on?
I just have a dick in my mouth...
So why does it feel so good?
Your mouth-pussy is the best!
It's hot, tight, and completely wrapping around my dick!
He's fucking my face so hard!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm going to cum from being face-fucked!
I'm gonna blow my load in your mouth soon, okay?
Your cock is filling me up!
You've completely destroyed my tit-pussy,
my mouth-pussy, and now my pussy-pussy!
Oh, no...
I'm starting to feel strange... Really strange!
Your dick is so tasty!
I love your dick! I love your dick so fucking much!
I'm cumming again!
You're messing me up so hard!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
If you stop prying into my family matters,
I'll reward you with something even better.
Wouldn't you like that, Ms. Nanae?
Yes...
Please give me a reward.
NA RU MI
So...
Now that you know the rumors are true,
what do you think of my family?
Wh-What do I think?
To be honest, I got a little excited when
I heard about your family... bonding.
I wish I had that sort of closeness with my husband.
I want to have a child, but he's really
busy with work all the time.
So...
Would please help me practice mating?
This is so embarrassing!
My husband doesn't do this to me!
Your pussy is very delicious, Ms. Yachiyo.
No... Please don't say that...
But you're already soaking wet.
Enjoying this?
No...
You're stirring me up! It's so intense!
Oh, no, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
I can't take it anymore!
My pussy is gonna explode!
I'm cumming!
Here, I'll wear a condom for you since I'm a nice guy.
But you have to put it on for me.
So good!
C'mon, shake those hips.
You need to learn how to stroke a dick.
Nice and slowly with big motions.
There you go. Good girl.
Does it feel good?
Always say whenever you're feeling good.
You'll get through to your partner that way.
M-My pussy...
It feels so good!
My pussy is burning up!
Procreation is a team effort.
Both of you have to make each other feel good.
My hips are gonna give out...
So good!
Your dick is going so deep inside me!
My pussy feels so...
Y-Your dick is so hot!
It's like it's on fire!
I-I'm gonna lose it! I'm gonna lose my mind!
Something hot is coming inside me!
I'm cumming!
No, I can't hold on!
My pussy's gonna explode!
I'm cumming!
There's so much hot stuff spilling out.
Uh-oh... Looks like the condom slipped off.
Sorry 'bout that.
Oh, no!
Don't worry about it.
Something like that wouldn't bother my little sex slave.
Right, Ms. Yachiyo?
This is the house. There's no mistaking it.
As City Council Chairwoman, I won't
let this debauchery go unpunished!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч