I believed in him...
Nice to meet you!
I'm Inui, the substitute P.E teacher.
Nice to meet you too!
I'm Suzumoto Kiyoka, the student representative.
I respected him as a teacher...
Tidying the place today as well, Suzumoto?
How about I help you?
T-There's no need for that-! I can't get a teacher to help with this...
Well, I can't just leave a student to do all the work, can I?
I'll help out.
Even though I started liking him as a guy...
Suzumoto, on your way home?
Oh, sensei!
No, since my club activities just finished
I was going to file some of the Student Council documents.
You sure are hard working!
Oh yeah, I'll give you this. It was a free sample, though.
It's a new sports drink from a pharmaceutical company.
Apparently it's great for replenishing energy after physical activity.
No, I'm fine, sensei.
Don't say that! I'm just trying to help you!
There are still about ten boxes of these left in the staff room!
I hear it's good for your looks too, so try it!
Then I will.
Tell me what it's like later. See ya then!
Yes, thank you very much!
But why-?
W-Why is my body so hot?
I can't do this-! Not at school!
This is different though, I can't help it!
No-!
I shouldn't be doing this!
It's dribbling out...!
I usually don't get this wet...
If someone found out that the student representative
was masturbating at school, I'd-!
But I can't hold back!
No, Kiyoka. I can't be doing this!
But I can't stop my fingers, it feels too good!
I'm gonna cum-! I'm gonna cum in such a place!
I'm gonna cum in the Student Council meeting room!
I'm cumming-!
W-Why?!
I sure was surprised!
I didn't think you'd be doing such a thing
when I came back to give you another free sample.
Who would have known that such a highly spoken of student had such habits!
N-No! This isn't...!
No need to be embarrassed.
It's natural for a girl your age to relieve herself.
However, you need to consider the place and time to do it.
No, it's not what you think!
When I drank that sports drink you gave me,
my body suddenly got hot and...!
It isn't like you to be blaming others, Suzumoto.
Besides, that's just a normal sports drink.
I've given it to other students, and they all seem fine.
B-But... Such a thing hasn't happened before...
That's why you don't need to hide it, Suzumoto.
I bet you were just under stress,
and needed to relieve it by masturbating...
N-No, I wasn't!
My body suddenly felt strange,
and I couldn't hold it in until I got home. That's why I...
Se-Sensei! What are you doing?!
It's a teacher's job to relieve stress.
No!
P-Please stop it, sensei!
You must have been backed up to react like this just by massaging you over your clothes...
I must properly massage you in that case...
S-Stop it, sensei!
If you don't cut it out, I-I'll get angry!
N-No!
Like I thought, she's quite sensitive to these kinds of things...
Otherwise she wouldn't squirt like she did with just the aphrodisiacs in the sports drink...
No! Stop it!
S-Someone help!
Are you sure you want that? It means that they'll see the video of you masturbating.
I wouldn't mind that, though.
Stop it already! I-I'll report you for sexual assault!
Oh really?
The student representative is going to repay the teacher's kindness with accusations?
Looks like you need to be taught a lesson...
S-Stop it!
D-Don't look!
Hey, by the look of your nipples, you're already aroused.
You must have been very stressed...
You're wrong! No! Stop it! Don't touch me!
Not there!
I don't want to be aroused by having my breasts rubbed by such a man!
Don't rub me so roughly!
Your breasts are soft, but your nipples are so stiff...
Please! Not my nipples!
Not my nipples?
No!
You must be perverted to cum just from having your nipples rubbed, Suzumoto...
I respected you, sensei...
How could you do such a horrible thing?!
Horrible thing?
I'm just teaching you a lesson.
This is my extra intense lesson for such a lewd student representative!
No!
You're going to resist? Miss Masturbating Representative?
You have nowhere left to run.
Unless you want that video of you spread on the Internet, take my lesson.
The student representative is quite lewd, isn't she?
N-No way!
If she weren't, she would at least be able to resist masturbating until she got home.
Y-You're wrong!
I said that wasn't-!
No! Please don't!
Don't touch me! Not there, I might cum!
If you rub so much, it'll be like last time and I'll cum!
No! Why?! Even though it's being done so forcefully, I-!
That's no good, Suzumoto.
Sensei is very upset that you're so perverted...
Don't tell me that... No! Please don't!
No more-! Please forgive me!
What are you saying? We're just getting started...
N-No! Don't!
Anything but that!
It hurts! It really does! Please pull it out sensei-!
Oh? You were a virgin, Suzumoto?
Of course! Sex should only be had after marriage!
Please! You shouldn't be doing this!
I'm not your wife, sensei!
You're not my wife, but you belong to me now.
No!
It hurts! Don't move!
Don't rub against my broken hymen!
I know that your body is getting aroused despite your objections!
That's a lie!
It's so painful!
No! Don't thrust so much!
Stop bullying me with your cock!
What's happening? I'm starting to feel strange again...
It's starting to throb down there!
Why? Why am I getting aroused from being raped?! It's not right!
This is your first time and you're starting to feel good?
I guess you're good at sex, just like your classwork.
No way!
It's a lie. It's a lie! It's not possible that I would feel this aroused!
There's no way I could feel good from being raped like this!
But... But-!
No! I can't stop feeling aroused! I can't stop my hips from moving!
That's good, I'll make you cum like this...
No, sensei! I'm reaching my limit!
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna squirt again!
I'm gonna cum-!
I'm cumming!
Sensei's semen is coming out... He's ejaculating inside me...
This isn't right...
He came inside me...
How lewd can you be to cum on your first time?
I'll make sure to teach you a lesson every day.
I won't allow bunking.
SubDESU-H Presents
Kyouiku Shidou
Student council meeting room
One down...
Looks like I have to train her until she likes it...
Now then, whom should I take next?
Takamiya Chinatsu from the athletics team...
Or Kiryuu Kaede from the swim team...
Or how about Honjou Yuzuki, the prized actress of this school?
Although, I can't get enough of Kiyoka's body...
W-What are you doing?!
Why are you getting an erection at school?!
How perverted!
O-Oh no!
It's not what you think, Honjou-! This happened spontaneously and...
Get away from me, you perverted teacher!
Oh, it's my master! No, I mean...
Inui-sensei!
No-!
Geez! Who is that?!
T-This is?!
D-Don't grab me so tightly-!
I-It's hard! No!
Ho-Honjou! L-Let go!
No! It's a penis! No!
Then let go!
T-The penis-! It's-!
H-Hey, Honjou! Hey, Dumb Tits! Do something!
Huh? Y-Yes! Um-!
Umm... There!
Noo!!
What the hell is wrong with Honjou?
Are you okay, Inui-sensei, I mean, master?
Yeah, wha?! Who are you talking to?!
Aww! You're putting it away?
Of course, you idiot!
Geez...
This is Kajiwara Akina, a.k.a Dumb Tits.
On the outside she's my colleague, and she's the art teacher.
But she's actually my servant, a real masochist.
She was an underclassman when I was in high school,
where I gave her the utmost discipline.
But she became employed at this school,
and coincidentally we met each other again.
I'm getting her to research potential targets since she'll do what I say...
So, what do you want?
Oh yeah, that's right!
It's about the info regarding Honjou-san...
Apparently something big happened in her past!
She was kidnapped and was nearly raped one time...
Hmm, I think we can use that...
Drama club
Thanks for coming.
That's because you sent me that photo!
Wasn't the photo well taken?
I have a video too.
Although I didn't think you'd go and masturbate after what happened...
I'm astonished that a millionaire's daughter would do such a thing.
Shut it, you coward!
Being called a coward is fine.
But since you came here, you have to do what I say...
You promised me that you'd delete those files if I did!
I'll delete it on the spot if you do what I say today...
That is, if you comply to the end.
Not complaining? How tough-minded.
Your tits sure are big.
Is it because you eat good food?
Resisting by not talking?
I wonder how long that will last...
Your pure white skin really shows your class!
You don't have to hold back.
W-Who's holding back-?!
I-It's a penis!
Now it's time for your beloved penis!
It's a real penis...
No...! Don't rub that against me!
I heard that you were kidnapped nearly raped one time...
Wha-?! How did you know?!
You ended up craving penises when they did things to you.
T-That's not right! I don't know anything about that!
Then you were born a penis maniac?
You were moaning about penises when you were masturbating yesterday too.
H-How perverted, he's the worst...
I can't believe he had an e-erection at school...
Getting hard like that...
Why are such hideous things attached to men?
It's already savage to start with,
b-but when it's so thick and hard and smelly, it's-!
I feel sick from just thinking about it!
What would happen to me if this were a real penis?
If someone did rub their penis against me here, I would lose my mind!
I want to forget about penises. I don't want to remember it, but-!
His hard penis is squishing my clitoris!
Don't push so firmly!
Don't push any harder!
Real penises are so hot! No!
Don't rub that against me!
Stop playing with my pussy!
Hey, it looks like you're wet already...
How does a real penis feel?
It's so hard and thick!
No! If he keeps rubbing me that much, I'll-!
No-! I'm gonna cum! I'm going to cum from his penis!
You came, huh?
Then I'll make you cum even more...
N-No way! Not that! Anything but that-!
Yeah, you promised me that you'd do anything for me today!
It hurts!!
My virginity... It was taken by this guy-!
Like I thought, this is your first time.
How does it feel to have your favorite penis inside you for the first time?
He's splitting me! He's going to rip my vagina!
The head of his penis is rubbing against my insides!
How is it? Doesn't it feel good?
T-There's no way that it would feel good!
No! How can this feel good?!
His penis... It's churning up my insides!
I can feel his penis so well!
His penis is rubbing where I normally touch when I masturbate!
His penis is entering me, it's-!
How does it feel to have sex?
Go on, feel aroused on your first time by my cock!
No! I can't fight the pleasure!
I can't stop myself from feeling good from his penis!
We're not done yet...
I'm gonna cum from his penis again!
His penis is going wild inside me!
It's so hard and thick!
It's the penis that came inside me before!
How is this? Aren't you happy that you're surrounded by penises?
You're like a princess being raped by enemy soldiers.
Looks like you're switched on, now that you're surrounded by penises.
You suddenly started tightening...
Yes. That's right, I was dreaming of this!
I dreamed of where they would rape and make me rub and suck their penises!
But-! But, but!
Multiple orgasms on the same day as losing your virginity?
You sure are a penis maniac!
His penis, his penis! It's raping me!
A real penis is breaking me from the inside!
I'm gonna cum inside you now...
No! I-I love penises, but no more cumming inside!
Cum outside! I don't want to get pregnant!
No!
His penis is pulsing inside me...
It's pouring inside me...
My pussy is full of his semen...
You're done already?
We've just started today's lesson.
Looks like we might have to go overtime...
With this penis you love so much...
Sensei...
You're not wearing any underwear like I said, are you?
Sensei, please stop this!
Why do you refuse after changing into that outfit?
That's because you threatened me and I couldn't help it...
Oh yeah, that's right.
We didn't want everyone to find out that you're a pervert
who was masturbating in the Student Council meeting room.
That's so mean!
It's time for your lesson...
It's nice doing you as a top student,
but doing you as an athlete is pretty hot too...
I can smell your sweat even though you've shaven here...
No! Don't smell me there!
You're sweating a bit...
You taste a bit salty, Kiyoka.
Don't lick me there! It's dirty!
What are you saying? Your squirting pussy smelt stronger than this...
No! It tickles!
Don't involve me in such things!
I don't want to be a part of your perverted fantasies!
Then you must be a total pervert,
since you cum like crazy thanks to me every day...
No! I'm not a pervert!
Your breasts are as hot as usual...
Your nipples are so hard just from me licking you...
Don't!
Here, it's time for the titfuck you love!
P-Please stop it!
I don't like it!
No! Don't do weird things with my breasts!
No! No! Take your cock out! Don't use my breasts in such a way!
No! Stop it! I might lose myself again!
Don't rub your penis against me!
I'm nearly losing it just from you touching me breasts!
No! Don't! I might cum, I'm gonna cum!
I don't want to cum!
I don't want to cum from such perverted things!
So hot... It smells and it's sticky... I came!
I came from him doing such horrible things!
Are you ready?
P-Please, not that! Please don't put it in me anymore!
If you put it in me again, I'll cum-!
It fits nicely; it must be from yesterday.
No, pull it out!
Don't rub against my insides with your cock!
I'll cum again if you do it so roughly!
Just cum all you want like a pervert.
What are you saying after cumming like crazy all this time?
No! I don't want to cum anymore! I don't want to cum again!
Your penis is hitting my deepest spots!
It feels like it's gonna enter my uterus!
I'm forced to have sex against my will again... But why am I...?
You're going to cum again?
I have to release a lot inside such perverted girls!
No! Please not inside!
I'll surely become pregnant this time!
I don't want to get pregnant before getting married!
I really don't want it!
Cum with me, Kiyoka!
No!
No!!
It's coming out... His semen is filling me up...
I'm gonna get pregnant even though I'm still a student...
I'm gonna cum inside you like this every day, so make sure you get pregnant...
Now then, whom should I teach next?