I who was sold and thrown into the mansion because of debt,
was raped and fell into a lewd state.
And the part of me that was raped
wasn't a girl's delicate part,
but my butthole.
My anus.
My master is one that called a vampire,
and my life force is being squeezed out by this cock in my ass.
The reason why my butt is always the part that gets raped
is to offer me as a sacrifice to the vampire's lair.
If this goes on, my butt which has been teased and treated as a toy,
Will steadily grow wider and will not be able to shrink back.
Still, in order to live and escape from this mansion,
the only thing that I can do is to endure.
But in my master's body,
there's a secret that even he's yet to know...
hentai-ni-juu.blogspot.co.uk
Translated by SubDesu
Butt Vampire
Chapter 02: Butt Pleasure Fallen Anal Drunker
H NI JUU
Here now, release it already,
Mikage!
N-No, it's coming out!
No... It's going in...
Into my butt...
Doesn't matter if it's your own pee, right?
There's no way...
This is filthy.
Lots of my pee...
...is going into my butt.
You can't release anything from your butt!
It hurts.
It hurts...
Stop this...!
Though we have continued to extract energy from her butt like this ever day...
How can my body still throb like this?
Please let me be...
Don't do anything bad to me.
What are you saying?
The main course is still ahead.
This would be your first time here, right?
N-No way...
That's...
It'll hurt if you don't relax.
As expected of a virgin pussy.
It's amazing.
The cock's being pushed back,
so I also feel good from this.
How does it feel
for your first time being taken by a toy?
Terrible!
This is terrible!
Or maybe you really wanted to be driven by a real raw rock?
No, I don't want that.
That's too bad.
Claude-sama,
the preparations are complete.
No way...
To even have my butt taken at the same time...!
Why are you doing this...?
Don't forget this part, too.
I'm being drilled!
My butt and my pussy...!
Both are rubbing in...
Stop!
Here, take in Claude-sama's semen,
and cum to your fullest.
It's going to cum!
With my... butt...
In my butt...
It's going to cum in my butt!
It has begun.
This is good.
My insides are getting full.
It's gushing out.
Interesting.
I'm going to tear you apart!
Here I go!
I'm going to die!
I'm really...
going to die!
What does this mean?
The throbbing of my body is disappearing completely.
Congratulations, Claude-sama.
You have successfully ascended as a vampire.
Ascended, you say?
Those scarlet eyes and that large amount of semen are the evidence for it.
I see.
So this is what a real vampire is.
With that, our taming methods for her will even evolve further.
And if that happens, I...
You're also quite thirsty, right?
I'll have you drink a lot.
There, there.
Oh, finished already?
Then, I'll give you the next one.
Don't put it in my butt.
If you want me to drink,
I'll drink it from my mouth.
Your anus is already a genuine "mouth", right?
No way...
My body feels hot.
My butt feels hot.
Now, Claude-sama.
This woman is ready to have your finishing touch.
Okay, then.
I'll thoroughly rape her today.
My insides are full.
My butt is hot.
I'm being pulled from my butt...
My butthole is getting drunk...!
It seems the wine made you quite loose.
Are you feeling good from, this too?
No...
No way...
I'm not even...
I'm not feeling good like this even a bit...
Be more honest.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm getting stirred up like this...
Why?
Why does it feel good?
Your cock feels good...!
It feels good... in my butt...
Claude-sama, please.
Let me also have a drink
It's entering.
Amazing!
My butt feels like it's burning.
Thank you for the tasty wine.
For pouring a lot of it in...
I have been truly waiting for your ascension.
Ever since I went to the village,
I already knew that you were half-human and half-vampire
You're different from other vampires...
You talk a lot.
Has the wine gotten into you?
Thank you very much...
The cock...
The cock is stirring the wine inside my butt.
You've been waiting for this cock to rape you like this, haven't you?
Yes, the entirety of my butt-pussy is only yours, Claude-sama.
So use it as you please...
It's hot, it's so hot.
My butt...
is so hot
If you push my belly now...
It's coming out from your butt-pussy:
wine and semen.
Is it very full already?
No, don't say that...
If you're about to spill it out,
then I'll plug it with my cock.
No...
If you stick it in...
My butt will be stirred too much.
My butt...
I'm going insane from being fucked in my butt!!
Claude-sama, please.
Give some to me, too...
That's...
This is also the first time for you, right?
W-wow!
With your hand, it's..
With your hand, it's being opened fully!..
This is amazing!
I can totally feel its mucous membrane.
My...
It's getting inside me...
This interesting.
I shall take both of you on then
My intestines are being touched directly!
I'm being totally stirred!
I'm totally getting lost in it...
I'm sorry.
My...
My butt hurts that is now starting to feel good.
Anal feels good...
It feels good. My butt feels good!
I'm also about to cum now.
The cock, the cock every time it moves, it feel like it's going to burst.
A cock in my butt-pussy...
A cock in my butt-pussy.....
A cock in my butt-pussy.....!!
If I continue...
If I continue getting filled anymore than this...
It's over now.
With this, she's now also...
Claude-sama...
Do you want to escape with me?
This woman has now become a special sacrifice.
If you offer her to the clan,
you'll finally end your role as a tamer, and you'll be free at last.
Is that the reason why you pushed Mikage to the edge of insanity?
I beg you, Claude-sama
Let's stay together like this forever.
Master ...
I ...
did my best...
I did my best until the end of the taming process.
So
Please...
Let me out of here!
Master...
Why? Claude-sama?
After all the...
Please set me free...
I'll do anything...
It's because you're too conceited despite being a mere human.
End