That's why when I was sold off to pay my parents' debt,
I knew what awaited me.
Greet him.
This is Claude-sama, the person who will be training you.
Yes.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Onohara Mikage, Kuroudo-san.
Claude-san?
It seems you don't quite understand your situation...
SubDESU-H
You will refer to me as Master, understand?
I-I'm sorry, M-master.
If you understand, then take off your clothes.
Eh?!
From today onward, you have no need for clothes.
Throw everything away, and strip completely naked before me.
N-No way...
Don't you get it? You have no other choice.
But...
U-Umm...
What?
If I was, um, to complete the training...
When the time comes...
Yes, when that time comes, you might just be able to get out of here.
I understand, I... I...!
I-I'll strip.
Oh, you have cute underwear. Too bad it's wasted on you.
U-Um...
Do I have to take off my underwear too?
Of course.
Y-Yes...
I'm stripping in front of people I don't know...
I-I've really become a slave...
But...
I have to bear with it...
If I get through this, I can be free once again...
I-Is this okay?
Don't cover yourself.
Show me everything.
That's right, show us your lewd breasts and your virgin pussy properly!
You know what's going to happen to you, right?
I-I know...
You're going to...
You're going to do dirty things to me, aren't you?
That's right.
But...
But please...!
Please be gentle to me...
I beg you... Please!
D-Don't!
Not so rough!
Please, not so rough-!
He's going to take it...
He's going to take my virginity...
T-That's-!
That's the wrong place-!
That's not my vagina!
This is fine.
No way!
That's my-!
That's my butt!
Don't stroke me there!
No!
This is fine.
It's okay!
N-No way, are you going to put your cock in there?!
I'm about to teach you the pleasures of anal sex.
N-No, it won't fit! Please-!
Please, I beg of you! It really won't fit!
No need to worry. It can stretch quite a bit.
No... Please forgive me!
No! No!!
No...
No way!
M-My butt-!
It's going in-!
It's in my butt! Master's thing is inside me!
We're just getting started!
No! You mustn't put it in there!
Don't!
Pull it out, pull it out!
Why are you using my butt?
If you were going to do so, at least don't do it in front of others!
Don't be ridiculous.
This is normal for me.
But, this is-!
It's filling me so much, something might come out...
What's going to come out?
I-It feels like I'm going to poop...
Looks like you lost your anal virginity before your real one.
No!!
Please don't say that!
I didn't want this to happen!
This girl... It must be...
She must be a pervert.
No no no! No!
Don't-!
I-I'm about to lose it-!
What's wrong?
You're overflowing!
No way!
I-It can't be!
It's not-!
I knew that you were a pervert who'd feel aroused from anal sex!
You've got great potential to be our Princess.
P-Please stop! I'm not feeling aroused!
There's no way this is making me feel good!
Ouch!
My insides are so full!
Please! Please, I beg you!
P-Please! I'll do anything, so please take it out of my butt!
I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die!
Don't worry, you won't die.
So hot-!
It's so hot!
It feels like my butt's burning!
It's burning up!
I'm going to suck you dry!
W-What?
What does that mean?!
No!
It's coming out inside of me-!
We're just getting started!
Huh?!
W-What is this-?!
No!!
Oh? Was that the first time you've ever cum?
No way...
I-I came... I came from this!
To think that your first time was anal sex,
and you came from such a thing...
I look forward to seeing what kind of Princess she'll be, right Claude-sama?
You're pretty keen on this, aren't you, Himeno?
Did you get excited before?
That might be true.
You sucked out her energy without any warning.
She'll be done anally every day in our vampire town when she completes the training.
She must be able to bear something like this, otherwise she's useless.
Yes, you're right.
She'll be done anally day and night, and she'll constantly have her energy sucked out.
And she will have no choice but to cum constantly from the anal pleasure!
Do you think she'll be able to become a vampire princess like you, Himeno?
Yes, I'm sure she'll become a great princess.
She'll be sodomized and teased by everyone, getting coated in their semen.
They'll do crazy things to her!
What's wrong?
You're already moving your hips.
Yes!
Claude-sama's cock is so hot and hard!
My pussy and butt are so wet!
I'm about to lose it from just thinking about being sucked!
That's fine. I shall suck plenty from you, then.
Amazing!
You're so hard again!
It's pulsing in my hand!
You look pretty happy for someone who's about to be sucked
and have their mind taken over.
It would be a pity not to enjoy things that feel good.
It went all the way in, Claude-sama!
You're being pretty eager, aren't you Himeno?
Yes!
How does my butt feel?
Are you enjoying my butt?
Yeah, it's not bad.
You're thrusting so much, Claude-sama!
You're cock is getting big again!
My stomach's so full! It's being carved out!
My intestines are being mangled!
Is that so?
Shall I rip through your intestines?
Y-Yes!
If that's what you wish, push it into my innards!
I'll probably pass on that.
I can't let you die right now.
Thank you very much!
You're nearly pulling out my insides with your cock!
We're not done yet!
I'm very sorry, Claude-sama!
Please don't mind me!
Do what you want with my butt!
Looks like you're more aroused than usual today.
That's because you're being so rough!
You're the one who invited me!
You pervert!
Y-Yes!
I am your slutty slave!
I-I like it in the butt!
It feels so good!
That's it!
You're very worthy of being my sidekick!
This is too much!
C-Claude-sama!
You mustn't! I'm gonna cum!
P-Please, I'm-!
I'll forgive you with this!
I'm going to suck you!
I'm gonna cum again!
N-No!
I can't stop it, it's going in so deep!
Amazing...
If only she understood this pleasure, then she would want to do this!
That's why we're going to teach her tonight as well.
You're going to help me out, Himeno.
Yes, Claude-sama.
I guess we should be a little creative this time...
Being locked in here naked like this...
I was losing track of what time of day it was...
Not again...
No way, not again...!
N-No more!
This position is hard for me!
It seems your pussy is throbbing. Can't you see it?
N-No, please don't look!
Don't look!
Your butt's also quivering while holding this thing in!
P-Please take it out!
Pull it out, pull it out!
Oh? Do you want it pulled out that much?
Y-Yes...
Please...!
It can't be helped...
M-My butt's going to break...
Your butt's going to leak like this...
I'll plug it up.
W-What is that?
M-My butt-!
It's twisting up my insides!
No!
Not this!!
Bear with it.
First, we're going to get your butt used to this.
No!!
No, it's going deep inside my butt! It's going in-!
I... I'm going to go crazy!
This is nice!
Should we use her as a decoration and hang her up on the wall?
P-Please stop this already! Let me go! Let me go!
I see.
Then as a reward, I'll make you cum.
W-Why?!
N-No more...
N-Not there...!
Wouldn't this be your first time cumming without being sucked?
C'mon, hurry up and cum!
No, don't! I-I'm gonna cum!
I mustn't...! I don't want to cum, but...!
No, no no! No!
No!!
Looks like you're ready to be sucked.
N-No way...
I-It's not over...?
You should look forward to it.
We've got a fabulous costume for you.
T-This is horrible...
My nipples, my nipples-!
Soon, you won't mind your nipples.
It'll be pushed from your mind by the pleasure in your butt!
N-No way...
What are you doing?
Hurry up and put it in yourself.
I can't-!
I can't do it!
Please forgive me!
You really can't?
I-I'm sorry...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's hot-!
It's so hot!
This is too much! No more!
Stop it!
What are you talking about?
Your butt has easily taken in my cock!
No! No!!
C'mon, hurry up and move your hips.
No, no way...!
I can't!
Oh really?
M-My breasts-!
If you can't do it yourself...!
F-Forgive me...
Please stop it!
You're moving pretty boldly, aren't you? Taking it in like that...
D-Don't look!
Please don't look!
That's it, keep going like this.
If you make me cum, I'll let this end.
Please...
P-Please cum quckly!
I-I'm-!
Squeeze tighter with your butt!
No! Not so rough!
No, my butt-!
You're gonna break it!
You're like a broken toy, aren't you?
I-I can hear it! It's hitting my deepest spots!
It's sounding in my head!
Mikage, I'm gonna cum soon.
Y-Yes!
Cum!
Hurry-!
Make it end!
Hurry up and cum! I'm...!
I'm gonna suck you now!
No...
I-If you do it now, I'll...!
No...!
I'm gonna cum...!
I'm gonna cum again!
No!!
More! Cum all you want!
You must offer Claude-sama your energy!
F-Forgive me, I don't want to cum anymore...
No!!
This is a good sight.
Aren't you happy that you're being trained so intensely, Mikage-san?
P-Please...
F-Forgive me already...
If you do it any more, I'll break!
You're right.
Then would you like something to eat?
Eh?!
It's a boiled egg.
You don't dislike them, do you?
W-What are you doing?!
That's my butthole! That's not my mouth!
This is your lower mouth!
Please stop it!
You mustn't play with food!
It's already halfway in.
This is quite a sight. Your butt's taking in the egg.
Please stop this!
Please don't play around with my butt!
Then should we stop playing around?
N-No-!
It went in!
C'mon, you have to push it out, otherwise it'll get stuck!
N-No way!
No-!
I see, so do you moan like that when you normally push?
N-No, I don't!
What's wrong?
It stopped.
Would you like me to help?
Please wait!
I'll push it out! I'll do it myself, so...!
That's right, keep going...
That's it!
That was amazing!
I can see your intestines!
We're not done yet.
What is this?
It hurts, it hurts!
Oh my!
We can see right into your butt like this!
No, no-!
Don't look!
Don't look into my butt!
N-No way...
No way!
You're kidding, right?
No... No!
They're going in...
No...
Don't-!
We're not finished.
If we push them in like this, we can fit many as we want!
No...
I-I hate them...
I hate eggs!
D-Don't push them in!
M-My stomach's getting full...
Stop it...
S-Stop it!
No, let me go!
Please let me go!
No!!
Since you've gulped down so many whole eggs,
I wonder if you're going to dream of being a snake?
How is it?
Are you full yet?
M-Master, what should I do...
What should I do?
What do you mean?
You have to push them out!
I-I'm scared...
There's so many inside me!
If I push them all out, I'll...
My butt's going to break!
It won't go back to what it was!
What on Earth are you talking about?
You've already become something that you can't turn back from!
I-It's coming out...!
T-The egg! I-It's coming out!
Claude-sama.
Are you going to suck out her energy?
Of course.
W-What is this throbbing throughout my body?!
It's hot-!
I should have sucked enough out, but this thirst, it's...
What on Earth is happening?!