Mizobe-kun, are you going to make me a victim?
To make a good union quickly,
the easiest way is to make enemies.
An incompetent, annoying female teacher,
there isn't a more obvious enemy.
That's such an unfair-!
N-No! Stop it!
I'll go first.
You lot get ready!
Tonight we're gonna take her down.
Yeah!!
The rest are waiting, so...
I'm gonna get on with it, sensei!
W-Wait!
No, stop it!
Stop it!
Stop-! This... is my first...
Noo!
It's-! It's entering me!
What? You were a virgin?
I'm not some cheap woman you know!
Isn't it time for a bargain sale?
S-Stop it!
If you stop now... I'll keep quiet!
This situation isn't one where you can order me around!
Okay, you guys, join in!
No! Not my ass!
Even though you say that, every time I thrust,
you're clinging onto me!
Eh? Sensei!
No... You're wrong!
My insides are getting twisted! I'm going to feel funny!
I'm... Gonna cum soon.
I'll make sure that I release lots into you!
No! N-Not inside! Don't do it! No, no, no!
I don't want your semen!
It's... filling... me...
I... I don't want this...
H-Haven't you had enough?
As if.
We have lots of time left.
Let's have fun, sensei...
SubDESU-H Presents
Where is Shinshia-san?
What's wrong?
Do you hear something?
From that meeting room...
See? Baseball club...
Won't it be good for you to join with us?
We can both use Shinshia-chan...
But... If our president found out...
Both our club presidents have ran away,
so we have to make our own decisions.
Anyway, you, the vice president, are now in charge right?
F-Fine then, we'll join you.
Sorry! Did I hurt you?
No worries, so then, over here too.
Um, what should I do?
This is a welcoming ceremony of the baseball club!
Lick me too, won't you?
Yes, I shall.
It's pulsing in my mouth...
Does this feel good? Is it alright?
It's fantastic! I'm about to cum.
Isn't it good?
When you join us, you can do it all you want!
I'm gonna-!
M-Me too!
It's fine! Let it out in my mouth!
Pour it into my mouth!
No! There no point going out now!
Look at them, they're like different people...
Fine then.
So, let's have more fun!
Come, you guys from the baseball club,
Karasuma-sensei has been taken by the rugby club.
Shinshia-san has been taken by the anime research club and the baseball club.
Kenjou-senpai has...
No! It's coming in again-!
It feels good! Your insides are clinging onto me, toilet princess!
T-Toilet princess?
Cum already!
Hurry up and finish, please!
I-I'm gonna cum-!
Not inside!
I don't want any more inside!
Please cum outside!
Shut up!
It's filling me again...
Such humiliation, no more!
Kenjou-senpai is with the survival research club.
Now, what should we do?
What should we- Are you serious?
Are you perhaps thinking we should go rescue the females?
We aren't?
Of course we're going to do it! We can't turn a blind eye to it!
Calm down, will you?
The anime research club and the baseball club have gone wild without any boundaries.
It would probably be impossible to gain control. It's a shame for both us...
Mizobe-senpai and Koga-senpai seem to be working together.
It looks like they're going to join clubs.
We can't do anything here, either...
Then what do you suggest we do?!
Wait for rescue.
They'll probably arrive in about a week.
Till then, we could keep hiding.
Are you being serious?
Please stop this!
Once he stops making stupid suggestions, I'll let him go.
I'm not being stupid!
If I was to protect you guys,
my childhood friends and Hinako-kun, I'm willing to leave the others.
What?!
Stop it!
Please you two, stop this.
What do you think Mochizuki-kun?
Do you think they'll listen to us?
I can't put Shinichi... Yoshiyuki... or Hinako-chan in danger...
I think... I...
Huh? Where is everyone?
We've gone to take a look around.
Wait here until we get back.
Don't go outside no matter what, okay? Yuki.
Senpai...
Good thing there was camping gear, now we can stay out in the forest.
It's not like we've decided on hiding yet.
Sure sure.
Hinako-chan...
Hinako-chan?
What's wrong?
Hinako-chan isn't here, neither is my letter...
I guess she couldn't keep waiting...
We must find her quickly!
Yes.
Hinako-chan, please be safe!
Where did everyone go?
Maybe I should return to my room...
It's not like everyone is bad, right?
Oh? Is that Yoshiyuki-senpai?
Yoshiyuki-senpai!
Oh? If it isn't Hinako-tan.
Were you perhaps looking for us?
You want to continue where we left off, right?
Since we were interrupted...
Um, I have to go.
Don't say that, c'mon! Let's continue from last time!
That same look in their eyes... I need to get away!
N-No! Don't!
C'mon!
Do what we say!
Don't move!
Let me go!
If you struggle, you might get hurt!
Okay, lets go! Our turn has come!
No! Please don't touch such a place!
Such a place? Sure, I'll let go...
Then please!
But I need to know where to let go of, or I can't do anything!
It doesn't matter where, please let go,
take your finger out and let me go!
Please...
You have to tell me where, because I'm not that smart...
My...
C'mon, c'mon!
Please take your finger out of there!
I don't know where if you say only there.
My v-vagina! So hurry, hurry, take it out!
That's a pretty technical term, but whatever, that will be fine.
Then how about I put this in next?
Put in? Put what in? What are you talking about?
Hm? Of course, we're gonna do it!
Since you're this wet, it should be fine.
No!! No, n-no more! Don't put it in!
Noo!!
For it to slide in so easily, were you wanting it Hinako-chan?
N-No! No, pull it out! Don't put it in!
It hurts! It hurts! No no no no!!
No, don't move!
It hurts, it hurts!
No more, please stop, please pull it out!
It hurts... Please let me go!
I-It hurts! If you grind my insides, I'll-! No!
I'm gonna let it out soon...
L-Let it out?
Of course, I mean inside!
No, n-not inside! Really, don't!
Please don't!
Don't worry, I'll take responsibility!
Let's fill this island with our children!
No no, anything but that! Please, not a baby!
Don't cum inside! Noo!!
I'm gonna cum, catch it... with your uterus!!
Inside... He came inside...
He came inside after my first time... I...
A-Again?!
N-No more, please no more!
What are you saying? We're just getting started, see?
I think I'll take the mouth!
Give me fellatio!
I can't hold back watching this, I get her hand!
Do me with your hand too!
No~!!
So let's get started!
No-!
Don't-!
If you do that so much-!
I'll break!
If you clench so much-!
I'm gonna cum!
Not so hard-!
Please finish!
I'm gonna let it out!
I'll let it out deep in your throat!
No-!
No more, not inside! Don't release it inside!
Stop-!
No, no!
It's coming out, it's coming out inside me...
I'll, I'll get pregnant with a baby!
Please... Let me go...
Noo!!
Hinako-chan, Hinako-chan!
Senpai... Where are we?
Hinako-chan, I'm so glad...
Sorry, since we weren't with you, you...
No!! It hurts! If you do that so much, I'll break!
I'm sorry, Hinako-chan...
I'm sorry, senpai...
I'm so sorry! It's because I acted on my own...
I wonder why Hina wasn't detained.
I guess they didn't want any unions to break...
What do you mean?
I told you about how they see us as enemies who threw away their clubs and ran away with their lovers, right?
Oh, I see...
So that's why Hina needs to be with our side.
Yes, the guys who raped Hinako-kun must have realized that
if they were to hold on to Hinako-kun, that would make them our target.
Still, I can't believe they make the females everyone's plaything.
Since Hinako-kun has woken up, lets move places, we can't stay here for-
It seems that you've been hidden nicely, however, it's the end of the road.
The survival club and associates have circled this area.
You can't run away.
Shinichi? Did something happen?
Mizobe-senpai...
And Koga-senpai...
Something wrong? What's with the blank expression?
Showing us something like this...
What's happened to you, Mizobe-senpai?
Hmm? I bet you guys fucked like crazy while you were running away.
Why would we do such thing?
You guys are about the only ones who would do such thing!
Hey hey, are you serious?
You guys had plenty of opportunities to do it.
Hey Hatsushiba, don't you get hard?
Then how should we do this...
It's a bit boring taking turns again...
Hey Koga!
You're right...
Then how about we do them in front of Hatsushiba and Yoshiyuki?
Not a bad plan, then...
Mizobe-senpai! Please stop this! I beg of you!
Sorry miss, but I represent everyone here.
Even if it is you, I can't grant your wish.
Shall we begin?
You too Hina.
Wait! Hinako-chan isn't-!
I heard that she was done by the guys over at the anime research club.
We dealt with them, but it's true that you guys ran away.
Give it up.
No way...
It's fine. I'll be okay. However, senpai, you...
Mochizuki was with the baseball club, right?
Hey baseball guys!
S-Stop this!
Isn't this nice? Things are getting exciting...
I never thought we could do the manager...
We were right to join Mizobe-san.
Hey you guys!
It wouldn't be fair if we were to be selfish like our leader right?
No...
N-No stop! Stop it! Don't!
Where do you think you're touching-!
No~!
Here!
It hurts! Not so rough! No!!
Take... Take your hands off me!
No... Don't put it in... Stop it...
Stop it!!!
Please, stop this!
Shinichi, don't look!
No... I don't want to lose it like this...
Stop, please stop! Don't put it in!
No~!
Pull it out! No!!
Yuki...
Hey, it's the scene where your loving girlfriend loses her virginity!
Make sure you watch thoroughly for her.
Senpai... So mean...
Hey manager.
Stop worrying about others, we're gonna get started too.
Hinako-kun!
Yoshiyuki-senpai!
I didn't know that the rugby club manager liked an otaku, how unexpected.
C'mon, we're starting!
N-No! Please stop!
I heard that you were done by the otakus the other day.
It's a shame you're not a virgin anymore,
but that means that we don't need to hold back, right?
Noo!!! I don't want to be played with anymore!
No, I'm being played with again...
Yoshiyuki-senpai! Don't look, don't look!
Please stop, it hurts, it hurts!
Don't move!
It's rubbing against my insides!
I'm gonna...
Not that, please don't!
Release it outside! Please not inside me!
Don't thrust anymore... No! I'll get pregnant!
If you release it inside me I'll-! Noo!!
I said... I didn't want it inside... Not inside...
Y-Yuki!
Okay, next one go!
Put it in anywhere you like!
No~!!
It hurts!
Don't move! Pull it out, please pull it out! N-No!
No, please, not my ass!
No, no! Not my ass!
Please stop it! No more! Don't defile me further!
Not inside-!
You'll break me!!!
H-Hinako...
Yoshiyuki-senpai...
I... Did I cum?
Did I cum from my ass in front of Yoshiyuki-senpai?
No... No, noo!!!
What? You're broken already?
These two as well huh?
That was pretty quick.
Mochizuki, you're the main course for these crazies.
I hope that you don't lose it or break, and that you'll keep being our plaything.
This crazed feast has just begun....
No! No more!
Noo!!!