What's wrong?
This isn't your first time touching such a thing, is it?
There's no way that such person as I, Kenjou Maya, have experienced such a thing.
Anyway, you should be grateful that I'm servicing you like this...
Yeah, it was a good choice choosing me,
I promise to protect you well.
Moreover, um, well, isn't the semen supposed to come out already?
Of course not, nothing will come out at this rate.
Use your mouth.
Mouth?
You want me to lick this with my tongue??
I'm fine if you don't,
you'll just have to find someone else to protect you.
F-Fine then, I just have use my mouth, right?
What a smell!
Even this is my first time seeing and touching a penis,
but for me to be doing this too...
Will the semen come out now?
What a strong smell!
This is disgusting in every aspect...
I'm about to cum soon.
Go on, hurry!
Let out your semen-!
Is that fine?
Sorry, I'm not satisfied yet.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
What's wrong? Hurry up, give me a titfuck.
U-Um, w-what is a titfuck?
I bet you already knew, but it's where you rub a cock with your breasts.
H-Hmph! I didn't need you to go over it again.
T-Then...
As expected from a high-class lady, you've got a good technique.
I think I can cum soon with this!
Of course...!
How would such person as I... be bad at it?
Let it out, won't you?
Amazing! You let out so much!
Even though I said you could, you got me dirtier than I expected.
Hmm? I must be seeing things.
What's up?
No, it's nothing.
Anyway, we can't get off this island any time soon.
You made a wise decision.
Yes... I'll keep the contract.
For such a person as Kenjou-senpai to go that far for protection...
Maybe it's time to make a decision.
SubDESU-H Presents
I am Mochizuki Yuki, the manager of the baseball club.
This area is owned by our Miyanomori Academy, where field trips are held.
The cause of this whole incident is
a coup d'etat within the country that this island is a part of.
The teachers decided that we should return to the country, but...
Without any contact outside the island,
the frustrated teachers decided to have a look first.
However...
The ship that the teachers were on was wrecked,
and was washed onshore.
There was no-one aboard.
Among the people left, the leader decided to have a meeting over the situation.
Are you suggesting that we should consider that all the teachers who went for help were killed?!
Anime research club president
Tada Yoshiyuki
With the state of the ship, I think that's a safe assumption.
Rugby club leader
Mizobe Tetsudai
Cut out the hysteria, won't you?
How can you call yourself a teacher?
Math teacher
Karasumaru Ikuko
What do you think, Hatsushiba-kun?
Baseball club president
Hatsushiba Shinichirou
I also think it is highly probable that the teachers all died,
however, I don't think we should decide on who's alive only on guesses.
Hatsushiba-kun...
Our teacher has gone into hysterics over these incidents...
Will it be okay like this?
And that look she has for Shinichirou...
It doesn't seem to be a normal look a teacher would give to her students...
Since we don't have any contact with the outside,
I think we should consider ways off this island.
Wouldn't that be a good plan?
That's not a realistic option.
Survival game research club president
Koga Naoya
You've seen the state of the ship, we'll probably be shot and killed.
Even though you teachers couldn't in contact with anyone,
please give it some thought.
If we don't return home on schedule...
Oh, right! Since back home they know that we're on this field trip...
Yes! I'm sure they'll come looking for us.
The issue here is more of food and our safety.
It seems as though there has been some fighting...
and we would need to decide on leaders.
So, you mean we should decide on the top dogs?
Then of course it should be the people in the rugby group.
If we are to fight, then the bigger the better.
If it were up to me,
I have confidence in having control.
In terms of numbers, my group's the top.
Also, we don't mind if the people in the baseball group would join us.
So there we have it.
What do you think Yuki?
I...
I think that the baseball club and the anime research club would be the best leaders.
Hey hey, are you being biased?
It's obvious that you're saying that to favor yourself.
I am the manager of the baseball club,
but leaving that aside,
I think that on normal grounds that this is the best idea.
Do you really think that the baseball jocks and anime freaks,
let alone Hatsushiba can control this crazy situation?
Hey, that's too much-!
This is stupid.
Um, Koga-senpai!
We haven't finished our...
It seems that it is useless talking further with you lot.
The others and I are going to find our own way through this.
I am willing to decide on people with the same taste in music.
Even if they are or are not worthy,
if our interests match then I have no problem.
Isn't that a bit...
Well, there's no use trying to persuade people who won't change.
So that's how it is, see ya then.
Um, has the meeting finished?
Yeah, we didn't end up needing any tea, sorry.
How unfortunate, today I made some Indian Chai tea.
The only local staff left
Shinshia Sakirito
Everyone is split up, I wonder what's going to happen...
Hey c'mon, it'll be fine.
Wan-king?
What's that?
Wanking means masturbation, you know that right?
Er, um, masturbation?
Not in front of o-other people...
We might be dead by tomorrow, this is a once in a lifetime wish!
You knew that this area was dangerous, right?
Since there's some disorder with your side of the staff,
why don't you show us something nice?
I... I understand.
You're right, it was our fault.
Is this all right?
This is amazing! She's actually doing it!
I can see her hole properly!
Does this mean you're not a virgin?
That's not...
I haven't done it-!
-Before!
What a situation!
Let's show her too!
W-What are you doing?
It won't be fair for you if we don't.
I can't... do this...
Is this...
I can't keep s-standin-!
It's making an embarrassing sound down there...
This is too erotic! I'm about to let it out!
Let it out?
For me to be touching myself in front of men...
It's too embarrassing!
Are you... done yet?
If I don't hurry... I'll feel funny!
Please finish! Please finish already!
Your hot fluid is covering me...
We can't bare with only watching you!
Yeah, since we came this far, we should...
Oh no! I have to go save her!
But I can't move myself!
Eh?
We'll have you stop right there.
Oh! P-Prez!
What are you guys doing?
P-Prez, we're...
I know that we're physically worn out, but this is wrong.
Shinshia-san, it's my fault the my members acted this way,
I am terribly sorry.
You can take any action you want.
N-No, it's fine.
I too understand how everybody feels.
It looks safe now.
I...
couldn't do anything.
Yuki!
K-Kenjou-senpai!
You had a bath too?
This heat is unpleasant, isn't it?
You get all sweaty,
and the smell gets annoying...
Oh, that's right Yuki!
Y-Yes?
There was a meeting earlier, wasn't there?
Since you went instead of me to represent the female students,
give me a brief description of what was decided.
Sure, well...
Is that so?
I guess this means I'll have to find my own protection.
Yuki!
You're a girl too, be careful.
I can't get that image out of my mind...
Oh! Yuki-senpai!
S-Since when were you there?
A-Ah Hinako-chan! You were changing?
I didn't know~!
What's with the sarcasm?
Anyway, Hinako-chan. Are you alright standing like that? It's quite a show.
No!
Geez, senpai! At least tell me when you're back, it's so embarrassing!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Um, senpai?
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
You seem tired,
you're also participating in meetings as a representative and stuff...
Well, it's not just our situation. There are other things that I am worried about-
Oh? Is that perhaps a crush?
A crush?
No? Was I off? It seemed that way...
I wonder if it is...
Y-You gotta be kidding... Shinichi... Do I like Shinichi?
You can talk to me about it, so talk away!
T-Then will you listen to me?
Sure! Leave your advice on me!
Sorry about that, I talked for too long. We nearly missed dinner.
It's fine!
I'm used to eating quickly.
Since back home my older brothers will eat it all if I don't hurry.
We've got lots of soup, so don't hold back for seconds!
Yes!
Shinshia-san sure is amazing.
It's as if nothing happened.
Whether I am...
There's no point of being down.
Huh?
Y-Yoshiyuki?
No need to confirm, it is I,
Tada Yoshikuyi, the man of the cell phone novels.
Well, that is a lie though.
W-Why are you saying that I'm down?
And also, don't read my mind!
Even I can't read people's minds.
It just seemed that Hatsushiba and Karasuba-sensei were getting quite close,
so I just guessed that someone was feeling down.
Here you go!
Um, thank you for before.
That was because of my bad awareness!
I am sorry about that.
Oh Hinako-kun, was it alright that I sat next to you?
Of course!
Oh? Karasuba-sensei and Hatsushiba-senpai?
C'mon, over here...
I think I told you before. It's not over until I'm satisfied.
You're the one that said I can do anything as long as I don't take your virginity.
However, putting it in my butt is...
To use such a dirty place...
Okay, I'm putting it in!
No, no!
Y-You can't put it in!
It's so deep! No! Don't move! Stop it!
No more! No more!
Not my bottom-! Don't be so rough!
My bottom, it'll break!
Hurry up and finish!
Hey! You're the one moving!
No!
My bottom... is feeling strange...
Even though I don't want it, I-!
My bottom is churning! My bottom is-!
I'm feeling funny!
I'm about to cum-!
Let it out outside! Not inside! I won't forgive you!
It hurts!
My bottom will feel funny!
No!
I won't forgive you if you let it out inside!
You let it out inside... No... No...
I said I didn't want you to many times.
Maybe I chose the wrong person...
The person who protects me, a person who can protect me...
I need to find another person...
So then, how about we go into the second round?
Huh?
You took my other private part instead of my virginity...
How can that not be enough?
I'm a big eater, so then princess, shall we begin?
Noo!!
Hinako-chan, where did you go?
It's been a while since dinner...
I hope I'm thinking too much, but...
P-Please, stop it!
Hey! You're late!
Sorry, took a while to find some rope.
Hinako-chan!
Yuki-senpai!
H-Hey, what do you want?
Hey, grab her too!
Aren't you guys embarrassed for doing this kind of thing to us?!
Not really, since the other group is doing Shinshia the maid.
Shinshia-san?
Oh, your breasts feel good!
This is better than an oppai mouse pad!
TL Note: Oppai mouse pads are mouse pads with female characters with padding on the breasts, a popular otaku item.
No!
I wish I could buy this!
Please stop it!
Whoa, I've never heard that expression before!
Hinako-tan being embarrassed sure is cute!
That means you're a virgin, right?
Hey! We're asking you, reply!
Y-Yes I am... I'm a virgin... So please let me go!
Hey, could you guys hurry up?
It's tiring trying to hold her, you know...
Yeah, you're right! Let's get started!
What do you mean?
No! No, please! I don't want to!
It's to late now! You're going to be done by all of us!
E-Everyone? By all of you?!
You guys!
Don't move so suddenly, you seriously wanna try it?
It's five against two! It's no use struggling.
Shut up! Let me go!
Someone... Someone help us!
So what if there are five guys?!
Shinichi?
Get away from Hina and let Yuki go immediately,
or else, I'll give each of your heads an individual home-run!
So, let's continue where we left off...
Last time the prez got in the way,
but this time, we'll go all the way...
Um, what does that mean?
Didn't we tell you before?
We just want a good time before we're killed.
Perhaps... Does that mean...
you want to have children with me?
Well, something like that.
It'll suck for you, but we're gonna do it.
B-But, in my country I cannot get married to three men!
It's here, right?
C'mon, suck me here!
It's so deep! Stop it!
Even though I'm unmarried,
for me to let out such a voice from getting my virginity taken and a penis stuck in my mouth...
Stop it! Stop! It's slipping in and out of me! It feels funny!
Even though it's my first-!
It feels unpleasant!
No more!
Don't be rough!
I-I'm reaching my limits!
Me too!
No! Don't do it! Not inside, not inside!
I'll get pregnant with a baby!
No, don't cum!
If you do that, you'll cum...
Now it's my turn, Shinshia-san!
Hey, what are you going to do?
Are you trying to get back at me for being rejected?
I don't care how you think of this.
However, we can't accept your offer.
From here on in, we're the ones who call the shots.
Detain this woman!
Noo...
Stop this! Let me go!
How about you just give up?
Don't be stupid!
Put that dirty thing away!
You sure are tough-minded for someone who is about to lose their virginity which they've held onto so tightly,
even under Mizobe's command.
As expected, I would say.
We're skipping foreplay.
I'm going to put it in now.
Noo!
How about you say something?
Does this mean you've got nothing to say to someone you rejected?
You're a good screamer... Let me hear it Kenjou!
Y-You twisted sadist!
It's hitting my deepest spots!
I-I'll break!
Won't you give me some excitement too? You're hogging the fun!
No way! I-Is that... A real gun?
Don't worry, it's not real.
However, it's been modified so it can piece skin.
Don't poke such a thing at my private spot!
Don't jiggle it!
I-If I knew... you were such a twisted person, I wouldn't have...
You wouldn't have come to plead?
You're blaming me for not agreeing with you?
Soon I'll...
D-Don't tell me that you're-!
You lost your virginity to me...
I'll make sure you regret it!
No no! Anything but that! No no stop!
If you do such thing, I'll really-!
No! Stop it! I told you to stop! Don't release it inside! Don't do it!
Stop it, don't! Not inside! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It feels disgusting...
Hurry up...
Not my ass too!
Not there... Not so hard...
No don't!
Not inside... I'll get pregnant... No!!
Your hot semen is...
Stop it-!
You guys, Kenjou says it's not enough!
You know what to do.
Are you okay Hinako-chan?
Yes, I'm fine now. But, Shinshia-san is...
I'll go find her!
Have you forgotten what just happened?
It's me, won't you open up?
It seems that things have gotten worse.
Various clubs have begun to rebel.