What's wrong?
This isn't your first time seeing one, is it?
There's no way that I, Kenjou Maya, am not experienced in this.
Anyway, you should be grateful that I'm servicing you like this...
Yeah, choosing me was a smart decision.
I promise to protect you well.
Moreover... Um, well, isn't the semen supposed to have already come out?
Of course not. Nothing will come out at this rate.
Use your mouth.
My mouth?
You want me to put this in my mouth?
It's fine if you don't.
You'll just have to find someone else to protect you.
F-Fine, then. I just have use my mouth, right?
What a smell!
This is my first time both seeing and touching a penis,
but for me to also be doing this...
Will the semen come out now?
What a strong smell!
This is disgusting in every aspect...
I'm going to cum soon.
Go on, hurry!
Release your semen!
Is that fine?
I'm sorry, but I'm not satisfied yet.
Hey!
What are you doing?
What's wrong? Hurry and give me a titfuck.
U-Um, w-what is a titfuck?
I bet you already knew this, but it's where you rub a cock with your breasts.
H-Hmph! I didn't need you to go over it.
T-Then...
As expected of a high-class lady, you've got a good technique.
I think this will make me cum soon!
Of course!
How could a person like me... be bad at it?
Let it out, won't you?
Amazing! You let out so much!
Even though I said you could, you got me dirtier than I expected.
Hmm? I must be seeing things.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Anyway, we can't get off this island any time soon.
You made a wise decision.
Yes... I'll keep the contract.
For someone like Kenjou-senpai to go that far for protection...
Maybe it's time for me to make a decision.
The Summer Camp Hidden Within the Mist
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Volume One
I am Mochizuki Yuki, the manager of the baseball club.
This area is owned by the Miyanomori Academy, where field trips are held.
The cause of this whole incident is
a coup d'etat within the country that this island is a part of.
The teachers decided that we should return to the country, but...
Without any contact outside the island,
the frustrated teachers decided to take a look first.
However...
The ship that the teachers were on was wrecked,
and was washed ashore.
There was no-one aboard.
The leaders among those left decided to have a meeting concerning the situation.
Are you saying that we should consider that all the teachers who went for help were killed?!
Anime research club president:
Tadayoshi Yuki
With the state of the ship, I think it's a safe assumption.
Cut out the hysterics, will you?
Rugby club captain:
Mizobe Tetsuhiro
How can you call yourself
a teacher?
Math teacher:
Karasuma Miyako
What do you think, Hatsushiba-kun?
I also think it's highly likely that the teachers are all dead.
Baseball team captain:
Hatsushiba Shinichirou
However, I don't think we can decide who's alive purely by conjecture.
Hatsushiba-kun...
Our teacher has gone into hysterics over these incidents...
Will it be okay like this?
And that look she gives Shinichirou...
It doesn't seem like a look a teacher would give her students...
Since we don't have any contact with the outside,
I think we should investigate ways off this island.
Wouldn't that be a good plan?
That's not a realistic option.
Survival game club president:
Koga Naoya
You've seen the state of the ship. We'll probably be shot and killed.
Even though the teachers couldn't get in contact with anyone,
please give it some thought.
If we don't return home on schedule...
Oh, right! Back home they know that we're on this field trip...
Yes! I'm sure they'll come looking for us.
The issue here is more of food and safety.
It seems as though there has been some fighting...
We need to decide on leaders.
You mean we should decide on the top dogs?
Then of course it should be the people in the rugby group.
If we are to fight, then the bigger the better.
If it were up to me,
I have confidence in my control.
In terms of numbers, my group has the most people.
Also, we don't mind if the people in the baseball group join us.
So there we have it.
What do you think, Yuki?
I...
I think that the baseball club and the anime research club would be the best leaders.
Hey, hey. Are you being biased?
It's obvious that you're saying that to save yourself.
I am the manager of the baseball club.
But leaving that aside,
I think that this is the best possible idea.
Do you really think that the baseball jocks and anime freaks,
let alone Hatsushiba, can control this crazy situation?
Hey, that's a bit much!
This is stupid.
Um, Koga-senpai!
The meeting hasn't finished...
It seems that it's useless to discuss this further with you.
The others and I are going to find our own way through this.
I am willing to decide on people with the same taste in music as me.
Even if they are or are not worthy,
if our interests match then I have no problem.
Isn't that a bit...
Well, there's no use trying to persuade people who won't change.
So that's how it is? See ya, then.
Um, has the meeting finished?
Yeah, we didn't end up needing any tea, sorry.
How unfortunate; today I made some Indian Chai tea.
The only local staff left:
Shinshia Saguritto
Everyone is split up. I wonder what's going to happen...
Hey, c'mon. It'll be fine.
Wanking?
What's that?
Wanking means masturbation. You know that right?
Masturbation?
Not in front of o-other people...
We might be dead by tomorrow! This is a once in a lifetime wish!
You knew that this area was dangerous, right?
As your staff bears some responsibility,
why don't you show us something nice?
I... I understand.
You're right, it was our fault.
Is this all right?
T-This is amazing! She's actually doing it!
I can clearly see her hole!
Does this mean you're not a virgin?
That's not...
I haven't done it...
Before!
What a situation!
Let's show her ours, too!
W-What are you doing?
It wouldn't be fair for you if we didn't.
I can't... do this!
Is this too much?
I can't keep s-standing!
It's making an embarrassing sound...
This is too erotic! I'm about to let it out!
Let it out?
For me to be touching myself in front of men...
It's too embarrassing!
Are you... done yet?
If I don't hurry... I'll begin to feel too good!
Please finish! Please finish already!
Your hot fluid is all over me...
We can't stand to simply watch you!
Yeah. Since we've come this far, we should...
Oh no! I have to go save her!
But I can't move!
Eh?
We'll have you stop right there.
Oh! P-Pres!
What are you guys doing?
P-Pres, we're...
I know that we're physically worn out, but this is wrong.
Shinshia-san, it's my fault that my members acted this way.
I am terribly sorry.
You can take any action you wish.
N-No, it's fine.
I too understand how everybody feels.
It looks safe now.
I...
I couldn't do anything...
Yuki!
Ke-Kenjou-senpai!
You took a bath too?
This heat is unpleasant, isn't it?
You get all sweaty,
and the smell gets annoying...
Oh! That's right, Yuki!
Y-Yes?
There was a meeting earlier, wasn't there?
Since you went to represent the female students instead of me,
give me a brief summary of what was discussed.
Sure. Well...
Is that so?
I guess this means I'll have to find my own protection.
Yuki!
You're a girl, too. Be careful.
I can't get that image out of my mind...
Oh! Yuki-senpai!
S-Since when were you there?
A-Ah, Hinako-chan! You were changing?
I didn't know!
What's with the sarcasm?
Anyway, Hinako-chan. Are you alright standing like that? It's quite a show.
No!
Geez, Senpai! At least tell me when you're back! It's so embarrassing!
Sorry, sorry.
Um, Senpai?
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
You seem tired.
You're also participating in meetings as a representative and stuff...
Well, it's not just our situation. There are other things that I'm worried about.
Oh? Is it a crush, perhaps?
A crush?
No? Was I off? It seemed that way...
I wonder if it is...
Y-You gotta be kidding... Shinichi... Do I like Shinichi?
You can talk to me about it, so talk away!
W-Will you listen to me, then?
Sure! Leave it to me!
Sorry about that. I talked for so long that we nearly missed dinner.
It's fine!
I'm used to eating quickly.
Back home my older brothers will eat it all if I don't hurry.
We've got lots of soup, so don't hold back for seconds!
Yes!
Shinshia-san sure is amazing.
It's as if nothing happened.
Whether I am...
There's no point in being down.
Huh?
Y-Yoshiyuki?
There's no need to confirm. It is I,
Tada Yoshikuyi, the man of the cell phone novels.
Well, that is a lie.
W-Why are you saying that I'm down?
Also, don't read my mind!
Even I can't read people's minds.
It just seemed that Hatsushiba and Karasuba-sensei were getting quite close,
so I just guessed that someone was feeling down.
Here you go!
Um, thank you for before.
It's because I wasn't paying attention!
I am sorry about that.
Oh Hinako-kun, was it alright that I sat next to you?
Of course!
Oh? Karasuba-sensei and Hatsushiba-senpai?
C'mon over here...
I think I told you before. It's not over until I'm satisfied.
You're the one that said I can do anything as long as I don't take your virginity.
However, putting it in my butt is...
To put it in there...
Okay, I'm putting it in!
No, no!
Y-You can't put it in!
It's so deep! No! Don't move! Stop it!
No more! No more!
Not my butt! Don't be so rough!
My butt will break!
Hurry up and finish!
Hey! You are the one moving!
No!
My butt... feels strange...
Even though I don't want it, I!
My butt is churning! My butt is!
I'm feeling strange!
I'm about to cum!
Let it out outside, not inside! I-I won't forgive you!
It hurts!
I'm losing my mind!
No!
I won't forgive you if you let it out inside!
You let it out inside... No... No...
I said I didn't want you to do it several times.
Maybe I chose the wrong person...
The person who protects me... a person who can protect me...
I need to find another person...
Now then, how about we move on to the second round?
Huh?
You used my other private part instead of my virginity...
How can that not be enough?
I'm a big eater. Now then, princess, shall we begin?
No!
Hinako-chan, where did you go?
It's been a while since dinner...
I hope I'm thinking too much, but...
P-Please, stop it!
Hey! You're late!
Sorry, it took a while to find some rope.
Hinako-chan!
Yuki-senpai!
H-Hey, what do you want?
Hey, grab her too!
Aren't you guys embarrassed for doing this to us?
Not really. The other group is doing Shinshia the maid.
Shinshia-san?
Oh, your breasts feel good!
This is better than an oppai mouse pad!
No!
I wish I could buy this!
Please stop it!
Whoa, I've never heard that before!
I said to stop it!
It sure is cute for Hinako-tan to be embarrassed!
That means you're a virgin, right?
Hey! We're talking to you! Answer!
Y-Yes, I am... I'm a virgin... So please let me go!
Hey, could you guys hurry up?
It's tiring trying to hold her, you know...
Yeah, you're right! Let's get started!
What do you mean?
No! No, please! I don't want to!
It's too late, now! You're going to be done by all of us!
E-Everyone? By all of you?!
You guys!
Don't move so suddenly. You wanna try it?
It's five against two! It's no use struggling.
Shut up! Let me go!
Someone... Someone help us!
So what if there are five guys?
Shinichi?
Get away from Hina and let Yuki go immediately.
If you don't, I'll give each of your heads an individual home run!
Now then, let's continue where we left off...
Last time the Pres got in the way.
But this time, we'll go all the way...
Um, what does that mean?
Didn't we tell you before?
We just want to have a good time before we're killed.
Perhaps... Does that mean...
you want to have children with me?
Well, something like that.
It'll suck for you, but we're gonna do it.
B-But in my country I cannot get married to three men!
It's here, right?
C'mon, suck me here!
It's so deep! Stop it!
Even though I'm unmarried,
to moan like this just from losing my virginity and having a penis stuck in my mouth...
No, stop it! This is too much!
It's numbing! It feels strange!
Even though it's my first!
It feels unpleasant!
No more!
Don't be so rough!
I-I'm reaching my limit!
Me too!
No! Don't do it! Not inside, not inside!
I'll get pregnant with a baby!
No, don't!
If you do that...
I'll cum...
Now it's my turn, Shinshia-san!
Hey, what are you going to do?
Are you trying to get back at me for being rejected?
I don't care what you think of this.
However, we can't accept your offer.
From here on in, we're the ones who call the shots.
Detain this woman!
No...
Stop this! Let me go!
How about you just give up?
Don't be stupid!
Put that dirty thing away!
You sure are arrogant for someone who's about to lose their virginity,
even under Mizobe's command.
As expected, I would say.
We're skipping foreplay.
I'm going to put it in now.
How about you say something?
Does this mean you've got nothing to say to someone you rejected?
You've got a good scream... Let me hear it, Kenjou!
Y-You twisted sadist!
It's hitting my deepest spot!
I-I'll break!
Won't you give me some excitement too? You're hogging the fun!
No way! I-Is that... a real gun?
Don't worry, it's not real.
However, it's been modified so that it can pierce skin.
Don't poke my private spot with that thing!
I-If I knew... you were such a twisted person, I wouldn't have...
You wouldn't have come to beg?
You're blaming me for not agreeing with you?
Soon I'll...
D-Don't tell me that you're!
You lost your virginity to me...
I'll make sure you get pregnant!
No, no! Anything but that! No, no! Stop!
If you that, I really will!
No! Stop it! I told you to stop! Don't release it inside! Don't do it!
Stop it, don't! Not inside! No, no, no!
It feels disgusting...
Even my mouth...
Not my butt, too!
Not there... Not so hard...
No, don't!
Not inside... I'll get pregnant... No!
Your hot semen is...
Stop it!
You guys, Kenjou wants more!
You know what to do.
Are you okay, Hinako-chan?
Yes, I'm fine now. But Shinshia-san is...
I'll go find her!
Have you forgotten what just happened?
It's me. Will you open up?
It seems that things have gotten worse.
The club members have begun to rebel.