– Eastal, a city of commerce was home to a
nefarious slave trade in the city's underbelly.
– Wh-Why is this happening?
– Eastal, a city of commerce was home to a
nefarious slave trade in the city's underbelly.
– I'm getting started.
– Eastal, a city of commerce was home to a
nefarious slave trade in the city's underbelly.
– No! That can't be true!
– Though Cless had tried to in titrate the city,
– I'm cleric – a servant of God!
– she was discovered, captured, and robbed
of her virginity by the bishop of Eastal.
– It's coming out... His hot stuff...
– she was discovered, captured, and robbed
of her virginity by the bishop of Eastal.
– There are a lot of horny guys here, we can never get enough help!
– she was discovered, captured, and robbed
of her virginity by the bishop of Eastal.
– There are a lot of horny guys here, we can never get enough help!
P-Princess Jill and Luna, why are you both...
– Princess Jill and myself were prisoners as well.
– Please, if you're going to rape someone, let it be me.
– Damn, it's tight!
– The three of us were forced to submit to
the sexual desires of the soldiers as sex slaves.
– Her pussy's getting tighter too!
– The three of us were forced to submit to
the sexual desires of the soldiers as sex slaves.
– Cum if you must!
– The three of us were forced to submit to
the sexual desires of the soldiers as sex slaves.
– Cum if you must!
– We were made into their playthings.
– Just hurry and end this already!
They're going to cum?
They're going to defile both my mouth and pussy!
Have mercy!
– No!                                 – No!                                – No!
– No! Stop!
– But I refused to give in to them.
– Let go of me!
– I was forced to fight a monster while practically naked
– and then was raped by it with the eyes of the audience upon me.
– If I could just use my magic, I could easily beat this thing.
– Look, your body's able to have sex with monsters now!
– They made a show out of me.
What's wrong, Knight?!
– Why are you so stubborn?
– And right when I was about to lose all hope,
a girl appeared before me.
– She was a prostitute named Airi.
– No, stop! Don't put that on me! My body's...
– Just give up.
– But even when she used her techniques
to make me cum countless times,
– It's not bad being a prostitute, like me, you know?
– But even when she used her techniques
to make me cum countless times,
I still... I still didn't...
Hey, you still haven't given up?
I will not give up!
I don't want to give up!
Lilitales
act.3 "Blood pact of the succubus"
Lilitales.
Okay.
I'll help you awaken to your power.
What's she doing?
I can feel something coming into me.
The power inside of you isn't one of brute strength.
It's a sexual power... a power of Lilith.
A power of Lilith?
It accepts both pleasure and desires.
Don't worry, you won't be affected
by those things anymore.
The thing you need right now isn't
the strength to stand up to your enemy.
You need nourishment and devotion...
to accept your enemy, enslave them, and love them.
What do you mean?
I don't understand what you're talking about at all.
You don't have to yet.
Your body will understand soon enough.
Good. You've become a lot more docile.
You're the spitting image of a sex slave.
Don't you agree, Lunalie?
Why am I sucking this by my own volition?
My body's on fire!
I can't stop this excitement!
No... I... I'm...
Good. You understand.
You know the proper etiquette of a sex slave.
Get ready. I'm gonna make you
heave and moan with my dick!
Why... I don't want to do this!
It's like my entire body's screaming
out for him to violate me.
It... It's saying that it wants to have sex!
Okay, I'm about to cum.
Take it in with your mouth!
We're not even close to being done yet.
I'm gonna have your bottom half get its fill too.
Got it?!
You're pretty wet.
Guess you really wanted my dick.
I can't stop myself from feeling good!
I can't fight against the pleasure!
What's the matter? You're being pretty quiet today.
No more fight left in you?
Huh?!
"What you need now is nourishment and devotion.
To accept your enemy and love them."
Please... do it.
Please mess up my body.
Fuck me as much as you want. Please!
Finally admitting it?
Finally admitting that you're a sex slave?
Alright I'll give it to you, just like you want.
Y-Yes... Right there...
I've made you into a good sex slave.
All right, I'll make you my concubine.
Come on, cum from my cum!
It's coming! I'm cumming!
I can't...
Come on, your body's still twitching!
Not enough for you?! Want more?!
I want your hard dick to keep fucking me! Please!
All right, I don't know what's going on,
but if you're into it, so am I.
I'll fuck you good!
I'll cum!
I'll shoot everything inside you and knock you up!
Cum!
Give me everything!
I'll take it all in, so give me as much
of your semen as you want!
All... All of it!
My body... My body won't stop!
More! More!
I'm cumming!
Wh-What's going on?
See? Just like I said.
You don't need to fight your enemies.
Airi, what's going on here?
What's this light?
You said that you'd sell your soul for power,
don't you remember?
But you didn't sell your soul to a demon...
But to a succubus.
Airi?
Well, let's get going.
There are people you want to rescue, right?
Such good fortune. Truly good fortune.
All right, just a little more. My climax nears.
Sir Bishop, please cum.
Please... Give it to me.
I want your semen, Sir Bishop!
– More! Let me experience even more pleasure!
– Yes, Sir Bishop!
Please use my body as much as you'd like!
I am your plaything! Do with me as you wish!
Good attitude.
I will take you up on that offer.
Yes! It feels good! It feels so good! My breasts...
That's good.
Put more strength in your asshole
and you'll squeeze tighter down there!
Understood.
How is this, Sir Bishop?
Does it feel good inside of me?
Yes! Just wait a little.
I'll pump you full of my cum again in no time!
It's so hot!
Your thing is twitching!
Cum! Please cum!
I'll take it all in!
Please go ahead and shoot it all inside me!
It seems as if you've fallen to my magic as well.
Yes! Yes!
Being able to have sex with you makes
me so incredibly happy, Sir Bishop!
Good attitude.
I'll teach you the pleasures of the flesh with my meat stick!
Thank you very much, Sir Bishop!
Please purify my insides with your meat stick!
Please!
Okay, okay. I don't see why not.
Savor this.
Amazing! It's coming all the way inside!
Your hot stick is mixing up my insides!
What a dirty cleric you are.
Can you tell how wet you are?!
Please forgive me, Sir Bishop!
Please... Please punish me!
Please give this depraved body of mine a punishment!
Very well.
Then accept my punishment in your womb!
S-So rough! I-I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Sir Bishop, please use my body more!
I'll do anything to make you happy!
I-It feels so good!
Thank you so much for licking my pussy, Sir Bishop!
So good! This tightness is amazing!
I cannot wait. I am cumming!
I am going to cum inside you!
I'm about at my limit. Let's call it a night, huh?
Not so fast, Sir Bishop.
Wh-What?!
She's right. We can't stop yet.
Let's keep going!
I-Impossible! Why can you two...
Look, your dick is already rock hard again.
I can't stop my hips from moving!
Sir Bishop, please show me more of your compassion.
These indecent juices keep flowing out of me!
S-Stop!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Impossible! C-Could this be an illusion?!
H-How long have I been...
How is it?
How does it feel to have someone like you who
usually hypnotizes women fall into an illusion instead?
Curse you!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
Cum!
S-Stop!
Stop!
You should be satisfied, right?
You came so much, after all.
Cless, get a hold of yourself!
I've undone the Bishop's brainwashing.
You're going to be okay.
Th-The princess... Princess Jill is still...
Where is she? Do you know?
She was taken by the man in white... to the royal ruins.
Something about breaking a seal...
Got it.
Wait for me, Jill. This time...
This time I will rescue you for sure!
Jill!
Luna! Luna!
Please, get me out of here!
Save me!
You just love to get in my way, Silver Hair.
It seems I miscalculated by leaving you alive that day.
I should have killed you right then and there, Silver Hair.
This is it...
I've been chasing you all this time!
Ever since that day!
Very well.
There's no choice now that you've made it here.
Wh-What?!
Oh... That doesn't look too good for us...
Is... Is that his true form?
Now, prepare yourselves wenches!
I will crush all of you!
Luna!
I will kill you and get revenge for my comrades!
And then I'll have you return Jill to me!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Look at the dance
Regular Customer
Audience Member
Airi
Back
"Luna-chi, wanna dance?!
Dance
Pass
Get on the stage
Listen to explanation
Ask about crowd size
Nevermind
Airi
"Okay, put this on. Oh, your hair's longer than it looks.
It looks good braided, but maybe you should try tying it up?"
Luna
"..."
"...Hey... Airi... I-I think... I'll pass... okay...?"
Airi
"Too late, so nope."
Luna
"But...! I-I'm basically wearing nothing but my underwear... They'll be able to see everything when I dance!"
Airi
"What are you talking about? Do you see what you usually wear?"
"If you're embarrassed, you can keep the clothes on, okay? Come on, let's go."
Luna
"No. Way!"
Airi
"Just give up."
Luna
(Uh...)
The lights were lit and the music started... There was no getting out of this now...
Audience Member
"Oh? I've never seen this dancer before."
Luna
"Ah... I... I'm new. My name is... Lunalie... Please, enjoy..."
(Uu... uuu... They're watching...)
The gazes from the crowd pierced me so hard, it hurt. They weren't even trying to hide the fact that they were staring at my boobs and butt.
My footwork was obviously that of a novice level. It took all I had to keep up with the unfamiliar music.
Luna
(Th... This outfit... It's so risque... and it's a little small on me...)
Every time I moved, it felt like the cloth was about to snap off of my body. If I mored any more vigorously, it just might all fell off...
Money received
0 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Audience Member
"Oh, a new girl?"
"Yaeh, her name's Lunalie. She's pretty high quality."
Audience Member
"Wow... Not a bad body."
Luna
(H... th-there... there are more audience members...)
Money received
0 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Audience Member
"That's quite the risque outfit. That bra looks like it's about to fall off. Can almost see 'em."
Luna
(Uu... I knew this outfit was too much...)
Money received
0 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Audience Member
"Hey she's shaking her ass! Spread your legs... hehe!"
Luna
(Eh...!? Spread my legs...)
Money received
0 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Couch and dance
Audience Member
"Hell yeah! Do it harder!"
Enthusiasm increased by 6. Received 396 Dina.
Audience Member
"Hell yeah...! Take off your damn bra! Take it off!"
Luna
(Huh...! T-Take it off...!?)
Wh-What should I do...? Take it off...? ...but...
Money received
396 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Couch and dance
Strip
Audience Member
"Ohhhhhhhhhhh!"
"Hell yeah! Awesome! Shake em! Shake em more!"
Luna
(...ah... uu...)
I stripped... in the heat of the moment and from the excitement from the crowd... I felt a strange chill of excitement down my back.
Enthusiasm increased by 10. Received 1923 Dina.
Audience Member
"Hell yeah! Take off more! Take off your panties!"
Luna
(Eh... awawa...)
...my... my panties? If take those off... I'll... I'll be completely...
Money received
2319 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Couch and dance
Strip
As soon as I took off that small piece of cloth, the audience roared with cheers.
Audience Member
"Fuck yeah! Give us a better look!"
"Shake it! Shake it!"
Luna
(Ah... Ahhh...)
I... took it off... I really took it off...
This is so embarrassing. My face must so red. They can see. They can see my vagina...!
Enthusiasm increased by 15. Received 3466 Dina.
Audience Member
"That's good! Shake your ass this way!"
Money received
5785 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Couch and dance
Strip
Audience Member
"Hot damn! That's good! Makes me hard!"
Enthusiasm increased by 5. Received 458 Dina.
Audience Member
"The new girl still is a little rough around the edges, but isn't too bad."
The crowd increased.
Money received
6243 Dina
Dance more vigorously
Lean forward and dance
Dance with your hips
Couch and dance
Strip
Audience Member
"Hot damn! That's good!"
"Take something else off!"
Received 2729 Dina
<Score>
Received Money: 8972 Dina <New Record>
Shady Men
"...hehe... We knew you'd come here..."
I ended up coming here... Just like what these men said... I came here by my own will...
Shady Men
"Okay, change clothes... Get on stage... The night show is about to start..."
Luna
"..."