J-Jill...
You all...
Let go of Jill!
Luna...
So this army is the personal royal
guard escorting the princess?
I'm begging you, don't kill her!
I don't care what happens to me.
I won't kill her. I still have something for her to do.
What does he mean by that?
For returning at the castle all by myself,
what awaited for me was torture from my comrades.
How can it be that you're the only one
that lived and returned here, huh?!
I know why. You're one of those treacherous knights.
You sold the princess to a slave merchant!
Y-You're wrong! I'm not—
I was framed up.
Lunalie, we have an evidence!
Where did you sell the princess off! Speak up!
I escaped from prison to find out where the princess is.
Wait for me, Jill! I'll definitely save you!
Silver Knightess In Captivity
Lilitales.
At the eastern desert is a city named Ishtal.
It is a large area where drifters
and slave traders are rampant.
If Jill is to be sold off as a slave,
it should be nowhere else but here!
I see... And so you came here to look for me?
Aren't you a well-known middleman
on slave trade in this town?
Please, I want to have any information I can get.
It's within my capability but such
insider information aren't free.
Let's see... It would cost around
twenty-thousand for the initial payment.
T-Twenty-thousand dinars?! It costs that much?
Well, if you don't have money
You can make use of that body of yours instead.
I'll introduce you to a high paying customer.
It's fine if you don't want to. That is if you think
that you can find the princess
in this large slave trading town.
So, what are you gonna do?
I understand.
With my body... I will pay using my body.
She's a fine jewel, indeed.
That guy Batil sent me a lady of such beauty.
You're called Lunalie?
You're a virgin, is that correct?
Y-Yes...
We have a deal.
I'll handle that initial payment for the slave search.
You'll be selling your virginity to me in return.
You'll have to give me plenty of pleasure.
There's no turning back now...
In return for money, I'm using my body...
I'm selling my virginity!
You're doing good.
Gobble it up and make me feel good.
We're far from done. I won't settle
down after coming just once!
I'm going to be deflowered by this thing soon.
W-With this thick thing!
N-No—!
What's this? Aren't you already wet?
You're wrong! This is...
Alright then, it's about time
for me to have fun using this.
Spread your legs and beg for it before I put it inside.
Offer your virginity on me in that manner.
I-I can't... say something like that!
Then the deal is off. Will that be fine?
P-Penetrate...
Penetrate me please!
I offer my virginity to you.
Okay!
You said it well!
I now just took your first time!
I beg you, don't be too rough on me!
You'll tear me up!
Your inside is so warm and wet,
it's wrapping around me tightly!
You're actually feeling good, huh?
No way! No way that it's true!
I'm feeling good from this!
Even though I sold my virginity
and have my body being violated...
I'm dripping more and more of love juice!
I'm rhythmically squeezing down there from pleasure!
Th-This can't be happening!
No—!
You're this lewd despite being a virgin until now.
Looks like you'll be a slut in no time!
No... Don't say that!
You're wrong! That's not true! No—!
I'm about to reach my limit!
I'm coming... I'm gonna come!
I beg you, anything but a creampie!
Wait... Wait—!
Make sure to remember the man you offered
your virginity on and tore your hymen!
The taste of your first man!
Coming... It's coming!
I couldn't hold it in! It's been
a while since I came this much!
An initial payment of twenty thousand dinar, indeed.
This should be alright. Hurry up for Jill's...
That should be plan but I was hired
for an earlier job, you see...
It's a paralysis needle. Don't worry.
When you wake up, you'll learn
stuffs that feel even better.
A lot of them.
Forgive me but compared to what you'll pay,
I can earn more if I'll sell you off as a slave.
N-No way...
Lowly liar! This isn't what you promised—
If a silver-haired woman comes in my turf,
I'll hand her over to your slave market.
Am I right, Master Grims?
Jill, I'm sorry! I'm...
How about it,do you feel like
cooperating with us now?
Quit joking!
L-Like I'd ever adhere to your will!
A royal blood...
The ability to break the seal in the Shandora ruins
was only inherited by you, Princess Jill.
If you keep rejecting our demands,
we have some ideas here to make you do so.
No... Stop!
Don't apply any more of that drug!
I-I feel so hot! My body feels
burning, it's driving me crazy!
I'm begging you, make it go away!
Make it go away right now!
Make this throbbing of my body settle down!
When it comes to pain, the human brain
is made to be able to bear it.
But not when it comes to pleasure.
No! That's my ass, no...
No—!
N-Not my ass—!
Don't finger me there!
Does it feel that much good?
So even a princess is just a woman when strip naked.
Stop it... Stop! Don't stir me up in that place!
I feel hot like my ass is on fire!
I can't take it anymore! No, no, no—!
How is it? Is it agonizing?
If you will agree on cooperating with us,
I'll release you immediately.
Th-That...
That will never happen!
I won't let things happen as you all please!
It can't be helped, then let's
proceed with the next plan.
No way! I-It's not over yet?
Well then, everyone that gathered here today.
Shall we start with the auction for the virginity
of the third princess of Grantz Kingdom?
Alright, I bid 780 000 dinar!
I can't help wanting that cheeky side of her!
Mine's 850 000 dinar!
Let me shove it in that tiny cunt!
No, no, no...
No—!
No...
My virginity is getting auctioned.
I'll become a plaything to satisfy these men!
Take a look here.
Just as you can see, it is a beautiful piece of meat.
Fine! One million dinar!
There shouldn't be any more problems!
Well then! I can now do as I please, right?
Right here? You're kidding!
Although everyone is watching?
I'm gonna turn the princess
into a woman using my thing.
Stop... No! I don't want this man to deflower me!
I'm being penetrated... No way!
My first time, my chastity—
You're a virgin but you're already dripping wet inside!
No way! It's my first time, but my body is feeling so hot!
I'm throbbing down there... This can't be!
This can't be happening! No!
I love this! I want this girl!
I want her so much, I'd make her my sex slave!
I can let you have the honor
to train her every night if you wish.
You can do anything with her as you please.
No, no!
I'll become a slave... I don't want to!
Even though I shouldn't... Why?
Alright, I'm about to come.
I don't want it, no!
I'll shoot all of my baby seeds inside the princess!
No, stop! Don't shoot it inside!
No way, I'll get pregnant! No!
No, no!
Don't!
H-He came in me...
He really came inside me!
Alright, it's no time for you getting wasted!
We're only getting started!
More! I'll shoot you more of my baby seeds!
I-If this goes on, I'm going to break!
P-Please help me!
Luna, Luna! Luna—!
Stop... No! No...
Woman from the royal guard that
survived, you came for us in the end.
You're quite the fool not knowing
that the broker is one of us.
Stop, let me go.
Don't touch me!
And as a result,
you got caught splendidly
and became our sex slave.
How pathetic.
Sex slave? Me?
No! You're wrong! This can't be happening to me!
If you still refuse to accept it,
I'll take my time to make you.
Come on! Tighten up more!
More! Tighten up!
This is bad. The collar prevents me from using mana.
I can't even use magic now! If I don't do something...
You have a great potential.
I only have to make your body crave for men,
and you'll become a top-notch slave.
Rejoice, Lunalie.
You will be trained personally by me,
the chief of slave trainers.
Wh-What's that? Stop!
This is the best drug to turn you into a sex slave.
You'll start to feel so good
you'd even hate it in no time.
Drug?
Everyone that had this became men's plaything.
You'll become one soon as well.
Stop fooling around! There's no way that I am...
I am...
I'm starting to feel itchy down there!
My body... my body feels hot!
This is bad, if this goes on,
I'll really become a sex slave...
Hey there, I'm going to come soon! Take it all in!
Stop! Th-That would be a creampie!
Any more of this and I'll go crazy.
I'm gonna come!
No, I'll come! I'll get creampied!
No, no, no!
Stop! Stop, stop, stop—!
Don't!
Too bad for you. You're no longer a proud knight.
Now you're a sex slave owned
by us, the Scorpion Troupe.
No, no way! Let me go!
Ain't she a fine woman.
Stop! Don't put it inside!
Don't shoot it out!
It seems like there's yet
another mouse that sneaked
into the slave market nearby.
Oh... There's another one I didn't knew about.
This one is also...
Isn't she such a high quality beauty?
I'll have this golden-haired girl as my prey.
It will be alright, won't it?
As you please.
I wonder how I should humiliate her?
I'm looking forward for it already.
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization