Lilith, that's the name of the slaves that
humans created to satisfy their sexual desires.
They were succubi made to amplify
the desires of men and drag them to depravity...
all for the sake of filling them with pleasure.
But even now in this ever-evolving world,
Liliths are still loved by all.
After tampering with their bodies' DNA to make them
even more beautiful, more capable of satisfying sexual desire,
Liliths began to outlive the humans who made them.
They'd practically become immortal.
And naturally, humans began to fear them.
The humans were frightened that they might
steal their spot at the top of the food chain.
We've been loved, hated, and discarded.
Lilitales
act.4 "The Wandering Dancer"
Lilitales.
It was only a matter of time before the Liliths
began being exterminated by the humans.
They began a hunt to kill us, the genetically
modified monsters, by mass-producing Incubi.
We were severely outnumbered.
Sophia!
N-No!
Nothing personal.
It's not our fault that we're made to eat you guys.
Stop!
No!
I love this.
Well, time to dig in!
H-He's sucking... Stop! No!
Please stop!
Sophia!
No! No!
No!
Okay, your turn, black hair.
This taste. It's been a while.
I'm going to take this slow, savor you, and kill you later!
I can't break free!
I'm going to be killed too at this rate!
Violated by tentacles and having
my life force sucked out of me...
Your magic is so full of life.
I can tell just from this little sip.
You're delicious!
No! Stop!
Stop!
No! No! No!
Let go of me!
How's it feel?
You're usually the one controlling the sexual pleasure,
but now your position's reversed.
Must be hard on you.
No! No!
Let go of me!
Stop!
Don't move in my ass like that!
No! No!
My throat...
My body's starting to feel weird!
I don't think I can wait any longer.
I'm gonna suck it all out now.
All of it!
Delicious! So delicious!
This is high-quality life force!
I can't get enough!
Stop! Stop! Please!
Don't suck it out!
It's so hot! My life force is being sucked out of my body!
Is this it for me? Am I going to die here?
No! I... I still...
No! No!
What's happening?!
What's going on?
It's like something light is running across my body.
It's like my body's floating!
Th-This can't be! It's flowing back into her!
Our life force is flowing into her!
Th-This is impossible! We're going to be absorbed!
What's this feeling?
This pleasure... It feels like it's going to overflow!
I... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I can't stop...
Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
H-Hey, wake up...
S-Sophia, you said we would run away together!
Sophia!
In the golden age, there were tens of thousands of Liliths,
but now they'd been scattered to the winds, impossible to find.
We began hiding in underground slums to avoid being found
by the Incubi, or by being close to those who didn't hate us.
The person I stayed with was a
very kind person who liked Liliths.
I think I was lucky.
If I wasn't able to stay there
when Lilith hunting was at its peak,
I probably wouldn't be alive now.
He was really fond of me and kept
me as his slave for a long time.
I did anything he wanted me to as long as he asked.
I was happy pleasuring him.
But that didn't last forever.
Even the longest human life can
only last about a hundred years.
He left me behind leaving me looking
exactly the way I was when we first met.
I went down to the slums and sold my body
before the Incubi found me and I had to escape.
I'd go somewhere new, meet someone,
and have sex... that was my life.
I lived like that for so long that the age
I was born in was no more than a distant memory.
Civilization and technology kept marching forward.
People now traveled by carriages or wooden boats.
History had started over.
Before I knew it, my fellow Liliths had completely
disappeared along with the Incubi who pursued us.
All those who loved us, hated us, and discarded us
had forgotten about us a long time ago.
So I began traveling from city to city to find other Liliths.
I performed on stages, brothels, and in taverns.
You could always find me at a place that sold pleasure.
If Liliths were to be anywhere,
they were sure to be at those kinds of places.
Wherever I went, what I did never changed.
I was happy to pleasure anyone who lusted after me.
That's why I was born, after all.
As long as they kept pouring
their semen into me, I could live forever.
I could keep traveling the world
and have sex with all kinds of people.
Sometimes I'd end up being someone's lover
and marrying them after they divorce their wife.
But even then, I'd only stay for about thirty years.
If I stayed any longer,
they'd start to notice that I wasn't aging.
Anyone who did find out what I was
accepted that they would die before I did.
I wonder what happened to the other Liliths.
They... aren't all dead, are they?
Am I the only one left?
Where are all of you?
Don't leave me by myself!
Hey, you there!
Halt!
Do you... need something?
You're not from around here, are you?
Show me your face.
She's a good woman.
Doesn't look fully mature, but she'll do.
Take off that robe.
Show us your body.
Your face might not look it,
but your body's definitely mature.
She's gonna sell for a lot.
What are you planning to do with me?
Isn't that obvious?
We're gonna sell you off as a slave.
Slave?
You're an idiot for traveling out here by yourself.
We're gonna have lots of fun with you.
Haven't had a gem like you in a while.
It didn't matter who,
as long as their lust was focused on me,
my body got hot and turned on.
Even being raped like this made me feel like I was
needed and made me feel like I had a place to be.
That's why...
No! No!
If you're so rough, I'm gonna...
I'm about at my limit.
Swallow it!
The men who captured me were bandits of this dessert.
They were slave hunters.
I was apparently their first prey in a while.
After being taken to their base,
I was gang-raped countless times.
After some time, I was finally about to be sold off.
They took me to a city that thriver on slave trade.
They put a collar on me, stripped me naked
in front of everyone, and began to auction me off.
Apparently they thought I had value as a sex slave.
I was sold at a high price to a broker
for the slave trade business.
I thought I was done being auctioned off,
but I was just auctioned off at another slave market.
It was an underground slave market
that focused only on sex slaves.
Many women were brought there as women
and made to be sex slaves before being sold off.
It was a place for slave trade and auctions.
I thought this was a good chance.
There was no better place to
surround myself with sex than here.
I could practically live and breathe sex here.
I might find a Lilith one day.
It'd be best if I could stay here for as long as possible.
I need to do my best to make sure that I make
them happy so they want to keep me here.
And then I met her.
I knew as soon as I saw her.
She was a blood relative of a Lilith.
She'd just not woken up to her latent powers yet.
I'm sure that she didn't even have a clue about it either.
But the nostalgia I felt when I touched her...
The name's Airi.
What's your name?
I... I finally found you.
My brethren.
translation: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч