Liliths... They have faces that look just like humans.
They are beloved slaves that satisfy the lust of humans.
They titillate humans and partake on their life force.
They are lust demons made for humans to indulge in pleasure.
In an era of civilization that was
more advanced than today,
the Lilith were greatly loved by the humans.
To make them even more beautiful,
and to better satisfy their lust,
humans resorted to gene editing
to enhance their body and its cells.
Somewhere along the line, the liliths
started to drift further away from humans.
They started to live just like nomads.
It didn't take long before humans started
to see liliths as dangerous beings.
They realized that there is no money
to get at the apex of ecosystem.
We were loved. We were hated. And finally...
We were thrown away.
Vagrant Dancer
Lilitales.
As the civilization started to deteriorate,
humans started to exterminate the liliths.
They used genetically modified organisms to prey on us.
They mass-produced these vampiric demons
and began the lilith hunt.
The lilith population started to rapidly decline.
Sofia!
No, you can't!
Don't hate us for this.
We vampiric demons have to eat you lust demons!
Stop!
Ouch!
No!
I can't get enough of this!
Alright then, shall I begin sucking you dry?
D-Don't suck me! No...
I'm begging you, stop sucking!
Sofia—!
No way, no way!
No way—!
Well then... Now it's your turn, black-haired girl.
It's been a while since we had a catch.
We have to take our time enjoying this one next!
We can just kill her afterwards!
I can't get away from their grip!
I'll also get drained to death if this goes on!
They'll violate me with their tentacles,
and they'll drain my life force!
I can tell the how the mana fresh from
the source is with just one sip!
You're delicious!
No way... Stop! Stop that!
No... No... No—!
Let go of me!
No!
How does it feel
as a lust demon that manipulates lust and pleasure,
being manipulated instead.
I'll bet that it's frustrating!
No, no, let go of me!
Stop!
Not there! Don't stir me up in my ass!
No way, no way! I don't want this!
My body is turning strange!
I can't hold myself anymore!
Shall I begin sucking your everything out!
Yummy, yummy! It's a top-grade life force!
I can't get enough of this!
Stop, stop! I'm begging you, stop sucking me!
I feel hot!
My body is getting drained of life force!
Is this the end for me? Am I going to die?
No way! I... I still...
No! No—!
What's happening?!
What is this?
I feel so light. It's like my body is floating!
U-Unbelievable! It's flowing out!
Our life force is flowing in reverse instead!
Th-That can't be... We're getting drained!
What's happening?
I feel the pleasure, like it's overflowing in me!
No! I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
I can't take it anymore!
Stop that!
Stop sucking! Stop sucking! Stop sucking!
No—!
H-Hey...
Wake up, Sofia!
You... You said that we'll escape together!
Sofia...
There were a few hundred of liliths at their peak.
But now there's barely a few around.
To avoid getting caught by vampiric demons,
we hid underground and in the slums.
The day came that a man
who's fond of liliths took me.
The man who took me in is fond of liliths.
He was a really nice person.
I thought to myself that I'm lucky.
If I haven't been able to take refuge here
when the lilith hunt was at its peak,
I doubt that I'd still be alive.
He was really fond of me.
He used me as his beloved slave for a long time.
As for me, I complied to whatever orders he gave me!
I served him with all my heart.
But those times never went on forever.
Humans live for about a hundred year at most.
Since the time he first met me who's a lilith,
not a single thing changed on me.
That man left me behind
and went on by himself.
I went underground and sold my body.
I run away to other lands when
the vampiric demons find me.
I encountered new people again in other places.
And I have sex with them.
Those days continued all along.
The era where I came from is already
far away when I took notice.
The civilization and technology are steadily growing.
Nowadays, people travel by
horse carts and wooden ships.
The history repeats itself from the start.
Before I realized it, my fellow liliths
are nowhere to be found
and the vampiric demons chasing us are also gone.
The humans that loved, hated and threw us away
have already forgotten about us long ago.
I went on towns one after another
trying to find fellows of my own kind.
Theaters, brothels, bars...
I went on every place where sex is involved.
If there are still some of my own kind,
I'm sure they'll be at these places.
Wherever I went, I never changed my ways.
I seduce men, and I comply on their desire for my body.
I was born for that particular purpose.
And as long as I get poured in with their life force,
I can go on living forever.
I traveled around the world
and had sex with various people.
There were times that great men take
me as a lover, or I get married on a whim.
Even so, I only stayed in a place
for about twenty to thirty years.
Any longer than that and I'll raise
suspicions for still looking the same.
At times men found the truth
but still accepted me as their wife.
But they all died in time.
I wonder how other liliths are now...
Could they have all been dead for a long time now?
Am I the only lilith left?
Everyone, where have you all gone?
Don't leave me alone by myself.
Hey, you right there!
Stop!
What's the matter, gentlemen?
You're not someone from here, right?
Show your face.
This one's a fine girl.
She still looks like a child,
but this one's ripe enough for the picking.
Take your robe off and no silly tricks! Show your body.
And here I thought she's a child.
Isn't that body splendid?!
This one's gonna sell high!
What are you planning to do to me?
Isn't it obvious?
From now on, you'll be sold off as a slave.
Slave?
To be a girl traveling here all alone,
what an idiot you are.
We'll have a lot of fun with you
before we sell you off!
It's been a while since I last had a fine jewel.
Whoever I do it with, I meet them face on.
For that purpose, my body heats up
and shivers in ecstasy.
Being raped like this... Whenever I am having sex,
it makes me feel like I'm needed,
and that I am welcome to be here.
That's why...
You can't!
No! If you do it that rough, I'm...
I'm already at my limit!
Suck me off!
The group that abducted me came
here in the desert  and camped here.
They were slave hunters.
Looks like they haven't got a girl in a while.
Having someone like me to sleep with them,
I got repeatedly gangraped for a few days.
After some time, the day I get to be sold came.
They brought me to a town booming with slave trade.
They put a choker on our necks.
They strip us naked in front of a crowd,
and people bid for us.
It seems that I've been deemed valuable as a sex slave.
Being offered by a huge sum of money,
it looks like I've been resold by a slave trader.
I got sold to one slave market after another.
It's an underground market
that only keeps female sex slaves.
A bunch of girls are taken in as slaves.
They are treated as playthings and then cast aside.
It seems to be a place where slave traders negotiate.
I thought that this was my chance.
As a place where sex is involved,
nothing else tops this one.
This is a place where one can indulge in lust.
Maybe I'll find one of my own kind here someday.
I'd prefer staying longer here
rather than being sold off to someone.
I'm going to stay here for a while.
To get on the good side of the traders,
I should serve them a lot.
And then, I met her.
I could already tell it at first glance.
This girl has a lilith blood in her.
The blood she inherited hasn't been awakened yet.
I'm sure that she isn't aware of it.
Even so, I can feel this nostalgia on my skin...
My name is Airi!
Hey, tell me your name!
At last... I met one at last.
A fellow of my own kind.
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization