The city of commerce, Ishtal...
In the underground of it is a slave market.
Why are you doing this?
It is a horrible place swarming with desires and conspiracies.
I'm going to indulge myself...
The cleric named Cless snuck inside it,
but ended up getting caught.
That can't be!
I'm a cleric, an instrument of God.
The bishop of Ishtal's religious group
took her and defiled her chastity.
It's pouring in...
There'll never be enough slaves
no matter how many we get!
No way... Princess Jill, Luna-san...
You've been going through all this?!
The similarly abducted Princess Jill and I, together with Cless
Rape me if you want! I'm here!
It's squeezing, yes! Your pussy is squeezing a lot too!
all underwent a severe training with these grunts.
Shoot it out if you want to!
We were treated like playthings.
Just hurry... Hurry up and make an end of this!
I'll be creampied... I'll be sullied
both in my mouth and down there!
...I'm begging you!
No—!
I, who resisted until the end
No... No! Stop...
Let go of me!
was forced to fight a demon while practically naked.
If only I can use magic, this monster is nothing!
I was raped in front of everyone.
You'll end up not getting satisfied with a human anymore!
Just like I'm in for a show!
Hey, what's wrong, knightess?
Having all hope abandoned and about to lose heart,
Why are you so stubborn?
a girl named Airi shows herself in front of me.
Stop! Don't put any more of that on me!
My body...
How about you give up already?
No matter how many times she caress and make me come,
even if I'm near to succumbing in pleasure,
Being a prostitute like me isn't that bad.
No!
I am... I am still...
Hey, are you still not giving up?
I won't give up.
I don't want to give up!
Bloodline of Lust Demon
Lilitales.
I understand.
Huh?
I'll let you awaken that power of yours.
What is happening?
It feels like something's being released...
Isn't the true power that you wield
a heroic power that can vanquish enemies?
Dyed with the color of sex... The power of Lilith.
Power of Lilith?
You'll be accepting pleasures and desires.
It's alright, the craving will subside
when you accept those into you.
What you need right now is to fight
an enemy you ought to defeat.
With cherishment and devotion,
take the enemy in you,
and captivate him with you affection.
What do you mean? I don't get it...
I don't understand what you're saying!
It's okay if you don't understand it yet now.
Your body will memorize it in no time.
That's good... Looks like you're
dealing with this quite well now.
That's how a sex slave behaves.
Am I right, Lunalie?
Why? Why am I sucking him on my own?
My body feels hot!
It won't stop throbbing!
This is bad! I... I am... again!
That's it, you understand it well.
That's a proper etiquette for sex slaves.
Get yourself ready down there.
I am about to make you moan with my penis!
Why? Even though I never... wanted to do this!
It's like I'm screaming "rape me" inside my mind!
Sex... I want to have sex!
Alright! I'm about to come!
Catch it with your mouth!
We're far from done! This is just the beginning!
I'll have you eat me next using this
lower mouth of yours, okay?
Aren't you dripping wet?
You're actually craving for my cock, huh?
That's because it feels like I can't help it
anymore when you began.
I can't fight this pleasure!
What's the matter, aren't you
behaving yourself now?
You don't feel like fighting back anymore, huh?
What you need for now is... cherishment and devotion...
Take the enemy in you... with you affection.
Please, do it...
Hmm?
Make a mess of my body
and violate me as you wish, please!
You finally accepted yourself being a sex slave!
Okay, I'm gonna do it just as you want!
Y-Yes! Right there!
You've become a good sex slave!
Alright, I'll make you my concubine!
Here you go, one creampie coming right up!
It's coming! I'm gonna come!
I can't take it anymore!
Come one, your body started to slack around!
Have you had enough, or do you want to thrust more?
I want it... I want you hard thing!
Shove it in! Please!
Fine then. I don't really get it,
but I'll let you off from being demanding. I'll rape you!
I'll shoot it inside you... I'll spray it in and knock you up!
Shoot it, shoot all of it! I'll take it all into me!
Shoot as much semen as you like
inside me! All of it, all of it!
What's happening? My body won't stop!
More, more!
I'm coming!
It feels good!
What's this?
Hey, didn't I say it earlier?
What you need to do now is fight your enemies.
Airi... What's with this shining thing?
"I want power even if I have to sell my soul to a demon!"
Aren't you the one who said it? But then again...
The one you sold your soul onto wasn't a demon.
For now, that is!
Airi...
Let's get going then!
Don't you have someone you want to save?
Auspicious! Auspicious indeed!
Alright, I'm almost there. I'm nearing climax!
Beloved bishop, please feel free to ejaculate!
I'm begging you, let us have it! Give us your semen!
Come on, more! Let me have more fun with you!
Yes, bishop! Please use my body as you please!
I am your toy! I'll abide with your every will!
Give in to the hypnosis, you'll feel better.
Good! Feels good! My tits feel good!
That's good, here you go!
You put more strength in your asshole,
and you'll squeeze even tighter down there!
I understand...
How's this, bishop? Does my insides feel good?
Oh, that's right! Just like that!
Wait for it, I'll be shooting it in you again!
It feels so hot! Your thing is twitching!
Shoot it... Shoot it out please! I'll accept all of it!
Please feel free to pour it inside me!
Have you already become a slave to my hypnosis?
Y-Yes... Yes!
I am... I am overjoyed to have
the beloved bishop as my partner!
So you finally gave in.
I'll give a cleric like you a guidance using my meat stick!
Thank you, bishop!
Use your meat stick on my sinful body
and purify me please!
I see, I see. Fine with me.
I'll have a good taste of it!
Incredible! It's reaching deep inside me!
Your hot thing is stirring me up inside!
Your inside is drenched!
What a scandalous and slutty cleric you are!
Please forgive me, bishop!
Please... Please reprimand me!
Please exact a punishment on
this scandalous body of mine!
Well said!
I will exact a divine retribution into your womb!
So intense!
It's coming again... Coming... Coming!
Bishop...
Please make use of my body even more!
If it will make you happy,
I'll do whatever you want me to!
I'm feeling it, I'm feeling good!
To have the honor of my body
getting licked by the bishop...
I can never be more grateful!
I can't get enough of this! You're squeezing
me so tight! I won't be able to endure this!
I'll be thrusting up to your best place inside!
I'm at my limit. I'm starting to get exhausted.
That won't do, bishop!
What?!
That's right, beloved bishop.
We can't stop ourselves as well!
Let's all come at the same time!
Th-This can't be! You two, what's happening here?!
Look, your cock is hard as nail again.
My hips are shaking on their own too!
I'm begging you, dear bishop!
More... Give me more of your compassion!
I'm dripping more and more
wet of dirty juice down there!
You! Get off me!
My consciousness is—!
Coming... Coming, coming...
I'm coming—!
Could this be... an illusion? It's an illusion?!
Since when? When did I start—?!
How is it? How does it feel to have someone like you
who usually hypnotize women,
to fall into an illusion instead?
Y-You—!
Shoot it out! Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it!
Shoot it out!
No!
This can't be...
Stop! Stop!
You came this much already.
You're more than satisfied, right?
Cless, get a hold of yourself!
The bishop's hypnosis is removed.
Everything's okay now.
Th-The princess... Princess Jill is still...
Where's Jill? Where did they take her?
Sh-She was taken by the
mysterious man in white robes
to the Royal Tombs to break the seal...
Alright.
Wait for me, Jill. This time for sure...
I'll definitely save you!
No—!
Jill!
Luna! Luna! Please get me away from here!
Save me—!
How far are you willing to go after
for her, silver-haired woman!
Sparing one little girl ended up
to be my biggest miscalculation.
Silver-hair, at that time...
I should have killed you...
I finally caught up with you! I've been
looking for you all this time!
Ever since that day!
Well then.
I'll entertain all of you guests who came here.
Wh-Whats this?!
This one looks very strong!
Is this his true form?
Alright, death awaits you, young girl!
I'll smash you down with all might!
Luna—!
I'll strike you down and exact
vengeance for my fallen comrades.
And then I'll get Jill back!
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization