To find Jill, the princess who was abducted
by mysterious men in white robes,
I snuck in Ishtal, a large slave city.
You'll have to give me plenty of pleasure.
I had no other choice but to sell my body
as told by the information broker.
I'm going to be deflowered by this thing soon.
I was ordered by the merchant to give
service on his swelled up meat rod.
W-With this thick thing!
Still having no experience, my virginity...
My chastity was defiled without any mercy.
I see... And so you came here to look for me?
An initial payment of twenty thousand dinar, indeed.
And afterwards, I was completely caught in their scheme.
This should be alright. Hurry up for Jill's...
It's a paralysis needle. Don't worry.
I ended up getting sold off as a sex slave.
When you wake up, you'll learn
stuffs that feel even better.
Quit joking!
L-Like I'd ever adhere to your will!
Jill, who was abducted by men
in white robes has a royal blood.
Wanting to break the seal in the Shandora ruins,
they used an aphrodisiac Jill who blatantly refused
to cooperate and drowned her in pleasure.
Alright, I bid 780 000 dinar!
I can't help wanting that cheeky side of her!
Even so, Jill is unyielding.
Mine's 850 000 dinar!
They auctioned her virginity to these men.
Let me shove it in that tiny cunt!
I love this! I want this girl!
No, no, no...
No—!
I want her so much, I'd make her my sex slave!
She was forcibly humiliated in front of everyone.
I can let you have the honor to train her every night...
Although I'm about to be with Jill soon,
I don't have a way to save her.
Woman from the royal guard that
survived, you came for us in the end.
You're quite the fool not knowing...
I continued to be raped as a sex slave.
No, I'll come! I'll get creampied!
No matter how my mind denies it,
No, no, no!
my body got corrupted from being drowned in pleasure.
Stop! Stop, stop, stop—!
And then,
Oh... There's another one I didn't know about.
there's yet another sacrifice in a nearby slave market.
Sacrificed To Scorpion
Lilitales.
Bishop... Why are you doing this?
We have a delicate political issue on a certain country.
This one slave went through the system.
We just got done having the said commodity handed over.
How treacherous of you.
You're supposed to be a minister.
First, take that robe of yours off.
Slowly, alright?
No way... I can't do such a shameful thing!
As expected from a priestess of Central Church.
You can resist my hypnotic magic.
How about this, then?
This can't be, why?
I can't... No way, I shouldn't take them off!
Why are my hands...
Come on, spread your ass wider and let me see.
N-No... I can't!
Alright, then.
I'm going to indulge myself
with a clergywoman's chastity.
Stop... Please, not that...
Anything but that, spare me!
What a tight grip you have! I can't get enough of this!
We can't do this! Please, pull it out!
Please pull it out! Stop thrusting!
You're still holding on? You're quite something!
No! My body!
I can't move my body!
My hypnotic magic also comes
with an aphrodisiac effect.
It starts with tainting your mind, and your body gets corrupted!
Look, your nipples already got hard.
Your body is awakening on the pleasure!
He's wrong! That can't be!
I'm a cleric, an instrument of God.
Such pleasure is...
I thought that you're just an innocent girl,
but you're so hot now like
you're melting me down there!
No! Please don't say that!
No, this can't be... I can't be improper like this!
Alright!
Accept all of it and make yourself at ease!
That is but yet another will of God as well!
No way, why? Why is my body throbbing this much?
It is my first time, and I'm being
raped against my will... Why?
I'm about to give my semen inside you!
And with this, you will be born again!
N-No! No...
Please!
Anything but a creampie... Spare me! Please!
Here you go! I'm coming... I'm coming!
I'm coming!
No... No, you can't!
Stop! Spare me! No way!
No way! No way! No way!
No—!
It's pouring in... Something hot is pouring inside!
From now on, you're going
to join the others as sex slaves.
Together with that princess and knightess.
Princess?
Knightess?
It can't be...
No!
I'll come again!
Spare me already!
Jill... No way, why?
Isn't that great? You're reunited
with your beloved princess!
I'm begging you, let Jill go!
In exchange, I'll... I will do anything you tell me!
We can't do that!
Even hungry beasts like us have our pride!
There'll never be enough slaves
no matter how many we get!
Luna! Sorry... I'm sorry!
You got yourself into this for my sake!
That's right! Isn't all this your fault?
You need to be punished for this!
It hurts! Stop, stop!
If you pinch it that much, my nipples will go numb!
No way... Princess Jill, Luna-san...
You've been going through all this?!
Do you get it now? Too bad for you,
but no help will come!
All of you will be sex slaves,
and become our playthings!
Rape me if you want! I'm here!
You can't do it to Jill and Cless anymore...
You got some guts! Well then...
I'm going to use this hole!
That part is—!
It's squeezing, yes! Your pussy is squeezing a lot too!
They're scraping me! My...
my insides are getting messed up!
Here you go, princess! This is
the taste of our plebian penises!
Your high-class mouth and pussy...
We'll enjoy ourselves with them!
This is cruel! So cruel!
Please, don't make Luna and Cless suffer this anymore!
I can't get enough of this! This blondie has
large jugs, rubbing them feels great!
Please stop groping them!
Let go of your hands!
You have this sexy body, and you're a cleric?
With this sloppy pussy,
I'm sure you can persuade men!
You slutty priestess!
N-No... Stop thrusting!
Th-That's not true, this is...
Okay... It's about time!
I'm going to shoot my thick semen into you!
It's alright! Shoot it out if you want to!
Just hurry... Hurry up and make an end of this!
I'll be creampied... I'll be sullied
both in my mouth and down there!
I don't want any more of this! Spare me!
No, No...
Please don't... shoot it down there!
I'm begging you!
No—!
I'll be taking this blonde girl with me, is that fine?
I still need something from the princess.
Okay, do what you want.
Wait!
Hmm?
I don't care whatever happens to me.
But don't do this to Jill and Cless anymore!
Her eyes show that she hasn't given up yet. How interesting.
Then show me how tough you are.
Until you understand that you're just men's plaything,
I'm going to train you hard.
Prepare yourself, Lunalie.
If only I can use magic, this monster is nothing!
There's no way I can win with just a cypress staff!
What's wrong? You look terrible!
Were you not once a royal guard?
You monster!
No! Stop...
No...
Let go of me!
Okay, the main show is about to begin.
N-No! Wait! Please!
No! Don't rape me!
You'll end up not getting satisfied with a human anymore!
Hey, what's wrong, knightess?
Show me what a young lady can do!
I look pathetic! I can't even
fight back on this dreadful state!
I'm just getting raped! It's like I'm just in for a show!
Hey, take a look! It's about to shoot one out.
I'm getting filled... No!
No way! No! No! Stop—!
Oh, that's amazing!
If she gets pregnant, I'll look forward
to what kind of child it will be.
Her heart is yet to be conquered.
Airi, you're going to train that woman tonight.
Drown her body in pleasure
so that she'll never fight back again.
Yes, Grims-sama!
I don't know how many
days had it been anymore.
Is it noon now? Or maybe it's night.
Why are you so stubborn?
You can just empty your mind and
let yourself captivated by sex.
Who... are you?
Hey, tell me your name!
Stop! Don't put any more of that on me!
My body... My body feels hot!
No... Don't!
How about you give up already?
Being a prostitute like me isn't that bad.
I get intimate with men and
I get to feel a lot good in return.
It'll be easier for you that way.
No way... I... I'm...
Not there... Stop!
There are a lot of customers
that loves going for the asshole.
You have to get yourself used to this.
My butt... Not in my butt!
I'm begging you, that's...
This is bad, if this goes on...
My body will be overtaken by
someone that isn't me anymore.
Being forced to go through all this, I will go crazy!
I'll really lose my mind!
Hey, are you still not giving up?
I won't give up.
I don't want to give up!
I want to have power.
A power to protect someone important to me...
I don't care even if I have to sell
my soul to a demon for that power!
I understand.
Huh?
I'll let you awaken that power of yours.
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization