In order to find Jill, the princess
who was kidnapped by mysterious men,
garbed in white, I traveled
to the stave market city, Eastal.
– You and I are gonna have a lot of fun.
– In order to pay for information I desperately needed,
I had no choice but to sell my body.
– You and I are gonna have a lot of fun.
– In order to pay for information I desperately needed,
I had no choice but to sell my body.
– I'm selling my virginity... for money!
– In order to pay for information I desperately needed,
I had no choice but to sell my body.
– This thing's going to be inside me soon.
– I was ordered to take care of the merchant's meat stick.
– This... This huge thing is gonna...
I was ordered to take care of the merchant's meat stick.
– I was ordered to take care of the merchant's meat stick.
And he took my virginity without even a second thought.
I see. So that's why you've come to me?
– The two hundred thousand advance.
– But I completely fell for their trap.
– It's all here.
– That's enough, right? Now find Jill!
– It's just a needle dipped in a relaxant.
– And then they forced me to be their sex slave.
– Don't worry, when you wake up, we'll
teach you even more pleasurable things.
– Don't worry, when you wake up,
we'll teach you even more pleasurable things.
– No! I will never work with you!
– The men in white that captured Jill wanted the
Shandorian blood running through her veins.
– But since she refused, they used an
aphrodisiac on her to break her down.
– I'll pay seven hundred eighty thousand Dinas!
– But since she refused, they used an
aphrodisiac on her to break her down.
– I can't wait to get my hands on her!
– But since she refused, they used an
aphrodisiac on her to break her down.
– I can't wait to get my hands on her!
– I'll pay eight hundred fifty thousand Dinas!
– But still, Jill wouldn't break,
so they sold her virginity in an auction.
– Let me plant my seed in that small body of hers!
– But still, Jill wouldn't break,
so they sold her virginity in an auction.
– I want her! I want this wench!
– But still, Jill wouldn't break,
so they sold her virginity in an auction.
– I want her! I want this wench!
– I wanna make you my sex slave!
– They forced her to endure humiliation.
– If you'd like, we can sell you a chance to train her every night.
– Even though I physically wasn't too far away from Jill.
– I knew you'd come here, woman.
– Even though I physically wasn't too far away from Jill,
– I couldn"t go to her aid at all.
– You came walking right into the arms of my brokers and subordinates.
– I couldn't go to her aid at all.
– I continued to be defiled as their sex slave.
– Stop! Let me go!
– I'm gonna cum!
– But no matter how much I struggled,
my body couldn't escape the pleasure.
– I'm gonna cum!
– But no matter how much I struggled,
my body couldn't escape the pleasure.
– No! No! Stop!
– And then, a new sacrifice appeared in the marketplace.
– Looks like there was another rat who snuck in here.
Lilitales
act.2 "The offering of the scorpions"
Lilitales.
Wh-Why is this happening?
We have complete control over this city.
Just need to pay the right price.
Know that you touch the body of a holy woman.
How about you take off those garments of yours.
Slowly.
I-I can't do something that humiliating.
Oh, you really are a holy maiden of the Central Church.
Not just anyone can resist my magic.
Well then, how about this?
No way! Wh-Why? Stop! Don't take them off!
Why won't my hands stop?!
Come, show me your ass more.
No! Stop!
Now then, it's time for me to fully
enjoy the virginity of a holy maiden.
Please, no! Anything but that!
Anything but that!
This tightness is superb!
No, please take it out!
Please take it out! Stop!
You still can will yourself to move? Impressive.
No! My body won't move!
My brainwashing magic is the same as an aphrodisiac.
At first it just affects the mind, but I think
it's time for you to feel it with your body as well!
Look, your nipples are already becoming hard.
Your body is awakening to pleasure!
No! That can't be true!
I'm a cleric... a servant of god!
I can't be feeling pleasure!
Your insides are so wet and hot,
it's hard to believe you were just a virgin a minute ago!
No! Please don't say that!
I need to fight it! I can't succumb to this!
Now then, it's time for you
to take it all in and fall into comfort.
This is also a part of God's will.
No... Why is my body getting so excited?
This is my first time and I'm being raped, so why?!
I will now unload my semen inside you!
And you will be reborn!
No! No!
Please, no!
Please not inside! Anything but that!
Please!
All right here I go!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
No! No! Stop!
Please, don't! Don't! Don't! Don't!
No!
It's coming out... His hot stuff is going inside of me...
You'll be a fine addition to our sex slaves.
Just like that princess and female knight.
Princess? Female knight?
Does he mean...
No!
Please stop!
Let me go!
Jill? Why?!
Aren't you happy? You've been wanting
to see the princess all this time!
Please, let Jill go!
I'll do anything in return!
Not happening.
There are a lot of horny guys here,
we can never get enough help!
Luna, I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
You came to save me, but now you're...
Yeah, it's all your fault!
I think you need to be punished!
O-Ouch! Stop! Stop!
You're going to rip my nipple off like that!
P-Princess Jill and Luna, why are you both...
Well, now you know.
You're out of luck. Nobody else is coming to save you.
You'll just have to be sex slaves for the rest of your lives!
Please, if you're going to rape someone, let it be me.
Don't subject Cless or Jill to this anymore!
I like your attitude.
How about we use this hole here?
That's...
Damn, it's tight!
Her pussy's getting tighter too!
They're rubbing against each other!
They're messing up my stomach!
Come on Princess,
savor the taste of our peasant dicks
with your royal mouth and pussy!
This... This is too horrible!
Please, stop doing this to me!
This is amazing.
This blonde bitch has huge tits... feel so good to rub!
Stop! Please stop!
Let me go!
You're really a holy maiden with an erotic body like this?!
Your pussy's sucking me in like the whore you are!
N-No,
don't say that!
Th-This isn't what it looks like!
Okay, I think it's time to give you some cum!
Fine! Cum if you must!
Just hurry and end this already!
They're going to cum?
They're going to defile both my mouth and pussy!
I don't want this! Please stop!
No! No!
Please don't cum!
Please! I'm begging you!
Mercy!
I'll be taking this blonde woman. Any objections?
I still have business with the Princess.
Fine. Do what you want.
Wait!
I don't care what happens to me, but Cless and Jill...
Please, let them go!
Her eyes say that she hasn't given up yet.
Interesting.
Let's see how long it takes for you to break.
I'll thoroughly train you until you realize
you only exist to be fucked by men.
Prepare yourself, Lunalie.
If I could just use my magic,
I could easily beat this thing.
There's no way I can win with just a wooden stick!
What's the matter? This is pathetic!
You were a knight, weren't you?!
Take this!
No! Stop!
Let go of me!
Good, this is where the fun begins.
No, please, don't!
– No, don't move!
– Look, your body's able to have sex with monsters now!
What's wrong, Knight?! Can't you fight back?
This is pathetic.
I can't fight back.
All I can do is get raped by this monster.
This wasn't a fight, this was a demonstration!
Hey, Luna, here comes round one.
This is too much!
No! No!
No! Don't!
Wow, can't wait to see what kind of child is born.
I'm not done breaking her yet.
Airi, you train that woman tonight.
Make sure she experiences pleasures
so great that she can never fight back again.
Okay, Master Karima.
How many days has it been?
I don't know anymore.
I don't even know what time of day it is.
Why are you so stubborn?
You should just forget about everything
and let yourself drown in sex.
Who... are you?
Hey, what's your name?
No, stop! Don't put that on me!
My body's getting so hot! No!
No!
Just give up.
It's not bad being a prostitute, like me, you know?
Just flirting with the men a little will result
in you being pleasured out of your mind.
It's so much easier this way.
No... I...
No, that's my...
No!
There are a lot of customers who like anal.
You gotta learn to like it.
No, stop... My ass...
Please! That's not...
If this keeps up, I'm going to lose myself
and become something else.
My head's going crazy from this!
I'm really going to go crazy!
Hey, you still haven't given up?
I will not give up!
I don't want to give up!
I want strength!
I want the strength to rescue the one I care about!
I'd sell my soul to a demon
if it meant gaining that strength!
Okay.
I'll help you awaken to your power.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Cless
"I'm going to try the incantation for purification. Stand back, I'll erect a barrier..."
"...!!?"
"...uh..."
Cless
"...Where... Where am I? Luna-san...? ...Irbam-san...!?"
"..."
In front of me stood a mirror... a single mirror...
But there didn't seem to be anything suspicious about it... But there might be a clue laying around...
While staying on alert, I carefully approached it... and I looked into the mirror.
Cless
(...huh...?!)
"...I... teach you... what... tastes like... thoroughly...!"
"...top...! ...Please stop...!!"
Cless
(...What...? ...Is this...)
"Hah... ah... no... hah, hah... hah, ...ahhh...! ...don't... uu... ahhh...!"
Bandit
"Gehahaha...! ...You moan cute...!! Come on, scream more for me!"
Cless
"Stop...! No...!! ...Please stop...!!"
What I saw in the mirror was a single, blonde-haired priestess being held down and violated by multiple men...
The clothes she were were familiar... Her voice was one I'd heard before... The girl getting relentlessly ravaged by the men, screaming the entire time was without a doubt... me...
Cless
(...Why...? ...Why... is this...)
(...Another... Mirror...)
Cless
(...)
"...ah... Lord... Bish... ah..."
Bishop
"Heh heh heh... How's that... You can't even focus, can you? Your body feels like it's on fire... feels good, doesn't it?"
Cless
"Ha... ah... ah..."
What I saw in the mirror was an image of myself in the clutches of the bishop, slowly falling slave to his powers...
Cless
(...)
My face became flushed due to the stimulation... Confusion and dismay filled my eyes... My face dripped with sweat, my breathing ragged...
The face reflected... if was just like the one I saw in the vision I saw...
Raped by the bandits, making strange moans... toyed with by the bishop... the look on my face... It was one of amorousness...
Cless
"...this can't be... I... I'm not... This has to be... a trick..."
Loose-lipped man
Bug-eyed man
Tavern: Silver Goblet
Stage Shed
Fortune Telling Booth
To the City Field
Man
"Heh heh... So you're the rumored sex-hungry servant of god... Help me find salvation too..."
Cless
"No... let go of me..."
Man
"So soft... Feels good to squeeze, my hands just in... Heh heh..."
Cless
"No... ah..."
A strange light is reflecting form the mirror...
Look into it
Leave it alone
Cless
"!!!"
Target>
The mirror prepares to attack!
Target>Magic Mirror
Normal attack from equipped weapon
Cless attacks,
Magic Mirror is dealt 153 damage
–Mana Break–
Cless takes 7 damages
Cless's mana is lowered by 1
Turn 2
Blessing (Support magic/M3)
Cless chants a blessing.
Cless's defense rises.
–Mana Break–
Cless takes 7 damage
Cless's mana is lowered by 1
Cless
"Hya... ooh, ah, ...ha... if you do it that hard... ahh, ooh..."
The man behind me fondled my breasts, pinching and flicking my nipples. His movement made my eyes gloss over, and the moans that came out of my mouth were ones that I'd never heart before.
...My heart began to beat quicker... Why...? This isn't something I should want to see, but...
I could hear the sound of me swallowing my saliva... It wasn't a sound that came out of the mirror...
Luna
"What's the matter Cless? Salman-sensei is looking a little backed up... You should hurry up and help relieve him, don't you think...?"
"Oh, I get it... You want to do it together? Okay. ...Fufu... Let's feel good Salman-sensei together...
Cless
"Wh-What... Luna-san... What are you saying..."
Airi
"What do you mean? That's something you're doing all the time, isn't it? What's the matter? Are you half-asleep or something?
Tawern Owner
"Where were you... The customers are waiting for you..."
Cless
"...Why... What has gotten into everyone!!? This...! Everything is messed up!"
"Everything you've seen until now are things deep within your heart,
they're your true desires... our twisted desires... our deepest desires..."
Cless
"M-My true nature!? That... Those obscene images are my true desires...!? ...Th-That's a horrible joke!"
"...Joke...? ...Fufu... heheheheheh..."
Man
That's right. It has to be you missile. You need to save those suffering from their carnal desires and purify them of their sins... You're the symbol of salvation – the priestess of obscenity."
Cless
"..."
(...aahhh... ah...)
Cless
"Hello... fufu... Welcome... To the Ishtal Orthodox Church... To the Room of the Depraved..."
"Man is but an imperfect offspring of God that has been possessed by demons... the demons come out through their flesh and scorch them. They are sinners, continuously haunted by their carnal desires..."
Cless
"This place is one to save those lost in the pleasures of the flesh... Do you require salvation...?"