Jill!
You bastards!
Let Jill go!
Luna...
For royal guards, they didn't put up too much of a fight.
Rlease, spare her!
You can do whatever you want with me!
We will not kill her.
We still have something we need that woman to do for us.
What is he talking about?
When I returned alone to the castle,
all that waited for me was
the horrible torture from my comrades.
Why are you the only one to come back alive?!
Huh?!
I know the answer.
You made a deal with those bandits
and sold the princess off as a slave!
N-No, I...
– Don't play dumb! We have proof!
– They set me up.
– The bandits framed me!
– Spit it out, you traitor! Where's the Princess?!
I escaped from my cell and began
searching for clues on where Jill might be.
Wait for me, Jill.
I promise, I will save you!
Lilitales
act.1 "The Silver Knight Prisoner"
Lilitales.
The eastern city of the desert, Eastal...
It's a spot where slave traders
and wanderers alike congregate.
If Jill is to be sold off as a slave,
this is where she has to be!
I see. So that's why you've come to me?
You're a big slave auctioneer in this town, aren't you?
Please, I need you to gather information for me.
I could do it, but information ain't free.
Yeah... this'll cost you about two hundred
thousand Dina or so in advance.
Two hundred thousand Dina?!
That much?!
Well if you don't got the coin,
you can always pay it off with your body.
I'll introduce you to someone
who can get you the customers.
It's okay if you don't want to.
If you think you can find your princess
in this huge-ass town with no leads, go ahead.
So, what's it gonna be?
Fine.
I'll... I'll pay it off with my body.
Oh yeah, these are valuable goods.
Vatil really brought me a good girl.
You said your name's Lunalie?
You look like a virgin.
I... I am.
Very good. I'll pay off the advance
you need for the slave search.
But in exchange, you'll give me your virginity.
You and I are gonna have a lot of fun.
No turning back now.
I'm selling my virginity... for money!
That's good.
Do that more.
Suck it. Make me feel good.
We're not done yet.
One time's not enough for me.
This thing's going to be inside me soon.
This... This huge thing is gonna...
What's going on here? You're already wet?
N-No!
I'm...
Let's get on to the main attraction.
But how about you spread your legs and beg for it?
Offer your virginity to me.
I-I can't do that!
Then we don't have a deal. All right?
Please... Please put it in!
I... give you my virginity!
All right.
Good.
And with that, your virginity is mine.
Please don't be that rough!
You're gonna break me!
Your insides are twitching and closing in around me!
Feels good, huh?
No! That can't be true!
That can't be...
I'm getting turned on!
I gave him my virginity against my will
and now he's doing me so mercilessly,
but my pussy just keeps getting wetter!
Why is it getting so excited?
This... This shouldn't be...
No!
How can you be this erotic when you're just a virgin?
You have a talent for this!
No! Don't say that!
I'm... I'm not like that!
I'm about at my limit.
I'm gonna cum. I'm gonna cum!
Please! Not inside! Anything but that!
Wait! Wait!
Remember the taste of the man who
broke your hymen and took your virginity!
It's coming! It's coming!
This is too good. I haven't came this much in ages!
The two hundred thousand advance.
It's all here.
That's enough, right? Now find Jill!
Sorry, I planned to do that,
but I had a deal with these guys.
It's just a needle dipped in a relaxant.
Don't worry, when you wake up,
we'll teach you even more pleasurable things.
Sorry, it's more profitable to sell slaves.
Y-You lowlife!
This isn't what we agreed on!
If a silver haired woman appears before me,
I'm to give her over to you.
That was the deal, right, Sir Grims?
Jill, I'm sorry, I...
So? Are you about ready to cooperate with us?
No! I will never work with you!
You have the blood of King Yukari flowing through you.
Your genes are the key to undoing
the seal of the Shandora ruins, Princess Jill.
If you refuse to willingly work with us,
we have our own plan.
No! Stop!
Please don't put that drug on me anymore!
So hot! My body's getting so hot!
My head's going crazy!
Please! Stop!
Stop my body from going haywire!
The human brain can typically deal with pain,
but not so much with pleasure.
N-No! Not my butt!
St-Stop! Not my butt!
– Take your fingers out of there!
– Does it really feel that good?
You may be a princess by name, but strip everything
away and you're nothing but a little girl.
Stop! Stop!
Don't rub me there!
It's like there's oil being rubbed inside my butt!
I... No! No! No!
Feel restricted?
If you work with us, we'll release you.
I... I will not!
I will never do anything you want me to do!
You've left us with no choice. We'll try something else.
What?! They're not done yet?!
Well then. To everyone that's gathered here.
I offer the virginity of Princess of the Grantz Kingdom.
I'll pay seven hundred eighty thousand Dinas!
I can't wait to get my hands on her!
I'll pay eight hundred fifty thousand Dinas!
– Let me plant my seed in that small body of hers!
– No! No! No!
No! My virginity's being sold!
I'm going to be their plaything!
How about it?
As you can see, she's still untouched down here.
Very well! One million Dinas!
That ought to be enough.
So, I can do whatever I'd like to, correct?
Here?!
This can't be real! They're all watching!
I'll make you a woman with my dick, Princess.
Stop! No!
I don't want to do it with this guy!
He's doing it...
I can't believe my purity... my virginity has been...
You're a virgin, but you're already a wet mess down here!
No! My body's so hot even though this is my first time!
My pussy's twitching so hard, I... No! No!
I want her! I want this wench!
I wanna make you my sex slave!
If you'd like, we can sell you
a chance to train her every night.
You may defile her as much as you'd like.
No! No!
I don't want to be a slave!
– I don't want to be, so why am I...
– All right, it's about time I come!
– No! No! No!
– I'm gonna flood you with my seed, Princess Jill!
No! Stop!
Don't cum!
I'm going to get pregnant!
No! Stop! Stop!
No!
He came inside me. He really came inside me!
You're not done yet.
We're just getting started!
I'm gonna fill you even more with my seed!
I'm going to break if this keeps up!
Please, save me! Luna! Luna!
Luna!
Stop!
I knew you'd come here, woman.
You came walking right into the arms
of my brokers and subordinates.
Stop! Let me go!
Don't touch me!
And now that you're captured
you'll become my sex slave.
Serves you right.
Sex slave? I am?!
No! No!
I'm... I'm not!
If you still don't understand that, I'll help you!
Come on! Get tighter!
More! Tighter!
It's no good. My magic's being sealed.
If I can't use magic, I can't do anything!
Your assets are high quality.
All that's left is to make you into
a slave that craves a man's body.
Rejoice, Lunalie.
You're about to be taught the ways of the slave by me.
Wh-What?! Stop!
This is a drug that'll help you become the best sex slave.
It'll make you feel real good real soon.
Drug?!
All women spread this on their skin and pleasure men.
You'll do the same.
In your dreams! I will not...
I will not...
My pussy's getting so excited.
My body's on fire!
– No! At this rate, I really will become a sex slave!
– Come on!
I'm about to cum. Take it in!
Wait! No anything but that!
If this goes any further, I'm going to lose it!
I'm gonna cum!
No! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna get cummed in!
No! No! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
No!
How unfortunate for you. You're no longer a knight.
You're a sex slave of the Scorpion Gang now.
No! Let go of me!
What a fine woman!
Stop! Don't put it in! Don't cum!
Looks like there was another rat who snuck in here.
Oh? Another fool.
Wait, she's...
She isn't too bad.
I'm going to hunt down this blonde woman.
You're okay with that, right?
Be my guest.
How shall I humiliate you?
I look forward to this.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Imperial Knight
Lunalie
Princess
Jill
As the Imperial Knight assigned to Princess Jill,
Lunalie accompanied her on a pilgrimage to the sacred land.
On their way back, they were met with disaster...
The guards that protected her were slain in a surprise attack by bandits and Lunalie was raped...
Jill
"No way!! I will never obey you!!!"
And the princess fell into the hands of the enemy.
But the lone female knight rose...
She headed towards the lawless slave market city...
If she lost, she'd become their plaything. If she was caught, she'd be their sex slave.
But all this was to avenger her comrades and recover the princess...
Target> Slave Hunter A
Luna prepares to attack
Slave Hunter A attacks,
Luna is dealt 11 damage
Counter -> Luna attacks
Slave Hunter A is dealt 48 damage
Slave Hunter B attacks,
Luna is dealt 13 damage
Counter -> Luna attacks
Slave Hunter B is dealt 45 damage
Informant Dill
"200.000 Dina in advance"
Luna
"Tw-Two hundred...!?"
Cless
Airi
Target> Bandit Leader
Cless attacks,
Bandit Leader is dealt 21 damage
Bandit Grunt
"Ha! Gotcha!!"
Target> Collared Guard
"Dancing Dragger"
<Input commands in allotted
time for HIT Combo>
Cless
"...No...! Don't!!!"
Airi
"...Ah... Haaa...!!"
Former Female Knight
"I was sold from one slave market to another... these slave markets are specifically for sex slaves..."
Bishop
"In the future... you will tail come here and you will accept my treatment... understood...?"
Luna
"Mm..."
Audience
"Just like that! Take off another piece!! Take off the bottom stuff too!!"
Luna
"Even if I don't want to give up... I don't have a way to fight back... I don't know what to do!"
Merchant Group Member
"Oh... This is a fine woman... Her body is absolutely lawless..."
Luna
"I will avenge my comrades and take back the princess!! I've been waiting for this day all this time!!"