Papillon Rose
Lingerie Soldier
City in the night. The world is sleeping.
yoru no tokai sekai wa nemuri
Rustle and whisper
zawameki mo sasayaki mo
Repaint the lies.
uso ga nurikaeru
Illumination. At the end of the maze.
illumination meikyuu no hate
Flies down upon the butterfly of darkness.
maiorita yami no chou
It now closes its wings.
hane wo ima tojiru
I just want you. Is that so bad?
tada anata wo motomeru no wa ikenai koto desu ka?
In my body, the energy keeps burning forever.
zutto karada no oku de moeteru energy
Even when I sigh.
kuchibiru toikisade
It doesn't reach you.
anata ni wa todokanai no
My heart. Can't find its love.
mune tsumaru ai no yukue
I will find the key.
kagi wo nigitteru
To get to you soon.
anata shidai na no dakara
Tsubomi's dream blossoms in the night
Lingerie Pub
Papillon
Here we go...
Sensei?
Well this is nice.
Alcohol tastes a lot better when it's from a pretty girl.
By the way, today...
Where is that girl?
That girl?
Yeah, what was her name again?
Um... the one that's always cheerful...
The girl that goes "Kyaa!".
You mean Tsubomi-chan?
Let's see...
Tsubomi-chan is...
Sensei, welcome!
Are you looking for Tsubomi-chan?
Damn right! Call Tsubomi-chan over here, Master!
Right away!
Tsubomi-chan!
Sensei is looking for you!
Coming!
Sensei!
Welcome!
This sensation...
This is heavenly!
Tsubomi here!
This is like a paradise!
What's this?
What?
Tsu-Tsubomi-chan!
What's with the hair?
Where'd this bothersome hair come from?
Bothersome hair?
A wig...
No way...
It's a wig! A wig!
Tsubomi-chan!
– Put it back!
– But it's a wig! A wig!
Tsubomi-chan!
What do you think you were doing? Sensei was mad!
That's not what I intended to do.
His wig just popped off.
At any rate, your attitude is bad!
On top of that, you were late again today!
That kind of girl...
will be punished!
In the name of the moon!
Master...
Forgive her for the incident...
Tsubomi-chan...
didn't do it on purpose.
As expected, Anne-chan!
My soulmate!
Anyway!
You're paying for this out of your salary!
Are you sure you want to do that?
I'll tell your wife...
about our adultery with Anne-chan.
Oh my...
That's fine with me...
You can tell her.
It's all about the body, isn't it, Master?
Our hearts don't connect.
A man and a woman's love game, right?
Master?
Anne-chan...
That's not true...
Do you think I can feel your licking?
You worms!
Step back!
Is there any warrior who can take me to my climax?!
How annoying!
Then, I, Regina Apis...
shall have all the power of male pleasure.
Well?
Who shall take this ecstasy-filled duty?
To go and create mayhem!
For this mission...
Leave it to Sister Beene.
Oh, go ahead, let's see Beene-chan do it.
I doubt this small fry can do the job.
What did you say?
For an indecisive hag who can't do anything, you'd better shut up!
That's mean!
Petite-La-chan is still a young girl's green flower.
Then this job is not for a mackerel like you.
What's that, you lesbo pig?!
Silence!
Bitch, don't mess with me!
Perverted hag!
Stop this meaningless fight!
Sister Beene.
This time, I'll trust the mission to you.
Yes, Ma'am!
I will collect fresh and superior rogue energy.
All desire and mayhem belong to our Dynasty.
I'm late! I'm late!
That cruel female teacher...
wasted my youth and beauty with her detention!
That's unforgiveable!
Hey, watch where you're going!
What a cool guy!
I can see them.
Oh nooo!
Can you walk?
I can't...
Where should we...
take a rest?
Welcome!
Come on, over here! Let's go!
This strong smell...
There is no mistake...
She must be close.
Yeeeees!
Oh... yeah!
Ugh... Oh yes!!!
Yes!!! Oh yeah!!!
Oh yeah!!! Oh...
Oh yes!!!
Th-that was amazing!
I...
I scored!
I scoooored!
The seed has been planted inside you.
A beautiful flower will bloom.
Tsubomi...
A dream...
What's wrong with me...
I see...
That was such a fantastic sex with Hikaru...
Was that only on my mind?
Kyaa! No way!
I'm thinking too much!
Anyway, Hikaru?
Could it be...
A sex-and-run?
Dammit!
– I should've known!
– Thank you very much.
Why do I...
have to pay for the motel fee?!
What's with this kitty?
Where are you from?
I just smelled a very familiar odor in there.
A faint but sweet odor.
Whoever has that odor is destined to be a hero.
Aaa! Demon cat!
Demon cat?
How rude!
My name is Rahma.
And I've finally found you!
Crystal of love, flower gem soldier!
What the hell are you talking about?
Crystal of love? Soldier?
For your information!
I scored!
Is this vulgar girl really a Papillon Soldier?
What's that?
– I'm not a dog! I don't greet people by sniffing them!
– I'm not mistaken, aren't I?
Help!
What was that?
That was the owner's voice.
As I expected from a Papillon soldier...
Yes... your male energy.
This Sister Beene-sama is so wicked.
I will suck you until you're dry to the bones.
Help me!
Feast time!
Stop! Don't stop...
Stop!
That's amazing!
I wanna join in too!
You idiot!
What do you mean you wanna join in?
Fine, fine, you idiot cat!
I was joking!
Joking!
You can make jokes at a time like this?
Well, Tsubomi-chan?
Transform to Papillon Rose!
Papillon Rose?
When are you gonna stop your prank?
Never mind that!
"Rose Orgasm Power Erection!"
shout out those words!
Roger! Got it!
Honey...
Honey fla...
That's not it, Tsubomi-chan!
Stop being such a low class!
No! Pervert!
This is not the time for jokes!
Fine, fine!
I got it!
I guess it's my bad luck to fall into your prank.
Well then, after much consideration...
I'll do it!
Rose orgasm power, erection!
Aa... I'm sucked dry.
If not for the job...
Why don't I get to do this to a pretty girl?
Being middle-class management is heart-breaking!
Stop right there!
You think this town is an oasis in a desert?
You, Dynasty's minion!
Who are you?
I can't forgive anyone who disturbs the pure,
righteous, and law-abiding citizens.
Who is this exhibitionist?
Exhibitionist?
That's rude!
You're not that different from me!
Dressed in a scantily-clad lingerie...
The fluttering crimson butterfly in the night!
Papillon Rose!
Papillon Rose, you say?
Tonight, I will give you...
all...
you can...
drink!
Defying our Dynasty?
Is she brainless or something?
You're quite charming from this angle.
Wh-what are you doing?!
Thank you!
But you're a bad one.
Shall I...
train you to be obedient?
Commence the attack!
What's wrong, Rose?
Running away won't get anything done!
Damn you...
What do you expect me to do against that many opponents?!
I'm just a girl passing by!
Your wit!
Use your wit!
Why you...
How dare you make fun of me!
There's no other choice, Papillon Rose...
Use the Pinky Vibrator!
Pinky Vibrator?
Inside your crotch, there's a flower gem!
That's your weapon!
Flower gem?
My crotch is exploding!
That vibrator will get bigger as it feels your rage.
Oh my, I feel stimulated now...
How dare you do that to my cute kittens!
I'll prove that I'm no small fry!
Perhaps a little SM treatment is too much for you?
Nooo!
A cute girl should act like a good girl.
Well then!
Where should I start feasting...
I failed again...
Well well, let's start from your cute butt...
Good shot!
Th-this is...!
What... That can't be!
You are a lady.
You should be ashamed of your bad taste in fashion.
Who are you?!
I'm the symbol of love in the night.
A nameless beauty...
You are no better than a regular prostitute!
It's not good to be a bawdy woman.
If you look at this body...
It's enough to enslave any men.
I am a gentleman and I know what to expect.
Stop it!
How dare a guy like you...
Your gasps and voice...
to my ears...
are like my favorite music.
You surely are an exquisite lady.
Papillon Rose, now!
Your ultimate attack!
Use your Rose Pinkish Viagra!
Got it!
Rose...
Rose pinkish...
Rose pinkish viagra!
I'm comiiiiiing!!!
Well done, Tsubomi-chan!
I mean, Papillon Rose!
Is this Papillon Rose's power?
That's right.
You are the Papillon soldier I've searched for.
Our protector from Dynasty's minions.
Nope!
I don't wanna get mixed up with those crazy people!
Besides, like hell I'm gonna be your servant!
By the way, where's the guy with the mask?
Wait!
At least... at least give me your name.
A nameless beauty...
I assure you we will meet again.
You can call me Dandelion.
Thank you for helping me a while ago.
Dande... lion-sama!
Papillon Rose?
That troublesome!
Anyone who defies the Dynasty...
will be tortured to death!
For this mission, leave it all to Sister Petite-La!
Well, Sister Petite-La?
Shall we show what you can do with your IQ of 300?
Hey hey!
Go easy on me today.
I ran out of energy.
I thought you're unbeatable at having
the most sessions in one night.
Cool it.
There are three more Papillon soldiers.
We must gather them quickly.
It won't be complete without them together.
Your seed is persistent.
For the sake of that person...
Please close your eyes.
please close your eyes
I reached out.
sashinoberareta
To return to the moment you hold my hands.
te wo nigiri kaeshita shunkan ni
Just like a dream.
just like a dream
A familiar body.
minareta senaka ga
Disappears along with the spirit.
kieteshimau youna kigashite
I still believe. Even though it's a dead end.
I still believe tomaru kotonaku
I will search everywhere.
subete wo motometeshimau no ni
Even though you transform.
anata wa kawaru kotonaku
oreta tsubasa dokomademo tsutsumikondekureru
With broken wings, I shall follow you.
Let me in, wanna kiss
let me in, wanna kiss
and make me feel whenever
and make me feel whenever.
I don't want the warmth to vanish.
sono nukumori ga kieteshimawanai you ni
let me in, wanna kiss
Let me in, wanna kiss
and make me feel forever
and make me feel forever.
mou ichido dake dakishimeteite
Please embrace me one more time.
Notes:
Papillon: Butterfly (Fr.)
Rose: Rose (Fr.)... do you expect something else?
Itteyoshi: This is a gamers' term for making a kill (score).
According to the official website:
Dandelion doesn't have a transformation scene, because he just cosplays.