Will... Will...
Will, do you really have to go?
This ship is heading towards Little Monica, the city where I was born.
I was an orphan, and was raised by foster parents who lived in a town far away.
Now that I've graduated college, I've decided to return to Little Monica...
...to bring whatever prosperity I can offer.
Leaving us behind?
I'm sorry, ladies.
I want to make use of the education I received here for Little Monica.
Please understand.
Receiving higher education had an unexpected effect.
A Renaissance man is popular with the babes.
Little Monica is the city of arts.
Everyone is happy and has a gracious heart.
It's a restless city...
My childhood friend Celia lives there.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what a beautiful woman she has become.
Is that the real reason? You're terrible!
What are you saying! Of course not!
I sincerely want to make a name for myself in my hometown.
How long have you been there?
Since a little before the Renaissance man part.
Are you from Little Monica?
Yes, that's right.
I'm Meow.
It will be my first time visiting Little Monica. It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
What? Little Monica doesn't look like that?!
What are you talking about? Little Monica is the city of arts, and...
No way! Why would I get invited to a place like that?
It's true, my body is a work of art, but...
That's true...
What about your childhood friend?
Celia? She lives here, so I can see her at any time...
...but I haven't asked Meow where she is staying.
I can't let this be our last encounter.
Plus, Celia could be a hideous troll by now.
It doesn't hurt to have a little insurance.
Meow, wait!
She went into the outdoor theater?
This brings back memories. I used to come here to see concerts and operas.
Meow was being hard on herself.
Performing here is such an honor! She's so modest.
I wonder what she's...
What are you mumbling?
The show is going to start. If you're not going to come in, leave!
I'm coming, I'm coming.
It's pitch black, but I can tell that nasty men are pushing each other.
What's going on? This placed used to be packed with elegant women...
...wearing fragrant perfumes. This nastiness could only be described as...
Welcome everyone! Sorry to keep you waiting.
And now, on to Miss Meow's show. Please give her a warm welcome!
Lights on! Music start!
Here I go.
It's a strip show!
The Little Monica Story
Part 2
Yeah girl! Meow, take it off! You're the best!
Hey, you're in my way! I can't see!
And that was the popular Miss Meow's dance! It was magnificent!
You were beautiful!
Thanks, Georgio.
Now, we would like to move along to our main attraction...
...but Miss Meow just proposed a very interesting idea.
Miss Meow will pick her partner herself! Who will be the lucky man?
Me! Me!
Calm down everyone! Miss Meow will point out the lucky guy! Go ahead!
The young traveler right there!
M...Me?
Yup! Come on up.
What's wrong? You can do whatever you want to me.
But...
Oh that!
I'll make you forget...
...that... they're... there.
Okay! Here I go!
You're so wet! Your pussy is making so much noise.
That's because you're so good...
It's such an honor to hear you say that.
It feels so good!
I can't believe it!
It feels so good. It's great.
It's so hard and full of life...
It's so nice.
R...Really?
I think I'm gonna forget that I'm working.
Will... Fuck me!
Will, this is so good!
Same here!
I'm going to cum soon.
Yes! Cum with me!
I'm cumming!
It was really good.
No, it was bad.
Huh?
I forgot that I was working. That's not what a professional does.
Don't be so hard on yourself. The audience loved it.
It doesn't take much to make them happy here.
It Looks like it was another hit. Good work.
What are you smiling at? Hurry up and go check the profits!
Got it boss!
Master Kajo!
Idiots.
The night of the full moon is coming up.
If I miss this opportunity, I'll have to wait another thirteen years.
The sun is so bright.
I was already exhausted from my journey, and then that happened...
This city... has changed so much.
It used to be such a beautiful city, filled with happiness.
I'd heard some of the rumors but...
Welcome! May I help you?
I'm Will. I'm pleased to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too. I'm Mei, the youngest.
I'm Tina, the middle sister. It's nice to meet you.
Ajo.
What was that?
That's Ajo. It just showed up one day and stayed here, so now it's our pet.
Our sister told us about you. Here, sit down!
Thanks.
We were too young to remember you, but you do remember us, right?
I do. You two were only babies back then.
By the way... where is Celia?
She is out shopping right now.
Ahem!
Long time no see, Will.
Hi Celia.
It has really been a long time.
I've been looking forward to seeing you.
You must be exhausted from your long journey.
Thanks for being so considerate.
Stop being so reserved, Sis!
You've been restless the last few days because he was coming!
Stop shaking hands and give him a hug!
Oh, stop it Mei!
I'm sorry, they're so...
It's okay. No worries.
You really look tired.
You have bags under your eyes.
Really? It's probably just because I was reading a book on the boat.
Sis is so lucky. Will is so handsome.
Hello, girls. Come here and line up in front of me.
What do you want? We're trying to run a business here. Leave!
This is an order from me, the great Kajo! Get over here and get naked!
Naked?
Wait a minute! You barge into their store and tell them to get naked? What is this?
What is the meaning of this?
Hi, handsome. You're quite powerful.
What makes you say that?
Because you made Miss Meow cum for real.
What? Who is Miss Meow?
Missy, this guy is amazing.
He was chosen by the popular stripper at the theater and had rockin' sex.
It was quite a show, you should have heard Miss Meow moaning.
That's disgusting!
But... That was...
Huh? Does he make you moan for joy, too?
What did you say?
I don't have time for this nonsense. Hurry up and grab those two.
Get him too.
Tina! Mei! Run!
No! I can't leave Sis behind!
That hurts!
What was that for! You guys, stop watching and do something!
W...What is this? I can't breathe. I need fresh air...
Boss! Where are you going? Boss?
Master Kajo! What do you want us to do with them?
I can't today. I physically can't... Leave them.
You heard that? He said he'll forgive you for today!
Ajo...
...Ajo...
...Ajo.
What's going on?
I see... I didn't know your mother was missing.
It happened right after you were adopted by your foster parents.
Then it has been thirteen years.
Mei...
Your mother was so sweet. She was so nice to me even though I was an orphan.
Mei, don't cry. Crying won't bring Mom back.
Let's play some music and have a good time.
Yes, we should celebrate Will's return.
That would be great! Play for us, Mei.
Okay!
It's open. Come in.
Mei.
Good evening, Will.
What are you doing?
As you can see, I'm reading.
You're so amazing. You're always learning because you read books.
It's not that kind of book.
What kind of book is it?
This? This is a psychology book written by a guy named Freud.
I know this book! It's about penises, right?
Huh? Well, I guess, but...
Will, I want to learn about penises too.
When they get excited, they change shape right?
They're so strange.
She really doesn't have a clue what she's doing.
I should teach her the correct way.
Mei, do you want me to take it out?
Okay!
It's so amazing. It's so hard.
It gets harder if I put it in my mouth, right?
It gets harder and harder... Then it erupts, right?
Y...You're right, Mei.
I wonder if she really knows what she's doing? Maybe this is a really bad idea.
I'm so happy you're here, Will.
M...Mei. You can stop. That's enough!
It feels so good! I can't anymore! I'm gonna cum!
Wow! It erupted! That was amazing!
Mei, thanks a lot. That's enough for today.
No it's not!
There's something on my body that changes shape and erupts, too.
Like here...
...and here!
Mei, it will be bad if your sisters see us. Go back to your room.
No! I want you to teach me about my body!
See? Your nipples are hard and knobby now.
Will, I'm getting hot down there. What is happening?
Down there? You mean...
Here?
Wow... It's so hot and wet. It's like a river. It's making so much noise.
Yes... Will... It feels so good. I think I'm going to erupt!
Not yet, Mei! I'm going to put something better in there.
It's amazing! It feels so good!
Your pussy feels so good, Mei. It's so tight.
Yes... Yes... Yes...
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
Okay Mei. Let's cum together.
Good night, Will. I'm so happy.
Thanks Mei. I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Good night.
I'm exhausted. I need to get some sleep.
I wonder what this familiar feeling is?
Before I came here it was a sensation that I savored every night.
Which means...
Tina!
I'm cold, Will.
Oh, sorry!
Wait a second. Why are you in my bed?
I've been so lonely. That's why I...
You're lonely?
When a woman is lonely, she seeks comfort.
Does she want mental or physical comfort? Or both?
I should ask just to make sure.
So, what do you want me to do?
I want... this.
Her boldness is turning me on. Those two are definitely sisters.
My drowsiness is turning into horniness.
Sure, Tina.
Tina, your pussy is taking it in.
Stop, Will. Don't say it like that. I'm so embarrassed.
What are you saying? You're the one who asked me to fuck you with it.
You're so wet, Tina.
It feels so good.
Tina, I'll give you something to suck too.
Okay.
Tina, you're really good. I should make you catch up.
No, Will... Not that...
We've just started, Tina.
Go ahead Tina. Lower yourself slowly.
Will, it's all the way inside me...
It feels really good, Tina.
My body... It's so hot... It's like it's burning.
I can't anymore! I'm going to die!
Tina, I'm going to cum!
I was exhausted, but it was heavenly.
I should have sent Tina to her room, but...
...she fell asleep, and I needed to get some sleep too. If Celia saw this...
What a cute pussycat.
Huh? What is wrong?
So that's what that no-good Kajo is up to.
Thanks for telling me!
The next ship has arrived, but now that I know about Kajo...
Is this Little Monica?
I can't remember.
What is wrong, Sister?
I've lost my memory and...
I'm so sorry.
When the ship arrived here, this place felt really familiar so I got off...
Recently, fragments of my memory have been returning.
There is someone out there that I want to meet. A very important person.
But, there is also someone out there who wants to hurt me.
I wonder if that person is here.
Tina! Mei!
Yes...
How could you do something like that before you are married?!
What were you thinking? I can't believe you two!
I'm sorry.
I'll never do it again.
How well can I trust you...
Um, we better start getting the food ready.
We won't be able to open on time!
Hey! Do you understand what you did?
You two are going to get a lecture when we close tonight!
Will...
...are you going to help with the store too?
Well, um...
Will, I can't believe you.
Just because my sisters asked you doesn't mean you had to do it!
You should have yelled at them.
I'm really sorry.
Why did you come back to this city?
You came here to put your education to use right?
You must have noticed how much the city has changed, and look at you!
You fit right in. You had sex with a stripper and both my sisters!
It doesn't matter as long as it's a woman!
No, that's not true...
Yes it is!
I'm sorry.
Sorry? Don't you have anything else to say?
Like, "I've had a change of heart and I'll do my best!"
Or "I'll try to change the city back to the way it was," or something!
If this is how you're going to be, you don't have a reason to stay with us!
So this is how my life in Little Monica started.
At this point, no one knew the danger that was lurking ahead.
Are you listening Will? Stop looking over there! Look at me!
S...Sorry, Celia.
I love you sekai de hitotsu
I love you! You're the only one in the world!
deatta kiseki saikou no present
Our miracle encounter was the best present!
itoshii kokoro kaze ni nosete
I trust my heart...
omoi mo koe mo kitto todoku kara
...and voice will reach you.
say my heart
Say my heart.
sepia iro no horidei
Holiday in Sepia...
kawaranai berube
Velvet never changes...
hazu atsu no koi wo
Passionate love -
omoi nobun so sogune
- I'll put my heart into it.
zutto anata wo shinjite
I'll trust you all the way.
moto yuuki wo de sou
Let's be more courageous.
kitto ii ne to omoeru egao
You'll smile and think everything is good...
kimi ni ageru yo
...I can give you that.
I love you sekai de hitotsu
I love you! You're the only one in the world!
deatta kiseki saikou no present
Our miracle encounter was the best present!
itoshii kokoro utabi nosete
My heart and thoughts will definitely reach you...
mirai mo yume mo kitto kara utara
...because I put my heart to the wind.
say you love me
Say you love me.
I love you sekai de hitotsu
I love you! You're the only one in the world!
deatta kiseki saikou no present
Our miracle encounter was the best present!
itoshii kokoro kaze ni nosete
I trust my heart...
omoi mo koe mo kitto todoku kara
...and voice will reach you.
say my heart
Say my heart.
sepia iro no horidei
Holiday in Sepia...
kawaranai berube
Velvet never changes...
hazu atsu no koi wo
Passionate love -
omoi nobun so sogune
- I'll put my heart into it.
zutto anata wo shinjite
I'll trust you all the way.