Summer.
I've stopped work, and came back home after one year.
So hot.
Shiro-nii, your hips are so big that it
looks like it's going to burst loose.
Akiyama Mizuki-chan.
She's in fifth grade now,
and everything I've done up till now has been to meet her.
She confessed to me last year,
and we've been in this relationship
ever since I took her virginity.
But, I wonder if she's turned into a slut who will fuck anyone.
I'm so, so, so, so worried.
I need to see her and confirm myself, or else I won't feel at ease!
Mizuki-chan is... Mizuki-chan is!
Mizuki-chan is my girlfriend!
I got carried away.
No, I'm fine.
Auntie's at work, so she's not there.
They allowed me to stay at their home under the condition
that I take care of her whenever she's alone.
Which means, it just the two of us when Auntie's away!
Hello!
You're finally here!
That's right... all this built up semen is just for her, and only her!
Anyway, could you please move away for a sec, Mizuki-chan?
Don't wanna.
It's stifling, and I'm drenched in sweat, you know.
I'm wearing a swimsuit, so it's okay.
It's A-O-K.
That's not what I mean, you know.
Then can I just cling onto your clothes?
Wait, you have to do that later!
My, my, welcome, Shirayama-kun.
Sorry for intruding, I'll be in your care.
Mizuki's been looking forward to her big bro cousin's arrival.
I've ordered sushi, so just play with
her until the delivery gets here.
Thank you very much.
Mom, can I carry Shiro-nii's things to my room?
Well, alright then.
Come, come!
You're already pooped, right?
I made my room cool,
so let's go and rest there!
Hey, you don't need to pull me like that.
I'm glad she hasn't changed.
She's still quite a kid when compared to me anyway.
Just wait a bit, okay?
I bought a few souvenirs for you and Auntie.
You never came to visit during New Year and Golden Week.
I got really worried after you also ditched children's day.
We've been in touch via pics and
mail almost everyday, you know.
I'm actually the one who was worried
that you'd become a bitch already.
I'm the one who's more worried for you!
I'm the one more.
The strong urge to do it with her made me feel embarrassed.
Because... she's already quite a girl.
Mizuki-chan, we're about to have a year's worth of sex,
so you'd best be prepared.
Really?
You might be the one crying after cumming a lot.
I've been thinking about you while masturbating a lot.
Shiro-nii.
Shiro-nii!
Come on now, swimsuits aren't underwear.
You often get wet a lot whenever your clit gets a hard-on.
It makes you able to have sex with big boys, though.
How slutty.
N-No.
I'm not a slut.
Really now?
Alright.
Shiro-nii!
It's a reunion with the puny slutty pussy.
You're calling it that again.
It only takes a finger to make you
release that slutty moan, right?
Th-That's because.
If you're really not slutty, then you'll
have to keep your voice down.
Shiro-nii's fingers feel good.
I feel pleasure as it rubs.
I'm about to cum.
It's about to make me cum!
Oopsie.
Your voice is too loud, so I'll have to stop for a bit.
Mizuki-chan, your cheek feels so soft and tender.
Jeez,
you're such a meanie.
Just a bit more and I would have.
For me to get a blowjob from Mizuki's tiny body,
the pleasure is really seeping into me!
You always say that, but you're also
always treating me like a kid.
This is!
It feels good when I caress the very tip this way, right?
I know everything about you.
You're sucking it deeply!
It's payback for earlier.
I'm going to let you moan lots as well.
Oh, that's good, keep it up.
The sensation of your cute teeth brushing
ever so slightly on my dick feels great.
I think I love licking his dick,
because I can make him completely
lovestruck with just my mouth.
Whoa, the sensation of your body is!
I'd wanted to tease him till the end
and make him go squirt squirt,
but I'm kind of craving it after touching it for a while.
Umm, well... you see.
You love having sex with my school swimsuit on, right?
Yeah... yup, that's right.
I love school swimsuit sex!
Well, actually.
I'm wearing it already.
The swimsuit, I mean.
Eh?
Wait, I told you that swimsuit isn't considered underwear, right?
B-But you see!
Don't you feel like doing it after seeing it?
You do, right?
Well.
Right, right?
I'm your girlfriend, so if you want to do it, I can't really say no,
and I'm going to keep myself from moaning too.
Please, please, please?
Pretty please?
Mizuki-chan, you want it already, right?
H-Huh?
If you know already.
I'm still okay with it.
So please.
That's so damn erotic!
Alright, I'm gonna cum inside!
I'm going to totally fill your puny pussy while
I take a good look at your pleasure filled face.
All while having a serious look on my face and
playing the role of the good boyfriend.
Your voice reeks of libido.
Keep your voice down, okay?
I really, really want to fuck you.
Do you hate having a sexually active boyfriend?
I-I love it.
Wow, you're actually pushing it in with your own hips!
So big.
Somehow, it feels kinda bigger than before.
Her puny pussy feels so tight that it's trying to push me back.
I wonder if keeping this a secret from Mom
until now is making me more aroused.
Until now? Aren't you going to keep it a secret forever?
Oh, you're right.
Does it feel better if I penetrate deeply,
or if I push in and out fast with the tip?
With this position, I think it's better to.
Now now, you're letting your voice out again.
Th-Then, let's do it while kissing.
Mizuki, Mom's just going out to buy some drinks, okay?
Also, the sushi might get delivered soon so
I'm leaving the house for a while to you.
O-Okay.
Oh crap, I came a bit.
You came with Mom's voice more than my pussy.
Is your dick more bitchy than me?
Will it cum for just about anything?
Stretches.
Sorry about that.
But, do you'really want to be cummed
in by a big boy dick that badly?
Such a lewd pussy.
Yup, I want it.
My pussy is lewd.
It's really okay, right, Mizuki-chan?
Yup.
Mom's not here anyway.
I can't get enough of this sweet smooth pussy tip kiss!
Sh-Shiro-nii!
Mizuki-chan, Mizuki-chan, Mizuki-chan, Mizuki-chan!
You're cute, you're very cute!
Shiro-nii, Shiro-nii!
I love you.
I love you very much!
I start losing control of myself once we're left alone.
It feels so good when I don't have to hold back!
You sure lose all your restraint when
we start having sex like this.
We did it first at school, and you even told
me before that you didn't want to.
B-But I just.
I just can't help but become slutty once you start getting lewd.
Shiro-nii, Shiro-nii!
What?
Craving a big boy dick's cum while wearing a school swimsuit,
Mizuki-chan, you're such a slut.
I-It's your fault, Shiro-nii.
I wasn't really into this at first.
It feels hot.
It rubs hard yet smoothly as it goes in and out.
It also feels like my insides are being pulled out.
I'm happy.
You came just for me.
Amazing, his click continues to twitch,
and it just keeps on getting hotter.
I'm going to get cummed in lots by him later.
Here we go, a huge one coming up, Mizuki!
Wh-What?
Cumming once!
That was such a loud moan.
Shiro-nii, that's not fair!
Cumming twice!
Come on, I still need to keep it up.
Cumming thrice!
Oh yes.
Yes...
– No way... I'm going to go crazy if he keeps on fucking me this hard.
– Four times!
– Five times!
– No way... I'm going to go crazy if he keeps on fucking me this hard.
– Six times!
– I'm about to lose it completely!
– Seven times!
Eight!
A ninth one for Mizuki-chan!
Your pussy feels even more tender.
I can't... I can't take it anymore.
I'm starting to become weird.
Your pussy is really trying to suck me in.
You're about to cum already, I see.
So hot, it's so hot.
More, do it more, please!
We're going to cum together!
I'm cumming, Mizuki-chan!
Let's cum together with a loud moan
that will be heard even outside!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Shiro-nii, I'm about to cum!
I'm really cumming!
It's pumping in.
That nice thing is seeping lots through me.
So good!
That felt really good.
It felt refreshing to moan to my heart's content.
I love it.
My big boy dick?
Huh? Wait no!
Jeez, you're such a meanie!
Sushi, sushi, sushi!
Here Shiro-nii, soy sauce.
Thanks.
I'm going to prepare tea, so go ahead first.
Sorry about this.
Don't worry about it.
Actually, I think I'm going to come home late tomorrow.
I'm going to leave food in the fridge, so
take care of the house again, you two.
O-Okay!
That's right.
Our summer had only just begun.