Summer time...
After a year, I decided to quit and come back home.
It's so hot.
Your hat is so big, it feels like it could fly away.
That's Akiyama Mizuki-chan.
She's my senior. This visit was actually just to see her.
She confessed to me.
After I took her virginity,
our relationship improved so much, but...
I hope she hasn't turned into
some slut that does it with everybody.
I'm so, so, so, so worried.
I need to talk to her, otherwise I'll never
be able to stop thinking about this!
Mizuki-chan is... She's...
My girlfriend!
I got it out of my system. I'm okay now.
Her mom is out for work, so I'm allowed to stay
at their house, as long as I look after her.
Which means, we'll be alone until she gets back!
Anybody home?
Shio-nii!
That's right. Mizuki is the reason
my body makes semen.
Do you wanna get off of me now, Mizuki-chan?
No way!
It's really hot and I'm already drenched in sweat.
You don't want any of that on you now, light?
You're here, so I don't care.
Not one bit.
That's not my point.
Then, if you take off your clothes, can we stay like this?
Let's save that for later.
Oh, my! How are you doing, Shioyama-kun?
Great! Thank you for letting me stay here.
Mizuki's been so excited after she
found out that you'd be staying here.
I ordered sushi, so you two can have fun until it's here.
Thank you very much.
Mom, is it okay if we put Shiro-nii's stuff in my room?
Sounds good. I'll leave it to you.
Okay!
Come here!
Shio-nii, you're tired, right?
You can take it easy in my room!
Let's hurry up and relax in my room!
Hey, come on, don't drag on me so hard.
I'm so glad she hasn't changed at all.
She's still just like a kid to me.
Wait a sec, okay?
I bought you and your mom a present.
You didn't even come to visit
during New Year's or Golden Week.
You left for an entire year and I was really worried.
We texted every day though, didn't we?
I was worried about you becoming a slut or not, you know?
I was more worried about you!
I was more...
After realising how much I wanted
to do it, I started feeling embarrassed.
Mizuki-chan is a perfectly healthy woman.
We're going to have a year's worth of sex
to make up for lost time. Prepare yourself!
Really? You might cum so much that you cry, though.
I thought about you every day, and practiced!
Shio-nii...
Shio-nii!
Come on, a swimsuit doesn't
count as underwear, you know?
Your clitoris gets really big when you're wet.
We can have adult sex thanks to that, though.
You're so dirty.
No... I'm not dirty.
You really think so? Let's have a look.
Shio-nii, you're so mean.
It's my tear-jerking reunion with your soft pussy.
Why do you always have to say it like that?
Well, you're moaning even
with just one finger, aren't you?
B-But...
If you really aren't a dirty girl,
then you need to be quiet.
Shio-nii's finger feels so good!
The way it's moving inside me is so nice!
I'm going to cum already!
He's going to make me cum!
Oops! You're getting a bit loud,
so let's take a quick break.
Ah, your cheek is so soft and smooth.
Shio-nii, you're such a meanie.
I was so close.
Having your small mouth sucking
on my dick makes everything worth it!
You say that, but you're really just trying
to treat me like a kid, aren't you?
Th-This is...
It feels good when I'm more aggressive, doesn't it?
I know all about that.
Right down to the base?!
This is payback.
I'm going to make you just as loud as I was.
That's good! Just like that!
The sensation of her cute teeth gently
stimulating my dick... it feels so good!
I think I might like licking his dick.
Even though he's older than me, I can make him
fall for me even more by doing this!
Mizuki-chan, your technique is so...
I want him to cum from this,
but licking and sucking it is making me so horny.
Um... so... you know...
You like having sex with me when
I wear my school swimsuit, right?
Yeah.
I love having sex with you in your school swimsuit.
I've actually been wearing it the entire time!
Huh? Oh yeah, wasn't I saying
that this wasn't underwear?
Yeah, but seeing me in a swimsuit makes
you want to do me even more, doesn't it?!
Yeah, I guess.
Right?! If you want to do it with me, I'll do it
no questions asked, because I'm your girlfriend.
I'll even do my best to keep my voice down.
So, let's do it, okay? Okay? Okay? Okay?
Mizuki-chan... Could it be that
you're really horny right now?
H-Huh?
If you know that...
You can cum in me today, so give it to me?
That's so damn sexy!
All right, I'm gonna cum in you!
Let's role-play you making a lewd face
as I fill your pussy up against your will!
Put your acting skills to the max
so we're not found out, okay?
I can't control my voice that well
when we're having sex, though...
You'll just have to try.
I want to have sex with you so bad.
You don't like having such a horny boyfriend?
I... love it. I love you!
Oh, she's pushing her hips into my dick!
It's so big. It feels bigger than it's ever been.
Her little pussy is so tight,
it feels like it's trying to force me out.
Do you think we only get excited doing this
because we're keeping it a secret from Mom?
Yeah, but haven't we always kept this a secret?
Th-That's true.
Do you like it when I move like this?
It feels good like this.
Hey, your voice is getting louder again.
Kiss me while you fuck me, then.
Mizuki, I'm going out to buy some drinks, okay?
I'll pick the sushi up too,
so watch the house for me.
O-Okay...
Crap, I came a little.
Isn't your dick the real slut here
for cumming after hearing Mom's voice?
Will it cum for just anybody?
Spread!
Sorry, sorry! You really want an
adult's dick to cum inside you, huh?
What a dirty pussy.
That's right... My pussy is dirty.
You're sure about this, right?
Yeah, Mom won't bother us.
Your pussy is so smooth...
I can't get enough of this feeling!
Shio-nii!
Mizuki-chan! Mizuki-chan!
You're so cute! You're so damn cute!
Shio-nii! Shio-nii! I love you!
I love you!
When we're alone, my body won't listen to me. Now that
I don't have to hold back anymore, it feels even betted!
You've gotten more perverted if you
really don't mind doing it in your swimsuit.
When we first did it at school,
you even said that you didn't like it.
Th-That's because... If you're happy,
my pussy is happy too!
Shio-nii! Shio-nii!
You're so dirty, cumming from an adult's
dick while wearing a school swimsuit.
It's all your fault!
I wasn't really even in the mood.
It's just too hot today!
It's moving so smoothly and deeply,
it's like my stomach is being pulled out!
I'm so happy that you came for me.
This is amazing.
His dick is getting bigger and even hotter!
After this, he's going to cum a lot inside of me!
Mizuki-chan, I'm going to cum lots!
What? What?!
Here!
There's still more!
Shio-nii, you're being mean! That's not nice!
Here's two!
Here's three!
It feels... so good!
– Here's four!
– You'll break my pussy if you keep on being so rough!
– And number five!
You'll break my pussy if you keep on being so rough!
– And six!
– You'll break my pussy if you keep on being so rough!
– You ll break my pussy if you keep on being so rough!
– Number seven!
– You'll break my pussy if you keep on being so rough!
Number eight!
That's number nine inside of you!
Your pussy is getting even softer!
No, no! I'm going to go crazy!
It's sucking me in so deep!
Looks like it won't be long until you cum.
It's hot! It's so hot!
More! More! Give me more of it!
Let's cum together!
I'm gonna cum! Moan for me when you do,
loud enough for people outside to hear!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum, Shio-nii!
Your adult dick is going to cum!
It's going inside me!
It's shooting so deep inside me!
It feels so good!
That felt really good.
I felt so good after moaning that loudly.
I love you so much.
You love my adult dick?
Ye... No! You're so mean!
Sushi! Sushi! Sushi!
Here's the soy sauce, Shio-nii.
Oh, thank you.
I'm going to make some tea,
but you two can go ahead and get started.
Oh, thank you very much.
It's no problem at all.
Actually, I'll be at work until late at night tomorrow.
I'll stock the refrigerator,
so please look after the house tomorrow too, okay?
O-Okay!
That's right, our summer vacation is just beginning!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч