Shirasagi Private High School
From the time I met you, I always thought
you were a strange person.
Really?
But whenever I'm with you, my heart gets warm
and I start wishing we can stay like that forever.
Weird, isn't it? Before I knew it, my
head was just all about you...
Even just writing your name makes my heart race...
And it makes me so embarrassed.
Amamase-san...
And then I realized...
That I...
I love you.
Start of daydream that continues through all eternity
The days of first love, once more
Amamase-san, are you sure about this?
Yeah, I came here with this very intention.
This is what lovers do after all, right?
Okay then, here I go.
This is my first time, so I'm not sure if I'll be good or not...
It's fine. It's my first time too.
We're the same.
I just felt your breath on my face.
Eh? I'm sorry.
It's fine. When I think of how nervous
you are, it puts me at ease.
I'm not sure how to put this, but...
Kisses are nice, aren't they?
Yeah, they are.
I don't know anything about this kind of thing.
So I'll leave it to you.
Y-You sure?
Y-Yeah.
It's embarrassing, but if you're the
one doing it, I'll accept anything.
Are you okay?
S-Sorry. It's nothing, continue.
You can do it harder, if you want.
What is this? It's so weird.
What do you mean?
I don't really know.
The places you're touching are getting hot and...
You're getting wet down here, Amamase-san.
Does it feel good?
I-It might feel good.
My mind is blanking out and I feel like I might
make weird sounds any second now.
You're taking them off?
You don't want me to?
I-It's not that I don't want you to, but...
It's so embarrassing!
It's not really beautiful.
T-That's not true at all.
Don't look at it so much.
Don't look...
No! Don't lick it!
Your tongue is coming in!
Your tongue is inside my embarrassing place...
Your hot, dripping juices are starting to flow out.
Wait! This... I...
My body is tingling and getting hot all over.
What should I do?
So this really feels that good, Amamase-san?
I don't really know...
But you doing this to me makes me so wet!
Sorry, I don't think I can hold on any longer.
Is that your dick?
That huge thing is going to go inside me?
Are you scared?
I am but, even so... I want to do it with you.
Don't worry, I can bear the pain.
Amamase-san...
Yes, it's fine. Put it in.
Are you alright?
I'm fine, so go all the way in, okay?
It's in!
Please, just like this is fine...
But don't move for a bit.
Wow, we really are connected now.
Your thing is pulsing inside me.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Hey, you can move now.
But...
It's fine as long as it's slow.
I want to feel good with you, okay?
Please, do it.
Okay, I'll do it.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, it hurts a little, but that's fine.
Just keep moving. Keep moving like that!
It hurts? Sorry to make you go through this.
You're really nice, aren't you?
You're worrying about me so much while
giving it your all to move inside me!
Your insides are so tight, they're squeezing me hard!
It feels so good!
I'm happy! Do it harder, let's both try and feel better.
Amamase-san, does it really not hurt anymore?
Yeah, I think my body's gotten used to you.
I can feel your big, hot thing rubbing
inside me. It feels so, so, so good!
It's getting even tighter!
This is just my first time, but I feel so horny.
My body feels so light...
I feel like I'm going to lose it.
It almost feels as if I'm in a different world.
In this position, I'm going in so
deep. It's going all the way in!
We're connected. We're really, really...
Go deeper, deeper inside me!
Amamase-san, I can't hold back anymore.
That's fine. My boobs, or any part of
my body, use them as you see it.
Amamase-san, your hips are moving.
And your pussy's making really lewd noises.
I can't hold back anymore either.
If it makes you happy, I'll do anything
for you! I'll become a dirty girl!
Sorry, I'm gonna cum!
It's hot, it's so hot!!
It's twitching a lot and getting even bigger!
Amamase-san!
What is this?
Coming...
Something's coming!
No!
Sorry... for cumming so much...
It's fine. I didn't know that my body
would act like that either.
If you hadn't taught me about this,
I might have never known.
I'm so happy when we're connected.
Me too, Amamase-san.
No, don't call me that. We're going out after all.
Call me by my first name.
Eh? Yeah, you're right... Yuuki.
Yep. I love you!
INFIRMARY
Sensei, are we really going to do this?
I only came because I fell down during gym class...
Oh, my. Alone together in the infirmary during class...
I wonder if you had any ulterior motives.
See, it's already this big. I wonder
what you were fantasizing about.
S-Sensei!
Do you have experience doing this with any girl?
No, this is my first time.
Wow. I can tell from the way it's pulsating
that you're getting turned on.
How dirty.
I-It's because you're the one doing it, Sera-sensei.
That's why...
You're not the only one getting turned on, you know?
Wow, they're huge.
Can you tell? My nipples are getting
erect, they're really hard.
It's your fault I'm getting so aroused.
Sensei, your breasts are so soft
and warm. They feel so good.
Well, here you go. Feel even better off my breasts.
You can play with them however you want to.
Okay.
There's some liquid coming out of the tip.
What could this be?
It-It's...
An erotic fluid, pre-cum, right?
Sensei...
It's your fault, you know? It's twitching.
Your pre-cum just keeps coming out.
If you keep doing it like that, I'm gonna...
Could it be that you're going to cum soon? Are you?
Y-Yes.
That's fine. Cum a lot and feel good.
Show me how you cum with that dick, okay?
Sera-sensei!
Okay then. Let's get it out all at once!
From here on, I'm going to make you feel even better.
So good! You're sucking on it!
Sensei!
Wow, I'm amazed you came so much.
Sorry. I made your face get all stick.
It's nothing to worry about.
This is proof that I was able to make
you, the one I love, happy, right?
Sera-sensei...
You don't need to hold back. I'll accept you
whenever you want me to, if you so desire.
To tell the truth, lately, I've been worried about something.
Alright, that ends practice for today.
And now, whoever is on pool duty,
please make sure to clean the pool.
Thank you very much.
Misasa-sensei?
I'll help you out if it's just cleaning.
I feel bad for just observing the club all the time.
Thanks.
What I'm worrying about is him.
I'm really glad he's decided to observe
the swimming club, but...
Recently, I've been bothered by the way he looks at me.
For example, my breasts and butt...
For him to be staring at them...
I don't dislike it, but...
But my body gets so hot.
Getting like that during club activities as an instructor...
I don't think it's a good thing.
It'd probably be better if I wore a jacket
like I do during gym class, but...
If I do that, he might get disappointed.
S-Sensei!
Sorry, I just can't hold back any longer.
W-Wait! In a place like this...
Everyone will see us!
If you mean the members of the swimming
club, they've already left.
Don't worry.
Huh, when did...
Sensei, were you spacing out, thinking about something?
Like about perverted stuff?
N-No, I wasn't. There's no way I would be, right?
I was though.
There's no school or club activities tomorrow,
so maybe today, you'll let me do these things.
Is that alright?
Oh no, your hard thing is rubbing against my ass.
No!
I've been watching you with lustful
eyes ever since practice started.
Looking at your boobs, your ass, your pussy...
No, don't say that! You know I'm easily embarrassed,
so you're saying these things on purpose, aren't you?
I-I'm sorry.
I can't stop after coming this far!
Hey, are you really going to do this?
Now that I've gotten like this, I'm so
embarrassed. I can't just go home.
Please, Sensei. Use your boobs.
I'm doing this j-just for today, okay?
Wow!
No, don't look at them so much.
It's embarrassing.
Is it okay like this? Am I too heavy?
Like this is just fine. The weight is good, in a sense...
I think your breasts are amazing, Sensei.
Geez, even if you compliment them
it doesn't exactly make me happy...
That's good!
It's getting so hot! It's going deeper
and deeper into my chest!
I can't help but get aroused. I'm being
touched by your dirty breasts.
So my boobs are really that dirty?
Wow, your dick is so big and hot!
Your boobs are getting hot too!
I think I'm getting aroused as well. The dirty
smell emanating off your dick is so strong!
My nipples are tingling and getting harder.
If you keep saying these dirty things, I'm gonna cum!
That's fine! Cum! Cum on my dirty tits!
Let out your hot stuff!
Let it all out! Feel good off me!
Sensei!
Wow, you came so much.
You're such a bad boy for drenching my boobs in your cum.
S-Sorry, Sensei...
Making me hot and then getting off all by yourself?
What are you gonna do about this?
I want it too...
It's embarrassing, but I'll show it to you myself.
Sensei...
Come on, look....
Look how it's dripping wet. I can't hold back anymore.
Give it to me, please.
Coming in! You're coming in!
It's in so deep!
Sensei, this is amazing!
No, what! My hips are moving on their own!
It feels like it's squeezing me in, swallowing me whole!
I can feel it, I can feel it squeezing tight!
So good!
Your boobs, your boobs are just so supple and plump!
Play with them all you want. Do whatever
you want with these boobs you love!
You're way more perverted than you usually are.
No, don't say that! I never thought I'd be doing something
like this in the place where we do our club activities.
No, no more!
I'm sorry I'm such a perverted teacher!
I can't stop myself anymore!
It's okay. Please free free to get more perverted, Sensei!
You're thrusting in so hard from the back! No!
Your dick is pushing my insides all around,
without me doing anything! No!
Even if you say that, your pussy just
keeps getting tighter and tighter!
My stomach is filled with it. No, no more!
I'm breaking! I'm going to break!
Wow! Both my womb and my stomach
are being kissed by your dick!
Sensei, I can feel you. I can feel the deepest parts of you!
It's so hot! I'm going to cum!
Sensei, I'm at my limit!
This is wrong! Even though I know this is wrong...
I'm going to get dirtied. My perverted insides
are going to get dirtied by your horny fluids!
I'm cumming!
Your dick is twitching!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!!
Geez, even though you were just doing all of that earlier?
Sensei...
I've had something I wanted to try out for a while now.
Doesn't swimming while being completely
naked seem like it'd feel really good?
W-Wait Sensei!
Wow. As expected of the swimming club's adviser...
She's so pretty.
Hey, why don't you take a dip too?
It's a bit weird, but the feeling of being liberated is amazing!
Yes... I think I'm getting turned on again.
If you can catch me in the pool, then... I'll let you.
Translator: Hikarucon
Translator Check: Jimaku-Danshaku
Rough Timing: Hikarukon
Fine Timing: MrMew
Editor : Punk4Real