Love Colon
Girls Locker Room
It feels so good!
Someone will come.
It'll be all right.
I locked it from the inside.
You're loud.
Someone will hear it.
But...
I'm so turned on.
Kuro-chan, your nipples are really sensitive.
Geez, you meanie!
There...
Don't do it there.
I'm cumming!
It felt... really good.
If you suck on it that hard, I'll cum again.
I told you not to blow it on my hair!
Sorry, but it felt too good...
Geez...
Kurosaki Erika is the ace of the Tennis Club,
and she's the number one beauty in the school.
There's not a soul who doesn't know her here.
See you tomorrow after school.
The other day, I had sex with her after a certain happening.
We've been doing this kind of stuff ever since then.
Our relationship is unclear, but this is my chance.
In the equipment room during P.E. class...
In the classroom after classes are over...
In the middle of our dates on days when there's no school.
But of course, the other people don't know about our relationship.
Ah, crap!
I forgot my jersey.
Why don't you borrow one from Class A?
Hey, Kenta.
Are you still trying to get Kurosaki?
Oh, for real?
I didn't think you were that persistent.
I'm going out with Kenta.
Kuro-chan.
This is how it is.
Huh?
Huh?!
It was painful.
Hm?
I didn't like that they thought of us like that.
And the guys at the club are troubled, too.
So I didn't mind it if people started gossiping that we're going out.
Huh?
For real?
That way, less people will join the club because of me,
only to quit after a short time,
don't you think?
And most importantly,
be honest and say that I'm your girlfriend!
I love you, Kuro-chan.
Geez, that was sudden!
I wasn't much different than those at first.
You're very different!
Well, you did join to be around me at first...
I did...
But I saw that you were taking the club seriously.
And didn't your skills get better too?
I like those who give it their all.
Kuro-chan...
What?
Hey.
Wait.
Right here and now?
Kuro-chan, you're too cute,
so I got excited.
But...
Someone...
might come here.
What's the problem?
We're going out anyways.
Geez, you're such a perv.
You're too wild.
You're doing it a little different than before.
You'll rip me.
Oh, no!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
We had sex before morning practice today again.
Let's clean up before the others arrive,
and start with swings.
Wow!
Did you possibly...?
Oh, Kurosaki, you're early.
Morning practices feel great, right?
You were peeping, weren't you?!
Hey, don't run away!
I'll punish you!
You can't do th-this.
If you go any further,
divine punishment will smite you.
You aren't very convincing the way you're dressed, though.
Sister-san
Please!
Besides, aren't you already really wet here?
In that case, please help me express my penitence with this,
Sister-san.
Your sticky tongue is coiling around me.
It's amazing, Sister-san.
I'm cumming.
W-With this, the sacrament of forgiving is complete.
Not yet.
Please let me use this one too, Sister-san.
You mustn't!
Not down there!
I said you mustn't!
That place...
Sister-san.
My workplace was downsized.
I was working at a large company with a good salary.
But everything was reduced in the recession the world's going through,
and it finally got me too.
I'm unemployed now.
Damn it!
I wanted to come to the church in the neighborhood to calm my heart,
but this tranquility had the opposite effect!
Damn it!
Why?!
Why did I have to...?!
I-I'm sorry.
N-No problem.
Huh? This person...
I can't recall her being here last week.
She's cute!
I wish this Sister would calm me down!
Um, it may be a burden for you,
but if you need help,
please feel free to tell me anything.
Sister-san.
Yes.
I love you.
Please go out with me.
Huh?
Sorry, you were just so cute I couldn't help saying it.
Oh, really?
My heart skipped a beat.
My workplace was downsized last month.
I've been troubling the people around me ever since then.
I'm burdening you right now, too.
Maybe it's because of my personality.
I guess I'm a lost cause, after all.
Please don't blame yourself so much.
There are many reasons to your problem.
Please let me express my penitence.
I want to be rinsed of my guilt.
Feel free to say a prayer.
No, I didn't mean spiritually, but physically.
Um, will it really be okay like this?
Of course!
As long as I can get your help, Sister-san,
everything will go well!
I'd like to express my penitence with this little guy here.
Please.
Sister-san!
I-Ish it okay like thish?
It's perfect!
I wonder what the cause for this is.
It's getting warmer and warmer,
harder and harder.
I can hardly breathe.
I'm cumming.
Oh, no!
I need to drink it all!
Thank you for letting me help you express your penitence.
Not yet.
Huh?
There's no effect.
You're a liar, Sister-san.
Huh?
Why?
I guess you need to help me with your pussy, after all.
Th-That's...
What's the problem?
I thought listening to penitence is one of your most important jobs.
Th-That's not it.
I understand.
I'm just a nuisance, after all.
I've already lost all hope to live anywhere at all.
I'll probably disappear from this world tomorrow.
Don't!
It's not your fault alone that your workplace was downsized.
I'm sure there are other reasons too.
That alone isn't a good enough reason to give up your life!
So please don't say things like that.
She's such a kind little lady.
I feel sorry for her.
Yes, yes.
It's all right.
I surely won't disappear.
W-Well then, please continue expressing your penitence.
It's really okay, right?
Yes, go ahead.
I'm putting it in, then.
Okay.
It's just as I thought.
Are you all right?
I'm... okay.
Please go on.
If you bite on it that hard...
You can't.
Your breasts are soft and squishy,
so I can't resist.
Please don't say such embarrassing things.
I can't hold back; it feels really good.
Your pussy is extremely warm, Sister-san.
I think my penis will melt.
No!
It's embarrassing.
Please stop it already.
Sister-san!
It's getting big again.
Oh, no!
My body ends up moving on its own, synced with his movements.
Why?
He's seeing all my embarrassing parts!
Don't!
You're so deep in there!
You even reached my womb.
Oh, no!
Your cock feels so good!
I'm gonna cum.
Huh?
Wait, you can't!
Not inside!
Wait!
No!
Not inside!
I'll get pregnant!
Cumming inside...
is amazing!
Half a year later
Congratulations on your marriage!
Congratulations!
U-Um...
Thank you everynun.
Please let me be in your care from now on as well, my husband.
By the way, bride, what do you like most about your groom?
Well,
it's his sturdy cock.
Huh?!
Sister-san
Please!