This situation wasn't even close to what I fantasized my first experience to be...
But with the sudden selection on this unusual day...
No one could doubt it happened.
Hurry, me too.
It's okay, put it in.
Ami-chan...
Nao-chan, can I come inside?
Please do.
I want you to come inside me...
It's deep inside...
It feels great...
I want your thing too...
I'm next...
I thought if this were a dream, I would never want to wake up...
As I continued to thrust deep inside them...
Then you know, he called to say he's not coming again...
That's what he said.
This is the prettiest girl in the school, Uehara Ami.
She still doesn't have a boyfriend yet.
Though I hang on to the glances that we sometimes exchange,
I never thought that day would come.
I was satisfied with just watching her and knowing that she didn't belong to anyone.
You'll be able to solve it using this formula.
If you do this, it'll become something like this.
This is how you solve it.
It might be a little difficult, but it'll be all right if you try slowly.
What are you guys looking at?!
Done!
Let's go home.
Hey, hey, what are you guys looking at?
Hey!
What are you guys looking at?!
We're not looking at anything...
What should we do today? A hotel? How about karaoke?
Sorry for making you wait!
The results for the investigation are that...
We're the only girls in the class who are still protecting their virginities!
At this rate, our school life will end without anything fun happening.
Yui, you're too loud!
I really want to try having sex one time.
Do you have someone you like?
Yeah right.
All the good guys are taken.
There are only useless guys left.
Because of your attitude, that's why...
What, Ami?
You turn down every guy who asks you out.
Well...
As usual, Nemoto doesn't have any shame.
How could she pull Ami-chan into this conversation?
Anyway, as far as this goes, if I ask someone, there's no way he'll refuse.
The easiest would be to pick a guy in our class, right?
No matter how useless they are, they still have a penis.
That's why I asked them to stay after school so I could make my choice.
What?
Hey, Nemoto!
You threatened us to stay and we heard your plan just now...
I won't need to explain if you heard it.
If you don't want to have sex, you can go home.
I won't.
Are you serious, Yui?
But why are you telling us this?
Well, it's like this...
Could you please stay with me?
I would feel uncomfortable by myself.
Okay? We're best friends, right?
What are you saying?!
How could we do something like that?!
As usual, another idiotic idea.
How could our perfect model of purity, Uehara Ami-chan, do such a thing?
I even made Akiha Daiki stay for you...
How did you know?
Because we're best friends, it's easy to notice.
He's not going to wait forever for you to confess.
Also, he's got to be interested in sex.
This is a great chance!
But...
Umm...
Would it be all right if I join you?
It seems like Akiha-kun is here too...
She's aiming for Akiha too, I never noticed that.
But it would be a nice assist.
Thanks, Nao!
See, a rival has appeared.
Hurry up and decide, or try imagining the two of them caught up in their first time having sex.
Well, it'll be all right, I'm looking out for you.
I get it...
Guys, the results are here.
You will have sex with the three of us!
But if you want to go home, feel free.
What?
Hot sex is now brought to our school. One could say it's a miracle.
Which lucky boys will be able to take the virginity of three pretty girls?
Show a little more appeal!
Do you think you can do whatever you want?
We've got conditions!
Line up in front of the girl you want to have sex with, and then we'll pick our own partners.
No way! What if we don't get picked?
Then you only have permission to watch. If you have a problem, get out.
If you get it, line up in front of the girl you like.
Your breasts are amazing. Can I touch them?
Sure...
Ami-chan, you're seriously going to do it?
Quit fooling around before it begins!
Hey, I was the one who proposed this...
I know how popular Ami is, but consider the chances of getting picked...
You can have my virginity instead, for sure...
Umm...
Yui, I didn't get a chance to say this earlier...
It's not my first time having sex, is that okay?
No way!
Nao, when did you...
When I was studying at home a while ago...
My older brother begged me to do it...
I couldn't refuse him...
No, Onii-chan!
You can't do this!
Being forced to have sex during her studies...
So moe...
Well, Kurada has those big tits...
They're being blinded by Nao.
Ami, hurry up and decide.
It's time...
I have to show her more appeal...
Just like Nemoto said, I'm a useless guy...
Even though I love her so much!
What should I do if she doesn't pick me?
One of these guys is going to do Ami-chan...
How am I supposed to fap to it?
No, that's not the problem...
I have to accept whoever Ami-chan chooses...
That is... That is my love for her.
Seriously?
I'll forgive you since you'll show me something I can jack off to tonight...
Well, that's decided.
So, Nao, who are you doing it with?
I don't really mind...
I'm fine with more than one...
As long as I can do it with Akiha-kun once...
You can't!
Well, even though you've got a harsh personality...
I'm kinda interested in your virginity, and your breasts aren't really that big...
Umm... But I think you're still the prettiest...
Cut the crap.
But let me give you some service...
You've gotten so hard...
Ami-chan, are you really fine with it?
I can't believe you're doing this...
Getting sucked off like this...
Your penis is so hard, but it's soft here...
You don't have to...
It feels so great...
Crap, Ami-chan, it feels too good...
Like this...
Daiki-kun, you don't need to hold back...
Come inside my mouth...
Ami-chan, I'm about to...
Nemoto-san...
Kurada, you're amazing.
Umm... Suck harder...
Nao-chan, I'm going to come...
Me too...
I came...
Suck it harder!
Amazing...
I'm going to...
Nemoto-san... I'm coming!
The main event starts now.
Next is...
Ami-chan...
Ami-chan, I'm coming!
There's still more!
This is the most I've come in one time...
Did you swallow it?
Yeah, I need to get used to it from now on.
From now on?
Do you really like this kind of sex?
If I wasn't here, who would you choose?
You're so wet.
Damn it!
I shouldn't think of anything weird!
Right now I should... Right now...
Daiki-kun, give it to me now!
God, what do you mean you can't get it hard?
I'm sorry!
It was just one blowjob...
Nao-chan, it feels great!
Kurada, I bet your brother doesn't do this to you!
Let's switch already!
Hey, you guys, are you guys waiting in line?
I mean, you can do me too...
Idiots...
Hey!
Shouldn't we have some foreplay first?
No, you're wet enough.
You'll get used to it quickly.
Stop fooling around!
I'm going to hit you!
You still don't understand the situation you're in now.
A useless guy's dick is about to make you happy!
Oww...
As expected from Nemoto, so tight...
Don't move so much!
Your personality is what I like the most!
It's fun looking at you when you're happy!
What are you talking about?
Sometimes you make cute faces too, it's amazing!
Just like that, you're so cute!
Idiot!
And when I say you're cute, your pussy starts squeezing my cock.
You're the best, Yui! So cute!
Idiot, don't call me by my first na-
Daiki-kun!
Ami-chan! Ami-chan!
It feels so good!
You're so hard...
You're pounding my deepest parts...
I can feel it too!
Does it feel good here?
Yes! Yes!
I... I...
I'm coming!
Sorry, I can't hold back!
Go on, Daiki-kun! You can come inside me!
Come whenever you want!
I'm coming too!
Daiki-kun!
Inside...
I'm coming!
I don't want to let anyone else have you.
Because you were here, I wanted to do it with you...
Shall we do it some more?
Daiki-kun, it feels so great!
I feel so good!
The girl who I always admired was riding up and down on my hips.
I lost track of time devouring her as I fell into an ecstasy, which stole my consciousness away.
God!
I was just about to come, you're really useless!
Nao, what about you?
I still haven't...
Akiha-kun...
I'm waiting since I promised to do it with Akiha-kun.
I'm coming!
Ami-chan, come, come!
No, it's all me...
Let's come together this time!
Fill me up, okay?
Ami-chan...
Umm... Do me too.
Ami, how many times did you come?
Fiv-
I mean two.
Liar.
Akiha-kun is licking my breasts!
You got even harder!
Daiki, hurry up and make her come!
I'm next!
No, I'm next!
I'm already so wet!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
What's that...?
It's amazing...
I can't hold it any longer!
It's a little late, but can you be my girlfriend?
I'd be happy to!
But, you know...
Thanks to me, you guys are together.
So thank me!
I'm not asking for a lot...
Just letting us do it with you is enough.
We've already got Ami's approval.
But don't have sex in places that I don't know about!
Because Daiki-kun is my boyfriend from today on!
All right, I get it... right?
Nao, don't just take out his penis without warning!
I changed my mind!
I wonder if I should be happy about this...