How's it?
The feeling of my butt, that is.
It feels great, right?
You really are a pervert.
To think that you're getting excited from having my ass pressed against your face...
What a masochist.
H-hey!
Don't move, ...no!
No!
Don't smell me so much!
Don't get ahead of yourself, you sadist!
Oh my...
Wasn't that a little too fast?
You couldn't have held back a bit?
Burying your face in my ass, and cumming so soon...
I sure am unfortunate to have a boyfriend like you.
And to think I have a girlfriend who mounted me without any warnings,
I'd say I'm the unfortunate one, no?
What?
You mean to say you want to break up?
I'll kill you.
Too bad for you, but I like seeing your disdainful face.
So no matter how much you cry, I'm not letting you break up with me.
Leaving my disdainful face out of this, that's just being a stalker.
Don't lump me with the common stalkers.
Because regardless of how much you want to get rid of me now,
or in the future, we'll be together.
Don't worry, I don't know if it'll make you unhappy or something,
but I will be happy.
If you're gonna regret something, regret the fact...
...that you made me, a girl from Märchen, your girlfriend.
No matter what I do, it's my loss.
It got big again!
So suddenly, geez, I guess there's no choice.
No, don't make sounds!
I'm gonna do more perverted things to your atrocious penis soiled by semen.
Great, thrust in your tongue more!
Hey! Don't rage around so much.
We're creating a really perverted sound...
My breasts are tingling,
and your dick is throbbing.
Your cucumber is delicious.
It's coming out!
No!
If you don't beg, I won't let you cum.
Hey, what happened?
You can't hold back anymore, right?
It's fine now.
I want to see your exhausted face after putting it all out.
Ah, it's coming out!
A lot of thick, hot semen...
A lot of it!
Amazing! You still came so much,
even though it's your second time.
You live up to your name of the "matchless premature ejaculator," indeed.
That's a horrible name, and besides,
You were being perver-
What did you say?
No well, I was just saying how happy I am to be desired by such a cute girlfriend.
And you think words like that will be enough to satisfy me?
It looks like your body needs more training.
Good boy. Look, just like yours, my pussy has gotten so slutty too.
Want me to continue?
You want to cum inside me?
I do! I want to cum inside you!
It's coming in!
Your hot boiling penis, is inside my gushing pussy!
H-hey!
Geez, I guess this is just how things are.
Doing it so roughly, you really are a monkey.
There's no way but to squeeze your dirty, unsatisfied penis with my pussy!
Amazing! Rapidly reaching so deep inside me, it feels like you're flying inside me!
It feels so good to have my tits fondled while you pound my uterus.
Are you gonna cum, hey?
I won't forgive you if we don't do it together.
Your eager face is shivering.
It's okay, cum!
Put it out, deep inside me!
Put out all of it!
Cumming!
I'm cumming!
Amazing, your semen is sloppily hitting the insides of my uterus, Toudou!
That was amazing.
Make it feel better,
since you're the only one allowed to drive me mad.
Love2Quad: "Perfect super-sadist lady Ell ~Gracefully sitting on my face giving me an erection~"
I won't lose, never!
That's a good pose.
I'm gonna teach you that you're really a perverted, lewd woman.
Shut up! I'm not like-
Heh, he's carefully looking at your shameless posture.
Ah, no!
Don't look, Toudou!
Please!
That's impossible for him.
He can't even move his eyeballs by himself anymore.
No, not there!
This place feels good, eh?
Somewhere like that c-can't possible feel-
I am you, you know.
I know of every spot in your body where you feel it!
T-that's not it!
Someone like you can't p-possibly be me!
Oh, you won't admit it?
Even though your pussy is this  wet?
W-wai-
S-sto-
No!
See, you feel it here too, no?
That's d-different.
You still won't admit it?
Even though you're completely overflowing from here?
W-what are you-
No, stop!
There's no way I'm gonna stop till you actually admit it.
Please, I'm begging you, stop!
Don't look!
That's not what you should be saying, is it?
I'm begging you, please don't look!
No, no!
It... feels good.
You need to become more honest,
since I'm you.
You're overflowing so much...
How lewd, even mine is...
It feels good, being kissed in my lewd pussy.
Me too!
Ell, pull yourself together!
Don't fuck with me, doing it like this is-
What's that supposed to mean?
Why?!
How can she attack-
Ell, are you okay?
To think that I almsot lost to someone of that extent...
...it's mortifying.
It's mortifying!
You're the holder, my partner, right?
Yeah, I'm your partner!
That means our connections needs to be strengthened a lot more, right?
That means that from now on, you can't leave my side,
and that you can't get excited from any other girl but me.
Did I make myself clear?
Yeah, eh ...?
By the way, your voice did indeed save me, but
you called out after you were done watching us, huh?
Right?
Shouldn't you have called out a lot sooner?
Well, Ell, that's-
I guess that means I need to know a lot of things about you too.
Toudou, pull yourself together!
Hey you! What do you think you're watching?!
Chitose, why are you here...?
W-well, I was supposed to train with you...
Or rather, get out already!
Well, I guess so.
I'm sorry!
Oh my, you already want to cancel our partnership?
Or does that mean you're telling me to overrule the master of the house and do as I please?
It's a misunderstanding, I'm telling you...
H-hey, don't come this way!
I can't hold back anymore!
No, what's this?
What this? You meant to say that you wanted to show me shower play with an infant?
Wait, that's not it.
W-wait, this is ...no good.
T-there...
You intend to show off to me with that?
Or does that mean you want to try the same with me?
Uhhhh, well....
The force is amazing this time...
Noooo, this can't be-
Doing these sort of things...
No, no.... no.
I can't hold back anymore!
To think she's come this far, right...
Sigh, you really are useless, huh?
Ell!
So?
I'm sorry, really.
I get that already.
I'll kill you if you look up.
Taking a guy who possesses an ever unsatisfied, honorless, beastly penis and making it rock hard,
as my boyfriend, was my mistake.
Can I look up now?
That's fine.
W-wait!
If you remove that, ...you understand, right?
That's a good obstruction,
you're shuddering.
I can imagine, but...
You can't move till I say you can.
H-hey, wait, Ell!
Oh my, to think it's getting big in a posture like this..
You really are a perverted boyfriend.
I wonder if doing it like this is okay.
It feels nice to sit like this.
Your penis's become pretty hard.
How perverted, to think your penis is twitching so much from my feet...
Ell!
No!
The breath from you calling my name is hitting my pussy!
I'm doing a really lewd pose at the moment.
You can't see, though.
E-Ell!
The tip of your nose is touching me.
You'll probably get excited from the smell, you perverted boyfriend.
Amazing! It seems like it got bigger again.
It got bigger from me sitting on you and stepping on it, you pervert!
How slippery!
Feel even better.
Hey! I'll do it a lot for you, so cum!
You perverted premature ejaculator!
No, doing it like this... how shameless!
I'm telling you, no!
They'll see us.
Your are... entering me!
My pussy's being... spread a lot!
Even though someone might see us, and despite being just Toudou, you're so forcible!
It'll be fine, they can't see here down below.
Great, be more rough!
It's okay to devour me, I want you to desire me!
I am!
There's no way I can refuse you, you should have more confidence.
Desire me whenever!
It feels great, reach even deeper inside me, to my womb!
You're even fondling my tits at a place like this and pounding my inside.
This is so perverted!
Great! Reach even deeper inside my pussy!
Mold it to your shape!
I'm already cumming, cumming!
You're cumming lots inside me...
It's still coming out.
That's because it's you, Ell.
I'm not gonna forgive you with just this much, nope.
That sure is a nice posture.
In such a shameful posture, having your asshole teased by your girlfriend.
You pervert!
Amazing, it's tightening on my finger.
It's so tight!
Oh my, you alreayd came?
It can't be helped, I guess.
I'll let you cum more.
Amazing, it got hard again!
What a shameful penis!
You want to plunge your shameful penis in my pussy, don't you?
If you can't hold back with this semen coated dick of yours, I'll let you put it in.
How unsightly
Amazing, you're gonna cum again?
If you cum so much outside, you won't be able to cum a lot inside me, you know.
Looks like you  can still go on.
I'm gonna feel it from the dick of my perverted boyfriend!
It's coming... deep inside me, your hot thing.
It's too perverted.
I'm so ashamed, but I can't stop!
Your dick is rubbing my pussy!
More, give me your dick more!
Pound me harder!
Indulge yourself in me!
No, perverted sounds are...
My pussy is overflowing so much!
To my inner walls, it's rapidly hitting my womb.
Your dick is driving me mad!
Ah, I'm gonna cum already!
Please let me cum!
Cumming!
I'm...
You let out so much, and it's still coming out.
You really are a pervert.
Queens have been anhilated, core memory destroyed!
Several Months later
W-wait, I've been saying, we can't.
Hey, wait!
Geez, we can't do things that'll give the baby pain.
Doing it that roughly... no!
The baby will be frightened!
The whole reason I managed to win... was because of her.
Your dick is gonna end up reaching our baby!
Letting out your breast milk, you're so lewd, Ell!
You're the one who turned me into someone so perverted!
Geez, I love you.