So, how do you like my fart?
Nice aroma, right?
You're a real pervert,
getting turned on by something like this.
So M~
T-That spot, don't move so much...
Nya!~
Don't just smell me.
I-I want to use my teeth.
I'm pretty sure I've had bigger.
Oh my, didn't you just cum a bit too early.
Couldn't you just hold it in a little longer?
That was so fast it wasn't even exciting.
I'm sorry I can't be a tentacle.
What is that supposed to mean?
I am too ugly for you? I'll kill you.
Too bad though, I've raped tentacles back before.
So you should be glad I'm doing this.
Wow, you've raped a stalker before?
Not just any stalkers, Starcraft ones.
Well whatever, I'll just continue for now.
Don't worry,
I won't rape your mind,
because there's no fun in that.
So for the time being, you can relax
and enjoy my rape.
No matter how you look at it, I'm just unfortunate.
Hey, it's hard again.
Guess there's no helping it.
No, d-don't get smaller.
I've had tentacles better than this.
I think I need some mouthwash now.
Yes!~
Blow it there more~
Here, how do my teeth feel?
Your penis is getting so small.
It's not fitting in my cleavage.
Your penis is shrinking,
please stop that.
It's cumming.
Wait, beg or I'll bite it off.
Hey, what's wrong?
You can't hold it in anymore, right?
Hmm, that's nice.
Your cum, I can see it coming.
Just wait, I'll chew it all out.
It came out,
So much of it.
Wow, you came so much.
I'm just lying, you're no match for tentacles.
Must you compare me?
It's not lik-
What was that?
Uh, I was just saying how happy I was that my penis is still on my body.
You should know better than to talk back at me.
You want a bigger penis, right?
I know that
you wished it was a tentacle, right?
Do you really want to...
... put it in?
I really want to be a tentacle!
It's going in!
Your small penis feels like hard poop!~
H-Hey~
You can't help it eh...
Trying to be rough,
you're worse than that monkey I had yesterday.
Your penis is shrinking in my pussy now.
Wow, I never knew it could shrink that much.
Tentacles feel better than your hands!~
I'm about to cum,
if you don't cum with me, I won't forgive you.
Your face is trembling.
It's okay, cum inside me.
It's not like it'd make me feel any better.
Spray it all in!~
Cumming~
It's coming out~
Wow, I can't feel your warm cum inside me.
Wow.
I want to feel even more better,
guess it's time to find me some tentacles.
I won't lose, ever!
How stinky,
you're about to poop.
You like me doing this don't you?
Shush, I'm not go-
Did you know your he's watching?
Nya~
Don't look.
Todou-kun, please!
It's no use,
he can't even move anymore.
Nya~ Don't touch that spot.
It feels good here, right?
It doesn't feel good at all!
I am your father, y'know?
I know everything about you.
You're wrong, you're not him at all!
My, do you want me to rape you.
I am doing it already, though.
Sto-... Nya~
See, you can feel it too, right?
That is... No!
Still resisting, or I'll inseminate you.
W-What are you-
No, s-stop it!
You know it's too late to stop now.
Please, stop. Stop looking.
That's wrong.
P-Please stop looking at me.
Nya~ I-It's cold.
Please shut up, your voice is annoying.
Why are you being mean?
Is there someone living in
your asshole?
I wonder if I should kiss someone after this...
Eru, get a hold of yourself!
Stop, you can't do this to...
W-What was that.
How can she....
Eru, are you okay.
I can't believe I got overpowered by that...
I'm so pissed. So pissed.
You're my Holder, right?
You're my partner?
Yea.
I am Eru's partner.
That bitch disappeared,
I guess I'll have to get my revenge now.
So you make me some poop,
and eat it so I can be amused for the time being.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Anyway, I wish I had my carp,
if I had it then I would have
raped you and her.
You love being raped by carp, right?
Uh, Eru that is...
That cute expression of yours,
I hope you're prepared for what's next.
Todou-kun, get a hold of yourself~
H-Hey!
What are you doing!?
Ch-Chitose-san, w-why are you here?
W-Well, I'm training so-
Wait, stop looking and get out right now!
Y-Yea, I should do that.
S-Sorry!
I am your partner to do what?
Kidnap little kids to play in your bathroom?
It's a misunderstanding.
H-Hey!
Don't come any closer.
I can't hold it in-
Eh?
Nya, what is this?
Well, you want shower pay for ransom?
No, I don't.
It's spraying even more now!
T-That-
That's nice to know,
but I'm getting 90% of the shower pay ransom.
It's-
I-It's s-spraying me~
Nya~
This is...
Nya!~ I can't-
hold it anymore.
So it's like this.
You're such an easy target.
So?
I'm really sorry!
I know that.
If you look, I'll kill you.
Since it's come to this,
guess it's time to sit on you
so that you are even more of a pile of shit.
C-Can you not...?
No.
W-Wait!
You know what's going to happen, right?
That quite suits you.
You're cowering.
Probably.
You better not move from now on.
Oh, you're hard in a place like this.
You really are a pervert.
I'm just gonna sit myself here.
And gonna use your penis for support, okay?
Your penis is too small.
I can hardly stabilize myself, how lame.
No, I think I can feel your nose.
Your nose feels better than your penis,
bet you didn't know that.
Eru~
I can't feel your nose anymore.
You really are a helpless pervert.
Wow.
It's slippery now.
Stop that, pervert.
It's splitting.
I'll shape it to a tentacle.
See? I do so much for you.
Cum already.
Such a helpless kid.
No, stop trying to rape me.
I said no!
It's not going to work
You're not a tentacle.
I'm not feeling anything at all.
I hope they find us,
you're not as satisfying as I'd anticipated.
It'll be alright. Use your imagination.
Yes~ that's the spot! Put it in me more!
Keep your voice down.
I can't visualize tentacles if your penis is this small.
kimochii~
Put it in deeper!
Even groping my boobs. It's still not working.
Mmm, go faster!
Into my pussy.
Cum inside me.
I'm cumming, now!
There's so much cum coming in.
It's still not stopping.
It's because you're Eru.
Don't say that.
I'm not forgiving you for that pathetic rape.
What a nice view.
Do you want my fist in there, pervert-san?
Wow, you're getting really turned on,
I bet you're imagining a tentacle.
Oh, you cummed already?
Guess I'll have to go in deeper.
Wow, it's all hot and stiff again.
What a perverted penis.
You're imagining tentacles, right?
How there is unlimited cum in tentacles,
you just want it all.
That was quick.
Wow, you're hard again.
Stop wasting cum, there are
starving children in Africa, y'know?
We have to go even further.
This small penis is entering me.
It's coming in,
this hot...
I can barely feel it,
it's embarrassing but I can't stop!
I wish this was a tentacle instead.
Todou-kun's penis is too small!
Please make it longer!
It's going in, go faster!
Nya~ it's throbbing in my pussy now.
I can't feel it hitting my womb.
Your penis is so lame.
I-I'm about to cum,
please cum inside me.
C-Cumming!
I...
So much,
and it's still coming in.
You're really perverted.
I am gay, cheer if you are too!
A Few Tentacles Later
Stop already, didn't you hear me?
Hey!
You're going to inseminate the baby, so stop!
Stop being so rough!
The baby is going to drown!
Your penis is going to crush the baby.
Eru, your lewd boobs are cumming.
The baby is perverted, not me, y'know?
Tentacles were my first.