Nooo!
N-No! Please don’t!
H-Hey! Stop it!
Hm, Masato.
How miserable for you.
What?
You lost.
I… lost?
Sure as hell you did.
Just accept your defeat and enjoy what’s about to happen, you useless scum.
S-Stop it!
C-Cut it out!
Shut up and watch!
I’ll let you enjoy this slowly.
N-No…
It hurts…!
Yes, just like that!
Stop it!
Now let me show you something even better!
What do mean?
Next… I’m gonna enjoy this part of her.
No, please don’t do it!
After this, you will belong to me!
No… No…!
Stop it! Please stop!
Now, here I go!
Masato…
I’m sorry…
Masato, you…
Dad, sorry!
Hey bro!
Kurumi…
I want to cry too.
Why… am I here?
Kurumi… what happened to me?
I was so worried…
After you got hospitalized,
a week passed without you waking up.
I got hospitalized?
For a whole week?
Yeah.
When we got home from uncle’s place,
we found you heavily wounded on the floor.
And…
And?
Was there something else?
Masato
You really don’t remember anything?
Me?
Remember what?
Brother, umm…
Sayaka-san…
Himenogi Sayaka was…
Sayaka was found dead.
She died right next to you.
They said she bit her own tongue.
Himenogi Sayaka… died?
presented by OppaiSubs
visit us @ hentaicloud.com/oppaisubs
TL: pinkunicorn123 I Edit, Type: Bl4Cc4t I Time: Mr.Mew
TLC: Applepiee I QC: Puck I Encode: Galan_rus
Sayaka
I’ll visit you again soon, Sayaka.
Masato, did you pray to her properly?
Sayaka was your girlfriend after all.
My girlfriend…
Hey Masato,
you really don’t remember anything?
N-No…
When I heard the news from Kurumi,
I really couldn’t believe it…
You and Sayaka…
You guys were so close.
Was… that so?
Yeah…
You two were always together.
Sayaka made lunch for you everyday.
What is it?
N-Nothing!
Oh, okay then.
B-But… it should be fine, right? You’ll eventually remember her!
I sure hope so.
You don’t seem like yourself anymore.
You used to think about Sayaka nonstop!
She always came first!
A-Ayana…
But… why are you not even trying to remember?
Don’t you feel bad for Sayaka?
H-Hey, Ayana!
If you don’t remember her, she’ll be sad!
The Sayaka who loved you so much would disappear!
Masato, there’s something wrong with you.
It’s not just you.
Everyone is acting weird since Sayaka died.
Ukyou also went missing.
Ukyou… is missing?
Is that true, Ayana?
Yes it is!
Both you and Ukyou are weird!
If you’re like this, what am I supposed to do?
H-Hey!
Ayana…
Long time no see, Masato.
You are?
Have you forgotten? It’s Roy.
I was the butler for Sayaka at the Himenogi residence.
I’m sure we’ve met several times.
I see.
My bad.
Don’t mention it.
By the way, is it okay not to follow your friend?
Friend?
Oh, no…
I see.
Then I shall leave now.
I feel like if I’m here,
I’ll disturb you and Sayaka.
What’s with him?
Kaiou Academy
M-Masato!
Umm… Ukyou… didn’t show up again.
Ukyou…
I wonder what’s with him?
I know right?
Acting normal even though Himenogi died.
Also, did you know?
Himenogi commited suicide in Himuro’s room.
Really? Is it possible that…
Yes indeed, it’s possible that
Himuro forcefully tried to attack her.
Masato!
You don’t have to worry about those rumors!
I know, I don’t care.
I’m not offended.
Ouch…
Who is it? Be careful!
Ms. Maki!
M-Maki!
Sorry! Are you okay?
Oh, it was you, Masato.
What happened?
You seem careless today.
Oh, nothing.
It’s the usual me.
Masato!
The next class is about to start!
Sorry, I’m gonna head home for today.
Geez, what’s with you?!
Masato…
Himenogi Sayaka… Who are you?
You lost.
I… lost?
What in the world happend?
Masato…
Who are you?
Are you Himenogi Sayaka?
It’s you, right? Please tell me!
Was I really your boyfriend?
And… what happened that day?
Tell me, please!
Masato…
I’m sorry!
Sayaka…
U-Ukyou?!
Hey Masato.
Long time no see.
“Long time no see”? Really?
Why are you walking around with such dangerous thing?
Where the hell were you?
There’s more important things, Masato.
Have you remembered?
Wha—Ukyou?
What are you talking about?
I guess not yet…
As your best friend, let me help you.
What the hell?
Why are you like this all of a sudden?
“All of a sudden”?
This isn’t sudden at all.
I mean, we continue where we left of last time.
Where we left of?
Exactly.
Now, Masato, show me what you’ve got!
I guess I have no choice.
There you go, Masato.
I won’t hold back now.
Was that your best?
I’m very disappointed in you.
Ukyou… You….
Whatever.
Sayaka is mine now anyways.
Sayaka?
You know Himenogi Sayaka?
Of course I do.
But I don’t see why
I should talk about her with you.
Because, you are going to die now!
Goodbye, Masato.
W-Who are you?
Masato. Get the sword, quick!
Oh, okay.
I see…
God is siding with Masato, huh.
Ukyou, are you running away?
I’m not gonna run away.
I’ll wait for you guys to come get me.
At Serikawa Research Lab.
You’re safe for now, I guess.
B-But who are you?
My name is Milfy, I’m an angel.
Angel?
Yes!
Umm… I kinda get that you’re an angel…
But what brought you to me?
I’m here because…
I need to give you some power.
Power?
What power?
The power to fight demons of course!
Demons?
Yes! The power you need to fight your friend Ukyou.
Ukyou?
Is he?
Yes, he’s possessed by a demon.
A powerful one, too.
But why would a demon take over Ukyou’s body?
Demons tend to look
for bodies filled with jealousy and hatred.
I’m assuming that Ukyou…
It can’t be!
But it’s true!
The demons are planning to invade humanity…
You’re the only one
who is able to stop this, Masato!
Masato…
So… what should I do?
Huh?
In order to fight the demon…
How are you planning on giving me that power?
L-Let me explain…
Wha—Hey! What are you doing?
Umm, this is the ritual to give you the power…
Why do you have to be naked?
To gain the power of God,
you need to be “one” with me.
In short, we need to have sex.
Se—x…?
What?
Sex?!
Yep, sex.
I’m feeling it…
No, not there…
I…
Oh wow… You’re already this wet.
No…
Don’t say things like this…
I’ll make you feel even better.
No, don’t…!
No…
I… won’t be able to control myself anymore…
Please… hurry…
inside me…
Okay.
Masato!
You’re filling me up inside!
This is great…
I… I can’t anymore…!
Me too…!
Please, Masato…!
Give it to me, please!
Now, you’re also a servant of God.
Okay.
Just you wait for me… Ukyou!
Serikawa Research Center
Milfy, how is it?
I can feel the demon’s power coming from this direction.
W-Who is it?
Is this…?
Ukyou’s father?
What on earth happened?
This is so cruel…
Milfy!
After this, you will belong to me!
Masato…
Sayaka?
My heart will always be yours.
Hey, Sayaka!
Stop! Please stop!
Sorry…
Sayaka…!
Ukyou…
How dare you did this to Sayaka?!
It looks like you finally remember it.
Yes… I remember what happened that day…
and what you did to Sayaka!
Everything!
So that means there’s no explanation needed?
Now, let’s have a touching reunion.
S-Sayaka!
Yes… this is my Sayaka.
Masato…
M-Milfy!
Are you alright?
Y-Yes.
More importantly,
I don’t feel a heart beating in Sayaka’s body.
No… heart?
Exactly, that’s because I used
a cloning technique to revive her.
Her heart’s not ready yet.
Clone?
Yeah, that’s only possible because of
my father’s, Serikawa Shuusaku’s research.
You’ve met my dad, right?
What? Ukyou!
He did a great job, but now he’s useless for me.
I can’t believe you would do that to your father…
Your morals really dropped that much?
Dropped?
You’re wrong, Masato.
I just realized that having power is crucial on this planet.
And I have received the demon’s power.
That’s why I was able to make Sayaka mine.
All that’s left for me to do is to kill you Masato,
because you are the wall between us.
How dare you…!
Masato, seems like you’ve got God’s power now.
Why do you care?
Let’s try and see which one is stronger!
Demon or God?
Masato…
Shit…
I won’t give up that easily!
Now it’s my turn.
You’re good, Masato!
So are you!
Masato…!
Die!
Masato…
Why did Sayaka…
S-She doesn’t have a heart…
How can she cry…?
Ukyou… do you still not understand?
Even if you overpower her, you can’t change her heart.
Maybe that’s true…
Ukyou!
Masato…
I’m sorry…
It’s fine.
Don’t speak anymore…
It’ll affect your wounds.
Masato…
Protect Sayaka.
Ukyou…!
Is this the end of the project?
Y-You…
Roy!
No, Masato!
Masato, this is the king of demons, Astalt!
King of demons?
Were you controlling Ukyou?!
What if?
I’ll kill you if you did!
But you don’t have any time left.
W-What did you do?
Since the project failed,
I am going to destroy everything.
What did you—
Well, I just turned on the emergency self-destruction timer of the lab.
What?
If you are willing to use that limited time,
I could deal with you.
You, don’t try to stop me you filthy angel!
Masato! Take Sayaka and get out of here!
But, you will…
This is my destiny.
Even if I need to vanish with the demon…
I have no regrets.
But…
Don’t do it, Milfy!
Masato!
Do what you’re supposed to do!
Bring back Sayaka’s heart!
But if you vanish…
That’s not a big deal,
I’ll just return to heaven.
Masato, please tell Sayaka your feelings.
Hurry up!
Milfy!
Sayaka!
Masato…
Goodbye…
S-Stop it! Let me go!
Serikawa Research Center
Sayaka…
Please… accept my feelings.
You’re beautiful, Sayaka.
Sayaka…
Show me everything…
Please.
Sayaka… Let me come into you.
Sayaka…
Doesn’t it hurt?
Sayaka, I love you! Sayaka…
I can’t…!
Here I go, Sayaka!
Masato…
Masato!
I accept your feelings.
S-Sayaka!
Then, you’re…
Yes.
Sayaka…
Mataso…
Thank you.
And… I love you!
Edo-Mae Sushi
Hey woman!
Stop fooling around outside and help out in here!
God… my dad really overworks me.
Hurry up you brat!
Okay! I’m coming!
Thank you!
Summer greeting cards, huh?
Oh, they’re doing great!