So, how does my ass feel?
Nice, right?
You're a real pervert,
getting turned on by something like this.
So M~
T-That spot, don't move so much...
Nya!~
Don't just smell me.
I-I can't stop myself.
Remember who's the one S here.
Oh my, didn't you just cum a bit too early.
Couldn't you just hold it in a little longer?
It's pretty unfortunate that my boyfriend suffers from premature ejaculation.
Having a girlfriend that only rides my face is pretty unfortunate.
What is that supposed to mean?
I'm not your type? I'll kill you.
Too bad though, I really like watching you suffer.
So you're going to be with me forever.
Aside from being S, you're just a typical stalker.
I'm not like those typical stalkers.
Well whatever, we'll be together from now on.
Don't worry,
I don't mind you being unhappy,
because all that matters is my happiness.
So for the time being, you can just regret
having picked me to be your girlfriend.
No matter how you look at it, I'm just unfortunate.
Hey, it's hard again.
Guess there's no helping it.
No, d-don't lick me.
I can taste your pre-cum.
I'll make you feel even better.
Yes!~
Lick it there more~
Here, does that feel better?
All your horny juices are coming out.
My boobs are all slippery.
Your penis is throbbing,
and the pre-cum is delicious.
It's cumming.
No, beg or I'll stop.
Hey, what's wrong?
You can't hold it in anymore, right?
Hmm, that's nice.
Your cum, I can see it coming.
Just wait, I'll get it all out.
It came out,
So much of it.
Wow, you came so much.
As expected of the Premature Ejaculator.
I hate that name,
anyway, you wer-
What was that?
Uh, I was just saying how happy I was with such a kawaii girlfriend.
You should know better than to sweet talk me.
You want to go even further with me, right?
I know that
you really want the insides of my pussy, right?
Do you really want to...
... put it in?
I really want to be in Eru's pussy!
It's going in!
Your hot penis is throbbing in my pussy!~
H-Hey~
You can't help it eh...
Doing it this rough...
You're a real animal...
Your penis is reaching the deepest parts of my pussy.
Wow, my womb isn't rejecting your penis at all.
It feels so good to have my boobs groped!~
I'm about to cum,
If you don't cum with me, I won't forgive you.
Your face is trembling.
It's okay, cum inside me.
Cum, fill my womb up with your cum.
Spray it all in!~
Cumming~
It's coming out~
Wow, I can feel your warm cum inside me.
Wow.
I want to feel even more better,
cause you're the only one allowed do this.
I won't lose, ever!
What a nice view,
you're really slutty.
You like me doing this don't you?
Shush, I'm not a-
Your boyfriend's been watching us this whole time.
Nya~
Don't look.
Todou-kun, please!
It's no use,
he can't even move anymore.
Nya~ Don't touch that spot.
It feels good here, right?
It doesn't feel good at all!
I am you, y'know?
I know everything about you.
You're wrong, you're not me at all!
My, so you're not admitting it.
I guess I'll play with your pussy then.
Sto-... Nya~
See, you can feel it too, right?
That is... No!
Still resisting, even though you're all wet down here.
W-What are you-
No, s-stop it!
You know it's too late to stop now.
Please, stop. Stop looking.
That's wrong.
P-Please stop looking at me.
Nya~ I-It feels good.
Please be more honest, you are me after all.
So much is leaking out,
your pussy is slutty too.
I'll lick you too.
Being kissed on my own lewd pussy, oh yes~
Eru, get a hold of yourself!
Stop, you can't do this to...
W-What was that.
How can she....
Eru, are you okay.
I can't believe I got overpowered by that...
I'm so pissed. So pissed.
You're my Holder, right?
You're my partner?
Yea.
I am Eru's partner.
I heard your voice,
which means that our bond isn't strong enough.
From now on you're not allowed to leave my side,
and you're not allowed to look at other girls.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Anyway, I'm glad your voice saved me,
but you only called out after you were satisfied,
weren't you?
You could've called out a lot sooner, right?
Uh, Eru that is...
That cute expression of yours,
I hope you're prepared for what's next.
Todou-kun, get a hold of yourself~
H-Hey!
What are you doing!?
Ch-Chitose-san, w-why are you here?
W-Well, I'm training so-
Wait, stop looking and get out right now!
Y-Yea, I should do that.
S-Sorry!
Oh, you have more partners?
And you're even into little kids as well.
It's a misunderstanding.
H-Hey!
Don't come any closer.
I can't hold it in-
Eh?
Nya, what is this?
What, so you shower play with her as well?
No, I don't.
It's spraying even more now!
T-That-
Are you forgetting that I'm here,
or are you hinting that you want to shower play with me too?
It's-
I-It's s-spraying me~
Nya~
This is...
Nya!~ I can't-
hold it anymore.
So it's like this.
You're such a helpless kid.
So?
I'm really sorry!
I know that.
If you look, I'll kill you.
Since it's come to this,
guess it's time I punish that penis of yours.
So that you know that it belongs to me only.
C-Can I look now...
Yes you can.
W-Wait!
You know what's going to happen, right?
That quite suits you.
You're shivering.
I am.
You better not move from now on.
Oh, you're hard in a place like this.
You really are a pervert.
I'm just gonna position myself here.
You like this feeling, don't you?
Your penis is throbbing already.
You're really dirty, for being so hard from just my foot.
No, I didn't say you can use your hot breath on my pussy.
I'm in a really lewd position right now,
though you can't see it.
Eru~
I can feel your nose.
You really are a helpless pervert.
Wow.
It's grown even bigger now.
Grow bigger, pervert.
It's twitching.
I'll make it feel even better.
See? I do so much for you.
Cum already.
Such a helpless kid.
No, we can't do this at school.
I said no!
They'll see us.
You're coming in!
My pussy is stretching from your big thing.
Even though they might see us,
I love sex with Todou-kun!
It'll be alright. Just don't raise your voice.
Yes~ that's the spot! Put it in me more!
Keep your voice down.
That's right, you've been holding back all this time and now you want to the dominant one.
kimochii~
Put it in deeper!
Even groping my boobs. It's making me feel dirty.
Mmm, go faster!
Into my pussy.
Cum inside me.
I'm cumming, now!
There's so much cum coming in.
It's still not stopping.
It's because you're Eru.
Don't say that.
It still isn't enough for me to forgive you.
What a nice view.
You're really turned on right now, aren't you, pervert-san?
Wow, you're getting really turned on,
even though it's your anal hole.
Oh, you cummed already?
Guess I'll have to go in deeper.
Wow, it's all hot and stiff again.
What a perverted penis.
You want to put your penis in my pussy, right?
The cum in your penis is about to burst out,
I'll let you cum.
That was quick.
Wow, you're hard again.
If you keep this up there won't any left for inside, right?
We have to go even further.
This pervert's penis is entering me.
It's coming in,
this hot...
I can feel it,
it's embarrassing but I can't stop!
Your penis is wrecking my pussy.
I want more of Todou-kun's penis!
Please put it in deeper!
It's going in, go faster!
Nya~ it's throbbing in my pussy now.
I can feel it hitting my womb.
Your penis is so deep~
I-I'm about to cum,
please cum inside me.
C-Cumming!
I...
So much,
and it's still coming in.
You're really perverted.
Queens have been defeated, core memory is destroyed!
A Few Months Later
Stop already, didn't you hear me?
Hey!
You're going to hurt the baby, so stop!
Stop being so rough!
The baby is going to be scared.
Your penis is going to poke the baby.
Eru, your lewd boobs are leaking.
I'm only this perverted because of you, y'know?
I love you.