Sorry.
No, I should be the one apologizing.
I was just so surprised because I've never seen one before,
so I was really embarrassed when a really thick
one just came out in front of me like this!
But since it's your dick, I thought that it was actually
really nice to look at, but I'm not really trying to say that,
but what I'm trying to say is that...
Calm down. Let's take some deep breaths, okay?
Y-Yes.
Um, not like that. Your breath's too ragged.
In the instructions, it says that I
should grip your... dick with my hands.
S-So, I...
What do you need to grip? You need
to explain these technical terms to me.
Your dick...
Nii-san, your dick is so...
Honoka, try slowing down a bit.
S-Sorry. I'm sorry that I can't get it right.
Well, it is your first time, but even though
it did kind of hurt, it still felt good.
Even though it hurts, it feels good?
Y-Yeah, just do it however you want.
Okay! I'll do my best to get better and make you feel good!
Honoka, your face is covered in it.
Nii-san, I'm so happy! Please pat me on the head more!
I would do anything if it meant I
could help you. Even sex training...
For me, you are...
You're...
I'm going crazy.
Please forgive me! I'm gonna cum! I'm
gonna cum!! I'm gonna cum with my ass!
Sorry, you were just going out of control.
Nii-san, your tongue is in my ass!
If you keep moving your tongue like that
I... I never thought you would lick me there!
This can't be happening! Your
tongue is going inside my ass!
Oh my god, this feels so good, I'm gonna lose it!
My tongue is going into your ass so easily.
That's because I was playing with it just a little while ago.
Nii-san, your fingers rubbing against the walls of my ass!
It feels like you're going to pull it out! It feels so good!
Nii-san, at this rate, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum by myself!
Nii-san!
That's fine, cum.
Nii-san, no! Nii-san, it's not fair! I want to cum with you!
Nii-san, no! I can't hold on anymore!
Nii-san, you made me cum with my ass.
Nii-san, is that your dick on my ass?
May I?
Please give it to me. Please feel good from my ass!
Your dick is spreading my ass so wide!
I can feel it coming deep inside me!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes! Your dick is coming really deep inside me,
it feels like it's lodging itself against my stomach!
Does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels amazing.
I'm ready, nii-san.
Oh my god, your dick is spreading me
and it feels like it's pulling me out!
Your dick is touching all the places that
I've never touched before with every thrust.
Every time your dick moves in
and out, it stirs up my insides!
Honoka, your ass is so smooth, it's easy
to move around in. It feels really good!
I'm happy that my ass is pleasing you!
It feels so much better than when
I do it by myself! It feels amazing!
Priestess Pudding – Honoka ~ Masturbating and
Cumming Lessons in an Uncivilized Land
Nii-san, your dick is so long and
you're coming even deeper inside me.
My ass feels so hot... I can't believe it feels this good!
Nii-san, does it feel good?
I'm not the only one feeling good, right?
Honoka, your ass is amazing.
I've never felt anything this amazing before.
I'm so happy... that I'm your first time...
More... I want you to feel even more pleasure.
I... I... Nii-san...
Nii-san, you can cum whenever you want.
Nii-san, you're being so rough!
Oh, no!
I'm going to cum too!
I'm cumming!!
Nii-san, your cum is pumping out inside of my butt!
So much of your cum is inside me, nii-san.
My stomach is spinning.
Nii-san, wait!
Don't!
No! Stop!
Don't look!
Nii-san, don't look!
I hate you, nii-san.
I'm sorry, but I'm really not bothered by that.
Yeah, but I am!
Being inside you just felt too good.
My butt felt good?
Very good. It was my first time too.
Because you told me you loved me...
You see, I've always loved you, so it just made me so happy.
If my butt made you feel good, then th-that means that
you'd feel even better with my other hole then, right?
H-Huh?
I want you to play with my body, so
I've been holding back all this time.
Yeah, but more importantly... this
place and that outfit you're wearing...
I'm here for training anyway, so I just
thought why not do this while we're here?
If I can make my beloved nii-san happy while also
doing my training, it's two birds with one stone!
This feels like sacrilege.
Nii-san?
Please take my first time.
Nii-san, your dick is... it's touching against my pussy!
Honoka, you...
I-I'm just reciting what was in the message.
I'm gonna take your first time, Honoka.
I want you to make me a woman, nii-san!
Nii-san, your dick is inside me!
The first one inside me is you!
Nii-san, please move.
Please make yourself feel good with my body.
This pain... I'm so happy!
Being able to give myself to you... I...
You're rubbing my boobs while stirring up my pussy!
Nii-san, your dick is so amazing!
Nii-san, your dick is coming so
deep and stirring me up inside!
The pain is making my pussy so hot.
I'm supposed to be doing training for an austere
life, but I just received the best thing in the world.
Your dick is rubbing my insides so
hard, it's starting to feel a lot better.
Nii-san, I love you!
I've always only had eyes for you, nii-san!
Nii-san! Nii-san!
I've always wanted to...
Nii-san, I... This is my first time, but I'm already...
I'm going to cum with your dick, nii-san!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!!
It keeps squirting around inside me! It's a
different kind of pleasure than I feel with my butt!
Your dick is spewing out so much cum!
There's so much...
I'm going to get pregnant with your baby, nii-san!
You've seen so many embarrassing sides of me now, nii-san.
Yeah, but I'm the perverted brother who
covers his little sister in his own cum.
But I love you for who you are, nii-san.
Let's get along even better than we did before.
I can't believe nii-san is doing this in a place like this.
This is training too.
Y-Yes, you're right.
That's what the message said.
Nii-san, you're so big.
Nii-san, you're so bold.
You're even fondling my breasts.
I'm just doing what you want me to do.
What are you saying? I'm just following the message.
I'm not like those girls you see in those books.
I just wanted to try out a role play that I thought you'd like.
Honoka?
It's twitching so much and it's getting really wet!
Now there's nothing in the way of your dick, right?
Please give me your dick in my butt.
If you don't put it in yourself, I will.
If it's for the sake of my dirty little sister...
Your dick is forcing its way into my butt!
I'm such a pervert for having a dick inside me on a train!
B-But this is training, right?
Th-That's right.
You should enjoy this, nii-san.
This is training, right?
Your dick seems like it's feeling really good right now.
The insides of my butt are being churned up
and it's poking all the way inside my stomach!
Seeing my butt get this satisfied from your
energetic dick is making my pussy jealous.
You're almost... about to cum, right?
Y-Yeah.
I can feel so much of you, I can tell
when you're about to cum so easily.
You're moving so hard inside me.
You're hitting me so hard inside.
I can feel you so clearly, nii-san!
So good! Your dick is doing me so
hard, it's making my head spin!
Nii-san, I'm about to...
I'm gonna cum!
Nii-san! Nii-san!
Nii-san, there's so much cum shooting inside me!
Nii-san... I love you so much.
translator: hikarucon
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч