Love Colon
Congrats, Erika-chan!
With this year's event, you've been participating in the national championship for three straight years.
Huh? Amazing!
Thanks.
It's only natural that you're going to win this year again, right?
There's not really any competition anyways...
It'll be an easy win.
Nothing less than what you'd expect from a champion; she talks big.
I guess.
What is it?
Nothing.
Could you stop staring at me?
Kurosaki's as cheeky as ever.
Kurosaki Erika is the ace of the tennis club.
Her powers surpass that of a school student,
and she even won the national championship several times.
Besides, she has a cute face.
She's really popular in school.
Club Joining
Application
I joined the club!
Club Joining
Application
For real?
Good for you!
Well, you don't get a lot of chances to see Kurosaki-san, so I thought "Why not?"
How nice!
I'm like them.
Heave-ho.
That's quite the destructive power!
I'm feeling horny.
Captain, I'm taking a little break.
Yeah, that's alright.
You!
Could you stop staring at me with such lewd eyes?
You're getting in the way of my training!
I want you all to quit right now if you only joined for some ridiculous reason.
Why's she so cocky?
She has a lethal personality.
Right?
What did you say!?
Run for it!
Guys like them — those who joined the club just for Kurosaki —
usually quit in no time because of her verbal abuse.
Nevertheless, I managed to stay for two whole months.
Maybe I'm a born masochist.
Huh? You're early!
M-Morning.
Morning!
Ugh, she's just so cute when she smiles!
Even though I was always first to arrive up until today.
That's a shame.
Just what you'd expect from Queen Hates-to-Lose.
Looks like it's true that she's the first to arrive at morning practice.
Hey, do you wanna have a match with me?
Huh?
Don't be so nervous.
I just want us to get our bodies moving around a little.
Uh, but...
I'm super nervous!
Hmm, let's do this:
You just need to score a point, while I win a set.
If the ball passes me even once, I'll do whatever you say.
Whatever it is, got it?
She's really selfish.
Let's have fun with it.
I'll win anyways.
She's so annoying.
Here I come!
It's boring!
No way!
Now you learned not to make a fool out of others.
You lose.
I wanted to tell you for a while now,
and I couldn't really hold back anyways.
It's perfect.
What is it?!
Now, a promise is a promise.
You'll do what I say, right?
I got it!
H-Hurry up already!
Why are you looking confused?!
You idiot!
Uh no, I was going to ask you to officially date me.
Jeez!
*staaares*
D-Don't look!
It's decided; I'll change my reward.
You can't!
I'll have sex with you!
First, you didn't say that I couldn't change my mind, right?
Hey...
that...
doesn't really matter.
She's sweating a lot.
So she's always sweating this much.
Her sweat, voice, and warmth is making me really horny.
You're already this wet; you're really wet.
No, this is... um... for your r-reward.
So it's not like I'm turned on or anything!
Alright, I'll take your pussy... my reward.
Wh-What're you doing, you perv!
Kuro-chan, you're so cute!
No!
What's... this?
My body feels numb.
Don't!
Should we stop?
No, that's not what I meant.
Midorikawa-kun,
put your thing in.
Ah man, you're too cute!
Here, you got your favorite penis in.
I love it.
I love your penis.
Kuro-chan, I didn't know you were this lewd.
You're okay with me seeing you like this?
It doesn't matter.
I love you.
You have a penis, so I love you, Midorikawa-kun.
It's so good!
It's... coming out!
Cumming!
Cumming!!
Kenta.
Ah, Kurosaki.
Don't forget tomorrow's morning practice.
Got it.
I decided to spend my youth playing tennis.
Welcome, Master!
Then, I'll cast a spell for Master.
From the bottom of my heart!
Piro-riro-rin, become delicious!
You...
Moe-moe-kyun!
Kyun!
I didn't know you had a part-time job there.
Sorry.
Why didn't you tell me?
Is there a reason you had to keep it a secret from me?
W-Well...
I joined it because the maid uniform there is really cute.
Huh?!
I really only wanted to try it on once.
Just for a little while, you see.
Hey, do you even have time to work, considering how you barely manage to get enough credits?
I'm against that kind of recklessness.
What if you'll have to repeat a year?
Well, I am studying hard, too.
Please Maa-kun, just for a month.
Only on weekends.
It's really so much fun!
Well, you did seem to be enjoying it.
Welcome, Master!
Even you went there to see maids, didn't you?
Well, I did it to change my mood.
Exactly!
I love how the customers start to smile.
Wearing cute clothes and talking to the customers
really makes me think
"Ah, how fun!" for some reason.
Um, do you happen to have the shop's maid uniform with you right now?
Hm?
Uh-huh.
Well, I do.
Actually, we're not allowed to bring it out of the shop;
I brought it with me in secret.
Then, try putting it on here.
Now?
Um, does it look odd anywhere, Maa-kun?
Yui-chan, I think you aren't just enjoying it when you're wearing that uniform;
your ecchi switch is flicked on, too.
Don't you like it when you're excited because your breasts are seen?
Don't!
My nipple.
You're so cute, Yui-chan.
Don't tease me!
But then maybe I really do feel ecchi when you touch me.
Man, now I have to worry about whether someone will take you away from me.
That'll never happen!
My feelings will never change.
After all, I really, really like you.
Yui-chan...
Amazing.
You're this wet just from kissing.
Don't look.
What's going on?
Is it because of this uniform?
I feel like a real maid.
I think I want it more than usual.
I'll service you a lot.
More.
Yui-chan, it feels really good.
Damn!
It's coming out!
Yui-chan, are you okay?
Uh-huh.
It felt so good; I couldn't help it.
I'm alright, as long as you feel good, Maa-kun.
I love you, Yui-chan.
Maa-kun.
It's going in...
Why?
You came just a moment ago.
It feels...
amazing!
Your insides are tightening a lot.
It feels good...
It's embarrassing.
Don't say it.
No, my nipples!
It's deep in.
I love you.
Your thing is hitting my insides, Maa-kun.
More.
Do me more and more.
Maa-kun.
You're amazing, Yui-chan.
You're this drenched.
You're sucking me in.
Yui-chan, I'm about to... ejaculate.
Cum.
Ejaculate it all deep inside me... in my pussy.
Yui-chan.
There's so much cum.
After that, Yui-chan did as she promised;
she quit her job after a month,
and she's in the middle of studying.
But her change of mood is still going hard.
Maa-kun
That's because...
Alright, say "ah."
I can have her as my own maid on days off.
It's delish!
Really?
I'm so glad!