Female Changing Room
Oh yes...
Someone might come here.
Don't worry,
I've locked the place.
You're moaning too loudly, someone might hear us.
But...
This sensation is just too intense.
Your nipples really are sensitive, huh?
Jeez, you meanie!
It's really... soaking wet...
I'm going to cum!
That felt really great.
If you suck that strongly, I'll cum again...!
I already told you not to squirt it on my hair!
I'm sorry, but it felt really great, so...
Jeez!
Kurosaki Erika.
The tennis club's ace player, and the number one campus beauty.
There isn't a single student who doesn't know her.
So, I'll see you next time after school, okay?
Before,
a number of events led to me having sex with her.
We continued that sort of relationship afterwards.
True, I'm not really sure what we are to each other,
but this is a big chance for me.
In the gym storeroom during PE,
in the classroom after school,
and during one of our dates.
Though of course, nobody else knows of this.
Oh crap, I forgot my PE suit.
Just borrow one from Class-A.
Hey, Kenta,
are you still into Kurosaki?
What, really?
You're surprisingly stubborn.
Kenta's currently dating me.
Kuro-chan.
That's how it is.
Eh?
Ehhhh~?!
I really can't stand it.
I don't like it when people talk behind my back,
and it's going to cause trouble for the other club members.
That's why I don't care even if the rumor spreads that we're dating.
Really...?
There are people who'll just give up once they know, right?
Besides, the important point is...
You should have told them properly that I'm your girlfriend!
I love you, Kuro-chan.
Jeez, why so suddenly?
Actually, I'm not that much different from them.
You're different.
True, you also seemed like the naughty type, but...
So, I also seemed like that...
But I saw that you were serious about the club.
And you're getting better at it lately.
I love people who work hard and do their best.
Kuro-chan...
Hey, wait... right here, right now?
You were just so cute, so I couldn't help it.
But, this place is...
Someone might come here.
It's okay, since we're dating, right?
Jeez, you're such a pervert.
This is too intense...
It's different than usual, I think I'm going to break.
Hey...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
We had sex before we did our morning practice.
Then, let's clean up before someone comes,
and do a few practice swings.
Hey there.
You guys, don't tell me...
Well, Kurosaki, you're quite early.
Morning 'practice' sure feels great, eh?
So you were peeping at us, huh...
Hey, don't run away!
I'll punish you all!
Please don't.
A-Any further and it shall be sinful.
Even if you say that,
it's not really convincing when you're looking like that.
Please Sister
Besides, you're already wet down here.
Then, why don't you just help me finish
my confession here, Sister-san?
This wet wrapping sensation...
You're the best, Sister-san.
I'm cumming!
N-Now that this activity is already done...
Not yet.
I want you to do it this way too, Sister-san.
No, you can't!
You can't... you mustn't...!
That's...
Sister-san!
I was dropped from the company.
The work was great there, and the salary was alright too.
But in these times of economic recession
the company decided to lay off some employees.
Eventually, I got hit by the wind of depression and got kicked.
Now I'm without a job.
Damn, I came to this nearby church to at least ease my mind,
but this tranquil atmosphere is just making me more...!
Damn! Why?
Why me?!
I'm sorry.
N-No, it's okay.
This person...
I don't think she was here before.
She's really cute.
I would have really wanted this kind of nun to ease my heart.
Umm...
It may sound imposing,
but if you have any problems,
feel free to talk to me about it.
Sister-san.
Yes?
I like you.
Please go out with me.
Eh?
Sorry, you're just so cute, I couldn't help but say it.
Is that so?
My heart was about to jump out of my chest.
I was laid off last week.
I've been causing trouble to those around me.
Right now, even to you.
Maybe it's my personality.
Maybe I really am a failure of a man.
Please don't be too hard on yourself.
Your problems aren't just caused by one single thing.
Let me confess.
Let me wash away my sins.
If it's a prayer, then by all means.
No, not by my soul,
but by my body.
Umm, would this really work?
Of course.
Everything will be alright once you help me.
I want to confess with this.
Please.
Sister-san!
Is this how I should do it?
That's really great.
What is this?
It's starting to get harder, and hotter.
I'm haying difficulty breathing.
I'm cumming!
Oh no, I have to drink everything!
My assistance for your confession is complete.
We're not finished yet.
That didn't work at all.
So you're just tricking me, Sister-san.
Eh, why?
I think what I really need is your pussy's assistance.
B-But that's...
Is there a problem?
Isn't accepting confessions one of
the most important jobs of a nun?
T-That's not what I...
Okay, I get it.
Seems I really am a nuisance.
I no longer have any will to live.
I might leave this world forever tomorrow.
You can't!
It's not your fault that you were laid off!
I'm sure there are many other reasons!
You can't give up living just because of that!
That's why, don't tell me that.
She's really serious about this, I'm starting to feel sorry for her.
Okay, okay, I'm alright.
I'm not going to disappear.
T-Then, let's continue your confession.
Is it really all right?
Please.
I'm going in.
Okay.
So she really is...
Are you alright?
I'm okay.
Please, just continue.
Don't fondle it like that.
Your breasts feel very soft and tender, I just can't hold back.
No, please don't say such embarrassing things.
I just can't help it.
Your pussy feels very warm, it feels like my dick is going to melt.
No, I'm really embarrassed.
This is embarrassing.
Enough... with this already.
Sister-san!
It's getting even bigger.
Oh no..
My body is moving in sync with his!
Why?
I'm already exposed and embarrassed as it is, yet...
Don't, not there...
It's deep, it's reaching my womb...
Oh no...
Your dick feels good!
I'm about to cum.
Eh? Wait!
Not inside, wait...
Wait!
Don't, don't!
Not inside, I'm going to get pregnant!
It feels amazing...
6 month later
Congratulations on your wedding.
Congratulations.
Umm...
Everyone, thank you.
Let's get along well from now on, okay, darling?
May I ask?
What is it that the bride found most charming about her groom?
Well...
His big and sturdy dick!
Ehh?!