I was surprised when it starting raining.
It's just an evening shower so I think it won't take long.
I should have brought an umbrella.
I messed up.
U-Umm...
It got wet, so... please don't stare at them.
I-I'm sorry...
This situation makes us looks as if we're dating.
No,
we're actually just pretending to be lovers.
[The Never Ending First Love Days]
The only reason this happened,
was because of that incident where I saved her,
by pretending to be her boyfriend.
But, if he finds out that it's all pretend,
he might start approaching me again.
W-Well, I guess that's true.
That's why,
this may be a really imposing request but...
Can you please keep up the dating act for now?
Even though it's not for real.
Eh?!
I can't ask any other guy for this,
would it be alright with you?
This feels somewhat embarrassing.
B-But,
we have to show everyone that we're really close.
H-Hey...
If it's okay with you, would you like some of my lunch?
It'll make us seem like more of a couple,
if we share a lunch together.
Y-Yeah.
Okay, here.
Eh? Is it okay?
Yup. it's alright.
Well? Is it good?
Yeah, very.
I see, that's good then.
Good morning.
Good morning, Nanasawa-san.
I was bombarded with questions ever since we did that yesterday.
It was quite a ruckus on my side too.
But, they've all gotten the message.
That we are dating.
Y-Yeah, they understood that we are dating on my side as well.
Well, we're going to officially pretend
to be a couple from now on...
So... let's get along, okay?
That was great.
You got to buy something good.
Yeah, I've got no complaints now.
I'm glad that you were the one to choose for me.
Umm... about how you call me...
What is it?
We are pretending to be couples after all so,
you can call me Yuni.
Eh?! But, that's...
It's alright.
But to refer to you informally so suddenly...
Can I just call you Yuni-chan for now?
Okay.
That's good enough for me.
Let's go, Yuni-chan.
Thank you.
For always listening to my selfish requests.
But,
as the memories of us being together continue to grow,
the mere act of pretending to be a couple,
is getting harder and harder to maintain.
H-Hey!
Yuni-chan!
You mustn't!
You promised that you wouldn't do anything else, not even a kiss.
I'm sorry, but I'm...
You can't!
I'm sorry...
Yuni-chan...
It's the afternoon of that next day,
when Yuni-chan suddenly visits my place.
I apologize, for suddenly doing such a thing.
You... hated it, right?
I'm sorry for suddenly running away like that as well.
It was the first time a guy did that to me,
I had no idea how to react.
I'm sorry.
I'll never do it again.
I promise.
That's not what I meant.
I've thought of this for quite some time.
Maybe that's what is naturally supposed to happen after all.
Naturally? What do you mean?
Well, umm...
Holding each other, showing affection to each other,
sweethearts normally do those things, right?
That's true, but,
but we're...
But, you want to do it, right?
Y-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
This is something that started with my request.
You don't have to hold yourself back so much.
Wait, just wait!
Yu-Yuni-chan?!
Umm... I'm not experienced with this yet so,
please, be gentle with me.
Can I touch?
Yeah.
If the bra's in the way,
here's a hook on the back.
If you open it on both sides,
... it can be taken off.
They're big.
Don't say that, it's embarrassing.
Oh no, my nipples are starting to get a hard on.
It's my first time,
and yet, I'm getting really aroused already.
I'm going to fondle them a bit harder.
If you fondle them like that,
my breasts will get squished.
Yuni-chan, Yuni-chan...!
His hot and stiff thing is hitting me.
Could this be...?
Hey, do you want to do it with me?
I'm sorry,
but I can no longer...!
It's okay, don't hold back.
It's my first time,
but if it's you... I'll gladly give it up.
Can I take it off?
It's embarrassing,
but okay, take it off.
S-So, so this is your...
It's beautifully pink.
And it looks very tender.
Please, don't stare right there too long.
What should I do?
I'm already very wet down there.
I'm starting to become hornier.
Yuni-chan, I...
I-It looks really big.
You're about to put that inside me, right?
Are you scared?
I'm a bit worried if we can do it properly.
But, it's alright.
If my first time is with you, I...
I will not regret it.
Th-Then, here I go.
Yuni-chan, shall I stop?
Don't... don't stop!
I'm okay, I'm really okay so,
please, do it until the end.
I'm sorry, you're doing this all for me and...
Hey, can you see it?
We're connected together.
This hard thing is filling my insides.
Yeah, I can feel it.
Your insides are also gripping me tightly.
You can move now.
The pain will eventually subside.
I'm alright.
Okay, I'll move.
Your hot thing is penetrating me deeply.
My insides are being stirred.
So this... so this is sex.
Yuni-chan, does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good.
I'm starting to feel good as your thing continues to rub inside me.
Me too, I can really feel your insides, Yuni-chan.
I'm glad that I've made you happy with it.
It's okay, you can push it harder.
Make yourself feel good with me.
Your dick is twitching.
It's coming. Something's coming.
I can feel it coming closer,
I think it's making me go crazy.
Oh no, I'm about to...!
It's okay, just cum when you want to.
Yuni-chan...!
It's hot.
There's lots of It.
So this is a man's...
I'm sorry, for making a mess of you.
It's okay.
I was just surprised.
But, you felt aroused with me, right?
Yeah, it felt good.
If, at a later time,
you feel like doing this again,
don't hold back, okay?
Yuni-chan, I...!
We're partners, right?
You won't be able to go on with it if it starts to hurt you too much.
Yuni-chan...
That's why, let's overcome this together, okay?
Yes.
Both of us are partners,
our relationship in playing make-believe
as to lovers has never changed.
G-Good morning.
Good morning.
Umm... is your body okay?
Yes, I'm alright.
Hey,
Yuni-chan, thank you.
I will never forget what happened yesterday.
Me too, I'll never forget it either.
Thank you.
So, see you again at lunch then.
But someday...
Yes, someday.
Lovely-cation!
Lovely-cation.
Every afternoon, Aya and I would usually
stop by the arcade for a few games.
The events that followed happened there one fateful day.
So, what are we playing?
Are we going to play against each other on a fighting game again?
It's not really cool to play the same thing over and over, so...
How about we have a little change of pace?
Eh?
Hey, I haven't really played this game yet.
Focus, senpai.
We're about to start.
What's this? A boss fight?
Hey, I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die!
Senpai, lend that gun to me.
Hurry!
Okay!
A dual gun wield?
I'm actually ambidextrous.
Hey, hey, your girlfriend's good.
Amagase-san?
So you're here.
Yup, and I've been watching the whole time.
Is your girlfriend a student at our school?
Oh, uh, yeah.
She's my underclassman, though.
That's amazing!
Will she be able to get to the last stage then?
W-Well...
I think it'd be interesting if she did.
Aya?
H-Huh..?
...She lost?
Everyone was watching earlier, you didn't
have to lose on purpose like that.
Who was that person earlier?
That person earlier?
Oh, you mean Amagase-san?
She's my classmate.
She's quite beautiful, isn't she?
W-Well...
I also talk with a few women besides you, you know.
Aya?
Senpai, there's actually one more game
that I'm interested in trying out.
Huh? What is it so suddenly?
This can't be done by yourself so,
I want you to help me out, senpai.
I have no problem with that,
but what's the game?
It's my first time getting inside,
but the interior is simpler than I imagined.
Gotta pay to snap first.
400 yen for one round?
This is quite expensive.
Don't worry about paying.
It's for myself anyway.
It's okay, you did treat me to Gun Blazing,
I'll pay for it.
I-I'm sorry, and thank you.
The main modes are Frolic with everyone...
... and Flirty with couples.
What are we going to choose?
I-It's just the two of us here, so...
Y-You're right.
Flirty with couples.
I... I think it's better if we get closer.
A-Alright then.
J-Just a little bit more.
Senpai, what's wrong?
Wait, you mustn't!
You can't do that here!
D-Don't...!
Sen..pai...
Senpai, my ears...
They're getting really wet.
Is he serious about doing it here?
W-Wait!
Just wait... no!
W-Wait, we can't!
We can't do it here!
Here, I'm going to use my hands.
That's why, please just help yourself..
... with a handjob from me.
Aya.
Amazing.
It's getting a lot harder than it usually does.
Umm... senpai,
what do I need to do to pleasure you quickly?
Then, try sucking on it.
Okay, senpai.
That feels good, Aya.
Senpai is feeling great with my blowjob.
is he feeling good then?
Jeez, senpai's such a...
Such a pervert.
Senpai, hurry...
Cum already.
Where can I cum?
Eh? Well, how about in my mouth?
Aya, I'm about to cum!
Go ahead.
Did that satisfy you?
I'm sorry, but I can't hold it in any longer!
I'll finish this quickly so...
Y-You... you can't!
You can't put it in.
You can't, you can't... and yet...
And yet it's slowly pushing deeper.
Aya!
It's deep!
This position feels like...
Feels like it's reaching the very depths of my body!
Aya, your insides are gripping me tightly!
S-Senpai,
the way you push it in like that feels really lewd.
Oh no, I'm really about to moan.
Don't! If you do that, everyone outside will notice!
Everyone... will see us!
Start Snapping!
Now then, we'll start snapping right away!
Take a good pose, okay?
Just wait, I don't like taking photos looking like this!
Stop!
Amazing.
So this is what it looks like.
No way, it just took our pictures.
This... our indecent pose,
has just been photographed.
Here's the next snapshot!
I can't take this anymore!
Don't take photos!
This bestial pose,
it's also going to be photographed!
I-I have to cover it!
Senpai, you're too intense.
I have to support my body, or else...!
I said I cant hold on anymore!
I said I don't want this anymore!
Oh no, oh no!
A-Aya,
are you about to cum?
N-No, I'm not!
I'm not about to cum!
Se-Senpai, you're really too intense!
This is the last snapshot!
Oh no, we're going to be photographed.
We're going to be photographed again!
Oh no, I'm about to lose it.
This is, this is just...!
Se-Senpai!
Aya!
Amazing.
Lots of the hot stuff is filling me up inside.
Aya... umm...
Sorry for a lot of things.
Pull it out before you try to apologize, please.
This position is just too embarrassing.
Jeez...
You've just fucked me here,
forced me to take indecent photos,
and you even came inside me without warning.
You really are a hopeless pervert, senpai!
Thanks for waiting, now get your photo!
Th-This is...!
Confiscated!
I really just wanted to take some photos with you, senpai.
Th-Then, shall we take some more?
W-We can't!
I'm already sick of taking snapshots for now.
B-But, maybe one day we can...
Senpai
Aya