Welcome!
Welcome to Royal Bust!
Ah, ehm...
Oh sorry, I'm here by myself.
Please proceed to the seat you like.
Thanks.
Family Restaurant "Royal Bust".
Even though the dishes aren't really that delicious,
due to the popularity of the waitress' uniform,
there are a lot of male customers.
I can't wait any longer.
There's still 1 point to go, Chief.
Is that so? My little thing down there can't hold on to any point anymore.
Lately, I've also been patronizing the restaurant...
...due to the new waitress, Saiko-chan.
Sir, since you've accumulated
enough points during this period,
This is your invitation to our "Special Service Day".
Oh...
What is this "Service Day"?
Yes!
We've prepared a special menu for customers...
...who have been patronizing our store.
You'll be coming on that day, right?
Oh yeah, it's a rare chance after all.
Thank you very much~
Saiko-chan's indeed cute!
See you.
Thank you very much.
Sir!?
Please be careful.
T- Thank you.
E- Ehm...
Oh, you dropped this.
Oh...
We'll look forward seeing you on "Service Day".
Y- Yeah.
Could it be a special event to try out the new dishes?
Presented by imuR88
And then, I went there without any
expectation of what was going to happen.
This time's really...
I should have come earlier!
How's the new menu?
It doesn't seem to be that tasty after all.
I'll still eat anyway.
Saiko-chan's really cute, right?
My answer is always the same.
This heated sensation...
It's gonna be Saiko-chan, right?
Saiko-chan belongs to me!
S- Saiko-chan!
Please enjoy yourself.
Oh, it's opening!
Welcome!
Sorry for the wait!
Well then, let's start the "Special Service Day".
Please, take the customers to their seats.
Yes!
What's going on-
Oh?
Are you alright, Sir?
I'll take you to your seat now.
M- Me?
Yes!
Who is that guy?
Saiko-chan...
What's with that!?
Hey! What is going on here!?
I've decided to take Saiko-chan today!
Didn't we made a reservation already?
I'm really sorry, Sir.
I'll take you to your seat today.
Eh? Oh hey!!
Please look forward to the special menu you've reserved.
Q- Quit joking with us! Let's go, Chief!
Oh well...
I don't mind the sequence as long as I get to have the new menu.
Yes, Chief.
T- Thank you very much.
Please, have a seat here.
This is the menu for today.
Why is she siting here?
This isn't a bar, right?
T- This is!?
Anyway, as a start, please select the girl you like.
The pricing is so reasonable.
T- That's what it's meant by "Special Service"!?
Is this for real!?
Can you recommend anything?
Ehm, it's weird for me to say this myself, but...
...it seems like newcomers are really popular these days.
Do you want to...
...eat me up?
O- Of course!
Thank you very much!
But since you're this popular, don't other customers want you too?
Newcomers get to choose their first customer.
I've decided long ago, that my first time has to be with you.
Saiko-chan...
I- Is it really alright?
I'm going to touch you...
Yes, please.
H- How soft... You don't wear any bra today?
It'd have been...
...taken off anyway.
Finally, I'm going to do it with the girl I like... Bon appetit!!
Amazing...
This is amazing! Royal Bust!
Sir, please hurry up with your orders.
But, just touching is free, right? Since it isn't on the menu at all.
Yes, it's a free service.
Well then, here's next.
It'd be such a waste if I weren't to enjoy this lustful body slowly.
B- But... There's no time...
Oh, by the way...
What exactly is the "Drink Bar" on the menu?
Yes, that refers...
...to those waitresses giving head,
drinking all your cum till you're dry.
Of course, customers could have a second serving if they're able to.
Their techniques are pretty good, and thus pretty much popular too.
I guess I'll try it too for now.
Yes, thank you very much.
You can choose to cum on the face or inside the mouth.
Indeed, I'll shoot inside the mouth then.
Wow, she's this wet already.
Let me repeat your orders again.
1 Blowjob, cumming inside the mouth.
You'll have to pay...
...for this order, is it alright?
Yes! Yes!
It's so big...
Is that so?
I'm so excited...
Even though I've studied it, this is the first time I'm doing it.
Do tell me immediately when I've done something weird.
Ahhh, that spot...
Right, the other side too.
This feels so good...
Saiko-chan...
W- Wait, that's too much...
If this goes on...
...I- I will cum!
Somehow, I really like this taste.
How is it? Is it good?
This is bad... Since it's such a rare chance, can you use your breasts too?
Yes, I got it. A side dish, right?
This feels so great! How soft...
That's right...
Lick it too.
N- No good!
I- I'm cumming!
Put it in your mouth... In your mouth!
No! S- Stop it!
I'll drink all of it...
It's still coming out.
Don't mind it, I still can cum a lot more.
A lot inside you...
Ding Dong!
Tendou-san! Tendou Saiko-san! Please, proceed to table 3!
Tendou-san, please hurry up. Another customer is waiting.
I- Is it time already?
But Senpai, he hasn't had his main dish yet.
There are many orders for you today.
If we can't go by timings, it'll cause inconvenience to other customers.
Yes, you're right.
I'm sorry, but please order me again.
How can that be...?
Saiko-chan?
Sir, do call for me if you want any more orders.
Sorry for keep you waiting!
Oh! You're here, Saiko-chan! Look at this! It's so lively.
What do you like for today?
Everything on the menu.
Please, don't be too restrained.
Oh, you're already this wet! I'm gonna put it in, Saiko-chan.
Eh? Already?
What am I doing?
So tight!
Chief, do let me have a taste too!
Urgs... Saiko-chan gets fucked by that old man...
It's all because of me taking my own sweet time...
Rub... Rub...
Saiko-chan...
She seems to be enjoying...
E- Ehm...
Hmm?
Who are you?
I'm Yayoi.
No, I'm not asking for your name...
How can I leave it alone when it's so energetic?
It's such a pity that your target is Tendou-san.
H- How do you know that?
Hey, look!
Mine is much more comfortable. It's the number 1 bust here.
I'll make you forget about Tendou-san.
But, aren't there many orders for you too?
I'm in charge of the "Drink Bar"-section, I came out to take a rest.
As long as I say I'm done, no one will notice about me.
Actually, I wanted to provide service to the one I'm interested in.
W- What do you mean by that?
This hard...
Do you feel good?
A- Amazing...
I'm cumming!
No!
You have to cum inside of me!
Alright...
Please, Taka-san... Please make me feel good there.
Hey...
I'm not good enough for you?
Y- Yayoi-chan...
Amazing!
Fuck me deeper...
Come to think of it, how do you...
...know my name?
I'll definitely check on the name of the guy I like.
I've always been interested in you.
S- So cute...
Sorry, I came inside...
No, don't pull it out!
But...
Am I not good?
Impossible! It's so comfortable.
That's good! You're free to bang me as many times as you want!
Is that true?
Yes, my special service. Since this isn't my job, my name isn't on the menu. Just cum all you want!
Yeah, I'll do so.
Great... Fuck me harder...
Fill my insides with your cum!
Yayoi...
This is amazing!!
Oh, is that really alright for me to join in?
Of course!
Saiko-chan, please lick mine too.
Yes!
This feels so good, Chief!
Is today really your first time?
You're moving your hips so fast... Does it feel that good?
It feels so good...
Chief, her mouth's pretty good too! Should we switch?
I'm not switching! I'm gonna cum inside her.
Hey, stop looking over there already!
Oh, s- sorry.
It's useless to apologize, I'm not going to forgive you.
Wai-
I did say it, right? That I'm going to make you forget about her.
Just look at me.
Y- Yayoi...
That...feels so great!
This feels so good, I'm cumming...
It will be bad if you do this...
It's punishment...
...for looking at other girls.
Stop it...
Don't take it for granted, Yayoi.
How's this!?
Amazing!
Great... Great... It's all the way in...
I- It's deep inside of me.
I'm cumming!
I' can't...take it anymore!
Me too... Together...
I'm sorry, Saiko-chan...
Chief, I'm already at my limit!
Me too! I'm cumming!
Yes, sir...
...feel free to cum inside!
It seems like I can't answer you today.
Feels so great... I'm cumming!!!
How is this, Saiko?
Your insides feel so good that I can't stop, Saiko-chan...
It's coming out... Together at the same time...
This feels so good!
Hey, we're pretty suitable for each other, right?
Oh, yeah...
Should I have a delivery service starting tomorrow?
I can't wait for the next Service Day.
There's such a service!?
No, it's my private service.
It's only for you. Keep it a secret from the store. There's no need to accumulate any points too.
T- That means...
To be honest, I don't feel that high, no matter how much I've cummed.
If something like this can go on everyday...
It's growing bigger inside of me again!
Everytime I hear Saiko-chan's voice while she's surrounded by men...
...excited and moving her hip vigorously... I'll feel regretful.
This feels so good~
After all, I still have to come back.
Since it's free for all,
just cum all you want!
Of course, after that day...
Yayoi came to my house for delivery service everyday.
Come to think of our talk about Tendou-san just now...
That is just a lie of yours, right?
No, it's true.
Lately, she seems to be engrossed in thought while working.
After some investigation, it seems like she overdid it during the Service Day.
Just a day ago...
Uhm, Tendou-san... The carrot...
What should I do? The ingredient section is waiting...
I like you...
More... Fuck me more!!
I'm going to cum deep inside of you...
The part-time employee got sacked
because he left his work for 3 hours.
Stop talking about that!
But... It's true!
And there's something like this too...
Uhm...
What is it?
Let me clean your thing...
Please wait for your turn, okay?
It's alright...
Do you think, I'll believe in those things?
She said it yesterday at the store too, that she's looking forward to my next visit.
I don't know!
Maybe she's already addicted to pleasure.
At the store, you've seen an old man, a regular, right?
It seems like he rented an apartment and brought Tendou-san away.
T- That chief!?
No, it's that spectacled and bald old man.
W- What!?
She usually went out late at night.
Providing service for all sort of people.
It's obvious why such rumors got spread.
That's... That's...
It's deep inside me...
Takashi... That's so great!
More! Harder!!
Even so, I'm... I'm...
Great... Feels so great!!
Feels so great!!!!
I'm cumming again!!
This is amazing...
I'm cumming!!!
Saiko-chan...
Cumming 5 times... That's the peak, right?
Come to think of it, the hardness of your dick seems different...
Well then, what will the next rumor be?
Oh, thank you very much, sir.
Since you've collected enough points, here's your invitation to the "Special Service Day".
Well then, we look forward to your next visit.
Brought to you by imuR88 (fireboy88 & Maciste)
We hope you enjoyed it!
Visit us @ http://imur88.blogspot.com/