LOVE COLON
Congrats, Erika-chan!
It's your third victory as the overall national
champion in singles tennis this year!
That's amazing.
Thank you.
You're going to be first again next time, right?
There's really no one that can take me on, so it'll be a cinch!
Ooh, big words from the big champion!
Well, yeah.
What?
Nope, nothing.
Can you stop staring at other people?
Kurosaki's as cocky as ever.
Kurosaki Erika is the tennis club's ace.
Her skills far surpass that of a normal student,
and she has won several national championship
tournaments already.
Plus, she's cute, so she's very popular at school.
I applied for the club!
For real?! You really did it, huh?
Well, there isn't much chance to see
Kurosaki-san otherwise, you see.
I want to enter too.
As for me, well... perhaps I'm just the same as them.
This is really amazing, as expected.
This is irresistible.
Captain, I'm going to take a short break.
Okay.
You three.
Can you stop staring lewdly at me like that?
You're a nuisance to my practice.
Just quit the club if you just joined
because of those stupid reasons.
What? Definitely not cute.
That personality of hers is the killing blow.
Right?
What did you just say?!
Just like that.
Everyone who enters the club because of Kurosaki,
usually ends up quitting because of her snobbish personality.
Though, I'm really impressed I lasted two months.
Maybe I'm actually a masochist?
Oh, you're early.
Hey, good morning.
Morning!
Wow, she's really cute when she's smiling.
I was the first one here yesterday though.
That's too bad.
That's our competitive queen for you.
She's even serious about being first in morning practice.
Hey, do you want to spar with me?
Eh?
No need to be nervous.
I just want to stretch my body a little.
Well, but...
But I'm really nervous!
Then, why don’t we do this?
It's my win if I get a set, your win if you get even a point.
If you can get the ball past me in any way,
I'll listen to one request.
Any request that you may have.
This girl really decides things on her own, doesn't she?
It's okay, it's okay.
No need to be too serious about it.
I'm going to win in the end anyway.
I'm pissed.
Here I go!
That's fast!
I'm not stopping!
No way.
This is the last time you'll be making a fool of other people.
You lost.
I've been meaning to say this,
but I'm already at my limit.
So this is the perfect opportunity.
What?!
Now, a deal is a deal.
You'll listen to my request, right?
I get it already!
Just do it already.
What are you getting dazed for, you idiot?!
Umm, what I actually want is for you to go out with me...
*stare*
D-Don't look!
I've decided.
I'll change my request to a prize!
Don't change it!
I want to have sex with you!
You didn't specify that I can't change my request, right?
Hey...!
That's...
That doesn't matter!
She's really sweaty.
So she sweats this much while playing.
Her sweat,
voice,
warmth,
every bit of it makes me aroused.
Your thing is very wet already, and it looks amazing.
No, this is...
This is the prize, yeah!
It's not like I'm getting horny or anything!
Then I'll be taking your pussy.
What are you saying, you pervert?!
You’re so cute, Kuro-chan.
Oh no, what is this?
My body feels all tingly.
Oh no!
Shall I stop?
No, I mean...
I want you to insert your thing, inside me.
Man, you're just too cute!
Kuro-chan, the dick that you want is inside you.
I love it.
I love your dick.
Kuro-chan, so you're actually a perverted girl.
You're completely fine being exposed like this.
That's not important!
I just love your dick, and you too Midorikawa-kun.
There, yes...
I'm about to cum.
I’m cumming, I'm cumming!
Kenta.
Kurosaki.
Don't forget morning practice tomorrow, okay?
Got it.
I've decided,
that I will spend my youth playing tennis.
Welcome home, Master.
Then, just for you Master,
I'll give you a little of my special magic.
I'll give you lots of love.
Abracadabra, make it more delicious!
You're...?
Kyan!
I never knew you were working part time there.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you tell me?
Is there a reason you hid it from me?
W-Well that's...
That's because the maid outfits there look so cute.
What?
I really just wanted to try them out.
Just a little, you know.
Do you really have time for part time
work with your baseline grades?
Pushing it too far like that is already a crime, you know.
What are you going to do if you repeat a school year?
That's... I also plan to study hard, you know.
Please Ma-kun, just for a month,
and I'd only do it during weekends.
It's really, really fun you know!
Well, I can see how it would be quite fun.
Welcome home, Master!
Why, you even went there to see maids yourself, right?
Well, I kind of wanted a change of pace.
That's it!
I love how people smile whenever they come to the shop.
When I talk to the customers wearing the maid outfit,
I really feel like it's a very fun thing to do.
So, do you have one of their maid outfits right now?
Huh? Yeah, I have it.
It's actually prohibited to bring it out of the shop,
but I just sneaked this one out.
Then, try it on here.
Right now?
Umm, is there a weird spot somewhere?
Ma-kun?
Yui-chan, I don't think you're just having fun wearing that,
but actually getting a bit horny with it too.
Eh?
You love it when people look at your
breasts when you wear that, right?
Don't! My nipples are...
How cute, Yui-chan.
Don't say such things out loud.
But, maybe I do feel horny, when you touch me like that.
Jeez, now I'm worried that someone will simply take you from me.
That won't happen!
My feelings for you will never change.
Because I really, really do love you, Ma-kun!
Yui-chan.
Wow.
She's already this wet just from kissing.
No, don't look.
I wonder why...
Could it be because of these clothes?
I feel like I'm a real maid.
I kind of want to do it more than normal.
I'm going to service you a lot okay, Ma-kun?
Yui-chan, that feels very good.
Oh crap, I'm cumming!
Yui-chan, are you okay?
Yeah.
It just felt so good that I...
I'm okay, it's fine as long as you felt good.
I love you, Yui-chan.
Ma-kun.
It's going inside.
Why?
You just came, and yet...
It... really feels good.
Your insides are wrapping around me tightly.
It feels great.
That's embarrassing, so please don't say that.
No, not my nipples.
It's going deep inside.
I love it.
Your thing is hitting me inside.
More...
Do it, more...
Amazing Yui-chan,
you're this wet, and I'm being sucked in by it.
Yui-chan, I'm about...
I'm about to cum.
Please, I want it.
I want you to cum inside my pussy.
Yui-chan!
Lots of cum came out...
And so, as we agreed upon
Yui-chan stopped her work for a month
to concentrate on her studies.
However, our 'change of pace' is still well in motion.
That's because...
Here yo go, say ah!
She becomes my personal maid during weekends.
Wow, it's good.
Really? I'm glad.