N-Nii-san, this is an experiment!
This is really an experiment!
Sorry, Honoka, but if you look at me...
S-Sorry! I'll look away so I don't bother you.
Right there... Nii-san's thing is right there!
Wow!
I'm not looking! I'm really not looking!
I'm not curious about it at all!
It's a bit late for that...
It's bigger than I imagined... It's twitching, too!
Come on, let's start.
R-Right. We should. This is training, after all.
I look away for a second and it got even bigger!
Sorry.
That was rude of me!
I've never seen one before, so I was surprised.
It's really embarrassing when such
a thick cock is suddenly in my face!
Since it's yours, I thought it was really nice
to look at, but really, I'm trying to say,
but what I'm trying to say is that...
Calm down. Take a deep breath, okay?
Y-Yes.
Uh, not like that. Your breathing is too ragged.
You're right.
I'm calm now.
I'm sorry, this is my first time.
I'd be depressed you were used to this.
I'm happy that you're acting like yourself.
Nii-san, I'll do my best!
Are you really going to keep on
acting surprised like that?
Well, yes. How do I put this...
Hm? I want to know what you think.
Um, It's just so big, so thick,
and I'm nervous because it's my first time.
Oh, I see. Maybe we should
just move on to the next step.
Uh... yes, you're right.
I'm sorry, we need to move on.
In the instructions,
it says that I should grip it with my hands.
So, I...
What do you need to grip?
You need to explain the terms to me.
Your dick...
Nii-san?
I'm fine. Maybe you should
get started some time soon.
O-Okay, then, excuse me.
It just jumped! Wow.
It's so hot! This is what it gets like?
It's hard and hot, but it's also squishy.
Now it's throbbing.
I don't know how much force
I should put in. Is this much okay?
I can't believe that it's so big.
C-Could you loosen your grip a little?
S-Sorry. I'm sorry I can't do it properly.
Well, it's your first time,
and it felt good even though it hurt a bit.
It felt good even though it hurt?
Y-Yeah, just do it however you want.
Okay! I'll do my best to get better
and make you feel good!
It's getting even bigger!
I can't believe how big it's gotten!
Please keep going.
Y-Yes! Please relax and try to feel
as good as you can from my hands.
Keep a good rhythm while rubbing it.
Something's coming out! Is this pre-cum?
This means it's starting to feel good, right?
Honoka, slow down a bit, or...
Nii-san, this feels good, right?
It's fine, you can just cum like this!
Nii-san, it's getting bigger again!
Nii-san...
This is amazing! It's giving off such a dirty smell.
Nii-san, did that feel good?
Y-Yeah, thanks, Honoka.
Oh, sorry. I'll clean you up.
Honoka, your face is covered too.
Nii-san, I'm so happy!
Please pat me on the head more!
I'm so happy I'm able to do this training with you.
That's right. Cradle is the last fortress.
We have to do our best, too.
Priestess Pudding - Honoka ~ Masturbating and
Cumming Lessons in an Uncivilized Land.
Seeing him after I did that makes me nervous
but if I don't wake him up...
There's supposed to be a test today.
If I don't use everything I have at my disposal...
Maybe he'll wake up if I whisper
in his ear, or if I k-k-k-kiss him.
Or I could use my training
and rub his dick to wake him up!
I wouldn't be able to live with myself if
he hated me for doing something so lewd...
Ah, what should I do?! Maybe I should just
get naked and hop into his bed and surprise him?!
I guess that'd get him to wake up, but the shock
he'd get from that happening would shock me too, and...
Good morning, Honoka...
N-Nii-san? Oh, good morning.
You woke up early today.
I actually woke up thirty
minutes later than I usually do...
What? Is it that late already? We need to go, then!
Y-Yeah.
I didn't think the test would take an entire day.
Sorry, do you think you could go back home, Honoka?
Of course! I was just thinking
that I would clean your room.
It feels so weird coming in here,
thanks to last night.
I was supposed to wake
him up this morning too, but...
I can't stay like this!
This is all so I can support nii-san!
I-I need to clean this up too, don't I?
I already know he hides a lot of these.
There don't seem to be any new ones, but...
This is an investigation of nii-san's fetishes!
It looks like he's still into younger girls.
If that's the case, then... wait, what am I doing?!
I need to put these back where I found them.
A-Are these...
W-Well, I guess I have no choice. He's such a slob.
These are the boxers he was wearing this morn...
I mean, the boxers that need to be washed.
That's right, just like usual.
I need to finish cleaning everything up soon, but...
Oh no, I'm starting to get excited.
I can't get what we did out of my head at all!
Oh no, if I stay here too long,
I'll be trapped in his scent and I'll...
He's not coming back soon, is he?
Nii-san's rubbing my boob!
Nii-san, my nipples are getting hard!
You're teasing them with your fingers.
Nii-san, ever since we were little, I...
I'd do anything to help you.
Helping you makes me happy, even if it's H-training!
For me, you are...
I'm even more sensitive than usual!
My pussy is only for you,
so I'll just play with my ass instead.
It feels so good!
My ass is making me so wet, it's overflowing!
Forgive me, nii-san!
I'm sorry that I'm such a perverted, dirty girl!
I'm sorry that I'm playing with my ass
while wearing your boxers on my head!
Nii-san, my ass is starting to feel strange!
Please forgive me! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!! I'm gonna cum with my ass!
My head is filled with you, nii-san.
Nii-san...
I need to finish cleaning up, fast.
There was something wrong with the system,
so the test ended halfway in...
Honoka-san?
Oh, is that right?
I'm so sorry I did that on your bed!
I'll kill myself to apologize!
H-Hold on! Hold on! Calm down!
Now that you've seen this shameful
side of me, you'll definitely hate me!
I don't hate you at all!
You're really ashamed of having such
a dirty little sister though, aren't you?
I love dirty girls!
But I'm just a perverted girl who
gets off by playing with her asshole!
I'm an even bigger pervert than you.
I was getting really excited watching you...
You got turned on from watching me?
Could you prove it to me, nii-san?
I'll show you all of my body, nii-san.
You're so wet. Can I touch it?
Yes, nii-san... Please touch it lots!
Nii-san, you're playing with my pussy!
You're rubbing it!
It's letting out a really dirty sound... Nii-san!
Show it to me.
Yes! Please look at it!
Please look at my embarrassing parts!
I'm in this position in front of nii-san...
Honoka, you're really sexy.
N-Nii-san, please touch me.
Can I?
I've been keeping it clean so you don't
have to worry about it being dirty...
I'd never think badly about
any part of your body, Honoka.
Really?
I told you before, but I love dirty girls!
Actually, I love you, Honoka!
I love you!
S-Sorry, should I not have said that?
Nii-san, that makes me so happy!
I've never felt this happy in my life!
B-But,
getting confessed to by the guy she likes
is one of the happiest moments for a girl,
then something like this suddenly
happens and I don't know what to do,
and I've found myself fantasizing
about a perfect confession,
and I never thought I'd be confessed to
while spreading my ass for someone...
It's not like I don't like this situation,
actually, I'm so happy I could jump for joy,
but this is all happening so fast and
I just want your dick in my ass already...
Ah! What am I even saying?
Basically, what I'm trying to say, is...
Nii-san, is that your tongue?! You're kidding!
Sorry, you were getting out of control.
Nii-san, your tongue is in my ass!
If you keep moving your tongue like that,
I... I never thought you would lick me there!
This can't be happening!
Your tongue is going inside my ass!
Oh my god, this feels so good, I'm gonna lose it!
My tongue is going inside your ass so easily.
That's because I was playing with it just now.
Nii-san, your fingers are rubbing
against the walls inside my ass!
It feels like you're going to pull it out! It feels so good!
Nii-san, at this rate, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum!
Nii-san!
That's fine, cum.
Nii-san, no! Nii-san, it's not fair!
I want to cum with you!
Nii-san, no! I can't hold on anymore!
Nii-san, you made me cum with my ass.
Nii-san, is that your dick on my ass?
May I?
Please give it to me.
Please use my ass to make yourself feel good!
Your dick is spreading my ass so wide!
I can feel it going deep inside me!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes! Your dick is going so deep inside,
it feels like it's lodged in my stomach!
Does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels amazing.
I'm ready, nii-san.
Your dick is spreading me so wide it feels
like it's going to pull my insides out!
Your dick is going where my fingers can't even reach!
Every time your dick moves
in and out, it stirs up my insides!
Honoka, your ass is so smooth,
it's easy to move around in. It feels really good!
I'm happy that my ass is pleasing you!
It feels so much better than when
I do it by myself! It feels amazing!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч