In a cultural sense, our sexual instincts
are usually the most controlled or suppressed.
However, They are also the one:
that we actually fail to control most of the time.
-Freud
M-Master,
I beg of you.
M-Master, please...
Please tease me more.
Even when I was just a child,
I already bore the burden of everyone's expectations.
Every one thinks of me as serious and diligent.
As a very capable young girl.
One day, the stress of bearing it just became too much.
At that time I learned,
that my Master, Yoshi-kun was into sadomasochism.
I knew that it was wrong but,
I was inevitably drawn into it.
I wanted the built up stress to go away.
I needed some room to breathe.
That's why...
I'm cumming...
Master!
Love S-M
The secret I cannot divulge
Yoshi-kun,
I mean, my master,
was my childhood friend, a neighboring kid,
and eventually became my boyfriend as we started dating.
W-We had sex like normal,
and if it's for him, I'm ready to do anything.
Please, punish me already Yoshi-kun.
Master...
Oh no...
I'm going to cum inside Ayaka.
Okay.
Just let it out.
Let it all out.
Master, I'm about to cum!
Yoshi-kun, please...
I want you... I want you to tease me.
Wait, Nee-chan,
even if you say that...
Please, tease me.
Master...
And with that,
I started to occasionally be my brother... my master's slave.
There's no romance involved.
A relationship out of pure sadomasochism.
Indeed, merely as playmates...
No there, don't rub it in there....!
It's already soaking wet.
Ayaka, you're such a naughty girl.
Yes, I'm sorry,
I'm naughty,
I'm slutty,
so please, go all out on me,
Master!
It's cold and stiff.
It feels weird.
Why?
This is just...
This is just embarrassing,
it even feels painful, and yet...
My insides feel all tingly.
I think, I really am feeling pleasure in this after all.
Ayaka,
if you want me to do more,
then beg for it.
If you cannot,
then we'll end this here today.
I beg of you, Master.
More... Please do it to me more.
I want it inside me.
That's wrong, isn't it?
Do it erotically, as I have instructed you before.
I beg of you...
M-Master,
please insert your thick thing,
inside my wet and lewd hole.
I know that it's wrong,
but, I can no longer stop.
Well? Can you see it?
Yes, I can.
This is the first time I've seen it so clearly.
T-This position makes it go even deeper.
My pussy is being spread wide by your thing.
It sloshes around as it moves inside.
It's really lewd!
Hey now, you need to beg for it more erotically.
M-Master, I feel pleasure while being violated like this.
So please, push ever harder.
Release all of your hot stuff inside me.
Amazing...
As he orders me to say those things,
I become more and more...
Horny...
Ayaka, I'm about to cum.
Yes, please cum!
Just... Just release it all whenever you want to Master.
I shall take it all!
We came to the peak of our pleasure many many times.
Afterwards, the master slave play stops
and we return to being siblings.
I thought of his sadomasochism as perverted before,
but I love Master,
I thought it was okay, even if it hurt
a bit as long as it wasn't too dirty.
At first, I agreed with him with only that kind of mindset,
but now, it's kind of different.
Ready...
Are we really going to do it.
If you can endure it until the end of the class
I'll give you a treat.
However, if you can't run through the entire course with it,
I'll punish you.
Right now...
Right at this moment...
Ready!
O-Oh no...
If I fall down here,
everyone will notice.
I must run the entire course.
It really feels intense.
The sound, it's reverberating.
Oh no, what should I do?
Soon someone will notice,
and they'll start to think of me as a pervert.
In the end,
I wasn't able to finish,
and Master had to lie about me being anemic at that time.
I was then brought to the infirmary.
Love SM
As punishment, he didn't take the vibrator out for the entire day.
Please, Yoshi-kun...
Remove... Remove the vibrator already.
I Won't be able to last until I get home.
It's okay Ayaka.
Our destination is up ahead.
Eh?
He brought me to a public toilet at a park near our school.
The vibrator, please pull it out...
Do not misunderstand.
You're not the one who's supposed to give orders here.
This is your punishment.
Ayaka, where's your apology?
I'm sorry, Yoshi-kun.
I wasn't able to run till the end.
That doesn't sound too respectful.
I guess I'll continue this.
Why?
I'm being treated horribly like this,
and yet I'm slowly starting to feel aroused.
My body is starting to feel hot.
My deepest apologies, M-Master.
Guess it can't be helped.
I think I have to punish you here.
Master, please punish me lots in this very lewd spot.
It’s already very wet, and it's wrapping me around nicely.
Ayaka, you really are perverted.
I'm sorry.
I feel really horny.
Now, now, if you don't hold that door properly,
it will swing open.
No way, if someone comes inside...
They'll see everything.
Your pussy is trying to squeeze me tightly.
You're really are getting horny.
O-Oh no...
That's... That's just...
No, whenever I think someone could come any minute,
I feel really excited, and my pussy starts
to secrete its love juices again.
Ayaka, it's about time.
Cum.
Please cum.
Please cum lots, Master.
I'm about to cum too!
I guess it's really stuck with me now,
Yoshi-kun... I mean Master's sadomasochistic plays.
Ayaka is Masters girlfriend and childhood friend.
So I thought of her as a little sister.
Me too, I also thought of Onee-chan,
Who's also bears the same name as I, as family.
That's why,
when I heard that she was also into
sadomasochism, I was surprised.
I actually had thought about ending this kind
of relationship for some time already.
But after he did lots of things to us many times,
I began to see how our Master truly holds us dearly,
regardless of whether as a sibling sweetheart, or as a p-playmate.
How much time as passed already?
I don't even know how many times I came.
There are still lots of students left doing their club activities.
If someone sees us like this...
Both of us would surely be violated.
If I could at least talk to her,
I could have tried to comfort myself a little bit.
No, please don't.
It's embarrassing with Nee-chan staring at me like that.
Preventing us from talking to each other,
was also part of Yoshi-kun, our Master's plan I guess.
Yoshi-kun?
Master?
You two seem to be enjoying this.
What are you talking about?
Hurry... Hurry up and let me go already.
What?
You want me to fondle your breasts?
No!
That's not what I... No...!
I'll lose myself if you keep squeezing them like that.
S-Stop it already.
My breasts... I really don't want Nee-chan to see me get horny.
Me too...
Please, do it to me too.
Not by a vibrator...
I want to be directly teased by him.
As for you Ayaka, maybe the vibrator
setting isn't high enough for you?
T-This is unfair.
Master, you already know what I want and yet...
He's deliberately playing with me.
Onee-chan, you took really horny.
Does it really make you aroused?
I also want to be pleasured more.
M-Master!
I don't think I can hold myself back any longer
if you two keep looking at me like that.
Oh look, it's quite wet.
I feel like inserting it now.
I-It's rubbing hard inside me.
But, it still feels good right?
That's... That's...
Ayaka, make my ass feel good too.
His ass?
No way, Onee-chan...
She's really licking Master's ass.
What should I do?
I'm doing something this embarrassing and yet,
I'm starting to feel excited.
I'm slowly getting aroused.
I'm really a pervert now.
Oh no, his thing is getting even bigger as it rubs inside me.
Onee-chan, I can't hold myself back anymore.
Ayaka, I'm sorry.
I can't stop myself.
I want to feel pleasure with Master.
It's getting really tight now, Ayaka.
Oh no, oh no...
If he continues to fuck my ass like this...
Say it properly when you're about to cum okay Ayaka?
I'm going to cum Master.
I'm cumming!
You did well Ayaka.
Next, we tease Nee-chan together.
O-Onee-chan?
Okay, I understand.
I'm sorry, I really wanted Master in me already.
Onee-chan, make yourself feel really good.
For me to be aroused like this...
It feels really great.
I just can't stop!
It's gripping me tight!
Master, please punish us more.
I'm starting to go crazy.
I'm going to punish both Ayakas.
Oh no, If that thing keeps on pushing inside...
I'm going to lose it, and cum.
It's alright, please make me go crazy some more.
Master, your thing feels hot and it's pulsating.
It's coming.
It's coming out.
I'm sorry, I think I overdid it today.
Are you still mad at me?
I-I'm not really that mad but,
when I think that someone else... when Ayaka saw me like that...
This will be the last time for this.
I'm really sorry.
N-No, this doesn't have to end, right?
I-If it's just occasionally, I think doing it
with the three of us is just okay, I think.