www.SubDESU-H.net
So?
The sensation of my butt...
It feels really great, right?
You really are a pervert.
Having my ass shoved in your face,
and getting turned on to such an extent...
You masochist.
H-Hey!
Don't move! No...
Don't... Don't sniff so aggressively!
D-Don't get carried away.
You're nothing but a chair right now.
My, my...
Well, wasn't that a little too fast?
You couldn't hold it in just a little longer?
Getting excited, shoving your face in my butt...
To have a boyfriend who cums too quickly,
I am so unfortunate.
To have a girlfriend who mounts my face without warning...
Wouldn't you say I'm the unfortunate one?
What was that?
You want to break up?
I'll kill you.
Too bad for you.
I love watching that reluctant face of yours.
So no matter how much you cry, I refuse to let you break up with me.
Putting aside this "reluctant face" banter, the other comments make you nothing but a stalker.
Don't put me in the same category as some common stalker.
Regardless of how much you hate it, from here on, I will always be around you.
It's okay.
Even though you consider this nothing short of misfortune,
I only feel happiness.
Although, the fact that you made a girl from Marchen your girlfriend...
It would be a better reason for being unfortunate.
Regardless of which, I am still unlucky.
It got hard again!
So sudden, geez.
I guess I have no choice.
No, don't make those sounds.
Your filthy, semen stained cock...
I will do more perverted things to it.
Yes!
Use your tongue more!
Hey! Don't go crazy!
We sound very erotic, don't we?
My tits... Your cock...
Your dick is twitching.
TLC Note: She is using the word "Khappa" which TLs into Cucumber... the closest thing to a penis.
Your penis tastes so good.
Are you cumming?
No. Unless you beg,
I won't let you cum.
Hey, what's wrong?
You can't hold it in any longer, right?
It's okay now.
I want to enjoy watching you as you exhaust yourself releasing your cum.
It's coming!
So much, so sweet, this warm cum, so much...!
Amazing. There's still so much!
Even though it's only your second time, you still live up to your name as "Loaded Premature Ejaculator."
That's some crappy naming.
Besides Eru's lasciviousness—
What did you say?
Eh...
J-Just...
I was just pondering how lucky I am for having such a cute girlfriend.
You think those words are enough to satisfy me?
So I have to train your body some more?
You're a good boy.
Just like you,
my pussy has become quite perverted as well.
Want me to continue?
Yeah.
Do you want to be inside me?
I want to be inside you.
Right inside you, Eru.
It's coming in!
Your warm erect cock!
Inside my wet pussy!
H-Hey!
Can't help yourself, can you?
To fuck this violently...
You really are an ape.
This immoral and barbaric cock...
The only thing I can do is to take it into my pussy.
It's amazing. The feeling of your throbbing cock, reaching my stomach...
It's reaching deeply inside me.
Having my tits squeezed, uterus torn apart... It feels so great!
You're cumming?
I won't forgive you if we don't cum together!
Your desperate face is flustered.
It's okay. Let it out.
Release it!
Your cum... All inside me.
Release it all out!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Amazing! Toudou-kun's sperm is
going all up in my uterus!
Amazing.
Make me feel good again.
The one who is allowed to push me to those limits...
is only you.
Perfect Lady~Sadist Eru gracefully riding my face and giving me an erection.
W
I won't lose.
Definitely.
Looking good.
You really are perverted.
I'll show you how indecent of a girl you are.
Shut up!
Like I would...
This disgraceful you,
I am going to make him watch carefully.
No!
Don't look, Toudou-kun!
Please!
That's impossible.
He is incapable of looking away.
No!
Not there!
This part looks like it might feel good.
That place...
D-Doesn't feel...
I am you.
Your sensitive spots in particular.
I know of all of them.
N-No!
There's no way you could be me.
Oh, you won't acknowledge it?
Even though your pussy is this wet.
No, don't... Stop it!
See, you feel here too, right?
That-- You're wrong!
You still won't accept me...
Even though your pussy won't stop flowing.
What are you doing?
Stop- Stop it!
Until you accept who I am,
I will never stop.
Please, stop! Don't watch!
Wrong, not like that.
P-Please, I beg you.
Do not look.
No, no!
It feels so good!
You need to be more honest...
For I am you.
Your pussy is overflowing so much... How lewd.
My pussy, too.
It's good! Having my perverted pussy kissed...
I am also...
Eru! Snap out of it!
Don't screw around!
If it has come to that...
W-What are you doing?
Why would you suddenly... N-Nooo!!
Eru, are you ok?
To think I was...
By someone like that...
With only just that...
Damn it! Damn it!
You're a holder, right?
My partner, right?
Y-Yeah.
The only partner for you, Eru.
My connection with you...
needs to be strengthened it seems.
From here on, you are not to leave my side.
You are not to indulge with any girl other than me.
Got it?
Yeah... Huh?
By the way...
It helped that you raised your voice.
But...
It seems that only after you were satisfied from watching us...
That's when you raised your voice.
Well?
You could have raised your voice earlier, right?
T-That was... Eru...
That part of you,
I have to remember carefully.
Toudou-kun... Do it properly.
H-Hey!
What are you staring at?
Ch-Chitose-san, why?
W-Well, I was wondering if we could train together.
Wai— Never mind that, hurry and get out!
Y-Yeah, you're right. I'm sorry.
What's this?
You already want to cancel our partnership?
Or...
Maybe you intend to show your affection for the Chief Advisor by doing whatever you want to her?
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
T-That's a misunderstanding.
H-Hey!
I was...
Don't come this way!
I-I can't hold it in!
Butt wash
Eh?
No... What is this!?
What?
You wanted to show me your shower play with Yoji?
N-No! You're wrong!
More of this... No, no!
T-There!
Are you trying to show off?
Or do you actually want to try that play with me?
That's just...
Now, it's there. Next is...
No! Don't...
If this continues, I'm going to...
No...
N-No, I can't...
I can't... I can't hold it in anymore!!
T-To such an extent...
Is that so?
You really are a useless boyfriend.
E-Eru!
And?
I'm sorry! Really!
I know that.
If you look up, I will kill you.
Taking a guy who possesses a barbaric, out of control,
constantly erect penis as my boyfriend, was my biggest mistake.
C-Can I raise my head now?
Yeah, it's fine.
H-Hey, wait!
If you take it off, you know what will happen, right?
Serves you right. I can sense your anticipation.
It's more like anxiety than anticipation.
Until I say it's okay,
you cannot move.
Wait... Eru...
Oh my, to have a boner in a situation like this.
You really are a perverted boyfriend.
I wonder if doing this is fine.
It's a great place to sit.
Your dick is getting harder and harder.
You are so perverted...
To have your cock get so stiff with just my feet.
Eru...
No.
The breathe you exhaled while saying my name just hit my pussy.
I am in a very perverted position right now.
But you can't see it, though.
Eru.
I can feel the tip of your nose quivering.
My perverted boyfriend getting excited over the smell.
Amazing!
Looks like it's big again.
Ridden on, stepped on and it still grows big. Pervert!
So slippery!
Give me more pleasure!
C'mon!
I'll give you a lot as well, so go ahead and cum!
Ejaculation champion, perverted boyfriend.
No, not this position.
It's disgraceful.
I said no!
We're going to be seen!
Your dick is coming in!
Its spreading my pussy so much!
Even though, we might be seen!
You are just simply Todou-kun, yet you're so forceful.
It's okay. They can't really see from this angle below.
Yes, fuck me harder!
Yes. I don't care if you ravage me like crazy, just desire only me!
I do!
Do you? There's no way I can refuse you.
So be more courageous from here on out.
You can have me whenever you want!
Feels so good! Deeper!
Hit my uterus more!
At a place like this, to have my tits squeezed,
my pussy pounded... This is so erotic!
Yes, reach deeper!
Into my pussy!
Mold your dick's shape into my pussy!
I-I'm...
I'm cumming. I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
A lot is spilling out.
It's still coming out.
Only because it's you, Eru.
No.
I can't forgive you with only this.
This is a nice position, wouldn't you say?
In such a sorry state...
Your butt hole being teased by your girlfriend...
Pervert-san.
Amazing. It's tightening around my finger.
Quite the tight hole, huh?
Oh my, you came already?
I guess we have no choice. I need to milk you some more.
Amazing!
It's getting harder again!
Such a lewd dick!
You want to put that disgraceful dick all inside my pussy, right?
If you can actually hold off that super active cock from firing off for a bit, then I'll let you stick it in!
How unsightly.
Amazing.
You are about to come again?
To let all this much out...
There won't be enough to release inside me.
You can still keep going, right?
I am about to get excited from this perverted boyfriend's cock!
It's reaching deep inside.
This hot stuff!
It's so erotic!
It's embarrassing but I can't get enough!
Your dick is stretching my pussy!
More!
Toudou-kun's dick!
Please, give it to me... Deeper!
Fuck me aggressively. Lose yourself into me.
No, such erotic sounds...
My pussy is all squirmy and overflowing.
Its touching the end of my uterus!
I'm going crazy because of this dick!
I'm... going to cum!
Please! Make me cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm...
For this much...
To still come out...
You're really perverted.
Queen has been defeated! Core Memory Destroyed!
It's finished!
Amazing!
Yay!
A few months later...
Liste—
I keep on telling you not to...
Hey!
We can't expose the baby to any pain!
No, don't...
Don't be so rough!
The baby will get startled!
Because this child was there... That's why I won.
Your dick might reach the baby!
You are such a nympho for even letting your breast milk out, Eru.
It's your fault for making me into someone like this.
Geez...
I love you.
www.SubDESU-H.net