Previously on Love 2 Quad...
Sorry!
No, it's my fault.
It's my first time, so I was surprised.
I looked up and saw a delicious-looking, rising
thick "thing". I was embarrassed but also amazed!
And it was yours, nii-san, so I thought it was
really nice, but I wouldn't say that out loud...
s-so...
What's wrong? Take a breath.
R-Right!
I mean relax. You're breathing too hard.
The instructions say I have to stimulate
your... penis with my hands.
So, your pe...
What was that? I'll need you to explain the terms.
Your penis, please.
Nii-san, you're so big!
L-Loosen your hand a little, please.
S-Sorry, I'm not very skilled at this.
You're just learning, that's all. Even
though it hurt, it still felt good.
It hurts, but it feels good?
Y-Yeah. Touch me however you want.
OK! I'll get better at this and make
you feel good, nii-san.
There's something on your face.
Nii-san, I'm so happy. Please pet me some more.
MARMALADE inside
Helping nii-san makes me happy
even if it's training.
Nii-san, I really.
I'm going crazy!
Sorry, you started getting out of control there.
Nii-san, your tongue... it's in
my ass, and it feels good!
If you keep moving your tongue like that.
I never thought you'd lick me there!
Your tongue's going inside my ass!
It feels so good! I'm going to lose it!
My tongue goes in so easilyю
That's because I was playing with my ass before.
Your finger's rubbing the walls of my ass!
It feels so good when you pull it out!
Nii-san, if you keep this up, I...
I'm going to cum, nii-san!
That's fine, cum.
Nii-san, I can't. Nii-san, that's unfair.
Nii-san, I want us to cum together!
Nii-san, no! I can't.
Nii-san, you made me cum with my ass.
Nii-san, are you putting your dick in my ass?
It's OK, right?
Please give it to me.
Please use my ass to make yourself feel good!
My ass is being spread!
Nii-san, you're so deep inside!
Are you OK?
Y-Yes! Nii-san, it's so tight!
It feels like you're lodged inside me!
Is it feeling good for you?
It feels so good.
I'm ready, nii-san.
My ass is spread so wide, and every time you go in.
Your dick touches the places I can't
reach with just my fingers!
Every time your dick moves in
and out, it stirs up my insides!
Honoka, the inside of your ass
is so smooth. It feels so good!
I'm glad you like it!
This feels so much better than doing it myself!
MARMALADE inside
Nii-san, your long dick is coming deeper inside me!
My ass feels weird! I never though
it would feel this good!
Nii-san, does it feel good?
It's not just me, right?
Honoka, your ass is amazing!
It's my first time doing this.
I'm his first!
Please keep making yourself feel good!
This... I... nii-san...
Nii-san, whenever you're ready.
Nii-san, that's so intense! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Nii-san, your dick keeps coming in and out!
Nii-san's, your dick is so big.
It's stirring up my insides!
Nii-san, wait!
No!
Don't look! Nii-san, don't look!
Nii-san I hate you!
I'm sorry. It honestly doesn't bother me though.
It bothers me!
Honoka, your ass felt just so good.
It felt good?
So good. It's my first time, after all.
It makes me happy to hear you liked it.
I've always loved you, nii-san,
so this makes me so happy.
If my ass makes you feel good, you'd feel even
better if we did it some more, like before.
I wanted you to tease my ass, so
I haven't touched it recently.
More importantly, why are you wearing
that outfit in a place like this?
It was on the training menu
so I might as well learn.
If my beloved nii-san likes it and
it's training at the same time.
Two birds with one stone!
What is she thinking!?
Nii-san.
Please take my virginity!
Nii-san's dick is touching my pussy!
Honoka, are you.
Um, it just said this in the message,
and I'm doing it like it said.
I'll take your virginity, Honoka.
Nii-san, please make me a woman!
Niii-san, you're inside me! I'm
giving you my first time!
Nii-san, please move inside me.
Please use me to feel good!
This pain... It feels good being done by nii-san.
He's fondling my breasts while
thrusting into my pussy.
Nii-san's dick feels so good!
Nii-san's dick is rubbing deep inside me!
The pain feels strange.
Even though we shouldn't be
doing it in a place like this.
I've received something amazing!
His penis filling me keeps making me feel so good!
Nii-san, I love you! Nii-san, I've always.
Nii-san, nii-san, nii-san, I've always...
Nii-san, even though it's my first time, I'm...
Nii-san, your dick is making me cum!
I'm cumming!
He's thrusting inside, and unlike
anal, this feels so good!
Semen's pouring out from nii-san's dick!
He came so much! I'm going to get pregnant!
I've shown you a lot of embarrassing
things, nii-san.
And I'm a pervert older brother who
came on his younger sister.
I love you just the way you are, nii-san.
Let's get along like before, and even better!
Doing it in a place like this with nii-san.
Th-This is training too, right?
Y-Yes, that's what it is. It said so in the message.
Nii-san, your large dick.
Nii-san, you're so bold!
You're grabbing my breasts!
I know you want it, Honoka.
What are you saying? It's the message's fault.
This has nothing to do with the
porn mags you tried to hide.
I took notes on the types of play you seem to like.
Honoka?
It's twitching like you could cum at any minute!
My hand's not in the way like this, right?
Please give it to me in my ass, right now.
Nii-san, if you don't put it in, I will!
If it's for my frisky younger sister.
Nii-san's dick fits so tightly in my ass!
To think we're doing anal on a train!
I'm such a pervert!
It's just training, right?
That's right. It's because I want to.
You said it was training, didn't you?
Nii-san, your dick feels so good!
It feels so good! You're stirring up the inside of my
ass. You're thrusting so deep and so forcefully!
His erect dick is giving me so much pleasure,
I'm starting to really want it.
You're about to cum, aren't you, nii-san?
Y-Yeah.
I can feel so much of you that it's obvious
when you're about to cum.
I can feel the wide tip.
I'm feeling your strong thrusts
deep inside me, nii-san.
It's so good! He's doing me so roughly!
His dick is driving me crazy!
Nii-san, I'm cumming!
Nii-san, nii-san.
Nii-san, you're cumming so much!
Nii-san, I love you!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч