Well then, lick my pussy.
Make sure I feel good, okay.
Stick your tongue inside.
You're pretty good.
Keep it up.
Not just the pussy, lick my butt hole too.
That's right. Suck and lick it.
Stir your tongue around.
Good job. Don't forget the clit either.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Feast on Masochist Men
Ah, it's almost time for the last order.
Huh? Are they closing already?
It's not even ten. They close too early.
Too bad. Let's find somewhere else.
Well, I'll go pay the bill.
This is your bill.
Huh!?
This is a complete rip-off!
It's because you come to places
like this with women only.
Fools.
If you don't have enough cash,
leave your bags here as well.
Or I could show you a place where
you could make money real quick!
You bastards... Stop joking around!
If you don't want to get hurt,
just hand over the money.
Get hurt... you say?
You're sure looking down upon us...
Huh?
You don't want to anger us too much!
I'll kill all of you!
Oh man, now you've done it.
You bastard!
Don't underestimate us!
How many thugs like you do you think
we've taken care of before!?
W-Wait!
Who are you guys?
The leader and deputy leader of a quite
famous violent gal's circle in Tokyo.
Well, at least before.
On closer look your face is pretty nice.
Seems like a waste to just beat it up.
I didn't come across any good men on this trip.
I was thinking of having some
fun at least on the last day.
Why, you have a good one there.
Hey! What are you doing!
Hey! Stop!
I'll let you come inside me so get hard!
What wrong? Hurry up!
Here comes Rina's specialty: reverse-rape.
Please stop! He's my boyfriend!
Please! Stop it!
So you're dating each other.
Erika...
Of course you wouldn't want to
see him do it with another girl.
Well then.
Do it with that guy over there.
Good idea! That sounds like fun!
It's hard to forgive others cheating on you,
but it's fine for you to do it yourself.
It's true for everyone.
Well, since that's decided. Take off your pants already.
The guy looks completely ready!
T-Tamura! Why are you hard!
Shut up!
I can crush this guy's Adam's apple
with no doubt if I wanted to!
Don't underestimate me!
Be a good girl. Take off your panties and show your butt!
Your boyfriend is going to get hurt.
Hey, Tamura, right?
She sticking her ass out saying 'please put it in'!
Hurry up and make her feel good!
Erika-san...
Kenji-san I'm sorry!
No... Stop!
No! You can't!
Huh? You got hard watching your girlfriend being fucked?
You're a huge pervert!
Well, it's not that I don't like such perverts.
They have their uses.
Let's enjoy ourselves as well!
No! Stop! Stop!
Stay away from Kenji!
Please!
Wow! It's gone deep inside. It's huge.
No! I don't want this!
Kenji! Kenji!
Hey, aren't I the only one doing nothing?
Well you there, lick my pussy.
Make sure I feel good, okay.
Stick your tongue inside.
You're pretty good.
Keep it up.
Stop! Get away from Kenji already!
Please!
Not just the pussy, lick my butt hole too.
That's right. Suck and lick it.
Stir your tongue around.
Good job. Don't forget the clit either.
There! There! Feels good doesn't it.
Just like that.
There!
Wow. I can see it going inside Rina clearly.
In and out, in and out! Your dick is twitching!
There! There!
Hey, Tamura-kun stop!
Kenji is... Kenji is!
Please stop!
No... no...
Hey woman! Watch this!
He's shaking his hips on his own!
So apparently my pussy feels better than yours!
Kenji...
There! There!
You feel good don't you! Don't you dare come yet!
I'm gonna have much more fun with you!
There! There!
It's getting harder!
That's right, more!
That's right! Keep it up!
Good work. Now lick it more eagerly.
Stir your tongue around inside.
Use the tip to poke my insides.
Don't forget the clit!
More, rougher!
There! There!
Can you feel my insides twitching!
It's because your penis feels good!
Match up with my movements and thrust more!
That's it! That right!
Please stop already!
Well done. Suck and lick it repeatedly.
That's right. Stick your tongue deep inside and suck!
Up and down, roughly!
Good job. Keep up.
Check it out! Feels good doesn't it!
Your hips won't stop!
Does my pussy feel that good?
It's twitching!
Don't you dare come yet!
Come on, come on...
Come on!
This jerk came inside.
No, no way.
Kenji...
Hey woman.
Hurry up and suck out the semen.
Huh?
If you don't hurry I'll get pregnant with his child.
It's your boyfriend's semen.
Don't leave out a drop and drink all of it.
Hey Tamura!
You've been doing it all this time!
You like this girl don't you.
He came inside me,
so you can cum inside her as well.
No! Don't! Please stop, Tamura-kun!
Please, stop it!
No... No...
No!
Don't tell me... No! Please!
No, no, no!
No!!
Inside... It's flowing inside...
Semen is flowing inside...
No... I'll get a baby...
Even though I said no...
No... No...
Why are you hard again from
watching her getting creampied?
You're really a huge pervert aren't you?
I'll let you put it inside me this time.
Make me feel real good, okay?
Wow, you're larger than I thought.
I'm so full inside.
How is it?
Check it out.
There! There! My pussy feels good doesn't it?
Let's have lots of fun.
Well then, make me feel good with your tongue this time.
You should be happy since it has lots
of your girlfriend's saliva on it.
There! Lick it!
Be sure to use your tongue properly.
There might be your semen left inside so suck it all out.
Wow, Rina's asshole is twitching.
You're such a pervert plus masochist!
I've gotten a liking for you.
Your dick's huge, and your tongue
technique is pretty good as well.
Keep that up and make me cum!
You're moving your hips around nicely.
You've gotten into the mood haven't you?
It feels good. Thrust in deeper!
That's right! It's good!... Feels good!
Wow, this guy's great!
This is bad. It feels good!
Amazing! It feels good!
Feels good!
Amazing!
His penis is getting even harder.
Feels good!
This is bad. This is bad Rina.
This guy's gonna make me cum!
Amazing! Cumming!
Cumming!
I wonder how those guys are doing.
Probably too broken for anything to happen.
Probably.
Guess we destroyed another store, didn't we?
Hahaha!
Let's go!
Okay.
Wanna find another place to drink?
Great idea! All-nighter?
Of course!
Let's look at the same skies,
onaji sora wo miyou
同じ空を見よう
And bask in the same light
onaji hikari abite
同じ光浴びて
The clouds that we've been chasing,
oikaketa kumo wa
追いかけた雲は
Still have that unchanged flow.
kawarazuni nagare
変わらずに流れ
And ringing in my head,
zujyou ni ukabeta
頭上に浮かべた
The same melody strong as ever.
merodi wa tsuyoku
メロディーは強く
Those days filled with trouble and worry,
nayami nuita hibi
悩みぬいた日々
We wet our pillows with tears.
makura wo nurashita
枕を濡らした
And all those sleepless nights,
isatoi yoru ni wa
いさとい夜には
We lost ourselves with the guitar.
mi wo yudareta gitaa
身をゆだれたギター
And all those seemingly endless days
wa ni natte hibiku shirabe
輪になって響く調べ
Is what brings such a lovely today. Yeah.
shinai naru kyou ga yeah
親愛なる今日が yeah
I'll go see you again in the spring.
haru ni mata ai ni ikou
春にまた会いに行こう
I'll go visit all of you.
kimitachi ni ai ni ikou
君達に会いに行こう
Those days of youth we rushed through.
kakenuketa seishunto
駆け抜けた青春と
Or should I say the times that belong to us.
kakiwaketa jidai wo iuka
書き分けた時代を言うか
I'll go visit again tomorrow.
ashitamata ai ni ikou
明日また会いに行こう
I'll overcome all obstacles to visit.
kabe wo koe ai ni ikou
壁を超え会いに行こう
To the place where the cherry blossoms fall.
sakura chiru ano bashou he
桜散るあの場所へ
Changing us bit by bit. Yeah.
bokura wo sotto kaeru youna yeah
僕らをそっと変える様な yeah
I'll go see you again in spring.
harunimata ai ni ikou
春にまた会いに行こう
Changing us bit by bit. Yeah.
bokura wo sotto kaeru youna yeah
僕らをそっと変える様な yeah