Haruko-san.
I can't.
Someone could hear me here.
Haruka-san is touching herself?
She is touching herself..
Such a shameful thing to do.
I shouldn't do this.
But, I can not stop myself.
What should I do?
It- It's is so wet down here!
So wet.
Haruka-san...Haruka-san.
N-No.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
No.
Like this.
In and out.
And...
Why?
You left me all alone.
Haruko-san.
Translated by OppaiSubs.net - Hosted on HentaiOppai.com
Her name is Ogiwara Haruko.
She is a manager in this condo.
(Good Morning!)
She got this position from her granddad
who insisted that good work leads to a good karma.
She is a very kind and beautiful person.
However
Her heart...
Her husband died 4 years ago.
Yes...
She is still young...
But already a widow.
Hey!
Shotaro-san
Ah, good morning!
Are you going to your university now?
Yeah
Today I have a part-time job after that
So I will return late
Ok. Got it.
Make sure to turn the light off when you go out of bath.
Oh no.
I wont get to the point like this..
Ah, Haruko-san..
Yes?
This movie.
I heard it's interesting..
So I bought tickets.
What?
If you'd like...
On a weekend...together
Well...
Let's go together!
Hee?!
Ehm..
Lucia-san told me this movie is good.
How about you two go?
No...I want to go with you.
I'm sorry!
Just forget what I said!
W-Wait..
Shotaro-san...
Manager...
Don't use my name for an excuse.
May Lucia-san...
You probably have heard everything?
You were so close to my room.
Of course I heard it.
Anyway
I heard that was about you, manager
What was about me?
That thing with Shotaro-kun
I think you like him, but..
You just decided to get rid of that boy.
To get rid of whom?
That's not what I meant to do.
So what are you going to do?
I was happy when he invited me, but.
If I go...
Hmm...
Damn..
What should I tell to Haruko-san now?
Shotaro-kun!
I'm coming in!
Do you mind taking a bath together?
Lucia-san!?
You can not enter until it's vacant!
Well-well, don't be fussy.
Don't you like gender-mixed bathing?
Eh, but...
So what?
Looking straight at my breasts...
Your little partner seemed to be motivated.
Wow!
Your hardness is amazing.
My heart is beating hardly now.
I'm getting wet.
I feel so good...
My hand feel that good?
Your dick is so aroused.
It's even burns my hand...
Lucia-san.
Boobs...Your boobs.
Don't resist anymore!
There...there...
Feel my boobs to the bottom.
It's so tasty!
It feels too good!
The juice is overwhelming.
Give me more...
It became so hard.
Lucia-san.
I can't hold it anymore...
Come on!
I want your cum!
I want your cum all over me!
It's coming..!
Ah, it's hot and smells good...
What a taste!
I will loose consciousness.
Excuse me!
I was so messy.
It's all right.
He is still so hungry.
This time.
Let me be satisfied.
Lucia-san..
You really want this?
You drove my girly things to this point.
So don't ashame me.
Your dick…is entering me.
Good! Excelent!
I missed it for so long.
More! More!
Lucia-san...I am...
It's ok.
You keep moving up, Shotaro-kun.
Enjoy my pussy! It's wide open!
This penis..
It's so big!
Makes me so horny inside.
Whoa! It's so tight...
There!
Fuck my tight pussy!
Awesome……
Lucia-san...
You really like it?
You really fuck me deep.
I'm so fucking wet.
Fuck me harder!
Boobs..
If you squeeze it like this--
I will moan out load.
If you rub my boobs like that--
That will be so good.
Don't!
.No...if you keep doing like that.
Cum!
I'm cumming too.
I want your sperm!
Just load your cum!
No!
I'm cumming too!
I cumming!
Wheew
You could cum inside me.
No, I'm not sure about that..
Hey
Huh?
You really like the manager, right?
Oh...I'm...
Hmm, really?
Lucia-san?
What are you doing?
Lucia-san!?
What did you just blow inside me?!
It's just a candy.
That's a lie!
The prep work will require some time, so...
'Till that time just sleep, ok?
Shotaro-kun.
Lucia-san…
Don't...Don't do that...
Miss Manager.
It seems Shotaro-kun is awake now.
No...Don't...
Shotaro-san.
Please..don't look...
Don't look at me.
Oh, nooo...
Haruko-san?
What? What is this?
My body feels so hot...
You two..
Just taking a sex drugs like this.
And?
Your sex organs became so sleepy.
That is so awkward.
Lucia-san...
Why you are doing...
Here, look.
The pussy of this lady manager.
is cumming for the 3rd time.
It is sooo wet...
No...Don't talk like this...
No...
Just...
I can't stop it...
I can't stop cumming...
Haruko-san.
Two of you talk too much.
You make too much fuss.
All you need is show each other bodies.
I'll go to bath now, and then go to sleep.
Lucia-san!
And you two have fun.
Ciao!
Have fun...?
Shotaro-san.
I beg you.
Please cool down my body.
It's getting really weird to stay like this.
But...
I've swallowed the drug as well.
and now...
If I do something like this..
I don't know if I can handle myself.
It doesn't matter..!
Shotaro-san, just use it how you want!
I got so horny in here.
I'm really ashamed.
So please..
Be quick...just do it...
Haruko-san.
Not like this...no...
Don't do that...Stop...
It's not clean.
Haruko-san is so shaky here..
She is full of sex lubricant.
No.
Don't look.
I want to pee, and can not stop it.
It goes through.
I can feel something hard at my back.
I can not hold for any longer.
Shotaro-san...I'm begging you.
Please allow me with your dick...
I just need it..
So strange to ask that.
Where do you want that?
Don't tease me.
There...
Here...I need it there...
Please Shotaro-san...
So strange...
Haruka-san...You you came already.
Yeah...I have.
When you entered...I...
That was so warm...and feels so good...
Shotaro-san...I'm ok, so..
Move...move a lot inside of me.
Please slide more deeper.
Haruka-san...!
Polish me inside.
Every time your dick is pounding me.
My dirty hole.
Just squirt a lot.
Feels so good!
If you go on talking like this...I...
Wow..
I can't stop!
With your dick inside.
Mixing with my body!
Stretching me.
Raping my inside.
I'm cumming..!
Dick...so hot...amazing!
I'm about to cum..!
You loaded a lot. And it's so hot..
I ... Did it again..
I am sorry!
I came inside you
It's ok... Don't mind it.
It probably doesn't matter today.
Wow...I could feel you grow again inside..!
.Your dick...it is so big again
I am sorry.
That's strange.
It's because of that drug.
turning me on...
The same with me.
There.
My pussy is just trickle. Can not stop.
Haruka-san?
Give, give me more.
I want your dick Shotaro-san...
Your sperm...
I want my nasty pussy to.
come over and over again.
I'm begging you.
Pussy pussy...
Inside...
My whole is open for your dick, Shotaro
It is so wet and messy...
Haruko-san.
Amazing.
You are so nasty.
I am sorry.
To talk dirty to you.
My pussy is so horny now.
I cum again.
My nipples...
Oh no...
My boobs are so hot now.
Your dick is thrusting me inside.
It feels so good.
Haruko-san.
Her pussy is squeezing.
Is about to explode again.
Please.
Your big dick, Shotaro-san.
My nasty pussy.
Go faster!
Yeah, like this..
That's so good.
My pussy became so wild.
Give me a big load of cum.
Make me satisfied.
I feel so awesome too.
Haruko-san.
Look at me.
Remember me like this.
I want your sperm all over my pussy.
Haruko-san.
I can't hold any longer.
Shotaro-san...Cum...
In my pussy.
Is your body okay now?
Eh, yes. What about you?
Me too. Cooled down finally.
I'm sorry for the mess.
How to say..
I'm so ashamed you know me now like this.
No...that was my fault.
I said a lot of dirty words.
I was like an animal.
Doing over and over again.
I feel so ashamed.
Not at all...
We could look at each other's...eh..
You are right...
We have shared the most ashamed part of each other.
Although I kept thinking of him for a long time.
Although I met so many new people..
Stop thinking about your dearest that passed away..
That is really hard.
Maybe it's time to try to move on.
This time I definitely..
Definitely..
Shotaro-san.
I'm going out..
Yes. Take care.
Shotaro-san.
Mind your study, ok?
Wait a sec!
It's not yet the end.
Just a little more..
To lick the sweet..
There is nothing wrong about it.
What's with you two?!
Again it's because of Lucia-san..
So, how do you like us as a students?
There are no students like this.
This uniform.
It's worse then beeing naked.
Haruko-san.
Lucia-san, well done!
This is a special scene.
This a full service center.
Even if you say it's getting so hard.
Wait..
Good for you, Shotaro-san.
Hey manager,
if you are not in the mood..
I can pleasure
Shotaro-kun myself.
Ok. I'll do it!
'Cause I cannot loose to you!
I can provide service..!
Alright!
Our manager seems to be o nthe good mood now.
Ok, Shotaro-kun. Get ready for action!
Two? Both of you at the same time?
No need to hurry.
How do you feel, Shotaro-san?
Feel good?
Hey, you see the double
creaming for the 1st time?
It's really feels amazing.
No, don't do that.
We gonna shake your dick.
It's getting hot.
That's ok.
You can load a lot.
We will catch every drop.
I'm so sorry.
What a stream!
You were keeping a lot.
It's hot and smells good.
Oh, I'm getting wet.
I can not hold it. Look!
I'm so horny now.
I want your dick.
Haruko-san, wait.
Shotaro-san, just treat my
pussy
till satisfaction.
So here..
Taste my pussy.
Lucia-san..
His tongue..!
He is licking me up.
His dick is getting bigger.
He is turned on.
He is eating your pussy, Lucia-san.
Making you feel good.
Hey...what...
No...…
My anus.
Just keep pleasuring me harder!
I-I..
Can't stop.
I keep on moving!
It feels soo good!
I'm cumming.. I'm cumming..!
Cumming!!
Me too...Cumming!
My pussy and asshole..
Crushing..
Please.
Together.
Let's cum together.
So.. how did you like it?
Our special service.
Did it feel good?
If you are in a bad mood..
Then we can help you with that.
Just come and play with us.