This... Is this the maseki?
How could this...
What... is this?
Saturme magnesia... Overdrive!
Attack!
Who are you?
Where did that power come from?
I'm impressed, Isuka-chan.
Looks like he couldn't defeat you.
Nee-sama!
Today, on this blessed day,
the curtain will open on a new witch hunt.
Shit!
Absorption
You're just a witch.
Don't be so damn cocky!
How hideous.
Looks like you ended up losing.
Y-You bitch...
Who told you I've lost?
Your turn ends now.
From this point on... That person will take care of everything.
Rotten spider, you just go back to bed and snooze.
That suits you best.
After all, you're too...
Don't fuck with me.
I ain't gonna let a stupid witch beat me.
Let go...
You rotten spider!
What are you gonna do?
I haven't lost yet.
Sorry, but I'm gonna steal your magic.
D-Don't tell me... You're going to...
We're both Mazoku.
You want it, don't you?
No! Stop it!
No!
Mahou Shoujo Isuka
volume 03   Fall Into Corruption
Defeat
That appearance...
Well?
Are you happy to see your beloved Nee-sama again?
Or perhaps... Are you disappointed?
"How do you know?" Is what you want to ask, right?
Of course I know. It's to be expected.
Memories of your beloved Nee-sama have been implanted...
...deep into the back of my brain, thank you very much.
Advance first, fall back second!
Isuka-chan!
You really are weak. Lazy. Dull.
I wouldn't expect anything more from a witch.
Aside from their powers of the flesh, a witch is no match for her hunter.
Shut... up...
That voice. That face. Don't talk to me looking like that!
My Nee-sama... Return my Nee-sama at once!
Nee-sama, eh?
Since we have this opportunity, I'll go ahead and show
you what happened to your beloved Nee-sama.
Rebirth
No... No!
Stop it.
I don't want to... anymore!
Oh, please.
You rotten spider!
How dare you take over my body!
Do you understand?
One by one, your senses will give in,
until your whole body is under my control.
Stop...
Get out... Get out of me!
How is it?
The power inside your womb is melding with my seed well, is it not?
Just like this...
No!
Stop it!
Let me go!
This isn't... This isn't...
I'm cum... I'm cumming... cumming...
Now, now... It's not over yet.
I'm cumming... I'm cumming, cumming, I said.
It's coming again!
It keeps coming.
I'm gonna die!
Not again...
Yes, again.
What... is this?
What's going on!?
Is something inside of me?
Something's growing in my womb...
Could this be...
It can't be!
I'm raising it?
Raising his seed inside with my magic?
Yes. How smart of you to realize this.
No!
My body is... it's so...
I don't want... I don't want to give birth to this thing!
I... I don't want this!
Spawning
Isuka-chan?
Isuka-chan.
Wh-Where am I?
Let go!
Don't struggle.
T-Tia Nee-sama?
I will show you what was done to me now.
Look.
No... Get away!
It's going to go inside you here now, Isuka-chan.
No... Don't... Not down there...
No!
Don't!
Not again... So slippery...
A monster... Coming into me...
So big!
My insides... will rip!
Come on, this one too.
Something came in!
Through my mouth and down my throat.
Not just through that "mouth"...
It's coming in!
All the way deep inside!
No!
That's...
The top and the bottom...
Take it out! Take it out!
No you don't.
It's barely beginning.
You have yet to experience what I have.
My mouth, and of course my pussy, were both fucked.
And also...
My body was perfected into a vessel for birthing eggs.
Isuka-chan, you will also birth eggs, be fucked by
your own offspring, then get pregnant again.
No!
I don't want to birth it!
I don't want to birth monster babies!
I don't want to!
No! No! No! No!
Isuka-chan.
Time to fall into despair.
You stupid witch.
Please...
My belly is getting big...
There.
Now you have a body that can birth the eggs.
Aren't you lucky to turn out the same way your beloved Nee-sama did?
I-I'm not...
I-I can't...
I'm not...
No!
It's moving!
It's moving...
Does it turn you on?
No! It doesn't!
This can't turn...
And besides, if it's moving so much... I can't stop...
It's coming out!
Something slippery is coming out! I'm birthing it...
An egg...
Come now, hurry.
Birth that egg.
Birth that egg at once, Isuka-chan.
It's coming out!
I'm birthing it!
Birthing an egg!
I'm cumming while I'm birthing!
I'm giving birth!
No!
I can't...
Spider
Pathetic.
Isuka-chan!
The warm-up act is over now.
How about we go to the main performance?
In that case...
Let me in on that.
Kusokumo...
What about Lux?
Oh, that.
I just fed her some of your manipulative magic.
Say.
What about this toy?
Will you let me borrow her?
Though stealing her by force is also fun.
Very well.
But if you break her completely, I want to recycle her like the other girls.
So make sure you give her back.
As for me...
I'd like to break this one.
No, stay away!
Isuka-chan!
Well then.
Oh no, oh no.
You need to stay as you are.
What... What are you doing?
Do you like it?
Acclimating to extreme pain helps the body
experience pleasure more thoroughly.
So just doing this much...
How is it?
Females are usually accustomed to being chosen by force in the wild.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Stop...
It'll break... My spine is going to break!
It's going to break!
It's so harsh. Stop it!
Now, now, if you scream so much just from that, how are you
going to top that when my little buddies enter your body?
No, not now... The feeling is too intense.
Don't!
No!
Stay back!
Stay away!
No!
Don't come in!
It's coming inside.
Even though I said no...
No...
I'm cumming.
Just from it going inside...
I'm cumming, cumming!
It's so tight in my pussy!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming,
Cumming so hard!
Shit.
If I wanted to borrow someone, I should've
borrowed a girl instead of a doll.
Birth
No...
It's getting bigger...
It's moving inside.
So big, fucking me inside...
The monster babies... So many will be born...
Don't move...
If you move... I'll...
No.
I don't want to birth any.
I don't want to be pregnant or birth monster babies!
No!
Stop it!
Don't come out.
Stop moving.
I can't stand this anymore!
I don't want to be a mother to monsters.
I don't want to birth the babies!
I don't want to!
No...
It's coming out...
I don't want to birth them!
They're coming.
Coming again.
I'm giving birth.
There's no end to them!
Oh no.
There's still more left.
Deep inside my womb.
There are still so many tentacle babies.
What?
More are coming?
No...
That's not it.
This is... isn't a baby?
It's not a monster baby?
What is this?
It's strange for a human to birth monsters, isn't it?
That's why your body is being perfected
into something more appropriate.
What?
What are you saying?
Something's coming?
No.
I'm raising it.
Raising something in my pussy.
It's getting bigger.
Is this... It can't be.
Impossible.
Why is this thing in my pussy?
It can't be true.
I'm a girl.
A girl would never have this...
It's attached.
No. It's inside.
There's a penis in my pussy.
This doesn't seem possible.
Huh? Oh no.
I can't stop.
I can't stop touching it.
Even though it's wrong!
Even though it's wrong for a girl to be stroking her own dick like this!
I can't stop!
It feels so good I can't stop!
It's so tingly.
Even though I'm a girl.
I can't stop this!
I'm cumming.
If I keep this up, I'll ejaculate.
Even though I'm a girl... I'll ejaculate sperm.
I'm gonna shoot out sperm!
It's all squishy and wet with girl juice and
man sperm... It's all gonna come out!
I can't stop it.
I can't stop the wetness or the throbbing semen flow!
I'm becoming a man and a woman while I'm masturbating.
More is coming.
So much is coming!
Fall From Grace
Isuka-chan.
You finally woke up.
You're a lazy one, aren't you?
You are...
How did you...
None of that matters.
My body is too sensitive.
It's turning me on...
I can't stop it.
I feel it so strongly I'm numb!
Isuka-chan... I had no idea your body was so nasty.
Well, me too...
See?
Isn't it amazing?
I have such a big dick.
It can ejaculate so many times.
While you were sleeping, I stroked it and made it cum over and over.
So this time... I can do it with you, right?
In your pussy.
My dick...
I want my semen... to make you pregnant.
No. Don't. Please, stop.
If you put it in now... Into my overly-sensitive pussy...
I'll lose my mind!
That's okay.
As long as we're here, you can go as crazy
as you want. That's what he said.
He said as long as you're here, you won't have to suffer anymore.
That's why...
This feels great!
Isuka-chan, your pussy... It's so soft and tight.
It feels so good!
At this rate, I'll cum right away!
Stop it!
It's too rough!
I'm going to cum!
If you do it so roughly... I'll cum!
I'm cumming.
Filling you full of semen.
I'll make you pregnant with my semen.
And this time... I'll have you give birth to my monster baby.
It's coming!
Coming so hard!
Coming all the way inside!
We'll be together forever.
Let's feel good together, right here, forever.
Let's stay friends forever...
I'll make you feel good.
Lustful Transformation
Isuka-chan.
Isuka-chan...
Tsumiki... Tsumiki... Tsumiki...
My belly is filled with your children, Isuka-chan.
I'm pregnant with so many baby monsters.
Me too.
I'm also filled with your babies, Tsumiki.
I want to birth more of them.
With you, Tsumiki... Lots more... I want to birth lots more.
Yes. Let's birth them.
Birth them together...
Together while we birth them.
It's here! Here again!
So many babies.
They're all born just for me!
Mine ore here too!
My babies are here!
So many are coming out!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming...
I'm cumming again.
Cumming while giving birth.
So much is coming.
So much is coming out.
I'm cumming while the babies are coming.
The babies are making me cum so much.
Isuka-chan.