Stop coming out... Stop coming out...
I don't want to be a mother to monsters!
It's coming!
It's still pumping inside me... Even more than before!
Even though its my first time, I'm going to cum!
It's cumming inside me!
Nee-sama...
Genji and Lux
Hey, are you okay?
You weren't able to do it alone, were you?
Shut up.
To think that kind of power exists... Even though she's a witch!
In human words, it's "security is the greatest enemy."
Will the mouse bite the cat?
No... Maybe it's because you're too weak.
Wh-What did you say?
This scent...
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Then, for the great Demon King, let us begin the witch hunt.
I will make use of you.
Mahou Shoujo Isuka
volume 02   Demonic Prison
Tsumiki's House
Are you okay now that you're awake?
I thought that leaving you alone would be
dangerous, so I brought you to my house.
Um...
As I thought, this sensation.
It's the power of Nee-san's maseki.
Nee-san's magic powers surely came from this girl's body back then.
But why are her powers coming from an ordinary human?
Um... I'm not really into girls...
Of course not!
I would never be interested in human girls!
So you feel the same way. That's a relief.
Are you hungry?
Wanna eat with me?
Um...
I have something to discuss.
Just as I said before, I am not... not like the humans of this world.
I am a witch, Isuka.
A witch?
That's right. We witches have come here to protect the magical shards,
which were the source of the Demon King's power before
they were shattered in the Other World from demons.
We are born into magic by the maseki stones.
That is what a witch is.
Witches... and "Mazoku"...
Is that other one like you the same thing?
Yes.
And you... the maseki that is inside of your body...
...is actually very precious to me.
At School
The maseki that is inside your body is actually very precious to me.
And I will do whatever it takes to protect it.
I still don't really understand...
But...
Note: Eat me! (Алиса?)
Rice balls...
Delicious!
Tsumiki?
What's wrong?
Um... Listen, listen.
Hyodo-sensei has... something to discuss... with you.
Hyodo-sensei does?
Um, Ayase-chan?
Come, lets go! Let's go!
When Sensei calls on you, you must obey, okay?
Okay?
Okay, just don't tug so hard.
Take that!
Isuka-chan...?
Sorry, you two, I'll catch up later.
So go see Sensei without me for now.
Isuka-chan.
Do you want to play with the others?
D-Don't be silly!
I am a witch.
A witch like me would never desire to play with humans!
If you want, I'll play with you after school.
But I said...
Ah, yes, I almost forgot this.
Th-That's my... Give it back!
Is it important to you?
This was Nee-sama's...
That's the mark of a maseki owner, and it was lodged inside your body.
Does that mean...
Yep. I've decided.
This afternoon, Isuka-chan, we're going on a full-course loitering spree!
"Isuka-chan"?
Well, yeah. We're friends, aren't we?
Well... I have to go see Sensei, so I'll talk to you later!
Yes, but...
Friends...
Excuse me.
Yayoi-chan?
Yes! Sensei, your cock is great!
It's throbbing through my dirty pussy!
Can't stop it!
Ayase-chan?
Tsumiki... You too... You do it.
Become Sensei's possession. Become...
No! Let me go!
I-It's coming!
Semen seeping in from the fat cock!
Semen that will impregnate me.
A lot of semen is coming in!
Yes... A lot of semen... Pregnant...
Yo. So you came, Kashiwagi.
Sensei, what are you...
Nothing much.
Never mind, and answer my question.
Why were you there with the witch yesterday?
You appear to be human.
So why are you with a witch?
S-Sensei?
Oh?
Isuka-chan!
You need to leave this place now!
Hurry!
So you came faster than I thought.
Isn't that right, witch?
A witch hunter, eh?
Mazoku Genji
This place is weird!
No matter where I go, the hallway never ends.
And also...
Why, you...!
Don't interfere!
So hot!
I'm impressed, witch.
So you show no mercy even against former humans?
Of course.
I protect maseki.
And I will do this by any means necessary.
Really?
Then why Kashiwagi?
She's just a human.
I have no need to answer to you, Mazoku scum!
You haven't learned.
Now I can clearly see the thread you used earlier.
You are weak.
I will ask once more before I break you.
What is a witch like you doing around a human?
I would never... tell demon scum like you!
Well.
So you look even weaker when your flesh is exposed.
That hurts!
Good grief! Tty having a sexier body.
The witches I have destroyed before had much nicer bodies.
Don't tell me you killed my sister?
Who knows?
I don't have time to keep track of every witch I've killed.
And besides...
In the end, everyone screams out, drools, and cums.
That never changes.
S-Something's... coming... inside...
Unhand me!
This is your final moment.
Enjoy being broken apart.
It hurts...
What... is this...?
Th-There's more?
S-Stop it!
Not there...
Have plenty of fun.
It's coming inside... inside of me...
Something's coming...
Stop...
S-So deep... swirling around... it hurts!
It's coming... all the way inside...
Moving... deep... inside...
W-Wait... not that hideous thing...
Stop...
It's coming inside...
Both front and back, scraping together inside.
No...
It's twirling around inside...
Stop... Not so roughly...
Something is rising inside...
No...
It's throbbing inside of me... Something is rising...
Demonic Embarrassment
She was so short-lived.
Then, next up, Kashiwagi.
Isuka-chan!
Are you okay?
Are you...
Can you stand?
We're running for it.
My body...
Attacking a teacher. That's against school rules, Kashiwagi.
I was thinking of fucking you leisurely after destroying
that witch, but it appears there's a change of plans.
No...
My body is moving on its own...
You need to be taught to respect your elders, Kashiwagi.
No... No...
Stop...
I don't want to... So dirty...
Kashiwagi, taste it well.
No! Penis... I'm... sucking a penis...
Sensei's penis... I'm sucking on it!
So human females are best used in this
manner before being turned into dolls.
Come, taste it deeper.
It's... so big... I can't...
Very nice, Kashiwagi.
I'm cumming now. So drink it all!
Ugh... It's stinky.
A man's juices are so stinky, but...
I'm... licking a man's semen...
That stinky semen... I'm drinking it.
Tia
I like you, Kashiwagi.
I will make you my doll with your consciousness still in tact.
Doll?
Yes.
Your body will remain intact, but you will only be
able to do my bidding. You will be my puppet.
To start with... Yes, break that witch for me.
Run away...
Isuka-chan! Run away!
You don't understand.
Your will has no power anymore.
Be a good girl and become my doll.
No... I don't want to!
Could this be...?
This... Is this the maseki?
How could this...
What... is this?
It couldn't be... Nee-sama? If this is...
It couldn't be... the maseki?
Kashiwagi... could you be...?
Saturme magnesia... Overdrive!
Attack!
Isuka-chan!
Who are you?
Where did that power come from?
I'm impressed, Isuka-chan.
Looks like he couldn't defeat you.
Nee-sama!
Then let us take you on next.
Today, on this blessed day,
the curtain will open on a new witch hunt.
Even now, the memory of that time
ano koro no kioku ga ima mo
Is a scar that can't be erased
kizuato ni natta mama kesenakute
Nails dig into my dirty wounds
tsumi de yogoreta kizuguchi ni
Creating new pain and erasing the old
tsume wo tate atarashii itami de gomakashiteru
I close my eyes and entrust myself to fate
unmei ni mi wo makase me wo tojiru
But it's no good, I'm still looking for "meaning"
na no ni dame watashi imi mada sagashiteru
With these hands, with these very hands, I lower the blade
kono te de ima kono te de tachikitte
And put an end to this chain of pain
kanashimi no rensa ni shuushifu wo utte
These tears, when these tears have dried
namida ga kono namida ga kawaitara
The light I once saw will return to the world
mou ichi do sekai ni itsuka mita ano hikari wo