Onii-chan, at this rate we'll never get the coin back!
I know that!
With this, the kingdom is mine!
Wh-What's that?
Ah! The sky has opened!
That brute!
He's run off to the human world!
Let's chase him, Ripple!
I'm on it, Onii-chan!
Magical Moe
Vol. 1
Hibari-chan, your lunch always
has a lot of goodies in it.
That's not true at all.
I'm so jealous!
By the way, Moe-chan, it's been a
week since you transferred here.
Are you used to life at this school yet?
Of course I am!
It's like I've been here for ten years!
That coin is really cute!
Lemme see it.
It's not the coin I'm looking for...
Moe.
Whose ass are you kissing this time?
Bunta-Oniichan.
Thanks for being so friendly with Moe.
N-No problem.
Moe-chan is really cute.
I'll let you have this, Moe-chan.
That's okay.
It looks better on you anyway.
Don't hold back.
I want to make you happy, Moe-chan.
But Moe doesn't want that coin.
What are you talking about?
Onii-chan!
Hey!
Here's your favorite soramame!
Soramame, eh?
Moe-chan's big brother...
What kind of coin does he like?
Bunta-san...
Oh, oh no.
Not there.
Y-Yes.
Th-That's the spot.
Yes.
Harder!
Harder, please!
You won't let go?
Then I suppose I'll have to take it by force.
Wh-What's going on?
No. No!
No!
No...
Help. Help...
D-Don't...
Not there.
Ouch! That hurts.
Did you find anything?
In order to return to the kingdom,
we need to find Godo and the coin.
The rod did react...
but it disappeared after we left the school.
If Godo gets his hands on a coin that powerful,
he'll be able to take over the entire kingdom.
And our magic powers don't
work very well in this world.
Hi.
Hibari-chan?
Yeah.
Eh, uh, yeah.
Yeah, speaking.
Eh?
Hibari-san has something to show me.
I'll be back soon.
Deeper.
Harder!
Harder! Deeper!
It's at school!
This feels great!
Right there. Right there.
Right there!
Wow!
This feels great.
Oh, oh no!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
The reaction disappeared around here.
Onii-chan, you were unusually excited that
Hibari-chan called you to come out.
Does Hibari-chan like my brother?
Godo!
Princess Ripple of Toridoramu.
I knew you'd come here.
Onii-chan!
How could... How could you!?
No need to despair.
He's merely unconscious.
Godo, I won't hand the coin over to you!
Well then, I wonder about that.
Just look over there.
How could you!?
You'll meet the same fate.
Onii-chan?
Stop it, please.
No.
Stop it, please!
You've wanted this all along, haven't you?
Only the first part is scary.
No, anything but that!
W-Wait!
Did you way, "wait"?
I'm sure you've wished for this all along.
You dreamed of being bonded to your brother,
who isn't related to you by blood.
Now, join with him.
Marvelous. What a marvelous view!
No!
Not like this!
Moe-chan, you know...
I've always wanted to do this with you.
Because, you see...
you were my first friend, Moe-chan.
What's going on?
Like you don't know.
Let's become one.
Let's all become one.
And let's all have fun as we do.
Taste it well.
Drink the sweet nectar that will alter your morals.
No! Stop... Stop it.
The drug has started to work, apparently.
Princess of Magic...
With the top layer of skin pulled
away, she's merely a normal girl.
Not there!
Oh, no...
No... No... No...
So you're turned on now.
What a hideous thing.
That's right.
Surrender your body to passion...
and become my slave.
No. Not there. Not there!
Oh, Princess.
Fall to Hell of your own free will.
You two should also have fun.
Yes...
It feels... so good.
Still not satisfied?
In that case,
you know what you have to do.
Good girl.
No...
Don't...
I'm... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
You will fall to Hell.
You will fall to Hell, dear Princess.
Now my task has become much easier.
I will not... allow it!
What do you think you can do in your condition?
Wh-What? The rod?
What's the meaning of this?
I won't let you escape!
Why is this happening?
My strength is disappearing.
Are you disarming me, the all-mighty me?
Godo, this spells your defeat!
Impudent bitch!
What's...
Shit!
The coin...
Don't leave me!
Go!
What power!
How could this be?
It's impossible. The Triamp Rod is...
Huh?
Why am I naked?
We don't know for sure if he's dead...
so don't lower your guard.
Yeah.
We need to find the remaining coins quickly!
See You Again