A world exists where magic is commonplace.
Here is the most prestigious school on the
continent, Wizadia Magic Academy.
Kef yukefu.
In order to tram the magicians of tomorrow,
outstanding practitioners of magic from participating
schools in various nations have gathered here.
The halls of the academy provide all of these students
a cooperative and nurturing way of life.
LECTURE. 1 The Magic Academy is a Harem?
Magical Witch Academy
My name is Tsukasa Strobilanthus.
I am the only male student at Wizadia Magic Academy.
There's a reason why I was given
special permission to enroll here.
Well then, is there anyone who'd like to
try reciting this magical incantation?
Tsukasa-san?
O-Okay!
Anatos Rakura. I call upon the departed
spirits to follow my commands.
Spirit of the Wind, hear my wish.
Aras Kuffiyah. Spirit of the Wind, free this ribbon,
and let it fly!
Huh?
My glasses!
Did I do it again?
Wh-What? My pussy is...
What's this? My body's getting so hot!
I did it again.
Tsukasa-san, this wouldn't happen to be...
I apologize.
I unleashed the power of my eyes again.
I knew it!
By some unknown mechanism, the Mystic Eyes cause
all the girls nearby to become extremely aroused.
Within my glance lurks the power of the Mystic Eyes.
If my glasses ever come off, I unleash a power
so great that I myself can't control it.
Shizuna, are you immune to the power of my Mystic Eyes?
Oh wow!
Huh?
What a magnificent...
Tsukasa-kun! I'm burning up!
Me too!
Huh?
I can't take it anymore! Forgive me, Tsukasa-san!
S-Sensei! We shouldn't! Please calm down!
Sensei, you're so greedy! Let me have some too!
I-I'm sorry! I can t resist any longer!
Stop it! Everyone please stop this!
Everyone, please! This is embarrassing!
Oh wow. It's gigantic.
W-Wait! Milfy! Stop it!
T-Tsukasa-san, don't move, please.
We'll make you feel good, so...
It's so warm, and it's pulsing and throbbing in my hand.
Milfy-san, keep doing that, and do it gently like before.
W-We really shouldn't!
Tsukasa-san, your voice sounds so lewd.
Does it feel good? Does my hand make
you feel good, Tsukasa-kun?
He's really feeling it, because his dick is really heating up.
S-Somebody! Help me!
I'm sorry, Tsukasa-kun. Rubbing
your dick is really turning me on.
I also want to see Tsukasa-san cum.
Oh, no!
Something moist and slippery is coming out.
My, my. It looks like it won't be long now.
Tsukasa-san's looks so strong and hard.
His dick is trembling.
S-Stop! No!
This is Tsukasa-san's...
It's so wonderful.
Even though you just came, it's still so hard, Tsukasa-san.
This is really bad! If you do it any more, I'll...
Rin. Keine. Elanes. Dasen.
Beneath the skies of the silver sands,
in the name of the Great Spirit,
let the powers of Fortunes and Demons
bring forth the world I desire!
Wh-What? Why am I undressed!?
Oh my, it looks like everyone's finally calmed down a bit.
Sylvia-sensei!
And the principal as well!
What a disaster for you, Tsukasa.
For crying out loud, you take up too much
of my time, you pretty-boy apprentice.
Performing a flashy bukkake in middle
of a classroom, of all places.
I keep telling you!
Be careful not to accidently take off or drop those glasses!
I couldn't help it.
I was trying to practice magic at the same time.
Speaking of that, did you like the handjob
your classmates gave you?
Did it eel good?
S-Sylvia-serisei!
What? Is something wrong?
Wh-Why are you naked?
Because I'm going to take a bath now.
Then please go already.
Oh? Is it possible that you're getting turned
on by your master's nude body?
Are you ready to get it on?
S-Stop it already, geez.
Good grief! As usual, you're utterly
pathetic, you stupid apprentice.
Do you even know why you, a person that
all girls adore, could enroll in this school?
So that I can find a way to control
my power, the Mystic Eyes.
And what do we need in order to do that?
Find a girl who can withstand my Mystic Eyes...
and obtain her assistance in taming this power.
That's right! So you do understand!
If you get all embarrassed and bashful just from looking
at a naked girl, you'll never get anywhere!
O-Okay.
A girl who can withstand my Mystic Eyes.
Actually, I think I've already found a girl like that.
Sorry for interrupting you during practice.
I need a favor from you, Shizuna.
From me?
Help you practice to control the Mystic Eyes?
Yeah.
It may be a selfish request,
but you're the only one I can turn to, Shizuna.
You'll probably say no.
All right, I'll help you.
Huh? Are you sure?
What? You're the one who wanted
help, and yet you're surprised?
Well, I mean...
I know how your daily life has suffered
because of the Mystic Eyes.
Besides, if the kind of commotion we had yesterday
in class keeps happening, it'll be a real bother.
Become reality, my shield
If we help each other investigate this power,
we can prevent incidents like yesterday's
from happening again.
Yeah. Okay, here it comes!
Shizuna!?
D-Don't worry about it!
Concentrate on controlling your Mystic Eyes!
All right.
S-Something like this... I-I'll show you!
I-It can get even stronger?
Hang in there, Shizuna!
Tsukasa!
Huh? Wait!
Cut it out, Shizuna.
I-I can't. I cant think clearly anymore.
That's...
Tsukasa, don't hold back, cum.
But you're...
Don't worry about me.
Don't, it's coming out!
Th-This is Tsukasa's semen.
S-Sorry.
It's all right. I'm okay.
Shizuna?
I don't want you to feel embarrassed, Tsukasa,
s-so I'll show you everything as well.
Shizuna...
Don't stare so intently at my naked body.
My body's not very feminine, is it?
All muscles and rugged angles.
N-No way...
Your body is beautiful.
Thank you, Tsukasa.
Shizuna!?
Sorry, Tsukasa. The burning in my body is still there.
Shizuna, s-stop it already.
If I remember correctly, I'm supposed to do this.
That spot...
This is where it makes you feel good, right?
Tsukasa, lick mine too.
But that's...
Please, do whatever you want with it.
Okay.
Your pussy is amazing. It's getting so wet.
Don't say things like that.
Right there!
Y-You've gotten big again.
Are you getting turned on from licking me down there?
Wait, that...
This feels good? Then I'll...
Shizuna, I can't...
D-Don't spread it so wide. It's embarrassing.
Shizuna, it's coming out.
Together... Let's cum at the same time!
It's coming out!
I'm really sorry, Shizuna.
This wasn't my intent.
No, don't worry about it.
My studying and practice weren't enough.
Don't say that.
I couldn't withstand the power of your Mystic Eyes.
Shizuna...
Forget everything that happened today, please!
Shizuna!
I didn't mean to do that at all.
Are my Mystic Eyes fated to bring girls to ruin?
I don't think that's true, but...
Huh? Who are you?
I'm Lyra.
In your language, I'm called a succubus.
A succubus... A female demon that
sucks the life juices from men?
That's right.
And I was summoned by your Mystic Eyes.
Girls would welcome that power of
yours anywhere. It's wonderful.
There's no need to pout and whine about it.
Th-That can't be...
The truth is that all the girls welcome it.
No way! I'm sick of having that kind of power!
You shouldn't say things like that.
I can't help myself any longer!
My body...
It's been a long time, so I'll make sure I enjoy this.
No, stop.
Oh? But it looks like down there isn't complaining.
Come on, I'll make you feel good.
D-Don't!
What a great dick!
It's big and hard, and it feels like it's
going to burst just from being licked!
This is so embarrassing!
Don't look so pained, Tsukasa.
I can't take this anymore!
Something naughty is coming out.
Does what I'm doing feel good? Let me be rougher.
You have a nice expression on your face.
This perverted dick... Give it to me.
No... That... I'm cumming!
You came a lot, huh? It was so tasty.
Y-You're satisfied, right? Please leave me alone.
What are you talking about? It's
your turn to pleasure me next!
Wh-What? You don't mean...
Look, I'm soaking wet down here just from sucking your dick.
Don't... do that... please... I'm still a...
Still a what?
I haven't done it yet. So please, anything but that!
This is great!
L-Lyra?
Well then, I have no choice but to be Tsukasa's first.
No!
Well? Doesn't it feel good to penetrate me?
You're too cruel! I...
Just shut up already. Let's enjoy this!
Even though you protest about it, you're already rock hard.
Don't say that. It's embarrassing!
Does it feel good? It's making all kinds of nasty noises.
Please, let me rest for a bit.
No way. Do you hear all those nasty, squishy noises?
Tsukasa's dick is so big. It's making
all kinds of perverted sounds.
What a slutty voice! I love it when boys moan like whores!
Lyra! I...
Is it starting to feel good?
I'm also feeling good. Deeper! Stir up my insides more, more!
Lyra, I'm really going to... Please, stop!
This hard dick is hitting me deep inside!
Don't! At this rate, I'll--
Tsukasa, are you feeling it?
My pussy is so gushy and slippery that it feels good, doesn't it?
No, that's not...
Please, let's cum together!
Make my body all sloppy with your semen!
I'm cumming, again!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Tsukasa, you cum too! Give me lots of semen!
I came... inside a girl.
You're so young.
Even though you just came so much, you aren't tired out.
It's not over yet?
I still have lots of cravings to satisfy.
Please, leave me alone! Don't do it.
Stop it!
Sylvia-sensei...
About Tsukasa's Mystic Eyes...
Yes?
The Mystic Eyes were originally an irresistible power for
manipulating those who came too close to the user.
Instead, it's become a power that brings
out the sexual cravings in women.
What do you make of it?
I think his physical body was lonely.
What?
From his childhood, Tsukasa has had to
avoid the gaze and company of others
to keep the Mystic Eyes under control.
That loneliness resided deep in his heart.
It caused the power to become what it is.
I see.
It would be good if a girl capable of
sealing that power appeared soon.
You can't save Tsukasa, Sylvia?
That's beyond my abilities, Principal.
You're still worried though, aren't you?
I don't expect I can forget it.
After all, it was originally our fault that the
Mystic Eyes took hold inside that child.
Sylvia-sensei, surely you at least can
do something about the Mystic Eyes.
However, it would be dangerous and risky to fully
reawaken the condition inside Tsukasa's heart.
That sealed-up power could run amok at any time.
Yes, I understand.
I want you to try investigating this more deeply.
What? Why are we looking into this again?
If Tsukasa's Mystic Eyes become uncontrollable and violent,
the lives of the students here could be in danger.
What would you do then, Sylvia Vesper?
Would you stand aside and be ruined?
Or join that boy in destroying this world?
Would you eliminate the source of the
Mystic Eyes by killing that boy?
We have to consider worst-case scenarios while we can.
If that happens...
If that happens, I will make my choice and
destroy Tsukasa and the Mystic Eyes.
But after killing my own student,
would I even have a reason to live?
Tsukasa...
Clouds are gathering near the moon.
I have a bad feeling. I hope nothing evil happens.
Wh-What?
What!?
I can't move!
No! Don't touch me!
Don't! Please let me go!
Don't touch me there!
What is this feeling? It seems like
I've been through this before.
Where am I?
Alcia. Finally, we meet.
Oh no! How!?
How? I came here because you called for me.
Ts-Tsukasa-san, you aren't wearing your glasses!
At this rate, I'll succumb to lustful thoughts again!
Well, that's exactly what you want, isn't it?
Tsukasa-san, this pose is too embarrassing!
Please turn away.
I'm sorry, but it's fascinating, because Alcia's is so pretty.
I beg you!
Please don't look at it!
I'm so ashamed!
You aren't allowed to lick it!
It feels too good. I can't stand up anymore.
Alcia, you're getting wet here.
Amazing. It's gushing steadily.
No! Don't say that!
Alcia, you can't hold back any longer either, right?
It's coming in! From behind!
I can see all of Alcia's most private place.
Tsukasa-san!
This is too embarrassing!
My pussy... and butt hole are in plain sight.
Please stop it already!
Huh? Do you really want me to stop?
Please, don't! You're rubbing me
raw down there. Not like this!
I'm feeling it.
Well then, I guess I should do it harder, right?
It feels so good! Tsukasa-san...
Please forgive me.
I'm really... such a slutty girl.
Oh no...
That's fine. I want you to become even sluttier.
Tsukasa-san, if you don't want me anymore
you don't have to keep going.
Everything you do makes me feel so good, Tsukasa-san!
Tsukasa... san...