My butt...
Don't!
You're spreading my ass wide open!
Magical Witch Academy
LECTURE. 2 A Tentacle-Induced Panic!
Sylvia! These surges are the Mystic Eyes, aren't they?
That's right.
The Mystic Eyes have...
Tsukasa's Mystic Eyes have...
been awakened!
With this spontaneous burst of energy...
The students might be in danger.
No!
I-It's coming!
What the hell!?
They're over there too!
What in the world is going on?
It couldn't be Tsukasa!?
Everyone really wants to do lustful
things with my body, right?
That's fine.
I'll make sure to do plenty of shameless things to all of you.
Wait, jeez! Stop it already!
Wh-What?
It's hot!
No! Stop!
Don't touch my breasts!
Milfy probably wants it rough and hard.
I'll be sure to provide her with a lot more pleasure.
Enough. Just stop!
Let me go!
No... Don't .. I can't think clearly anymore.
What am I... What is this!?
This is a guy's dick.
Wh-Why is this happening?
There you are.
No! Don't look!
Don't worry. I'll return you to normal.
Have I become a boy?
Nothing like that.
See?
Look how wet you are already.
The proper girl's parts are here.
But if I'm a girl, this dick...
I-I'm erect. It's so embarrassing.
At times like these, it's best just to cum.
I'll do it for you.
Your dick has gotten bigger again.
Does it feel good?
D-Don't say that! I'm so embarrassed!
Everyone's watching too.
Amazing. Milfy's dick...
It's become so big and hard.
It looks like the vital juices are about to come out.
No!
Please, I beg you! Don t look!
Milfy, I'll make you feel even better.
Tsukasa-kun's dick is...
going in!
If you get it both ways, you might
feel more pleasure even faster.
N-No! Y-You're doing both! I'm going to go crazy!
You're so tight down here. It almost hurts.
That's because...
your dick is driving me crazy.
My body is burning up!
Milty-san, so much juice is flowing from your pussy.
A dick looks like it would feel so good.
You look like you're going to cum already.
D-Don't rub it so hard!
Semen! Semen is coming out!
That's good. Show everyone how you cum.
Forgive me! I can't hold back! I'm cumming!
My dick can't take it! Semen is leaking!
Please... Please stop rubbing me already!
Hark! All living things that inhabit
the same world as Wizadia.
I am the Headmistress and Principal, Iris.
Presently, a powerful dark magic is
pulsing throughout the Academy.
All students must seek protection or evacuate immediately.
This tainted magic can easily overpower most barriers.
All teachers must cooperate to reinforce barriers
shields, and other defensive spells.
We will lead the students to safety!
We will not fail to protect them!
Even with all my power, I can barely keep the
dark magic from breaking out of the school.
I'll trust the rest to you, Sylvia.
Iris-sama.
Do whatever you want.
No one has cared for Tsukasa the way you have.
I leave everything to your judgment.
Let me ask one favor.
If Tsukasa defeats me, and he leaves the
Academy and goes to the outside world,
show no mercy in sending him to oblivion!
Even with the Principal's powers, you can't stop me.
I'll make everyone feel this pleasure.
Somehow, I have to somehow protect these children!
Eclair-sensei.
You tried your best, but it's over now.
First, I'll have these three.
Wait!
Don't lay a finger on the children!
Let me take their place for any shamelessness you desire!
If there is to be suffering...
then please inflict it on my body!
P-Please... be more gentle!
If you're so rough...
This feeling... Tsukasa-san?
Eclair-sensei!
Tsukasa-san?
Please, Sensei. Let me do whatever
I want with you for a while.
Tsukasa-san?
Tsukasa-san, you...
Your breasts are so warm and soft.
This feeling... It's been so many years!
It's become really hard.
I shouldn't, but those lips sucking on me felt so good.
I'll do it harder, okay?
Don't! It's coming out!
What is?
My breasts... My breasts!
Coming... It's coming!
Sensei, please make me feel good next.
Your dick rubbing against my breasts is electric.
Sensei, you're also making me feel really good.
Me too... My breasts are getting so hot!
Sensei, it's okay if I cum like this, right?
Yes! Don't hold back and cum in my mouth!
Me too, I'm also going to cum!
Sensei, let's cum together.
Please, let's cum together!
It's coining! So much is coining out!
My breasts... My breasts...
My breasts are...
It's coming out!
Persistent, aren't you?
That didn't even faze you.
I knew it. I have to find the source, Tsukasa, or else...
If you're looking for that child, isn't he in
the observation room under the school?
Lyra, why are you...
I thought it strange as well.
There's a magic barrier to repel any intruders,
but that boy just waltzed through like it was nothing.
The observation room under the school? If he's there, then...
Hurry up and get down there. He's waiting for you, isn't he?
What a suspicious turn of events.
Demonic beings like you usually don't get involved.
That's boy's dick was pretty darn good.
I thought if it'd be a waste if I never tasted it again.
Your concern is unnecessary.
Just wait, you stupid apprentice!
Your Sensei's on the way to discipline you!
Are you here, Tsukasa? Answer me at once.
Sensei, did you come to kill me?
Unfortunately, I'm hungry as hell,
so I've come to take you home.
Come on. Hurry up, get your butt home and cook my meal.
Sensei, do you love me?
A self-evident question like that is a waste of time!
Lies are delicious, aren't they?
Tsukasa! Wait, Tsukasa. Open your eyes and wake up!
I really want to get to know the Sensei
who talks about sex all the time.
Stop this at once!
It's wonderful. I can see all of your most private places.
Why you... I had no idea your style for
these kinds of things was so poor.
We're only just getting started.
I have to have more fun with you.
It hurts! No! Stop!
It's amazing, isn't it? They're all part of my dick.
As I thought, you feel so good, completely
different from everyone else.
How could I feel pleasure from this kind of thing!?
Don't worry, Sensei, this slippery liquid
is a drug that will give you pleasure.
Oh, no!
Please suck my dick.
You want it rougher, don't you?
You really love dick, right?
Stop! I'm going crazy!
It feels great, doesn't it?
No... It...
In that case, I'll give you a drink that
will make you feel even better.
You love my semen, don't you?
Here it comes.
Sylvia's magic power is weakening.
At this rate...
Fifteen years ago, my former master...
...the great wizard August destroyed an entire city within
a single day when one of his magical experiments failed.
Yes, the August Tragedy.
Having used up all its destructive energies
my master's Mystic Eyes sought a new vessel.
The one chosen was you, Tsukasa.
I was?
Ever since that tragic day fifteen years
ago, I've been searching for you.
To free you from the suffering brought on by the Mystic Eyes.
Sensei...
It's funny, isn't it?
The bearer of the Mystic Eyes that could destroy everything...
ends up using that power just to get to me.
You foolish apprentice.
The evil presence is gone.
Sylvia...
S-Sensei, I'm so sorry.
Jeez, what a foolish apprentice.
You're so good at everything else,
but you're horrible at sensual matters.
So good! It's wonderful! You can do it harder if you want.
Amazing. It's already sloppy and soaking wet.
Sensei...
You're making a really lustful face.
I'll make you feel even better.
Don't! It's too good!
Sensei, I still haven't...
I'll do it for you.
It feels so good! Sensei!
Sensei, can I come inside you? I...
Go ahead! Fill my womb with your cum!
Give me all of your semen!
Sensei!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I can't take it. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
For goodness sake, what in world are you two doing?
You still need lots of training from me, don't you?
I'll help you grow up to be an even better man,
my darling little Tsukasa.