The Destruction of Tia
Don't cum inside me!
Are you ready to become one of us?
To be raped until you want to die... and then more?
Like her?
I don't want to give birth!
No... No...
No!!
Stop coming out... Stop coming out...
I don't want to be a mother to monsters!
God, my ass... the tentacle is so deep in my ass!
It hurts... I feel them in my ass, my throat, my...
Oh no, they're coming out!
No more, please!
No more rape! No more babies!
Leave me alone. Just leave me be!
It's coming... It's coming out!
Coming out of me! Out of my body!
Stop it! You're messing me all up inside!
Kill me! I cant take any more...
Hurry up and kill me!
Kill me!
It's your turn now.
Let the witch hunts begin!
No!
On this most sacred of days, another witch is vanquished.
No!!
Mahou Shoujo Isuka
Encounter
VOLUME
A Day in the Life of Tsumiki Kashiwagi
Sheesh, aren't you worried about leaving a girl all by herself?
Time to go!
Encounter
I'm late, I'm late!
Ouch. Sorry!
I was in a hurry.
You all right?
Pardon me. I was in a rush, too.
No, it's my fault.
Well, gotta run.
She was a little weird.
Did she drop this?
Crap, look at the time!
Lux
Wanna play, mister?
Genji Hyodo
Tsumiki?
What?
Class is over.
Oh yeah. Thanks, Yayoi-chan.
Tsumiki, you're really spacey sometimes.
I hadn't noticed.
Right, because you were spacing out. Just try to be careful.
I will.
Well, then. See you tomorrow!
Miss Kashiwagi. Are you hurt?
Oh, Hyodo-sensei...
Mind your surroundings, will you?
I'd hate to think you're daydreaming during my class.
Do I need to bring you in for a private lecture?
I think I'll pass. See you later, sir.
Watch out for cars. We don't need you getting hospitalized.
I don't like Hyodo-sensei very much...
Mazoku
Hi! How's it going, Genji?
Well, if it isn't the vagrant groupie.
That's not a polite greeting.
Got some info for you. There's a new witch in town.
So?
So, you said I could help with the next witch hunt.
What makes you think you could be any help to me?
Hey! I have skills, all right?
So, what do you say?
Fine. So where's this witch of yours?
I've got her right where I want her.
If you're not interested, I'll catch her myself.
I'll believe that when I see it.
So I guess I can just put my feet up?
Don't mock me, you slob!
We Meet Again
Let's see...
Ow. That's been happening a lot today...
Huh?
You...
Um...
Oh! The hair clip!
Wait!
Again?
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
What's the big rush?
Oh, sorry!
Are you all right?
Yes. Pardon me, ma'am. I'm in a hurry.
Be seeing you... Tsumiki-chan.
Gotta run!
The Curtain is Raised
Puppets... There's too many of them.
Not good.
I'll destroy you all where you stand!
Get ready! Sorcery engine saturme magnesia, engage!
It isn't over yet.
How'd she do that? What a disgusting mess.
Are you a friend of hers?
If so, you're both in for a wild show.
What?
So you're Isuka, the Witch who stole the Mazoku's magic stone.
Mazoku? Then who are you?
Ouch. Let me go.
I knew it!
You witches are in cahoots with normal humans.
You're wrong.
I don't know her. Beat it, or else!
Or else what?
Or else I'll end you!
End me? That's a laugh.
No witch beats a hunter.
The Rape of Isuka
Lookin' good!
Why that spot?
Obviously, it wants to play.
What the hell?
Wait, are you a virgin?
I guess you are.
The fun factor just increased.
Now then, which hole's virginity do we take first?
No, stop...
No, stop rubbing me!
Let's take them in the logical order.
It hurts!
It hurts!!
Stop...
What's... What's going inside me?
They say you never forget your first time. Or your first tentacle.
Go on, scream! Cry and gasp!
No...
Tentacles?
Tentacles!?
Huh?
My mind... it's going blank!
My throat is full of disgusting, slimy flesh!
It's going deeper down my throat...
It's going deep inside me!
Well, how is it?
How do you like the taste of that slimy, cum-slicked tentacle?
We're just getting started.
No, stop!
Stop jerking around like that! It's ruining my insides!
No, something's coming out...
It's going inside me!
Slimy, sticky stuff is squirting into me!
It's pumping into me like a flood!
It's a very special kind of tentacle cum.
With the amount you just received, you're guaranteed to be pregnant.
Be... pregnant?
Preggers. Knocked up.
With a monster baby!
No! Stop it!
I don't want a baby, much less a monster baby!
Stop! Stop filling me with semen!
Hmm... What's next?
The Rape of Tsumiki
That's the fifth time today!
My God...
Are you okay? I'll help you, somehow.
No you won't, vermin!
You worthless piece of human trash!
You'll pay for your inference.
All right, since you wanted to join the party, here's your chance.
Right?
Something... Something's moving inside me!
No...
It's slithering around inside me!
Something slimy and putrid is slithering around inside me!
Take a good look.
This is just a preview of what's in store for you.
No! Don't touch me there!
I love your begging voice.
It's irresistible.
Gross!
I'll offer you a special service...
...The rape of your entire body.
Your ears, your nose, even your pores will hemorrhage semen.
My insides are flooded with cum!
My entire body is full!
But first things first.
No, stay out!
Get out of there!
It's inside me! It feels so gross!
I can't lose my virginity to a monster!
I cant stand it!
It's still pumping inside me... Even more than before!
So much slime...
This monster cock... It's winding deeper and deeper into my pussy!
It's too deep! It's wriggling around too much!
It's going to make me cum!
Even though it's my first time, I'm going to cum!
Thick tentacle dick... deep in my pussy... deep in my ass!
No more! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
The monster prick is twisting around in me like a fish!
Babies! So many monster babies...
Monster babies are coming out of my pussy and ass!
It's cumming inside me!
I'm going to get pregnant with disgusting beast offspring!
No more! Let me go!
I want to go home!
Giving birth to monsters is going to ruin my body forever!
It's coming out.. It's all coming out!
All that tentacle cum is gushing out of my holes!
I'm going to die. I might die at any moment.
Onee-sama!
Maseki
I caught a witch and a bitch in the same day! I'm a genius!
Okay, okay! What's next?
What's this?
Nee-sama...
The stone chose her?
That's strange.
But I can't hesitate now!
How could a human absorb a maseki? It's impossi...
Saturme magnesia...
...Overdrive!
Tempest gale! Attack!
Wow.
Who are you?
How did you absorb that maseki?
Are you...?
Umm...
What should I do!?
ano koro no kioku ga ima mo
Even now, the memory of that time
kizuato ni natta mama kesenakute
Is a scar that can't be erased
tsumi de yogoreta kizuguchi ni
Nails dig into my dirty wounds
tsume wo tate atarashii itami de gomakashiteru
Creating new pain and erasing the old
unmei ni mi wo makase me wo tojiru
I close my eyes and entrust myself to fate
na no ni dame watashi imi mada sagashiteru
But It's no good, I'm still looking for "meaning"
kono te de ima kono te de tachikitte
With these hands, with these very hands, I lower the blade
kanashimi no rensa ni shuushifu wo utte
And put an end to this chain of pain
namida ga kono namida ga kawaitara
These tears, when these tears have dried
mou ichi do sekai ni itsuka mita ano hikari wo
The light I once saw will return to the world