Translation from Japanese: mike74
Timing: Нарру
Translation from Russian to english: Anonymous
Magic LIPSTICK
Anata no hana to wo tsukamaetakute
(just a heads up, these lyrics are WRONG!)...
watashi hajimete no pinku no ruuju.
that ... the first time in my life used the pink lipstick.
Hayaku kinjiite kocchi wo muite
Rather, the same drop everything and come to me.
Iromeku kokoro wa anata tsugi tsuzukeru no
My heart trembles in anticipation.
Kuyashikute
If you're not in the mood ...
hoho yasereba
...I'll frown...
yasashii kisu ni kuchibiru torokesou
...melt... your lips from my gentle kiss.
Like a cat
Like a cat...
...is in your life... so love is wonder forever.
Kizuite kuretara akete mo ii
If you pay attention to me, anything that's over.
Tobikiri tagayaku
An extremely ...
suteki na suteki na
...wonderful...
naito
...night we will have!
Что случится с Юмой?
Ожесточённая! Битва любовного треугольника
Ожесточенная! Битва любовного треугольника
Что случится с Юмой?
Ожесточённая! Битва любовного треугольника
Ah!, just missed it!
No-o!
Оh, No...
Yes, who is it?
I-uh, wanted to bring to your attention a number of new products.
No thanks! We don't want anything!
I See...
Excuse me...
Wait a second! Ah-ah-ah! Stop it! Get away from me!
Mommy...
Eh...
You seem a little slow getting it up today.
Do you not find me attractive anymore, or what?
No, of course I do.
Great! Then let's get started!.
Oh broth-!
Come on...
I'm almost there already....
No-o-o!!!
Who was that?
Just this neighbor girl.
Even though she's a little kid, she's been trying to seduce me.
Seduce?!
Yeah.
She deliberately leaves her curtains open when she's changing...
When i'm taking a bath she'll barge right in and claim she got lost...
I try to scorn her but she gives me those Bambi-eyes.
She's growing up, she's started seeing you as a man.
Now then...
...let's get back to work!
What can I do to make these tiny breasts bigger?
What would he think about this place...
That hurts!
What?
What? Did I hit someone?
I'm so sorry!
Water...
Bring me water-r-r...
Water?
Here!
Thanks, I owe you one.
Why are you sleeping out here in such a public place?
Okay...
It's a bit of a long story so i'll make it snappy.
I'm a travelling salespig.
I arrived on Earth about a week ago, only to be shoved away by almost everybody I talked to.
No matter how good my pitch was, in the end, I haven't sold a single thing.
Oh, by the way, dear! Are you interested in buying one of my fine products?
Oh, how lovely! I want this!
It won't open.
Ah, yes, that thing is broken.
It's wonderful when it's set-up, but...
...when it arrived on Earth, something happened to it.
That's okay! Then i'll just take it!
Bye!
Hey, you gonna pay for that??
I came to your rescue, did you forget?
Аh... well...
Look who it is, it's that neighbor girl.
Little girl, shouldn't you be going home? It's getting late!
But not too late for you, right?
Not at all, I'm ready to have fun tonight.
C'mo-on, let's go to the club soon.
Dear God, please make me grow up quickly!
Maybe if I use the lipstick, I can at least look a little older.
Oh it's hopeless! I wish everything would change!
Huh?
Who are you?
My name is Rip.
I am the spirit of this lipstick.
Spirit?
With that lpistick...
...you can tint your lips and turn into an adult!
You see when you apply the lpistick and wish...
...everything you paint becomes real, all thanks to the gods.
Ehhhh??
But this model of lipstick is just a prototype, so its effects don't last very long.
And yeah, I'm aware of how silly this all sounds.
Are you a good artist?
Umm... drawing... that's kind of my weak spot...
Well, nevermind then, just forget it.
I guess this lipstick was wasted, just close it and put it away.
Wait a second! If I became an adult, I can go to the disco!
Okay!
Now, brother...
...will be mine!
LIPSTICK
What the...
You're a great dancer!
You're not so bad yourself.
Hey, listen...
...both of you, let's stop this bickering.
Let's all get along, huh?
And who do you choose - me or her?
I can choose?
But you're both so beautiful...
I'd prefer it if both of you could be with me, rather than one or the other!
Are you crazy?
C'mon, choose! Choose!
She's pretty, but she has a terrible temper, eh??
But I'll be gentle!
No, I'll be gentle!
Oh, crap!
If you don't clean it fast, the stain will stay!
Yeah!
Hey, want to come back to my place?
Sure!
Ugh, I'm all wet... Wha!
That bitch!
All right, this party is over!
No-o...
How dare you steal him from me!!
Gotcha!
Shit! Looks like I missed ...
Wha-?
♪♪She took the midnight tr-AUGH!
She's gone! Maybe she won't fire at us anymore.
Really? Well then, how about we go someplace more private?
She's back! Be careful!
Right!
Gotcha! Now return my property!
Damn, this situation is terrible.
Good evening. Haha...
Quickly, Mr. pig salesman, lend me something that will help me win!
You mean borrow something?
Oh! Actually, I have just the thing...
How about this? It's a "power suit."
Hurry up, give it here!!
Aha, this is quite a nice suit, but it's pretty expensive, my dear.
I don't care! We can talk about the price later!.
Did you forget that I saved your life earlier?
I remember, but didn't you get a free item from that?
Got it! Thanks, pig!
Now my brother and I WILL be a real couple!
Hey! You gonna pay for that "power suit"?!
You think you can steal my boyfriend from me with that tiny robot?! I sentence you to death!
Die!
Help me-e-e-e!!
That power!
You're the girl I've been waiting for my whole life!
I'll remember this! I'll get you someday, mystery woman!
The view is just beautiful...
No! It's embarrassing...
Faster-
Hurry!
I'm putting it in.
I'm cumming!!
NO!
Huh?
Forgive me!
Oh I forgot to mention, when your sexual pleasure peaks, the magic wears off.
So I can't come?
But... I feel so strange...
And it's so wet down here...
Shit, is this illegal?
See you later!
Good morning.
Good morning, brother!