According to the Meteorological Agency.
a large-scale, intense typhoon has hit Kyushu
and is moving slowly in a north by northeastern direction at 25 km/h.
The barometric pressure at the eye is 906 kPa.
Maximum wind velocity is 60m/h.
and precipitation is currently 70mm.
It is speculated that the typhoon will strike the Kanto region the day after tomorrow.
Experts speculate that this large typhoon developed as a result of global warming.
but it is yet to be discovered how this is possible.
The Second Coming of Magical Girl
Mahou Shoujo Ai San
Not so fast!
You might be a magical soldier, but in this
situation you're nothing but a woman.
Look in front of you.
You can see clearly that my tentacles
are going in and out of your vagina.
No, I won’t let you do that.
You aren't allowed to close your eyes.
Your body is restrained, you can't move!
We even used an aphrodisiac on you.
Doesn't your entire body feel good?
Let me see what a magical soldier tastes like!
Dammit...!
So they were raping women to their heart's content in here...
However, that ends now.
Are you sure about that?
Die.
You were planning on hunting us, weren't you?
I couldn't sense his presence in the sewers...!
How unfortunate.
You're the one who's being hunted now,
magical soldier.
I infused the water that splashed on you...
with an aphrodisiac!
We'll kill you...
After we have our fun!
These yuragi who were previously acting independently
are now cooperating with each other?
Tasty! You're so tasty, magical soldier!
Let me taste you more!
I'm going to swallow this magical soldier!
You're going to cum...!
You can no longer return to the way you once were!
We'll cum too!
I came...
She did too...
A magical soldier!
She had it coming!
I can't believe we used to be scared of her.
How pathetic...
We'll finish her off with her own staff.
This staff that she used to slash
and kill so many of our comrades.
Great idea, Aniki!
Carve her up like a sculpture!
Hold it!
Ai!!
What the...!?
Ouch...
Why did he even come here?
Well, now we have someone to watch us.
Ai...
Why don't you just sit back and watch as we
turn this magical soldier into a shish kebab?
This is it, magical soldier!
Playtime ends now.
Die.
Rin...
Geez, just look at you.
Well, whatever...
Anyway, you'd only get in my way if you were out running around.
You should just lie low from now on.
I'll take down both Shin and Mayu.
But Mayu is...
Putting all that aside,
I won't allow you to get in my way.
Rin...
The yuragi are different than they were before.
What of it?
They're the same if you just kill them.
Rin...
Face the other way.
Okay...
It's all sticky and smelly.
Hey Ai,
what did you mean when you said that about the yuragi...
It's like they're working together.
It seems like they're now a part of some organization.
Anyway, why did you come?
Why?
Because I was worried about you, of course.
It's not like you arriving actually did anything.
Oh, but I created a new weapon...
But I guess that didn't really do much.
I heard that the yuragi were weak against strong light, so...
It's actually the flash that attaches to a camera.
There's so much inside me...
I can't get it out..
If you look, I'll kill you.
Hurry up and get this place cleaned!
The fact that I chose a bankrupt hotel as the location for the
Urban Legend Research Club's party was a fabulous idea,
but the cleaning part is a huge hassle.
What about this one, Senpai?
Put it on the edge of the stage.
Well, it's a good thing that my uncle
happened to be one of the creditors.
We were able to get this place rent-free.
Hey! Desks over there!
Chairs are that way!
Geez! Not like that!
Are you okay?
Ai.
Y-Yeah...
Are you thinking about the yuragi?
More importantly, how did you know where I was?
Oh, with this.
This thing that you gave me?
Yup. I can get your location because of that.
That's pretty convenient.
So, it has more uses other than communication.
Ai.
I'm dirty.
I'll make you clean.
No.
I really...
Ai...
I'll make you clean.
Your vagina tastes good...
D-Don't...
say such things!
But...
Can I put it in?
I'm coming in.
I'll do it slowly.
Ai, I'm sorry...
Well...
Mine isn't...
Idiot.
Sorry...
You're warm... I love it.
Ai...
Thump... Thump...
I like this sound in your chest.
Ai...
I'll find them for sure.
And Shin and Mayu will...
I'm... almost...
Wait!
B-But...
Oops, s-sorry...
Yukari
Hello?
Oka-chin!?
You finally picked up your phone!
Where did you go after ditching cleanup duty?
We have to get this place cleaned up today! The party is tomorrow!
Oh...
If you don't get your ass over here now,
I'll get my uncle to cut your wages in half!
But...
Oops...
I followed the stench here, and...
Looks like I hit jackpot.
Fabulous.
Your battle abilities are flawless.
Shin!
Mama! I wanted to see you!
Don't call me "Mama"!
I wanted to see you too.
So much so that I want to kill you!
Oh, sorry.
What!?
I may be getting old, I can't hear you too well.
Could you come a little closer?
Stop fucking around!
Oh, that spot is fine.
Now, would you be kind enough to say your punchline again?
Do your best, Mama!
Don't you dare mock me!
Huh?
Is that enough?
Then can I say my two cents as well?
You...
can no longer move.
What!?
What is this!?
Didn't you realize?
That water is a cluster of yuragi.
You've got strength, but you're lacking in brains.
You're beautiful, Mama.
Don't look down on me. This is nothing!
Your power is formidable.
I'd love to make you a part of my plan.
What do you say?
No way I will!
Not my ass!
How do you like the sound of a "Fiendish Magical Soldier"?
Geez, Mama, you're even drooling down
here. Where are your manners?
I-I'ts because my ass feels so good...
N-No! Stop!
My ass! I can hardly think straight!
I've already researched the fact that you can only cum with your ass.
My asshole!
No! You'll stretch it out too much!
I can do this every day if you'll join our side.
You're enjoying it, Mama.
I came out of here, right?
Can I go in it again, Mama?
No!
Thanks for giving birth to me, Mama.
I didn't give birth to you!
You were only living on me!
Amazing!
Mama's cumming!
Stop!
Mama, Onii-chan says he wants to do it, too.
No more!
Stop!
Oh, don't say that.
In order to send you to heaven, I prepared this especially for you.
What do you say?
If you join our side, we'll make you cum every single day.
Think hard about it.
Help me!
No... No more!
It seems like you don't even have the time to think.
Stop!
No!
I'm going to cum!
Forgive me!
No!
I'm cumming!
Mama just came!
She just came!
Onii-chan!
She just came by herself.
What a bad girl she is.
That's one down.
Once we get the other two...