Oh, yes!
Amazing!
This is so good!
More!
Harder!
Yes!
I'm impressed, Mezger Heinkel.
To have such exquisite sex
slaves at your command.
And what's more, they're Magic Knights who
belong to the proud and powerful Queen Gloria.
This is the result of impeccable training.
At this rate, that troublesome goddess
Konoedan can be destroyed at last.
It's only a matter of time now.
The only Magic Knights not yet imprisoned
are a band called the Sweet Knights.
About that.
I just received intelligence.
Their camp has been located.
By the time you reach them, we will have
discovered their secret identities.
At last, huh?
I'm counting on you, Mezger.
Capture the Sweet Knights and enslave them.
Sweet Thunder Attack!
Boomerang Hoop!
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: v1touch | TS & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
Mahou Senshi Sweet Knights
~Heroine Rape Order~
What's the matter?
Are you lost?
Y-Yeah. I just transferred here.
Oh, a transfer student.
This place is quite big.
Where are you headed?
Class A for students of International Studies.
In that case, you're in the same class as me.
Huh?
I'm Nanase Ririko.
And you are?
I-Is there something on my face?
Uh, no.
Homura.
I'm Homura Tatsuto.
That's a nice name.
Homura-kun, huh?
Well then, let me show you to the classroom.
Homura-kun, you have a mysterious
aura about you.
Cool, I suppose, or maybe a bit supernatural.
That's why I spoke to you back there.
Good morning, Nanase-san.
Who is this?
I haven't seen him around the
International Studies Department.
He just transferred here.
He's Homura Tatsuto-kun.
I see. I'm Sakura Airi, department
chair for International Studies.
Nice to meet you.
Airi-sensei may be pretty, but she's
very high up around here.
She's very strict and kind of scary.
Now, don't put it that way, dear.
I have to ensure the safety of the students
and the integrity of the program.
Lots of strange things have been
happening around here lately.
Well, class is about to start.
Go to the classroom at once.
Homura-kun?
Should I give you a more
thorough tour of the school?
Good idea.
I guess I'll take you up on the offer.
This cafe is run by the students
in the Nutrition Department.
Welcome, Senpai.
Oh, Kanaha-chan!
Good timing.
I've got someone for you to meet.
This is Homura Tatsuto-kun, a new student.
Hello.
I'm Yuzuki Kanaha.
Kanaha-chan is like a little sister to me.
I trust her with my life.
What's wrong, Kanaha-chan?
N-Nothing.
You're blushing, you're blushing.
Senpai.
Oh, Kanaha-chan, you're silly.
It's gotten really late, hasn't it?
Yeah.
Earlier today, Airi-sensei mentioned that
things have been creepy here lately.
Actually, you see...
Watch out!
Homura-kun! Run away, quickly!
I guess I have no other choice.
Sweet Magical Sensation!
I am Sweet Lip, a Magic Knight
fighting for Love and Justice.
In the name of Queen Gloria's smile,
I will destroy those who threaten
the peace of this school!
Crescent Hurricane!
Homura-kun, are you hurt?
No, I'm fine. It didn't get me.
That's a relief.
You're surprised, aren't you?
It was a monster... and... I'm a...
Homura-kun, this has to be kept a secret!
Well, bye!
Welcome back, Mezger-sama.
Kokono, your reports were correct.
Nanase Ririko is indeed a Sweet Knight.
However, there are more Sweet
Knights than just her.
Their identities should have
been found before I arrived.
I apologize, my lord.
I think you need punishment.
Yes, lord. As you wish.
My... My nipples...
My nipples are getting hard!
Put... Put it in.
Please.
So much nasty juice...
Mezger-sama!
Deeper!
Mezger-sama...
I want it.
You want this one instead?
So hot!
Inside my mouth. Delicious!
Put it inside.
It's inside!
Mezger-sama is inside!
So big!
It's so thick!
Harder. Deeper, please.
Thrust it deeper!
Yes!
I'm gonna cum!
Yes! Harder!
Do it harder!
Oh, no!
I'm cumming!
I apologize, Mezger-sama!
I was the only one who came.
And here you were so kind as to fuck me.
I am a failure as your slave.
Don't worry about it.
With just one more step,
I will achieve my desire,
and I will be the ruler of this world.
Magical Syndicate Zero will rule this world.
And to make this happen, I must capture
the Sweet Knights and train them
to be my slaves, thereby stealing
the power of Queen Gloria.
I will always follow your orders, Mezger-sama.
Call my servants.
Call as many as you can.
Invite Ririko out again to lure the
other Sweet Knights to us.
Yes, lord.
Good morning, Homura-kun.
Good morning.
Hey, Homura-kun... about yesterday...
I haven't told anyone.
Thank you!
But what exactly is going on with you?
I'd like an explanation.
You're right...
Let's meet after school in Kanaha-chan's cafe.
Enjoy yourselves.
Actually, I have a mission.
A mission?
Yes.
I must protect this world.
Maybe you can't believe it, but
this world has been invaded
by a magical organization from another
dimension called "Magical Syndicate Zero".
To thwart their evil plans, I have been sent
here from that dimension by Queen Gloria.
She gave me special powers.
I'm called a Sweet Knight.
That's really amazing.
So you're a superhero.
That's not true at all.
I'm just a normal girl, usually.
Looks like we're going home late again today.
I feel at ease with you, though.
After all, you're a Sweet Knight.
What's wrong?
Be quiet.
Homura-kun! Stay back!
Sweet Magical Sensation!
I am Sweet Lip, a Magic Knight
fighting for Love and Justice.
Crescent Hurricane!
Sweet Thunder Attack!
Kanaha-chan!
Senpai!
I am Sweet Kiss, a Magic Knight
fighting for Love and Justice!
Magical Syndicate Zero!
In the name of Queen Gloria's smile,
I will thwart your evildoing!
Sweet Magical Sensation!
Boomerang Hoop!
Crystal Explosion!
Justice Evolution!
Thank you, Kanaha-chan. You saved me.
Thank God I made it in time.
I've never seen so many monsters.
What a shock.
I would never have suspected Kanaha-chan.
Yes. Kanaha-chan is also a Sweet Knight.
Yes, I am.
I swore to Queen Gloria that
I would protect the world.
Sweet Lip and Sweet Kiss.
Don't stare at me like that.
No, I'm just very impressed.
And I hope to help you out from now on.
Really?
You really want to help us, Homura-senpai?
Yeah. If something comes up,
don't hesitate to ask me.
Thank you, Homura-kun.
Ririko and Kanaha...
When the two join their powers together,
they're a force to be reckoned with.
We should probably target
them when they're apart.
Kokono, summon the Jouma.
Yes, lord.
So you've shown yourself again.
What's the occasion tonight?
You've brought different guests this time, I see.
Things will not go as they did last night.
Oops, I forgot to introduce myself.
I am Mezger Heinkel.
I'm honored to meet you, beautiful Sweet Lip.
So you're the leader of the Syndicate, then?
In that case, as long as we
Sweet Knights are here,
we won't let you do as you please!
Magical Sensation!
Crescent Hurricane!
Justice Evolution!
This is nothing to me.
Get her, my Jouma!
No!
Do you like it, Sweet Lip?
Don't do such lewd things!
What are you going to do to me?
Imprint the joy of penetration and violation
deep into the womb of your pure body!
But I have a precious mission
to protect love and justice!
No matter what you do to me, I won't be defeated!
I wonder how much you'll be able to endure...
No!
No! Stop it!
I could really suck these toys dry.
See? They're erect now.
Th-That can't be!
My nipples wouldn't get erect because of you.
Your body doesn't lie.
But...
How about this end?
No! Stop it!
Beautiful.
Almost like a jewel.
Don't look at it.
D-Don't put your finger in there!
You won't defeat me.
Very nice smell.
You have the scent of a virgin.
Don't! Not there!
Don't lick down there!
Please, stop it.
Stop it!
It's coming out...
It's coming out!
It's hot.
My body is so hot.
Do you want it?
Do you want my flesh rod?
No!
D-Don't put something so dirty in me!
But your body wants it.
No!
Don't put that thing in there!
Stop acting so proud.
That hurts!
It's inside of me...
It's inside...
Inside of me...
It's hard.
No, stop it!
Don't move!
It's rubbing... It's rubbing against me!
How does this feel, Sweet Lip?
How does it feel to be fucked by your enemy?
I hate it!
Even the deepest hatred will turn
in time into the deepest pleasure.
My flesh rod will change you!
I don't feel anything... at all!
No, stop it!
No, not there...
You look very pretty, Sweet Lip!
So hot. I'm so hot down there!
No!
I can't take it!
I'm losing my mind!
What a sweet scene, Sweet Lip.
A beautiful scene of a knight of love and justice
cumming from getting fucked by her enemy!
I won't cum!
I-I can't cum.
I don't wanna be a slut.
No!
Here I go!
No! Not inside!
Please, don't cum inside of me!
How was it, Sweet Lip?
How was your first taste of a flesh rod?
I haven't lost hope!
N-No matter how shamed I am, I will
not let myself do your bidding!
Nicely put.
But how much longer will you be
able to resist my sex appeal?
I will resist it!
You will not defeat me!
I look forward to it, Sweet Lip.
Senpai!
Sweet Magical Sensation!
Sweet Flash Illusion!
In that case...
Crystal Explosion!
How dare you do something
so disgusting to Senpai.
I won't let you guys get away with it!
I'll have to say goodbye for today.
Sweet Lip, thank your cute
little sister for saving you.
Wait!
Eventually, I'll shame that
little girl as I shamed you.
Come back here!
Ririko-senpai, are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Thanks, Kanaha-chan.
I hope she's okay.
Senpai...
Good morning.
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
Oh...
Well...
Homura-kun...
Come meet me at the rooftop at lunchtime.
Actually, you see...
Last night, more monsters showed up.
And the new leader of the enemy brought
some monsters I've never seen before.
Then what happened?
Well, I don't know what to say,
but they were different from
any enemy I've faced before.
What do you mean?
I mean... they didn't try to defeat
me through strength.
But...
They shamed me.
I was incapacitated by shame.
They "shamed" you?
I-I can't go into the details.
I see. Then what happened?
I can't!
I can't say it!
I can't talk about something so humiliating!
Humiliating?
It was a difficult battle, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you.
I don't want to remember it.
Well, don't force yourself to talk about
something you don't want to.
Thank you, Homura-kun.
But don't worry.
I won't lose.
I won't let Mezger have his way this time.
Mezger?
The name of my new enemy.
Oh, really?
I feel a bit relieved after talking to you.
You're really strong, Nanase.
That's not true at all.
I'm just a normal girl.
Well, class is starting.
Welcome, Homura-senpai.
What's wrong?
You look glum.
If it's Nanase you're worried about, she's fine.
I heard everything from Nanase.
And she's strong.
Yes, you're right!
Um, you're Yuzuki Kanaha-san, right?
Yes.
I have a message from Nanase-senpai.
From Senpai?
Yes.
She wants you to meet her at
the park near school tonight.
The park? Where is she right now?
I don't know. She just sent me here.
Well, I'm in a hurry.
That's strange.
Why don't you just go to the park tonight?
I'll come with you.
No. I'll go by myself.
I see.
You don't need to worry about her.
Yeah. You're right.
I wonder where Senpai is...
Oh, just stop it!
Perhaps Sweet Kiss needs to send you
guys back to where you came from.
Sweet Magical Sensation!
Here we go.
Boomerang Hoop!
Crystal Explosion!
No!
kinou no kuchizuke mada setsunakute hitori nemuru beddo de furueru
Yesterday's kiss is still painful. The bed I sleep in alone shivers.
ashita mo issho ni kono te tsunaide anata to nemuru yume no naka de
I'm lost in a dream of tomorrow, holding hands with you as we sleep.
sekai ga futari dake ni natte mo ai o tsukurotte ikite yukeru
Even if we're the last two people in this
world, love will mend everything.
sekai ga futari o yurusanakute mo ai no kusari o hanasanai de
Even if the world won't forgive us,
please don't release our chains of love.
mahou ga watashi o hadaka ni suru hikari no naka de umare kawaru
Magic makes me naked. I will be reborn in the light.
mahou ga watashi o otona ni kaeru anata no tame ni kirei ni nareru
Magic makes me an adult. I will become prettier for you.
kiss in the sweet nights kono omoi o todokete hoshii
Kiss in the sweet nights. I want these feelings to reach you.
kiss in the sweet nights zutto amai yoru ga tsuzuku you ni
Kiss in the sweet nights. I hope these sweet nights continue forever.