Sexy Magical Girl VOL. 5
Pervert Fansubs Presents
Editors: Monti and DarkZhiro
How's it going Okajima.
Naito-sensei are you crazy?
Now you finally know,
who is on top position in this school.
You bastard!
Wait a little.
We have to wait for an opening to save the hostages.
What's with the scary look Okajima?
Do you really think that you can trick your teacher.
I already have this body.
Don't Onii-chan.
I don't want you to do it with Harumi-sensei.
What's this?
Aren't you two related by blood?
But… But…
I really love Onii-chan.
Okajima.
We are brother and sister after all.
Onii-chan.
Is that so?
Very well then.
I'll make your dream come true.
Teacher is really kind.
What the hell do you want Naito?
Naito-sensei… right?
Sen...sei……
You see Oomi's desire is that,
her brother doesn't get snatched by someone else.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan ever since Kagano Kagano.
There's been nothing else on your mind. I don't like that.
Yua...
We do not have to wait for polite Kagano to dig in.
Right Okajima?
Naito! You bastard!
Don't Onii-chan, look only at Yua!
Yua's going to make you feel good at all means.
Yu-Yua!
Stop!
Okay, what now?
Not yet, we still have to wait for an opening.
Stop this already Naito-sensei!
I just want my little sister back!
Interesting, I'll let you feel your sisters taste. The taste of regret.
Aren't you still a human being?
Yes I was a low human biologically.
Before i became king of the Naito!
And started to dominate the humans.
That way all women in the world are mine.
Okajima your body is being honest.
Yua...
Ai!
Since she is your sister…
A big change?
You should do it.
Your joking, what guy could stand this.
What?
Why are you so mad at me, I… I…
I love you!!
You know I like you right?
What are you saying at time like this?
Onii-chan.
Look at Yua's pussy
Stop it Yua.
No. I want you to lick Yua.
Don't say that you wont.
Stop it.
That's right onii-chan lick Yua right there.
Lick it.
How is it Okajima  do you like your sister.
It looks satisfying.
Onii-chan, look, Yua is so wet down there. i can't hold it any more.
Onii-chan!
S-Stop it Yua!
We can't... that!
Stop It!
You're thing is inside me.
Onii-chan!
Yua is so happy.
Onii-chan.
It feels good, It feels good down there.
Onii-chan, please enjoy this too.
How is it Okajima?
Does it feel good inside her?
It feels so good Onii-chan, so good.
I like how you fuck me all the time.
Please sensei, more more!
It's fine.
It feels so good onii-chan.
It can't be any better.
Right there, yes, right there.
Yua....
Yua, I'm so sorry,
I'm Sorry Yua...
I...I'm cumming!
Friendship transformation …!
Love is loaded inside!
I'm cumming!
You…
Dot come near me!
Help!
Ye-sama please help me!
You are waste.
You are useless.
Ye-sama!
You…
Thats right.
Huanchu was one of my tentacles demons.
But he was playing when everything has changed.
How can I compare him now.
The trash is always a trash.
But you will like what I'm going to do with you.
Take this!
I will not let you succeed!
She is to good.
She is a devil full of tentacles.
You are finished!
Lightning!
You bitch!
What the...
Ai now is you chance.
Okajima!
You bastard!
What's the matter? Can't you attack when Okajima is in front of me?
Dam it
I see! Then I'll use him.
How about this.
I am sorry Ai
Damn it!
I will not give you my brother.
Yua!
What's wrong with you, let me go!
What?
Ai! Yua!
What's going on?
That's what happens when you cut off my tentacles.
AI!
At least give me some credit for that.
Magical warriors can be killed that way.
Chairman what are your orders?
Do as you like.
But move her inside first.
Thank you very much.
It hurts, it hurts!!!
I can do whatever I want with you.
So I want you to like whatever I do to you!
Okajima, I want your heart to be filled with despair.
How… how is it?
Do you feel completely comfortable.
Then I will start abusing the magical girl.
How nice.
She seems to be a virgin.
And she's so wet down there.
Look how i made a dick out of my tentacles.
Don't.
Okajima does this make you jealous?
Look how I'm going to fuck this virgin magical girl.
I am inside the her.
Too bad for you Okajima.
What a cute boobs you have.
Lets play with them too.
How about this.
This tentacle I made is very comfortable.
Now it's time to fuck your ass.
It's much more important than the pussy.
How do you like it?
Your body still wants more.
I will fuck you till you die.
Yes, Yes, your ass is so tight.
I'm cuming! I will cum inside your ass.
You came so much and you can still go.
Not so fast, I'm not done with her.
Now suck it.
The Magical girl will actually  lick my thing.
Now suck your masters thing!
Just as I thought. He's a good for nothing.
You...
That right.
Now I'm gonna deal with you.
Hurry and prepare yoursel,f or you will die.
Harumi-sensei that's enough!
I will do anything to save Ai!
What's that? So you really  like this woman?
Okajima do you want to do it with her?
Such a thing.
Well, I'll let you to it with her.
Se...Sensei
What's that?
What's going on?
Oh, Your thing is getting magnificent Okajima.
This is too weird even for a teacher.
You like this magic girl don't you?
Stop it!
Stoooop it!
You will have only one chance to have her.
So be thankful Okajima.
Ai.
How is it Okajima?
I'm a very kind teacher right?
It's better for this woman if she enjoys it.
Let's fuck her to death.
How is it Okajima?
How's the first violation of your favorite woman feel?
Is this feels good?
Come on, give her a kiss.
Stop it!
Would you like to get it?
I am sorry Ai.
It's fine as long it's with you...
Ai.
No! You can't just give up! Hang in there!
Okajima Akitoshi!
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
Stop it!
I will not let you succeed!
Say what?
Stop it Okajima!
Damn you!
You scum!
Okajima!
It's 100 years too early for you to beat me
Unforgivable…
We did it Ai.
The end of it.
It's not over yet.
(Please help me)
What's going on?
Hurry and run! you can't stay here.
It's the accumulation of the several hundred years of tentacle demons.
Wait Yua is still there!
No! It's already too late.
Sempai!
Okajima-kun!
Onii-chan!
Yua !
No it's too late!
Quickly! let's get out of here.
Yua...
The entire place is collapsing.
You will no longer be you.
We are also no longer the same.
That's why at that time when you were little,
I took part in the fighting.
My body was swallowed by the devil.
When I lost my self.
Only my heart still belongs to me.
In order to not let them succeed.
Sister…
So I lived in your body.
Because I believed that the next battle will come.
Then in that dream you gave me advice...
Because the benefits will be null and void for my sister in magic.
It's a dead end.
Look above!
The bright spot above us.
That is the devil's lair.
That's right you have to destroy it.
I know that.
That is a big ginkgo tree school.
So sister please.
Understood.
Let's go, hang on to me.
Wait.
Akitoshi
Do...Dooru!
What?
I would also like to come with you.
Stop it Dooru!
We are good friends.
Quickly kick him off!
Akitoshi.
Stop it, let me go!
Let go of me! Let go Dooru!
Dooru, you are really cute.
What?
Akitoshi!
This is no good we can't win.
Listen to me now, we need your help.
We have to enchant the destruction of the Ward tentacle demons.
But the enemy is too strong.
Accumulation of several hundred years of the tentacles demons…
Have set up.
To your Yua and other people yearning for the catalyst.
We need to join forces in order to enhance the elimination magic of tentacle demons.
What do you need me to do?
Step up here.
Then we think.
There are many happy memories.
I understand.
Ai.
This is bad we can't focus.
Yua,Tia-san, and all of our friends.
If you care about the generous-minded people around,
The eradication of the tentacle demons heart
The integration of our souls.
Any resistance is useless.
We will go out of here.
Yua!
Tia-san!
Miraiko!
Dooru!
Ai!
After the things I went through, I don't know.
The time to wake up.
The school found there was a backyard pit.
Even the ginkgo tree disappeared.
Several nude students were lying nearby.
Harumi and Naito-sensei, and several more people have disappeared.
Although people asked many things.
None of them was answered.
Even Ai  disappeared.
Because of this incident the cultural festival was also abolished.
The lives of all were soon restored to normal.
Yua-attack…!
Excellent
Just perfect.
Since then I don't know what happened to Ai.
But the time I was with Ai.
will stay in my heart.
My real love.
Good morning Onii-chan.
Yua.
Ai will.....surely come back someday.