The Zoid have begun their massed attack!
I will save everyone!
That's not possible!
Don't get in my way!
I told you, it's not possible!
There's too many of them!
The only solution is to go to the moon and defeat the Zoid Overlord!
But am I able to travel to the moon using my own power?
If I transfer all of my power to you, then it should be enough.
Is it really okay for you to do that?
If I use all of my power, I may perish in the attempt.
However, we have to save Emille and the citizens of Earth!
Ovi...
Don't hesitate.
The fate of your family,
no, the fate of everyone on Earth rests on your shoulders.
Erena, that is why you have to go now.
Even if I perish, I don't want you to look backward.
Erena, I'm glad I was able to meet you.
Ovi...
Presented
by Shikkaku
Erena, blasting off!
Father, Father!
Where am I?
Ovi? Ovi!
Ovi, I guess you used up all of your power...
I'll be going, then.
To the moon.
That won't be happening,
Onee-chan.
Emille!
What a splendid sight, Onee-chan.
Emille, please let me go!
Let's talk this out!
Onee-chan, don't you understand the situation you're in?
This is war.
A war which will determine the fates of the Zoid and the humans.
You and I are enemies.
The only thing that won't change is that we're family.
So I'll share with you the pleasure and humiliation I suffered at the hands of the Zoid.
Not so suddenly!
It's spreading me from the inside out!
No!
My stomach feels so full!
You sure are lively! I'll stir you up some more.
You're going to break me! My stomach!
Your ass looks like it's enjoying it, Onee-chan.
My intestines! They're going to burst!
However, I'm going to use this to make sure you belong to me!
I'm gonna die!
Oh, do you want it there, too?
The fact that I get to see you make that expression is like a dream come true.
It's so embarrassing, and yet I'm the only one you'd show it to, right?
What a thrill!
The tentacles have met each other inside of you!
What is this? It's like your stomach isn't even human!
You didn't think that I wouldn't touch your pussy, did you?
Don't worry, I'll make sure to play with it.
Do it!
Can you tell?
This is the first time that you've been so full.
Now we're going to flood your insides with the Zoid!
It's fine.
The fluids released will heal your wounds.
It'll come gushing out.
Don't struggle; every touch of the Zoid brings nothing but pleasure.
Amazing, amazing!
It's going inside me!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Feel it more!
More, more!
Go crazy from the pleasure!
Onee-chan.
Here we go.
Can you tell, Onee-chan?
The Zoid tentacles are getting excited and spreading your ass even further.
You know what this means, right?
The semen from their seminal duct is causing your intestines and throat to bulge!
They're going to fill your insides with semen!
Onee-chan, I love you!
I love you so much!
Emille is in love with you!
I loved you before I even became a part of the Zoid!
That's why I'm going to break you.
I'm going to break you!
I want to be with you forever and ever!
I'm the only one who's allowed to break you.
Onee-chan...
I'm the only one who's allowed to rape you.
I...
I won't lose!
Emille!
Onee-chan!
I won't lose, either!
Emille, stop this!
I can't lose!
Never! Never ever!
I can't let you win, either!
I have to save you from the Zoid!
You're full of lies.
You just want to see me as a pitiful person so you can feel better about yourself!
No way! I've been doing this all for you!
You're trying to mask your loneliness by being kind to me.
That's so mean!
You're the one who's mean, Onee-chan.
It's because of you, because you're so kind to me, that I can't stay away from you!
My stomach!
I won't... I won't let you go to the moon!
Why are you so protective of what's on the moon?
Shut up! Shut your mouth!
You belongs to me!
There's no need to meet him!
Emille! Who's him?
Shut up!
I told you that I mustn't lose!
Is this your true strength?
Emille, please wake up!
The Emille I know isn't this stubborn!
You don't understand.
You don't understand my feelings at all.
I do understand!
I do understand your feelings, because we've known each other our entire lives.
I share your feelings!
I love you right now too!
These feelings for you have never changed!
Onee-chan?
The magic is overflowing. It won't stop!
Stop it, Onee-chan! Please!
Our magic is getting out of control!
No! It's not stopping!
I'm dying! I'm gonna die!
I'm really going to die!
My stomach! The tentacle is out of control!
I'm cumming!
It won't stop! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
It feel it! I feel you, Emille!
Ah!
Are you cumming?
You're going to cum! We're going to cum together!
Emille!
Emille! I'm going to die, too!
I'm cumming! No!
Onee-chan!
I'm cumming!
Emille, you pulled the Zoid inside yourself at the last moment, didn't you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
I promised to protect you, Emille.
There's no need to apologize.
There's no need for both of us to die.
As long as you're safe, I'm happy.
It's over.
Emille...
Onee-chan.
Emille! Stay strong!
I love you, Onee-chan.
Emille, Emille!
Emille, I'm going for it.
For Mom, Ovi, and Emille!
For everyone on Earth!
Dad's space shuttle?
What?
Why is Mom here?
Onee-chan, didn't I tell you not to come to the moon?
It looks like we're all finally together.
We'll be able to live together again.
Is that the Zoid Overlord?
No, it's not, Onee-chan.
Take a closer look, Erena...
No way, Dad was...
It's not a lie.
I promised all of you.
We would meet again.
I've waited a long time for this day, Erena!
Ouch! No, let me go!
Stop it! Dad!
Dad! Please don't touch me there!
Erena, you've grown so much; I'm flattered.
Your pussy has matured and ripened wonderfully.
And your breasts have become so big.
It makes me so happy!
Dad! Please come to your senses!
Dad wouldn't say things like that!
You mustn't lose yourself to the Zoid!
Dad's finger...
Dad's finger. No, I can't get any pleasure from this!
No!
There's nothing to be embarrassed about, Onee-chan.
It's the Zoid Overlord that's touching you.
Of course you'll feel aroused.
I-It feels good!
Does it feel good?
Then I'll make you feel even better!
No way!
It's so thick!
This is!
Why is this happening?
This is merely to see how well you've developed.
This is to see if your body is capable of being a host for the Zoid.
A host for the Zoid?
The Zoid are strengthed by being born from similar bloodlines.
For Dad to reproduce, he has to use either my or your uterus.
And your uterus was further developed, Erena.
That's why I told you not to come to the moon.
Because Dad is going to take you away.
I'm going to bear the Zoid Overlord's offspring!
Don't twist around inside of me!
Watching Erena is making me want some as well.
I want some! I want some, too!
Mom! Emille!
Then I'll give it to you two, as well!
No!
This feels amazing!
My uterus feels like it's on fire!
It's going to melt together with your cock!
It's so hot! I'm melting!
It feels so good! I don't care if this is because of the Zoid!
My family is together again!
My butt feels amazing! I want it to leak semen!
More! Give me more!
I want us to love each other even more!
Dad is penetrating every hole in the family!
I can feel it! I can feel your presence, Onee-chan!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
You can't! We need to cum together as a family!
Let's cum together!
Give it to me!
Give me your thick, slimy, tentacle semen!
Please pour it deep inside of me!
Cocks, cocks! I love cocks!
Something big is coming!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
My pussy and my ass both feel amazing! I'm going to cum from both of them!
I'm cumming!
Erena... Erena!
Ovi?
Does seeing you mean that I'm dead?
This is your soul realm.
Some of my magic was still within you.
I guess I'm still alive, then?
Erena, can I ask you a question?
What is it?
Which of the two are you going to choose, your family or the Earth?
I...
What's this light?
Onee-chan?
What the hell is this light?
Summoned by the stars, the ancestors of the universe: Magical Girl Erena!
Together with the Lunar Empress, reporting lift off!
What is this light?
This light is so bright and warm.
Stop it! My body!
What are you doing?
Emille! Mom!
You came back to your senses!
That's right, and it's thanks to your light.
Listen closely, Erena!
You can only defeat the Zoid Overlord right now!
But if I shoot, you two will...
Erena, what are you doing? Hurry up and shoot!
But...
Onee-chan, hurry!
I can't do it! I can't shoot!
Why do I have to shoot?
Erena, you've grown up to be such a caring girl.
There's no need to worry about us.
We have no regrets.
I was able to tell you that I loved you.
And I was able to see my precious daughters again, an opportunity I thought I'd never have.
Now, please do it!
Shoot it, Erena!
Shoot it!
Luna Empress of Serenity!
Mom...
Emille...
Dad...
Thank you, Erena...
Thank goodness...
I'm home, Erena.
Everyone, we're going to have breakfast.
Okay!
Dad, welcome home.
Jeez, Emille. You're still sleepy?
Oh, that's right. I have a special present for you two.
It's something you've both been wanting.
He's a part of our family now.
Huh?
He's wearing quite an interesting necklace, isn't he?