Mama!
Finally!
You're late, Okachin!
Yeah, my bad.
Hey, Okachin!
Tomorrow is the Kantou-wide presentation party...
...for our Urban Legend Research club!
Sorry...
Something urgent just came up.
What!?
Hey! Get back here, Okachin!
Geez!
Okachin, you idiot!
Meg Asain
Mahou Shoujo Ai San
Mama,
this is the first time we've kissed, isn't it?
Hey Mama,
you'll stay with me forever, right?
Especially now that we're both on the same side.
Rot in hell, bitch!
Mama...
Mama?
Stay with me forever, okay?
Or else, I'll...
Leave her be for now.
Huh?
But I want to beat her up some more.
The party has just begun.
You're right.
Beating up Mama won't be enough to satisfy me.
Now! Come with us!
To the land of happiness!
How do you like my "Mind Crusher Spin"?
Stop!!
No more!
I can't take anymore!
I'm going to die!
We'll always be together, Mama.
It's hot!
My vagina is burning up!
My uterus is going to be ripped apart!
Now, let's go.
Come with us to the land of happiness.
Seems like the big guy finally decided to show up.
You must be Ai-kun.
There's another one, Onii-chan!
You're right.
This is quite convenient for us, Ai-kun.
That's what I should be saying.
I can now take care of both of you at once.
I wouldn't be so sure about that...
We'll meet again, Ai-kun!
Ai!
A-Are you all right!?
You came again?
I thought I told you that you wouldn't be helpful at all.
However, since you're here, please take care of Rin.
I finally found Shin and Mayu.
I'll find their hideout for sure!
Wait!
Ai! Wait!
You're not completely healed yet are you?
Coming!
Meg-Oneesan!
I'm so glad you're back!
Oh, my!
Great timing!
I had gone to the other world for a checkup, and I just now got back!
Here's some mahou manjuu and mahou senbei.
U-Um, Meg-san...?
Akitoshi-chan, do you not like sweet things?
Huh?
Isn't that Rin-chan?
What happened?
I was about to explain...
I see.
Shin and Mayu...
Ai is still injured from when she fought the yuragi.
So please, Meg-Oneesan,
I'm begging you... Help Ai!
So Shin was there...
Meg-Oneesan?
I understand.
Don't worry. I'll bring Ai back.
The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
They're this way.
Below here?
How far does this lead?
Another hole...
That's...
What is this place?
Something's strange...
Their aura disappeared right here...
Tama Water Drainage Station
Ai.
What a relief.
I lost their aura in a large tunnel.
How is Rin doing?
She still hasn't gotten up.
Meg-Oneesan didn't meet up with you?
Meg-Oneesama?
Oh, so Meg-Oneesama...
What the hell?
Who is it? Geez?
Okachin!
I'm going to get you fired for skipping so much!
You just put my name down without my permission!
Today is a big day for our club!
And what are you busy doing!? Inviting girls into your room!?
And two, at that!
You're far too young to be attempting a threesome!
That's not..
Hey, she's doing an interesting cosplay!
Today's event is a costume party, too. I've got good timing!
Okachin, you should cosplay, too.
I'm fine.
Here, why don't you draw an eye on your
forehead and go as a three-eyed dancer?
That sounds so old-fashioned...
Okay, lets roll!
Hurry up and get in!
Okachin, you're going to be cleaning
the place afterwards on your own.
What!?
No way!
Shut it!
This is...!
What smells so horrible, Yukari!?
Incense!
I've gotten hooked on this stuff lately!
Don't you think it's works well for
the Urban Legend Research Club?
7th Annual Kantou Region Urban Legend Research Club Party
And to top it off, these decorations...
Is your taste seriously this bad?
Okachin, you're the one with the bad taste!
You just don't understand the beauty of this setting.
Is everything ready, guys?
People are going to be rolling in here soon!
Yeah!
Okay, how about you two be in charge of reception?
Reception
I'm from the Urban Legend Research Club of East Musashi University.
Welcome!
Please sign here.
What's wrong, Ai?
No, nothing...
A magic circle barrier!
It's been a while,
Meg.
Shin, you...!
Did you really think you'd be able to get away from me?
I won't be controlled by you anymore!
Oh?
That must have been troublesome.
But things won't work out as they did last time.
I'll destroy you!
M-My body won't move!
Everyone!
I'd like to welcome you and begin the seventh
annual Urban Legend Disclosure Party...
hosted by the Urban Legend
Research Club of Ebawa University!
The purpose of this party is for the Urban Legend
Research Clubs from all over the Kantou region...
to gather and share their research gathered over the
past year in order to strengthen our bonds together!
Now!
The first story will be about the Kuchisake-onna
who appears at Jounan University!
Okay, everyone from Jounan University,
please come on stage!
Everyone!
Are you aware that the Kuchisake-onna
has mingled with the crowd at this party?
That's right, the woman who refuses to take off
her mask because she always "has a cold"...
She's the Kuchisake-onna!
According to a student who once took her home,
her mouth opened as wide as her ears,
and she was able to give four simultaneous blowjobs!
It's quite peculiar. Also, her tongue is supposed
to be able to stretch to a length of one meter.
Those who have an orgasm with her
tongue end up being cursed for life!
According to them...
What are they talking about?
It's a club where they attempt to humorize some mysterious tale.
They must be bored...
So, the key here is to make it so that the
Kuchisake-onna is the only one who cums!
If you were unfortunate enough
to have an orgasm by her tongue,
you must hand her fried tofu pierced through with
a rubber band, so that it's like a replacement mask.
For some reason, the Kuchisake-onna hates that!
However, under no circumstance should you
ever hand her rice wrapped in fried tofu!
If you were to do that, she would just swallow it whole!
What is this feeling?
Those who become victims of the Kuchisake-onna...
What a nice position.
A pig's posture is most fitting for a traitor.
I didn't betray you!
It's just that the mind control you had over me was deactivated!
Then in that case, allow me to control you again.
So that it can never be deactivated.
Don't fuck with me...
You won't be able to act strong like that for long.
Next up is Houkei Academy!
Does "Hanako in the Bathroom" prefer
a Japanese toilet or a Western toilet?
You're up!
Huh?
Houkei Academy?
Umm... Umm...
Are you here?
Weird...
Maybe they're in the bathroom?
Oh well.
They might be still getting ready,
so let's have one of our club members
tell us some stupid jokes. Okachin!
Just make something up!
Why, all of the sudden!?
I won't make you clean up on
your own if you can pull this off!
Umm...
So...
What should I talk about?
Oh, right!
About the bizarre incidents that have been occurring in Tokyo lately...
Are you all aware of these things called "Yuragi"?
They're humans who have been turned into monsters
due to being overwhelmed by their desires.
And those monsters just keep-
Huh?
Th-This is...!
I guess that was too difficult for Okachin.
They're yuragi!
M-Mayu!
You're right they are all yuragi.
See? Lots of them.
President!
Could we possibly...
ask that the payment for cleaning yesterday...
be paid with your body instead?
Wh-What the fuck are you talking about?
Hey! Stop!
What are yo-
S-Stop it!
I said, cut it out!
Okachin, there's something wrong with them!
Yukari!
Can I have your cock?
Yukari! You too!?
Okachin...
Hey! Let go!
I want to tease you!
Ai!!
Is that all you've got?
This is what feels like when you give it your all,
Ai-Oneechan!
So what do you say?
Do you feel like working for me again?
Why would I do something like that?
Your breasts are as firm as ever.
You're trash!
Don't touch me!
I'll slice you into ribbons someday!
Oh?
It seems like you've still got some strength left,
even in that position.
Since you're a pig, why don't you oink for me?
Shut up!
You're the one who should be on the
ground, begging me for forgiveness!
Oh, my...
Your beautiful breasts have turned bright red.
Look at all those marks.
People misunderstand me often
but I'm actually quite the feminist.
That's why, look.
I prepared a gift for you.
A liquid that will give you the utmost pleasure.
Wh-What...?
There are lots of yuragi in that liquid.
S-Stop!
It's cold!
Cold liquid is going up inside!
It's yuragi water, after all.
I'm sure they'll wander all around your body, giving you pleasure.
Everybody, are you all fucking?
Today is the day for you all to let
your desires run wild and have sex!
Let out those pent-up feelings
from your daily life and go crazy!
Don't let anything worry you!
Do whatever you want!
You're all fantastic yuragi!
Hooray for yuragi!
I love yuragi!
Yuragi!
We get to live free!
What do you think?
Isn't it great being a yuragi?
Ai-Oneechan, it feels wonderful being a yuragi.
Shut up.
They've just had their souls removed, that's all.
This is the true nature of humans.
They want to have sex...
and let their desires run wild.
Don't you want to do the same?
See? You're wet.
I'll take care of you, Ai-Oneechan.
Stop!
Your mouth might be saying that but your
vagina's wet and looks like it wants it.
Hey!
Lick me!
Lick my pussy more!
Hey! Cut it out!
Look!
You're already a pig!
Now, oink!
Oink...
He-
Please, stop!
Come on, let's fuck!
Your cock is so hard!
N-No!
J-Just a bit further...
Ai! Close your eyes!
Ai! Don't kill them; save them!
I won't...
let you!!!
Thunder!
Ai! Get Mayu!
Mayu!
Ai.
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
So, she got away?
What was that just now...?
Oh, that was something I got from a
friend who's really into the militar-
I found it.
Meg-Oneesama's location.
Wh-What?
Typhoon #25, a large typhoon that just hit Kyushu,
just grazed Shionomisaki and is moving very slowly at a rate of 25km/h.
It is projected to hit Omaezaki sometime tonight.
The air pressure around the center is 915kPa.
Maximum wind velocity is 60km/h.
In some places, precipitation has surged past the 100mm mark in just an hour,
and other places are still being measured.