Meg-Oneesan!
Mahou Shoujo Ai San
The Coming of The Magical Girls
You stay here.
Hang on, Ai!
Why are you coming along!?
I want to be useful, too!
But you're not!
Strange...
It should be here.
Ai!
There's another entrance on the other side!
It's no use.
It's locked.
Step aside.
It's open.
Another passage?
This is the place. The aura of the yuragi...
Ai!
Found it.
What is this!?
I feel nauseous.
It's yuragi miasma.
If an ordinary human stays in there for too long, they'll go crazy.
I know Shin and Mayu are here.
Now, you're mine again.
Oink under my command like you used to in the past.
Yes!
I'm a disgraceful pig.
That's right.
You're just an oinking pig!
No!
That's so...
Do pigs speak!?
N-No...
Oink...
That's right.
You're my toy.
Soon enough, I'll turn both Rin and Ai
into the sex slaves they used to be.
Shin.
This is as far as you get.
Meg-Onee-
Shit!
Was it a trap?
Rin!
Dammit my body won't...!
Why is Rin...
It looks like all three of you have gathered here now.
Now, the new world begins.
What the hell are you thinking?
You won't be able to move for a while after that strike.
Both Meg and Rin are now under my command.
I'm going to need you three to help
me open the door to the new world.
I won't allow things to go your way.
I'll be looking forward to that.
Well then, why don't we begin preparing?
Ai-Oneechan, I'll entertain you even more!
Mayu...
Ai!
What should I do!?
Dammit!
Stop!
Now,
let's give Ai-kun the greatest pleasure she can experience.
R-Rin...!
Don't!
Meg-Oneesama...
Why!?
Rin...
N-No!
R-Rin, stop!
Meg-Oneesama!
Once you three, the strongest magical soldiers, gain happiness,
you will become the foundation for my plan.
Until then, enjoy yourselves.
Stop, Rin...
Meg-Orieesama...
Wake up!
It's no use, Ai-kun.
Both Rin and Meg are under my control now.
If I could move my body, these tentacles would be nothing...!
Meg-Onee-
Please stop Meg-Onee-
No!
It seems like Ai-Oneechan's given up as well.
My stomach... No...
Don't thrust it in like that!
Rin!
I'm at my limit...
With so much friction inside my vagina!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Meg-Onee... No!
My...
My vagina is getting hot!
My womb is going to open up!
No!
My entire body...
I can't even think straight!
N-No!
I'm cumming!
Onee-chans, please give me those droplets
and the blood of the Beatitude.
Chief!
The underground water tanks have gone over the 80% line!
I understand.
Displace the first and second pumps.
Roger.
Beginning displacement of the first and second pumps.
Chief, what about this?
Even if we let the main pump go all out, I'm not sure
whether the displacement will make it in time.
Yeah.
It hasn't rained this much in a hundred years.
Tsukimiya-san.
Tsukimiya-san?
Yes!
I'm currently in front of Roppongi Hills!
The rain is blasting from the side and it's difficult
to even communicate with the people around me!
Huh!?
I see our lone audience finally woke up.
What do you think?
Behold, the three strongest magical
soldiers in a miserable state like this.
That's right your name...
It was... Toshiaki?
Oh, right, Akitoshi-kun,
I'm going to allow you to be the witness for the new era.
What!?
The new era begins now.
In exchange for the lives of these three.
Do you get it,
Akitoshi-Oniichan?
With the blood of these magical soldiers
who have killed countless yuragi,
I'm going to create a new world where yuragi roam free.
No!!
Stop!!
Now,
make them release an abundance of their love juices.
It'll harden like thread and create a cocoon.
A cocoon in which Mayu can rest and be reborn...
as the yuragi of the new era.
The millions of yuragi who have been reduced to grudges
and who are lurking below the earth will be revived.
My ass, it's...
so hot!
Mama, you're amazing!
You're really feeling it!
Stop!
Not my ass!
No more...!
I'm really sensitive after I cum once!
D-Do whatever you want!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
My nipples!
My nipples are so hot!
No!
That feels so good!
Have your way with my entire body!
I'm cumming!
No!
I-I'm cumming!
M-My ass, my pussy, and my womb are so hot!
There!
The cocoon is complete!
Now...
Because of the typhoon,
all trains on the Yamonote line have been stopped.
Yes!
I don't think it'll last for more than ten minutes!
Chief!
The turbine has gone over its limit!
We won't be able to displace any more water!
At this rate, the entire town will be flooded!
I have an idea!
Can we use the second drain?
Well, we haven't performed maintenance on that drain in a long time.
There's no telling if it'll work or not.
Make it work!
How is it?
Yes, the circuit went through, but a couple of motors are dead.
As long as the turbine will move...!
Please work!
Water is filling up the vertical tank.
Thank god!
That alone can buy us half an hour.
That's right.
Suck up all the blood of the three strongest magical soldiers.
Now, the world will be filled with yuragi,
Akitoshi-kun.
What is this?
Who's getting in our way!?
Hyper Regeneration...
Activate!
Ai! Now!
Meg-Oneesama!
How did you...?
You didn't take full control of my heart.
I gave Akitoshi a part of my heart in the past.
The piece is still within him.
And I allowed myself to be violated by you
in order to find out what you were up to.
Shin, I won't forgive you.
How creative.
Dammit!
How dare you trick me.
But it's too late!
What!?
Millions of yuragi have been released on the earth.
Meg-Oneesan!
I'm fine,
but once I use the Hyper Regeneration spell,
it's really hard for me to move around.
So Rin was being controlled through her womb with these...
I won't let you get away, Ai-kun!
No...
No!!
What!?
D-Dammit...!
Ai!
Ai...
Take...
Take my strength!
Ai's...
Ai's being washed away!
I won't let you interfere!
Stop!
Please, stop it!
Who are you!?
Ai's...
Ai's being washed away!
Calm down!
S-Stop the machine!
There... There are people inside!
A-A monster!?
They're not both monsters!
One of them is human!
Shin, I won't forgive you.
You're the one person I won't forgive!
W-Wait!
Like hell I'll wait!
This is it for you.
Dammit!
Ai!
The large-scale typhoon that hit the Kantou region
last night vanished suddenly early this morning.
We're currently looking at data from around the region,
but it could be a phenomenon that has never occurred before.
The violent acts that occurred around the same time seem to have suddenly ceased, as well.
According to scholars, the sudden change in air pressure may have lead to...
M-Meg-Oneesan, where is Ai?
Where are Ai and Shin!?
No way...
Don't worry.
Ai is alive.
We can sense her presence.