The movie was very interesting, wasn't it?
I... I guess so.
It was your first time watching a romance movie, right?
W-Well, it's probably the staple genre to watch for lovers.
Lovers...
You're right, we're sweethearts already.
Ken-chan...
W-What is that?
K-Ken-chan! Ken-chan!
Please hold on! Don't leave me yet!
Ken-chan! Ken-chan!
Am I going to die?
Iori...
My life as her sweetheart is now wasted...
Damn...
Magical Girl Transforms With A Kiss
~To Do It With Someone Other Than My Boyfriend~
Ken-chan, your packed lunch!
Here.
Thanks.
There's a one-set-per-person egg sale at the supermarket today.
Oh, is that so?
So please go with me to the market, okay?
Okay, got it.
Umm, this is...
I'll go on ahead.
I wonder who wrote that letter.
Maybe I can ask her.
Mornin’ Iori!
Good morning, Saeko-chan.
Huh? Wait, is that a love letter?
S-Saeko-chan, your voice is too loud!
Oh, so there are still people who are
sending love letters to you, huh?
So, what does the spouse think?
Who's the spouse you're referring to?
What are you saying?
Have you forgotten the Dream-for-the-Future
essay writing incident?
So, who wrote it?
Well, it's from Higuchi-kun of Class F.
Higuchi? You mean our student council president?
Well, if I was the receiver I'd give a yes right away.
But, what are you going to do?
I'll properly decline the letter.
Jeez, how pathetic of me.
I'm sorry, but I already have someone I like.
I see.
So, that person is Kiritani?
Yes, Ken-chan is the only person for me right now.
Iori...
Ken-chan, did you wait long?
We're going to buy eggs, right?
Yup!
Hey, Iori.
Do you still remember the essay that you wrote
during grade school about the future?
Oficourse, I could never forget.
I'm really sorry about that.
Okay, next is Minakami Iori-chan, can you read your piece?
Okay!
Grade 2 Section 3, Minakami Iori.
My dream for the future, is to be married to Ken-chan.
I want to be Ken-chan's wife in the future.
Jeez, guys you see, tend to be very bashful about those things.
Thanks to that, it took a really long time
before  strengthened my resolve.
You don't need to tell me.
Say what you want, but I realize I've just
been holding on to those feelings.
K-Ken-chan...
Iori, I love you.
I always have, ever since that time.
Iori?
I'm...
I'm just so happy...
Iori, hey...!
What should I do?
Ken-chan!
That feels refreshing.
I wonder what Iori is doing right now?
Iori?
I was wondering what you were doing right now.
Can I come over?
Y-Yeah, okay.
Hey, umm...
We just started dating.
Don't you think this is a bit too early?
I... I think it's never too early.
Because I have had feelings for you ever since we were young.
Iori...
Ken-chan, if it’s you then I'm perfectly fine.
I want to give you everything.
D-Does it hurt?
N-No, I'm okay.
Is this fine?
How is it?
I-It looks really cute, and it suits you.
Thank you.
Iori... I'll be gentle.
I-It feels really embarrassing when you stare like that.
I-I'm sorry.
Can I touch it?
W-Well, do it gently... please.
N-No, not there...!
Sorry.
Can we do it now?
Okay...
Iori, are you okay?
It's alright, I've already decided to have my first time with you.
Iori...
Okay, here I go then.
I-Iori, are you okay?
I'm okay, so just continue.
Iori...
I want to be one with you.
I'll try to hold on.
Are you okay Iori?
Yeah, I'm fine.
We're connected as one now, I'm so happy.
Then I'll continue, but please tell me if it hurts, okay?
It feels kind of weird, Ken-chan.
I'm... Ken-chan...
Ken-chan...
Iori, I'm about to...!
K-Ken-chan... Ken-chan!
Ken-chan...
Iori...
Your first time is now mine, right?
I'm happy, Ken-chan.
Me too.
Ken-chan, it's morning already.
If you don't wake up and eat breakfast you'll be late.
Hey, wake up already.
Umm... Your breakfast is already prepared downstairs,
so just come down and eat it, okay?
I'm really thankful for Iori.
She's taken care of the house while Pops is away.
That wasn't just a dream, right?
Oh well...
Oh, Ken-chan, just wait a bit more, okay?
O-Okay.
Iori being here with me in the kitchen makes me really happy.
These are all my favorites!
I think I may have overdone it a bit.
Here, your rice.
Thank you.
Oh crap, she's really cute.
Eat lots okay, Ken-chan?
Alright!
Mornin', Iori!
Good morning, Saeko-chan.
Hey there.
What happened yesterday after that?
Well, umm... he confessed to me.
I know that already.
I'm asking what did you do?
I bet you dumped him right away, right?
I... I would never do that!
Because I've loved him for a long time!
I was really happy that he did!
I-Iori...!
Oh, I see...
So, who did the confessing?
Why Ken-chan of course!
Congrats!
Our soon-to-be couple is now an official couple!
Official couple... well...
H-Hey, Iori...
I really love it!
Hinata is quite the babe, but Himekawa is really erotic too!
Damn, having a girlfriend like that really makes me feel envious.
Make sure to treat her well, okay?
So Ken, how do our swimsuits look?
Getting a boner, yet?
Wh-What are you saying?!
Woohoo! Boner, boner!
Maybe this sports-type swimsuit isn't erotic enough for you?
Your husband looks a bit unsatisfied, Iori.
W-What are you doing, Saeko-chan?
I'm helping you present yourself better to your husband!
Woohoo!
Saeko, cut the crap already!
Ken-chan, I'll help too.
Oh Iori, thanks.
Oh yeah, Iori...
Do you want to hang out somewhere this Sunday?
Like around a theme park, or to the movies, perhaps?
Ken-chan, is that a date?
Y-Yeah, it is...
Ken-chan!
Yes, I'll go!
I-Iori, that's dangerous!
Ken-chan...
Iori...
O-Oh crap!
We need to put them all away quickly!
Ken-chan, how's my dress today?
It's wonderful.
It's really cute.
The movie was very interesting, wasn't it?
I... I guess so.
I was so moved that I cried a bit.
We used to watch lots of movies together before,
but it was your first time watching a romance movie, right?
W-Well, it’s probably the staple genre to watch for lovers.
Lovers...
You're right, we're sweethearts already.
Actually, I really didn't pay much attention to the movie.
I wasn't able to concentrate because
I was too conscious about you.
Me too.
I wasn't watching the movie, I was watching you.
I'm starting to love you even more with each passing day.
Ken-chan...
W-What is that?
Ken... Ken-chan! Ken-chan!
Please hold on! Don't leave me yet!
No, I don't want to live without you!
Ken-chan! Ken-chan!
Damn...
Am I going to die?
Iori...
My life as  her sweetheart is now waste ...
Damn...
Ken-chan!
Do not lose hope just yet.
That man, do you want to save him?
P-Please help me, please save him!
I can save him, but only if you agree to
become a Magical Girl and defeat him.
Magical Girl?
If you become a Magical Girl, you can save him using your powers.
Of course, you'll have to pay the price of reviving him.
I'll do anything for Ken-chan!
In order to gather energy, you must,
have sex with other men.
Also,
a kiss from me will be required for you to transform.
Can you do it?
S-Sex with other men?
But doing it with someone else other than Ken-chan...
If you don't, he'll die.
Ken-chan... Ken-chan will die?
I don't want that to happen...
I-I'll do anything to save his life.
Then our contract is sealed.
Stop...
Iori, you need to do this to transform into a Magical Girl.
I need to do this...?
T-This outfit?
Iori, there's no time to be surprised.
What? There's a voice inside of me...
We are now united as one.
R-Really?
Iori, here it comes.
Oh no!
No...!
No!
This feels gross..
No, this monster is...!
Oh no, my mind's going blank...
Ken-chan... Ken-chan!
Stop... I'm going to cum...!
If you really hold him dear, then I suggest
you cease fighting from now on.
Stop!
Wait, what in the world...?
Was that a dream?
Even that realistic pain?
Ken-chan, it's morning.
Oh, you're awake already.
That's unusual.
W-Well, sometimes I get up.
Is that so? Well, getting up early is good.
Breakfast is ready so come down already, okay?
Yeah.
What’s going on?
Was that really a dream?
Not only was I dying, but I also saw Iori kiss another guy!
Was that really just a dream?
This might be a bit sudden, but I'll
introduce a new transfer student.
I'm Ragjulius, pleased to meet you.
He's the man from my dream!
What in the world is going on?
That wasn't a dream after all?
Iori, I'm going on ahead.
I-Iori...
Iori, can I talk with you for a moment?
Does Iori know him?
Then that dream...
Hey, wait!
Where did they go?
No, no...
Y-You mustn't...!
I knew it,
you are affected by the Aigul's poison.
Aigul?
I was referring to that monster.
You were bathed in its fluids, right?
Please, stop this already.
You'll become sex craved if you keep that poison within you.
Like this...
Stop, don't fondle me so much...
No, I don't want this...
Iori, the poision can only be extracted by having sex.
You have to prepare for your next battle, correct?
In order to acquire the needed energy as
a Magical Girl, you need to have sex.
But, having sex with someone else other than Ken-chan is...
Once you lose your powers, Ken dies.
He is alive only because of the temporary life force you gave him.
No...!
Iori, are you really okay with him dying?
For Ken-chan, I...
Ken-chan, I'm sorry...
Don't...!
This is terrible...
Ken-chan, I'm sorry.
This is for Ken-chan.
I'm going to save you...
Iori, get more aroused and cum!
You will get stronger that way.
Ken-chan...
Eventually you'll be able to save Ken.
Ken-chan!
Iori, I'm going to cum inside.
No...!
You can't refuse, this the best method to infuse energy into you.
Don't, no. Please, you can't!
Someone else can't cum inside me!
I'm cumming!
Ken-chan, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry...
Where are they?
Iori, where were you?
Ken-chan I'm s-sorry, I was giving him a tour of the school.
Sorry, I asked her to do this.
Ken-chan, I'm sorry.
But someday I'll save you, I promise.