I wonder where Senpai is...
Sweet Magical Sensation!
Boomerang Hoop!
Crystal Explosion!
No!
Mahou Senshi Sweet Knights
~Heroine Rape Order~
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Collectr | Timing: vltouch | TS & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
I have captured you, Sweet Kiss.
Are you awake now, Sweet Kiss?
Who are you?
M-My body won't move.
Resistance is futile.
The Jouma venom contains a relaxant.
Also a sleep aid.
Simply lie back and let me have my way with you.
Let me expose your shameful spot.
No, stop it!
What an adorable pussy.
You're like an unripe fruit.
Stop it, please.
The Magic Knight of Justice is sobbing?
Well, I'm embarrassed.
Embarrassed?
So Sweet Kiss seems to like
having her nipples rubbed.
That's not true!
I just don't like my nipples being touched.
The shock is making me react.
Don't!
Don't lick them!
No, don't!
My body is getting hot...
Apparently the venom has taken effect.
I have a perfectly clear view of your butt too.
Don't! Please don't look at my butthole!
Don't touch me there!
Don't!
Don't put your fingers in!
No. Stop it!
If you do that, I feel like I have to... have to pee!
Don't!
Don't lick me!
Erotic juice... Naughty juice is flowing out.
It seems as though you've
succumbed to passion at last.
That's not true at all!
It's about time for me to taste
this unripe nectar of yours.
Take a look...
at this firm flesh rod.
I-I don't wanna look at it!
That's because your body resists me.
Don't! Don't put it inside!
Please, stop!
You're so... tight inside.
No. Don't!
That hurts!
That hurts...
How is it, Sweet Kiss?
How does it feel to experience the same
pleasure that I gave to Sweet Lip?
I won't be conquered. I won't let you defeat me!
Don't move me so roughly.
No!
It'll come out!
Naughty juice will come gushing out!
Oh, no!
It's hitting me.
Hitting me all the way... deep inside.
I feel it.
It's throbbing... throbbing inside my pussy!
Oh, no!
A knight mustn't experience sexual pleasure!
I'll completely fill you with erotic pleasure!
No, don't!
Oh... Oh, no!
I feel something sloppy inside my pussy.
It's so hot.
Now, both Sweet Knights have lost their virginity.
But we still won't lose.
We won't give up hope,
no matter what you do to us.
W-We won't be defeated!
So you really are the knights
that the goddess chose.
I suppose you won't fall so easily.
Mezger-sama, may I partake of her next?
I don't mind.
Have your way with her all you want.
No!
Go forth!
Not so fast!
Sweet Magical Sensation!
I am Sweet Lip, a Magic Knight
fighting for Love and Justice.
Sweet Thunder Attack!
Damn!
Crescent Hurricane!
Justice Evolution!
Senpai!
Mezger...
Not only did you shame me,
but you also shamed Sweet Kiss?
You'll pay dearly for this.
Can you make me?
Justice always prevails.
Justice Evolution!
Crescent Hurricane!
Trying this again and again is useless.
Wouldn't you rather taste my flesh rod again?
Sweet Lip...
You're running away, Mezger?
I will retreat for today.
In order to defile the white, supple bodies that
lie beneath those sacred battle clothes,
we will appear before you time and time again.
Next time, I will pleasure both of
you at once. Look forward to it.
See you later.
Mezger!
Kanaha-chan!
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry I didn't show up sooner.
I'm fine, Ririko-senpai.
I won't let something like this get me down.
That's right!
We're the Magic Knights of Love and Justice!
With our powers combined, Mezger
will be brought down!
Yes. I'll try my hardest.
And so, Paris still has problems today.
Looking at modern society, it's evident that
past struggles are influencing the present.
Like their relations with England...
She really interests me.
Sakura Airi...
I need to investigate her for a while.
I wonder how much longer she'll
be able to endure our lust.
Impertinent brutes!
Sweet Thunder Attack!
Crescent Hurricane!
So you've finally shown yourself, Mezger.
This time you won't defeat me!
I've changed my battle plans a little.
Look.
That's dirty!
You're using a hostage.
If you want to save this girl, then do as I say.
Let go of her!
Shall I slice this girl to bits right here?
You... you wouldn't!
Remember, as we planned from the start.
P-Please stop it!
Help me!
P-Please stop it.
I don't care what happens to me.
Just... please let her go!
Please!
You'll do anything, right?
Anything. I'll do anything you ask.
Okay.
Then suck me off.
Make me feel good.
Lick it systematically, then
squeeze your lips around it.
I... I can't do that!
Wait!
I'll do it.
Then come over here.
Tell me what you're going to do.
I-I'm going to suck it...
In my mouth...
Gently, with my tongue and lips.
How, exactly?
Very well.
Then let's begin.
No!
Don't do it!
You look very nice, Sweet Lip.
Ask her to look at you.
Please look at me.
Are you watching?
I'm licking... a man's large thing...
I'm licking it erotically with my tongue.
The pretty knight of justice sure has
some dirty skills in her bag of tricks.
Don't touch it!
You're soaking wet.
Don't put your fingers in!
I'm cumming.
Swallow it!
How the mighty have fallen, Sweet Lip!
To see my snot-like cum in your mouth.
You must simply love the taste of it.
I did as you said.
So please... let her go.
I can't do that, I'm afraid.
But you...
You promised you'd let her go
if I did as you asked!
That's right.
But there's still one thing missing.
Do one more thing for me,
and then I'll release her.
Please... h-help me!
I-I understand.
This time, what is your biddin...
Wh-What did you do?
Now, let's go.
Wh-Where?
I wish to know your true identity.
What should I do?
I want you to masturbate for me.
Right here?
Yes, that's right.
You want everyone to watch, don't you?
You want all the humans
you protect to watch you.
I can't... I can't do that.
That hurts!
S-Stop it!
Very well.
Then let's begin.
Hurry it up.
Ouch!
No, stop it!
I'll do it.
I'll do it, okay?
Stop being so rough with her!
We want to see it better.
Show some enthusiasm.
I-I feel strange.
My body is hot.
The Jouma venom seems to
have taken full effect now.
Their venom has three levels to it.
Now, take off your underwear.
This is so embarrassing.
Your other hand isn't playing along.
My body is... enjoying this against my will.
Use it.
B-But I can't!
Yes, you can!
Suck on it.
That girl... What's she doing right there?
Could it be... she's masturbating?
Please... don't look at me.
Don't stop!
Face them all and explain to them
what you're doing as you proceed.
B-But I...
Don't you care what happens to the hostage?
W-Wait!
I'll do it.
This hard thing is... hitting inside...
My nipples are getting hard.
Hey, isn't that a Sweet Knight?
Whoa, you're right!
This is the first time I've seen the real thing.
But the Sweet Knights are superheroes, right?
Should she really be doing that
sort of thing in public?
Still, this is really starting to get me off.
I can't stand it!
Such a sweet-looking girl is doing that.
It's inside!
Inside my pussy... It's going inside!
A thick and hard thing is...
Going in and out..
Oh, no.
I don't want to like it.
But...
Y-Yes!
This feels great!
Oh, I'm cumming.
The hard, big thing is...
Oh, no!
I don't want to like it!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Wh-Whoa, shit!
I'm kinda scared now.
This has to be an illusion.
Let's get out of here!
I-I did exactly as you said.
So now, you'll release her, won't you?
I am a man of honor. I don't go back on my word.
However, I wonder what this girl has to say...
This girl is my slave.
Nice to meet you, pretty knight of justice.
Th-This can't be!
You liar!
If you wish to hate someone,
hate yourself for letting
your self-righteous beliefs
interfere with your judgment.
M-Mezger.
The battle isn't over yet.
No matter how much you shame me, I will protect
this school from you and your organization!
Your proud face is also cute.
I will leave for today.
But in time, we will appear before you again.
Wait!
Mezger!
I still have some fight left in me.
I won't let Mezger defeat me.
I swear!
She still entices me... Sakura Airi.
Perhaps I should test her.
I'm leaving this place.
Call my servants.
Yes, lord.
So you've appeared once again,
Magical Syndicate Zero.
Here I go!
Queen's Rod!
Sweet Mystic Flash!
Wild Temptation!
If you're there, please show yourself.
As I thought.
So the leader finally shows himself.
So you are the third Sweet Knight?
I'm sorry for the late introduction.
I am the leader of the goddess Konoedan's 13th
squadron of knights, the Sweet Knights.
I am Sweet Rouge, a Magic Knight
fighting for Love and Beauty.
Sweet Rouge?
And the leader of the Sweet Knights?
I hope we can be good enemies.
Then why didn't you rescue Ririko and
the others when they were in trouble?
They may possess virtuous
hearts filled with justice,
but their magical powers are still immature.
So I subjected them to harsh battles
to complete their training.
Oh, I see.
Your greedy desires will never come
to fruition as long as we are here!
I will end things for today.
But in time, you will see me again.
And you will see me ruling the world.
Come back here!
Kokono.
Capture Kanaha.
Prepare for it.
Yes, lord.
But... before that... I want to...
You want my flesh rod?
Yes.
Be patient.
Kanaha's capture is our top priority.
Very well.
I guess she wouldn't be here at this time.
Homura-senpai!
What's wrong? Why are you here so late?
Well... I was hoping I'd run into you, actually.
Can we talk for a bit?
I'd love to!
What's wrong?
I don't like this place.
Why not?
A horrible thing happened to me here.
A horrible thing?
I was attacked here.
Ririko-senpai rescued me, but...
I'm scared!
I'm trying my best as a Sweet Knight,
but I'm losing my confidence.
Don't worry.
Yuzuki Kanaha. You are strong.
Senpai...
I won't forget it.
I'll never forget your kiss.
From now on... forever...
You are...
I'm taking you back to base.
Now, preparations are under way.
I'll be waiting, Nanase Ririko, Sakura Airi.
kinou no kuchizuke mada setsunakute hitori nemuru beddo de furueru
Yesterday's kiss is still painful. The bed I sleep in alone shivers.
ashita mo issho ni kono te tsunaide anata to nemuru yume no naka de
I'm lost in a dream of tomorrow, holding hands with you as we sleep.
sekai ga futari dake ni natte mo ai o tsukurotte ikite yukeru
Even if we're the last two people in this
world, love will mend everything.
sekai ga futari o yurusanakute mo ai no kusari o hanasanai de
Even if the world won't forgive us,
please don't release our chains of love.
mahou ga watashi o hadaka ni suru hikari no naka de umare kawaru
Magic makes me naked. I will be reborn in the light.
mahou ga watashi o otona ni kaeru anata no tame ni kirei ni nareru
Magic makes me an adult. I will become prettier for you.
kiss in the sweet nights kono omoi o todokete hoshii
Kiss in the sweet nights. I want these feelings to reach you.
kiss in the sweet nights zutto amai yoru ga tsuzuku you ni
Kiss in the sweet nights. I hope these sweet nights continue forever.