It has been three days since I became his maid.
Again today I will be the best maid ever!
Oni-chan was my friend growing up.
He is a little lecher, but the man of my dreams.
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
Train me!
When I come home after working long hours,
inside waiting is the maid of every man's dreams.
Plus, she has big tits!
I don't have any regrets in my life!
I'm back.
Welcome back Oni-chan!
you want to eat or take a bath?
or do you...
First, I want these big breasts...
Oni-chan, what would you like?
You were so innocent, Nagisa.
you're so grown up now
A big breasted maid, what all Japanese men's dreams are made of.
I'm going to teach her what it is to be a maid.
I'm going to wash your back.
Oh, yeah.
Nagisa, you want to be a real maid?
Yeah, of course.
My dream was to be your maid since I was little.
From now on, you have to call me "Master".
You have to obey all my orders.
You got it?
Uh....from now on?
Yeah.
Whenever?
Of course, you're a maid, right?
There is a passage in the maid guide book.
That's a fib.
What did you say, huh?
No, nothing, master.
Ah.... it feels good!
Your hands are great!
Wait a little bit.
I'm going to bring it now
Don't spill it.
What? What are you going to do?
Don't worry.
Ah...
Oni-chan, it's cold.
I told you before.
You're now a maid and I am...
Master...
Ah...Ahh!
Master... that is...
You haven't put anything in here besides me, right?
No, only yours, master.
So, this is for my private use, right?.
But...are you going to put that in?
I'm not ready yet.
This is our special first time, so...
Ummmm, a little bit more....
It's hard to put this in, unless you drop your panties.
But, my hands...
Don't you want this in you?
As a maid...
that's what you desire...
Don't you want to be a real maid?
Ummm....
Yes, master.
You're really lecherous.
Gyrate your hips more.
Yes, master.
I can't see if you don't spread your legs.
Let me see you move, boldly and sexually.
Great! Woof!
It's the power of the maid, isn't it?
Ah....
Uhh.....
Master, it's going to spill.
Your cum has already spilled.
Ah...
I told you don't spill.
This is a punishment for you.
Okay, lie down now and open your legs.
Take off your dress and show me your breasts.
Now show me your ass.
Yes, master.
Master, I can't.....
Not yet. Do this first.
Lesson one, lick it slowly
Umm, it's good for the first time.
Okay, suck it now.
Lick it as you suck me deeper.
Now move your head.
You can't hold it?
As a master, I know everything about my maid!
Ah!
Ah... no... I'm going to cum...
Ah....
Not yet.
you're a maid, so you can't cum without my permission.
You have to make me cum first if you want to.
Umm, this is a maid's skill.
You're doing good!
I'm cumming.
Gosh, he's so perverted and dirty minded.
I wonder if he's really smart or not.
Um.....
Master, no more...
I was right.
The maid needs a vibrator.
The vibrator needs a maid.
How wet are you now?
Open your legs, and show it to your master
It's drenched.
Master, please, no more....
I'm embarrassed...
Don't depend on people.
You're going to cum alone.
Very well.
I'm a nice master, so this is special.
My pussy is being watched....
Good! Ah, ah!
I'm cumming!
Ah...
You're only wearing this tomorrow Okay?
Without underwear
Yes, master.
Today I have to work in this because its Oni-chan's order
He is really leecherous.
No one is here, but l'm a little nervous.
What? Who?
Matsudo-san, a delivery for you.
Yes, I'll be right there.
Ah...what should I do?
Is this the famous naked apron?
Where is the delivery?
Here it is.
I need your seal or your signature.
Ah, from Oni-chan?
Thank you very much.
I really was being watched.
I wonder if Oni-chan imagining how I look.
Tonight we're going to the park, so put this on and wait for me.
Nagisa... I wonder if she's wearing it.
If not...
No, it's okay.
Master's order is absolute.
I'm back.
Welcome back, master.
Drink more. More!
Oops, I need to have this for our walk.
Okay, let's go.
It's cold and tasty. Drink it right away
But, my stomach....
I'm your master and you're my maid.
Okay?
Yes, I understand, master.
Take off your coat, and show me your beautiful body.
Someone may come.
Hurry!
Your master is not happy with that pose.
Open your legs wider
Turn sideways, and lean forward.
Turn your back towards me.
Stick your ass out.
Open your legs wider
Oh, what?
Are you feeling it already?
You are a real maid.
Come here.
Hurry up!
You know what I want to say
Yes.
Yeah, good...
Maid's lips, maid's tongue.
Master, let me go to the bathroom.
In the middle of service, are you going to walk out?
No, no. You have to do it here while sucking.
But, the underwear you gave me...
No problem!
You're going to wash it.
What's the matter?
Be serious.
Come on.
Oh, no, I'm going to pee!
Don't stop sucking!
You can pee anytime.
I'm not finished even if you're done.
After the appetizer is the main dish!
I'm cumming!
I told you, I'm not done yet!
Found my panties.
Nagisa.
Yes, master.
That is mine...
So, open your mouth wide.
You stay right there.
I'll let you experience traditional Japanese entertainment.
Something like austere refinement and quiet simplicity
You know what to do with this, right?
I can't do anything about him...
But, I'm a little excited.