Oni-chan, who said, ''I like maids with big tits'',
is definitely a pervert.
So l said, ''I'll be yourmaid!''
I've realized that
I'm perverted too.
That's how I became a maid.
Now that I started,
it's rough!
Oni-chan says,
''Referto me as
Master!''
Or that,
''A maid must absolutely obey their Master!''
He keeps on going!
On top of that, his demands at night are unbelievable!
I wish he'd be thoughtful
of me having to clean my uniform.
But...
I love Oni-chan
so much!
I'm the best maid
for Oni-chan
in the world.
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Master!
Corrupt me more.
SERVE! And SERVE!
When did he learn this stuff?
He's a genius at perversion.
He digs it into my pussy and turns me on.
A little stimulation,
and I can't stand anymore.
I've become Oni-chan's toy.
This is what it is to be a maid.
That's too much. Stop it.
I'm starting to like the pain.
l'm scared.
My pussy juice won't stop.
Oni-chan, I need to cum.
Otherwise, I'll go crazy.
Oni-chan, you're going to put that up my ass?
Oh no. I'm going to cum on a banana.
Look at that!
That dildo is so thick!
You're going to break my cunt!
My Master hasn't cum yet. I shouldn't cum before him.
Oni-chan...
Is this some kind ofjoke?
What's this?
Oni...Master...
Where...
Where are you?
Is that you, Master?
What? Really?
You can see into my pussy hole.
I'm getting horny.
No. I'm not turned on.
My whole body is turned on.
I'm going to cum right away.
Um...
But, we just did it.
If Master isn't satisfied, neither am I.
Please torment me until Master is satisfied.
Please, Master.
Please torment me more.
Master's fingers.
I just came.
And I'm going to cum again.
He's ravaging my body.
I need your cock. Put your thick dick up my pussy.
Oni-chan!
Master...
I beg you.
I beg you, Master.
Please stick it in my pussy!
Please put your cock in my hole.
Master...
Yeah.
Yeah!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
That was awesome last night. I came so many times.
Oni-chan has more up his sleeve.
This is real hardcore and it makes me dizzy.
Yes...
Master.
Master, my stomach aches.
Master...
Please don't.
No, please.
If you keep doing that...
Oh, no.
I have to shit.
Oh no. It's going to smell.
So please...
Please let me go to the toilet.
I beg you, let me go.
My ass is going to explode.
Oni-chan, sometimes you're the devil.
This is so hard. But it feels so good.
Master...
please...
Oh, no. I can't hold it anymore.
My ass gets turned on when I walk.
This is so weird.
My pussy's getting wet.
Yes, Master.
Oni-chan, you want to watch me take a shit.
I'm a total slut.
Yes.
Master, please watch.
Seeing your dick get so big and hard after watching me take a shit,
makes me so happy!
Your cum tastes so good. I love it.
Yes... Master.
Oni-chan's demands
have increased everyday.
Why do I love this person?
The thing is, I love him even more.
It's digging into my pussy lips.
I guess I'm perverted.
Oni-chan's...
My dear Master's nice smell.
Master.
Hurt me more.
I've become perverted.
Fuck me, fuck me!
Master, please...
torture my pussy!
No. Not yet.
Deeper. Stick it in deeper.
I did it again.
I wish he'd come home.
Master.
Then we could do all sorts of perversions.
I'm the only submissive maid in the whole world, who can satisfy my horny Master.
l have to show Master that l'm a maid.
A submissive maid.
So this is the least I could do.
Welcome home, Master.
Master, please take me for a walk.
Sometimes, Oni-chan is in his own world.
I can't always keep up with him.
It may be the most perverted part of my master, the hentai.
Yes, please.
When Oni-chan ties me up,
my pussy gets turned on.
Yes, I'm happy.
Master, don't look at me like that.
My pussy juice is coming out.
Master wants to show my submission
to perfect strangers.
Yes.
I hope my body looks beautiful.
Master wants to show off my horny body.
Master? Isn't my body something else?
I haven't cum yet. I'm hanging in there.
I will fulfill my mission as a maid.
Thanks to Master's teachings,
my mouth has become real nasty.
I'll suck harder.
Teach me more.
I want to suck more cock.
But my ass is getting hot.
Any hole you desire, Master.
It hurts.
Yeah! Awesome!
Pinch my clit!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, Master!
Master!
I'm cumming!
So much of Master's thick hot cum, deep in my pussy.
Hot cum is oozing out.
Yes. I'll be right there.
Oh, yes.
Why is Oni-chan so nervous?
Weird.
Um, my birthday was three months ago.
Thank you, Oni-chan!
I also have something.
It's different from Oni-chan's present,
but I know he'll appreciate my sincerity.
Master, please.
I've become a complete submissive pervert. What a fool.
But it feels good, and I'm with Oni-chan, whom I love.
It's alright!
Always having a wet pussy is great!
DlD YOU CUM ALOT?