Next is Momozono Momo-san.
Umm, chief, I'm still...
Don't waste time now, Momo-san.
It's already your turn.
What...?
She just came in today, so I suppose it's
her first time meeting the Master?
Oh, that's true.
It's a bit strange for her to be a head maid
candidate despite being a newbie.
S-So this isn't a maid cafe after all!
The interview yesterday was also quite odd.
My apologies for not explaining in full.
However, we saw potential lurking inside of you.
You were the pervy kid who always visited Benson before!
Wait, why in the world are you here?
Momozono Momo?!
It's been a while, but that's quite the terrible greeting.
Anyway, you sure grew up to be a fine woman.
Momo-san, regardless of your past circumstances, you're now
in the process of being hired as an
official maid of this residence.
I request you uphold respect when speaking with the Master.
She's right.
Anyway, in celebration of our reunion,
why don't you give me a good tit fuck?
Master, that is one of the three primary techniques.
What are you talking about?
Oh? You don't know anything about it?
See? You use your boobs like this...
You pervy fiend!
My, my, my. I told you so.
You've dug you own hole, Master.
Ow, ow, ow...
That was a nice right punch there.
But I'm not really thrilled with you
punching your Master like that.
Master, are you alright?
Oh yeah!
All of your debts were actually now transferred to me.
I'm willing to consider no longer requiring you to pay the
capital amount because we're childhood acquaintances,
but if you quit now...
So I have to pay my debts to you from now on?
Such a delightful deal yes?
I believe there is no other job out there as special as this.
I apologize for what happened earlier, Master.
I shall be the one who will discipline her from now on,
so please forgive her.
Don't worry about it.
It's nothing.
Now then, if you'll excuse me.
Maybe you're the one who needs disciplining?
You're a dunce, perv, and a lecher!
You can still speak like that?
What a stubborn woman you are.
Anyway, got something you need?
Calling me out to this place.
When I ask to be alone with a woman in
a private room, it only means one thing.
Huh?
I'll ask just in case, you're a virgin, right?
Wh-What are you trying to ask me?
I can't believe you've still yet to meet a man at that age.
Ms. Thousand-year-old Fossil.
Stop saying such nonsense, you shitty fiend!
I want you to be more honest with yourself, though.
What?
This is why it's so troublesome dealing with new girls.
Isn't it about the time of day for us to 'watch over'?
Watch over?
Now, come closer.
What the hell are you doing?
Wow, your left punch is also amazing.
Hey, what are you...?
What are you doing?
Momo-san, you're now about to be lectured about proper
service, by none other than the Master himself.
Ow ow! That hurts, you know!
It's going to feel good soon enough.
No, wh-where are you trying to touch me?
No... no...!
No, don't put it in...
Please stop...
Don't rub my breasts like that.
You're moaning erotically, don't you feel embarrassed?
No, this is not me...
Well then, how about this?
No don't, please don't look...!
Not there!
I feel like something's going to burst out.
It's my first time feeling like this.
My part down there feels all tingly.
It feels weird.
My mind is going completely blank.
You're about to cum... wait, it's already there.
Something's coming!
Oh no!
Momo, you seem more docile now after cumming.
Now we just have to leave the rest to the Master.
I would request that you maintain restrai-
I know, I know.
She's my precious maid.
I'll take real good care of her.
This thick and stiff thing is now between my breasts.
It's being squeezed in the middle.
No, don't!
Please don't rub my breasts onto your dick like that...
Seems your body is actually feeling good with it.
Don't fondle it too hard.
Your dick feels very hot.
I'm almost there!
I'm about to cum!
So this is hot cum?
It has a bitter taste, what is this?
But, it's tasty.
Momo, you're actually very erotic!
What now? This kinda feels ticklish.
You're quite wet now, so I bet this will no longer hurt.
Come now, lower your hips more.
What's this?
It feels as if this stiff thing is filling me inside.
Ouch! Stop, stop!
Your dick has penetrated me all the way inside.
I'm going to move now.
This feeling, it's the first time I've felt like this.
Oh no...
It feels good as your dick rubs inside my pussy.
I'm losing my mind!
Momo,
I'm cumming now.
Me too, I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
How is it, Xiao Mei-san?
Have we already decided on our main dish yet?
Oh my, what shall I cook indeed?
Nothing good is coming to mind.
If it's troubling you that much,
then why didn't you consult me?
Aoi, do you have something in mind?
You see...
Oh, that's a nice idea!
Ah yes,
you're going to help out with this as well.
Me too?
I feel somewhat uneasy about this, though.
Everyone, I believe that you are all
already enjoying the festivities,
and so, it is already time to present our main dish.
Mikage, to keep this dish a secret even from me...
You sure this is going to be alright?
Hey, Mikage, this is...!
Master, we now present to you, Japan's nyotaimori,
the traditional human platter.
Well then, I shall have the honor of taking the first bite.
Oh, this isn't just an ordinary xiaolongbao bun!
As expected of you, Master.
This is a new recipe.
Only small quantities of regular meat are used,
and instead it is filled with top quality foie gras.
Then how about here?
H-Hey, where are you touching me?
It tickles.
Oopsie.
Impressive, Xiao Mei.
Your cooking is top notch.
And this human platter...
You are indeed my maids.
Now everyone, please behold our wonderful human platters.
Oh my, such predictable old men.
This looks like sweet and sour pork.
Th-That's...
A type of Italian dish which is...
Oh, I see...
And this is... puffer fish sashimi.
Oh no, the food is going to fall off.
That's... not food, sir.
Oh, my apologies, it looked like a very delicious piece of cherry.
I wonder what kind of delicacies are hidden under here?
Well, well, it's Shaoxing wine!
You're supposed to use a small cup to drink from it...
You mean like this?
It'll be embarrassing if you mix it like that.
No more, please!
We can't hold back anymore!
Hey, wait, no!
Please, gentlemen, we would like you
to refrain from touching the maids.
My, oh my, looks like I will have to deal with these men myself.
I wonder what happened to our guests...
Everyone looks so surprised.
Master, our guests seem quite fatigued already.
I suggest cutting the festivities short for tonight.
O-Okay.
Looks like your last job as head maid ended without a hitch.
If not for you, the guests wouldn't have
enjoyed themselves so much earlier.
Please praise everyone else as well.
You're right.
Looks like choosing the next head maid from now on,
will be another one of my troubles for the coming days.
Good morning, Aoi.
Did you get a good night's sleep?
Hey, what is the meaning of this?
I said, what are you planning with this?
It's exactly as you see.
You're supposed to be the one who knows
the purpose of this room best, right?
Why do I have to be tortured like this?
Listen, Aoi.
This isn't torture.
It's punishment.
I don't understand what you mean.
Just unbind me from these ropes already!
Xiao Mei and Momo's bodies were completely exposed
to those old timer bastards during the last party.
It's just not fair for you not to share in the pain as well.
My breasts are going to be torn off!
Then why don't we make them feel better?
It hurts... they're getting torn apart!
My breasts are really going to be ripped off!
Then how about here?
Stop, please stop this vibrator!
Now, I think it's about time I start enjoying this myself.
No, it hurts, please, not my ass!
Pull it out.
I beg of you, please pull it out!
My ass is in pain!
It's so tight that I can't pull out.
Try to relax, Aoi.
Good girl, Aoi.
How terrible, you tricked me!
I'm...!
What? You're were screaming in pain just a while earlier.
Are you getting horny now?
You slutty maid!
I'll... never forgive you.
I'm your Master.
Looks like I need to punish you more.
I'm going to cum from my ass!
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum it all inside.
No, please don't!
I'm about to...
Cum from my ass!