Welcome home, Master!
The Master is wound up pretty tight this morning.
Just what happened?
No matter what he does, he goes full-steam ahead!
It's almost like he's a spy!
Keep it down. We're working now, you know.
Are you sure about this, Master?
Holding a party for the members of your orgamzation
without even informing the staff first...
I'm using my own estate.
I'll do as I please.
I'll stake our family's name on showing
them a night they'll never forget.
I realize nothing I say will sway you, but...
That's the Mikage I know.
You were always the one who understood me best.
Oh my! Have you decided to pay me some attention after all?
I see you've become a fully fledged man at last,
Young Master.
Hey, now! Don't treat me like a kid all of a sudden.
By the way, the time has come for
you to choose my successor.
I suppose that's true, but
there aren't many people who could take your place.
With my husband returning soon from abroad,
this party would be the perfect occasion.
I have gathered all the household's maids for you.
Please, choose your favorite from among them.
You'll stay on this until the end, won't you, Mikage?
Maid-san and the Spirit
of her Bonneing Tits
Pardon my intrusion, Master.
Mikage, is that you? Please come in.
Oh? Mi-Mikage?!
That outfit...
I'll be gone soon, so I want to give you a special treat.
I was worried what would you think if I wore this
outfit before some other maid came but...
Not at all! I wish you'd always dressed that way.
You've got me hard.
Oh my!
No need for you to exert yourself, sir.
Now then, Master... Or should I say, Young
Master? Please do as you like with me.
Mikage!
You're so fierce!
There's no doubt, Young Master, tits are what you love most.
Having such glorious tits in front of you
when your first sexual urges start,
anyone would get a kink for big boobs.
But if you stroke me so hard and suck me off
like that, my milk's gonna squirt all over you!
That's what I like to hear! Let's see how much you've got.
I'll drink all of the milk I get!
No, Young Master...! If you keep
going, I can't hold it any longer!
Amazing! You're amazing, Mikage!
Mikage, tasting your milk after so long is the best!
Now you really do sound like a child, Young Master.
Has our young lord really grown so tall and strong?
I'm so proud to have served you, now that
I can see you as such a splendid man.
Mikage, your boobs are so soft and supple,
you've got my cock under you spell!
Oh, your willy, Young Master!
I can feel it twitching between my tits.
Fuck, I'm about to come!
That's right, Young Master! Please, don't hold
back! Let everything inside you shoot out!
Oh my! You really were loaded.
But just this won't be enough to satisfy
you. Am I right, Young Master?
Of course it's not! Don't write me off like that!
Young Master! How many times have I told
you, you must be gentle with a lady?!
Don't be stupid! You expect me to calm
down after seeing you like this?
Honestly! You're such a spoiled child.
Well then, would you close the curtains?
If they stay open, everyone will see us like this.
In that case, why don't we really give them something to see?
Must you, Young Master?!
What would the servants say, to see the Master
having his way with the Head Maid?
It's stunning, what a fine young man you've become!
My Young Master's little cock has
grown so swollen and flushed!
I'm already trembling! Please, enjoy your
fill of me to your heart's content!
Well then, here I go!
You're thrusting your dick so deep in
my pussy, I can feel it in my womb!
But your pussy doesn't feel surprised!
You keep gripping me tighter and tighter.
It feels so good, I might just blow!
Sir, I think my pussy might cum before your cock!
Oh, like that... Just like that, Young Master!
It's so good when you do that. My pussy
just wants to drink up all of your juice!
Mikage! You'd better take in every drop of cum I give you!
Young Master! Please give it to me,
all at once, while you get me off!
When you ride me so hard, every part of my
pussy feels like it could cum any second!
Mikage!!
Young Master, there's nothing more I need to teach you.
Well then, Master, we'll begin selection shortly.
This audition is a critical part of choosing the new Head Maid,
so please judge seriously, with full diligence.
I get it, I get it.
As I present the candidates for Head Maid,
I will ask you to judge their Three Skills.
"Three Skills?"
Within the maid industry, these are taught as the
three greatest services we can do for our Master.
Now, Aoi-san, if you please!
Alright, Master. I'll lay it all out in
front of you, so prepare yourself.
Hm? Just what should I be prepared for?
Please, come on in.
You're so tight!
The first of the Three Skills:
the maid's pussy will grip you as tightly as it can.
I-I get it! I understand, so please loosen it up a bit.
Now, Shao Mei-san, please.
Hi!
Master! I don't really get it, but is this good?
The second of the Three Skill:
a special fellatio.
It's a technique far greater than vacuum
fellatio or a rolling tornado.
Once it grips you, it won't let go until you ejaculate.
I've never felt a throbbing like this before!
Wh-What is this?
Next is Momozono Momo-san.
Eh? But Madam...!
No dawdling, now!
Momo-san, it's your turn.
What?
That girl just came here today.
Isn't this her first time meeting the Master?
I'm pretty sure it is!
She's auditioning for Head Maid, even
though she's brand new? How weird!
This place isn't actually a maid cafe, is it?
I thought something was weird when you hired me yesterday.
I apologize for not telling you,
but I have high hopes for you, in many ways.
Huh? Eehh?!
You! You're the perverted kid who used
to come to our villa every day!
Wh-Why? Why are you here?!
You're Momozono Momo?!
What a rude greeting, after not seeing each other in years.
But still, you've grown up into a fine woman.
Momo-san, no matter what happened in the past,
here and now, you are a newly hired maid.
You must address your Master in a respectful manner.
That's right! In any case, maybe I'll have you
do a titty fuck to celebrate our reunion.
Master, that technique is the third of the Three Skills.
What is that?
What? You don't even know something like that?
Here, it's when you use your boobs like this...
Yo-You horny beast!
Oh my, I told him so!
You reap what you sow, Master.
Ouch! You've got a good right hook, don't you?
But you won't win points for hitting
your Master right off the bat.
Are you alright, Master?
Now I remember!
I paid all of your debts!
I'd been planning to forgive the expenses
since you're a childhood friend,
but if you plan to quit...
Then, I'd have to pay off my debts back to you?
Aren't you happy? You won't get
a great offer like this anywhere.
I apologize for what happened earlier, Master.
I will take full responsibility for disciplining the girl,
so please forgive her.
Don't worry! It's a minor detail.
Well then, I'll excuse myself.
Aren't you the one who needs discipline here?
You're an idiot, you're horny, and a big pervert!
If you can say things like that, I guess you're
the same strong-willed woman I knew.
Anyway, what do you need me for?
You're the one who called me here.
Coming alone to a man's private chambers,
there's only one thing it could be, right?
Huh?
And just to be sure, I have to ask. You're a virgin, right?
Wh-wh-what are you saying?!
Reaching your age without touching a man!
Girls so guarded are an endangered species!
Don't say such stupid things, you sexually-harrassing brute!
I'll have you show more of your true colors from now on.
H-Huh?!
See, this is the kind of childishness I can't allow.
Isn't it about time you learned to take care of a man?
By "take care", you mean...
Come on, come a bit closer...
What the hell are you doing?!
You punch pretty hard with your left, too, Momo!
What? Wait! What are you doing?
Momo-san, allow us to train you in how
best to serve your Master from here on.
But that hurts! It hurts!
I promise, it'll start feeling good soon!
No! Wh-Where are you touching me?!
No... No!!
No! Don't touch me there!
Please, stop!
Don't play with my boobs like that!
Aren't you embarrassed, letting out such a filthy moan?
That's... That's not me!
Oh, really? And what's this, then?
No! Don't! Don't look at me!
Not there!
It's so strange! My body feels so strange!
I've never felt this before!
Where you're touching me, it's throbbing...
Something's wrong! My mind is going blank...!
When you're about to climax, everyone feels that way.
So-Something's happening! N-No!
You're so obedient when that excess strength is gone, Momo.
I will leave the rest to you, Master.
Please don't be too rough with her.
I know!
Momo is my precious maid. I'll take good care of her.
Translator: Maq-kun | Lpin
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Punk4Real