It has been three days since I became his maid.
Again today I will be the best maid ever.
Oni-chan was my friend growing up.
He is a little lecher,but the man of my dreams.
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
Train me!
Pretty soon, he'll be back from work.
It's my job to greet him after his long day at work.
but sometimes, his face glows with perversion.
Welcome back Oni-chan!
You want to eat or take a bath?
or...
Well, which are you deciding on?
I found out after becoming his maid that he is obsessed with big tittys.
since when is he so obsessed with big breasts?
I'm going to wash your back.
His penis is already so big.
I wonder what he is thinking.
He was probably thinking about fucking my big tits.
that must be it.
Yeah, of course.
My dream was to be your maid ever since I was little.
Uh....forever?
Whenever?
That's a fib.
No, nothing, master.
It's so hard.
Doing this makes me feel good.
I'm starting to feel it.
Wait a little bit.
I'm going to bring it now
What? What are you going to do?
Ah....it's cold, master.
I'm feeling weird.This won'tbe good.
Master...
Master....that is.....
I never thought that staying still would make me this excited.
No... Only yours, master.
Theirs bumps on the cucumber
But, are you putting that in?
I'm not ready yet,
for that to go in me.
What should l do?
But, my hands...
That's what you think you wish.
Yes, master.
So perverted.
Master, it's going to spill.
I want him to do more.
This is embarrassing me.
But I want him to see me.
Oh my.. does this make me a pervert?
Yes, master.
Master, please...
It grew so big.
I have to do my job as amaid.
It's so big, I'll choke on it.
I'm starting to feel anxious.
No, no!
But I have to make him feel good.
I want to suck ita little longer.
He came a lot.
Makes me feel better
Satisfaction.
Such a pervert. He thinks fast about nasty stuff.
I wonder if he is really smart or not.
Just by walking makes me feel it down there.
Oh my...
I can't stay quiet.
No... Someone will look at me weird.
Someone will look at me all wet down there.
Please, I'm already feeling weird.
Look, I am so wet now
My pussy
Master, please already. It's embarrassing.
But I feel it especially when someone's watching.
Look more.
Look at me being so nasty!
My pussy is being watched.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, cumming!
It was embarrassing to be masturbating in front of him.
It felt really good.
I hope this won't be a habit.
Yes, master.
Today I have to work with this because it Oni-chan's order.
He is really lecherous.
No one is here, but my heart is pounding.
What? Who?
Yes, I'll be right there.
Ah...what should l do?
Where is the delivery?
Ah, from Oni-chan?
Thank you very much.
I really was been watched.
I wonder if Oni-chan is imagining how I look.
Tonight we're going to the park, so put on this and wait.
Oni-chan keeps on coming up with new perverted ideas.
But, I think I expect it.
Welcome back, master.
I bet he's up to something.
Wearing these skimpy panties makes me nervous.
I wonder what he's going to do.
Going outside in this?
You're too great!
Huh?
What?
Am I now officially his pet?
I'm so embarrassed, my heart's about to burst.
I'm getting wet.
My stomach can't bare it any longer.
but, my stomach...
Or maybe he's just simply being nice to me.
Yes. I understand, master.
Someone might come.
People looking might think that I'm a perverted maid.
But, I want Oni-chan to look at me more.
Especially my wet pussy
I'm completely Oni-chan's pet.
But as a maid, I'll be the best pet I can be.
Even so, my stomach is at the limit.
Anymore stimulation, and I'll leak.
Master, let me go to the bathroom.
gosh, your face is turning mean.
The blowjob made me wet down there.
But, the underwear you gave me...
When I think about leaking, I feel like going crazy
Is it okay for me to leak here?
Oh, no, I'm going to have to pee!
I leaked in front of my master...
But, it feels so hot down there.
I want his cock!
Cumming!
It was so embarrassing, but it felt really good.
I'm his maid, but he helped me to cum.
Cumming as I get my tinkle all over me.
Ah yes, master.
That's mine...
He's going to continue more.
He wants to do more embarrassing things.
It makes me wet just by thinking of it.
My master has problems.
but it's a little exciting...