Oni-chan, who said, "I like maids with big tits",
is definitely into it.
So l said, "I'll be your maid!"
I've realized that
I'm really into it too.
That's how I became a maid.
Now that I started,
it's rough!
Oni-chan says,
"Refer to me as
Master!"
Or that,
"A maid must absolutely obey their Master!"
He keeps on going!
On top of that, his demands at night are unbelievable!
I wish he'd be thoughtful
of me having to clean my uniform.
But...
I love Oni-chan
so much!
I'm the best maid
for Oni-chan
in the world.
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Master!
Corrupt me more.
SERVE! And SERVE!
There.
Tight.
Pretty good for a novice.
A genius is a genius at anything!
I can't get enough of these.
The body of this big boobed maid!
Now I get it.
You want something inside here.
Don't worry. I'm prepared.
Hey. She digging it.
Legally, a maid's hole belongs
to her master.
Good.
You're starting to look like a maid.
You're feeling good.
This is what a maid should be like.
Add a little more.
Nice and smooth.
I'll try this in your cute hole.
Make it wet and it'll go in.
Nice and tight.
I've got to work this too.
What a maid!
You take it in easily.
You cum too quickly.
As punishment, I'm leaving you like this.
Oni-chan...
Is this some kind of joke?
What's this?
Master...
Where...
Where are you?
Is that you, Master?
Don't worry, I'm right where I can see everything.
What? Really?
You're already turned on.
Good. You're a model maid.
No. I'm not turned on.
I understand maids.
And this is honest.
Um...
But, we just did it.
What? You had enough the last time?
I'm not, yet.
If Master isn't satisfied, neither am I.
Is that right?
Not enough?
A demanding maid!
But, unless you tell me,
what can I do?
Please torment me until Master is satisfied.
Put your heart into it.
And you're forgetting something.
What about saying "please"?
Please, Master.
Please torment me more.
Good! Now you're a maid.
Well, which hole should I put it in first?
I wonder what she wants up her back door?
Master's finger.
You're getting real wet!
Maybe you're about to cum.
You can't hide it from me.
I can see deep into your crevice.
I can see it quiver.
Master...
I beg you.
No, not yet.
A true connoisseur likes to look at these poses.
I beg you, Master.
Please stick it in!
Please put your thing in my hole.
You're all wet!
Yeah.
Yeah!
Awesome. Tight!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too!
Nagisa, holding it in is bad for you.
We better do another one.
Yes...
Master.
Wow! You can take it all!
You took in a quart!
Master, my stomach aches.
From now on, I'm calling you bottle maid.
Master...
Please don't.
Is that so?
You don't want to be called a bottle?
It's not that.
If you keep doing that...
You're being sensitive.
Being sensitive is proof you're alive.
It's not that...
I'm about to leak.
What? An exploding maid?
So please...
Please let me go to the toilet.
No choice.
I'll pull this down so you can go right away.
Now you can go.
Oni-chan, sometimes you're the devil.
Unless you're careful,
if you fall or something,
you're going to explode.
Master...
please...
Oh yeah! Let's take off your skirt so you can go quicker.
That's my maid.
She shows Master she's turned on and goes to the toilet.
What splendid thoughtfulness!
You have to clean it later.
That milk that's leaking from your butt.
Yes, Master.
I'm as kind as an angel.
Do you know how to sit on a toilet?
Yes.
Master, please watch.
That's good. I'm going to shoot!
That was quite good.
Make sure you clean your butt.
Because it's mine.
Yes... Master
Oni-chan's demands
have increased everyday.
Why do I love this person?
The thing is, I love him even more.
It's digging in.
I guess I'm perverted.
Oni-chan's...
My dear Master's nice smell.
Master...
Please torment me more.
I've become perverted.
More, more!
Master, please...
torment me here!
No. Not yet.
Deeper. Put it in deeper.
I did it again.
I wish he'd come home.
Master.
Then you could make me do all sorts of things.
I'm the only maid in the world that can satisfy dear Master.
The king is back.
What?
Welcome home, Master.
Master, please take me for a walk.
Say that again.
Yeah! You've come this far.
I've been waiting so long for you to become complete!
100 points for teasing. But don't think this is it!
Just a collar doesn't make you complete!
The wall to the world is thick!
I will properly tie you up.
Yes, please.
Are you
getting turned on?
I can smell your crotch.
Yes, I'm happy.
Master, don't look at me like that.
My juices are about to leak.
We'll have to check that.
Showing it to everyone is your first step into the world.
Yes.
Your nasty body.
Everyone must to see it.
Wetter than usual.
Very nice. Good maid.
Cleaning up is a maid's mission.
I will fullfil my mission as a maid.
Good. You still have a long way to go,
but you are definitely getting good.
Let's see
how you're doing.
Which hole shall I start with?
As you wish, Master.
This hole first.
It hurts.
It's still tight.
This hole grips.
Yeah! Awesome!
You're hitting the spot!
This hole also looks good.
It seems about ready.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, Master!
Oh, yeah.
Going to cum.
- Nagisa.
- Master!
Cum!
Awesome, Nagisa.
You've become an impressive maid.
Hey, Nagisa. Come here.
Yes. I'll be right there.
Sit there.
Oh, yes.
Here, your birthday present.
Roll around in joy before you graciously accept it.
Um, my birthday was three months ago.
No matter how great I am,
how can I give something to somebody who was not here?
Thank you, Oni-chan!
I also have something.
Oh? What is it?
Master, please.
I've completely given into this. What a fool.
But it feels good, and I'm with Oni-chan, whom I love.
It's alright!
Being a wet fool is great!
DID YOU CUM ALOT?