Man, I ditched school again for today. Besides, I don't feel like studying on such a beautiful day!
If I can become president like my dad then I would try.
Like parents, like children. It's the same life even if I do try. Ha-ha.
If I graduate somehow, I'll find an easy job.
Then, I'll have fun for the rest of my life.
Yes, that's a good idea.
Huh? Who is it? Mom's at work.
I don't have any money for deliveries. Shit, right when I was about to jack off.
Um, excuse me. Is anybody home?
Huh? Is she the life insurance lady?
Hmm, I thought It was this house.
Oh, cute bombshell! She's young too!
I brought the package but is anyone home?
Yes, I am home.
Ha, you scared me.
Haha, excuse me. I was doing research.
Is this the Sensei Takahata's residence?
Huh?
Um, maybe I was wrong...
Hmm? Takahata? This is the Takada residence, and I have no reason to be called sensei.
Anyways whatever her business is, she's hot.
She looks younger than her twenties.
Maybe she's a part time student, but I can't just send her away.
All right, I'll play around a little.
Mmm, certainly, this is the Takahata's residence. How may I help you?
Good. I wasn't wrong after all.
Mmm.
Your nameplate was fading, so I was worried I had the wrong house.
And, what do you want?
Yes, umm, my name is Mahya. Umm, I think you already heard.
Mahya... Yea, yea, you are Mahya.
Yes.
And, what was it again?
Huh?
No, umm, I was just wondering what you were here for.
A little ago you said you had a package or something.
By any chance is the package the shoes you're holding?
I am the package... Mahya.
I fulfilled your requirements on your order, so I was sent from the company.
Um, am I good looking enough for you?
Huh?
The first impression is crucial. You can return the order if you didn't like it after a look.
No, that's not it. You gave me a good impression.
Really? I'm happy.
Rather than bullshitting, come inside, Mahya.
Yes.
I'll play it out until she figures out. Besides, I have nothing to do at home.
Huh? Yea, what is it?
Um, what may I do first?
Let's see...
I heard that your occupation is a writer.
Huh, that's right.
The company told me to study your writings.
That's good. My work is esoteric, but if you read it thoroughly, you should understand it.
Yes.
And, what did you read?
Uh, umm...
I don't know what you read if you don't tell me the title.
Umm, "Dripping Wet M.I.L.F. Pussy Punisher."
Hmm, what the?
Oh yea, and, "Tour of Anal Fucking Bus Guides."
I, I see.
The editorial department asked me a favor, and I wrote it reluctantly. Hahaha.
I knew it, I heard your specialty is training women.
Training?
Yes, like to never wear underwear.
I heard that's your policy so I came without underwear.
What is this?
She's completely got the house wrong, so I have to take advantage.
Umm...
Not good enough.
Huh?
I'm not impressed even if you don't have underwear on.
Think of it like you're taking a test to see if I should hire you permanently.
Yes. What shall I do, sensei?
Don't you even get that?
Umm, sorry.
This is my first time to working this type of job, so I'm not used to it...
Hey hey, that's troublesome. I thought I said an experienced worker.
Everyone else went out and I was the only staff left.
Then let me see if you're not wearing underwear or not.
Um, I can't do that.
Huh? What the hell?
Such thing is forbidden by the company. It is also written in the contract.
Yes, that's right.
You just have to believe me that I don't have underwear on.
Very well then.
Yes.
But still...
Um, sensei. I will do my best, so please consider me.
Even if you say that...
Please. I'll be in trouble if I get returned.
Then would you show me something?
Huh?
Something that would please me.
Then...
What's that?
Yes, this is your favorite carrot.
A Carrot? Interesting.
Yes, I thoroughly analyzed you favorites.
You understand quite well.
With this...
What do I do with this?
Pickle it.
Pickle?
Yes, I heard that you eat pickled carrots during work.
What the?
Umm, is that wrong?
No, no, that just doesn't excite my imagination.
Sorry.
Very well...
Um, I'm good at cleaning. I heard that you're single so let me clean for you.
All right, all right. Do whatever you want.
Thank you.
Huh, her cleaning doesn't make me happy or anything.
But I have to do something with this cute girl who has no panties. Ohh!
Heave-ho, heave-ho. Sensei, it seems a lot of dust has picked up.
Oh really. Would you mind cleaning more?
Yes, leave it up to me.
I see. Looks like she's sucking up to make a good impression.
Ooh, I can see she has no panties. All right.
There's a lot!
Keep up the good work. You can clean more.
Yes, I'm good.
Aah shit!
What happened, sensei?
Hey, Don't move.
Yes, what happened?
The cord of the typewriter got caught around your legs,
What?
If it unplugs, I would lose a month's worth of data.
You haven't saved the work sensei?
I don't have time, just spread your legs.
Sensei, please...
Spread wider. You're gonna unplug it.
But sensei...
This manuscript is worth over a hundred thousand dollars. Can you compensate for its loss?
No.
Oh no!
Now what's wrong sensei?
Oh Mahya, the area around your pussy is wet.
What?
If you're that wet, it will short circuit.
Short circuit?
If it short circuit right now, you'll be electrocuted and the data will be lost.
No sensei!
Wait, I'll wipe you off.
Yes.
But why is it this wet?
No, umm sensei, you can't be so sexual.
Um, it'll violate the contract.
Stupid ass, Do you think that I have a dirty mind?
No, umm...
You seem not to understand my passion toward literature.
Sorry sensei, I just...
I have lost hope in you. Once this is taken care of, you can leave.
It's insulting for you to think of me like that.
Of course I would have to touch your fragile parts to avoid being electrocuted.
Don't you understand?
Yes sensei, I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Like this.
You think my actions are based on my dirtiness?
No, I don't think so.
Right? Then what about this?
And this?
No, I don't think so. No, it's not.
Yes, I, Mahya, would hang in there.
Okay, now I'll take care of this so we won't get fried.
Yes sensei.
First, don't you think this wetness is the problem?
Yes I do.
Now time to check.
Yes.
Huh? It's dangerous moving so much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's see. It's pretty wet in here. What happened?
Nothing at all.
Mahya, lying is bad. A girl that is this wet. Something must happened.
Yes. I encountered molesters in the train.
Oh, and because you're this wet, you felt something?
It's not that.
Nope, you can't hide your arousal. Tell me honestly.
A little.
How were you molested?
Three guys surrounded me.
Hmm, why didn't you yell?
I was too scared.
No, no, isn't it because you were feeling good?
No, it's not.
You know I used to major in psychology. So I can read your feeling.
Sensei.
Did you like it even a little?
A little.
Yup, or else it would of been weird. But don't be embarrassed.
Yes.
Hey hey, you're dripping wet again because you've been thinking of the incident.
Oh no, if this goes on, we'll be electrocuted for sure.
If that happens, you'll be cooked.
Please help me sensei!
Hmm, I have to plug it with something.
A plug?
Yes, I have the carrot from earlier.
Yes.
This is perfect. Looks good too.
Looks good?
I seek for beauty when doing something. Understand?
Yes.
Then this, I'm putting it in.
Your pussy is drenched.
There, it went in.
Sensei...
No no, don't tense up or it's going to come out.
Yes.
Good, hold it there fi rmly.
Oh no, my editor is coming to pick up my work today.
So I have to finish it.
Sensei, we can't do anything like this.
My work is my life. Let's hurry on. I'll have to write like this.
Yes.
Umm, where did I go up to? Ah yes, the maid starts to feel weird.
A maid? Are you writing a maid in training, sensei?
Yes. Umm, the maid's pussy twitches, as she thinks about masturbation...
Sensei, your diction is different from usual.
Can you be quiet? I'm trying to concentrate.
...and the maid is wet. Then she feels like masturbating.
Sensei, don't pull the cord so much!
The maid was thinking of playing with the carrot in her pussy.
Sensei, is that...
My style is to put new experiences in my literature.
Sensei, the carrot is about to come out.
Please, you don't want me concentrating?
But sensei, the carrot... It's going short!
Hey, don't move around.
It's coming out!
Don't move, don't you move.
Oh, sensei!
If you move now, death would befall us both.
No sensei, please do something.
Oh no, the plug's out.
Sensei.
I can't reach the carrot, but if we move, it'll fry us for sure.
I'm scared.
Oh well, The last resort. There's only one thing to plug you up.
But let me tell you before, this is not dirty.
Is it not?
Yes, so this is not violating the contract.
Yes.
Anyways, we can't waste time.
Heave-ho! Now we're prepared.
Yes.
My thing is becoming hard now.
Sensei, something's touching me.
Take that and invite it into your wet hole.
No!
Now is not the time to fight it.
But, but sensei...
Come on, your pussy is becoming more wet.
No, no!
And look, it's going to run on to the cord. Then it's over. Hurry up.
Yes.
There, good. Hurry and put it in.
Oh wow, so tight.
Sensei, it's going in. Sensei!
Yes, that's good. It's so soft.
Sensei, don't move. No, if you move it's contract violation.
Hey, your pussy is twitching.
No it's not. I'm not moving at all.
Ooh, definitely it's moving.
No, you're the one moving Sensei.
Silly girl, I'm here sitting still. Aah, yup, it's you.
Aah, no! Don't move so much, sensei.
Aah, the one moving is you...
Not me!
Aah, It's the same thing as moving if you're squeezing my cock that much.
You're becoming bigger, sensei.
Oh, no more!
What is it sensei?
I can't bare it!
What, what?
I can't bare staying still like this.
No sensei, we'll get cooked, we'll die!
Aah... more, ready Mahya?
No!
Slowly, slowly. Do you feel it coming out?
Good, we can avoid danger by going slowly.
Aah, sensei, it's getting faster!
Oh No, I'm cumming sensei!
Me too. Cumming!
No sensei!
It'll be okay if we go slowly.
There, there's no danger with this speed.
No sensei!
Nice, nice.
No... No sensei, sensei!
Aah, I'm Cumming, Cumming... Ooh... I came in you.
Oh no sensei! The typewriter's plug came out.
No~! Oh no, what should we do sensei?
Sensei, why not trying to plug it in again.
The plug?
Maybe the data is still left in there.
Hahaha, maybe so.
Please typewriter, have the data saved!
My literary life has ended.
Although it was an accident, I have failed.
Sensei, hang in there, don't give up hope.
No, you don't understand. The torture of creation is something unimaginable.
Thinking about writing from scratch, I rather die.
I understand.
No you don't. What part of me do you understand?
Sorry, I...
How can you help me when you're talking bullshit?
If I can do anything.
You can't. That's the end of me. I'll go throw myself in the river.
Sensei, ask for anything you like. I will do it.
I would like you to show me how your masturbate.
Masturbation?
Yes, I have never seen a girl masturbate.
Masturbation...
Yes, but I'm not expecting that you'll do it.
You can't masturbate because of your company policy.
Sensei.
You see more value in the company policy than my literary masterpiece?
No I don't think so. I think your work is brilliant.
I'm tired of your flattering.
It's not flattery.
What?
I will masturbate.
I see, but it's not the same old masturbation. It's an intense masturbation. Okay?
Yes, I'll do anything. Let me do it.
I won't stop you even if you sak me to.
Yes.
Now begin!
Umm, this is...?
Rubber Eel.
Umm...
I thought you said you're going to do anything.
No, that's not so. But this...
As you can see, it's a bubber eel.
Uhh...
Stick that in and masturbate.
You're not important to that company.
All right.
No, it's rotating.
It's wiggling around.
The head went in.
Good, stick it in deeper. Inside more so you'll hit your g-spot.
Good, good. Feels weird!
No, no, it's going wild. No, I can't take it out.
Now that you understand, concentrate on the feeling.
Look, a regular masturbation won't do. You have to be dirty, beyond my imagination. Okay?
Yes, it's wild!
Now focus and feel it.
The movement will stimulate your pussy, feeling the sensation that has no words.
Yes. Really, it's getting me hotter.
Then, feel it more.
Aah no, Mr. Eel...
There, there, good. Nice, Mahya.
It's embarrassing.
What are you doing spreading your legs in front of me?
Masturbating. The eel, I'm masturbating with the eel.
That's my crazy girl. Like a pervert.
Don't say that.
What kind of company would hire maids like you?
Pervert!
It's moving a lot.
What? You want one more?
No Sensei, I didn't say so.
You're so hopeless.
No!
There, the two together. I'll stick it in now.
If one felt good, two would double the effect!
One is enough.
Oh, I'm so tight.
Please stop.
What are you saying? I'm trying to help.
I don't need any.
What? Who do you think you're talking back to?
I can say that you're a bad maid, and get my money back!
I'm sorry.
I don't feel that you're really sorry.
There, both inside of you, watch them go crazy.
No, pull it out sensei!
Okay, now a blowjob.
Huh? Sensei, that is...
Don't talk back. Who is evaluating you?
Sensei.
As long as you understand.
There, lick the tip. Don't let go of Mr. Eel.
Yes.
Man, how come a maid like you gives such a good blowjob?
I don't know.
Lick the tip with your soft tongue.
No, this is violating the contract.
Isn't it cheaper compared to my destroyed work?
Aah, Mr. Eel is going wild!
Haha, the eel's and I are cooperating to fuck a girl.
This is literature. This is art.
Sensei, Mr. Eel is moving a lot.
Aah, wow, I'm getting harder.
Sensei...
Okay, now it's time for the eel trio.
What? Forgive me please! I can't fit any more.
What are you saying? You still have lots of space.
I don't.
There is a hole right here with no eel.
That's...
Your asshole is left. Let's see...
Aah, not there sensei! Not there!
Don't be silly! Then where am I supposed to put this?
But sensei, there's no more eels.
Hahaha, it's here, all pumped up.
Sensei, is it...
Yea you're right, This one! It's going in.
There there, the tip is going in your ass.
No, it won't go in.
Wow, it's so tight. It feels so good deep in your ass.
It's like a giant eel is born from your ass.
Ouch, please! Sensei, please, don't move!
Oh so fucking good. It's like your whole ass is tightening.
I barely feel the two eels. I can't stand it!
Please, pull it out, or I'm going to cum!
Now it looks like big eel wants some action, Mahya.
No! No!
There, there!
Ouch, ouch!
Wow, it feels great!
No, no!
Come on eels, hang in there!
I'll cum if you don't stop!
It's okay, just let go. My work is gone anyways.
Wow!
Wow, wow, it's tighter! Mahya, you're tighter!
Are you cumming?
Good, good!
There, you're cumming Mahya.
Good, it feels good!
So it feels good. Hahaha! Then I'll make you feel better.
Sensei, more... faster...
All right, tell me to fuck your ass deeper!
More, fuck my ass more!
I'm going to fuck your ass till you cum so hard!
Come! Fuck me!
More, more sensei! Fuck me until I cum again!
I'm fucking, fucking, Fucking your asshole!
More, more more, more please!
I'm Cumming!
Cumming!
Sensei's asleep but I'll do more service. I want him to like me.
There's no salary since our company is based on commission.
So cute, look how he sleeps.
It's the phone.
Yes, Takabata residence.
Hey, Takada!
Huh?
You bastard ditched school again!
I think you got the wrong number, this is the Takahata residence.
Dumbass! Do you think I'd make a mistake somewhere I call everyday?
Umm...
Using a female voice? I'm not forgiving you today!
How stupid!
What do you mean stupid?
Stupid. Huh? Wait a minute, I'll call the company.
Um, this is Mahya.
What!
Huh? Oh, Looks like I fell a slept.
Good morning sensei.
Mahya, you...
It tastes good, sensei. Looks like I'm captured by you.
Hey hey...
Sensei, please let me take care of you from now on.
I can't let you.
Huh? Why sensei? Did I do anything bad?
No, you're perfect. But there are some problems.
What is it sensei, what is it?
That, I can't say.
Oh no. I can't say that she's got the wrong person. What should I do?
Sensei?
Yea, okay, okay. So it's like you're too beautiful that I can't focus on work.
Really?
Yea, since you did well, I'll give a good report back to your company that you're no problem at all.
Thank you sensei.
Okay, now... He, hey, what's this?
Hey, what's this for?
Hiroshi Takada, how dare you to trick me.
You understand your consequences, right?
You're the one who came to me.
You still think that you can talk back?
I didn't trick you.
What are you doing?
Just wait and see.
I have no money.
Dumbass!
What?
Is he your invite Sensei Takahata?
Yes, this is great!
They said they have no guys so I was stuck with a girl, but look at this cutie!
No, no way...
Sensei, he's pretty good. He has a nice thing for his appearance.
Good good, this will satisfy me.
No! Hey!
Ok sensei, I received five hundred thousand for his eternal maid fee.
Umm, because I'm this old, money doesn't mean a thing. I rather have him.
Isn't it great Hiroshi? The sensei will care for you forever.
Wa, wa, wa, wait!
Hohoho, energy! Energy is everything!
Let go, let go!
Sensei, why don't you taste him first?
Oh, yes yes. It's been a long time since a young body.
Stop, stop!
Energy, energy is everything!
That's what you deserve!