Next up is Momozono Momo-san.
What? Um, wait...
Quit dawdling. It's your turn, Momo-san.
What's this?
She was only recruited today and she's already
meeting the master? That's gotta be a first.
Oh, you're right.
She's just a newbie, and yet she's already
a candidate for next head maid. How weird.
I-I knew it. This isn't a maid cafe.
I thought that interview yesterday was strange.
I do apologize for not telling you,
but we expect a lot of things from you.
You're that pervy brat who
used to come to the villa every year!
H-How? Why are you here?
Are you Momozono Momo?
We haven't seen each other for a while
and that's the first thing you say?
That aside, you've grown into quite the looker.
Momo-san, whatever happened between
you two in the past is irrelevant.
Right now, you work as a maid for the Master.
Please show him some proper respect.
Let's see... How about a titfuck to celebrate our reunion?
That's the Three Sacred Techniques' third move.
What does that mean?
Oh? You don't even know that much?
I'll show you. First, I grab your tits...
Y-You pervy demon!
Oh well, I did warn you.
You reap what you sow, Master.
Jesus, ouch...
Wow, girl. You pack a mean right hook.
But punching your master all
of a sudden is quite displeasing.
Are you all right, Master?
Oh, that's right!
I shouldered all of your debts.
Since we're childhood friends,
you don't need to pay the interest.
However, if you quit...
Wait, does that mean I have to pay you back?
Isn't that great?
It's not every day you get a job with favorable conditions.
I apologize for earlier, Master.
I'll make sure she is properly educated.
So please forgive her.
No need to worry about something as trivial as this.
I'll be taking my leave, then.
I think you're the one who needs some educating.
You're an idiot, a sicko, and a huge pervert!
You've still got that sharp tongue of yours, huh?
You're one tenacious woman, I'll give you that.
So why did you call me here anyway?
Did you need me for something?
There's only cone thing a man and a woman
would do in a room alone together.
I'll ask you just in case
but you're a virgin, right?
Wh-Where did that come from?!
You haven't hit it off with a guy at that age?
You're like one of those rare endangered species.
Cut the crap, you pervy devil!
I'd rather you call me honest.
What?!
Christ, this is why the younger ones are a pain.
I would say that now
is the perfect time for lovemaking.
Lovemaking?
Now... come closer.
What the heck are you doing?!
You pack a mean left hook, too.
H-Hang on a second! What are you doing?
We will now be educating you on
how to serve your master, Momo-san.
Ouch! That hurts!
You'll feel good soon enough.
Where are you touching me?
No!
N-Not there!
Please stop!
Don't fondle my breasts!
You're letting out lewd juices.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
N-No! It's not me!
Then how about this?
D-Don't! Please don't look!
Not there!
M-My hips are g-going numb...
I've never felt like this before...
It feels finely down there.
I feel strange.
My mind is going blank...
That's what everyone feels when they're nearing climax.
S-Something's coming!
No!
Oopsie.
You've become more docile now that
we've gotten rid of that excess energy, Momo.
I'll leave the rest to you, Master.
Please don't be too rough on her.
Yeah, I know. Momo is one of
my precious maids, after all.
I'll take good care of her.
Maid-san and the Spirit
of her Bonncing Tits
I feel something hard
and hot between my breasts...
No! Don't stick your dick in there!
Please stop! You're rubbing my breasts with your dick!
Your body seems to be liking this, Momo.
Don't be so rough...
Your dick's about to enter my mouth!
No!
I'm at my limit.
I-I'm cumming!
Th-This hot juice tastes bitter. What is this?
It tastes good...
You're fucking sexy, Momo!
What's going on? It's tingling.
You're wet enough now, so it shouldn't hurt.
Drop your hips more!
Huh? I feel something hard inside me.
It hurts! Please stop!
Your dick is reaching all the way inside...
I'm gonna move now.
No!
I've never felt like this before.
No...
My pussy is being rubbed. It feels like heaven!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
I'm about to cum, Momo!
Me too!
I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
How are you getting on, Xiaomei-san?
Have you decided on the main dish?
Not yet. I don't know what to prepare.
Nothing's really coming to me.
Why don't you ask me if you're having trouble?
Oh, Aoi! Do you have any ideas?
Well...
That's a great idea!
Oh, right. You're going to help.
Me too?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Hello, everyone.
I know you're all having a great time right now,
but it's time for the main dish.
Mikage, what's this secret dish of yours
that you won't even tell me about?
Are'you sure it's gonna work out?
What the hell is this, Mikage?
Behold the Japanese tradition of serving food
on a woman's body. Feast upon me, Master.
Now then, everyone.
Allow me to have the first bite.
Whoa, this isn't any ordinary steamed bun, is it?
You never fail to amaze, Master.
Indeed, this is a new type of cuisine.
Only a small amount of meat is used,
and it features the highest class of foie gras.
How about this one here?
H-Hey, where do you think you're poking? That tickles.
Gotcha.
I've gotta hand it to you, Xiaomei.
Your cooking's top-notch.
And these bodies are spectacular...
I'd expect nothing less from my maids.
Well then, everyone.
Feel free to partake in this banquet.
My, my. Pervy geezers are always like this.
This looks like sweet and sour pork.
Th-That's an Italian dish called...
I see...
Is this blowfish sashimi?
Please stop...
The food's gonna fall off...
That's not food, you know...
Oh, please excuse me.
It looked like a delicious cherry to me.
What kind of dish is hidden here, I wonder?
Oh, it's Chinese wine!
You're supposed to use a ladle...
You mean this, huh?
Don't stir it up so much. It's embarrassing.
I can't take this anymore!
Same here!
No!
N-No, please!
Please refrain from inappropriately touching the maids.
My, my. I guess I'll have to handle things here.
What's wrong with the guests?
They all look groggy.
It seems our guests are exhausted, Master.
I believe it would be best to send them home.
R-Right...
Well, your last job as the
head maid went off without a hitch.
If it weren't for you, the guests wouldn't
have enjoyed the party to this extent.
Please offer those compliments to the other maids.
Yeah, you're right.
It looks like I'm gonna have a hard time
choosing the next head maid.
Good morning, Aoi. How's your day going?
Hey, what the heck is this?
What are you trying to pull?
It should be obvious, no?
You know exactly how this room works.
Why do I have to be tortured?
Listen here, Aoi.
This isn't torture. It's your punishment.
What? You're not making any sense.
Hurry up and untie me!
You let those geezers play around with
Xioamei's and Momo's bodies at the party.
It's only fair to have you go through the same thing.
M-My breasts are gonna tear off!
I'll make you feel good, then.
That hurts! Y-You're ripping them!
I'm sure they're gonna get ripped off!
Then how about this?
Stop! Please turn off the vibrator!
It's time for me to have some fun too.
No, that hurts! Not my butt!
Stop...
Please take it out! My butt hurts!
You're squeezing too hard. I can't get it out.
Loosen up, Aoi.
Good girl.
You tricked me, you cruel sicko!
Oh? You were in pain just moments ago.
Are you finally feeling it, you dirty maid?
You won't get away with this.
That's "Master" to you.
It seems I need to punish you more.
No way... I'm gonna cum from my butt!
I'm about to cum
I'm gonna let it all out inside you!
Please! Not inside!
It's hot and feels tingly...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
translator: nyanpasu
translation check: hikarucon
timing: fyurie
typesetting: haidaraaaaa
editor: punk4real
quality control: fyurie