Welcome home, Master.
Master sure is very active early in the morning.
What just happened?
You always ask a lot of questions, are you a spy or something?
Shh, be quiet. We're at work right now.
Would this be alright, Master?
You've just arranged preparations for a business
party of the committee leaders,
without the approval of other members.
I'm the one who uses this mansion.
I shall do as I see fit.
In the name of my family, I shall make this night
something that nobody will ever forget.
I understand that your decision will no
longer change no matter what I say.
Indeed. As expected of you, Mikage.
You're the one who understands me the most.
Oh, do you understand how I feel?
It would seem that you already became
a fine adult, young master.
Hey, hey, stop treating me like I'm still a child.
In any case, I believe it is about time you choose my successor.
Even if you say that, though...
I don't think it'd be easy to replace someone like you.
Your father is about to return from his business travels.
The upcoming party will serve as a good turning point.
I shall prepare a group of maids suitable for the task.
I want you to choose from them.
You sure like to make this difficult for me till the end, Mikage.
Excuse me, Master.
Oh, Mikage?
Come in.
Mi-Mikage?
That outfit...
This is my last special service.
I did have some second thoughts, as this is
far more than what I have done before.
Well, I think you should stay that way.
Man, it's all stiff now.
My oh my.
No need to rush.
Now, please do it, Master.
Do whatever you please.
Mikage!
Already fondling them this hard...
Young master, you do love breasts, don't you?
I've been exposed to these big breasts ever since I've known sex.
Anybody's bound to become a tit lover that way.
Milk will come squirting out if you caress and suck it that much.
It's alright, just let it all out.
I'm going drink it all no matter how much gushes out.
That won't do, young master.
I-I won't be able to restrain myself anymore.
Amazing. This is amazing, Mikage.
It's been a while since I got a taste
of your milk, and it's still the best.
Young master, you really are a child.
It's so big and stiff, and looks very sturdy.
It's grown wonderfully, makes all the
years I've served totally worth it.
Your breasts feel so soft and flexible.
Their tenderness makes it feel like my dick is about to melt.
Young master's dick...
I can feel its twitch and pulse in my breasts.
Oh crap... I think I'm about to cum.
It's alright, young master.
Just cum without restraint.
Oh my, you sure came a lot.
Young master, you're not actually satisfied with this yet, right?
Of course.
Don't underestimate me.
I've already taught you many times to be gentle with women.
Stop kidding me.
Do you think I can stay sane after showing this to me?
Oh my, you're such a spoiled child.
Well then, could you please lower the curtains?
We're going to be completely exposed.
In that case,
we have all the more reason to expose ourselves.
Oh my... young master...
It won't be good for my subordinates if they see the head
maid and the Master doing some nude sex play.
I'm happy that you've grown up to this point.
Your small dick has now became so monstrously huge.
Please, get a good taste of my aroused pussy.
Here I go then.
My womb is starting to feel tingly as your dick pushes in and out.
Your pussy is still as fine as ever.
It has its firm tightness, and an excellent rubbing sensation.
It feels so good that I'm about to burst!
Your dick's tip is hitting my womb!
Oh yes, this feels great, young master.
It feels like the pleasure is going to overwhelm me.
Mikage, take every last drop of my cum!
Young master...
Please keep hitting my most tender spot.
If you keep fucking me that intensely,
my very depths are going to be aroused.
Mikage...!
Now, I no longer have any regrets... young master.
Well then, Master.
We are about to begin,
but this is also part of the selection
process for the next head maid.
So please judge fairly, and observe to the best of your efforts.
I get it already.
Now then, three of the candidates shall
now present their techniques on stage.
Candidate's techniques?
Three of the most important techniques for Masters
as officiated by the maid service industry.
Now, Aoi-san, on stage, please.
Well, Master,
I'll be sure to squeeze out every last drop, so prepare yourself.
Oh? In what way should I prepare myself?
Please do.
It's so tight!
One of the three main techniques:
The Pussy Vessel.
Also known as the larva constrictor.
Alright! Alright!
I understand the technique already,
so please loosen it up a bit.
Alright then,
Xiao Mei-san, please do it.
Okay!
Let's go, Master!
I'm not sure if this is right, but would this be okay?
One of the three main techniques:
The Special Fellatio.
It's a complex combination of several techniques
such as the Rolling Tornado and Burst Tit Fuck.
Once she takes it in, she'll never let go until you cum.
This is the first time I feel like it's melting in such a manner!
O-Oh no, what is this?
Next is Momozono Momo-san.
Umm, chief, I'm still...
Don't waste time now, Momo-san.
It's already your turn.
What...?
She just came in today, so I suppose it's
her first time to meet the Master?
Oh, that's true.
It's a bit strange for her to be a head maid
candidate despite being a newbie.
S-So this isn't a maid cafe after all!
The interview yesterday was also quite odd.
My apologies for not explaining in full.
However, we saw potential lurking inside of you.
You were the pervy kid who always visited Benson before!
W-Wait, why in the world are you here?
Momozono Momo?!
It's been a while, but that's quite the terrible greeting.
Anyway, you sure grew up to be a fine woman.
Momo-san, regardless of your past circumstances, you are now in
the process of being hired as an official maid of this residence.
I request you uphold respect when speaking with the Master.
She's right.
Anyway, in celebration of our reunion,
why don't you give me a good tit fuck?
Master, that is one of the three primary techniques.
What are you talking about?
Oh? You don't know anything about it?
See? You use your boobs like this...
You pervy fiend!
My, my, my. I told you so.
You've dug you own hole, Master.
Ow, ow, ow...
That was a nice right punch there.
But I'm not really thrilled with you punching your Master like that.
Master, are you alright?
Oh yeah!
All of your debts were actually now transferred to me.
I'm willing to consider no longer requiring you to pay the
capital amount because we're childhood acquaintances,
but if you quit now...
So I have to pay my debts to you from now on?
Such a delightful deal, yes?
I believe there is no other professional
job out there as special as this.
I apologize for what happened earlier.
I shall be the one who will discipline her from now on,
so please forgive her.
Don't worry about it.
It's nothing much.
Now then, if you'll excuse me.
Maybe you're the one who needs disciplining?
You're a dunce, perv, and a lecher!
You can still speak like that?
What a stubborn woman you are.
Anyway, got something you need?
Calling me out to this place.
When I ask to be alone with a woman in
a private room, it only means one thing.
Huh?
I'll ask just in case, you're a virgin, right?
Wh-What are you trying to ask me?
I can't believe you've still yet to meet a man at that age.
Ms. Thousand-year-old Fossil.
Stop spouting such nonsense, you shitty fiend!
I want you to be more honest with yourself, though.
What?
This is why it's so troublesome dealing with new girls.
Isn't it about time for us to 'watch over'?
Watch over?
Now, come closer.
What the hell are you doing?
Wow, your left punch is also amazing.
Hey, what are you...?
What are you doing?
Momo-san, you're now about to be lectured about proper
service, by none other than the Master himself.
Ow ow! That hurts, you know!
It's going to feelgood soon enough.
No, wh-where are you trying to touch me?
No... no...!
No, don't put it in...
Please stop...
Don't rub my breasts like that.
You're moaning erotically, don't you feel embarrassed?
No, this isn't me...
Well then, how about this?
No, don't, please don't look...!
Not there!
I feel like something's going to burst out.
It's my first time feeling like this.
My part down there feels all tingly.
It feels weird.
My mind is going completely blank.
You're about to cum... wait, it's already there.
Something's coming!
Oh no!
Momo, you seem more docile now after cumming once.
Now we just have to leave the rest to the Master.
I would request that you restrai-
I know, I know.
She's my precious maid.
I'll take real good care of her.