My life's already been saved once.
If I can save the life of someone in front of me.
Like those people who saved me before!
No matter what kind of obstacle.
I'll face it no matter what!
I'm scared.
I'm so tempted to run away.
But.
Compared to the fear of that time... This is nothing!
Hurry, run away!
Y-yes!
Those people were fighting these things?
Tsubaki!
Kika-chan.
What am I supposed to do?
What is... this?
No! It's making me feel hot inside.
The monster is sucking my nipple so hard.
And gently rubbing my clitoris...
If it touches me like a lover.
I can't help but feel good!
No, there is.
Please, just not there.
No!
Let her go.
What happened?
You did great you two, protecting a stranger like that.
They're from that time...
Oh? These are the girls we saved that other time.
It was dangerous to do that, you know?
I wanted to be like you two.
You want to be a magical girl?
How wonderful! Looks like it's time to scout you right away.
What do you think? Won't you become a magical girl?
Kika...
Tsubaki.
I want to be like these two!
Wh-where are we?
Why are we naked? Where are our clothes?
It's a purifying space.
This is a spiritual realm.
Originally, it was a place for us to return
Lust Beasts to their original form, but...
What's up with her body? Why is a man's penis sprouting from her?
We ended up becoming those Lust Beasts ourselves.
This is where we release our libido and desire.
In here, we can even sprout a penis if we want to fuck cuties like you.
You became Lust Beasts? I don't understand.
Why do you have a penis? Is it proof you became a lust beast?
We got tired of having to do perverted stuff all the time as magical girls.
Tsubaki, no!
If you become a lust beast, you start loving those perverted things!
You understand why we want to tell everyone the wonderful news, right?
Here, I'll make you feel good if you ask me to make your pussy feel good.
My head... is going blank... It's making me want the dick.
But... I can't lose.
I have to save Tsubaki!
Onee-sama! Please hurry and fuck my pussy. I can't take it anymore!
Tsubaki.
Come on, come on, just say it already.
Please do my pussy too! Make me your dick slave!
Good girl.
It's coming... The dick's coming into me!
At this moment we.
Kika-chan, you're so wet and tight inside!
Fell to the Lust Beasts.
Onee-sama, your piston movement is too
good! You're going to crush my pussy!
It's my first time, but my pussy feels so good!
More, please make my body more perverted!
If you become a Lust Beast, you can feel even better!
I will!
I'll become one of you, so please!
What about you? Do you want to feel good with us too?
I will!
Hurry, release your semen into my pussy!
So much cum.
We.
Ended up becoming Lust Beasts.
Magical Beast Purities Girl Utea
Soul.4 Sisters
Our target today is an old man, right?
I heard he's a higher up in the government.
Our onee-sama's are busy turning magical girls into Lust
Beasts, so we have to do our share of the work as well.
Yeah, but a middle-aged man?
Hey, there's a hierarchy for Lust Beasts too, you know?
Today's target... is here: Men who became Lust Beasts.
King
Blood Relations to the King
Women who became Lust Beast
Men who became Lust Beasts
Those in power have a lot of greed and
desires, so they become extra cute Lust Beasts.
Thinking of it that way makes me look forward to it!
What the fuck is happening? Who are you!?
Please, get this disgusting creature off of me!
We can't do that. It's ok, don't be scared.
Soon, you'll be feeling so much pleasure you'll
be drooling, so be happy you were chosen by us.
Just don't worry about anything and enjoy it, oji-sama.
You're already rock-hard! Did you get excited by the scent of young girls?
My body won't move.
See? Don't your nipples feel good?
Please stop.
You're thrusting your hips up and letting out so much precum.
Come on, lick me.
Doesn't my pussy drenched in sweat and love juices taste great?
He's doing his best not to cum, so cute.
It's beginning to taste a little like semen.
I can't defy them.
What are these little girls?
Hey, can I be the first one to get the dick tonight?
I guess I'll let you have it.
Yay!
I'll soothe your soul with my pussy.
Your dick is the best!
It's so big and feels so good!
Why are you sucking my breasts even though Chilly's are bigger?
Here, you can move on your own already, right?
You enjoyed it enough already, Chilly. Time to switch.
I haven't been able to cum yet.
It's no fair if you keep hogging it!
I must... Keep shoving it in...
More... Pleasure...
Just like you said, Chilly.
He did become a cutie, but... This might be a bit troublesome.
We might be the ones forced to cum!
Amazing! Lust Beast dick is so good!
I'm feeling good from my ass and pussy at the same time!
Our whole insides are being violated, up to our stomachs!
My pussy feels so good!
He's trying to drive us both crazy! My pussy can't resist it!
Keep going! Crush my ass and my cervix!
No... he's going to make me cum!
Me too, I can't hold it in anymore!
Give us your Lust Beast Juice!
Make us cum!
Amazing... He's still cumming.
Oh, you're still so energetic...
Looks like he's going to violate us even more.
He might destroy us...
Charm!
Are you okay?
Charm, the King is awaiting you.
I know.
In front of the King, make sure you don't.
Shut up, you're getting annoying.
So that's...
Our King...
Translator: ShamelessPermission
Timing: ShamelessPermission
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч