I, Towamizu Karen, have been friends with Tomonom Mizuki,
practically since childhood.
We're pretty much stuck with each other whatever we do.
Even now we're planning for our
all weekend stays as we usually do.
I have club activities today, so I'll
probably arrive around evening.
I've already bought the cake that you really like.
Lately we've had a shared secret
that brought us together even more,
and that's...
Yeah.
#unrecognized text#
Mizuki!
Got it!
Here we go!
Utea Charm!
Utea Grace!
That secret of ours,
is the fact that we're actually Magical Girls!
Hello there ~Kuri!
I'm Curio, a familiar.
This may be sudden,
but are you interested in becoming a
Magical Girl that can fight these magical beasts?
Curio!
Magical beasts?
Magical girl?
Correct.
To be specific,
do you want to be a warrior of the magic realm, an Utea?
These evil creatures from the magical realm
come upon the human realm to wreak havoc.
You need to,
defeat them,
Return them to their ethereal form,
and absorb them using your magic stick.
You'll then take the soul within you,
with the Utea cleansing it from within her.
Then, you'll send it back to the magical realm.
With Utea Grace injured now,
the only that can fight these magical beasts,
the only one that save this world,
is you.
Do you really intend to let your friend
carry such burden on her own?
What will you do?
Karen!
I'm glad that you understand!
The cleansing of magical beasts.
As an Utea, this will now become your...
It's our duty, as an Utea!
Charm, handle the students who weren't able to escape.
Roger.
I'll leave this to you, then.
That was very close.
Th-Thank you very much.
Umm... who are you?
I'm Utea Charm.
I, Utea Charm, and Utea Grace have sworn to
protect this world from the likes of such creatures.
Utea Charm?
Utea Grace...
Charm, this is bad!
Grace is...!
Grace!
Why? Hasn't it been cleansed yet?
I don't understand!
It should have been absorbed and cleansed already.
But it still maintains its form.
It's the first time this has happened.
Charm, be careful!
Gather, o' cleansing light!
Bloom, o' blade's blossom!
Blossom! Majestic Flower!
Charm, there's its soul!
May this soul enter a deep slumber.
Utea Fertilize!
Give up and be consumed already!
May this soul be guided to the path of love.
Utea Birthing!
Charm.
Charm!
Wait, huh?
I... blacked out?
What is this?
We failed to cleanse it?
I don't know.
We were suddenly taken to this isolated space.
Grace!
Ch-Charm...
Run... run away.
What is happening?
Why is Grace doing something like this?
Grace...
Stop this!
Please don't let Grace suffer any more like this!
Grace, Grace!
Charm, I think this is a Carnal Beast.
Carnal... Beast?
They simply exist to satisfy their sexual instincts.
The concept of being cleansed as
a malicious entity is beyond them.
They are very powerful magical beasts.
Which is a why a special method is heeded to cleanse them.
This dimension is actually a cleansing space
generated when your Utea powers detected its presence.
We created this?
You mustn't resist it!
It's the sworn duty of an Utea to cleanse magical beasts.
Besides, if you attempt to resist,
you'll just be drained of your strength.
If that happens, you can no longer cleanse the beast,
and it will return to its original form.
As long as they aren't satiated sexually,
they will never be cleansed.
Which is why Grace simply kept
trying to absorb and cleanse it repeatedly.
But, it looks like Grace is at her limit.
Then... no one else will be able to do it but me.
So gross.
So she tried to take this in her?
What is this?
Emotions... from a carnal beast?
Something that feels like
someone's feelings are flowing through me.
Emotions telling me that it wants to impregnate me,
that it wants me to bear its child.
This is... something that's secreted out when aroused?
It wants me to drink it?
I can't breathe, it's trying to seep directly in my throat.
But... this is amazing.
It feels as if my nerves are being torched.
My sensations are reaching new heights.
I'm starting, to understand and
know everything about this carnal beast.
It's rubbing my breasts whole... stop...!
This is the process of cleansing?
To accept their soul into the body.
Don't play with my nipples with that strange thing.
I'm... about to moan!
Oh no, it's teasing both my nipples and my pussy.
It's pleasuring me, preparing me for
the copulation that's about to take place!
My clit is actually quite sensitive, so I don't like this.
Oh no...
It's even trying to push into my pee hole.
It's even trying to caress me with a gentle bite.
Please don't caress me so amorously.
We're going wild!
It gently stimulates me.
This is a sign of its love.
It's very stinky.
So gross.
But, my instincts as a female mate are being stirred up!
Its saliva's going straight from my ear to my head.
My brain feels like it's about to melt.
This monster is getting aroused with my body.
Oh no, my mind's going completely blank.
Wait, don't lick my pussy!
No way... what...?
It's not going to fit.
Oh wow!
It's going deep inside my pussy!
Its slimy dick is practically kissing my pussy's insides!
It's trying to go into my womb!
No, its saliva is going to seep inside me!
Stop sucking me like that!
This is... its dick.
It's several times bigger than normal.
It's definitely a monster's dick.
So this thing will rape and impregnate me?
It's an Utea's duty to cleanse magical
beasts, and send them back to the magical realm.
Your pleasures... I can feel them within me!
Especially when a special form of cleansing is required.
The moment the best method for this is realized...
The smell is enough to make you vomit right away.
But, I just can't get enough of this scent.
My mouth can't getaway with it!
I want to lick it more!
I want it, I want his dick!
... The magical girl's instincts will
strongly drive her toward that course of action.
In other words...
Wait.
Stop... this thing won't it no matter how you put it in!
My pussy will get ripped apart!
Huh?
Why?
That's what I've been saying...
...the desire to bear the child of a carnal beast,
I actually want to be fucked by this carnal beast's dick!
She will inevitably crave font to happen.
I haven't even properly done it with a man yet.
And yet my first time is with a giant carnal monster's dick.
A carnal beast's dick is amazing.
It feels as if my womb is about to break
as if my insides are about to be molded!
It feels so good to be fucked like this that I'm about to pass out.
More, please more, let your dick fuck me more!
Charm?
Grace...
I'll... never let them do this to you.
Th-This can't be.
Curio, please do something!
I cannot do anything at this moment.
The only thing you can do is to
accept what she's feeling right now.
My womb is getting ripped apart.
It's pushing completely inside my womb.
My ass?
No, not my ass!
Getting fucked at both sides, my
ass is going to get completely filled!
Wow...
It feels so good to be fucked on both holes at the same time.
No, don't suck my breasts like that.
I'm lactating.
So it feels this good to have your milk sucked out.
For me to lactate like this,
means my body is being changed to one
that will be impregnated by a carnal beast.
My pussy feels great.
Oh yes...!
lean feel its cleansed soul and
mine growing ever closer together.
I can feel every bit of pleasure that it feels.
Something's slithering out of its dick and into my womb!
Oh wow...
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!
It's pushing in and out of my womb!
The pleasures given by carnal beasts is a mazing!
Its pleasurable sensations are being transmitted to me tenfold!
Yes!
So good.
It just feels too good.
Are you about to cum?
Okay.
Just cum.
I'm going to cum with you too.
Just cum in my pussy.
Cum lots and lots.
Impregnate me with your carnal
cum until my pussy gets torn apart!
Pump all your seed and impregnate me!
It's cummmg so much in my womb that it
feels like it's about to seep throughout my body.
I can totally feel its cum tiling me up inside.
It's bulging and full of cum.
It looks as if I'm already pregnant.
My pussy has been completely stretched open.
It's overflowing with cum, and is yet to stop
Is it over?
Yes.
I see.
Hey, Curio.
Are we going to fight those carnal beasts again?
Can't we stop being a magical girls?
You can.
In that case,
I shall then search for another
one worthy of being a magical girl.
If I cannot find someone worthy,
this world will be conquered,
and all humans will become property of the carnal beasts.
Mizuki, Karen,
what will you do?