One month has passed,
since we became magical girls.
There's the soul!
Let's go, Grace!
Okay!
...And two weeks after the appearance of carnal beasts.
We were simply rolling between pain and pleasure.
Utea Fertilize!
I just felt that we're that way right now.
НАЗВАНИЕ
Around one carnal beast appears each day.
Whenever we dearly wish to evade such a fate,
there it appears, betraying our hope.
We were granted power far surpassing that of a human,
and now we're forced to pay the price.
God sure is a meanie...
...was what I said to Karen?
That was our primary objective.
These monsters would then instantly
appear, completely awakened,
driving themselves solely on the scent of us magical girls.
With that the union with the Utea gets stronger and stronger...
Carnal beasts' cum...
...it's overflowing in our cum dumpsters!
...allowing myself to get stronger as well.
Karen!
Sorry.
I can't just go on dropping dead every
single time we purify them, I guess.
You don't have to think about that!
She's able to endure it less and less.
Whenever she transforms, her link to the Utea grows stronger,
transforming her into an even more magical girl.
I should be happy about it however...
She's just getting hurt now,
and this is all my fault.
I got her involved.
That was my responsibility.
From now on, I shall never let her suffer.
We're on our thirteenth encounter.
Let's hurry and beat them all,
to protect this world,
...and go back as normal girls, okay?
I alone...
...shall be burdened with her suffering.
Are you doing this again today, Grace?
It's crazy to try and defeat all of the carnal beasts on your own.
After all, you just purified one earlier during the day.
I think you should really call Charm and team up.
Shut up!
Say anything else,
...though we can't really do anything
to you using our powers anyway.
It's a defense against abuse and retaliation.
There it is.
Grace,
are you really...
Doing this just for Karen's sake?
When operating alone, the first and most important objective,
is to defeat the target swiftly and soundly on the spot.
All of the things I've learned from our past encounters...
Guide this wicked heart!
Shine o' Moon in the heavens!
Swirl and gather! Suigekkou!
Grace, its soul's over there!
O' Soul.
Go down and slumber!
Utea Fertilize!
Now then, let us begin.
The dance beneath the moonlight.
Let the soul be guided by love.
Utea Birthing!
So this one is already in an awakened state as I enter this realm.
How in the world am I going to purify this?
I see.
I was swallowed whole, I think.
This place is its belly.
The surroundings smell so sweet.
This is... a carnal beast's special secretion?
Mizuki.
Dad! Nii-sama!
Why?
No, I can tell.
They're not real.
They couldn't possibly be here.
The carnal beast must have done something...!
But, if I'm going to get raped by a carnal beast anyway,
it's probably better for me to get violated
by these fake family members.
Mizuki.
Dad...
This saliva is something these monsters use to
make it easier for them to impregnate us.
Nii-sama, no...
I drank lots of your saliva, Dad.
I've always wanted to do this to you.
Can you look at me from now on as a male partner?
Huh? I'm starting to feel lightheaded.
Mizuki, you've grown so beautiful now.
Everytime I look at you now...
It was really difficult for me to restrain my urges.
But, you're going to comfort my heart from now on, right?
Yes, this is really a lot better than some carnal beasts.
Alright, I shall now comfort you both... Dad... Nii-sama...
Dad, that's unfair.
Letting you have her blowjob...
You've been licking her pussy for quite
a while already, haven't you?
Dad's dick tastes really good.
Mizuki, it feels really good.
Such a slutty taste.
Truly the thick scent of a woman.
So this is what impregnated Mom.
It must have felt good.
It twitches as I lick it.
Do you want a dick that badly already?
Your pussy's so delicious, Mizuki.
I... want to do it too.
Mizuki's love juices.
More, more... more!
Will you please rub these voluptuous things on my dick?
Okay, Dad.
Then lick the secretions coming out at that tip.
Mizuki, your breasts feel great.
Its fleshy firmness feels like I'm already fucking a pussy.
Dad's dick feels so hot and stiff.
It twitches whenever I try to suck on it.
So he's getting aroused by my breasts.
Mizuki... Mizuki...
Dad, it's alright.
Pleasure yourself with my breasts even more.
Dad's cum is flowing out!
Dad's scent is completely filling my mouth.
Mizuki, I can't hold back anymore.
I'm putting it in.
Nii-sama, wait!
Growing up to have a sexy and slutty body like this,
yet it feels like yesterday when as a kid
you said you wanted to be my wife.
I'm truly happy as your brother,
for seeing you become a woman that
anyone would want to impregnate.
Nii-sama, please don't suck my breasts like that,
while also rubbing me hard in my pussy,
please!
So big...
Oh wow...
Nii-sama...
Oh yes...
Amazing, your dick feels hot, Nii-sama!
It's pushing deep inside me.
Yes...
It feels good.
Nn-sama!
So sex can feel so different just by changing partners.
Your dick, your dick, this dick!
This dick, this dick, dick, dick...
More, more... please fuck me more!
Nii-sama, Dad, please don't!
You can't...!
The sensation of the flesh between
my pussy being rubbed like this,
I never thought that being fucked both in the ass
and pussy at the same time could feel this good!
I'm comforting both Dad and Nii-san at the same time!
Yes...
It feels good.
Nii-ama's kiss feels good.
Fuck me, fuck me more!
Push deeper in me!
My, such obscene words you speak now, Mizuki.
Have you now learned the pleasures of being a woman?
Then, let us teach you the pleasures
that will take you even further.
Let Dad plant his seed into you, Mizuki.
The greatest joy a woman can have,
is to be impregnated by a man.
I want... I want that joy.
Let me bear your child, Dad!
Cum, cum in my pussy, Dad!
Plead more.
Please, please, Dad!
I'm going to cum lots in your ass too.
Please, pump it both into me already!
Pour lots into my womb!
I want to give birth to both your children!
Give me, the greatest joy there is!
I'm happy.
Now that I've been given,
lots of joy...
No, I've been seeing them as Nii-sama and Dad the whole time?
This can't be.
No, no...!
What have I done?
Something's moving inside me.
It's coming out!
Something's...
Why... does it feel so good?
As I give birth to them one by one,
my head becomes more and more hazy...
They're feeding off me as they try to grow.
More, please let me give birth more!
They're sucking my breasts.
They can tell that I'm their mother.
I've gone crazy already.
I can't tell if I should feel pleasure or not anymore.
I was never able to stop from having
sex with these carnal beasts.
It just felt good, and good, and good.
...and good, and good...
and good, and good... and,
good!
Even when I'm alone, those thoughts never leave my mind.
Karen, I can't...
I can no longer go back to being a normal girl.
Wh-What is this?
I had a hunch you'd get to it faster.
I actually took quite some time.
What are you saying?
Mizuki,
you've accepted it already.
You've taken carnal beasts, and became too attached to them.
Your soul is now actually no longer human,
but is now almost like a carnal beast's.
Now, give yourself entirely to Utea.
Take the last step.
Curio...
You're...
Grace, how does it feel to be reborn?
The best.
Now, on to our true objective.
Let the Utea Project...
...begin.