Mitsuki, I haven't been able to
contact you the entire day.
Did something happen?
Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
Since I was little...
No matter what happened...
We would do it together.
Although we had a lot of good memories...
Now, I can no longer smile the same as I used to.
Should we continue to be like this?
Mitsuki.
What's this feeling?
Is it the Lewd Beast?
Mom, I'm going to the convenience store.
Mitsuki mus have felt this too.
What is it?
I have a very bad feeling about it.
soul.3 love affair
Why?
Why is the smell coming from Grace?
The scent of the Lewd Beast.
I was reborn as Grace.
Is it better to transform back to my true self?
What is going on?
The Utea Project.
The plan is to disband magical girl warriors
and transform then into Lewd Beasts.
This plan was made to ensure that we could multiply
for the next generation of our Lewd Beasts.
This was my real mission.
Although, I didn't have any success. Until now...
A few months ago,
I captured a magical warrior messenger
who came to this world.
Before the Utea's egg was given to its rightful owner.
I bathed it in the semen of the Lewd Beast,
So that we could get closer to you.
Does this mean...
The Utea we have...?
The more you use your magical spirit, the more
you would be corrupted by the Lewd Beast.
How does it feel to be bathed by sperm all
over your body as you transform-kuri?
You're lying!
This Crio has to be fake.
You're...
A real demon!
I almost forgot-kuri.
As an Utea, you were the first to be defeated right?
Even your sounds of plea were ignored.
This made it very simple.
Deceive children during puberty.
Crio!!!
I am sorry, Charm.
No, Karen.
Grace.
Well, allow me to purify you so
you become the real you again.
Purify... ah?
If this goes well,
we can purify the Lewd Beast inside Grace.
Do you want to purify me too?
Well then, lets' find a place to fight.
Good Luck, Utea.
Purify...
this means...
to fulfill Mitsuki's desire.
This type of things
will be spread out.
It's the first time I have a serious kiss.
It feels like we want each-other.
But... if it's with Mutsuki... It doesn't matter.
Karen, you're so beautiful.
Mitsuki, no!
Karen's perverted scent.
It tastes so good!
If you keep licking me like this...
You're all wet, Karen.
That... don't put your finger in... Mitsuki!
Between women.
We can only invade areas that feel good.
So much perverted juice that is coming out.
Your clitoris is so cute, twitching up and down.
Wow, Karen.
Don't purify me.
Though, I guess if you do that,
my pussy will feel really good.
The smell of woman.
There is so much juice coming out of Mitsuki's pussy.
The juice coming out of Karen's pussy tastes so good!
Now I know that the taste of pussy juice
is sweet and it tastes of perversion.
Karen, you're very good!
If we continue like this...
My penis will feel great!
Even though you're a Lewd Beast...
You have such a huge thing...
Lick my penis.
Did Mitsuku just say that from her mouth...?
It's too big! I can't fit it in my mouth!
Karen...
Karen's oral sex is so good!
The dick in there!
It feels like it's going to melt!
Mitsuki's dick became harder than it was before.
Karen's juices are splattering everywhere!
Pre-cum is coming out of her penis.
This feels so good!
My waist is starting to go numb.
Having a penis feels so good!
What? The penis grew again!
I'm cumming!
Karen! Karen!!!
I'm swallowing Mitsuki's sperm!
Karen, I can't hold it anymore.
We will soon become one.
The inside of Karen is so warm.
Her penis! It's so deep inside!
Your pussy feels so good!
My penis! My penis feels like it's melting inside!
All this time, I've wanted this.
Ever since my birthday, the day Karen
gave me a teddy bear as a gift.
I masturbate with it every night.
I'm so bad right!?
I'm a pervert right!?
Have you changed your mind about
how you feel about me!?
This feeling... don't stop!
I'm so happy! I love you so much Karen!
Please! Put your finger in my ass!
Will you become a Lewd Beast with me?
No... I can't do that...
If I did, I wouldn't be able to
revert back to a normal girl.
If that's the case, then we can never be together.
If you become a Lewd Beast we could
do so many things together.
Wherever and whenever we want.
Isn't this... a great thing?
This is how I look...
I have such a perverted look.
Even you could become a Lewd Beast, Karen.
Me... a Lewd Beast?
I don't want to live for Utea.
I could grow into an adult just like this...
I wouldn't need anything else.
Doing this is painful...
Once you become a Lewd Beast, we
could do this together, forever!
Once you are engulfed in this event...
All painful things, will end.
Also, the two of us will never have to fear again.
Together with Mitsuki...
This would be very fun.
Why... Why do I feel so sensitive all of a sudden? It
feels like a wild beast inside more than it did before!
So you finally understand.
It feels so good!
Let's feel good together!
I feel so happy, Mitsuki!
Karen was once so majestic...
But now that she has been corrupted
by my penis, look at her...
Mitsuki, my pussy is filled with lust!
Come on! Come inside me!
I've thought it through.
All I can think of right now is your dick.
Karen, I'm about to cum.
I need to cum!
But my penis keeps on thrusting!
I am also about to... Mitsuki! Let's go together!
I'm cumming, cumming! I'm cumming!
Mitsuki's warm and sticky sperm
are going to make me pregnant!
I have injected a baby in Karen's uterus.
It feels like a dream.
Mitsuki.
We have to be together from now on.
This is amazing.
We finally have the power!
You guys have finally transformed from
Magical Girl Warriors into Lewd Beasts.
You are now Uterus!
You are now the beginning of the
Lewd Beast multiplication-kuri!