Because my life was saved once.
If I can save the people before me, then...
Just like those two who saved me back then!
I need to face anything and everything head on!
I'm scared!
I wanna run!
But...
Compared to the fear I felt back then...
This is...
Run! Hurry!
R-Right!
Were those two always fighting these things?
Tsubaki?!
Kikka-chan...
If this keeps going on...
What's going on... My body's getting so hot!
I-It's sucking my nipple.
And it's playing with my c-clitoris!
And now it's starting to make me feel good!
N-No, don't!
Anywhere but there!
No!
Let go of her.
What's going on?
You two did really well to save perfect strangers.
You're that girl...
Hey, these are the girls we saved back then.
What you did was dangerous. Try to be more careful.
I want to become like...
You two...
Oh? You want to be a magical girl?
That's wonderful!
Then maybe we should scout you right now.
So, how about it? Do you want to be a magical girl?
Kikka...
Tsubaki...
If I can become like these two, then...
I'll do it!
What is this place?
Why are we naked?
Where are our clothes?
This is within the purification zone.
This is a place for souls.
It used to be the area we used to turn lust
beasts back into their original form, but...
What's wrong with your body?
Why do you have a guy's dick on you?
We became lust beasts ourselves.
If I said that this is a place where we can release our
desires, would that make more sense to you?
If we want to fuck you two then growing dicks
is well within our capabilities in here.
Did you become a lust beasts?
I don't understand!
Why do you have a guy's...
Is that proof that you've become a lust beast?
We found out that magical girls are nothing
but sex slaves and became sick of it.
Tsubaki, don't!
But when you become a lust beast, you love having sex.
Don't you want to share this amazing
experience with everyone?
Come on. If you say, "please give me
your dick", I'll put it in your pussy.
My head's been spinning for a while now.
I'm starting to want her dick!
But, I can't lose!
I need to save Tsubaki!
Please hurry and put your dick inside my pussy!
I can't hold on any longer!
Tsubaki...
Come on, hurry up and say it already.
Please put it in my pussy too!
Please make me into your dick slave!
Goo girl.
It's coming! Her dick's coming!
It was at this moment that we...
Your insides are so wet, Kikka-chan!
Fell to the lust beasts.
Onee-sama, you're moving inside me so hard!
Does it feel good to thrust your dick inside me?
This is my first time, but it feels so good!
More! More! Make my body into an even dirtier one!
After you two become lust beasts, you'll be
able to experience even greater pleasures!
I'll do it.
I'll become one of you!
What about you?
Will you join us in the pleasure?
I will!
Put your semen inside me onee-sama!
The baby milk...
There's so much...
We...
We became lust beasts...
Magical Beast Purifier Girls Utea
soul.4 Sisters
Who do we have tonight again? An old man?
He's apparently an important guy in this country.
Our onee-samas are working hard to change
all the magical girls into lust beasts,
so we have to do our part too.
But really? An old guy?
Hey now, lust beasts have a hierarchical system too.
The King
Blood Relatives of the King
Lust Beast Turned Women
Lust Beast Turned Men
Normal Humans
And today our target is right here.
These important people have high libidos.
When they become lust beasts, they get really cute.
Well when you put it that way, it sounds kind of fun.
What are you doing?!
Who are you?!
Please! Get this disgusting creature off of me!
Sorry, that's not happening.
But you don't have to be afraid.
Now that you've been chosen by us, you'll
be drooling with pleasure soon enough.
Just forget everything and have fun with us, mister.
Wow, you're hard as a rock.
Does the smell of young girls turn you on?
I can't move my body!
Come on, doesn't this feel good?
Look at all the pre-cum pouring out.
Come on, lick me.
My pussy is wet with my pussy juices and sweat.
Isn't it tasty?
His dick is so sweaty, it tastes so good.
I think I can taste his semen.
I can't fight back.
What are these two girls?!
Hey, Citrus, can I take the dick first today?
Oh, fine.
Yay!
Okay, I'm going to make you feel good with my pussy now.
Your dick is the best!
It's so hot and big!
Wait! Are you sucking my boobs?
Chili's boobs are bigger though.
Come on, you can move by yourself now, can't you?
You've had your fun, Chili, now it's time to switch.
But I haven't even cum yet.
But it's not fair if only you get to have fun, Chili!
I'll fuck both of you at the same time!
Even harder!
Just as you said, Chili.
He's cuter now, but this is a little too...
dangerous maybe?
He might make us cum!
Wow! This is... This is so amazing!
Both my ass and pussy are being fucked at the same time!
Everything all the way to my stomach's being fucked!
My pussy feels so good!
More! Lust for us more!
Fuck us like you're trying to get all the way inside us!
Keep shoving into my ass and pussy
until you get to the end!
Oh no, he's gonna make me cum!
Me too! I'm gonna cum!
His lust beast juices are gonna make me...
Make me cum!
Wow, it's pumping out.
Oh? You have a lot of stamina, huh?
Looks like you want to keep going.
– We might break.
Charm?
Charm!
Are you okay?
Wait for the King.
I know.
When you're before the king, don't...
You need to shut up already.
So, that's...
Our... king.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч