Mizuki... you haven't come back at all.
Did something happen?
How did things come to this?
Ever since we were little...
We always did everything together.
We made tons of memories together, but...
But now we're not laughing together tike we were back then.
I... I don't want this anymore.
Mizuki!
This feeling... It's a lust beast!
Mom, I'm gonna run to the convenience store real quick.
Mizuki must've sensed it too.
But what is this... I have such a bad feeling about this.
Magical Beast Purifier Girls Utea
soulю3 love affair
Why...
Why is Grace giving off the aura of a lust beast?!
I've been reborn.
Or maybe it'd be better if I said that I became my true self?
What... What's that supposed to mean?
The Utea Project
The Utea Project...
It's a project to turn the magical girls into lust
beasts and have them get rid of other magical girls
in order to eliminate obstacles in our
way to making a lust beast world.
That's my true duty.
Until now I've never succeeded once,
but a few months back I was able to capture a magical
warrior's familiar that had just moved to this world.
Before we could find out if the Utea egg was compatible or not,
we tainted it with the cum from a lust
beast and then approached you two.
Wait, then...
The Utea that you took into yourselves slowly eats away
at your soul until you become a lust beast yourself.
How'd it feel to transform and be covered in cum-kuri?
This can't be...
You're an imposter?
Then where's our real familiar?
I don't remember at all-kuri.
I think you two killed him the first time you transformed.
Even though he was crying for help, you just ignored him.
It was so easy.
Like taking candy from a baby.
Kurio!
Sorry, Charm.
Or should I say, Karen?
Grace?
I'll purify you so you become your true self.
Wait, that's right! Purification!
If I do this right, I can save her!
I'll be able to purify her!
Are you trying to purify me, Karen?
Okay then, how about we duke this out at a special place?
Utea Birthing!
Purification...
Basically that means I have to fulfill Mizuki's desires.
I wonder if she always wanted to do this with me?
This is the first time we've kissed seriously.
It's our first time lusting for each other too.
I don't mind it if it's you, Mizuki.
Karen, you're so beautiful.
Mizuki, don't!
This is your dirty smell, Karen.
It tastes so good.
Don't lick...
You're already so wet down here, Karen.
That's... Don't put your finger inside!
Only girls can keep hitting each other in their soft spots.
It's so cute how your pussy's
overflowing and your clit is twitching.
Hey, Karen, aren't you going to purify me?
If you are, I'd like it if you licked my pussy too.
It has such a strong smell and
there's so much liquid gushing out.
Your pussy must've really wanted this badly, Karen.
I never knew that a pussy was this sweet and dirty.
Karen, you're very good.
If you do it that strongly, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna want you to make my dick feel good too.
This is too crazy even if she is a lust beast.
You'll suck my dick, won't you?
Mizuki's?
In my mouth?
It's not gonna fit!
Karen!
Your blow job is so good, Karen!
I just got my dick out, but...
It feels like it's going to melt!
Mizuki, your dick is getting so hard!
And you're getting even wetter, Karen.
I keep tasting a trickle of liquid coming out
from her dick. Does that mean it feels good?
My hips are going numb. They feel like they're floating.
I never knew a dick could feel this good!
What's happening? Your dick is getting even bigger.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to ejaculate!
Karen! Karen!!
I'm drinking Mizuki's cum!
Karen, I...
I can't wait any longer.
I want to become one with you already.
Your insides are so warm!
So deep... her dick is coming in so deep!
I didn't know pussies could feel this good.
I feel like my dick is gonna melt!
I've always wanted to do this!
You know that stuffed animal I got from you for my birthday?
I would masturbate with it every night!
That's gross, isn't it?!
I'm disgusting, aren't I?!
You probably hate me now, don't you?!
I could... never... hate you.
I'm so happy!
Karen, I love you!
No! Don't put your fingers in my asshole!
If you don't hate me, do you want
to become a lust beast with me?
No, I can't.
We need to become normal girls again!
But then we can't be together anymore!
That's not true!
If we both become lust beats we can freely love
each other wherever and whenever we want!
Isn't that really good?
Look at your face right now.
I was really making a dirty face like this?!
You're really close to becoming a lust beast too, you know?
I'm close to becoming one?
You don't want to live as an Utea like this forever do you?
Doing this even as an adult?
I don't want that.
It'll be painful if you continue that life.
But if you become a lust beast with
me, we can be together forever!
Can I really endure any more of that?
I can make all that disappear.
There's nothing to be afraid of if we're together.
Mizuki... If we're together, then...
That might be okay.
What? I suddenly got so much more sensitive.
I'm hundreds of times more sensitive than I've ever been!
You accepted me, didn't you?
It feels so good!
Let's feel good together!
Mizuki!
She's usually so calm and composed, but now Karen's
making a face filled with ecstasy because of my dick!
Mizuki, thrust your dick in my dirty pussy more!
Karen! Karen!!
I can't think straight anymore!
My head is filled with her dick!
Karen, I can't hold on!
I... I'm gonna cum!
My dick is throbbing so hard right now!
Me too, Mizuki!
Together!
I'm cumming!
Your hot, sticky cum is shooting
into me, trying to get me pregnant!
I'm shooting my seed into her womb!
This feels like a dream.
Mizuki, we'll always be together from now on.
Wonderful.
We've finally gained power.
You two are magical warriors who've
fallen into becoming lust beasts.
Uterus's Womb
You're now Uterus's Womb!
This is the beginning of the age of lust beasts-kuri!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч