Demon City Tokyo.
A place populated by both humans and evil spirits.
The peace has been kept for ages by an unspoken
agreement between humankind and the demons.
But now, humans have fallen from grace,
and formed a secret criminal organization with the demons...
Did you know that woman?
This is no place for a girl like you.
Run home.
Finally found you.
Makai Kishi Ingrid
Episode 01 Ingrid's Suffering
Ingrid, you will capture Murasaki.
Yes sir. Leave it to me.
Don't let me down.
Enter.
I've captured Anti-Demon Ninja Murasaki.
I told you to keep a low profile. I hope you did.
I'd never disobey you.
I simply set a trap and let her wander in.
I'd like to interrogate her and learn the
whereabouts of the ADN's hideout.
Pathetic, Kiryuu.
On top of disobeying Black-sama, you intend to pursue
your own petty vengeance and torture this woman?
Ingrid.
I'm not asking your permission.
What are you playing at?
I see you sneaking around in the shadows like a rat.
That's not fair.
If you want to accuse me of betrayal, you better have proof.
All right. Permission granted.
But I want you to let lngrid participate in the interrogation.
Yes sir.
I shall retire for the night.
I think you know what will happen if you betray me.
Of course, sir.
Today's ritual is over.
A man with no soul, standing in the pulpit. Ridiculous.
Are you playing God to compensate for your shortcomings?
Call it what you want. I call it "eliminating the
pesky witch who keeps getting in my way".
Traitors must die.
This means you, Kiryuu.
You call this a trap?
Bring it on.
You bitch!
Dark Knight!
Dark Knight Ingrid!
Oppose us and be raped into oblivion!
Get out of here, grunts.
I'm only interested in Kiryuu.
What?
Our sworn enemy...
Cursed Dark Knight!
Out of the way, you slime.
This "slime" died at your hand once already,
long ago, in this very church.
It stands to reason they'd hold a big grudge.
Karma's a bitch, isn't it, Ingrid?
Where is she?
My sword is feeling feisty tonight.
There you are!
Ingrid, you bitch!
Stop her, fools! She's running circles around you!
How many more?
Looking for me? Over here.
Perish in flames!
You...
I don't know how you're involved,
but you won't stop me.
Stand aside.
Gullible as always, aren't you, Ingrid?
Who are you?
Got you, my pretty.
I prepared this aphrodisiac especially for you.
Enjoy it.
A normal demon would have fainted from such a heavy dose.
But you seem fine.
Kill me!
You choose death over shame...
Too bad it's not your place to choose.
Your clitoris is standing.
Fight all you want, but you can't resist the aphrodisiac forever.
Go, boys.
N-No... No!!
What are you...
No! Don't!
Beautiful.
Get up.
What a face.
Very good.
I'm cumming!
No sleeping.
Kill me!
Not that cute, are you?