Rika... right there...
This is so great...
...cumming...!
Open your mouth...
Rika...
Feels... good...!
Ms. Otonashi... suck on it...
Make me... feel good too...
Good...
Lick it like a little lollipop.
Feels... great...
I... can't... hold... Move, Nishikawa! Let me jump in!
I'm going in.
Your thing is too big, Kubota. It won't go in!
It's alright... see?
Ms. Otonashi, you're hole is... magnificent.
My stomach... it hurts...
Their penises are twice the normal size, thanks to my
magical powers!
Be happy, you will get use to it very soon.
I have to punish you now, because I can't do it while
you're Misty May.
Are you not satisfied because it's not Naoto's?
Naoto...
That bitch!
Rika...
Na... Naoto...
I'm gonna... cum!
Rika, I'm going to cum!
No, not the... inside!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
No...
I will protect you, Rika...
Naoto...
Rika... lets do it again...
Yeah?
You use Amore as an excuse, but aren't you enjoying
a bit too much?
Umm, well...
What is it?
Well, I want to protect you from the demons...
Liar!
You're doing more of regular sex, rather than...
...trying to achieve the new powers
I have enough Amore to transform already.
Well, I want to...
W, well...
I want to make "love" you know...I want a rich
relationship.
I see... well...
I can't do some thing weird, and my butt still hurts from
last time...
Yeah... I'll be careful.
Well, are we going to do more of Amore storing...?
Um, well... yeah...
Yes, lets do it!
What kind?
Hmm, well I do want to try that thing.
What is it?
S...
S?
S&M play!
I gotta go do homework.
H, hey...
Wait a secon...!
Oh well, we still have plenty of time.
Rika...
Naoto...
Rika?
Ouch!
That hurts, Naoto.
I knew it was you, Loveriel.
How did you know it was me?
I love Rika
...of course I can see right through!
From the start?
Of course.
Then, why did you kiss me?
Well... I though it was a nice idea to taste
some other girl...
Lets make love then.
Sh, shut up! I only want Rika!
Anyway, you guys have plans already for the next
battle?
No, not really...
Just waiting for their attack.
Defense is always the best offense!
That's the other way around...
you think very different...
You're going to be one unique grownup.
Loveriel is already a grownup though.
That reminds me, how old are you?
10,009 year-old
I see...
Hey, Loveriel. You have to store some Amore to
become Jiburiru, right?
Yes, you two have to constantly make love.
In an event there is a battle, if she doesn't have
enough Amore, she won't be able to transform.
Even if she does transform, without Amore, you can't
use the special powers.
Is there that many special powers?
It seems like there are 48 deadly sex patterns that
humans can pull off.
But Jiburiru can pull off more than that.
Really?
Yes, really!
I don't know whether to be happy or worried...
I really gotta do some work...
I can't just keep having normal sex.
That's right, you can't rest.
Please continue to make love with Rika.
Hey, don't narrate the story. Think about Rika too...
Oh, it's Meimi
He, hello Naoto.
What is it?
Umm, well...
Long as I'm with Naoto, he will never give me some
rest... from morning to night...
He even came inside me today...
It seems as if he's only having fun...
I do love Naoto... but I would rather go out to dine or
watch a movie...
But, today's sex felt so good...
Am I becoming a pervert?
I promised to myself, I won't have sex until I get
married...
Hey, Rika!
Naoto? I wonder if he's here to have some S&M...
What is it, Naoto?
Lets go out and eat.
What?
Why do I continuously have to carry you on my
shoulders!
Because, if I fly, people would panic.
Walk!
I'll get tired.
You make no sense.
Look at the costume play.
How embarrassing.
Costume play?
Naoto... does Meimi work there?
Yeah, these are some left over tickets from her work.
A free dining and movie pass.
She gave it to me because we're classmates.
From her work?
Welcome!
Welcome, everyone.
Let me show you the way.
It's my first time coming here.
Welcome, everyone.
What?
Huh?
I've seen her before...
Yes?
Hey!!!!
Oh well, at least she doesn't remember a thing.
I hope...
Another costume player.
How embarrassing.
Stupid
Oh good...
Damn, I'm full.
It was delicious.
Human realm food is sure taste great for us angels.
Human realm? Angels?
She means, if she were an angel.
Oh, was it that good?
Loveriel...
Lets go to the movies!
Looks... like it's over.
Y, yeah...
Huh?
Don't tell me!
Oh no!
Ms. Reina!
Naoto!
OK! Rika, transform!
Yes!
Angel Amoooore!
Let me explain! Rika Manabe transforms into a the
holy battle angel with the power of the Amore Power.
By the way, she saves up for this power by having
sex. Sex is the secret to her powers!
Devil Angel Jiburiru, at your service!
I can forgive a little mischief, but I can not forgive you
when you get innocent civilians involved!
This act must stop now!
Angel Cutter!
Good job! After all, we did have great anal.
Hehe, lets do it again.
Naoto!
Rika!!!
Jiburiru!
Hmm?
Naoto...
I feel... sleepy...
Loveriel! Naoto!
No!
Stop it!
What!?
Looks like the drug is working.
Naoto...
Now is your chance!
...Shut up!
Do it! You might be able to cancel out the other guy's
cum with his.
I said, shut up!
Stick your favorite thing in your little pussy.
Come on, come on
SHUT UP!
DIE!
...Stop...
Why am I... doing this... with a stranger...
Ouch...
Don't pull on my nipples...
Naoto... I love you...
She is fighting them off well... my master will be
pleased.
The more slutty she gets, the easier my job becomes.
No, I can't look at this!
Oh, I hope Naoto doesn't wake up...
Naoto... I'm so happy...
Your thing is so big... it's so meaty.
Why am I saying such things?
This might be bigger than Naoto's...
It feels good... I want to keep having sex with this big
thing.
Wha... what am I saying. I don't want to have sex
with... someone I don't... know... I have Naoto...
My pussy... feels great! Please cum... please cum
inside me!
Why? Why am I saying such things?
Rika...
Something is tickling my butt...
Stop it... I have... Naoto... oh more.
Why... does it... feel good?
Looks like the drug is working for her as well.
I feel it, I feel it... No! Naoto...
Me and... Naoto... I can't believe...
I'll stick it... in...
Naoto!!!
Ri... Rika...
What!?
Rika...
No, you are mine!
Naoto, help me!!
Rika!!!
No!!
Crap!
Naoto?
Hold still...
The shower... it's hitting me...
How about more.
No... this is...
Don't say that... we have to clean you.
Feels... good...
We are done with the shower.
Lets see if you're clean.
Sorry.
Naoto...?
I'm sorry I wasn't there for you.
Naoto...
Rika, you are my girlfriend... you are my treasure.
Ri, Rika.
Rika, here I go.
I like Naoto's the best.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Please... cum inside me... Cum inside me, Naoto.
Are you sure... Rika?
Yes...
Naoto... it's a lot...