Jiburiru The Devil Angel
W
What? A Jibril Zero?
An artificial living thing born from the heavens.
An artificial living thing?
That’s impossible!
You say that the heaven already succeeded in the experiment?
Nagi-chan..
Misty May.
Be prepared!
Eternal Worm!
Get away from me!
High energy output detected.
Shield deploy.
That won’t affect me!
It's dazzling!
I mixed in a flash bang.
Now! Eternal worm!
You useless!
Noooo!
Rika!
She’s falling here with great momentum!
Well then.
I’ll catch her.
Eh?
Stupid love power exceeds the laws of the physics.
Ok then do your best.
Ok!
Thank you Nagi-chan.
Jibril’s support is also part of the mission.
Well of course the outcome would be like this.
It looks like Onii-chan is not included in the mission.
Jibril Zero..
It's hard for me to take care of her.
Then I’ll just have to use the pocket capsule made by Feitus.
Come out! Field worm!
Field worm, deploy a demonic field!
This is bad!
We’re been trapped in the different world!
Nagi-chan!
You can’t resist!
In this field, the power of the angel will be down to 1/10 it's maximum.
Are you ok Rika?
I can’t feel my powers.
That’s reminds me that me too.
The lower part of my chest feels like it's being smashed.
It's really annoying.
Love-chan, you ate 50 pieces of fried chicken this morning that’s why..
It's just your chest!
*Burp*
Ok then!
Let’s start the fun time!
Worm, you can use Zero as you like.
It seems like he likes your mouth.
It’s a waste so let your lower mouth taste that too.
Nooo!
It's round and cute.
Oh? It's already wet.
You can no longer handle it because you were sucking it?
No I’m not..
Is that so?
Then, let's see.
It's wet!
Hey worm!
Thrust as you please!
Oh, there’s still a part which you can put in.
Worm, don’t hesitate.
It's coming in!
It's coming in through my ass.
That part is getting hot.
I can’t stop shaking.
It's good.
I don’t understand this feeling.
No, I’m cumming!
It seems like worm has reached his limit.
No, don’t release it inside!
What a dirty pose.
I got horny too.
Is Nagi ok?
But we must leave this to Nagi.
I must help Nagi-chan!
You can’t!
It's impossible to fight with your status.
Yeah.
Instead of helping her, you’ll be captured again.
But… if I don’t go, Nagi-chan will..
Rika-oneechan!
Nagi is… Nagi is an artificial living thing!
Even she’s ripen apart, she can recover herself.
And if something happens to Rika-oneechan..
You…
You shouldn’t speak that way!
Nagi-chan is our comrade!
Nagi fights as she understands it all.
Let’s get along with Nagi-chan.
My purpose is to save the Naoto’s Hikari.
Getting along is not part of the mission.
I can’ leave her!
Nagi-chan is Nagi-chan.
I…
Have an idea!!
Love-chan?
Come here Manachuu.
Fuse with me.
You’re sucking my blood and I’m feeling dizzy.
Ok then, make me feel good too.
I can’t..
It won’t come in.
I’m going to break.
I barely got out in the field without being noticed!
Angel cutter?
Yes.
But with my power right now, I have to get near to Misty May.
Or else it won’t hit.
Leave it to love!
Hgraaaaaaaaa!!
Hgraaaaaaaaa!!!
What?
I’m at a good part right now, don’t disturb me.
If you don’t behave,
I will hang you out and sell in the Chinese restaurant!
Ok, sorry for making you wait.
Let put it in.
Noooo, my pelvis!
It looks like it go in deeper.
Your nipples are hard too.
My stomach will be ripped apart!
You’re inside is full of sperm!
Shut up!
You got impudent suddenly.
You squeezing it better.
Oohhh it's so good.
It's hard, hot and going deeper!
It's intense.
Don’t do it so intensely.
I’m going to break!
I’m going to break!!
Good, I’m going to release it Zero!
I’ll release it inside Zero!
Don’t release it inside, I’m going to get pregnant!
Here I come!
I’m cumming!
It's been released inside me again!
Angel cutter!
What’s happening!
No! the demonic world field!
All my powers came back.
You have no chance to win.
Zero cannon,
Amone charge.
Jibril Zero.
Fire!
Love! Are you ok?
The dark wind is gone.
Nagi-chan..
Nagi..
Naoto, where am I?
The infirmary.
You fainted and slept for a long time.
Wait for a while.
I’ll call the Sensei now.
Oh?
My body is fine already.
Aside from that, I have a favor for Naoto.
Favor??
The capsule used by Misty May.
It was a technology which did not exist in the demonic world before.
I feel a new power behind it.
I need a amore to fight against it.
I want to refill the amore here right now.
Eh?
This one is for me and Nao-kun.
Another one is for Nagi-chan.
What?
This is..
Demonic field!
Taking advantage of my absence.
Rika-oneechan is really a bitch of catching the attention.
Of Onii-chan by giving him a bad tasting lunch box.
That voice.. don’t tell me!
Here's a gift from demon world to Rika-oneechan.
How does it feel Nagi?
It tickles a bit.
I feel more pleasure.
Do you hate being kissed on the neck?
I don’t hate it.
Naoto, my body is getting hot again.
Do you mean of this part?
It's all wet already.
No..
The fluid won’t stop flowing.
It’s making an erotic sound.
It's getting louder.
Good!
Naoto it's good!
Your finger is moving!
Something is coming!
No..
I can’t…
Wow.. what’s this juice?
I don’t know.
When I feel good and lose strength..
Nagi.. are you alright?
No problem.
Ok then, next is Naoto.
It's so tight!
It's big!
Good!
If you touch that, I’ll get even more excited!
You’re sucking my nipples!
It's because Nagi seems like to have her nipple sucked while I’m putting it in.
No I’m don't.
Is that so?
Nagi’s pussy starting to squeeze mine.
This is..
This is what?
I’m going to cum with this.
Come here!
Just wait!
I’ll cum!
No, I’m going to cum!
It's getting hot and..
Nagi!
The amore is coming in!
That ring is a trap item from the demon world.
If you change your form with that, your body will be devil’s.
You deceived Onii-chan with this right?
My Onii-chan!
It hurts!
Stop it!
Hikari-chan!
It hurts?
If you compare your pain with mine..
Hikari-chan?
What are you going to do?
You ask me what?
Of course, it’s a lecture.
Ok, today’s lesson for Physical Health Education is..
About the female body.
Everyone?
The doll we’re going to use is Manabe Rika-chan.
Ouch!
Stop it!
Stop it!!
Hikari-chan!
Hmp.
Ok, Rika-oneechan.
You open it so that everyone can see it.
No… stop..
Everyone don’t look!
Hey everyone look!
This is the vagina of a female.
Wow!
So this is Manabe-san’s...
No!
Hata-kun, you can’t put it in!
There.. no..
Rika-oneechan’s ass is so lame.
So I think we can’t help it if you’re mistaking it.
Ok then, Aria-kun.
You’re the one who’ll put in Onee-chan’s place.
Really!?
The other guys too, don’t hesitate and do it.
Ok!
Your boobs are soft.
There.. the nerve part, it's so good!
It's like a dream having a hand job from Manabe-san.
You seem like you’re happy being surrounded by your friend’s penises.
It seems Onii-chan picked a bad girlfriend.
Don’t talk about Nao-kun!
Manabe-san’s ass is so good!
This is good, you’re boobs are so soft and I can’t hold it.
Stop it already!
Even if you’re saying that, your pussy is squeezing.
Nao-kun..
No…
Even if you’re not Nao-kun, I’m already…
Your tongue technique is so good!
I’m cumming!
I’m going to release it inside!
No don’t release it inside!
Me too!
Nao-kun… help me..
What’s the matter Nagi?
I feel magnetic field disorder in the classroom where Rika is staying.
What!?
We must hurry or else Rika will be in danger!
You come too Loveriel!
Oops.
Love-kou.
You took a hidden camera again!
Naoto, stop!
Love, you too!
High energy heat body approaching!
It's coming!
Nagi!
Leave it to me here Naoto.
Go to Rika quickly.
Onii-chan!
We must deliver the ring to Rika-oneechan!
I know!
Ok then, I’ll leave it to you Nagi.
We’re going.
Angel amore!
Oh... I see.
So you’re the artificial living thing made in heaven.
Jibril Zero..
Who are you?
My name is Feitus.
I’m the one who researched about the artificial living thing in the demon world.
And she’s the artificial being I made.
I was bit late compared to heaven but,
The experiment was successful because of Aries’ powerful amore.
And it's being introduced now.
Her name is Demon Angel Super 32-x.
The name is weird.
Shut up!
Please change my name.
It’s not weird!
The important stuff is the inside!
Let that tiny angel know that you’re far greater than her!
Roger.
Zero Cannon, amore charge!
Fire!
Give me amore.
I got the amore.
To tell the truth, the main power of 32-x is also amore.
It was really hard for us demon to produce amore on our own though.
So she’s been made to absorb the amore from the angels.
I captured Zero.
Start investigation.
Investigate.
Peeling the skin.
Found the clitoris.
She’s feeling it.
No I’m not!
It’s a lie!
You’re lying even you’re artificial living thing.
The juice is flowing.
Nooo!!
Don’t look the part where my juice is flowing.
Investigate more.
Investigating more inside.
It's full of juice.
It's wet and rough deeper.
It's wet.
32-x, how long are you gonna play?
Absorb the amore faster.
I forgot about it.
Don’t forget even though you’re a robot!
Start absorbing amore.
Don’t do it fast.
I’m going to break.
Rika!
Nao-kun, help me!
Aria, Hata… what are you doing!?
You’re asking what?
Of course it’s a class.
Yeah.
This is a part of class taught by our teacher.
A teacher?
You’re late Onii-chan.
Hikari?
It's you Hikari! Are you alright?
No!
Onii-chan, it's not her!
Hikari-oneechan is already fallen to the demons.
She’s a devil right now.
To be continued...