In the demon realm, Ingrid fell into Kiryuu's trap.
He had both her mind and body modified.
She ended up as his obedient puppet.
The once feared Dark Knight Ingrid...
now has...
fell down to a mere sow slave who does as Kiryuu says.
Makai Kishi Ingrid
The Dark Knight That Fell Down To A Sow Slave
W-Welcome, master.
I'm going to take care of you again for today.
Understood...
Please give this pitiful girl lots of love today as well.
It's delicious.
Master, your foot tastes good.
It reeks of sweat,
It's salty and it stinks...
M-Master...
Do you want my thick cock?
Yes... I want it...
I want your cock, master.
Strip down!
I-I understand.
Please have a good look at my
indecent and shameful body.
Haven't your tits become
more sensitive that before?
Th-This is...
Umm...
They got stiff just as you wanted.
Do you want to suck my cock that much?
Y-Yes!
I want it!
I'm craving your cock so much
that my nipples are throbbing!
They got stiff so much to my embarrassment.
Master's cock...
Penis!
Meat rod!
Just thinking about your cock
makes my nipples so hard like they're gonna burst!
I'll help myself...
...with your meat rod penis.
Thanks for the meal.
Master, your cock is delicious!
Right here? You want it here, right?
Next...
Please make yourself feel good
from my soft and huge tits, master
Your hard and slippery cock feels good!
More... Please savor the sensation
of my huge tits even more!
No, no! You shouldn't come yet, master!
It's delicious.
Master, your smegma is delicious.
Let me have it.
Let me have more of it from your cock.
Your smegma... Your sticky cock cheese...
Please let me have it.
Please give me more, give it to my mouth-pussy!
I want to have your cock up to the base!
It's delicious and addictive!
Your cock is addictive, master!
Your cock is releasing something
stinky and bitter. It's delicious!
Let me have more!
It tastes good!
Master, your cock was throbbing!
Give me your cock juice.
Please shoot it inside my mouth.
Please shoot your mushy semen inside my mouth!
Master, your sperm... your baby seed tastes good!
You came...
You came a lot of thick semen, master.
Yes, I'll swallow it.
I'll gladly drink your baby seed juice.
It tastes good.
M-Master, your sperm... your baby seed juice...
I gulped it down with pleasure.
Master, your semen was delicious.
I'm putting it inside. Stick your ass out
so that I can see your asshole.
It went in!
Your robust and stiff cock
went deep inside my sopping wet pussy!
Please stir me up a lot!
Master, use your huge cock to
stir up and make a mess of my pussy!
Mold my pussy into the shape of
your cock and unable to retract!
No way! It's going even deeper inside me!
It's going even deeper in my pussy,
reaching my cervix!
Your huge cock is hitting me deep and filling me up!
Please push it deep so that it will bump
against the entrance of my womb!
Please stir me up even more!
That's it, push the whole thing inside my pussy!
Please thrust your cock up to its base
and shove the whole thing inside!
Cock, cock, cock!
My head is filled with nothing but cocks!
I can't think of anything else but your cock, master!
That's great! That one felt good!
Being punished and having
my ass spanked feels good!
Hit me more, discipline this indecent sow!
Please discipline me!
More, please!
More, more more... Give it all to me!
My ass, my pussy, and my mouth... I want it in all of them.
Please make me feel good through my whole body!
It feels good! You're reaching deeper than before!
Your cock reaches deep as you spank my ass!
My cervix is opening up and your
cock is intruding into my womb!
Keep thrusting more! Thrust and wear me out!
Please ram my pussy with your cock, master!
It's coming! My pussy is coming up until it's worn out!
Thinking about cocks... Just thinking about your cock...
I'm coming just from thinking about it!
I'm coming! I'm coming again!
Something huge is coming!
I'm coming one after another!
Master!
Come deep inside me! Deep inside!
You can come as you please!
I'm gonna come. I'm coming, coming, coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
There's a lot coming out!
Master, you're pouring a lot of semen
inside my womb.
I'll bear your child, master.
Master, you're semen
is gushing into me.
Master, your baby seed juice
has been poured inside
me without any problems.
As a reward for being able to satisfy her master,
she has to accompany these brutes for reproduction.
Moreover, their orders are directed
towards the captive Dark Knight.
Stop this already!
Stop!
Don't touch me with... with those filthy hands!
This one will end up in climax as well.
This one's the Dark Knight, huh?
My body feels hot...
What did you spread on my
body? An aphrodisiac lotion?
My body is acting weird...
No! Any more of this and I...
Stop—!
No! No! No!
No!
No! No! No! No!
I'm coming...
I'm coming... I'm coming!
I won't forgive you...
I absolutely won't forgive all of you!
I'll cut all of you down!
Stop...
Stop!
Don't you dare put your filthy sperm inside me!
Bearing your children is...
Stop!
It's pouring into me...
Their filthy orc sperm is pouring inside me!
It's all gushing into me!
Remember this...
I'll absolutely slay all of you...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Support the group by sharing the releases
and and giving it proper credits.
http://sakuracircle.animeholics.org