Anti-Demon Ninja Murasaki pursues Kiryuu...
...but falls into his carefully laid trap.
She is then ravaged by his beast-like body.
Meanwhile, Ingrid is help prisoner and raped by orcs.
Treating Ingrid as his personal plaything,
Kiryuu demands that she summon Edwin Black.
When she refuses, Kiryuu tries to break her will.
Ingrid is humiliated in front of Kiryuu's demonic dinner guests.
This is just the beginning.
I'm going to keep on violating you,
and expose your wrethcedness  for all to see.
Is the tumor attached?
Yes. It's firmly rooted.
Splendid. And how about the alterations?
Successful.
30% increase to erogenous sensitivity so far.
She's receiving a constant flow of aphrodisiac.
Kiryuu-sama, with such drastically heightened sexual sensitivity,
there is a danger of fatal encephalitis...
Don't worry.
She's Edwin Black's aide, Dark Knight Ingrid.
She'll live.
I want it increased to 80%, so that she can't
even breathe without having an orgasm.
Pitiful. Poor, miserable Ingrid.
All right. Let's disengage the tank and wake her up.
Wakey-wakey, Dark Knight.
Ki-Kiryuu...
What have you done to me?
We implanted you with a special tumor.
Put simply, it's like another brain.
But this brain was engineered from my own cells.
All right. As you were, Ingrid.
Your carelessness will cost you your life.
What the...
What's wrong? You're not going to kill me?
I can't... move...
Your new "brain", which I control, supersedes your old one.
That means I control you.
Kiryuu...
That's not all we did to you.
I'm... cumming! What the hell?
You like it? Your whole body's sensitive as a clitoris now.
You're a walking G-spot, Slut Knight
You...
How... how dare you!
And I'll alter your body further, until your every action causes an orgasm.
Doesn't that sound nice?
Live with a body of your design?
I'd rather die!
Death is one luxury I can't offer you. Certainly you understand.
Damn you!
You're nothing but a puppet now.
You'll help me capture Edwin Black, whether you like it or not.
No. I can't do such a thing.
Oh, but you can. Want me to prove it?
No. Kill me. Kill me now!
Well, I don't suppose I can make you understand.
You'd rather die than betray your master, after all.
So, I'd be happy to kill you on one condition.
What?
All you have to do...
is whore yourself out.
Let's say... one hundred.
One hundred satisfied customers. Do that and then you can die.
Why would I agree to such nonsense?
If Edwin Black's number two can be a good little whore,
I'll be convinced of the Ryuumon Organization's power.
I'll be most impressed.
If you don't like it, so be it.
But the alternative is helping me kill Black.
Anything but that I can't... Please.
Wha'll it be, then?
I'll do it. I'll service one hundred men.
Well, then...
You look good in chains.
From now on,
this is how the honorable Dark Knight will be remembered.
You'll get down on all fours like a pig and
change everyone's conceptions forever.
It's going to be hard work.
Let's go visit your friend.
Makai Kishi Ingrid
Episode 03 Oath of Humiliation
I'm looking for my sister.
Tell me what you know.
Go fuck yourself.
Tell me. Tell me about Ryuumon.
I don't...
Spill it!
I heard one of their officers, Kiryuu, opened up a shop nearby.
They've got a captured ADN and another woman,
putting on shows every night.
Where?
Check the invitation on the table.
Demonic nobles go to watch...
some real sick shit...
Murasaki.
Yeah! Take it deep, you bitch!
You've got to slow down!
You're mashing my pussy to a wet pulp!
What a cunt!
We should fuck ADN bitches more often!
Don't talk to me like that!
Squeal like a pig!
Stop it, please!
I'm cumming!
Good! That makes two of us!
I'm gonna hose you full of sauce!
No, not inside me!
I don't want a monster baby! Cum somewhere else, please!
Ah, save it. You're probably already knocked up.
No, no, no!
I don't want an orc baby! Please!
Here it comes!
Get this cum up in your cooze!
My uterus is cumming... My pussy is cumming...
I'm cumming like an earthquake!
Suck it.
Kiryuu's a genius. He's got this ADN worshiping our cocks like gods!
I don't wanna suck any more cocks!
I'm gonna cum! Here it comes!
Please, my pussy is going numb!
I'm cumming my brains out with a womb full of hot ore slime!
I can't stop cumming.
I'm having one constant orgasm!
Here's some food. It's our "special sauce".
Disgusting...
Sorry to interrupt dinner.
Kiryuu.
Don't mind me. Go on.
Bon appetit.
Good girl.
Get a stomachful of those essential nutrients.
Drink down every last sperm cell.
All right.
I brought you a new friend.
If you work well together, I'll kill you mercifully.
Will you kill Asagi for me?
Will you do me this favor and earn my respect?
Think about it carefully.
Murasaki, you will act as a sex slave.
Use your body to pleasure one hundred clients.
Ingrid, have some dinner.
Eat.
As I thought. You hero types are greedy.
Go on, lap that scum up like dogs.
We have another guest.
Let's serve them some seconds.
Good, good. Enjoy every mouthful.
Swish it around in your mouths with your tongues.
Swallow it... slowly.
Feel it slither down your gullet.
Open up and show me your tongue!
How was it?
Good?
It was good...
Kiryuu-sama.
Indeed!
We have to go out looking like this?
We're going to be humiliated in front of the whole town.
Get to work.
Don't worry, well get customers.
Yes, you will. Now go.
Attention, residents and patrons!
We have here Edwin Black's aide,
Dark Knight Ingrid,
and Anti-Demon Ninja Murasaki.
Thanks to the charismatic influence of Kiryuu-sama,
they have volunteered to become slave whores.
Come on.
Say hello.
Do as you've been told.
Is she really a Dark Knight?
Unbe-fucking-lievable!
I'm Ingrid the pig-whore.
Thanks to Kiryuu's modifications to my body, just grabbing
my breasts will cause me to orgasm wildly.
Anything goes. ¥3000 a night.
I look forward to servicing you.
I'm Murasaki the pig-whore.
My body's also been modified.
Giving a blowjob brings me to orgasm.
Nothing is taboo. ¥3000 a night.
I promise to serve you with all my might.
Ingrid the Nomad, with sensitivity modifications?
She can cum just from having her tits squeezed,
did you hear that? Awesome.
Kiryuu-sama's completely broken her.
Not so proud anymore, is she? She's a total whore now!
That ADN bitch killed my buddies! Time to avenge them.
Ladies!
Please feel free to watch the festivities.
Or participate, if you want.
Gentlemen!
These whores are now open for business.
Special grand opening price: ¥1000, all you can fuck!
Please form an orderly queue.
What a cocksucker! You really like my dick, huh?
I'm only doing this,because I have to.
Really? You sure seem to be hungry for it.
But I'm...
Your huge cock is... thrusting in and out of my throat...
She's diddling herself while she sucks cock.
My hand is... moving on its own!
Are you ready to cum already?
That wouldn't be very "professional."
You shouldn't cum before your client does.
If you do, I'll force you to kill Asagi.
Kiryuu...
Don't stop!
Look at her. What a dog!
Come on, fuck me, you pig-whore!
Who do you think I am?
How the fuck should I know?
Nice titties.
Please, not there!
Where? Here?
Stop!
Bite her tits and she squeaks like a leaky balloon!
Keep it up. Let's make her cum!
Stop biting me!
Stop chewing my nipples!
She's settled down.
My throat is...
full of cock...
Here it comes, baby! Guzzle my cum!
No, not in my mouth...
Just the idea of this cock in my mouth makes me feel so...
Come on, there are lots of guys waiting.
Shit! Her throat is hugging my prick!
I'm going to cum from being throat fucked.
So good! Even as it's smothering me...
this cock is so good!
Murasaki, you are now a complete slave.
Are you happy your body could offer such a service?
No... This is the worst!
Yet, I'm loving this.
I love cock! I want to eat cock forever! Cock cock and more cock!
God damn, here it comes! Eat it, bitch!
She really drained my balls.
Drink up, girl.
Check it out! Getting her throat raped
is making her cum. What a nympho!
It's so deep!
Your big dick is pounding me deep!
Shit! What a cunt.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
I can feel your dick throbbing...
getting ready to spew!
I'm cumming... again! At the same time as your gnarly dick!
Wow, her tits really are sensitive.
What if I work on your tits and pussy at the same time?
Oh God... My tits and my pussy?
If you do that. I'll...
Cum! I'm cumming!
We're not done here yet, baby. Push your ass against me!
I'm full of cock!
It's pounding all the way into me!
Pushing against my cervix!
Your cock is making me cum again!
Your fat, veiny cock,
filling up my cunt and making me cum so hard!
That's damn right.
You're just the town cum toilet.
You're our fuck toy!
Fuck my fuck hole!
I'm cumming all over your big dick!
Oh God, I can feel you cumming!
Filling my pussy with your jizz!
I'm gonna get pregnant.
With so much sticky cum, I'm sure to be pregnant!
It's coming out...
You're making a mess.
Yes! Yes! Fuck, yes!
Pound my holes!
My pussy... my ass... it feels like they're melting!
My whole body's throbbing with pleasure!
I'm gonna die!
I'm cumming myself to death! Cumming!
Thinking about cock... Getting fucked by cock... is making me cum!
It's making me cum again!
Fuck yeah. You're all slut, all the time.
Worship our cocks!
Cocks, cocks... Gimme more cocks!
Tell us how much you like it!
I like it... I love it.
I love cock! Fill all my holes!
Blast my womb full of your hot, gushing semen!
Empty your balls into me until I burst!
Here it comes, bitch! Prepare to get pregnant!
Me, too. I'm gonna cum in her ass.
Both my holes are so full...
So hungry for cock and cum!
Cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming!
Beautiful.