Rika, don't give up!
You are the only one for me, Rika!
Rika!
Rika!!
It hurts...!
You act as if you don't like it, but yet you want it.
You are a slut!
Huh?
Wha!?
You... you are!!
Asmodeus, I will lead the next attack.
Ms. Reirouge herself!?
Pipe down, Meimi...
Na, Naoto... stop.
Rika, don't give up. This is a training.
It hurts.
Ouch.
Naoto...
You're doing good, Rika. So cute.
It's strange!
I can feel it! No, I'm going to cum!
How is it, Rika? You want it?
I can't... wait!
You want mine, right?
Naoto...
Say that you want it!
I... I want... it!
Rika, you sure got trained well.
I can stick it in without using my hands.
You... meanie.
Hey, it's you!
Hey, you guys...
How dare you attack us during this, you're very rude.
It's not my fault!
I came here because it's Ms. Reirouge's order
Ms. Reirouge?
Who is that?
Ms. Reirouge is the general of Hell and is responsible for
this plan!
What!?
Shit, I came.
Oh, cream pie again.
Ms. Reirogue wants you to come to Gekokujo this
evening.
You can not run away! Accept the challenge, Rika
Manabe!
What!?
Don't forget.
Naoto, what should I do?
Rika...
Jiburiru -The Devil Angel-
Vol. 4 Battle! Blood Initiation!
Being the general of Hell, is Ms. Reirouge a tough
opponent?
Loveriel?
Well, to be honest, I don't know.
Putting that to the side, aren't you guys a bit too close?
After a round of S&M, it makes you want to cuddle.
Anyways, why don't we just finish these guys off with
Jiburiru's power.
She's right, Rika. We have to do this!
I'm here, so don't worry about a thing.
OK...
They need to hurry-up, so slow.
Are they screwing again?
Don't say such things!
Anyway, humans are so pathetic.
Ms. Reirouge made this world to awaken their desires.
Part of a plan to capture Rika.
Hey, we're here.
How do you want to battle?
Yes!
Reina having sex with another man!?
Why are you concerned, Naoto?
Errr... nothing.
You're here, Rika Manabe.
Huh?
Reina?
What!?
You are!?
I am the general of Hell, Ms. Reirouge.
I will get Rika Manabe myself.
Why are you always after my Rika!
What are you guys up too!?
You humans don't need to know!
Rika!
Rika!!
No, please forgive me!
No!!!!!
Shit, let go!
You... let go of me!
I said let go!
The last time felt good.
You want it again, Naoto?
Never with a demon!
Really?
I can control how you feel regardless of your will.
I kind of like this thick thing.
Wow, it's big!
Misty mei, this is part of the plan, don't worry.
Leave it up to Ms. Reirouge.
Great. Reina, it's good!
Naoto...
Hey, hey. Calm down Mei.
In return, you can have any other guy.
Asumo, you peon!
You can't do anything yourself
so a weakling like you can only depend on your superior!
What did you say, you stupid angel!
I will take care of you myself!!
I know you love this.
Oh, that is...!
Naoto...
Great, it's great!
Oh, right there!
Great!
How is it? You like it?
It feels... good!
Great! I can feel your thick meat inside!
It feels weird...
Great!
How is it, the best?
It's the best!
Wow, shit!!!
Rika!
Naoto...
Are you alright?
Naoto... did she make you feel better than me...?
Of course not! I was just acting!
None of it is true.
Naoto...
Rika...
Well, it did feel good...
Alright, transform!
OK.
Jiburiru, at your service!
Get her!
Angel Special Cutter!
Jiburiru, you have fought well...
but you can't beat me!
I will take care of you, Jiburiru.
No, Rika Manabe!
Jiburiru!
Rika!
Just stay put. I will soon show you hell, Naoto.
What!?
Let go!
No, I don't want others to touch me! Don't come!
Resistance is futile. Your body craves for it.
Stop it!
Rika!
How is it? Don't you like it?
You can't get this kind of pleasure on a normal day, isn't it
addicting?
You angelic slut.
No, no. I'm not pleased.
Be honest to yourself, Rika.
How is the nonstop pleasure-fest?
Doesn't it feel good?
Rika!!
Naoto. I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
But it feels good!
Time to finish her off...
What's this!?
I'm scared, Naoto! Help me!
No!!
This is a small dimension I made, The Cradle of Hell.
A space specifically for the ceremony.
Ceremony?
Yes, this ceremony is a must to initiate the next plan.
A very important ceremony.
W, what is that?
You want to know?
It's better for you not to know until after the ceremony.
Just think of it being the only thing that will save you from
despair.
Come now, drink a drop of my blood.
The world will change soon after.
A new genesis.
No...
Your body has become vulnerable thanks to Asumo and
Mei's attacks. Oh, we can't forget Naoto.
Without you knowing, your mind is always seeking for
pleasure.
Now that your virginity is long gone
a drop of my blood, a demon's blood, is the next step to a
new genesis.
A drop of holy-blood will make you a Holy Angel.
A drop of unholy-blood will make you a Devil Angel.
That is your destiny.
Holy-blood...
Jiburiru, the time is near!
Holy...
Naoto!
What...!?
What is this!?
Angel Super...
Nova!!!!!!!
Rika!
Damn! Why? Why won't it go right?
Everything was going right...
Naoto, I think I know... No, I'm beginning to understand.
The reason why I feel like this after being attacked.
But until I can put it into words, I'm not positive.
Rika, were you afraid?
But I'm alright... I have you, Naoto.
Naoto, show me your love... love me.
I can become stronger with your love.
Naoto! Naoto!
Naoto!
Rika...
Rika!
Naoto!
Naoto, thank you...