Kiryuu's wicked revenge plot continues.
He tells Ingrid, now his helpless sex doll,
that she must help him take the head of Edwin Black.
When Ingrid refuses, Kiryuu puts her to work
serving us minions as a slave whore.
Under Kiryuu's orders, In grid and Murasaki offer
their bodies to the city's demonic denizens.
What a fucking hassle.
Okay... How about I take you each one at a time?
Unfortunately, you don't have the luxury of that choice.
Our mission is to kill you, and that we will.
That didn't go so well.
Surrender.
Your luck ran out the minute you set foot in this city.
Really?
Hey, kid! It's dangerous!
I know where to find what you seek.
Huh?
Makai Kishi Ingrid
Episode 04 Ultimate Misery
Please... I'm sorry...
You disrespected an important guest.
Now, to make up for it, you will do what ever is demanded of you.
Even if you're told to eat shit.
Hey!
Dinner time. Here's your food.
Yes...
How's that taste?
Very good, sir. Your cock is delicious.
Suck the scum off my prick. It's good for you.
Yes... Dick is good...
Dick cheese is good, too...
C'mon, this isn't break time!
You squirmed at first, but now you're deep throating
it like you can't get enough, aren't you?
Yes... Thank you... for fucking my throat-cunt...
That's the spirit. Fill your throat-cunt with my cock.
Yes!
The great Anti-Demon Ninja Murasaki is now
a lowly pig sucking my demonic dick.
Imagine that!
Please... kill me!
Do your job and I'll think about it.
Kiryuu wants you to bear our demon offspring.
Squeeze out, say, fifty babies, and then you can die.
N-No!
Kill me!
C'mon, c'mon! Use that tongue!
Oh yeah, oh yeah, here it comes!
Suck it down!
Wash your face with it!
Oh. We have a customer.
Get ready to work.
All right, in we go.
Yeah, bitch. Squeeze my dick.
Seems like you get tighter every time I slap your ass!
Here it comes, bitch! Get a cunt full of my sauce!
My turn. I hope you like'em big.
Fuck! You like my big dick, don't you?
Oh yeah! Fuck yeah!
I'm fucking you deep. Time to go deeper!
Fuck... Fuck...
How do you like having your womb pounded?
He came... So much cum...
Hot and sticky, deep inside my pussy...
Please...
leave me alone.
W-Welcome...
Master.
As you wish.
I'm your pitiful sow. Please love me.
Delicious. Master's feet are sublime.
Sweaty, salty and...
Master?
Oh, yes. I want it.
I want Master's cock.
All right, please gaze at my shameful flesh.
How's this?
Yes.
I want it I want Master's cock.
Seeing it makes my nipples embarrassingly turgid.
Master's cock... fuck rod... meat pole.
Just thinking about it makes my nipples swell to bursting.
And now, I'll suck Master's meat pole.
Master's cock...
You like it like this, right?
Next, I'll pleasure you with my soft milk bags. Oh, Master!
Your hard, slimy cock feels so good!
Wait... Don't cum yet, Master.
So good.
Let me have more. More cock, please.
Let me eat your nasty dick cheese.
More, please. Fuck my face-cunt
All the way down.
Master's cock. So smelly, sour, nasty, and delicious.
It's throbbing. Master's cock is pulsing hot.
I want you to cum.
Cum straight into Ingrid's cocksucker, please!
Give me your thick, thick fucksauce.
Master's seed... It's so... yummy...
How was that?
Did it feel good to pump your sperm into me?
Now, I'll swallow Master's cum.
Down it goes.
Delicious.
Thank you for that rich helping of semen, Master.
Your cum was sumptuous.
It's in! Master's big, stiff manhood is in my sloppy, melting pussy!
Fuck me, Master. Pound my pussy with your big man meat!
Fuck me until my pussy permanently takes the shape of your dick!
Yes! Yes, it's filling me up!
Pounding all the way back to my uterus!
Pound me hard!
Make your prick pound on the entrance to my womb!
Fuck me! Ravage me!
Bruise my pussy with your powerful cock! Rape me hard!
Cock, cock is all I can think about!
Master's cock is all I need!
Yes... Yes, I like to have my ass slapped.
Slap me more! Punish your dirty fuck-pig!
Harder, please! Harder, faster, more, please!
Give me your whole length!
Fuck my pussy, ass, mouth...
Fill all my holes with your meat!
Good... It's going even deeper!
Slap my ass and push it in deeper!
Fuck my cervix!
Fuck my pussy, fuck my pussy, don't stop!
Cram me full of dick!
Fuck me until my pussy's exhausted!
Just thinking about Master's dick is making me cum!
The very thought of a dick makes me cum!
Oh God, here it comes!
I'm going to cum hard!
Fuck me deep! Pour your seed inside me!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming!
So much cum.
My insides are full of Master's hot semen.
I'm pregnant with Master's child.
My fucking ass...
It feels like it's melting with Master's thumb in it.
Thank you Master, for giving me your sperm...
Well? Say hello to our guests.
I'm Kiryuu-sama's faithful fuck-sow, Ingrid.
I'm Kiryuu-sama's faithful fuck-sow, Murasaki.
Tonight we celebrate as these two pig-whores
enter into the majesty of motherhood.
This is a dangerous creature of the Demon World.
It's no ordinary monster.
I've altered its genetic material and vastly improved its strength.
Let's call him... Nabelius.
Nabelius is a fully-controllable bioweapon.
With his strength, we cannot lose.
Nabelius has multiple talents.
For example, his zeal for breeding.
This bioweapon will mass-produce itself.
Tonight, I invite you all to witness the start
of that mass-production for yourselves.
This Dark Knight... and this Anti-Demon Ninja...
...will provide tonight's entertainment!
How... could this happen?
Please kill us.
Looks like he has big plans for you.
This will be a spectacular show.
Really? I'm already bored.
Identify yourself.
Have you forgotten my face already, Kiryuu?
What?
No... It can't be!
Black-sama!
I can move...
Edwin Black. I've been waiting for this.
Indeed.
You didn't track me down.
I lured you here!
Nabelius!
I've found a way to beat you, the so-called immortal vampire.
Nabelius here is a bioweapon engineered from your very cells.
He may not look like you, but genetically, he's the same.
I wondered why you wanted to join my staff so badly.
And now it turns out you just wanted my DNA.
Yes!
Your genes, the very key to the immortality that you hold so dear!
However, your immortal genes can't save you from your own kind.
Nabelius has a venom that will kill you...
even if his teeth just graze you!
I'm in trouble then, aren't I?
Edwin Black, your reign is over!
Black-sama, watch out!
Sic him, Nabelius!
What's wrong, Nabelius?
Nii-sama!
Dogs. Always too dumb to know what they shouldn't eat.
Are you all right, sir?
Quite. Thank you, young Anti-Demon Ninja.
Guess I'm done here, then. Contract complete.
It's been real.
You're done here as well, Kiryuu.
In your dreams!
Damn you!
I am...
Invincible!
Well then...
Ingrid, put an end to this worm.
Yes,
Black-sama.
By the power residing in my body...
Burn to ashes!
Black-sama...
Quiet.
This is no time for words.
Right.
Thank you.