Why is my body hot?
Especially the area near my pussy is bothering me...
Oh, Jiburiru-chan...
...nothing is being done to you and you're making these sexual sounds.
Rococo...
My pussy feels hot!
Seems like the effect is showing already.
Why?
There's a boy's part on me!
I worked on your clitoris a bit while you were asleep.
Aren't you happy?
No! I don't want to have an embarrassing body like this!
This is punishment for not being able to make Aries fall.
My gosh, Jiburiru's penis is sending off a perverse aroma already.
What is this feeling?
The boy's part isn't too bad, right?
You're so fast.
It's okay. Just let it all out like this.
If you suck on it that hard, a hot one is going to come up!
No! It's going to come out!
Such thick semen... I feel like it's going to stick to my throat.
It's coming out...
The semen is pouring out...
Seeing how it is, it seems like it will keep on coming out.
Eternal Worm!
No! It's going in and out inside and sucking up the semen!
Not done yet. There's still your anus.
My butt! My anus!
No, the semen keeps on pouring out...
I'll make it so that you can't think of anything but sex and penis.
I'm going to fall apart...
I just came before and I'm about to come again!
It's coming out again! Lots of semen!
It's still coming out!
How much do you have to ejaculate to be satisfied?
But this feels good!
Did I push it too far?
How much longer are you going to keep on playing with Jiburiru?
You're not by any chance planning to let Aries go, are you?
I know.
It's not going to be like last time again.
Then you have a trick up your sleeve already?
Of course! But in exchange, I'm going to have you work this time around!
Of course, Jiburiru too...
Kazumi Osoda's horoscope of the day! Here I go!
The one with the best luck today is you, the one with the Virgo sign.
On the other hand, the worst luck today is...
I'm going to say it...
It's you, the one with the Aries sign!
No!
A rival fighting over the man in your heart might make an appearance...
...so be careful.
The next sign that has bad luck is...
Hikari, if you don't get going, you're going to be late.
Brother...
Don't be so down with just a fortune thing from TV.
I feel like I just want to not go to school today...
Man, Hikari, you're being so over dramatic...
Jinno-kun, Hikari-chan.
Good morning.
Otonashi!
Meimi-san!
You're okay to get around already?
Yeah, I'm sorry to worry you. I'm totally fine now.
A rival fighting over the man in your heart might make an appearance...
Maybe that new rival is Meimi-san?
I'm totally losing to her...
Brother! Sister Hikari!
That freaking hurt!
Where the hell were you looking!
Don't you hit the brakes before you run into people?
Brakes!
C-Calm down, Hikari...
T-That's right, Hikari-chan...
There are no brakes on a tricycle...
I'm so sorry. What am I doing?
For a second, you were scarier than a demon...
More importantly, Brother, it's terrible, it's terrible!
It's giga-terrible!
Oh, what's the matter?
It's information from the Heaven Information Division...
...and apparently the school was taken over by demons!
What!
Just what is going on?
No one is here and even though it's morning, it's so dark.
What is this feeling?
I have a really bad feeling about this.
Rika!
Sister Rika!
I was waiting for you guys, Naoto Jinno and Aries.
Oh, Meimi-chan is with you too?
Rococo, how could you do such a thing to Rika?
Hey Jiburiru, how does it feel...
...to be violated by the worm while being watched by Naoto Jinno?
It turns you on more than usual, right?
Nao-kun...
You're pouring that much love juice.
It seems like your pussy has become pretty sensitive.
Nao-kun, don't look...
Please don't look...
You little runt demon!
Let my Rika go!
My Rika?
Hikari, it's transformation time!
O-Okay...
Luv-kou!
Yes, sir!
Here we go!
Angel Amore!
Let me explain!
Hikari Jinno uses Amore power to transform into Holy Angel Jiburiru Aries!
It's Sister Rika and the school's trouble!
Do your best, Jiburiru Aries!
Once again, the shy maidens behind the flowers are shining and beautiful.
You capture those maidens and steal their purity erotica!
I won't forgive those perverse crimes!
I'm sorry, but this time around, I have business with Naoto Jinno.
Hikari!
You finally awake, Aries?
Luv-chan!
Sister Hikari...
Please let go of Luv-chan!
Well, I can let her go, but under a condition...
Condition?
What is the condition?
Aries, you must violate Meimi Otonashi who is next to you!
What?
You didn't hear me?
You have to violate Meimi Otonashi.
W-Why do such a thing?
There is no way I can do that!
Oh, really? Then let's have this one die.
Come on, worm!
Luv-chan!
Hikari-chan...
Meimi-san?
I don't mind. If this keeps on going, Luv-chan is...
Aries, if you are able to make Meimi come...
...then I will release this Lolita-complex angel.
Damn it, without Hikari, how am I supposed to save Rika?
What is that glow?
As I thought.
She's filled with shame and a pleasant feeling because you're watching her...
...which is magnifying the release of Jiburiru's sexual desire energy.
Nao-kun, it's so good...
My pussy and my butt are full!
It's just a matter of time now for Jiburiru to turn into the demon king.
It can't be...
Um, I'll try to make you come as soon as possible.
Okay, if you can, please tease my clitoris.
It should be fast that way.
Okay.
Hikari-chan is licking my clitoris...
Hikari-chan's tongue is hot and the love juice is all slimy...
Hey, Meimi, don't let Aries be the only one servicing you.
You should lick her pussy too.
It feels so good...
The bumps on your tongue are rubbing against my exposed clitoris...
Hikari-chan's tongue is coming in... No, that spot is dirty!
Hikari-chan, I want you to feel good too...
No...
Meimi-san, don't suck on my clitoris...
N-No, if you suck on it that much...
...I'm going to come!
I can't hold it in anymore either! My clitoris, I'm going to come!
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming...
It won't stop...
I came...
I came too...
Now's your chance, Eternal Worm!
No!
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing? I'm going to put an end to you guys.
Misty Mei! You're going to break the promise?
That is unfair!
Of course demons are unfair!
N-No! No!
Not the tentacles!
No! The sliminess came into me again!
It's moving...
The fat one is rubbing inside me!
If this keeps up, Meimi-san will be in trouble...
Then, I'll try it!
Amore power unleashing!
What is with this glow?
Amore ball!
Angel Drive Shoot!
I never thought Aries would have this much power...
Meimi-san!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, so please hurry, Hikari-chan.
Go save Manabe-san...
Sister Hikari, we need to go save Sister Rika right now!
Yeah.
The tentacle is going crazy inside...
It's so good...
Well, seems like Worm-chan is at his limit too.
No, Nao-kun's watching, but I'm going to come!
I'm going to come!
Rika came with that stupid tentacle?
Nao-kun, the tentacle made me come...
How stubborn...
We made you come that much, and you're still not a complete form.
I have no choice.
We need to have you reach climax once more!
No, I can't anymore...
Brother!
Sister Rika!
Hikari!
Thank goodness.
You were safe?
Why is Aries?
Misty Mei failed, huh?
That's right!
Sister Hikari beat that cockroach woman with her holy powers!
How could you do such a thing to Sister Rika...
I won't forgive you!
Angel Spreading Cutter!
Rika!
Nao-kun!
Brother, now's our chance!
Yeah!
Aries, I definitely won't let you get away.
Nurse's Office
Nao-kun...
I'm fine now, so don't worry about me.
O-Okay...
Hikari?
I'm okay. I'm just a little tired.
It seems like since she used her last move, she's totally out of Amore.
What?
Rococo might come attack again.
Rika's also not in any state to be able to fight.
What should we do, Luv-kou?
You don't have to worry about anything!
If you replenish the Amore here, then everything is okay!
Luv-chan, you mean...
Yes! Everyone's been waiting!
It's mating time!
On top of that, since there is less time this session...
...please take care of both of them at once!
So let's mate!
Mate! Mate!
I'm embarrassed to be in a pose like this...
Hikari-chan, your body is soft. It feels so good...
Maybe I should just move to this direction from here on.
What?
But I have a little curiosity about that stuff too.
Sister...
Hikari-chan, this part of you is starting to heat up.
Yeah, those are my petals...
These thin petals of yours have been quivering since a moment ago.
No, I'm embarrassed...
Sister, yours is also becoming hot.
Because you're so cute, Hikari.
Sister Rika's fingers are coming into my pussy...
Hikari-chan, your pussy is starting to get wet.
You too...
Sister Rika, yours is starting to become wet too.
Brother, you've been totally forgotten about.
Yeah...
I'm sorry to leave you all alone, Brother.
In exchange, we will warm you up inside us.
Rika, it feels so good...
Hikari, here I go.
Hikari, it's a lot tighter than usual.
Because you and Sister Rika are so close to me...
I'm embarrassed and it feels so good...
Hikari-chan, it's my first time seeing your face this sexy.
Sister Rika...
Hikari, this is bad. I feel like I'm going to come already!
I'm fine now, so please put it in Sister Rika now.
This feeling...it's Nao-kun's penis!
Rika, inside your pussy is really hot too!
I feel like I'm going to melt, Rika!
Nao-kun, please give it to me deeper!
I was waiting for this for the longest time!
Rika! I can't hold it in anymore!
Nao-kun, me too!
I'm about to come too!
Me too, I can't hold it anymore...
I'm about to come!
Hikari! Rika!
It's pouring into me... Nao-kun's semen...
You guys are such nymph angels for having sex at a time like this.
Found you! This time, I won't let you get away.
There you are Rococo!
Hikari-chan, let's go!
Yes!
Sis, now that your Amore is replenished...
...you can use your special powers!
Angel!
Double!
Cutter!
I won't forgive you...
I won't forgive you!
I'll get rid of all of you all at once!
This is bad!
Brother, throw the halo one more time!
If this keeps up, then Brother will be...
Hikari-chan! I'll stop it, so please defeat Rococo!
Sister Rika!
Vanish!
Even if I defeat Rococo, Sis will...
Hikari!
Gate of Heaven!
Sister Hikari, with your abilities right now...
...you should be able to use the sacred sword!
Go, Hikari!
Okay.
Excalibur!
It's no use!
Wha...
Aries!
Rococo!
What...
How could an angel take me down...
Yeah! You did it!
Yeah, yeah! You did it!
We finally defeated the demon!
Here, Brother!
Here, Brother! Nao-kun!
Hikari-chan, this is my job as his girlfriend!
No! This is my job as his sister!
Both of you, please get along. I'll eat both of them.
Jinno-kun...
Hey, Otonashi!
Um, I made a lunch box for you too.
If you would like...
Brother, I made one too!
Otonashi...
Hey, Nao-kun! What are you doing!
Brother, you do like bigger breasts better...
Leave that all aside! This is something that I have poured all my love into.
It's Luv special, 100% love juice!
Bon appetit!
I-It's good!
Love juice! Love juice!
Love juice! Luv's love juice!
Jinno-kun, you mean...
You love Luv-chan that much...
Brother, you perv!
Brother, you fool, fool, fool!
I don't really understand it well, but it's most likely a misunderstanding!
Let me explain!
Love juice is...
You don't have to explain it!
Little My Star. Little My Star. Little My Star.
If you open the door, all the different stories start.
The light that shines the roads you could get lost in...my theory...
Shoot your rocket up into my sky.
I will power up more than when I'm alone.
I know, forever and ever I couldn't decide. Yes!
Finally, finally understood.
If it was possible to tell the feeling clearly...
1, 2, 3, 4, you can!
Oh my, oh my, Little My Heart!
I will show my courage.
Fighting! Fighting! Little My Star!
Angel, please awaken. Yes!
Oh my, oh my, Little My Pain!
When it changes to strength.
Fighting! Fighting! Little Your Smile!
I found the night sky. Yes!
Little My Star. Little My Star. Little My Star.