Naoto...
This is embarrassing...
Is this... correct?
We can't help it. This is your training! Do you best, Rika!
It's hard for me too.
You sure don't look like it.
Now, the skirt.
I want to bury myself.
I know how you feel.
Someone... is there.
That's why it's good.
What is that?
Did you cum, Rika?
Angelic
Illusion!!!
Wow, five Rika... no Jiburiru!
We can have a group orgy with this!
Naoto, you pervert. Don't think like that.
Amazing!
Sheshh...
Jiburiru -The Devil Angel-
Vol. 3 Charm! Evil Seduction
Rika! No time to rest.
Next training!
Lets do this at home...
This is embarrassing...
What are you saying. This is an important training!
Naoto...
Naoto!
I'm going to move, Rika.
Rika... yours feels the best!
Mine...? You mean you had others?
I didn't mean that.
Rika, I'm glad you're my first...
Why?
I liked you since we were little.
Me too...
I can't have sex with anyone else.
This thing is only for you.
Naoto.
I'm going to cum soon.
Please cum.
I'll spray it over your butt.
Please, spray it.
It's warm. It's warm. Your thing is warm.
Rika, it was great.
It felt... good.
C'mon Rika!
Transform and lets see your new powers!
What's this new special attack again?
Lets see... it's called Angel Dynamite.
The functions?
I'm not sure. There's no pictures.
Angel!
Dynamite!!!
An amazing attack...
Loveriel, take care of the mess.
I will...
I ban this attack when I'm around!
What? You want to continue?
Train! Train! Train, Rika!
I want to call it a day, I'm tired.
I have to go home and do homework.
You should do homework too, Naoto.
Loveriel, lets go.
OK.
Man, I'm not satisfied yet.
You better be ready for tonight, Rika.
Oh, Naoto.
Hey, Reina.
How are you?
F, fine.
Be ready for what tonight?
Well, umm...!
Naoto, you live around here?
Umm...
Naoto?
Uh, Y, yes!!
Naoto, may I please stop by your house?
Um, but why?
I wanted to talk to you about Meimi.
About Meimi?
Yes.
Alright.
No!
No!!!! Please stop!!!!!!
How do we always get so close but end up losing against
Jiburiru.
I must attack her before she transforms, just like with
Meimi.
Asmodeus.
Ms. Reirouge!
Do you already have your next plan ready?
Things are getting as we speak...
I won't forgive failures.
Y, yes! Understood!
Alright, Meimi! It's time to attack!
Man, you sure are perverted.
Why am I always being attacked?
Hey Loveriel, do you know why?
To be honest, I don't have an answer.
One thing sure is that you have something.
Something?
There has to be a reason why Asumo and them are
always attacking you.
Reason?
You're here to protect me, right? Didn't you hear
anything?
I'm just a low-rank angel. I'm just following orders.
Either way, it's always about sex.
To get Amore for transformation is sex.
Enemies attack me with sex.
I just want a regular relationship with Naoto.
Am I a tragic heroine?
But sex feels really good, right?
Yeah...
Um! I don't think about that!
Rika, your face is red like an apple.
Loveriel, you are mean.
Here you go.
Why, thank you. I don't mean to be a pest.
No, you're not.
Thanks for the drink.
Naoto?
Y, Yes!
What are you looking at?
Errr, nothing.
I see.
Naoto Jinno... I guess I will help Asumo this one time.
Naoto...
Y... yes.
I think I want you, Naoto.
Wha, what!!?!!!?
What are you saying? I thought you wanted to talk about
Meimi.
Meimi? I can't remember.
Anyway, Naoto, I think...
I like you.
Naoto...
Naoto Jinno, the key for Jiburiru's transformation. I will
make sure to weaken him.
Reina, what are you...!?
I've been looking for the perfect young man.
Naoto, that is you...
See Naoto, aren't they big?
Don't my breast look delicious?
Reina...
You can have me anyway you want.
I can't do that, Reina.
Don't worry. I'll keep this our little secret.
That's not what I mean.
Oh my, you are already hard.
Naoto, you pervert.
I can't help it in this situation...
Wow, you are so big. Talk about being young.
Rei... Reina!
It feels too good...
So hard and delicious.
Amazing. Your cum is thick and juicy.
What the heck? She only sucked me for a bit and I
already came.
She's different from Rika.
Naoto.
Make me feel good too.
But, I have a...
You have what?
You have a girlfriend, so you can't?
Um... well... errr...
Don't say such nonsense.
You should take the offer while you can.
What's that word for this?
Take it while it's free?
I don't think that's it...
Good, it's good.
Naoto, it's deep inside.
Reina, your inside... feels so good!
I haven't had a... young man for a while!
This is my first time... having an older woman. Feels good!
I'm so happy that you're happy.
I can't hold it.
I'm going to cum!
It's ok, cum. Cum inside me.
B, but...
Don't worry. Give me all of it.
I'm sorry! But it felt so good I came inside.
Don't worry... lets do it again.
Huh?
The door is open, he must be home.
A women's shoe? Is someone here?
Give it to me from behind.
Naoto, do you have guests over?
Naoto?
Great, it feels great!
What is this?
It feels like it's swallowing my thing.
This feels to great!
Reina!
Naoto!
Right there... that's the spot.
Naoto, are you here?
Is a guest here?
It's great!
Naoto?
Reina, you're too loud!
That's dangerous.
I'm sorry, but it felt too good.
But I thought I heard Rika's scream.
I will have it with you today.
You mean 'finally'.
Shut the hell up!!
You can't do this to an angel.
Naoto, you're so great, almost like an animal. It's
wonderful.
Reina, your pussy is great too. It's like its own living thing!
You like it? Give me more then!
Great, it's great!
Stop it!
Naoto, help me!
Rika!?
Don't stop...
Please don't stop. Move your hips.
Great...
Naoto...
Naoto!
Naoto!!!!
Rika!!
Naoto!
Reina, I'm sorry!
Shit, I almost had him.
I can't believe it.
Naoto's sexual drive is higher than I expected.
You look like a whore.
Rika!!
You guys!!
Naoto!
Loveriel, your halo!
Rika!
Here!
I don't think I need to explain!
Rika Manabe transforms again!
That's it! Go for it! Fight for us, our angel!
Hey, demons!
You asked for it, you guys better get ready!
Shit!
Hey, Misty may... crap!
Jiburiru, do it!
Angel!
Dynamite!!!
No, wait! I hate that!
Rika...
Rika!
Naoto...
So... I'm saved again...
Rika, I'm sorry...
Why are you apologizing?
I was saved because you helped me transform into
Jiburiru.
I have Rika... my Rika.
What are you talking about, Naoto?
I'm right here.
Rika!
Naoto...
Naoto, it feels good...!
Rika.
Naoto!
Rika, you are the best.
I'm sorry, Rika.
Naoto!
Rika, I'm going to cum!
Naoto!!!!!
Rika!!!!!!
For the next round
I will take care of this face to face.
With my powers...
To be continued, Volume 4...