Damn.. How dare you lock me up!
Don't think that I'll end with this.
My my, your in a foul mood.
Misty May.
Feitus!
Oh.. how scary.
You must not behave that way to the one who saved you.
Hmp I didn't want any help.
Oh.. how regrettable.
I even thought of making you fight with the Jibril.
What!? You said Jibril!?
Oh your attitude changed.
Eternal worm!?
Failure is not acceptable in the next experiment.
You're weak you know.
I'll give you powers for special.
No.. stop it.. worm.
Shouldn't you listen to my orders?
It's impossible.
It's a special worm made by me.
How about you feel the tentacles with your own.
Isn't it good?
Don't fool around!
Is it good?
You're moaning so loud.
It doesn't feel good.
With this tentacles.
Oh yes, I forgot to tell you.
When I revived you, your virginity is also recovered too.
I think it will hurt a lot when the worm comes inside.
But I don't have a time so I'm sorry if I can't make you all wet.
Charge worms!
No!
Stop!!!
It's coming in.
The tentacles are coming inside me.
It's spreading.
Inside me is spreading.
I didn't thought you'll moan.
Even you only spit boos.
Shut up!
I'm Misty May!
I won't moan with this..
You're not honest.
Then how about this?
I injected you a love drug to make your nipples numb.
This warmth is from me.
I don't care about you.
Ok then, let's finish this.
Worms, start the power up.
I'm cumming.
Noo!
I think it's done perfectly.
With this, your power must be increased 30x.
You fool.
Did you not think that I can squeeze your neck with this power?
I don't need to worry about that.
With the power up device, I can also inject a certain device to your body.
What?
It's like a curse.
If I pray for it, it will run a serious pain to your body.
For example, like this.
Let me think of that device if you successfully bring the Jibril here.
My experiment will be successful if I have the Jibril's amore.
I will complete this before heaven will.
Right? My angel?
Jiburiru The Devil Angel
W
Oh, Rika's chocolate banana crape also looks delicious.
Can I eat a bit?
Sure.
Here ahhh.
Hey you ate too much.
One bite is one bite.
Nao-kun, you really..
Sorry.
Here eat my double cream strawberry too.
But.. but..
If I eat the part you've eaten..
It will be an indirect kiss.
It's embarrassing.
They're really stupid lovers.
Even of it's just a Hawaii souvenir.
There's really stupid lovers.
Hey Hikari.
I don't accept it!
An indirect kiss in front of your sister.
Nao-kun.
It's really hard being a popular guy right?
You you.
Don't make fun of me.
Love-kou.
But Onii-chan, Rika-oneechan and Hikari-oneechan.
You think seriously about which of them you'll choose.
Even you say who will I chose,
I already...
No!
Help me.
What's that?
Nao-kun!
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hmp.
Don't strip my panties.
Here here.
Here's the just striped female student's panties.
1st come 1st serve.
How about 10,000 yen for one?
10,000 yen? That's too high!
It's too high!!
Is that so?
Then how about 1000 yen?
Give me 3.
Me too!
That's..
Credit! Credit!
Isn't she…
Misty May??
What's she doing?
Selling off the girls panties 90% off,
I won't forgive her!
There's no time for watching it Nao-kun.
Oh yeah.
Then, let's transform.
Onii-chan, the ring!
Here I come, Rika!
Angel amore!
Give the violet one.
Mine is this stained one.
Ok ok, fall in line.
Hey you wait!
You are!?
Panties are the life of a woman!
It's unforgivable to smell it!
With that harassment.
Being spread in the world.
I won't forgive that erotical crime.
Hmp, so you've finally come Jibril.
Misty may, I won't forgive you!
Try it if you can.
What? Is this all you've got?
No way, she doesn't budge an inch.
Sorry if you even show up but,
I don't have a time to play.
Eternal worm!
Rika-oneechan, watch out!
Hikari!
Hikari-chan.
She's Jinno Hikari
How dare she disturb me.
It's terrible, Hikari-oneechan has been captured!
It's alright.
There's was no certain Jibril order.
We'll retreat.
See you later.
Give back Hikari-chan to us!
Hikari!
Onii-chan!
Hikari!!!
Damn!
That Misty May..
After Rika, she attacked Hikari..
Damn.
I really won't forgive you.
Misty May has powered up a lot compared before.
I don't think Rika can fight against her.
At least, I need one more Jibril to fight with us.
What's this?
What!? Is it Misty May?
Uhm...Oh..You...
Do you have some business with my..
Nao-kun
Onii-chan.
What's the sound right now?
Ah, Nao-kun...
Rika, calm down. Let's talk about this.
Stupid!!!!
It's hot, My body is hot.
I applied a fast effecting love drug in your pussy.
How is it? You can't even comfort yourself with that right?
Misty May-san, I..
Don't worry.
These ones will play with you instead of me.
Noooo!!
It's already wet.
No don't look at it.
Wow, it's staining.
You're crotch is getting bigger.
I want to watch it more but,
I must get into the main part.
Hey worms, rape Aries as much as you want!
The thick one is coming in.
It's big..It's bigger than Onii-chan's.
No..It's coming.
I'm cumming.
What is this?
It'll come out.
Nooo..There's a milk coming out from my boobs.
Ok, the next is here.
That part I can't..
That part? Where are you referring to?
Nooo, even you know that.
I know, but worms are dumb.
So if you don't say it, they don't understand.
I said the puss..
The puss?
No I really can't say it.
Then we can't help it.
Noooo!!
It's thrusting in the ass hole,
No way!
I.. I!
Why.
I'm cumming..I'm cumming.
After the milk is the juice?
How much you will flow it out until you satisfy?
What are you soaking for?
We haven't come once here.
Right worm?
Let's continue.
No way...wait..
Are you sure?
If you bite it, The worm will rage out.
It's not good just to behave.
Let it feel good.
No.
Don't come in..
I can't breath.
Why don't you let the worm do what they want?
So that you'll just end up being raped by the worm.
I think they reached their limit.
The worms will ejaculate.
They will release it inside you!
Oh, you fainted because you came a lot.
Wow this is great..This is great Misty May.
The pure amore is charging up.
With this, I can complete my artificial living being.
Oh my god, the power of amore is going beyond my expectations.
At this rate.
Damn, that fool.
Hey, are you alright?
Damn, I didn't think that amore is this powerful.
We can't help it, I'll put it and back to the start.
Is Aries alright?
Aries is back.
How cruel..You're cruel Onee-chan.
What's this mean Feitus?
I think it's because we absorbed all the amore.
She fallen in to demon because of its side-effects.
Don't take Onii-chan.
Even he's my Onii-chan.
Why are you taking Onii-chan?
We failed in amore's recovery but,
I think we can use her.
It was a bit fast delivery.
Love-kou, I see this is your doing.
Yes, This is a secret device made to save Hikari-oneechan,
She is the artificial living being Jibril made in heaven.
A Jibril!? This tiny kid?
First introduce your self.
I'm called Nagi, The 6th angel frame made in heaven.
Nice to meet you Nagi-chan,
I'm Manabe Rika.
And this guy here is Jinno Naoto.
That girl there is Loveriel-chan.
I'm love.
I save it.
Let get along Nagi-chan.
My mission is to save Jinno Hikari..
Getting alone is not part of my mission.
Are you really sure brining her to the school?
It's alright.
I wrote in her application paper as Onii-chan's cousin.
Yes, there's no problem.
Nao-kun, you have another sister.
Nooo.
Stop.
Ok then, who's next?
Leave your Bulma and panties.
It's the under ware which the sweat in the morning practice is stained, It will surely sold at high price.
Misty may!
I wonder why I heard screams.
As I thought it was really you who cause the trouble.
You appeared finally.
We won't be the same like last time.
We got a secret weapon you know.
A secret weapon?
Ok, Nagi, transform!
Onii-chan, please don't throw the ring on your own.
Hey Nagi
What's the matter!
Nagi-san?
Even you said transform, I still lack of amore.
So I can't transform.
What!?
Nao-kun, I'll be the one to transform.
Rika, but you..
It's alright, if my punches wont work, I still have my secret technique.
Ok, But don't over do your self.
Onii-chan, here's the ring.
I'll leave it to you Rika!
Angel amore!
How erotic, disgracing the sweat of the girls I won't forgive this erotic crime!
What's the secret weapon?
It's still the same Jibril.
Nao-kun, bring Nagi-chan and run away.
Lets go Nagi.. Love, you too.
Yes.
Just wait Rika, I'll surely come back to save you.
Angel gorgeous attack!
Ok then, it's good that we ran to the infirmary but,
What are you going to do??
I need to copulate to charge the amore, We came here for that reason.
Well, I know that but..
I can't fight if we won't copulate.
Ok everyone, here the one we have waited.
It's amore time.
I'm going to start.
Here I come.
I'll be taking the video in a secret place.
It's the same one as I see in the bath.
Is it good?
Yeah it's good.
The tip is sensitive compared to the root.
Yeah.
The speed too, it got hard when you change the speed compared to constant one.
What's your request?
If there's another of method make you feel better, tell me
Ok then, the mouth..Use the tongue and lick it.
Roger.
Nagi.. it'll come out..It'll come out.
Release it.
It's coming out!
Sorry for making it dirty, I can't hold it.
No problem.
Aside from that, I don't know why but my lower body is weird.
It's something like ache or it wants something.
I understand, then.
Why are you not wearing anything?
What? Please do something with this ache.
Oh, yes.
I'm being licked.
Why there's some liquid flowing out from there?
It's because you feel it.
Ok then, I'm going to put it in.
Put in what?
It's coming in.
Wow,
it has a hymen.
Deflowing confirmed.
Nagi, does it hurt?
It's alright.
So please continue.
Ok.
It so good inside Nagi.
Naoto, what should I do?
Somethings coming inside me.
There something coming inside that part.
I don't know..I don't know.
Nao-kun..I'm afraid..
It's alright, leave it to me.
It's coming..I'm cumming.
No..
I'm going crazy.
I've been raped by worm and going crazy..
Ok worms,
you can release it inside your favorite Jibril.
No..No..You can't release it inside,
I'm going to get pregnant.
I'm going to be the mother of a worm's baby.
Noooo!
How is it?
You don't want to taste this again right?
Hey, just come to demon world with me.
I don't want to, I'm a heavenly angel Jibril.
Even how I'm being raped,I won't listen to you.
Ok since we can't help it,
I'll just add more tentacles and rape you again.
Don't complain if you brake.
Go eternal worm!
Nao-kun.
Nagi-chan.
Rika, sorry for being late.
What!? She crushed it with bare hands?
Angel amore.
She transformed on her own?
Who are you?
I came to earth along the new era.
You demons must retreat.
This evil harassment, I won't forgive this perverted crime.
So this is the artificial living thing Jibril.
Heavenly angel Jibril Zero!
Newly arrived!
To be continued...