Gosh, I only looked at the worm...
...and started to have perverted feelings again.
Thanks for waiting.
Huh?
You're horny already?
But...
Well, well, you really became a perverted angel, huh?
I can't take it...
Okay! Then I will make you fall completely today!
I'm sorry, Nao-kun.
It seems like I look forward to Roco's training now.
T-There! It tickles!
No, don't expose the clitoris! That's a sensitive spot!
We just exposed your clitoris, then your pussy's entrance just closed up.
No! Don't say that...
I'm so embarrassed and l...
Wow, the love juice just came pouring out all at once!
No! It's embarrassing me and I'm getting all hot...
You're making such dirty sounds...
Gosh, Jiburiru-chan, you're such a perverted angel.
Yes, I'm a perverted angel...
Wow, you've become pretty honest, huh?
Okay, I'll give you a treat!
The worm's coming inside!
Deeper...a lot deeper!
Apparently that's what she wants.
Stick it in there a lot deeper like you're plowing into her uterus!
It's in me!
It's pounding my uterus! It's so good!
My breasts are being massaged and my pussy...the tentacle is going crazy!
My butt! My anus!
It's rubbing inside my pussy...
My pussy and my butt are both full!
Aren't you in sheer bliss because both are being fulfilled?
Y-Yes, I'm very happy.
I'm going to go crazy...
If I stay like this, I'm only going to have sex left in my mind!
It's been that way already!
You perverted angel!
I-I can't, anymore...
All right then, we'll put an end to it.
Worm-chan, shoot it in her!
It's full...
My stomach is full of semen...
Well, well, you're covered in semen.
Are you satisfied now?
No...
I-I still want it...
I want more of the worm's dirty semen.
It's delicious...
That's good! That's good, Jiburiru-chan!
I'll do more erotic things to you!
Really? I'm so happy!
Here!
Okay!
Pass! Pass!
Run!
Over here!
Yeah, over here!
Run, the side!
Nice shot!
Brother!
Yo!
What happened to class?
Brother, what are we going to do in a place like this?
Today, we're going to try a threesome!
A threesome is...
What! No way!
I don't want to have sex with someone other than you!
And even though you say threesome, there's nobody besides you and me.
Don't worry about it, Hikari!
In situations like this, she shows up even if we don't call her.
She?
Yeah, she...
Right there!
Brother, did you call me?
It did hit you.
Sister, the way you were surprised...
...it's as if I'm a beautiful girl angel!
No, no one thinks that.
Why is Luv-chan in a place like this?
That's because the third person is myself, that's why!
Hikari, it's okay if it's us three, right?
Well, if it's Luv-chan...
Yeah, we did it!
Mating, mating, mating!
Luv-chan, don't say it so many times. It's embarrassing...
Sister, please stick out your tongue.
What? Like this?
Okay, Hikari, now get on all fours.
Like this, Brother?
Yeah, that's good, Hikari.
I'm kind of embarrassed, Brother...
On top of that, if you rub that much, my underwear is going to get dirty...
Then, I'll take it off for you.
No, I'm embarrassed!
My pussy... Brother's fingers are rubbing it...
I'm going to come... I'm about to come...
I'm sorry...
I'm going to come...
I'm going to come!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Sister Hikari, you come too fast.
The Amore doesn't get filled up that way.
I'm sorry. I couldn't hold it in...
One more time, let's try again!
Sister, please lick my pussy thoroughly.
Okay...
It's an even more amazing sensation than I thought...
B-Brother...
Y-Yeah...
It's good...
It's about ready.
Brother, please put this big penis inside Sister.
O-Okay.
Hikari, I'm putting it in.
Yeah...
It's coming in me!
A really thick one is coming into my pussy!
It's coming all the way to the back!
It's tight...the back of my pussy is really tight!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, so please move, Brother.
So please, Brother, give my pussy a lot of Amore!
My pussy feels amazing again...
Sister Hikari's is delicious...
Luv-chan, your pussy is sweet and delicious too.
Hikari, it's getting close now. It's about to come out!
It's okay, Brother, let it out.
Please pour a lot of Amore inside me!
Hikari, I'm going to pour it in you!
Hikari!
There's semen pouring out of my pussy...
Are you okay, Hikari?
Yeah, it was amazing, Brother.
Sister, you definitely powered up now!
Then, let's take a look into that powered up ability, why don't we!
You're...
Rika?
There's no mistake! It's Rika!
Thank goodness! You were safe?
It's me, Naoto!
What's wrong, Rika? Say something already!
Hey, that is Rika, right?
Brother, something doesn't seem right...
Sorry, Naoto Jinno.
Jiburiru-chan has already become my sexual slave.
She wouldn't even turn her ear to listening to your voice.
You demon runt!
What the hell did you do to Rika?
Shut up! Don't call me a runt!
Eternal worm!
Brother!
This is the punishment you deserve for calling me a runt!
How could you do this to Brother? You won't get away with this!
Luv-chan!
Yes!
Angel Amore!
You pull in those who have no sin.
Erotica that wets their panties!
I won't forgive those perverse crimes!
My loyal sexual slave, Jiburiru-chan!
Make Aries fall completely!
Please leave it to me, Rococo-sama.
Long time no see, Hikari-chan.
Sister Rika!
Hikari!
N-No, that spot is...
Well, well, your clitoris became this big!
You're going to squash it!
You cry with such a nice voice...
Here, I'll make it stronger!
What a perverted clitoris!
This is how you seduced Nao-kun, right?
No, you're wrong.
N-No! It's going to come out...
I'm going to pee!
Why don't you wet your pants as much as you need, Hikari-chan!
N-No! It really is going to come out!
It's coming out...
That's a lot! So embarrassing!
I-It won't stop...
It's so embarrassing...
Don't worry about it, Hikari!
In my books, wetting your panties is a good job!
That's just because you're a pervert!
Sister Rika, right there...
This spot turns you on, right?
Your nipple is hard too.
What a reaction!
Hikari-chan, you like sex that much, huh?
My body is getting hot on its own, and it's so good it turns me on!
Then you like being abused by tentacles too, right?
A thick one is coming in!
It's moving inside of me too!
It's rubbing! The tentacle is rubbing inside my pussy!
It's grinding inside me...
I love the tentacle...
I love it!
Hikari, you like it too?
I like it. I love it!
I love having sex with tentacles!
Hikari! Why are you saying such vulgar things!
I don't remember raising you into a little sister like that!
It seems like Aries finally became the worm's prisoner too.
Sister Rika, I'm going to break soon!
Me too...
Together, okay?
Together!
Come on, Worm-chan! Pound the white stuff into them like usual!
I'm going to die!
I'm going to come!
I-I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming too!
I'm going to squirt stuff out too!
My stomach is becoming filled with the tentacle's semen!
I love this feeling... It really turns me on...
This is bad, Brother!
If this continues, Sister Hikari is going to be...
I'm so happy the tentacle came inside me...
I'm so happy...
Luv-kou! Hikari is...Hikari is...
She's never said such a thing to me before!
P-Please calm down, Brother.
Come on, Hikari-chan, let's fall deeper down together.
Yes, Sister Rika...
H-Hikari! No, get yourself back together!
Hikari!
It's no use.
Hikari, please don't!
If you go over there too, I'm...I'm...
...going to become alone again!
No!
Don't cry, Hikari!
I will definitely protect you, Hikari!
What is this!
Hikari...
T-This can't be. Why?
Aries should have already been fallen.
Eternal Worm!
Rococo!
This is the power of love between Brother and l!
It was so close!
Wait!
Rika!
She did it!
Sister Hikari got rid of the demon!
Yeah!
I sparkled!
Brother.
When I was still little you comforted me like this, remember?
So this time, it's my turn to comfort you, Brother.
Hikari...
Yeah?
Why is my heart pounding this much?
Hikari's my stepsister.
Brother, you can do sexual stuff to me.
H-Hikari...
Not because of Amore or anything...
...but because I want to be embraced by you as a woman.
Hikari, l...
It's okay, Brother, please...
My breasts...they're both being massaged...
I really like your breasts, Hikari. They're so soft...
Brother, my nipples... It feels so good...
Brother's tongue is licking my precious spot!
Can I lick it harder?
Just a little bit, okay?
It feels good. It's being rubbed by Brother's tongue...
It feels so good...
Brother, no!
If you play with my clitoris that much...
It's really intense...
No! Not there!
It turned you on that much?
You want me to tease it more?
No...
I...I...
I want you to put it in...
I want you to put your big one into my pussy.
Hikari...
Brother's hard one is moving intensely inside me!
Oh no! My spot is starting to feel numb!
Where do you mean by my spot?
Tell me.
That spot where you and I are connected as one.
My...
No! I'm embarrassed!
Brother...
Brother, I'm going to come!
I'm about to come!
Me too...I'm about to come too!
I can't anymore! Brother!
Brother!
Hikari!
It seems like Brother is feeling better.
I thoroughly recorded what was going on before!
If I have this, I can have about three bowls of rice easily!
Brother's face while he's sleeping is so cute.
Rika...
It's okay! I will definitely save Sister Rika.
So it's okay if I keep you to myself until then, right?
Little My Star. Little My Star. Little My Star.
If you open the door, all the different stories start.
The light that shines the roads you could get lost in...my theory...
Shoot your rocket up into my sky.
I will power up more than when I'm alone.
I know, forever and ever I couldn't decide. Yes!
Finally, finally understood.
If it was possible to tell the feeling clearly...
1, 2, 3, 4, you can!
Oh my, oh my, Little My Heart!
I will show my courage.
Fighting! Fighting! Little My Star!
Angel, please awaken. Yes!
Oh my, oh my, Little My Pain!
When it changes to strength.
Fighting! Fighting! Little Your Smile!
I found the night sky. Yes!