Noooooo!
She isn't it either... oh well... hehehe.
Rika...
No, something has to change!
I have to change this situation during this summer!
I'll tell her!
Naoto...
Once Rika comes, I'll tell her this!
Rika! We've been friends for a long time!
We've been friends ever since we've met!
Lets stop this relationship!
And be my...!
Why the serious face, Naoto?
Um, Rika...!
Hey, Rika!
Y, yes!
PL, please go out with me!
But, Naoto... I'm here with you right now.
That's not what I mean, Rika... I'm trying to say,
please be my...
I've finally found you! You must be Rika Manabe!
Yes, I am!
W, who is this kid?
Little Boy, it's not safe climbing trees.
I'm not a kid or a little boy!
I am a private from Hell's army, the great Asumo!
Um, what were we talking about?
That's right, I was proposing my love to you!
Huh?
Uh...
H, hey...
Naoto...
Rika, please be my girlfriend!
R, Rika, what's wrong? Did you not like it?
That's not it...
Hmm?
I'm happy...
So... does that mean you will be my girlfriend?
Yes, I will! Please let me. I hope I'll be your best
girlfriend ever!
Hurray!
You fools...
Rika, it's so great!
Lets go home and talk about something fun.
Yes, and lets also have sex!
Not until we're married!
Hehe, sorry.
You mortals... how dare you ignore the great demon...
DIE!
Naoto!
Let go... of Rika!
Rika Manabe! I will corrupt your soul!
Ri... Rika!
Hold it right there!
Huh?
I command you to let go of them now!
Who are you!?
I'm the angel apprentice, Loveriel!
You damn peon, go to hell!
Rika!
Argh!
Devil Storm!
Angelic Wind Storm!
Wha, what is it!
I will remember you... you Angel!
Wait... you Dem... on...
H, Hey!
Hey, Rika.
Y, yes?
Didn't they say they were demons and angels?
Yes, they did.
What should we do with her?
Lets take her to the hospital.
N, no...
What you mean no...
I, I can't be lying down. I have to hurry up and get
that demon kid!
What, an angel!!
Although, I'm still under training.
I was sent to this realm because we've heard that the
demons are up to something.
I was following the scent of the demons and found
you two being attacked so I came to the rescue.
What are their plans?
That little demon was trying to do something on Rika.
I see, so the demons were after you.
I...
Do not worry! Now that I'm here, I will protect you.
...however... I'm weakened and I won't be able to stay
here much longer.
Don't say that.
Then what should we do?
Don't worry, that's what this book is for.
Lets see here... when an angel can't engage in battle,
have someone lend you a helping hand.
In return, they can transform into the holy battle angel.
The holy battle angel?
Transform? A super hero? Alright, let me do it!
I am sorry, but a man can't do this job.
Why is that?
Because angels are all girls.
I see...
You need this halo to transform into an angel, but...
Yes!
Rika, you're going to transform?
Yes! I'm the one they are after, so might as well fight
for myself!
Rika, you're right!
But, seems like there's more to it than the halo.
Just hurry up and transform Rika.
Um, in order to transform, you need some Amore.
Amore?
Amore is the point of love. Hmm... I see... well, lets
start saving Amore.
How do you save up for Amore?
Lets see...
I found it, it's right here.
What do you have to do?
Make love with opposite sex you care for... is what is
says.
Make love?
Make love...
Whaaaaaaaa!!
What's there to be surprised about?
Well, lets get going. You have to make love to store
Amore, otherwise, you can't transform.
Get going, come on.
Loveriel!
Oh, I don't have much time...
Are you sure...
Naoto...
Rika...
Y, yes...
Who would've though I would...
Naoto...
OK!
Rika...
But...
But?
I'm... afraid...
It's ok... I'll make sure you feel safe.
Leaving an angel out here... you're guys are going to
be punished... it's so hot...
Naoto, be gentle with me...
Naoto... why... why...
Hey, you
I, I, I like him so much.
You were the girl that was crying at the park, weren't
you?
So this is the pain of being rejected...
Rejected?
Naoto... I like you so much... why do you have to be
with Rika...
You are jealous of the two, aren't you?
Is it impossible for this love to be true...?
Don't you hate Rika, the girl who took your guy away
from you? Don't you want to hurt her?
Hate... Yes I do hate...
Who are you?
I am the great Asumo, a soldier from the Hell's army!
Um...
To make a long story short, I'm going to take
advantage of you.
What?
Use your dark emotions to bring chaos to this world!
Whaaaaa!?
Here I go!
And... poke!
W, what is this feeling?
The demonic transformation!
Looks like the transformation was a success.
Today you will call yourself... lets see... Misty May!
You will do really bad things from now on!
Go, Misty May! Go destroy the town for fun!
Did you just tell me to destroy?
Huh?
Who in hell do you think you're talking to?
Who else, I'm talking to you, Misty May!
Be careful how you talk to me. I'm angry enough that
I have a private as my slave!
Don't you dare talk back to me!
sl, slave!?
I can't hear you ?
Y, Yes!
I guess I'll go destroy for some fun.
I, I said tha...
Rika...
Naoto...
My neck... no...
Does it feel good?
I don't know, I'm so nervous.
Don't touch it, please...
I can't do anything without touching.
No, please!
It's ok, I'll be gentle.
That's not it!
It's alright...
No...
Oh...!
Rika, you're...
I was to embarrassed to let you find out...
Rika, I'm touching your little spot.
It's so embarrassing... I want to bury myself in a hole
...
I'm grown up, but I still have no pubic hair.
Don't' worry about it, I'm so happy.
I know something about you that no one else knows.
Naoto...
Please... stop...
Rika, this is your...
So cute...
It's embarrassing... don't look...
The last time you saw my thing was when we took a
bath together as little kids.
Well, it's all grown up now.
I'm... afraid...
Relax...
So tight...
It hurts, it hurts...
Relax your muscles...
I am...
I can't penetrate her...
It hurts, right?
Yes, it does...
This is her first time... I should concentrate on the
foreplay...
My nipples, they are... oh!
I'm so embarrassed I just want to die...
Nipples getting hard.
Hmm, it feels great.
I'm about to cum.
But, I want to cum at the same time with Rika, since
this is her first time.
I want to orgasm with Rika.
Naoto!
Do, don't lick... ah!
Ri, Rika... your... oh!
It should be fine now.
You're going to stick it in? Stick it in?
Yes, I am.
Ouch, It hurts! It hurts!
...It hurts...
I'm going to move, relax alright?
Ri, Rika!
Nao... Naoto!
I'm going... to cum!
Rika... I'm going to cum!
No, no, not the inside!
Rika...
I was so afraid...
Rika, you did well... Attagirl.
Naoto...
Did you guys finish making love?
Is making love something to be embarrassed about?
Drop it! We have Amore stored now right!? What to
do next?
Yes, you have nothing to worry about.
While you guys were making love, I was studying how
to the Angelic Ceremony!
Angelic Ceremony?
What is that?
Please, no more!
What just happened?
Beats me...?
That's what you get for walking around in the park
holding hands!
Man, what a bitch...
Alright, here are the steps for the Angelic Ceremony,
listen up.
Lets first start with Angel Cutter.
In order to learn this attack, you must...
either have sex with her breast or anal sex, so it says.
Anal sex!?
Really?
And, why these two possibilities?
Looks like it's different depending on the current
status.
The two ways are better known as the Hell Form and
Heaven Form.
What do you mean?
I'm not quite sure, but the anal is the Hell Form and
the breast is Heaven Form.
The way they learned are different, but the results are the
same.
It means, you can pick the way you want.
I see!
Next is, Angel Shadows.
The Hell Form is exposure fetish and the Heaven
Form is feet fetish.
That's... great!
The next one sounds powerful.
It's called Angel Mermaid Stance.
That sounds awesome.
Hell Form is outdoors and Heaven Form is costume
play.
I see, I'll do my best!
This sounds deadly, Angel Dynamite.
Sounds strong.
Heaven Form is bathroom play, Hell Form is
masturbation.
Wow, I'm so happy! What's next?
Next is... Angel Overdrive.
Wow, sounds deadly!
To learn that... Heaven Form is 3way and Hell Form is
S&M.
3way? But with who? Rika, lets do our best for this,
ok?
Rika?
I can't do all that...
Please, no more!
Huh?
You guys are... so cruel...
Hmm, look who decides to drop by.
Don't get in my way!
Rika Manabe, I will not forgive you! Prepare for your
death!
What! But how do you know my name?
I will crush you!
Rika!!
Naoto!
Rika, transform!
Alright!
Angel Amoooore!
Let me explain! Rika Manabe transforms into a the
holy battle angel with the power of the Amore Power.
By the way, she saves up for this power by having
sex. Sex is the secret to her powers!
Devil Angel Jiburiru, at your service!
What!?
I can forgive a little mischief, but I can not forgive you
when you get innocent civilians involved!
This act must stop now!
I, Loveriel, can not fight right now, so I'm letting
Jiburiru taking care of you guys!
You stupid angel, don't copy what I do!
Let go of the innocent people, now!
In your dreams!
Rika is... fighting...
The halo is helping her fight.
But it is Rika who is using it to its potential!
Really? Wow, you are amazing, Jiburiru!
She's already in danger!
You are so weak!
Ri, Rika... That's it! Use the Angel Cutter!
I don't know how to use it...
Naoto, did you have sex with her breast or anal?
I did have sex with the breast...
The breast!?
Strange... she'll learn the attack naturally if done
properly...
Well, I did have my thing between her boobs...
Did you cum with that?
Well, not with her breast...
Why!
Well, it was her first time and I wanted something
normal!
Anal sex?
Sex means sex! Where else would I stick it in, stupid!
You called me stupid!
Well, did you cum?
I did!
How?
I ejaculated towards her...
Ejaculation!?
Hey, don't touch her butt! I am going to be the first
one to have some of that!
What the hell!
Hey, Rika...
Rika...
Naoto...
She came to her senses!
Oh, I...!
Where are the enemies? What about the people?
The enemies ran away, but the people are safe; they
won't remember a thing about this, thanks to me.
Naoto... I'm glad...
Rika...
Where is this? This is... let go...
You screwed up, so now you're being punished... plus,
you treated me bad.
I'm, I'm sorry. Please stop... stop... please...
I do not like foreplay.
Huh?
Thrust it!
It hurts... it hurts...
This is your first time... how pathetic... I can't even pity
you.
Naoto...
Gentle... ok...
You seem like you are ready for it...
Rika!
It hurts...
I'm ok, so... so...
I'm going to... cum inside!
Rika!