Ingrid pursues the traitor Kiryuu Sabat.
Soon, however, he traps her in a dark church,
where she is attacked by lustful beasts.
Ingrid is injected with an aphrodisiac and then ravaged.
Kiryuu aims to break her and make her into a sex slave.
Makai Kishi Ingrid
Episode 02 Masochist Murasaki
At first you wanted to bite my dick off, but now you're behaving well.
You're awfully cute when you're taking two cocks at once.
I can't understand a word you're saying.
Yeah, here it comes! Swallow it all!
We fucked you good and painted you white with our cum.
How's that feel, Dark Knight?
You vile slabs of filth.
Looks like the party's in here.
Yikes.
Only Edwin Black-sama's aide could muster up
that kind of angry mug at a time like this.
Kiryuu, you won't get away with this... holding me here,
not to mention stabbing Black-sama in the back.
You'll pay, do you hear me?
Well.
If that's how you feel, why don't we bring
your precious Black-sama here?
What?
I'll bring in Edwin Black.
And you'll help me do it.
How does that sound?
What makes~
What makes you think you can do that?
What makes you think I can't? It's all been arranged.
You're funny.
Let's see, let's see. What should I use?
Or would you like to change your attitude?
Shut up, you slime.
Dr. Slime, if you please. I'm a scientist. An explorer.
In my quest for the meaning of life,
I've torn skin, cut out organs, and sucked bones of their very marrow.
Of this I assure you.
Now, then...
Luckily for you, I'm bored with simply dissecting people.
So today I'll show you the beauty and wonder of science,
using your body.
I'll cut you up, gradually, starting at your
fingertips and continuing down.
Then I'll stitch you up like new and start all over again.
It's going to be fun.
You'll cry, writhing in exquisite agony.
Degenerate.
Can you picture it? Does it excite you?
Your beautiful body, locked in an endless
hell of destruction and reconstruction.
What fun.
What absolute fun.
Do what you want. You haven't got what it takes to break my will.
Even dripping with cum, your defiant strength is beautiful.
You truly are a Dark Knight
But your strength is not what I want to see.
I want to see you make a different face.
You can do that, right?
You know, like her...
So you're alive, Kiryuu.
More or less.
I did die once, but I'm back now.
You should try it, Murasaki.
Having your head cut off is a one-of-a-kind experience.
Prepare to die, scum.
I told you, I did already!
I'll never forget it.
The skin splitting, the vertebrae disconnecting,
seeing the blood gush out my neck with
the eyes in my own disembodied head!
The price of my rebirth: Having this ugly body.
Freak.
It's your fault that I'm like this!
I liked my original body.
But you destroyed it!
You left me with this awful husk!
Serves you right.
Human or not, you mess with black magic, you pay the price.
Shut up!
I'll show you the pain and humiliation I experienced. Have some!
Pretty weak for a guy who cheated death.
How did you know where to find me?
Huh?
This warehouse is unknown to most.
Even to many in' the Chaos Arena's inner circles.
How did you find out about this place?
What are you trying to say?
Don't you see?
You didn't track me down. You were Hired here by me!
A trap, huh?
This ends now!
I'm dying!
Dying, dying, dying, dying! Dying again!
Feeling wounded?
You won't come back this time.
I'll take your head with me.
Will you?
What the~
What is this...
I'm so...
So hot?
Kiryuu... what have you done?
Your blood's been spiked with an aphrodisiac.
That's why your body's burning.
A normal human would faint at the mere smell of this drug.
But you...
See?
Stop it...
Stop!
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
Don't cum yet, we're just getting started.
Just getting started!
What is that?
Do you know what this is for?
Don't you dare inject anything into me!
I can feel it... pumping in...
Did you just have an injection-induced orgasm?
We're not even close to being done here.
That hurts!
I don't think so. What you're feeling...
It isn't pain, is it?
It feels... good? It feels good.
The pain... feels good.
Exactly, and it's thanks to that injection. See?
Stop...
So sood!
The pain is so good!
How's this part of you feeling?
As I predicted.
What?
You're a virgin.
When your hymen breaks, that'll feel good, too.
You'll never forget your first time. Isn't that what they always say?
Please...
Wait...
How's it feel to lose your virginity to the guy you killed?
This is a most rare circumstance, indeed.
You beast!
Don't make that face. Your first time is supposed to be beautiful.
Get a good look at my face.
Never forget who was your first!
Get your ugly mug away from me!
God, it's rough! Plunging so deep into me!
It's making such an awful sound!
Something's happening deep in my body.
Something terrible is coming.
Something terrible, but... oh, God!
Yes! An orgasm! Cum for me!
I'll fill you up with my seed!
No!
I feel so much hot slimy goo oozing into me.
Looks like you enjoyed that. We must have chemistry, Murasaki-kun.
But if you think we're finished...
What are you doing?
Time for your next lesson.
W-Wait!
It hurts!
It's so deep inside me...
Feel that? Can you feel me pushing into you?
You like having your ass raped, don't you?
No. Get your disgusting tentacles off of me, you fiend!
Is that how you feel?
I guess I'll have to try harder.
Stop...
Stop it!
I don't want you in my ass...
Not in my ass...
God, my ass! It's going to burst!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Semen...
Semen is pooling up inside... deep in my bowels...
You've fainted from the strength of your orgasm.
But this is far from over, Murasaki-kun.
What are you... doing this time?
What? What is this?
What are you going,to do with that?
I think you know.
No! Enough. No more!
Shut your mouth!
No... No!!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you all for joining my soiree.
I have a special treat for you, my distinguished guests.
I've captured the first aide to our mutual enemy, Edwin Black.
This woman.
Dark Knight Ingrid. She has withstood all my torture thus far.
No matter what we do, she does not break.
It would seem the word "submission" doesn't exist in her vocabulary.
Or so I thought...
...until I found the Dark Knight's weak point.
This pitiful sow values her pride over all else.
Her high self-opinion will be her undoing.
The semen from a week-long rape session is bottled up inside her.
We filled her to the limit with this cum enema,
and used an anal plug to stop it from spilling out.
Currently, Ingrid's whole body is in a drug-induced state of rut.
On top of that, she really needs to evacuate her insides.
Scum! All of you!
Watch your mouth in front of my guests.
I'll kill you. I promise I will!
Begin.
Let the entertainment begin!
Wait.. If I'm penetrated now...
Stop! This is humiliating.
Slow down. You're moving too fast.
It hurts... It hurts my stomach. Slow down.
Look at that huge belly. She's a real glutton for cum.
She calls herself the Dark Knight, however
she's nothing but a common whore.
And a fat one, no less. What a huge gut.
Turn your wretched eyes away from me!
Yeah, yeah! How do you like the feeling of my giant monster dick?
Your dick is rubbish, you filthy orc.
Then I'll have to fuck you harder!
No...
You pukes!
Get your hands off me, or you'll be sorry.
You don't scare me, woman.
You're just slut who needs her eggs fertilized.
Stop it.
I don't need to have your ugly, purple baby.
No more. I'm going to cum.
I can't hold back! I'm cumming!
Go for it! Let it all loose!
I'm cumming! I'm going to be pregnant with an ore baby!
I can feel it... gushing deep into my uterus...
I'm soaking with orc semen.
Her half-orc baby is sure to be adorable.
Looking good, Ingrid.
I'm... going... to... kill... you...
Even with a body full of orc sperm, you continue to defy me.
I think it's time for the big finale, Dark Knight.
Wait, if you take it out...
Show my guests what you can do!
I can't stop it... It's all going to gush out...
Look at her face. She's trying to hold it in.
Can her ass pucker up tight enough?
How miserable!
Don't look at me like that. Look away at once!
Oh no, here it comes.
Please, put the plug back in!
I'll cum again if I shit it all out at once!
Exquisite. Open the floodgates!
Don't say "floodgates!"
Oh God, it's coming!
My ass is going to burst!
And I'm going to cum!
It's all coming out! All that semen!
A geyser of cum is gushing out of my shithole and making me cum!
I'm still cumming!
Being watched is making me cum even harder!
I'm cumming so hard! I can't stop!
I'm cumming again!
My ass will never be the same...
A fine performance...
Dark Knight.
Damn you.
Feel like cooperating?
If you do, I'll see to it that your death is as pleasurable as possible.
I'll kill you. I swear I'll destroy you, Kiryuu.