Clumsy Tsundere Princess Knight: Sheila Magnus
Sheila is the first princess of the Macden Kingdom.
She takes a lot after her beautiful and well-renowned mother,
from her well-defined features to her well-developed body.
Sheila's mentor Nina has trained her well to the point
that no typical knight can rival her sword skills.
Sheila has this fondness of acquiring more powerful weapons
which led to her downfall. Her personality of being highly curious to a fault and knowing no fear brought misfortune upon her.
The dubious cursed sword sealed within the treasure room made Sheila
impulsively pull it off the scabbard to satisfy her curiosity.
This, in turn, dragged her into the erotic curse of orgasm hell.
The Kingdom's Beautiful and Erudite Elf: Nina Magle
Nina came from the long-living elven tribe. She is adept
in both martial arts and sorcery, and sports such beauty
that captivates even the same gender as well.
Nina has been serving the Magnus clan for a long time now,
from Sheila's parents and even way back in the early days
of the Kingdom. She is essentially the "brain" of the nation,
even though she couldn't care less about it herself.
Instead, Nina amuses herself with her favorite pastime of doting
on her beloved Sheila with Eric, teasing the two to each other.
Childhood Friend from a Low-ranking Nobility: Eric Smedt
Eric is a boy with an androgynous face, who's shorter and a year younger
than Sheila. He has been attending to Sheila as her page since their childhood,
and thus grew up being trained in swordplay and academics by their master Nina.
And while Sheila just laughs him off as someone like a younger brother
to her, his mere presence makes her chest tighten nowadays.
When Sheila unsheathed the cursed sword, Eric took notice of the
catastrophe that befell upon her. He heedlessly threw himself afront
of Sheila to her rescue, willing to sacrifice himself if need be.
Possessing skills enough to subjugate demons whilst inheriting
her mother's beauty, such is Princess Sheila Magnus. On the other hand,
she is much of a tomboy with an excessive amount of curiosity to a fault.
She is accompanied by her attendant, Eric Smedt, who has been working
hard in hopes that she will take notice of him even a little.
Dying of curiosity, the tomboyish princess knight coerced Eric together
towards the treasure room, where Dáinsleif, the dubious cursed sword
filled of malevolence is sealed within.
Dáinsleif is a sword forged by the world's best swordsmiths who poured all
of their skills on making it. Engraved within this sword is a myriad of legends.
Sheila, the tomboyish princess knight, took the cursed sword out of curiosity.
She ended up having a nightmare and wallowed herself in self-pleasure afterwards.
Eric and Nina walked into her room, only to witness her
as she teases her breasts and hidden lips.
Sheila wanted to resist what's about to happen but couldn't
as her fingers kept moving intensely. Eric pushes his rod into Sheila
with the help of Nina's guidance. Sheila experiences the pain
of her first sexual experience.
Sheila couldn't believe the fact that her first time was with Eric.
This made it embarrassingly difficult for her to face him upfront,
though nothing has really seemed to changed
among the three on the following day.
She went to a thicket nearby,
squats down and lays bare her hidden lips.
Her body shivers from an urge to pee, just as she does at any normal day.
Or so it should, until Nina appears right in front of her.
Nina gives Sheila an intense gaze
as she ties her up with tentacles using some dubious magic.
The tomboyish princess knight is on the verge of wetting herself.
Her whole body throbbed as Nina presses her lower abdomen
while carefully massaging it.
Despite the princess knight's desperate attempt hold her bladder in protest,
she ended up spraying herself wet from her cute peehole.
Nina is the kingdom's most intelligent individual.
She is adept in using any skill and even is blessed with such beauty.
Taken aback by what the obscene cursed sword revealed about her, Nina is now in front of Eric, exposing her bare body...
Original Animation
The Princess with a Cursed Sword is Very Lewd
That Time When I Got Bound by a Slime
Last Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero Ero Desu...
Wh-
Wh-Wh-
Wh-Wh-Wh-
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What should we do now?!
E-Even if you ask me that...
Aren't you my servant? Aren't you my slave?!
I'm your attendant!
But aren't you my friend?
Aren't we childhood friends?
It's not like I'm asking for so much!
That's not fair...
I thought I'll finally go on an
adventure, then this happened...
They talk about that curse...
No... What? My pee... Huh?!
It's getting sucked out!
Why on earth are they here?!
No! Stop!
What's with this? What's happening here?!
No!
Stop!
I don't want this, yet my body is...
No... No—!
Eric... Nina... These guys won't stop!
No way, not down there!
No! No, no! No—!
You know what's going on,
don't you? Do something!
No way, what is even happening?
Alright, Eric. It's your turn.
No, what's this? It's rubbing against my insides!
That's wonderful, you already
are taking it all inside!
I'm coming—!
Not now!
If you keep on moving right now...
Wait, I already said no!
If he keeps this up, I'll end up falling in lust!
That sly elf...
She's been living her life just to tease me!
You shouldn't go after and peep on her.
Please stop teasing me!
Nina! What are these... Stop...
Wait, I'm...
Stop fooling around!
Do you understand the consequence of your—
I am asking you a question. Answer me.
That's right, isn't that obvious?
That's because I was about to do it!
That felt good, right?
I-I don't know what you're talking about!
Sh-She'll keep doing this until I answer her...
No, thank you! I'll pass!
Wait, stop! If you push me right there...
It's not good to hold it in.
S-Stop... I'm begging you, Nina! Don't do that!
Not Nina, call me onee-sama instead.
I-I'm begging you, onee-sama! Stop!
If you keep on doing that, I'm gonna...
You passed the test, princess!
Nina, is there anything I can do to help?
Thank you, Eric.
I was about to ask you something
which no one else can do.
Yes, ask me anything.
Please sleep with me, Eric.
N-Nina! Huh, why?
The princess might have a high affinity
with the sword to cause it to activate abruptly.
And so, we need to use a potion on it
that's made by using a woman's
love juice as a catalyst.
We now have a sure way
to suppress its activation.
O-Okay, I understand.
H-Huh?
Nina, are you alright?
Are you stupid or something?
Didn't you see how the princess was last night?
Cursed or not, a woman's first time
is a nerve-racking experience for her!
Yeah, Sheila was definitely...
Wait, huh? First time?
I know it in theory, but I have no experience.
The same goes for kissing, of course.
Do you find it hard to believe?
That's because you're the best
woman that I know of, Nina.
You can get any man you wish...
I'm happy to hear that from you, Eric.
It was worth waiting for this moment.
Do you want to check it?
This is my genuine hymen.
I already knew it from last time,
but this sure grew up into something impressive.
N-Nina...
Learn to have self-control.
The same goes for me, though.
This is so embarrassing that
it's making me nervous.
Nina, you look so beautiful that
I can't take my eyes off you!
Thanks for the compliment.
Your full attention was on the princess last night,
but think only of me for tonight.
Okay.
He's using both hands all of a sudden?
I'll end up letting my voice out!
Amazing... This boy's hands are good!
He has such a talent...
He's suddenly poking inside me with his tongue!
He's stimulating me in such a way!
This kid is unbelievable!
H-How am I doing?
Y-Yeah, you're doing very well. Good job.
To think that he has such a talent in this...
I never felt any sensation as strong
as this before! If this goes on...
You're amazing down here, Nina!
It's dripping so much, and it smells so strong!
Y-You don't have to tell me about that stuff!
You're insensitive to women's feelings...
Are you listening? Hey, Eric!
I'm being licked by an incredibly cute boy below!
You're just my disciple...
You're being cocky despite being
a virgin up until last night, Eric!
You can't do this, Eric!
I won't forgive you if you make me
come with just your tongue!
I won't forgive you if I ended up coming this way!
Are you alright, Nina?
You made me come using your mouth in no time...
You're quite skillful.
I-I'm sorry...
You don't need to apologize.
It felt so amazing that my pussy is still throbbing.
If there is one thing you have to apologize for,
it would be for not making love with me any sooner.
O-Okay!
I am an honest-to-goodness virgin.
And I never had any lover before.
Yeah, though I still can't believe that
a pretty lady like you are, Nina.
I have already been told that,
but I just happened to not meet anyone I like.
Be more confident in yourself, Eric.
Not only your face but also your voice is cute.
But that's not what really matters.
Please use this monstrous dick of yours,
and devour the hymen of this capricious elf!
I expected him to be a little more nervous,
but it's me who's less experienced than him.
I'm putting it in, Nina...
I see, so this is how a deflowering is...
The pain that I've been longing to feel for so long...
Now I'm a "used good" just like the princess.
D-Doesn't it hurt?
I'm alright.
It's all thanks to you caressing
my female part a lot earlier.
How is my first-timer pussy?
It feels so incredible, it's like
I'm gonna melt inside you!
I'm starting to feel better now.
You can start moving your hips.
Just tell me when it hurts, okay?
So this is how a dick feels...
It's reaching so deep inside me!
This thing is poking on parts
that my fingers couldn't reach!
Eric, you are so cute!
It's like I'm being raped by a girl, this is exciting!
I'm a boy!
What is this? The sensation suddenly
got stronger! It's scraping me inside!
Eric, wait!
This is my first time, you know!
You're poking deep inside me!
Just wait for a moment, Eric!
To think that he's this talented!
I'll come earlier than usual from this!
Wait, Eric! Anything beyond this...
It's my first time feeling this!
I'm sorry, but this feels so good!
No, me too... Feeling this good...
Eric, don't! I'm gonna... This is...
For him to kiss me right now...
You are fantastic, Eric!
I never felt anything like this by myself before!
It seems that the princess is in a bad mood today.
Y-Yeah... I wonder why.
Maybe she noticed that
something's up with me.
It feels like you're still inside me.
What's up with Eric?
My type of guy is someone well-built, strong
and dependable!
Huh...
I really ended up doing it with Eric...
I shouldn't get worked up from it, but...
What a nice bodyguard you are.
Eric, shouldn't we inform the princess
about what exactly happened?
I mean about last night.
W-Wait! But, that's because...
Calm down, I'm just kidding!
Jeez...
What's up with Nina, showing off like that?
If you want to be with Eric that much...
Let's get moving!
Hmp! Wait...
What am I getting pissed off about?
Nina and Eric are just talking to each other...
I should wait for them here.
This should suppress the sword even a little.
What? You should've done this from the start!
I couldn't since I only obtained
the ingredients yesterday.
What's up with me?
Why am I feeling uneasy? Gosh!
Wh-What's that?
There shouldn't be any strong monsters here...
I don't want to encounter orcs though!
Gah—!
Wh-Why does it have to be this thing?
This can't be happening!
Nina, Eric! Get yourselves here already!
Sheila-sama is gone!
Where are you, princess!
It's dangerous around here!
Oh, here she is.
And she's surrounded
by something she hates.
So, she ended up using
the cursed sword again.
Don't tell me that she's...
Yes, she should be having
a very lewd dream right now.
What's happening here?
I remember that right here...
Th-That's right, there was one of these earlier!
And I used this sword to...
Wait, what?!
Wait! Huh, where's the sword?
Th-There it is!
Wh-Why?! Huh?
What... You're kidding, no way! Why?
You... Let go of me!
What's wrong with you, doing this to me?
Just who do you think am I?
No, no, no... Why...
Wait, stop this! You...
Are you kidding me?
What do you think you're doing, naughty slime?!
Humiliating me like this!
After putting me in such a position,
where does this thing think it's touching?
This is the worst, the worst, the worst!
You... Enough of this!
N-No, I ended up swallowing it!
Or rather, why does it taste delicious?
What... is that an aphrodisiac?!
Don't do that! This can't be...
I-It feels good?!
No... Why?
I don't want to feel good, and yet...
That's not true!
It's your fault that I'm feeling good!
No... I-I'm gonna come from this?
I can't ever do that!
Even though I hate this and this is frustrating...
Eric, I'm... I'm...
Save me, Eric! I don't want to come!
Not from a slime, not from something like this!
I'm gonna come from a slime!
I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
This can't be real...
In such a state, I...
No... I'm begging you!
No more... I can't take any more of this!
I'll never ever forgive you!
Not from something like this! I'll never ever...
No way! I came!
I came just from being lapped by that thing!
If that thing enters me...
Right there? You're kidding!
That's wrong!
That's the wrong spot!
No—!
Don't go in such a dirty place—!
Uhh... Huh?
Eric! Eric! Eric!
You made it in time, Eric—!
This is Eric's scent for sure,
but why am I also smelling Nina from him?
Nina also looked for me to save me!
Are we really doing it here?
The seal has weakened so we have to hurry.
I've already put up a barrier so we're safe.
It can't be helped that she used the sword.
But even so, the seal is weakening too fast.
Right now, we have to collect
a huge amount of my love juice
and use the potion on it as soon as possible.
You too, Eric. Hurry up.
Caress my pussy and wring it out of its juices.
So, this is how Eric tastes like.
This is wonderful.
He's amazing as always! I can't get enough of this!
Eric, you're doing great!
While I'm in this position, Eric is...
My disciple is violating me! This is fantastic!
You're rubbing my tits as well?
This feels good as well!
Eric!
Come together with me—!
Nina, I'm coming too!
I'm coming!
It's deep inside me!
You're pumping me with your spurting semen!
I'm sorry to interrupt your steamy moment, but...
How does your body feel right now, princess?
N-Nothing in particular!
Of course, not something like a slime can...
Is that so?
And another thing...
What is it?
You said something earlier that intrigued me.
I'd love to know what you meant
by "that place is dirty".
Huh—?!
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization