Clumsy Tsundere Princess Knight: Sheila Magnus
Sheila is the first princess of the Macden Kingdom.
She takes a lot after her beautiful and well-renowned mother,
from her well-defined features to her well-developed body.
Sheila's mentor Nina has trained her well to the point
that no typical knight can rival her sword skills.
Sheila has this fondness of acquiring more powerful weapons
which led to her downfall. Her personality of being highly curious to a fault and knowing no fear brought misfortune upon her.
The dubious cursed sword sealed within the treasure room made Sheila
impulsively pull it off the scabbard to satisfy her curiosity.
This, in turn, dragged her into the erotic curse of orgasm hell.
The Kingdom's Beautiful and Erudite Elf: Nina Magle
Nina came from the long-living elven tribe. She is adept
in both martial arts and sorcery, and sports such beauty
that captivates even the same gender as well.
Nina has been serving the Magnus clan for a long time now,
from Sheila's parents and even way back in the early days
of the Kingdom. She is essentially the "brain" of the nation,
even though she couldn't care less about it herself.
Instead, Nina amuses herself with her favorite pastime of doting
on her beloved Sheila with Eric, teasing the two to each other.
Childhood Friend from a Low-ranking Nobility: Eric Smedt
Eric is a boy with an androgynous face, who's shorter and a year younger
than Sheila. He has been attending to Sheila as her page since their childhood,
and thus grew up being trained in swordplay and academics by their master Nina.
And while Sheila just laughs him off as someone like a younger brother
to her, his mere presence makes her chest tighten nowadays.
When Sheila unsheathed the cursed sword, Eric took notice of the
catastrophe that befell upon her. He heedlessly threw himself afront
of Sheila to her rescue, willing to sacrifice himself if needed be.
Possessing skills enough to subjugate demons whilst inheriting
her mother's beauty, such is Princess Sheila Magnus. On the other hand,
she is much of a tomboy with an excessive amount of curiosity to a fault.
She is accompanied by her attendant, Eric Smedt, who has been working
hard in hopes that she will take notice of him even a little.
Dying of curiosity, the tomboyish princess knight coerced Eric together
towards the treasure room, where Dáinsleif, the dubious cursed sword
filled of malevolence is sealed within.
Dáinsleif is a sword forged by the worlds best swordsmiths who poured all
of their skills on making it. Engraved within this sword is a myriad of legends.
The two easily managed to sneak inside the treasure room which
should be difficult to gain access into, just to end up on their own undoing.
To add up to that, the chain that seals the sword also accidentally broke down from being weathered in time. And thinking that it couldn't get any worse,
Sheila happened to be holding the cursed sword on the hilt pointing downwards,
unintentionally drawing it out as its scabbard fell on the ground.
What awaits her are the most atrocious events of her life,
more dreadful than anything she can ever imagine.
And thus, Eric looks at his first love, the tomboyish princess knight,
as she tightly holds onto the cursed sword Dáinsleif. Her cheeks are flushed as her overwrought body seemingly suffers in agony.
The cherry boy beholds the alluring figure with his eyes,
a sight he never even thought of even in his wildest dreams.
The girl that is his first love concupiscently crooks her slim pretty fingers
as she spreads open to rub and wriggle them on her hidden lips.
The cursed sword unexpectedly takes people's wildest fantasies
and exhibits them to its keeper.
O
Ori
Origi
Origina
Original
Original A
Original Ani
Original Anim
Original Anima
Original Animati
Original Animatio
Original Animation
The Princess with a Cursed Sword is Very Lewd
The Tsundere Princess Knight's
Urination Bondage And Discipline
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What should we do now?!
E-Even if you ask me that...
Aren't you my servant? Aren't you my slave?!
I'm your attendant!
But aren't you my friend? Aren't we childhood friends?
It's not like I'm asking for so much!
That's not fair...
Bring Nina down here!
Are we gonna bring Nina into this?
Oh, she's been with us since we're both little.
Do you want Nina to feel left out?
...and thus, the princess is currently keeping it.
Oh my, what a problem child.
And then? Are there any changes on Sheila?
It only happened last night, so there isn't anything yet.
However, it is my first time to work on this case...
So we have no choice but to
replace the sealing gemstone...
I will leave with Eric for a search.
Oh, that girl... Did she become naughty now?
No, she is very lewd!
I thought I'll finally go on an
adventure, then this happened...
Wasn't it always your dream to embark
on an adventure, Sheila-sama?
We originally had the sword sealed to some extent
for it to weaken so that we can
subdue it using a special ritual.
But a princess from who knows where suddenly unsheathed it and broke the gemstone.
And so, we're here right now.
Do you feel anything wrong on your body?
No, I'm okay! I'm feeling really lively today.
I'm just...
They talk about that curse...
No... What? My pee...
It's getting sucked out!
Wait—!
Why on earth are they here?!
Wh-Why can't I cut you down?
I did it so easily this afternoon!
Huh?!
No! Stop!
No, no—!
What's with this? What's happening here?!
Stop...
Stop!
Th-This feels gross! No!
No!
Stop!
I don't want this, yet my body is...
No, don't! Stop this!
No...
I'm feeling hot deep inside my body!
No... No—!
Eric... Nina... These guys won't stop!
No way, not down there!
No! No, no! No—!
It was... a dream?
Could it be... that this is the curse?
Why does my body feel so hot?
Even when I don't want to...
It's about time...
The effect of using the cursed sword
against the orcs will start to show.
Something odd should start happening on the princess...
...or rather, on the cursed sword.
Eric!
Sheila-sama, are you alright?
Please excuse...
Wait! Just wait...
You idiot! Why are you barging in?
My, my... Isn't that such an indecent
appearance you have there?
You know what's going on,
don't you? Do something!
No way, what is even happening?
Alright, Eric. It's your turn.
The sword was sealed within the scabbard.
The power of the Goddess Hegni
is evidently dwelling in it.
I feel so hot!
No... My body won't stop!
Nina, what are you doing?
Getting ready, what else?
Hurry up and strip as well, Eric.
We're going to alleviate her arousal.
It is a toiling task even when you're used to it.
It's unnecessary for a virgin yet
to be kissed like you to know.
The only thing unnecessary here
is that mouth of yours, Nina!
Just as expected from the princess. You still
make good responses at a time like this.
Though instead of responding on my remarks,
you have to respond to that
thing for you to settle down.
What is that thing? It's huge!
It looks nothing like it used to way back then!
Eric is looking at my most important place!
Please forgive me, princess.
I have no other choice but to do this,
even though I feel bad for doing so.
This naughty elf... She's definitely enjoying this!
I made you wait long enough, Eric.
Alright, please use that bulging and
seemingly about to burst virgin cock
and shove it into her slippery pussy.
Will that long, thick and hard thing take my first time?
Sheila-sama, please forgive me!
Just wait right there! We have
to properly peel it off first.
This is... A penis...
A meat rod... A dick...
A cock... A boner...
N-Nina?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Alright, I'll be here to assist you
so please proceed just like that.
His dick went inside me!
No, what's this? It's rubbing against my insides!
That's wonderful, you already are taking it all inside!
No, this is supposed to be my first time...
No... I can't take it anymore!
I-I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
Not now!
If you keep on moving right now...
Wait, I already said no!
If he keeps this up, I'll end up falling in lust!
No!
Eric, you idiot! It's your fault
that I'm coming over and over!
You shouldn't lie.
No!
Don't pinch both my nipples and clit!
Sheila, show me more of your cuteness!
What's with him calling me by my name
like how he used to back then?
It's coming! His dick grew bigger!
No, I wasn't thinking about wanting
to come together with him!
C-Coming... I'm coming...
I'm coming—!
You're spraying it deep inside me!
This feels incredible—!
Am I... being kissed... right now?
He's licking me all over.
To think that both my virginity and
first kiss will be taken this way...
Seems like we're a bit behind the schedule...
Is that so?
If it's just a bit then we should be fine.
The princess is in a state
like you saw last time, right.
That sly elf...
She's been living her life just to tease me!
I had my first time like that...
Gosh!
Sheila-sama!
You shouldn't go after and peep on her.
Please stop teasing me!
It feels like it's still inside me!
Eric, who's been like a younger
brother to me, took my first time...
No way!
Uhh...
W-Wait, Nina! Why did you
follow me here? Go away.
Are you acting as an exhibitionist pervert out here?
What pervert are you talking about?
It's a call of nature so there's nothing else
I can do about it! I'm perfectly hidden here.
Didn't I teach you that you're most vulnerable
when being too complacent, princess?
Nina! What are these... Stop...
Wait, I'm...
I'm about to pee!
Are you about to pee?
Stop fooling around!
Do you understand the consequence of your—
I am asking you a question. Answer me.
That's right, isn't that obvious?
That's because I was about to do it!
Aren't you an indecent and perverted princess?
Ouch!
Nina, do you understand what you're doing?
I'm a princess!
This is a punishment.
Moreover, you are a princess but...
You're a pervert first and foremost.
What was that just now?!
My, my... You're feeling good from being spanked.
Your punishment turned into a reward instead, huh?
That's not—!
That felt good, right?
I-I don't know what you're talking about!
Sh-She'll keep doing this until I answer her...
I-It might have felt good...
Nina, I'll never ever forgive you!
I already said it, why do you keep hitting me?
Didn't I teach you about the manner of speech?
I-It felt great for me.
Good, here's your reward.
Huh?
No, thank you! I'll pass!
Wait, stop! If you push me right there...
It's not good to hold it in.
S-Stop... I'm begging you, Nina! Don't do that!
Not Nina, call me onee-sama instead.
I-I'm begging you, onee-sama! Stop!
If you keep on doing that, I'm gonna...
You passed the test, princess!
Let it out!
No—!
No, no way! Stop!
I can let go of your carelessness, but isn't
your pussy sopping wet right now?
How indecent!
The exhibitionist and perverted princess
is in the mood for a workout!
Huh?
What on earth is with that thing?
No... Ni—
Onee-sama, I'm begging you! I don't want to!
No—!
The curse has reactivated!
At this rate, it's just a matter of time
until the curse consumes her.
Is her situation that serious?
No, she should be fine at least
until we cross the mountain.
But other than that...
I did that? And I even made
you call me onee-sama?
My secret fantasy was revealed
by a mere cursed sword!
I've never seen Nina looking like that before...
Nina, is there anything I can do to help?
Thank you, Eric.
I was about to ask you something
that no one else can do.
Yes, ask me anything.
Please sleep with me, Eric.
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
N
Ne
Next
Next Ti
Next Time
Next Time on
Next Time on Ma
Next Time on Make
Next Time on Maken
Next Time on Maken no
Next Time on Maken no Hi
Next Time on Maken no Hime
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa E
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero E
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero Ero
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero Ero De
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero Ero Desu
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero Ero Desu...
I already knew it from last time,
but this sure grew up into something impressive.
N-Nina...
Learn to have self-control.
He's using both hands all of a sudden?
I'll end up letting my voice out!
Amazing... This boy's hands are good!
He has such a talent...
So this is a dick...
It's reaching so deep inside me!
This thing is poking on parts
that my fingers couldn't reach!
Just wait for a moment, Eric!
To think that he's this much talented!
I'll come earlier than usual from this!
There shouldn't be any strong monsters here...
I don't want to encounter orcs though!
Huh!
Wh-Why does it have to be this thing?
What's wrong with you, doing this
to me? Who do you think am I?
No, no, no... Why...
Wait, stop this!
Are you kidding me?
What do you think you're doing, naughty slime?!
Humiliating me like this!
No... I'm begging you!
No more... I can't take any more of this!