Kingdom of Macden
In the underground treasure room of this kingdom lies a sword
which the world's best swordsmiths poured all their skills into forging.
Despite making various legends of itself on the battlefield,
this cursed sword (Dáinsleif) was tightly locked away in chains.
The tomboyish princess knight took it
just to satisfy her own curiosity (Sheila Magnus).
Together with the boy she coerced to go with her (Eric Smedt),
and the elf who's fond of teasing her (Nina Magle),
the three's extremely erotic epic tale begins.
Clumsy Tsundere Princess Knight: Sheila Magnus
Sheila is the first princess of the Macden Kingdom.
She takes a lot after her beautiful and well-renowned mother,
from her well-defined features to her well-developed body.
Sheila's mentor Nina has trained her well to the point
that no typical knight can rival her sword skills.
Sheila has this fondness of acquiring more powerful weapons
which led to her downfall. Her personality of being highly curious to a fault and knowing no fear brought misfortune upon her.
The dubious cursed sword sealed within the treasure room made Sheila
impulsively pull it off the scabbard to satisfy her curiosity.
This, in turn, dragged her into the erotic curse of orgasm hell.
The Kingdom's Beautiful and Erudite Elf: Nina Magle
Nina came from the long-living elven tribe. She is adept
in both martial arts and sorcery, and sports such beauty
that captivates even the same gender as well.
Nina has been serving the Magnus clan for a long time now,
from Sheila's parents and even way back in the early days
of the Kingdom. She is essentially the "brain" of the nation,
even though she couldn't care less about it herself.
Instead, Nina amuses herself with her favorite pastime of doting
on her beloved Sheila with Eric, teasing the two to each other.
Childhood Friend from a Low-ranking Nobility: Eric Smedt
Eric is a boy with an androgynous face, who's shorter and a year younger
than Sheila. He has been attending to Sheila as her page since their childhood,
and thus grew up being trained in swordplay and academics by their master Nina.
And while Sheila just laughs him off as someone like a younger brother
to her, his mere presence makes her chest tighten nowadays.
When Sheila unsheathed the cursed sword, Eric took notice of the
catastrophe that befell upon her. He heedlessly threw himself afront
of Sheila to her rescue, willing to sacrifice himself if need be.
The obscene dreams that the cursed sword shows het up Sheila's body.
She ends up showing herself being lost in self-pleasure to Eric and Nina.
She then follows Nina's guidance to accept Eric's penis,
and experiences the pain of having her first man.
Sheila takes the sturdy meat rod of Eric,
a childhood friend that she treats like a little brother, inside her.
However, the curse that has been consuming her only intensified.
It started giving her even more vivid dreams
of having her obscene genital being violated.
This started to take a toll on Sheila's mind,
but then the smart and beautiful Nina gave her a suggestion.
"Why are you this good at binding women, stupid Eric?!",
angrily screamed by Sheila as the princess knight in bondage
was hung on air with finesse by her childhood friend in no time.
"Hey, it's this attire that is improper!",
the princess knight clad with skimpy armor said
after wearing the said outfit that resembles
a tight and undersized swimsuit.
Sheila's body feels hot, flushed, and she gets on the verge of tears
every time she runs into a traveler on the way
while almost naked in her armor.
Original Animation
The Princess with a Cursed Sword is Very Lewd
The Tsundere Princess Knight's Upfront Skimpy
Armor Clad Abuse and Sex Behind Her Back
Yeah, Sheila was definitely...
Last Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero Ero Desu...
Wait, huh? First time?
I know it in theory, but I have no experience.
The same goes for kissing, of course.
Do you find it hard to believe?
I already knew it from last time,
but this sure grew up into something impressive.
Wow... This boy's hands are good!
He has such a talent...
H-He's suddenly poking inside me with his tongue!
So this is how a dick feels...
It's reaching so deep inside me!
This thing is poking on spots
that my fingers couldn't reach!
Eric, you are so cute!
It's like I'm being raped by a girl, this is exciting!
I'm a boy!
What is this? The sensation suddenly
got stronger! It's scraping me inside!
Eric, wait!
This is my first time, you know!
You're poking deep inside me!
What's wrong with you, doing this to me?
Just who do you think am I?
No, no, no... Why...
Wait, stop this! You...
Are you kidding me?
What do you think you're doing, naughty slime?!
Humiliating me like this!
After putting me in such a position,
where does this thing think it's touching?
This is the worst, the worst, the worst!
No... I-I'm gonna come from this?
I can't ever do that!
Even though I hate this and this is frustrating...
Eric, I'm... I'm...
What is it?
You said something earlier that intrigued me.
I'd love to know what you meant
by "that place is dirty".
Huh—?!
Say it to me, princess.
What sorts of lewd stuff did those slimes do to you?
I-I don't know!
This is a matter of great importance, Sheila.
The cursed sword is probably affecting
not just your mind, but your body as well.
To be more precise, anything
you had from your dream
will end up affecting your body.
And as a remedy,
we'll have to replace it in your memory
by reenacting the same event.
I'm fine with that,
but what else are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about your own welfare!
So, about my question before...
U-Uhh... What was it, again?
You can't talk yourself out of this.
Please tell it to me with
as much detail as possible.
This should be about right.
It's a restrained gorgeous princess knight!
Good job, Eric.
I-I'm sorry, Sheila... Umm...
Apology not accepted!
Or rather, why are you
this good at binding women?
Eric has always been ambidextrous
and nimble-fingered.
He's also good at a variety
of things aside from combat.
Well then, for our reenactment...
The scene is about a princess knight suffering
in a slime hell and having her every hole violated.
Action!
Huh? A-Are we really doing it here?
What are we gonna do
when someone shows up?
If they'll hear your beastlike moans,
they'll think of it as nothing but mating animals.
Huh?! Is that how I sound like? No way!
Please think of us as slimes and
remember what you went through.
This slime is no match for me...
Put your heart into this if you still have
a pride to spare, or the effect will wane.
Right... The slime hung me up. It melted
my armor and what's underneath...
Alright, after they melted your armor,
in what outrageous manners
did the slimes attack you?
They wrapped themselves around me...
No, don't lick me...
Come on, Eric.
Hurry up and start going lovey-dovey
and making her sticky.
Just where are you licking? You're even
more persistent than the slime?
Y-You don't have to do that place!
Enough of your futile resistance, please.
It's not like you're a virgin.
You're already so wet down here...
Not there!
You've been teased by the slime down here
and it made you wet, am I right?
No, stop saying that!
Stop licking me as well!
Sorry, Sheila.
Don't grope me in the first place
if you feel sorry, stupid Eric!
No, stop licking!
If you do that much to me...
Why does this feel so good?
I'm more excited than in my dream!
Please don't hold back and be honest with yourself.
We'll burn the true joys of womanhood
into your mind and body.
No... I'm gonna come from this...
It feels good!
Coming... I'm coming from this...
I'm gonna come! Let me go!
I'm coming—!
Your orgasm is splendid as always, princess.
Looking forward to what will
become of you made me wet.
No, stop...
Do you hate me?
No way, I love both you and Eric
from the bottom of my heart.
Then, why...
That's the very reason.
I won't ever allow such a lowly
cursed sword take you away!
That's why you have to use
his ferocious and long cock
that doesn't match his cute face
to overwrite your lewd dream.
You're kidding... Are we going to continue this?
We already are halfway on dealing
with your lewd dream, however...
An even more intense pleasure is necessary.
Princess, you were coming non-stop
from having your pussy
gouged and stirred up by your hated slime cock.
They haven't done that to me!
Didn't I tell you that I barely avoided it?
I called for Eric and...
Your pussy smells sweet and sour. That's unexpected.
Shut up, Nina...
Then, won't we considerably
suppress the dream's effects
if we'll give you a stronger
stimulation down here?
I-I get it already!
I'm glad that you're quick on the uptake, princess.
Alright, Eric. Slide it in just like how you did to me.
Huh? Nina, Eric... So, you two really are...
Sheila...
Sorry, I'm putting it in!
Why is your thing so...
Isn't that great? That's an actual cock.
It's way better than a slime.
Eric, it's so long!
Don't do that!
Don't suck it like that!
I can't take any more than this!
Get more pleasure and feel good!
Idiot!
I've been telling you over and over
that any more of this...
No, doing this non-stop is too much for me!
This is too much—!
Stop this!
I've been telling you to stop!
No more... No, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Sheila... I love you, Sheila!
Love me... H-Huh?
No way... No, I came...
No way, stop...
No...
Uhh, I feel sleepy...
My body feels heavy, it's so hot!
You're being grouchy.
We all feel the same so
please bear with it, princess.
A-Am I not the only one who feels hot?
It's because you're wearing that manteau.
It's going to get even hotter today.
Then do something about my armor!
You have to wear this instead.
Your previous armor is well-made,
but it's unfortunate.
Isn't that the unfortunate one?
You even lie about it being broken.
Give it back to me already!
That's sad to hear from a knight
defeated by mere slimes.
B-But aren't you doing this for your
own amusement as well, Nina?
You always accuse me of that.
This is the best choice we have.
I'm only concerned about your welfare.
If that's so, then what's up with that grin?
Oh, I'm just happy that this armor came out good
despite our lack of time and materials.
H-Hey, Nina!
What's the matter?
What, you say...
My, my... It has to be like that down there.
Do I really have to wear these?
I won't mind you going out there
bare naked if you want to.
How's the armor I worked hard to make?
Yes, I have no complaints about
its ventilation and weight.
I'm just worried that it'll be
distracting for being too skimpy.
It'll protect your body in dire situations
with defensive invisibility magic, so you'll be fine.
Won't a normal armor do?
I'm still fine now while we're here.
I can bear with this with only you two around.
Right? You were in an even
more silly state last night.
You were fully exposed in front of us.
That was incredible. Just remembering
about it makes my pussy wet.
Why are you being annoying
with a straight face so early?
Nina, you idiot!
Nina, you idiot! Lewd!
Nina, you idiot! Lewd! Lecher!
Nina, you idiot! Lewd! Lecher! Pervert!
It's nice that you're already abusing me
verbally so early in the morning.
It's gonna be alright. If it's you,
you'll get used to it in no time.
Gosh, I don't want to drag
this out while wearing this.
Let's just get this done.
I can't get enough of the gap
between her words and actions!
You're so cute, Sheila!
Wow!
There's plenty of Eric's sperm flowing into me!
Eric's dick is still stiff.
He's still lively despite coming so much, and I'm...
Looks like you're still far from satisfied.
It's alright, push it between my tits just like that.
This feels amazing, Nina...
Seeing you that delighted will make me wet, Eric.
You can do it just like that.
This is something called titjob.
How does this feel?
It looks cute when I see it like this,
but it's ferocious when inside me
that it drives me crazy.
You don't have to hold it in.
Please shoot it out just like this.
O-Okay, Nina...
You're being forceful!
Oh... You're even going this wild...
You really do surprise me, Eric!
That's good, Eric. Shoot it out!
Spray me with plenty of your sperm!
Your thick sperm is fantastic!
How is the princess?
Umm, she was kind of alright, but...
We should take a break.
I'm fine, though. I can still keep on walking.
I'm still far from tired!
We still have a long way to go,
so we should take a rest first.
We have to do things in the right manner.
She has been quite mentally exhausted.
It's quite troublesome either way.
Our situation is complicated, but...
I'll have to take you inside me so I can wring you out.
W-Will this be alright?
Yes, although I never did it
in this position before.
You can shove it in just like this.
Please put your stiff cock inside me.
You're going to rape me, Eric!
Nina!
Eric, your dick is so good!
This is great! It's as if my own disciple
is roughing me up and raping me!
Nina, your insides feel good!
You're more excited than usual.
Eric?!
What's happening?
He started hitting a different spot! It feels wonderful!
Your dick is so amazing!
It's hollowing me up deep inside!
You're breaking me!
I'm already coming! I'm coming...
I'm coming!
Eric...
Nina!
Y-You two...
Princess!
Sheila!
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Next Time on Maken no Hime wa Ero Ero Desu...
Gosh, I can't go out there looking like this!
Damn you, Nina... Gosh!
No way, it's because I've
been dragging my feet!
Is that Princess Sheila?
For real?
Does this mean that our nation's princess
is an exhibitionist and perverted sow?
No!
This slut!
Being treated like an exhibitionist...
Eric... Nina... Why?
You're doing great, Eric!
Nina, I love you!
I'm not gonna sell that. But in exchange...
They're looking! Everyone's staring
at my tits and down there!
Wait, I won't let you treat Nina alone like a dog
being taken for a walk crawling on all fours.
You're cute even as a dog, princess.
This is making me wetter than I expected.
Woof!
Woof! Woof!
Woof! Woof! Woof!
Woof! Woof! Woof! Woof!
Woof! Woof!
Uhh... Woof!
What are you doing, Nina? Hey...
Woof... Woof! Woof!
I'm begging you, master!
Eric, your dick has always been
fantastic since our first time!
Why? Don't you love me, you idiot?!
My pussy feels incredible!
Princess, you're making such a very lewd face!
You too, Nina! You're making an indecent face!
Your face looks like you're filled with pleasure!
You too, princess.
I changed my mind, so I'm gonna
take care of this little thing.
It's twisting around.
Yeah... Sheila, I really...
I never felt this excited before!
Why is this happening?
Yes... Eric, your dick is so hard and splendid
that my hips won't stop!