Cum lots inside me.
I'm cumming.
Lots is pouring inside.
I may still be inexperienced,
but I hope we can get along, Onii-chan.
Now, for our second round.
Shall we let you do some BDSM rape?
Huh... BDSM?
It's a rank above anal sex.
Oringinal Animation Disc
~The hole that is yet to be challenged by the sisters
The Sanjou 'adventure' squad shall 'cum' again! Chapter~
This position is very embarrassing.
Yup, your shameful spots are completely exposed.
P-Please don't stare at me like that.
Your anus is pulsating, really erotic and cute.
Are you all right, Yuki?
I'll loosen up the rope if it's too tight for you.
No, I'm okay.
It's just that the rope is chafing my skin.
My heart is pounding really hard, and I'm starting to feel tingly.
I see, then let's get this inside your ass right away.
Sakonji Seiichi.
A light novel and hentai game writer.
The boyfriend of this story's heroine, yours truly,
and also my future husband.
He might not look too trustworthy,
but he's a really nice guy.
Come now, Yuki,
you have to relax your anus a bit more.
Sanjou Maki, the girl who loves sex and
is willing to give everything to Seiichi.
The self-conscious erotic and slutty beauty.
She's not only gorgeous,
but also a top student and a strong athlete.
In other words, the perfect model student.
I know, but my body suddenly reacts as it enters me.
My anus is getting excited.
Former Misono, Sanjou Yuki.
She's now in the care of our father after our mother's divorce.
After a few fateful events, and transfer procedures,
she's now living with her sister.
Here's the next ball.
It hurts.
She also has a very erotic body like her sister,
and she's currently trying out anal sex for the first
time to satisfy her beloved brother-in-law.
Do your best, Yuki!
Can you still endure it?
Yes, I can still do it, Onii-chan.
Look, it's almost all the way in, Yuki.
But, it looks like she's already at her limit.
This sensation as it gradually pierces my ass...
Now, I'll pull it out slowly, okay?
Oh, it seems she just came a bit at that moment.
Now, Seiichi, try pulling the rest out at once.
Okay then.
It feels like my anus is going to explode!
I think I'm starting to lose it.
Let's see, it seems your ass still hasn't calmed down.
But, my anus reflexively gets excited.
Well, his thing is quite big.
But we won't get it done if this continues.
It can't be helped.
Here, take these.
Now, we'll use this for now in place of my dick.
Guess this is your limit.
The way both vibrators are in your holes looks very erotic, Yuki.
This is embarrassing, Onee-chan.
Well then, Yuki-chan, are you ready?
Both holes are getting stirred!
My insides are getting rubbed as it turns!
So, how does it feel to be penetrated by
two vibrators at the same time, Yuki?
I'm interested to know how your ass feels.
It's getting stirred hard and deep, it feels very erotic.
It's actually tearing me apart. I'm about to go crazy!
My pussy is about to cum really hard!
This taste and smell is the best.
Onii-chan's taste is also erotic, that's why it's so good.
Hey there. Good morning, Yuki-chan, Maki-chan.
Good morning, Seiichi-san.
Good morning, Onii-chan.
Seeing you guys giving me a blowjob like this
really tells me that we're back to our normal days.
I feel a bit excited.
Oh, Yuki-chan, that uniform.
Yup, this is the uniform of my new school, Onii-chan.
I see, it really suits you.
It's very cute.
I'm glad.
But, I really feel a bit uneasy.
I wonder if I'll be able to get along well with my new mom.
Oh yeah, Seiichi-san,
about what we'll do from now on,
it might be a bit inconvenient for you to handle
us both at the same time everyday.
That's why,
during weekdays we'll switch at least once a day,
starting with me and then ending with Yuki.
I think that would work best for all of us, Onii-chan.
I'm thankful for that.
I'm going to cum, you two.
Onii-chan, there's so much cum.
Your morning cum is thick and smells really strong, as usual,
and it s delicious.
I'll be going.
Be careful, you two.
I've already seen the draft.
Nothing wrong with it, I think.
Okay, now send.
I'm home, Onii-chan.
Oh, Welcome home.
Yuki-chan, how's your new class?
Well, I really did feel nervous.
But the girl next to me was very nice.
She was kind enough to help me, so I
think I was able to make it through.
I see, that's good.
Yup!
I'm home.
Huh? Maki-chan?
You're quite early today.
How was your student council work?
"I was worried about Yuki, who just moved schools,"
or something along those lines, then pushed all the work
on to the other members and came home quickly.
Nyan~
In any case, Yuki seems to be doing fine,
so I'm quite relieved.
I heard she's already made a new friend.
As a new student I was worried she might really
be left behind, or bullied by her classmates.
You really are a worrywart when it comes to your sister.
Though, we're also talking about the naughty big sister
who suggests using ropes and anal sex
on her little sister with a straight face.
That's because she also has the same erotic body as mine.
I didn't want her to experience the same hardships.
You just don't know how much I've repressed
these feelings before I met you.
I only had masturbation to comfort me.
But in the end, my fingers just weren't enough to satisfy me.
That's why I had Yuki...
I see, you're quite the worrywart.
Though, you sure love these BDSM plays we've been doing lately.
That's because...
Whenever I get tied with a rope
my holes become really sensitive,
and my mind becomes clouded with sexual pleasure.
I see.
That's why...
If you stimulate my nipples like that,
I'll get aroused even more, and go crazy!
It's sucking on my dick too hard.
More, push it harder.
Penetrate me deeper with your sturdy dick.
Oh yes...!
Maki-chan, I'm about to...
Give it to me.
Give my pussy all of your thick cum.
Pour it all inside my womb!
It's coming out, it's going wild inside me.
Your dick is pumping hot cum inside me!
I'm cumming, my pussy is cumming!
It's flowing inside me.
Next, we move to the next hole, okay?
Alright.
I'm going inside this other hole liked you asked, Maki-chan.
It's trying to widen it as it pushes inside.
Your ass is very tight, as always.
No, your dick, it just came,
yet it's driving me crazy to no end!
More, push it in more.
Just keep on pushing.
The pleasure that I feel when penetrated anally...
I think I might really love this.
I really want Yuki to experience this pleasure as soon as possible.
You're right.
We'll try our best tomorrow.
Though it's actually just her.
I'm about to cum...!
I'm really going to cum from my ass!
Maki-chan to Nau!
Yes, I'll just send the drafted script right away in that case.
Yes, it'll probably take about five days.
See you then.
Thanks for waiting, Yuki-chan.
Sorry, I suddenly got a call from work,
and accidentally made this a forsaken play.
Is your ass okay?
It's halfway inside of me, and it kind of hurts,
but I'm okay, I can still endure this, Onii-chan.
Yuki-chan, you really are the hardworking type.
Because I really want to have anal sex with you just like Onee-chan.
We pulled out the beads quite quickly last time.
We'll let your ass get used to them for a while.
So let's play with this first, Yuki-chan.
Is that a low burning candle?
Yup.
I see you know about this.
That's right.
Onee-chan told me that dripping low
burning candles can hurt quite a bit,
but she also said it'd feel great.
Is that so?
I'll start dripping it then.
Just tell me right away if you can't take it anymore.
It hurts, but...
It feels quite...
Well, can you still hold on?
Yes, I still can.
It's hot, but it really feels good.
Let's drip some here too.
It's starting to feel really good.
You're also dripping it on those spots?
Yup, you also drip it on those spots.
I think I'm going to burn up.
And my clit's about to cum!
Can you really put it in by yourself, Yuki-chan?
I'll try my best, Onii-chan.
Your big thing is now inside my ass!
Yeah, it's inside already,
and it's very tight.
Your ass also feels very hot.
I'm glad, then I'll drive it all the way in.
Oh wow, I can really feel it widening my insides.
Does it hurt? Or does it feel good?
I don't know.
It just feels very full inside me.
When I think of you completely inside
me, I start to get really aroused.
It has become quite sensitive after its been stimulated for so long.
When your dick rubs inside, it makes me feel all tingly and slutty.
It feels even tighter as I rub it inside you.
The twisting sensation as it grinds feels very great!
Me too, I think I'm starting to feel pleasure in my ass.
My womb can really feel your dick rubbing near it.
Onii-chan, I told you that I want to get used to this quickly,
and I can really feel it right now.
I'm, I'm about to...
It's alright, Yuki-chan.
I'm about to cum myself.
Please cum, Onii-chan.
It feels so hot inside, and it's about to leak out.
I can feel it pumping cum inside my ass.
Onii-chan, your hot cum...
Is completely filling my ass...
And so,
the weekend has finally arrived,
and it's a Saturday.
Today, Onee-chan shall check if Yuki
is now capable of having anal sex.
Umm, when you say check, do you mean...
It's something that should be checked?
Anyway, aren't you being a bit too hasty?
You just got home from school and you're already nude.
Well, it's just that my passion for love and sex
when it comes to both of you is unstoppable.
Now, you two, undress!
Here, Onee-chan.
He can fuck me in the ass now, see?
Your cute anus is actually taking in Seiichi's big dick quite nicely.
It feels really pleasurable when his dick rubs the tip of my anus.
I see you finally mastered anal sex.
And to celebrate this,
I want to give you a special reward.
Ta-da!
Maki-chan, when did you start carrying that along?
I haven't been able to use this for the longest time,
but now my chance has finally come.
Don't tell me the reason why you had
Yuki-chan learn about anal sex,
is because you wanted to use that so badly?
Whoa, she ignored my question.
O-Onee-chan?
For a masochist like you, Yuki-chan,
I'll give you a double penetration.
O-Onee-chan, Onii-chan's dick is already inside my ass.
I don't think it can fit inside my pussy at this point.
It fits you perfectly.
First his dick, and now this one's filling my pussy.
See, it went all the way in.
How does a double penetration feel?
Both my ass and pussy are stretched really wide.
I can't even breathe.
But it really feels great being violated like this, right?
Onee-chan, if you push it like that I'll...
I'll completely lose it.
This is amazing.
It feels so tight that it feels like your ass is going to crush my dick.
Onii-chan and Onee-chan are both rubbing hard inside me.
I'll even do this, and go deeper inside.
Then, it'll feel even better than before.
This dick feels like it's going to go right through my womb.
My oh my.
Yuki, you came already?
I guess this was just too intense for you.
Onee-chan, we're still continuing?
Of course.
Until Seiichi-san cums.
After that, we'll switch places.
I'm... with Onee-chan...
It's because I really want to experience the pleasure too.
The two dicks are rubbing really hard inside me again.
I'm going crazy!
It's okay, just give in to your pleasure.
Oh no, I'm already....!
I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming, Yuki-chan.
So am I, my pussy is already...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming even more as Onii-chan cums inside my ass!
My oh my.
Yuki, you have such a happy expression as you pass out from this.
Tomorrow's a Sunday.
So let's just fuck each other until we
collapse tonight, okay, Seiichi-san?
I don't think we should do it until we collapse, though.
Besides, there's still light out, so there's still time until evening.
Oh well...