Not that this is any more weird to me, but...
You really swing out far too much.
Delicious.
But, your morning wood just tastes so good.
Is Onee-chan already done waking Onii-chan up?
Your hot cum is pumping inside me.
It feels great...
Onii-chan, Onee-chan, breakfast is ready!
Nyan...!
Oh, Yuki.
Morning.
Oringinal Animation Disc
~Maki and Yukno's Extremely Perverted Sex Life~
It's still morning and you're already pumped
too much for it, Onee-chan.
But, I just can't leave that wonderful lovely morning wood alone.
I understand what you're saying, but...
You understand...?
She's my sister, after all.
Right, Yuki?
Yep, because Onii-chan took really good
care of me last summer vacation.
Oh yeah.
I made lots of extra stew.
Just heat some up later if you want.
And don’t forget to put it away afterwards.
Is everything packed already?
Yup, I'm up and ready to go.
You'll be saying goodbye to Seiichi's dick for about a week.
But you still need to greet it at least, right?
Oh yeah...
That feels good, Onii-chan.
Lick it more.
Please lick my sensitive parts.
Your cute clitoris is already bulging.
It looks really cute, Yuki-chan.
No, if you go too deeply I won't be able to control myself.
I want your big and sturdy dick to rub my insides, Onii-chan.
Okay then.
Onii-chan, it's opening up my pussy.
Yuki-chan, your pussy feels tight, it's very
wet, and it's wrapping around me nicely.
Your thing too feels hot, it's very stiff,
and penetrating deep inside me.
You're squeezing me too much.
But, just thinking that I won't be able to taste your dick for a while,
makes me so anxious that my body just pushes hard on its own.
It's just going to be until the end of the week, you know.
It's going to be over an entire week!
Your dick is pushing in so hard, it feels great.
Actually, I don't really feel like going back to Dad's home.
I still have to say goodbye to my friends back there.
Besides, you'd still need to make quite
some preparation before you move in.
It's going deep inside me.
It's even going inside my womb.
I'm going crazy!
Sanjou Maki.
A self-proclaimed slutty beauty.
One night during summer,
she was seen masturbating on the balcony,
by none other than her neighbor, the eroge writer,
Sakonji Seiichi.
After revealing their sexual fetishes,
they're now like an inseparable couple.
Today, they are living the ever-fulfilling carnal sex life every day.
Okay, perfect.
Now then...
Onii-chan...
Do it more intensely!
Penetrate me more!
Yup, yup, just let yourself be pampered by Seiichi-san.
Isono Yuki.
Maki's younger sister.
Due to their parents' divorce,
she was taken to her father's side.
It was not long after she visited her sister's place that summer.
Her father remarried, to a divorced woman already with kids.
The poor girl eventually lost her place in the house,
and simply found herself finding refuge in her sister's’place.
Her natural sexual instincts are just like her sister's.
She has an aura that makes you want
to "play" With such a cute little sister,
and it was not long before she finally gave her virginity to him.
Her potential to have slutty sexual fetishes
like her sister were soon revealed.
Well taken care of by her loving sister and her new Onii-chan,
she spent her days in full enjoyment of sexual pleasures,
and in this last day of summer,
she started moving forward towards a new adventure.
Onii-chan, your stiff thing is rubbing hard inside me.
Oh yes, it feels great.
Are all the paperworks for your transfer already done?
I talked it over with Mom and Dad, and
it seems they've done it already.
But, I'll still attend school there for one week,
before finally transferring to a school here.
It's quite complicated actually.
I'm really quite shy,
so I feel uneasy about transferring schools.
Will I make friends here?
It may not be convincing from someone who's
practically a loner during high school,
but I'm sure it'll be just fine.
Why do you think that?
Because you're a good girl, and very cute at that.
Onii-chan.
I'm about to cum.
Pour it all inside my womb.
Pour all the hot thing inside.
Okay, Yuki-chan.
I'm cumming.
My pussy... is already feeling it!
Your cum is filling the inside of my womb.
It's filling me up.
Your dick felt really great.
Looks like he pumped a lot inside you, Yuki.
Onee-chan? Since when did you...?
Maki-chan?
Yuki, you have to close your pussy firmly,
so that Seiichi-san's cum won't spill out.
Onee-chan, what are you...?
You won't be able to get some for a while,
so you'll have to spend this entire day with his cum inside you.
Okay?
With his cum inside me, all day?
Okay!
You're right.
My insides feel very slimy and sticky with Onii-chan's cum.
Maki-chan to Nau.
You could have bought a ticket with better seats.
Dad's going to pay for it anyway.
I'm fine with a normal one.
I'd feel too anxious sitting in first class anyway.
Will you be okay, Yuki-chan?
Yes I will, Onii-chan.
Yuki, how many times did you cum before we got here?
Umm... around three times, inside the train...
I think...
Okay, that's great.
I'm proud of you as my sister.
I'm not sure if that's really something to be proud of.
Well then, I'll be going.
Take care.
There she goes.
It’ll be a week without Yuki-chan, eh?
Feeling lonely?
Well, I did get used to life with her around quite quickly.
True.
Even so, I'm really glad that her parental authority
switch to Mom was done without a hitch.
Anyway...
Maki-chan.
Since we're already out here in town,
why don't we go on a date?
A d-a-t-e.
In there...
Sitting there for a long time with this inserted inside me...
I really can't keep holding on.
The vibrator keeps stirring my insides.
I really feel aroused when I get touched and rubbed like this.
Onii-chan licked and sucked me lots of times,
so now my nipples have become this sensitive.
The vibrator's going wild.
It's rubbing my sensitive spots.
And it's mixing Onii-chan's cum inside as it drips.
I'm going to cum!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Someone's using the toilet here too?
Oh well, guess I'll just have to hold it in further.
That surprised me.
Oh no, the vibrator is going too deep inside.
Look Onii-chan,
look at how I cum with a vibrator.
I'm cumming while taking a leak!
Anyway, getting invited to go straight to a love hotel,
shortly after sending off the little sister,
and we even rented the S&M room.
But...
I really wanted to try out plays that we can't do at home.
True, the wooden horse is out of the question at home.
I know, right?
Ah, I think you could use a few ideas here as reference.
I won't.
The tip is rubbing hard against my clit.
It feels like it's going to be pressed further.
You still seem happy about it though, Maki-chan.
How's the rope's tightness?
Eh...
It's trying to squeeze my skin tightly as it rubs.
And the sensation it gives at it presses near my pussy is great.
Seiichi-san, you seem to have gotten good at tying me up.
Using that forbidden skill, I want you to bind Yuki-chan next time.
Yuki-chan?
I think she's at a good age to Experience
something more hardcore.
Even you also want to tie her up and "play" with her, right?
Onii-chan, this position is embarrassing.
Don't look!
Well, I guess that's true.
Yuki-chan is the same as me, a real masochist.
I think she'd get used to S&M pretty quickly.
I love how you're really conscious of your own sexual fetishes.
But, to ask me to tie her little sister
up and do these things to her too...
I think we need to punish the naughty elder sister.
Oh my, Seiichi-san, you're really cruel!
It's hot.
My arm, and part of my back is...
My pussy is starting to feel tight too.
I can't get enough of this two-pronged sensation!
My breasts are going to burn!
My nipples are feeling tingly!
My pussy feels like it's going to rip itself apart as it pushes harder.
Oh no, that part has been dripped on
earlier so it's gotten more sensitive.
Its hot!
Oh no, it's coming out.
I'm about to take a leak!
It's going to...
Are you about to piss?
It's going to leak!
Watch closely, Seiichi-san!
Watch how I piss and cum.
My ass is getting opened further.
As this thick and stiff dick is pushing hard inside.
It's business as usual here.
She came home after the new school term's opening ceremony.
I'm busy with work, though she doesn't care about that as always.
Push it harder.
Push it further inside my ass!
Pierce it hard! Violate me more!
I'm envious of Onee-chan.
I really wanted to hear your voice so I called
as soon as I came home from school.
Could I have bothered you with your work?
No, it's perfectly fine.
Anyway, how are things there?
It's good.
I talked about my transfer to my friends here.
Everyone was surprised.
But, there's the internet and phone nowadays.
So it wouldn't really feel that lonesome.
True, it's not like you'd really get separated from people nowadays.
That's right.
It's even more lonesome for me that I won't
able to be with you for this week.
That's why I gave you the vibrator yesterday, right?
Well, that's what she says.
But that vibrator isn't even close to your dick, Onii-chan.
Are you lonely that I'm not there?
Of course I am.
And the impending doom of unfinished
meals is probably going to kill me.
I'm missing your homemade meals badly already.
Don't worry about that.
I'm going to make him some meals while you're gone.
All for Seiichi-san.
You're suddenly going intense...!
I'm going to go crazy.
My butt is so hot, it feels like it's going to rip apart.
Onee-chan, you're doing anal sex with Onii-chan right now, right?
I want some too.
I want to be able to have anal sex with him as soon as possible.
Then come home soon.
We're going to make it happen right away.
Okay.
As soon as I come back,
I want to be able to have anal sex with
the help of your dick, okay Onii-chan?
Of course. I’ll be glad to.
I think I'm at my limit.
I'm going to cum while being fucked anally.
The hot thing is about to pour in.
I'm cumming, Maki-chan.
My butt is going to burst!
I'm cumming!
Yuki-chan, I'm about to cum.
Okay.
Getting at it right away as soon as all preparations were over...
Yuki, you sure have the taste of Seiichi-san's
cum already remembered.
Taste good?
Yeah.
It's been a week since I got a taste,
so it tastes especially good.
Then let your pussy have some nice
sex after one week of abstinence.
The wind feels nice.
Umm... why did we have to come to the balcony?
Well, fall's coming soon, so it'll eventually get cold.
This is the best time to do some outdoor sex.
That's something I'll only ever hear from you, Maki-chan.
Also, this place is where we first met, it's important to us.
And I want it to be important to you too,
so you can make memories here as well.
Not as Misono Yuki,
but as Sanjou Yuki.
Onee-chan.
Now, put your butt out, you still have
to seduce Seiichi-san, you know?
Or else he won't put it in.
Mine's already okay, Seiichi-san.
No, you can't, I won't let you take his dick first, Onee-chan!
I'm going to be fucked first!
There are two delicious flowers in front of me!
And I just can't hold myself any longer!
It's tight!
Onii-chan, your thing is penetrating my pussy,
and it instantly went completely inside.
Yuki, did you just cum?
Y-yeah.
It's been a week since I didn't get a taste of Onii-chan's dick.
So I came quickly as soon as he pushed his way in.
If you're already at this level, then I guess going
into high gear quickly would be okay.
I'm fine, I want it hard.
It's been a long time since I got a taste
of your pussy, and it's tight as always.
It's wrapping firmly, so it feels great.
Your dick too, it just came a while ago and yet...
It's so hot and thick, and sturdy.
Does it feel good?
Yeah, it does.
It feels very good.
Oh, then would it feel better if we play with this too?
Onii-chan, that's...
If you play with that, I...
It feels embarrassing.
But Yuki, you already planned on learning anal sex
with Onii-chan when you come home, right?
That's...
That's true, but...
Onii-chan, my ass feels ticklish.
Oh my, your ass seems sensitive too.
Anyway, it seems I can no longer hold on as well, Seiichi-san.
Then let's switch holes for the moment.
Sorry, Yuki-chan.
No, don't!
You can't pull out your dick!
Your dick is wet with Yuki's love juices.
It's rubbing deep inside me.
Onii-chan, you're such a meanie.
My pussy is itching for it badly.
Just endure it for a bit Yuki.
My womb's about to get completely aroused anyways.
So I can't really hold out for long.
This thick thing is pushing inside deeply!
Your insides are wrapping me nicely.
Feels like it's holding the dick below, while squeezing it at the tip.
Which do you prefer, mine or Yuki's?
Tightness-wise, Yuki-chan's the winner, but...
The overall wrapping sensation is better in yours.
Anyway, both feel very different so I can't really compare.
Both pussy's fit quite nicely to my dick regardless.
It feels good, oh yes!
Push it harder please!
Penetrate through my womb!
I'm, I'm already...!
It's okay, I'm about to cum as well.
It's okay, cum inside.
Pump all of your cum inside my womb.
Lots of it is coming out...
Your sticky cum, it's flowing inside my womb.
Sorry for the wait, Yuki-chan.
Your thing is pushing its way inside me again.
It just came inside Onee-chan and yet...
And yet it's still thick and stiff.
That's because I won't let it go limp until I completely satisfy you.
Don't poke my ass too much.
I'm about to faint from embarrassment.
Faint? So that's how much you get aroused in your ass, eh?
I don't really know.
It feels all tingly and weird.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Beyond that tingly sensation is the pleasure from anal sex, Yuki.
Oh no, I can't control myself anymore.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's alright, I'm going to cum with you.
Cum, Onii-chan.
Cum with me.
I want your hot stuff inside my womb.
Cum plenty inside me.
I'm cumming!
It's coming out, pumping inside me.
Its cumming lots inside me.
It feels warm and nice.
That felt good, Yuki-chan.
I may still be inexperienced, but I hope
we can get along, Onii-chan.
Sounds like you're Seiichi-san's newlywed wife.
And for my precious little sister, I've prepared a little present.
A present?
A brand new straw rope.
Now then, let's start the second round with
you being violated while tied up, Yuki.
Tied up?
Combined with anal sex,
we'll go and challenge a few more hardcore plays.
Eh?!
The night is still young, so let's enjoy this further.