Sounds, light and vibrations.
When people perceive the rhythms of these intermittent sensations,
they are easily susceptible to hypnosis.
And if this happens in an enclosed space, the effect is more apparent.
Yes.
Take, for example, a train.
The soothing rhythm of a train...
Translation: Voldemort
Timing: Ratbunuts
Edit: Collectr
Man`in densha
Hey, there.
Watch where you're walking!
If only my little sister weren't there, I'd love to invite you to my house.
I'm very sorry.
I'm very honored you invited me, though.
I hope I dream about you tonight.
Men really are simple animals.
Men like that will leap through hoops just to satisfy their lumbar vertebrae.
How amusing.
At the next transfer...
I'll escape.
I'm not suited to be an office lady.
Were you out late last night, too, Sayaka Nee-san?
Aya, you're not a child anymore.
Be more careful about what you wear.
Aw! I-I don't really care what I wear.
But someone who might become your boyfriend cares.
So did you wear that G-string because your boyfriend likes it?
It's a "thong". Don't call it by such a lewd name.
And I'm not so cheap that I'd show it to just anyone.
They've been saying this train has a lot of sexual predators on it.
Good grief. I'm sick of all this gross staring!
What did you just...
"This is the first time I've seen boobs as full as yours."
What the hell is this pervert thinking?
"On top of having a sexy body, you've also got a sexy voice."
"With that sexy mouth of yours, just how many cocks have you captured?"
File 1
Big-Breasted Elite Office Lady,
Accosted on the Way to Work
Invistigation Office
Since this is a sensitive and private matter,
you need not answer all the questions.
Would you still like to tell us about it?
Sendo Sayaka-san.
First, this perfume-like substance was dripped onto my neck.
Then, my body suddenly lost the ability to move.
Yes...
No, stop it.
Hey, stop it!
"I see your huge ass hanging out for the picking."
"You really want me to fuck you that badly?"
Wh-What are you talking about?
Why can't l move ?
Y-You're horrible...
"You're the horrible one."
"Spraying your pheromones all over the place,
and making men bow to your will."
"You think that's funny?"
No, he's telling me such gross things. Why?
"For an elite woman, you sure have a lewd voice."
He asked, "Is your pussy throbbing?"
You'll never get away with this.
If I press charges, you won't -
You're gross.
Saying such gross things out loud...
"You're just a bitch in heat, yet you're lecturing me about being gross?"
"Aren't you the one who should be lectured on being gross?"
O-Oh, no. Why?
I'm so embarrassed to hear these words directed at me but I can't get away.
"You're a nasty bitch in heat."
"Why are you glad I'm molesting you in public?"
"I'll knock the horniness out of you, you over-sexed pig."
Just stop it al -
"Your boobs are almost like cow udders."
"Is it because they're popping out that you grew up to be such a whore?"
He asked me,"Do you use them every day to help men cum?"
"I can already see the disgusting line of your dirty pussy from the outside of your panties."
"It must be throbbing through your hot panties."
l hate this. I'm not like this.
I'm not sick like you are.
"You want a cock right away, don't you?"
"You're oozing forth all this hot juice..."
"You must've been holding back for a while."
Don't...
Stop it. Don't come into me.
Stop filling me with dirty talk.
Stop trying to control me with your words.
"Just try asking me lewdly for my cock."
No, l can't...
Don't.
I can't think. My head is full of perverted thoughts.
I can't think of anything else.
"You get turned on so easily."
"Is that because you masturbate every day?"
Don't. That's not true. I'm not that kind of woman.
Please...
Just stop it.
"There's a very female scent emanating from between your boobs."
"Smelling it now makes the back of my nose tingle. "
I'm serious! Please stop it!
"Stop talking like a little sweet virgin with that smoking hot body of yours."
Why? Why won't they help me?
They're our "free audience"?
"Your body... It's feeling lewd."
"Even though I'm not touching it, I feel it."
"Do you have a vibrator in your tits?"
"I'm surprised you can be so cool when I'm teasing your tits like this."
My body is getting more turned on.
Not... Not this!
"Don't try to act righteous now."
"Don't think you can convince me you hate it when your nipples are sticking out so much."
"How many ways can I get such a great feeling out of these tits?"
"Do you squeeze them every day?"
No, I don't.
They're watching.
They're watching me.
They're watching me!
Did I just cum?
Did I cum, while I was peeing?
In front of all these people. This can't be happening.
"Releasing so much cum in front of all these people."
"You really are elite."
"You fearless slut!"
Kana says it's really yummy there.
Man, this sucks!
What the hell!
N-Nee-san...
"Now, you don't need to hold back anymore."
"Just ask me politely to stick it in your cunt."
l can't say such a disgusting word like"cunt" in here!
l can't say "cunt".
No!
"To let something be buried in your gaping pussy,
you'd spread your legs for anyone, wouldn't you?"
"That's nice, coming from someone who just pissed herself in public."
"You cocksucker."
No. No way. No! It's inside.
An erect dick is inside of me!
No! Don't!
It's in deep. Don't put it in so deep!
"Too bad, but it's already deep inside."
"My entire cock is inside your pussy. Can't you see it?"
It's inside of me! This hard... big dick...
This big dick.... inside of me.. thrusting into me!
"I know you like it. You're oozing juice as we do it."
"You really are an elite bitch."
"I respect that. "
That's not... That's not... true at all!
I'm dreaming!
Yes. This is all a dream
It's just a dream!
"You reject reality when times get tough?"
"Then I'll spew plenty of proof into your dirty cunt to show that this isn't a dream."
Don't do it. No more.
Why? This is just a dream.
It's just a dream.
Why does it seem so real?
This dick... even feels real... and thick.
l feel it all... all of it. l feel all of it!
No. No, this isn't right. This isn't the real me.
"You shouldn't stress yourself."
"The walls of your pussy are squeezing my cock like they're stressed out."
That's not it. Your dick... is so thick... and hard.
"You're pushing your ass into my face."
"No pill can cure a sexually perverted bitch like you."
But I... But I...
It's so deep... so deep.
It's hitting my womb... pushing against it!
So rough. It's so rough, I'm losing my mind!
Oh, no.
I'm trying to hold back, but my voice... my voice is screaming!
It's hitting it. It's hitting... my womb.
My womb... my womb.
It's throbbing... throughout... my body.
This dick...This dick...
So big. Oh, no, I can't... No. Not inside.
Not inside. No, don't cum inside of me.
It's dangerous. Stop thrusting your throbbing dick so deep!
I'm gonna get pregnant.
No! I'm cumming! It's coming out of me.
From inside my womb.
The hot, oozing, magma-like semen from the tip of his dick is coming out of my womb.
Oh, no. There's more coming in.
It's a dangerous day for me. This is my ovulation day.
It's a day when I'll definitely get pregnant!
Inside a train, while everyone else watched...
Then you, uh... came from your pussy.
That's not groping, it's rape!
Why didn't anyone help her?
How could a sicko like that still be wandering in public?
He's gonna pay.
He's a menace to women and society!
I'll catch him for sure.
But even so...
What if...
What if I had been the one assaulted?
Thinking about something that gross makes me suddenly want to go.
Lemme see...
Yellow makes you more socially accepted.
It's "perfect to wear when you're feeling under-confident"?
I wonder if they mean like when you're in a haunted house?
I wonder if Yuzu's okay with me leaving her alone.
Ah, but it's not good to trouble others so much.
That's what Miwa-sensei said, remember?
We should be fine. It's not like there's anyone else around.
Wait a minute.
Are you listening to me, Aya?
Yeah, I guess it's scary.
They say there are lots of predators on this line.
You're not talking enough precautions. You a rookie?
C-Cut it out, Miyuki-chan!
But your white panties scream "virgin", don't they?
"Pure" white? You're so clean?
You're just inviting boys to take you.
"Inviting?"
I see.
Yes, maybe he invited his victims.
Cut it out already.
I must've been seeing things.
My sister wouldn't do something like that.
Something so perverted...
I'm not doing it.
I'm not "showing you I want it in my face".
Was that Nee-san just now?
The victim I just talked to?
Not like this. I mean, I can't go home.
I can't go home throbbing like this.
I'm just... so...
I'm not begging you for a favor.
I can't pretend I like it.
I can't just turn on the sexiness because you want me to.
I never asked for your dick. I never wanted it in me.
No. Don't leave me alone. If you do...
I want a dick.
Your big, thick, throbbing hard dick.
l want you to thrust it into me.
l didn't see it! No...
l did, but I'll forget it.
I thought I was satisfied, but I'm not!
My nasty cunt needs a hot, throbbing, big dick inside,
or it won't stop gushing!
Since you're so well-endowed, I need you inside of me to stop the gushing.
Ah, dick, dick!
Your dick has turned me into a slave!
Please, hurry! Your dick... in my cunt. Smash it up!
"Dick"? That's a "pee-pee", right?
My sister...
is soliciting a man?
I need to go there. I need to help her.
But then, why? Why won't my body move?
If it smells too much like pee in here, then make me gush more.
Make me scream more!
Make me unable to walk tomorrow!
Make me into a woman who screams "dick" in a crowd!
Make me your dick slave!
Kill me with your dick!
Oh, no! No! Not like that! No! Please, don't stop!
I love it. If you stop, I really will lose my mind!
Keep going... Keep going until we finish!
I want to finish with your dick!
I want to go to heaven with your thick, hard dick!
Yes!
Your dick is amazing!
I love it!
Oh... Oh, God. Oh, God!
It's so amazing, I can't think of anything!
Um...
your hand.
I'm cumming. Oh, God, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! Yes! I'm cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming...
It's coming! The big, mighty dick throbbed inside of me,
and released its wonderful hot semen in there!
His seed is flowing deep into my womb.
Cumming so violently into me, I-I'm gonna cum again!
I'm cumming again!