Translation: Voldemort
Timing: Ratbunuts
Edit: Collectr
Man`in densha
File 3: An After School Prank, Beware of Discharge!
A groper?
I don't want the other passengers to hear!
It happened on the train?
Yeah. It's been happening the last couple of days.
At first, I glared at him, and he went away.
I don't like how this feels...
I thought of making a big noisy fuss at the next station,
but I couldn't move at all!
I was touched until I got off the train.
There are plenty of girls sluttier than me.
So why was I the one who was targeted?
The answer should be obvious.
Ack, it's raining!
I think too much about myself?
That's usually the way it goes.
Girls dressing room
In the eyes of men, we might be women.
Yuck, gross. My panties are all wet.
When you're going through puberty,
you notice differences between ourself and your peers, even if you don't want to.
What is it?
N-Nothing.
It may seem trivial, but it's a very crucial time for girls.
Jeez. I told you to let it out at the park.
But it's so creepy and dark over there!
I guess since it's raining, there won't be any trace left behind.
I thought the ones I'm wearing now are rather adult.
Shounan. Shounan.
I won't
let
you
grope
me
!!
Protect
yourself
while
going
home
!!!
Yes. That's why they say it's easier to influence someone before she grows up.
They learn the lesson after it's too late.
Nanase Yuzu. Shounen Academy, Ordinary Class.
Seat number 37.
Bust: 74
Waist: 53
Hips: 80
Beware of her bourgeois attitude.
I advise you to cajole her, Corporal.
What's this?
A prank text?
We have encountered a problem on the tracks.
We apologize for disrupting your busy schedules.
We appreciate your patience while we sort this out.
Why now of all times?
Yuzu!
Open the door behind you!
Sorry for the wait. Now we will start the train again.
Shin Shigeru Railway Police Station
Gropers can be arrested if there's a witness, right?
I saw it! That should be enough.
Listen, you.
If you confess everything and turn yourself in now, you'll get off lightly.
Is this always the way it is?
It'll be too late if we wait around much longer!
You want proof from the scene?
Even I don't k now how to find that.
After I came to, he was gone.
I-I'm not a lewd girl!
And there are many girls with bigger boobs than me.
For starters, I don't flaunt myself.
No!
It's nasty. Look.
Huh? But I don't really think that's sexual harassment.
But...
"Even you're getting hard", he says.
I'm so embarrassed that I can't think of anything to say back.
Hey, man...
Where do you think you're touching!?
l mean, don't stare at my panties!
Okay, that's enough. Just cut it out!
Huh?
"How was your friend touched?" How would I know that?
All I know is that touching her and touching me are both against the law!
"You're hotter than your friend.
l guess that means you like being felt up more than she does", you say?
Just leave me the hell alone! You assholes!
Stop it! Y-You're a real pervert!
That guy over there keeps watching like he's interested.
His arms are folded across his chest.
He looks like a gang member.
"Those are the eyes of a male beast wanting to put his dick into a bitch's pussy"?
No! No!
Don't!
No!
Miki-chan!
Y-Yuzu!
AKA: The Corporal
Gropers live to embarrass girls.
No, stop it!
No...
"You're the kid I chose. You'll keep me healthy."
It's a dangerous day for me, but I'm wearing pink.
Almost like I'm expecting it.
I wonder if that's perverted of me.
Why am I even checking to see if it's a "dangerous" or "safe" day!
Thanks to that pervert on the train, I've become obsessed with sex.
"Wearing matching panties on the same day is a sign."
I see.
A circular line.
But once you're on it, the ride lasts a long time.
Looks like that guy they call "The Corporal" is pretty young.
The way he handles girls is very rough.
He's using the fragile moment of puberty well.
Even a strong-willed girl...
will want to feel like a woman when she's seen naked.
That weakens her pride.
I'm just wearing pink panties, but two at once?
l just don't know what to do anymore.
Inside my blank mind, the only thing I can focus on is the moving fingers.
And also...
Even when a woman cums, it doesn't mean it's over.
Because my body is a woman's, it can cum time and time again.
If it's done to me over and over again, I'll still want it.
I'll go anywhere with him.
They saw me!
Even though I'm a girl...
and it's something I don't want seen!
And even though he's just a passing stranger...
Just because he's so hard like that,
I'm showing him my lewd side.
Please keep the room clean
I just wanna die!
I've gotta get out fast!
If I stay here alone with him any longer,
I'll just embarrass myself further!
Ever since Miki-chan came out of there with him,
she's been their slave.
I'm sure they're doing really embarrassing things to her too!
How cruel! This can't be happening!
I'm so sorry, Dad.
I'm not a good girl anymore.
l don't even know this guy.
But he saw everything.
He found out... my girl's secret!
It's becoming so hot. This is embarrassing.
He's turning me into a weird creature!
What a horrible man. He does this to anyone.
While his victim is focused on the pain...
he enters her.
Is he trying to make her forget?
But Yuzu's just a virgin.
This strange smell...
It stinks!
It's the smell of my own pee.
But he forced it out of me!
How mean!
It's too hot! So stop! Please, stop.
No more!
No! Stop it. Not in here...
No, not so hot...
What!?
It's a dangerous day,
but I'm wearing pink like I'm expecting something.
Does that make me lewd?
No! Stop it!
Just stop it!
Just stop it! If you're any harder with me, I'll... I'll die.
My pussy will melt.
Me too. It'll never go away.
My pussy will be stained forever.
The pain will never leave my pussy!
No more.
Oh, no. No more! Not so deep!
No, no! It's hot! It's too hot! I'm losing my mind!
Not so deep inside!
Not today! I can't do this today!
Why did I become such a bad girl?
My insides are all... I don't want cock, but I ask for it.
It's so weird. Oh, no, please don't turn me into a bad girl!
Stop it! When we get off at the next station, I'll... No!
I hate this. I thought I hated it, but I want your cock.
No, that's not right! But I love it!
Today is a dangerous day for me to be doing this,
but I want it inside of me!
I can't control myself.
This hot cock is fighting inside of me!
I think I'm cumming.
I'm lying! I was lying back then! So release it inside me!
Cum inside of me! I think that will make me feel better!
Please!
I don't mind if I become a bad girl either.
No, I want to be a bad girl. Take me with you.
Make me your bad girl.
If you did this to me every day, I wouldn't mind.
Hurry up. I'm cumming soon. Let's cum together!
I can't hold back anymore. I'm gonna cum!
Shoot a lot into me!
It's so hot!
Wow! There's so much coming out!
One more time... please.