Protect
yourself
while
going
home
!!!
Translation: Voldemort
Timing: Ratbunuts
Edit: Collectr
Man`in densha
File 2: The Virgin Road Covered in Semen. Lucky It's a Safe Day!
Jeez. If people laughed that hard at me, I'd be hurt.
The students keep pestering me, asking me if I still look good.
You think they're just messing with me because I'm a teacher?
How rude!
I just wanted to communicate with the students on their level.
Though I do admit I stand out a little.
But...
In the end, they've caught up to me.
Mitsurin Haruka
So are you serious then?
Looks like they're getting married.
Apparently, he was her tutor when she was a student.
Or rather, he was her "tutor with benefits".
Hired by Her Alma Mater One Year Ago
"Compared to the busy bee who flew here and there all the time,
the dead bee was overcome with a sense of calm."
"He was lonely."
Teaching Modern Japanese
A wedding dress, yes?
Do you know your sizes?
My bust is 89 cm. My waist is 65. My hips are 88.
You hooked up with one of your students? Not fair!
Compared to the suffering I had to endure during that time,
I think it was plenty fair.
But more importantly... Who was this with?
Stop that!
Naaty! Who's the lucky guy?
I'm not wearing these specifically for my boyfriend!
l just felt like wearing them.
My students have been a lot more friendly to me recently.
Just the other day, they asked if they could come over to visit.
AKA "The Sergant"
He Likes Stealing Wives
"You're wearing such sexy panties."
"Why not show them?"
How gross. Must he a student prank.
What? What's going on?
Oh, no. How gruff he is.
I haven't said this is okay, either!
Why do I have to be groped by someone I don't even know?!
It's hot! Oh, no! I want to run away, but I have no strength.
"You love men, and you bring out the inner pervert in your own."
N-No! Leave my boyfriend out of this!
He's never even touched me.
Something slipped!
That hurts...
Machido. Now arriving at Machido.
Please enter and exit the train calmly.
The door is closing.
No further than that. You mustn't...
"Don't raise your voice. He'll hear us."
"Sitting and taking it,
while your precious wife-to-be is molested on a train. That's what a pervert is."
I hate this dirty talk. But for some reason, I can't escape.
Yuck. It's deep inside.
The flavor of a man's saliva. This is my first taste!
It's paralyzing, yet warm.
Oh, no, how can you say that?
Of course not! How could I be pregnant?
Don't you remember what I told you before, Dad?
l haven't because I want to be married first.
No. No.
He's touching under the sweatband.
I'm feeling a man's bodily warmth on my skin.
My... pu...
Just now, he said something so vulgar.
"Don't hold back. The underside is even more vulgar and feels great."
"You probably think about lewd, perverse things all day."
You're wrong! I don't!
I'm not a lewd woman like that.
"You may look sweet and innocent,
but I know you think of nothing but dirty things all day."
No, I don't!
Don't pinch it!
I'm so sensitive down there!
No, you're wrong!
I'm not a lewd woman!
Please...
Please, don't.
Someone help!
Hey, look at that. What's going on?
Oh, no. Why?
"Your sluttiness has been asleep until now,
but I can see it shining brightly."
You're lying. That can't be true!
Wh-What's that thing?
It's hot.
Don't tickle me.
No, don't. He couldn't...
How hot! That hot thing is inside of me.
Oh, no. Don't go into me! Don't come into me!
Please!
I'm begging you!
Oh, no, I hate this!
So this is... what a man is like?
So thick... so hard...
Please forgive me. I don't want this!
"While your boyfriend sleeps next to you,
you're giving some stranger a special lap dance."
No, that's wrong. You're forcing me to do this!
Don't put it in anymore!
What you're saying is just too cruel.
How much more do you need to embarrass me?
I'm sorry... I... I...
What? It got bigger?
Amazing... and hot. Don't tell me he's...
Oh, no!
Amazing. More and more is coming out!
So much hot stuff... inside me.
l must get it out quickly!
No way...
What should I do? It's inside me.
Totsugaya. Next stop, Totsugaya.
Yes? Haruka speaking.
Ah, yes, I'm sorry for getting off the train before you.
I was feeling a little ill.
No. I'm okay now.
"You can wash it all you want,
hut you'll never rinse off the smell of sluttiness."
"It's still wet and smelly inside your hole."
"It's turning me on."
How much more is he going to invade me?
Please, forgive me!
l must forget it. Even if it's just a little at a time.
Oh, dear. There's a hole.
At this rate...
I guess this is the girl's bathroom.
Nanase-san!
I'd rather pass just this once. The lock's broken too.
From this point, I can see everything.
Wow! She's hairless like a kid.
And something smells milky.
l told my friends a Japanese toilet is better for this.
But I hate this position.
It's so embarrassing I might die.
But I can clearly see the pink between her legs.
If I'd used this bathroom in her place...
No!
Since I can't stop my pee from making a sound, I'll cover my ears.
And my embarrassing hole is exposed for all to see.
I can imagine my naked pussy.
And then a cock comes in.
Amazing! Just like hack then!
It's hot, just like it was when it took my virginity.
This thickness is so hot and throbbing.
This was the first cock to make me cry.
This cock broke my hymen.
This cock was the first to cum inside of me.
You're going to thrust around inside of me again, aren't you?
Even if I cry or beg, you won't stop.
You keep pushing up to my womb.
Even though I never told you I wanted you to.
Even though I was saving it for someone else!
l was made to lick the tip of a cock that I didn't want to lick.
And I was made to suck on my stained panties after he broke my hymen.
But that was just the beginning.
He's haunting me more and more.
In my bed at home.
In the train.
In the classroom.
In the faculty lounge.
Stripping me completely naked in front of all my students.
Everything exposed to everyone. My pussy being pierced.
But not just my pussy.
My butthole, and my mouth too.
Even the hole where pee comes out.
The hot, thick cum spills into it.
He cums over and over again.
And in the end, I faint.
Even so, you still punish my pussy with your cock.
Sensei!
Haruka-sensei!
Please, won't you close the door quickly?
Everyone will see me naked!
I haven't told Mom about this,
but I think I'm old enough to wear a bikini now.
l haven't even bought it yet, but I'm so embarrassed.
I wonder if...
if I'm just repressed.
Sensei! Are you sure I can pick any one I want?
Even if it's against the school dress code, you won't tell anyone?
Right. It's my way of apologizing.
If you wear them on a medical examination day, however, the deal is off.
Thanks!
The sensation won't go away.
That hot, hard sensation...
still remains inside of me.
And the more days pass,
the more vivid the sensation becomes.
It becomes clearer.
Until I've become exactly what that man wanted me to become.
Thank you. I'll just have tea.
I couldn't sleep very well last night either.
Even inside my dreams, I can't escape him.
Please.
Set me free.
That was fast.
It's you.
My boyfriend decided to leave us alone?
"This is the best deal for both of us."
"If we're in here, no matter how loud you scream,
your boyfriend won't find out."
"With your nipples so happy and erect,
don't pretend you don't like this."
"A dirty slut like you...
doesn't have the right to act embarrassed."
I'm sorry.
I monopolize every man's attention,
and I get a kick out of it.
Yes, my boobs are lewd!
I can't hold back anymore.
May I ask... May I ask you to satisfy me?
Please, let me beg you!
Please, get bigger. Hurry. Get bigger. Get harder.
Please.
Get hot... Hotter... Hotter... More.
Get hotter... More... Even hotter... Hotter!
Get so hot you burn my boobs.
Just like when you stole my pussy the first time, get hot and hard.
One more time. Fill my slippery pussy with your seed!
N-Not yet! But your cock just... throbbed a lot.
If you cum now, there won't be enough for my pussy.
If you have to cum, then please cum inside my mouth-puss-
Oh dear. What a waste.
Please. Don't lose focus.
Without your cock, I'm going to lose my mind.
He embarrassed me with his dirty talk,
and filled my head with all kinds of lewd thoughts.
Ever since that day...
Ever since the day he turned me into a woman,
I've only been able to see his cock in my mind.
"Your lewd body. If you show it to me now,
it'll he tough to leave the train soon."
Please don't tease me anymore!
I want your cock!
That's all I want!
As long as your cock is inside of me,
l don't need anything else!
If you don't like the fact that I'm a teacher, then I'll quit!
I don't even care if you make me pregnant.
Or even if you leave me a special "present" that never goes away.
As long as you can turn my pussy into something that helps me remember your cock forever...
So... So... So!
Be harder! Be rougher!
Just like in my dreams. Please mess me up, like an animal!
Use your cock so hard my pussy rips.
Cock!
The muscles of my pussy are contracting.
You're touching my womb.
And I want your cum in there.
Do you intend to make me pregnant?
If you do, then go in deeper.
Put your cock deeper inside of me!
You say I'm screaming too loud? That someone will hear us?
But I'm about to cum. I can't help it.
I'm about to show you the way I'm transforming...
by the power of your mighty cock!
It feels so great that I want you to watch.
So I want it raw.
Your cock that I kissed so many times before...
is now kissing my pussy over and over again.
My most important place... where babies come from.
A place where no one else has been except you.
Shower me with your cum!
Please turn me into a mother!
My womb belongs only to you. Fill it with your hot cum!
Please! Please, I'm begging. Inside of me. Cum inside of me!
Send me to a cum paradise!
It's cumming. There's lots of hot stuff inside of me.
I'll take it all. I want to drink up all of your cum.
I don't want to waste a drop. I want it all.
I'm going to be a bride soon. I'm sorry my pussy is so smooth.
I'm sorry someone else is going to leave his seed in my womb.
But you're wonderful. You're so warm.
I must've gotten pregnant just now.
I belong to you. I am...
No, but myself and the baby inside of me are...
That's right, I'd better tell my dad about this.
Mitsurin Family Grave
See? Isn't it wonderful, Mom?
I'm gonna be a mother too!
Until I am, I'm going to keep doing this!
Please watch me get pregnant!
To cerebrate, we're bringing you lots of cum!
I'm so sorry, Mom, for stealing your cock.
"I know. I know, Haruka."
"It's that dangerous time of the month for you."
"Just like the time when I got pregnant with you, Haruka."
"No matter how many times I did it, my vagina tingled."
"And I cried. Goodness, Haruka, you'll be a child forever."
"I can't let you get married like this."
"Even if you leave the family, I'll still have to watch over you."
"So even if I give birth to a little brother or sister for you, please forgive me!"