Ah, this place might be more convenient
since it's closer to the train station.
So that's why they can charge less...
We have a strategy to counter this, right?
Nope...
Huh?
But if the power you have is the real deal...
Things should work out, shouldn't they?
You mean... we came here without a plan?
Yep.
Original Animation Disk: Mankitsu Happening.
Tsun Tsun Dere Dere. The Horizon of S and M.
"Do you like big breasted stupid daughters!?" Arc.
This is the real deal.
Their equipment's a lot newer than ours.
Oh? I seem to remember the faces
of the customers over there.
Huh?
Scouting out your competition?
Or have you admitted defeat and want me to hire you?
No, we just wanted to know
what kind of store we're up against.
Now that you know,
what are you going to do?
There's nothing you can do,
except to realize the power gap between us.
First, the steady flow of customers we get from being new
and then, the distinguished branding of a chain store.
There's no way to possibly bridge the gap between us.
It's like the difference between heaven and earth.
Or maybe between Dragons and Wyverns
I don't really get those comparisons...
I guess the poor can't comprehend anything
that isn't at a commoner's level.
Show me your faces twisted in vexation.
There's a saying that says,
"The cornered rat bites the cat."
Maybe rats can fight back against cats.
However,
there's no way to strike back at an
intergalactic spaceship now, is there?
I still don't really get your comparisons,
but I understand that you're trying to say
there's a huge gap between us.
I know, right? It's frustrating, isn't it?
Show me more of those frustrated expressions.
I can't get enough of this.
Taking down the guy who put me in such
an embarrassing position feels amazing!
That said... What's up with her?
She has boobs that you just can't stop squeezing...
Even if she's not showing it,
this vulgar woman should be pent-up too!
Well, whatever. Come in and
take a look at our discounts and sales.
I'll excuse myself since I am quite busy
with managing this chain store.
Seriously, what's up with her?
Something looked off about her...
She was probably pretty happy
about "Freedom" being crushed.
Let's leave. If we stay any longer
we'll just be helping with their profits.
But we haven't even done anything yet...
Huh, Rei-san?
Wait, is that a... Huh?
Wai...
Wh-Why did something like that fall down there?
Probably a result of your "happening" power.
What do you mean by that?
This way.
Huh? Where are we going?
Here.
You can't just open that...
It's filling me up inside.
It's so amazing.
Their faces full of frustration...
The faces they made after knowing there
was nothing they could do make me feel so good!
I can't help myself. I want more!
All these toys are going wild inside me!
They all want more of my high class pussy.
This is the punishment for those commoners
who dared to even stand before me.
I can't wait to tear their store apart, piece by piece.
They're definitely gonna make faces
that are even better than what I saw today.
My ass feels good too!
The two holes are competing with each other
to see which one provides the most pleasure...
My pussy... My high class pussy!
It's already wet and now it's getting
even wetter from being stirred up!
It's gotten to the point where I don't care who or what
sticks their huge cock inside my sophisticated pussy.
But I won't let anyone but myself
do what they like with my pussy...
The vibrators rubbing against each other feel so good!
It's coming, it's coming!
In my ass and my pussy...
the pleasure is...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Masturbation is the best...
This isn't enough...
I want to do it one more time, no...
two or three more times... or just do it for the entire day...
You still want to do it, right?
Keep going.
Wh-What are you saying?
Keep. Going.
Y-Yes...
O-Onee-sama.
Even though I'm being watched, I just can't...
Being watched by commoners while I masturbate...
You get off on being watched?
Y-Yes! I do! I totally do!
Wait, have you been doing this
ever since we saw you today?
Yep. You didn't notice?
Notice? This isn't something that people normally do!
Agreed.
If you get off on being watched,
how about we go get more people?
Eh? O-Onee-sama, what are you...
What is she doing?
Look! Please look!
Today for a limited time only,
the owner's pussy is on display.
This still isn't enough for you, is it?
Let's put it in further.
Any more than that and I'll...
Oh, I forgot to return this...
It's spreading me open!
My pussy is being spread open in front of all these people.
This is the widest it's ever been!
Try moving it yourself.
P-Please watch how I masturbate.
Rei-san, isn't this going a little overboard?
There are so many cocks inside me!
Not just in my pussy,
there's something deep inside my ass as well!
It's twisting and turning inside me!
Yeah, that's good.
Onee-sama. More! Suck on it more!
These two thick vibrating toys
are rubbing together,
making me so wet,
and spreading my pussy open so wide!
They're going in so deep...
My pussy is being spread so much!
They're rubbing together and it feels so good!
In front of all these people,
with two dicks in my dripping wet pussy...
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Please watch me, the manager of this store,
as I cum with my dripping wet, high class pussy!
I'm cumming!
Ow!
What are you doing?
That all happened so fast,
I was just making sure it wasn't just a dream.
What I thought was a dream,
was actually an inevitable consequence.
After a few days, net cafe Medium
was closed and torn down.
The rumors of the owner, Sayaka, masturbating
spread straight to the head of the company...
Thanks to that, business has come back to Freedom.
And even though we've managed to avoid
being shut down for the time being...
My mind still can't wrap around
everything that has happened.
Rei-san said it was all thanks
to my "happening" power,
but I never expected
something like this to happen.
I guess all's well that ends well.
Yeah, I suppose.
What do you mean "ends well"?
There's nothing that ended well at all!
I keep telling you that only staff
are allowed past this point.
Shut up!
Thanks to you, I've been kicked out of my home
and blacklisted from all other net cafes!
It's at least half your fault, though.
Shut your trap!
Stop slacking off and clean the room I'm in.
Yep that's right.
After being kicked out of her house,
she's been living in Freedom's common room.
Understood. I'll clean it immediately.
Hmph. You should've done it
without me asking. You're so slow.
Look, you totally missed a spot.
What are you, my mother-in-law?
How dare you use that tone of voice
to address a god-like customer like myself?
I-I apologize. It just came out.
Wh-What a rude man.
You've put me in such an embarrassing position.
Falling over was my fault, but after that...
Silence! I'll have your body take responsibility.
Um... by that, you mean...
You do it with the other girls all the time, right?
So just do it with me too.
You can't.
Rei-san...
Wh-What are you wearing?!
Well, I was feeling kind of hot...
Since I'll be using that hot,
thick, hard, manga cafe dick.
B-But what about me?
Let's see.
I'll let you use my dick.
You have a good one, right?
Onee-sama's dick?
Yes! Of course!
Mankitsu happening.
I'll put my dick in for you.
The dick that's sticking out of your pussy is so thick!
This is the thickest toy from my collection.
I'll drink some of your erotic and delicious milk.
Onee-sama's dick! Her big,
thick dick is going in and out of me!
It's going crazy inside me!
Come on, bring your dick here...
Rei-san...
It's here! The real dick is here!
My ass is wrapping itself around your dick!
My asshole is being spread open so wide!
I can feel the pleasure you're feeling
by the way your dick's moving inside me!
A real... a real dick is spreading my asshole out so wide!
It's stirring up my insides!
Rei-san, your asshole is really amazing.
It's squeezing me so tight!
Your dick feels so good.
It feels so good that I'm starting to lose my mind!
More! Do me harder! Make me feel it
even more using my asshole!
You really like it in your ass, don't you?
Even though you usually have a poker face,
now it's showing some raw emotion!
R-Rei-san, I'm gonna...
Cum! I want your hot stick cum inside my ass!
Yes!
There's so much cum coming out from your dick!
It feels so good that I think I'm gonna lose my mind!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming with both my pussy and ass!
I'm gonna cum from both of them!
I'm going to cum with you too!
I'm going to cum with your cock inside me!
I'm cumming, I'm still cumming! This is the best
I've ever felt! I don't ever want to forget about this.
You're playing around while
you're supposed to be working!
Huh?
How's this? I have a swimsuit too!
Why are you wearing a swimsuit?
I was wearing it for a photo shoot earlier.
I don't have one.
W-Well, nobody usually brings
a swimsuit to a manga cafe.
Anyway, it's my turn to have you for myself.
What?! I'm here too, you know!
There won't be anything left then!
What won't be left?
– Isn't that obvious?
Keiihi-san's...
Onii-chan's...
Dick!
Onii-chan's dick wants me.
It's definitely picked me.
Look, it's getting so hard.
That's because it's getting hard for me.
If you really want to feel good,
I'll help you cum.
I-I won't cum! How about I help you get off?
Hey, this feels good, doesn't it?
It does but doesn't!
This isn't going to end any time soon.
Come over here already.
Choose one of us with your dick, Onii-chan.
All right.
It's here! Onii-chan's dick is coming inside me!
You're so kind, Keuchi-san.
I'm sorry. I can't decide between the two of you.
That's fine. That's just who you are after all.
Then satisfy both our pussies with your dick.
Your dick is so hard even after cumming!
It's so big and hard. It's going deep inside me!
I love how your dick moves in me!
I'm a dirty girl who likes to be screwed with dicks!
Having sex in a swimsuit kinda turns me on.
Using the swimsuit I used for work feels so wrong!
But I like it so much!
Just when I thought he pulled his dick
out of me, it came back inside!
Why does it feel so good?
I don't know! I don't know!
What is this? His dick feels so good!
It's going so deep inside, it feels so good!
It's okay if you have sex with other women,
but make me feel good too!
That won't do, Onee-sama.
Even after being fucked so hard with that dick,
you still want more up your ass?
Yeah...
I might want more of that hot, sticky cum
to be shot right inside my ass.
Well then, allow me to satisfy your beautiful asshole.
Doing it like that isn't even close
to how it feels with a real dick.
Is that right? Well, then...
W-Wai...
Wow, your asshole is like a bottomless pit.
Looks like even more can go in!
My asshole is being spread open so wide!
Any more than that...
Any more than that and I'll...
Wow! The size and shape
of your asshole is just amazing!
I'm gonna cum!
Everything's moving around wildly
in my asshole! It feels so good! I'm gonna cum!
The dick milk that was inside her
shot out onto my face!
It feels so good!
Please, wait! Otona-san! If you do that, I'll...
I can feel your dick going
deeper and deeper into my pussy!
If you keep on doing that,
I'm gonna lose my mind!
No way! I'm not gonna stop!
This feels so good!
Your dick is getting bigger!
It's getting so big!
Something's starting to come out of the tip!
I can't hold back anymore...
You can cum, but make sure
you have enough left for me, okay?
No guarantees,
but I can't hold back anymore!
Onii-chan's sperm is filling my pussy up!
Don't take a break.
Give the rest to me.
It's so wet!
What is this? It feels so good!
Your dick milk is spreading inside me!
His cum is coming out of me!
I can feel his dick milk welling up inside of me!
It's going to come out!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Your dick is still good to go, right?
What?!
Wait, Rei...
And thus, the manga cafe, Freedom,
somehow avoided being shut down.
A lot of things have happened here,
but it seems that it'll
keep running for days to come.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My womb has filled up with you!
I'm cumming again! I'm gonna cum again!
I'm going to cum again!
Your dick... your dick... feels so good!
translator: hikarucon
translation check: jimaku-danshaku
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: punk4real
quality control: fyurie