I can't believe I got fired from my part time job again.
It can't be helped with my constitution.
Three months is a rather long for me.
I can't Just laze about forever.
I wonder if there are any jobs left that I can handle.
It'd be nice if I could find something where I could
be alone and didn't have to deal with people.
Oh?
Oh, it's you, Yoshioka?
Hey! I heard you got fired! Again!
You sound happy even though I'm in a pinch.
I'm in the same boat as you. I do have a job for you though.
Come work for me. I'm short-handed.
Huh? But you run a manga cafe. No way.
Customer sales are the last thing I can handle at the moment.
Don't worry about it. If you're worried about female customers,
we don't really get that many. That's
about it, so get over here now.
You're just laying around anyways, right?
Wait! He hung up. It can't be helped.
Might as well go in and check it out.
This is the Freedom Manga Cafe.
That's the name of the shop that the Yoshi family runs.
Well, I gave you a job, so could you start today?
This is rather sudden.
You were a regular here in the past, so
you should know what the job entails.
I won't make you do everything on your own, so ask your senior
workers if there is something you don't understand.
Senior workers? Not you?
Oh, right. Could you come here, Rei?
Hm?
This is Rei Suzukawa-san.
She's been at my store the longest and has lots
of experience, so she's in charge of training.
Nice to meet you.
Wait a second! I have no problem with
having a trainer, but she's a girl.
There wouldn't be a problem if you didn't see her
as a woman with a chest and body like that.
That's not what I mean! Why are you pairing
me on a shift with a girl right off the bat?
Don't worry. She's rather special, she's off
in her own little world most of the time.
Even so...
Don't keep your senpai waiting.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Okay, I'll leave the rest up to you, Rei-san.
Huh?, you're leaving?
I've been up all night. I found hired
help, so I'm going home to sleep.
Hey, hey hey! You're just gonna leave me like this?
There are two of you. Keep up the good work.
Take care.
Well, I am in your hands now, Suzukawa-san.
You can call me, Rei.
Nice to meet you.
And that's how I got a new job against my will.
Mankitsu
Happening.
Original anime disk
~Woman troubles out of nowhere!? Protect yourself from the beautiful ladies! Compilation~
Ah, onii-chan!
Wh-What?
It is you, right?
Uh, Kururumi-chan?
I haven't seen you in a long time, so
I thought I'd never see you again.
Well, I haven't been around since leaving university.
This is Kururu Hiiragi. She is the daughter of Leela, Freedom
Manga Cafe s owner, Leela, which is where I currently work.
She's been calling me "onii-chan" ever since we met by
chance from the time we were both regulars here.
I almost didn't recognize you, Kururu-chan.
It took me a second.
I've become more womanly.
But you haven't changed at all.
Well, I was already a university student back then, and
my height and weight are pretty much the same.
Wait a second. You're wearing a uniform.
Do you work here now?
Well, a customer wouldn't be mopping now, would they?
I suppose i can see you all the time here.
Of course, when I am here.
Yay! I'm so happy!
You just gave me another reason to come here.
Good luck with your job, onii-chan.
I seriously didn't recognize Kururu-chan.
Her face hasn't changed much, but her body...
I don't remember her looking like this.
She has a completely feminine body now.
This is bad. It will affect my stamina and I might get a boner.
I used to think of her just like a little sister, so I never
thought about her in a sexual way before.
But that feeling just now...
Just focus on work!
I'm finished! What should I do next?
Let's see... you could clean in between the booths.
Got it.
It'd be great if I just get through it at this pace.
Sorry about that.
This feels so good.
I really shouldn't be doing this.
But I just can't stop moving my fingers.
I thought I'd never see him again, but I did.
I never would have imagined that Kururu-chan
would do something like this.
Onii-chan! Onii-chan.
Huh?
Come here, onii-chan.
Okay!
I didn't see anything.
Yes you did. And you're going to keep watching.
Kururu-chan!
I'm doing something so unladylike in front of you, onii-chan.
I-I sometimes hide out and do naughty things like this.
It's not like I do this every day, just once....
Just once every now and then!
Uh, what I'm seeing is real, right?
This isn't a daydream, right?
I never thought I would think of Kururu sexually until now...
But who would have thought she would turn
out to be so sexy the next time I saw her?
I'm being watched. Your gaze is locked fight
on a place I haven't shown to anyone else.
Watch me. Keep watching me more, onii-chan.
I don't mind being watched if it's only you.
I came. I came in front of you, onii-chan.
You're all hot and bothered now, onii-chan.
Kururu-chan!
Do you want to come too, onii-chan? Then we'll be even.
Okay then!
I just had my face buried in her tits, but who would have
thought I would be titty-fucked by her this quickly?
It's so hot! So this is how hot a penis is.
Wow! You're so big that I can't cover it with my breasts.
But I won't lose either. Look, look!
My breasts have gotten bigger, haven't they?
Yeah, that's the part I didn't recognize the most.
I remember you being so flat-chested before.
You haven't been here in so long, so I have
so many pent-up thoughts and feelings.
Take responsibility for them with your penis.
The part between my breasts feels like it's going to melt.
It feels like they are really melting even
though they have a hold on your dick.
I-I feel like I am gonna melt too.
It's twitching, but I have to grab onto
it firmly or else it might slip out.
Something came out. It's so sticky.
My tits feel so good!
They're going to smell like your dick.
Your penis is even bigger than I imagined.
The tip of your penis is touching the base of my chest,
and I can really feel its warmth from its entire body.
You've been waiting for it right, onii-chan?
I'll keep squeezing your dick until you cum.
Sorry, it felt so good that I wasn't able to concentrate properly.
Th- This... this has got to be a dream.
I will just go with it being a dream for now.
Your dick and my tits are so sticky.
The wetness is on my tits now.
It just keeps coming out from the tip.
An indecent amount has come out.
So this is what a dick smells like.
The scent from the inside of your dick is going to seep into my tits.
It has even formed a string.
Your dick is making my tits perverted.
They are so wet.
I'm going to cum!
You're going to come already, onii-chan? I'm so happy!
My tits do feel good.
Cum, onii-chan!
Show me your cum!
Show me right here in this booth, in
your special titty-fucking booth!
This tastes so good!
So this is what your dick tastes like.
It tastes funny, but it's your flavor.
I could get hooked on it even though it smells and tastes like this.
Ow!
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes, what is it?
I saw you when I was passing through.
S-Sorry! It just sort of happened!
It's fine as long as we aren't busy, but still.
What should I do? This person is my trainer.
It might be better if I told her about my constitution.
Um, could I have a word as well?
Huh, what is it?
This might seem a little far-fetched,
but I have trouble around women.
I told Rei-san about my constitution.
I told her about my tendency of turning into a lucky
pervert around women, and doing illicit things.
It is something I have absolutely no control over.
I left nothing out and told her everything.
That's right. I haven't been able to hold down a job for long
because I can't help but succumb to my condition.
Hm?
I guess it really is hard to believe.
Yeah, but if you say so.
I don't know whether she believes me or not,
but she she seems to accept it for now.
Rei-san has been acting strange ever since
I talked to her about myself yesterday.
Hm? Thank you, come again!
I'm gonna go behind you.
Okay!
It can't just be a coincidence.
Rei is getting close to me of her own accord. What for?
I told her about my problem and assumed
she would be avoiding me.
Is she trying to see if she can set off my
special powers with her own body?
I-I'm going to the bathroom!
Ah! Even she wouldn't follow me into the bathroom.
R-Rei-san!
I'm going to the bathroom!
Don't worry. I just came to do a routine check.
It doesn't have to be right now!
Owwww!
I'm so sorry, Rei-san!
What the hell just happened? I'll move right away.
What do you mean it's okay?
So this is what a dick tastes like.
Rei-san!
Hmm, I can't seem to suck it properly this way.
You don't have to do that.
It tastes a little funny.
Ah!
It's gone already.
But it's hard to get the tip in my mouth.
Stop, Rei-san! I'm going to come!
Don't worry, it's actually better for me in this position.
It doesn't strain me, and I can stay for as long-
Something slightly thick is coming out of it.
Sorry, I'm cumming!
This is a dick's cum... It feels like...
I'm so sorry, Rei-san!
Don't worry about it. Get back to work.
O-Okay. Excuse me then!
So this is what he meant.
It looks like my little problem is already running rampant.
I thought I'd just rekindled my relationship with Kururu,
but ended up doing something perverted.
Who would have thought I would do something
like that with my senior, Rei-san, as well?
I never could hold down a job for long with this pattern.
Good morning!
Morning! Huh? Why are you wearing
the store uniform, Kururu-chan?
I'll be in your care starting from today.
I heard you were short-handed from
Yoshio, so I got a part time job here!
What?
Yeah, this will make my job easier too.
Let's do our best together, onii-chan!
Alright.
This is bad. First Rei-san and now Kururu-chan, I
now have girls around me all the time at work.
Come on! Your voice is too low!
Cheer up!
It's important for clerks to be lively.
I-I guess you're right.
Watch out!
Ow! Huh?
Onii-chan, this is an awkward position.
Sorry! I'll put you down right away!
Don't! Hold me like this.
Hey!
You're so hard, onii-chan!
Teach me a lesson with your big hard dick, onii-chan.
Ah. My panties came off.
Okay, here we go.
It's thick!
You're inside me, onii-chan!
Kururu-chan!
Your thick training dick is deep inside me.
Train this part-timer well with your penis!
B-But, it really is too thick, onii-chan.
It keeps pulsing and throbbing inside me.
It'll be bad if we get caught.
Th-Then I'll continue to organize the bookshelf while we do it.
So please keep training me with your dick!
This is the first time I've felt your entire dick inside me, Onii-chan.
And we're doing it here of all places, even though we shouldn't.
It feels too good to stop!
This is such vulgar sex!
We're doing something bad, but it feels so good!
S-Sorry, onii-chan!
Your dick feels so good!
This feels so good!
W-Well, I will do my best to make your thick dick feel good!
Your dick is too big, so it hits all the way to the back.
It's all the way in me, even though it's so thick.
It's all the way in my pussy!
We can't keep this up forever, so I'm going to cum!
Your entire dick is being swallowed by my pussy.
The tip of your dick is hitting all the way at the back!
I can't hold it!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
I'm going to have my first vaginal orgasm
for the first time from your dick.
I'm going to cum, too!
It's getting bigger!
Your dick is getting bigger!
Your sperm is spreading out inside of me!
Hot and sticky liquid is coming from your hot dick!
I'm still cumming!
Oh no!
You came inside me.
My body is full of cum.
Kururu-chan went home, but Rei-san
is still here, so I can't relax just yet!
How long has she been there?
You done yet?
I just finished!
Okay, then I want you to help me with
my work next. Would you mind?
Got it!
I'll start here, so you start over there.
Got it.
It looks like she can handle this alone, though.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What's this?
Sorry about that!
This is a problem. You made me leak.
This is bad. I'll need you to service this drink bar as well.
From the top to the very corners.
All the way to the corners?
That's right.
It seems I'm leaking from quite a few places because of you.
Alright, then I'll start by servicing the drink bar.
You can be stronger and rougher.
But why do you have milk, Rei-san?
It just started coming out a while ago before I noticed.
I see.
You're not so bad at sucking! Keep servicing my tits!
I'm going to squirt!
Keep servicing!
This one, right?
My nipples are squirting out milk like a dick.
This is so perverted.
This one is doing it too. I want your thick dick inside me.
This part looks broken too.
Y-Your dick is making my pussy overflow onto my ass.
Rei-san's insides feel so good.
It feels like I'm going to drown in perversion.
Just refill me as you want to.
Rub it in really hard and really wet.
My pussy drink bar is too.
This is bad. I can't control my body. I'm going to break again.
Your dick is is piercing my pussy.
I want a drink from my perverted drink bar too.
Being able to suck tits like this,
feels really something.
Milk, milk, my perverted milk juiced drenched breasts
and my dick loving sex hole, I'm cumming with both of them!
Rei-san, I'm gonna cum too!
Your dick is hits on my womb hard as it pumps cum inside it.
My semen tank is full to the brink!
My body and pussy are being maintained by a thick dick!
My breasts!
I'm cumming out of my pussy and breasts!
I'm such a jerk.
I've gone through a world of trouble as a lucky pervert.
But who would have thought that I would so willingly go along
when I had something perverted right in front of me?
I wonder if I'll be able to continue my part time job at this rate.
I don't care anymore. I'm going to bed.
I just have to get used to it.