Due to my extremely potent "Lucky Pervert" power,
I find myself in a lot of lucky, perverted
encounters with girls.
I'd be fortunate if the effects of the powers ended there,
but it ended up affecting my relationships too.
I thought it wouldn't affect my
work at the manga cafe but...
Kururu-chan, the girl who became attached to me,
Rei-san, my senpai at work,
And the extremely popular idol, Otona-chan...
I've entered a sexual relationship with all three of them,
and it's going pretty well so far.
It seems like my power is equally
affecting each one of them.
At any rate, it'd be great if nothing bad happens.
But who knows...
Mankitsu Happening
The Lucky Pervert is in donger! The President's doughter is getting a search warrnant?!
My, what a tiny building.
I wonder what the inside look like.
Is she looking for something?
That's a weird way to go about it though.
Ma'am, only employees are allowed past that...
Ow! What's going on?
Ma'am?!
I can't see her face, but this is the
same person from before, right?
U-Um...
I'm fine, just go away!
E-Even if you say that, this place is off limits.
W-What are you doing then?
Hurry up and help me already!
Make up your mind!
Yes, at once! Okay, please pardon me...
Ma'am, please stay still!
I can't because you're touching me in weird places!
You're useless!
You can't even help me out elegantly?
I will, once you let your legs behave "elegantly"!
I thought I was a goner.
Wh-What embarrassing things were you doing to m-me?
I-I'll remember this!
What just happened...
What's wrong with that shop?!
Doing that kind of thing to me...
Just you watch!
I, Midou Sayaka, will make sure to return the favor!
Something wrong?
I might just be imagining it,
but aren't there less customers than usual?
It's probably just your imagination.
Well, coincidences do happen.
We're the newly opened net cafe, Medium!
Please come, take a look!
Please come!
Netcafe Medium
Commemorative sale for the
grand opening of the net cafe "Medium"?!
This is why!
What? You knew about that new rival?
You sound pretty nonchalant knowing that though.
Over the past few days, the amount of customers
coming here has clearly decreased.
"It'll go back to normal soon, so it's fine?"
Well, I hope you're right...
So, a similar store opened next to us?
And it's so much cheaper than ours.
Looks like it.
What do we do?
If the amount of customers keeps decreasing...
But this is a commemorative sale for their opening, right?
Oh yeah, as soon as that sale ends,
everything should be fine, right?
Yeah, that's what I think.
Onii-chan, were not getting too many customers, are we?
We're not gonna go broke, right?
This shop's manga collection is really good.
Switching to a chain store wouldn't be the same.
Well, I think we'll be alright, so long
as we can brave the storms.
That's only if the storms ever stop.
Huh? What's with you? Seriously, you're...
Um... who are you?
You're acting like this after everything you did to me?!
Eh? Did you do it with her too?
Huh, what? What're you guys talking about?
Eh? Um, I don't really know either...
What the hell!
You must really want this shop to be crushed, don't you?
I get it!
I'll take full responsibility and completely
annihilate this store!
I've decided.
I'm going to extend the commemorative
opening sale for Medium!
Extend it!
Eh? Wait, by commemorative sale, you mean...
Also, who are you anyway?
Oh, I'm a bit late inroducing myself.
I'm the President of the net cafe
chain Medium, Midou Sayaka.
President of Medium, Midou Sayaka
Have fun waiting for the inevitable end of your store.
Have a good day!
What's with her? She just said what she wanted and left.
What's going on?
I-I have no clue either.
Wait, was she that girl?
Does this mean that I brought trouble to my
workplace again because of my power?!
BANKRUPTCY
Wh-What's wrong, Keiichi-san?
Onii-chan? Onii-chan?
What the hell?!
This place is in trouble.
Now that the entire store's involved,
it's not just my problem anymore.
So slippery!
I stopped.
Onii-chan?
Sorry, Kururu-chan.
Oh, you surprised me.
You just suddenly appeared under my skirt...
I might be so surprised that I'm
losing the strength in my legs.
You're bad, Onii-chan.
You're the one who surprised me
and started this whole thing.
My body feels so weak now.
Don't talk.
When your mouth moves,
all sorts of places start feeling weird...
Don't breathe on it.
Suck on it!
B-But!
Onii-chan, you pervert!
You're sniffing my panties and sucking on them.
I'm gonna cum! Suck me off more!
This thin thing is...
That's my pussy.
The same pussy your cock has penetrated
so many times. Mine...
Onii-chan, your movements are so perverted...
Because of that, I can't feel my legs or hips anymore!
More, do it more, okay? Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, it's good. You're so good!
Onii-chan, your tongue is drilling into me!
Right at my pussy's entrance,
something soft is wriggling and...
I-It feels so good!
Your tongue feels so good in my pussy!
It's pushing my panties inside me...
Okay, I'll read this now...
That's...
It's hitting me, it's hitting me!
It's completely going inside me!
My perverted pussy-juice soaked panties
are getting pushed in so deep!
Even if there are less customers,
doing it out in public like that?
She's even making a face like it feels good...
He's moving his tongue so hard...
I wonder if it feels like... this...
I can't take it anymore.
Onii-chan, do it for real now. Lick my raw pussy.
Kururu-chan...
My pussy is getting slimy and moving
all around because of your tongue!
Even though I shouldn't be letting out my voice like this...
They're doing that kind of thing raw?
Like this maybe?
It feels so good.
Your tongue in my pussy is...
It's getting all messed up and stirred around!
I can hear my juices stirring about!
I'm cummmg. Something good is coming!
Onii-chan, sorry.
I'm going to dirty your face further
with my perverted juices!
Your tongue's in so deep... I'm cummmg!
Don't worry, I'll clean it up...
I came with Onii-chan's tongue...
Mankitsu Happening!
Ma'am, I'm really sorr...
Oh, Otona-chan?
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Wait...
T-This isn't what you think!
Um... um...
This is all because you two were doing something like that...
Something like that? You can't mean...
I saw what you two did.
After seeing something like that, even
I would get into a weird mood!
It's my turn next, right?
Onii-chan, where are you?
Um, where can we hide?
I thought I heard him over here...
He walked this way, didn't he?
Hmm, maybe it was just my imagination.
Looks like we made it.
We pulled off the hiding maneuver quite well, huh?
Yeah, but...
But it's pretty hot in here, right?
I'm sweating already.
Your body's really getting hot, Keiichi-san.
And on top of that, this hard thing is touching me.
Sorry, my body's just honest.
Honesty is good.
I-It means that I turn you on, right?
But I'm turned on by your body too, Keiichi-san.
Oh my...
My body's going crazy from your dick, Keiichi-san!
Our bodies are so close and it's hitting me so deep!
Is this what your hard, hot dick feels inside me?
Your throbbing cock is making me feel so hot!
Otona-chan!
It's coming in so deep and pounding my insides!
Your tongue, Keiichi-san. Keiichi-san!
Let's get connected up here too!
We're connected everywhere now!
We are one, in both body and mind!
We're connected!
More! More!
Let's satisfy our desires together!
I want you to release all your built-up manly desires,
shoot it out in the deepest part of me!
Alright, you got it.
Do it...
Deep, deep inside me!
I want it all inside!
I want the thing that feels really good!
I want your hot, manly desires.
Keiichi-san, your dick is so amazing.
It's moving my insides around so much, it feels so good!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I want to cum with your dick!
Of course!
It's going so wild. My pussy's cumming!
I'm going to cum!
Let's come together!
I'm cumming!
In my stomach... there's so much...
Feels so good...
No, it's still cumming.
There's more coming in!
Alright, I'm off to work.
Cool, break a leg.
Huh, where were you, Onii-chan?
Oh, I was moving around a lot, so...
Hey, Onii-chan, let's do it some more, okay?
It was pretty slow during the day,
but it's even slower at night, huh?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
R-Rei-san?!
Rei-san...
Hm, it seems kinda tight in there, doesn't it?
Oh well, it's too hard to focus on work like this.
Looks like we'll have to do this right now, don't we?
This is great. It's got just the right thickness.
It feels as if it can never be satisfied.
There's still some left, right?
What is?
Isn't that obvious? Whatever.
Guess I'll just ask your dick.
I-If a customer happened to walk in right now...
We're behind the counter, so no one can tell.
And it doesn't look like your dick cares too much anyway.
It's lively enough to be moving around my butt, right?
What a cheeky dick.
It's rubbing against my insides!
Don't be so rough.
Rough boys get punished.
Rei-san, that feels so good!
I think my ass feels pretty good too.
I need to make sure I squeeze every last drop out.
You can squirt it all over my butt if you want.
Your dick is twitching so hard while cumming!
My butt has gotten so wet, covered with your cum!
I need to satisfy you further, don't I?
I need to please you until your balls are drained.
No, that's not it.
Even if they're empty,
if you're still hard, I might need to keep squeezing your dick with
my butt and make you shoot blanks until you're satisfied!
N-No way!
You don't sound too happy.
Your huge, thick dick is turning my butt
into its own personal plaything.
Rei-san, I came again!
It's dripping everywhere!
Please give my butt more!
I want more of your cum all over it!
U-Um, Rei-san, I just came so it's really sensitive...
That's fine, because we're going to keep
going until you're completely empty!
Come on, give me more of that
thick cum right off your balls.
It's coming! I can feel you're gonna cum
soon and cover my butt with semen!
I want it! Come on, cum!
Even after cumming so much, your dick is still so hard.
I need to keep using my butt to make
you cum until it gets used to it.
T-Then I'll just...
Take this!
W-What are you...
T-That's...
Your dick is spreading my asshole wide open!
Squeeze my dick until it's all empty!
Let me cum just like this!
It's so deep in, so big!
It's just going in and out, so deep inside!
I'm cummmg! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
In my asshole!
There's so much cum, filling me up inside...
Oh no, it feels so good...
So good! There's so much cum in me!
Thanks to you, I feel a lot better.
Well, I was the one who forced you to feel better.
I wonder if Kururu-chan, Otona-chan,
and Rei-san were all trying to cheer me up.
But if this store goes under, I'm sure
our relationships will end too.
Looks like you aren't feeling better mentally though.
Sorry.
When I think that this store might close
down for good, I start to get worried...
I see.
Well then, how about we solve that problem...
Eh?
translator: hikarucon
translator check: jimaku-danshaku
timing: v1toush, hyakupercent
typesetting: ephemere, hyakupercent
editor: punk4real
quality control: hyaku, punk4real