Because of my little "issue" with women,
I've never worked very long in a single place.
But even at the manga cafe that I just started working in,
my co-worker Rei-san and Kururu-chan
already started having sex with me.
I wonder what's going to happen to me now?
Original Animation Disc
Even new idols can be lucky perverts?
Lovey-dovey developments at the manga cafe! - Chapter
Mankitsu
Happening.
Thank you very much.
Female customers might come,
so I don't really to work long at the counter.
Whoa,
a female customer already.
Welcome.
We'll be taking your membership card.
Thank you very much.
Please, feel free to choose any seat you want.
Then, I'll be at the reclining chairs.
Oh, that would be seat 20, please.
Enjoy your stay.
I feel like I've seen her before.
Well, guess I'm just overthinking things.
This is weird.
Why doesn't it come out?
Jeez.
You...!
Miss, wait...!
Wh-What?!
M-Miss!
Are you alright?!
Oh, come on...
I know I love cola, but...
I don't really want to be totally drenched in it.
Oh, now I remember!
I've already seen her face somewhere!
She's not one of the girls affected by my lucky pervert aura!
Not one of them, and not even someone that I know!
She's Mitsuki Otona, the star idol!
Why?
Why is an idol like that in here?!
Wh-What is it?
Is there something on my fac-
Wait, just wait!
You... don't you dare tell anyone else that I'm here!
Yes, of course I won't!
You have showers here, right?
Let me use it now!
Yes, right away!
That's better...
Getting exposed there...
I'm such an idiot.
And this place happens to be my favorite cafe.
I'm worried I might not be able to come here anymore.
Oh crap.
Huh? I feel like someone was here.
Umm, hey...
Alright then, if that's how you want it.
Whoopsie.
I got him.
Maybe this far is okay now
This far? Then what?
Wh-What do you need, miss?
That's my line!
Why were you always trying to sneak away?
W-Well...
That's...
What? Is it something you really can't explain?
I understand.
I'll talk then.
Just like how I explained it to Rei-san,
I tried to be as detailed as possible as I explained
my "issue" with women to Otona-chan.
So, that means you were avoiding me because
you don't want me to be involved with that?
Yes, that would be the case.
I think exposing your identity to me was
also connected with it in some way.
Hmm...
That's quite an interesting story.
But, don't you think it's far too manga-like for it to be real?
No way...
Was that for real?
Hey, come in.
Let's talk for a bit.
Eh? But...
The shower doors are closed.
So it's okay.
O-Okay.
Then, excuse me.
I'm sorry, for getting you in trouble again.
Well, I never really thought someone like you really existed.
Th-Then...
Yeah.
I've decided to believe your story.
This "issue" that you inherently have with women,
I would have dismissed it as a trick if it was just one time,
but the last one was completely due to my own actions.
I guess I'll just have to believe in it.
I'm really sorry.
Whenever you're close to me,
what you might consider coincidences happen at a place,
timing and frequency that would make you think otherwise.
Coincidences, huh.
But, my feelings aren't just a coincidence, right?
Huh?
I think I'm in love.
...with you.
Eh?!
Well, you did keep silent about me.
Even if you did find out my identity,
I was still able to go to this cafe normally.
I just... did what any guy or cafe staff would have done.
There are many who can't do those simple things, you know.
Besides,
you even exempted the fact that I'm an idol all this time.
When I'm doing the job, you see,
lots of people get to be in contact with me.
So I just naturally would like someone I can really trust.
Oh well, just forget all about the rest.
Let's take a shower together!
O-Okay.
I got you!
I'm usually the one being chased.
But I got really pissed off and ended
up chasing someone instead.
I'm cleaning you now, okay?
The tip is starting to get harder.
This actually feels good.
I might get addicted to it.
There, there!
Otona-chan.
Keiichi-san...
My name...
I asked.
The big-breasted female cafe staff.
Oh, Rei-san.
So, umm... are you also doing lewd stuff,
with that girl too?
S-Sorry.
I guess it can't be helped with your predisposition.
This might turn into a rival's battle.
But idols have lots of other rivals, right?
Not really.
There's really just one person of the opposite gender that I like.
So, even if I have lots of rivals here,
I can still have you all for myself right at this moment.
Man, things really went in an unexpected direction.
I mean, that part of yours.
Well...
S-So it becomes this big.
I-I wonder if it can do me.
W-Well, you see...
It's my first time,
so can you take the lead from this point on?
Alright.
I'm going in.
O-Okay.
I can pull out if it hurts too much.
I just jumped a bit right at the moment when it went in.
But this is nothing.
Try moving, make yourself feel good.
I understand.
Oh wow.
This big thing is actually going in and out.
It's going in, it's really going in deeply.
Just do it more.
Fuck me more.
Let my pussy remember the taste of your dick!
It's really going all the way inside.
This is amazing.
More, just keep it up...
What's this? It feels great.
It feels really great being completely filled with a dick.
Me too, it feels good for me too.
Of course it does.
Because it feels really good for me as well.
It's just not possible for you not to feel good.
It's hitting the very depths.
My hips are being pushed up.
My body is starting to react on its own with this dick.
This is intense...!
The tip of your dick is hitting my deepest spot,
and yet it's still trying to pierce through even further.
But...
It's my first time and I think I'm already
about to go crazy while being fucked.
I'm getting completely filled inside as it fucks me.
My pussy's starting to get used to it's shape
and used to the way you fuck me.
Otona-chan, I'm about to...!
Are you about to cum?
Me too, I want to cum too.
Together. I want to do it together.
I really want to cum together.
I want my pussy and your dick to be in synch.
Okay.
Your dick is pushing even faster now.
See? It gets even stronger with each push.
And I can feel it hit inside.
It seems as if it's going to melt my insides.
There, is it about to come out?
I'm cumming.
Your dick...
It's letting out everything,
All the while trying to poke its tip through my womb.
It's pumping, and at the same time it's overflowing.
It's my first time, and yet...
Now this forbidden dick play,
has been carved on my body...
My pussy and womb...
It, it's still coming out...
It's already full,
it's already so full and yet...
You see, I really liked this cafe.
Unlike chain manga cafes,
the selection of manga here is actually quite specific.
Do you like manga?
You bet.
I love them!
That's why I always look forward to days when I just
spend my time reading here while drinking cola.
That's why,
when I realized that I needed to change
cafes because I was exposed,
I became depressed.
But!
Now I have another reason to come here.
Please get along well with me from now on.
Okay, Keiichi-san?
I'm, I'm going back to work then.
Okay, I’ll go read some manga then.
I haven't finished the one I'm reading yet.
You two, why are you...
Done already?
Can I go next now?
No, I'm next!
Besides, it was awful of you to have
forgotten your work, Onii-chan!
W-Well, I thought it'd be okay with you two around.
Hey, just wai-
They're really big...
You can still do it, right?
Do... what exactly?!
My, my, what a troublesome person.
He's my Onii-chan!
Kururu-chan, calm down!
Rei-san!
This is really...
I'm going to be crushed!
Mankitsu Happening.
Hurry.
That monstrously big dick...
Please fuck my dick-loving sex-manic asshole with it.
Rei-san...
Here.
It's opening wide, it's opening wide...
It's being opened wide as it goes deeper!
This thick dick makes me even hornier
here than when it's in my pussy.
Your dick is trying to open my asshole as it pushes hard.
More, give my asshole more...
Any other dick won't do.
It has to be your thick dick.
It's all your fault.
It's all because I'm used to the way
you've fucked me over and over.
It's at the point where I just can't get horny enough anymore,
if it's not your dick.
So please violate me with it more!
More, violate me more!
This is dick is just so good.
Rei-san, doing anal sex with your is amazing.
Your dick is even more amazing.
I never thought it could open me up wide like this.
I just love anal sex.
It makes my hips move on their own!
Try stimulating my outer butt too.
I'm starting to go even crazier as it continues to fuck my ass.
Something's welling up inside me.
Now I'm wet over here too.
My breasts are starting to become a milk dispenser again!
It's coming out, it's coming out!
I'm going to cum with both my asshole and with my breasts.
it's going to seep deep inside me, and
your dick will go even deeper inside...
This tight feeling...
The sensation as it grips me is really great!
The flesh inside gets pushed so much because of its thickness.
My insides...
I'm feeling totally ecstatic with this penetrating sensation!
No, you just can't cum inside me.
I want it to rub my ass more and more.
W-Wait...!
Wait, just wait...
I'm being squeezed.
It just continues to come out.
All my milk is being taken out!
I'm being squeezed.
I can't hold back anymore.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
P-Please...
I want you to cum it all inside my ass.
All of your sticky, creamy and thick, cum...
It's pumping in, it's coming out!
His cum is going inside me.
It's going deep inside... and I'm going to cum with it!
I'm also cumming with my suckled breasts!
That was great...
Here, we sucked all that we could for you.
We're up next, Onii-chan!
Not 'we',
it's 'my' turn.
Your cum..
So you came this much inside her.
This dick was inside her ass just a moment ago.
I-I just can't stop.
I-I just came earlier,
so it's still quite sensitive.
You can still do it, right?
Come in, Onii-chan.
Please, I want it inside my pussy, Keiichi-san.
His thing is starting to push inside.
I guess it really feels better inside me.
Hey, how about the one left here?
Left? He came lots already so maybe
there actually isn't much left.
Your dick already came but it's still this hard.
Otona-chan!
What is this?
It's getting even harder than when we were licking it.
Keiichi-san's such a perv.
So you love getting sucked by pussies more than mouths.
It's a naughty pervert dick.
More, fuck me more.
Fuck my pussy more.
I want you to fill me up with its cum.
Otona-san, it looks really pleasurable for you.
Oh wow, it really feels so good!
Your dick is totally rubbing my pussy.
It's even twitching hard inside!
Oh no, it feels too good...
It's gripping me tightly up to the very base.
No, no, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
But I want to do it more!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
Your hot stuff is seeping through inside me.
Me too!
I want to cum like how Otona-san did!
Give it to me!
I want to cum with your dick too!
Okay, here I go then.
Your dick's now inside!
It came a lot already,
and yet it's still very big.
Onii-chan, you're pushing really hard.
If you push really hard and deep inside, I'll...
It's constantly knocking inside my
most tender spot near the womb.
The sensation around my dick is starting to feel so
strange, that I can no longer hold myself back!
No way...
But whenever it tries to penetrate me entirely,
it feels so different than when I'm just
trying to play with it on my own.
I'm going crazy, my mind's going blank.
some weird sensation is starting to well up around my pussy.
Amazing...
I can even feel the rubbing sensation on me.
It can totally feel it.
Jeez, Keiichi-san you're such a...
Hey, what are you trying to do?!
Why, making it into an ass pussy of course.
The hole that's currently drenched
in fluids, and with his own cum.
No, please, no.
I'm an idol and yet my asshole's being played with like this...
I actually shouldn't do this...
Oh no, I'm really going to cum.
My ass' insides are being licked right now...
Oh no...
Your dick just feels too good inside me.
My mind's really starting to go numb
as it keeps on fucking me so much.
Even though I'm supposed to be used to it already,
and it's still trying to penetrate me harder.
No, please not that!
Don't rub my clit like that.
I'm cumming, Kururu-chan.
Lots is coming out, and lots more is being pumped in.
It's trying to pump and load all the
cum that it can inside my womb.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
Onii-chan, Onii-chan,
he's impregnating me with all of his thick cum.
Probably thanks to these three trying to quell my sexual drive,
it seems that my lucky pervert aura
effect has finally began to wane.
Even as I continue my days living with my "issue",
it looks like I won't have to quit my
current job just because of it!