Umm.
Are you really okay with this, sir?
Y-Yes.
Please go ahead.
Doctor, how is it?
How are my wife's breasts?
Very erotic, aren't they?
M-Ma-kun!
Indeed, aside from their big size and firmness,
they're on a level where you just can't
help but want to suck them.
Doctor, my wife loves sex, you see.
Th-That's... not true.
She especially likes being fucked from behind.
H-Hey!
Stop that!
Why?
It's the truth.
We have to properly tell the doctor.
Is it true that you like it from behind, ma'am?
Yes, I think.
Say it properly.
I love being fucked from behind.
S-Say it again.
I love...
being f-fucked from behind.
Doctor, did you just hear that?
Please examine her lower body parts as well!
From behind, right?
Eh?! Wh-Why?
We're about to have a child,
so we need to examine your body through and through.
It's for us to have a happy family.
Okay?
Alright.
I'll... do as you say.
So Ma-kun gets aroused when he sees
me get dirty with someone else.
D-Doctor,
how is she... down there?
It has a nice, faint, pink color.
The shape also looks very good.
You won't even think she's already long married with this.
That thin layer of fluid slowly forming around it looks also nice.
M-Ma-kun, this isn't what you think.
I-I'm not really.
Doctor, please do a palpation on her.
Sakimi?
Yes?
Where are you being touched now?
I-It should already be obvious for you!
O-On my sex organs.
Don't use such a general term.
Say it properly.
I can't, I can't!
So you can't say it when I'm around after all.
Even though you can be totally slutty toward other people.
N-No, that's not true!
I know.
Because there's someone more important to you than me now.
That's the reason why you can't say it, right?!
M-My pussy.
Huh?
It's my pussy.
He's been touching my pussy!
In what way?
Just like how a dick fucks it.
Stirring his finger deep inside me.
Inside my pussy!
Oh yes.
This is good, this is good, Sakimi!
My oh my, oh my.
Ma-kun's dick feels a lot more stiffer than usual.
He's that aroused already?
D-Doctor, please,
please continue her palpation.
I can't satisfy my wife with this dick.
I can't make her cum with it!
S-So...
I-I understand.
That's not true. That's not true!
He's the one I love the most!
Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
I love you.
I love you, Sakimi!
Me too.
I love you.
My mouth, my breasts, and my pussy.
My entire body is all yours!
Please do what you want with it.
Maybe I should give these two some privacy.
Sakimi, your pussy is sucking me harder then normal.
You're exposing yourself to the doctor which
is why you're aroused like this, right?
I have to give him what he wants.
I have to become a sluttier wife for him.
Yeah, I get really horny whenever other men watch me like this.
My pussy gets drenched.
These big and slutty nipples.
You mean you always get horny whenever
you're exposing yourself to other guys?!
Yeah.
Even the old men in our neighborhood,
they always see me exposed, and I get a good hard on with it!
D-Damn it!
Your dick that's even bigger and harder than usual,
will surely make me cum.
You're going to cum inside of me!
I can also...
I can also cum lots inside you!!
It's okay, Ma-kun.
Feel really good with it.
You can make a total mess of me!
I don't care how you love me.
Just simply love me!
I'm at my limit already.
I'm going to cum!
Ma-kun, hang in there!
Me too, I'm also about to cum!
I'm about to cum with your dick!
P-Please, let's!
Sakimi!
It's coming out.
I-I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to hold back.
N-No way.
Just a bit more.
Just a bit more and I could have cum together with him.
It's still no good even after all of this?
I wonder what happened to your husband.
Ma-kun might have known about it.
The night when the doctor snuck into my room.
He already had an appointment scheduled
for next week, though.
What are you going to do with it?
I'm really an idiot.
Why is that?
I never thought that he'd been worried about it all this time.
Did you not like how he acted yesterday?
Nope.
If that's how he really is,
then I'm prepared to accept it.
You do love him from the bottom of your heart.
Oopsie.
It's this late already?
I have to go now.
What?
I'm sorry, but could you please use the window
again later when you're about to go home?
Just leave the door locked as it is.
H-Hey, Doctor!
Jeez.
This is the order for Satou-san in the second district.
And get the bowls from Fukuda-san as well!
Got it!
Umm, I'm really sorry.
For asking you to help me with the delivery like this, Doctor.
My brother is always so bossy.
Don't worry.
So long as many know how delicious your brother's ramen is,
I'm sure customers will just keep pouring in.
Hey, those might turn all soggy if you don't hurry up!
Alright!
Umm.
Yes?
Why are you so kind to us?
We can't even pay you enough for your work.
I just want to keep seeing your smile.
Your smile, the gentle and happy kind.
M-Me?
If it's for your smile,
I can keep working hard.
Now then, I shall take my leave.
I can do this.
I can really do this!
If I keep going like this, Yukina-san will soon.
This is the only way I can repay you.
I'll do my best.
I-It feels tender.
Doctor, your dick is very big.
I want you to stir my pussy with it.
I want it to penetrate me.
I want my clit's tip to be rubbed.
I want this big and thick dick to make a complete mess of me!
Yu-Yukina-san.
Doctor, I can't wait anymore!
I'll do it already, okay?
Your dick is now about to go inside my slutty pussy.
Sensei, are you looking at this?
Your dick is going very deep inside me.
Y-Yes.
Doctor, I feel really happy.
I'm going to move my hips with the vigor
of a true lover just this one time.
Y-Your breasts are jiggling hard, and it looks very lovely.
Please,
please look at them more.
Look at my slutty breasts more and more!
Yu-Yukina-san.
Your dick is deep inside me, Doctor.
It's stiff, and thick,
and it feels very good!
Y-Yes, I can feel it rubbing inside.
Amazing,
amazing.
Not too deep.
I'm about to become consumed
by ecstasy, even more than you!
Are you about to cum?
Yes.
My pussy is now so aroused, it's about to cum.
We're lovers right now, so I want for us to cum together.
I can't hold back anymore!
Are you alright with me cumming inside?
Please do.
Cum inside me raw.
Please pump your cum into my deepest part!
Doctor, I'm cumming!
Cum, cum.
Please give me your cum!
Oh yes.
This feels great!
I'm cumming!
It's hot.
Doctor, I feel happy.
Yes, hello?
U-Umm, Doctor?
My, what's wrong, ma'am?
If I recall, your husband had an appointment scheduled today.
Y-Yeah.
About that.
I was thinking of cancelling it.
Oh, is something wrong?
I feel like I'm about to get sick.
My oh my, that's not good.
Shall I make a house call?
N-No, it's alright.
It's really not serious.
B-Besides, Ma-kun is here.
I understand.
Get well soon then.
Th-Thanks.
I'm going to call again later.
She seemed strange earlier.
Is she really that sick?
Miss,
suck this one, too.
It stinks!
That's what's great about it.
Stop.
Please stop it already!
Don't do it to my wife anymore.
What are you saying?
You're the one who invited us here, right?
You asked us to take real good "care" of her with you.
Am I wrong?
Th-That's...
That's because I thought that if I tried,
my wife and I could become a lot more aroused than usual.
That's why!
Mister, you're the type to get a boner when
somebody else is fucking your wife, right?
You're getting quite lively down there
already as we violate her, see?
Ma-kun's dick is getting big again.
It's getting aroused while I get fucked.
You're wrong.
That's not true.
I simply get aroused when I see my wife get aroused.
Because I'm simply unable to satisfy her.
So I...
Which is why,
we're going to pleasure your wife for you.
Just sit still and watch over her.
This can't be.
I never intended for this to happen.
I really... I really, really love my wife!
Why did this have to!
M-Ma-kun!
All of the men around the neighborhood have had
their eyes on your wife for quite some time now.
Haven't you noticed?
Sa-Sakimi, Sakimi!
Our dicks are a lot better suited for your tastes
than your husband's pathetic dick, right?
P-Please don't.
Please don't badmouth how Ma-kun does it!
But you see.
You yourself already knew that it
would turn out this way, right?
Were you actually looking forward to this?
So long as Ma-kun wishes for it, I'll do anything.
But, if it's not the case,
I'll never take pleasure in anything that you do!
Acting stubborn, eh. How cute.
Then we'll just have to make you moan with our dicks.
Loudly and vigorously.
Sakimi,
sorry, I'm really sorry.
I-I never wanted things to turn out like this.
M-Ma-kun, please don't look at how shameful I am right now.
Please look away!
Your pussy is trying to suck me in, Miss.
Are you getting aroused as he watches you?
No way, that can't be!
I'm not aroused, not when I'm being forcefully raped like this!
Now now,
make me feel good here, too.
Using your mouth pussy, of course.
No way, his dick getting even bigger.
It's completely different from Ma-kun's!
It's stiff, thick,
it's like the doctor's!
Your nipples are even getting this hard now.
It really feels good, right, Miss?
Wh-What should I do?
I shouldn't feel aroused from this, and yet.
Oh no.
I-I can't stop my body from getting horny!
I beg of you.
Let me rest, even just a little.
Even just a little, please!
Giving in already? Can't be helped then.
I'm going to use this then.
No, not there!
Sakimi!
No, don't.
Stop.
My, ass... my asshole!
Oh, so this is your first time in here?
It feels really tight, Miss.
It hurts, it hurts!
No, please don't move too much.
Pull it out, pull it out!
This is amazing.
Both holes look like they're starting to squeeze very tightly.
My asshole's insides are being stirred like crazy!
I'm losing it.
I-I'm going crazy!
It's all right, just cum as hard as you want to.
No, no!
This can't be, I don't want to cum.
I don't want to cum in front of Ma-kun!
Oh no, I'm really sorry, forgive me!
Sakimi, Sakimi!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
This can't be.
Y-You've had enough already, right?
Please be done with it already.
What are you saying? We're just getting started.
If it's about time, don't worry, we'll be at it until dawn.
N-No, way.
It's not over yet!
Fake make-up punch!
Fake eyelashes kick!
D-Doctor?!
I won't forgive anyone who abuses his wife!
Here,
and here.
Wh-What just.
What did you make us swallow?
You guy sure know how to overreact.
It's just a dose of some super-effective,
fast-acting sleeping pills.
Sakimi, I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
Ma-kun.
Well then.
If you'll excuse me, I'll be taking my leave.
Our out-of-clinic counseling ends here.
Doctor, thank you for coming.
No, I just happened to have some time to kill.
I see then.
After that incident,
I decided to rejuvenate myself by going
to Yukina's place again, but...
Tenant's Wanted
Wh-What happened?!
I've only just heard about it,
but the shop hasn't been doing well lately,
and her husband got into debt on some shady deal.
H-Husband?
Whose?
Whose? Yukina-chan's husband, of course.
The owner of this shop.
B-But!
But Yukina always referred to him as "Onii-chan"!
I heard they were childhood friends, and were raised as siblings.
But they're officially married, you know.
N-No way.
You didn't know?
Why didn't she saying anything about
such an important thing to me?
This is also the first time I've heard about the debt!
Maybe she just couldn't.
She became fond of you.
That's why she never told you.
I also think she didn't want you to get involved,
so she also never spoke about the debt.
Sh-She didn't have to hold secrets from me!
You cry like a baby.
Yeah, I'm just a kid after all.
Hey, Doctor,
are you available tomorrow night?
There will be a test of courage event at the city park festival.
Care to join?
Wait, what does that?
Take it as your consolation prize.
You have some time on your hands, right?
Well, yes.
Tomorrow then.
I'll be picking you up at the second story window.
She seems to be strangely happy for some reason.
I wonder what happened.