Madam, what happened to that
hard place on your breast?
Oh, it’s gradually getting smaller.
Just like you said it would, Doctor.
I'm glad to hear that!
Just to be sure, you should show me your breasts again.
EH?!
B-But... today my husband is with me.
I want to show the treatment to your husband as well.
If he knows what to do, he'll definitely
notice if something changes in the future.
Yes, I understand.
Sir, are you ready?
I-I'll leave her in your care.
Sakimi, does it hurt?
I'm completely fine.
Your husband must be proud.
A-About what?
About the boobs, of course.
Great size and great shape
You don't see that every day.
D-Doctor? Saying something like that at a time like this...
The bra is in the way...
Let's take ft off, madam.
N-No way...
If you're going to have a baby, we should confirm
that there's nothing wrong with your body.
This is all part of the treatment, madam.
I'm sorry... I understand.
Doctor, please...
No matter how many times I see them, they're amazing.
U... Umm... Doctor?
D-Don't keep staring at her. Start the treatment already.
I beg your pardon.
These tender breasts...
Every night, your husband must be...
By the way, I have good news!
There was no problem wit your husband's sperm.
Eh? Is that true?!
T-thank goodness!
All that's left is for madam to receive it...
With her body!
Work...This will work!
If it's like this, it will work!
Um, Doctor?!
That... That place is a little...
It's an important part of this treatment.
Please bear with it, even if it's difficult, ok?
Yes...
Noo...
Doctor!
Next, I'll touch deep inside.
P-Please don't, that place is...!
Is this the place?
Doctor, don't! You can't!
That place is... Really, don't!
Don't! Dooon't!
Ever time I touch you here, your voice becomes so sweet!
B-But... It's just that, Um...
That Place is...! No!
Congratulations!
This is the entrance to your womb.
Wh-what?
If you want to become pregnant, this is very important.
Let's inspect it thoroughly!
Doctor, you can't!
Fast...You're doing it faster than before!
If you keep doing that, I'll... again!!
Again?
Again... Again... Something bad will happen!
Nooo!
This is a hospital, so you don't have to worry about that.
No! Don't! You really can't!
Doctor!!
So deep... not good...
Not good?
I... I don't really know...
I don't know, myself!
S-Something...
Something is...
No, I'm there!
This is a splendid feat indeed!
I've had enough. I don't want this any more.
I-I don't want this...
Just like that...
Making madam fall for me is a matter of time!
U-Umm... Doctor?
Hm? Well then, let's proceed to milking.
H-Hey... Do it a little more gently.
I-I'm fine, It just surprised me a bit.
This is the important part. Watch carefully, okay?
C-Can't you see it's hurting her?
It doesn't look that way to me at all.
S-Sakimi!
I-I'm fine...
Listen, okay?
Just like this, make the breast swell
until the milk gathers at the top...
And then pinch the tip like this...
Here, sir, are you watching carefully?
D-Doctor!
Wha-What do you think you're doing to my wife!?
Nooo!
You bastard!
You've been getting hard off of this, haven't you?
I'll kill you!
It hurts!
They-They're gonna break!
You pervert doctor!
I'll make sure you can never use them again!
M-Ma-kun! Don't!
Maro no Kanja wa Gatenkei
Sakimi Charapter
It hurts!
Ahh, it hurts, it hurts!
I think I went a little too far...
Pardon the intrusion...
What? Why from the window?
Well the door downstairs is locked...
And even when I called, nobody answered.
Ta-Tamemuchi?
Her spirit seems so different for some reason...
Thanks for not telling the police.
I'm talking about Ma-kun,
You didn't tell anyone in the hospital either, right?
That was... well, as an underground doctor
I would have a lot of problems if I did...
To repay you, I will look after you until your injuries heal.
So can you please forgive Ma-kun?
At my morning and lunch break...
And after work, I will come here...
Do the cleaning, laundry, food, and all the housework!
Eeeh?!
W-What the hell is this?!
This is like a slutty nurse outfit or something!
I-I'm sorry.
These are the closest things to women's
housework clothes that I have.
Can't help it, then.
Well, whatever.
You can't do anything weird with your hands like that anyway.
After that day, she really came here every day...
And did everything for me.
Blow on it.
Here, aaah.
Even though it's homemade,
it tastes pretty good, doesn't it?
Huh? Well...
How is it?
Are the angle and the direction all right like this?
P-Please raise it up a little.
It's coming out!
It's fine. I'm all right, so you can let it out!
You definitely can't look back, okay?
The clothes would get wet, so I had to do this!
I understand.
Don't make weird noises!
Just stay still, It'll be over soon.
I-It's going to cum on its own!
H-Hey!
Don't get big!
Don't touch my dick like that!
You always make it the other
person's fault, just like that!
Wai-Wait!
That's too rough!
That's how the warm time passed in the blink of an eye...
It really passed by in the blink of an eye.
They feel a lot better!
Your cast just came off, so...
Should I come back next week?
No, I appreciate your feelings, but...
Please return to your husband's place.
Okay. I get it.
I really have been in your care!
The towel is hanging outside the dressing room, okay?
Okay.
The socks are in the top drawer.
Underwear and shirts are in the one below it.
And the scarves and other accessories are in...
Everything is written in the memo.
I'll be fine.
Is that so? That's right, isn't it?
Yes.
Well then, I'll be going, okay?
Bye, bye!
Goodbye!
I wonder what this feeling is?
Absence?
That's not it. It isn't emptiness.
It's nostalgia!
Its so nostalgic, it's painful!
The woman who always came in and out from the window.
The woman who would take me to the toilet
no matter how many times I messed up.
The woman who made me rolled cabbage and oden.
Cleaning this floor, bending over to clean this part.
Getting mad, getting troubled, laughing...
Is this love?
Have I fallen in love?
It doesn't matter if she is someone's wife!
I can't deny my feelings!
In that case, there is only one thing to do!
Are you awake?
D-Doctor!?
I've fallen for you!
I love you, madam!
Idiot! Stop!
Stop it!
Even if you already love someone,
I can't hold back these feelings!
W-Why? Such a...
I don't care if you call the police!
H-Hey! Don't suck on it!
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
I... I hate you...
I hate the Doctor who does stuff like this!
I really hate you!
Is it my imagination?
Your nipples seem to be standing up.
Are you feeling it?
Th-That's a lie!
Well then, let me confirm it.
Wha-What are you doing?
Idiot... Idiot... Idiot!
This is quite something!
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
Its not because you did something strange to me!
St-Stop! Stop moving it around!
No-No way!
You're this wet even though you're not feeling good?
B-But, that's because...you've been touching me there.
That's why...
Are you sexually frustrated?
I'm a bad woman, right?
You can laugh if you want...
You are so sensual...
Huh?!
You are too beautiful to be sexually frustrated...
I'm falling for you more and more!
I-It's dirty, Idiot!
Don't! Doon't!
You can't help but crave sex, right?
That's why you got all wet!
You're wrong!
Don't misinterpret things like that!
I will fulfill madam's wishes.
That... No! Don't!
It's coming!
It's all gonna come out!
I-Idiot!!
No more!
Where are you going?
Le-Let go!
I said let me go!
I can't do that.
S-Stop it!
You're not even wearing a condom!
You can't, you definitely can't!
You're tighter than I thought you'd be.
S-Stop... pull it out!
I beg you, pull it out!
Don't move!
No way! Something like this!
It's so much bigger than Ma-kun's!
I-If you keep doing like this, I'll...
Again!!
Again? Are you cumming?
To-to feel good from someone
other than M-Ma-kun...
Something like that... Do-Don't!
Madam, is this your G-spot?
N-Noo!
What is this? D-Don't!
Stop! Stop moving!
Bad, this is bad!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming soon!
It's all right. Please cum!
I don't want this anymore!
Ma-kun, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
It's still, still coming...
It's... It's still coming inside of me!
Yes, the real thing starts now!
I-I beg you, please don't move right now!
M-My stomach is going numb!
It's not good! My body is going crazy!
You're feeling good with your husband
sleeping over there, aren't you?
I am! I am!
I feel good with Ma-kun lying over there!
What do you think about yourself?
Lewd....
I am lewd!
My heart and my body, all of it...
Madam, break out of your shell more!
Expose your true self!
Show me your true nature!
Do-Don't, don't do it anymore!
It's going deeper than before!
It's hitting me so deep inside!
It's because you keep having dull, everyday sex!
This catches you by surprise!
N-No... I don't know!
I don't know!
You wanted your husband to fuck you
like an animal at least once, right?
At-At least once... like this...
I wanted... Ma-kun to do me
from behind like an animal!
I wanted him to fuck me up!
To look for a way to feel good together...
I wanted us to find ways for both of us to be happy!
I wanted us to make love together!
Come on...harder!
I actually... I wanted to do it a little longer...
Sex... I want to have sex!
Well said!
Well then, let me give you a reward.
What?
The pent up semen from a month...
Please accept my love!
I... I don't need it!
Idiot! Don't, don't!
You're not wearing anything!
You're not wearing a condom...
Nooo!!
Take it out!
Doctor! Take it out!
No!
N-No, it's still coming out...
It's coming inside.
Stop it...
Please stop this!
Why did it become like this?
Madam, you are the best.
A-As I thought, I'm lewd...
E-Even though Ma-kun is lying beside me...
I got all wet and I really felt good.
In front of Ma-kun, the Doctor made me cum!
Yamiisha Hikomaru, 45.
A natural, I dare say.
After spending a night of great work...
I'm in great spirits today!
I'm just an earnest, hard working man.
Great taste
Ramen
Futoshiyuki Restaurant
And I already have a new target in sight.
W-Welcome!
The poster girl of this shop is Ishihara Yukina-san.
She is 22 years old.
Onee-san, I spilled some water, can you wipe it off?
Y-Yes!
She is a busty beauty who wears this sort of
embarrassing outfit to raise the popularity of the shop.
Oh! I dropped the pepper shaker!
Onee-san, I'm sorry but could you pick it up for me?
Y-Yes!
That classic appearance! She stole my heart!
Honey!
I'm gonna fall for you baby!
I won't waste the happiness Madam taught me!
I will definitely grasp eternal warmth
With these hands of mine!
Hohohoho
You came back earl today, didn't you?
Y-Yes.
Just by coincidence!
No! There's no way I can tell him something like that happened!
Ma-kun would definitely kill the Doctor this time.
Sakimi, could you schedule another
appointment with Dr. Hikomaru?
Eh? W-Why?
The counseling was interrupted
halfway through because of me, right?
B-But... That's...
I need to apologize for injuring him,
And I want to make things right again.
Is that a no?
We-Well, it's not a no, but...
That's a relief. So we can continue
where we left off last time.
M-Ma-kun... What happened...?
You're acting weird...