Mrs. Wife,
could you tell me how the stone-like
object in your breasts feels now?
Well...
It feels like it became smaller during my period.
It was as you've told us, Doctor.
That is good then.
How about we do a quick check up of it from my side?
B-But, my husband is here right now with me.
I also want to show it to your husband in person!
So that he'll be able to do something in the
event that something happens to it!
O-Okay, I understand.
Mr. Husband, are you prepared for this?
P-Please do.
Does it hurt near the tip?
No, it doesn't.
You must be proud of these, Mr. Husband.
P-Proud of what?
Why, of your wife's breasts of course.
Apart from their size and shape,
there's only a selected few who have these kinds of breasts.
Se-Sensei, why are you talking about that at this time...?
I see that the bra is getting in the way.
Let's remove it now.
Eh? B-But...
If you're about to consult about 'that,'
it's imperative that we check if there is any problem with it.
This is just a mere palpation, Mrs.
I'm sorry... I understand.
Doctor, p-please go ahead.
Oh, I see!
They look very wonderful no matter
how many times I look at them.
U-Umm...
Sensei...?
S-Stop staring already and start your 'palpation'!
Oh, how rude of me.
Your husband must always get excited
every night with these breasts.
Oh yes, I have some more good news.
There was no problem with your semen examination.
Eh? Really?
Th-That's great.
It's all now up to
your wife's body at this point!
This will do.
This will really do!
If I continue with this...
Umm, Doctor...
That's... that's...!
This is a very important part of palpation.
Please endure it a bit even if it hurts.
Okay.
Oh no...
Doctor...!
I'm going to touch your insides a bit.
Don't, not there...!
Do you mean here?
Doctor, please, please don't!
No, please, you really mustn't!
Don't. Don't, don't!
Your voice sounds sweeter whenever
I try to dig through this spot.
B-But...
Something... on that spot...
Congratulations.
This ring around here is probably the spot
where your womb plans to make a delivery.
Eh? Wh-What?
It is a very important issue if you plan on giving birth soon.
So let us examine it carefully.
Doctor, don't!
This is fast.
Even faster than before!
If this continues...
Again, I'll...
Again?
I'll... I'll...
It'll be bad for me!
Oh no...!
This is a hospital, so everything is just fine.
No, really, you mustn't...!
Doctor!
It's not safe inside...
Not safe?
I-I don't know what's happening inside me anymore.
I can't understand it myself.
So, something...
Something is...
No, I'm about to...!
Oh. this is yet another secretion I must examine!
No, no more...
Really, no more, please...
I-I don't want this anymore...
Now, taking her down will be just a matter of time.
U-Umm... doctor?
Oh? Then next is...
We'll examine how well they'll be able to lactate.
H-Hey...
Can you please be a bit gentler?
I'm, I'm okay.
I was just a bit startled.
This is the part where we focus.
So, please watch it carefully.
H-Hey, my wife looks like she's hurt from it!
That's not really what I hear however.
Sa-Sakimi!
I-I'm fine.
Listen carefully.
You focus all the potential secretions of the
breast to one point using this method.
Lastly, you do this to the very tip.
Now, now, Mr. Husband, are you even watching?
Doctor...!
What do you think...
... you are doing to my wife?!
N-No...
I bet you already got a boner from all of this a while ago!
I'll kill you!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
They're going to break!
You perverted doctor!
I'm going to make sure you don't use those hands anymore!
Ma-Ma-kun... don't!
Maro's
Patient
is aBlue-Collar
Employee
Sakimi Charapter
How mortifying.
Mortifying, mortifying, mortifying.
I really overdid that.
Oopsie.
I'm coming in!
Wh-Why through the window?
It's locked down there.
You wouldn't even come out even after I called you.
What in the...
She feels very different from before.
Thanks for not calling in the cops on him before.
You never told anyone in the hospital
about what Ma-kun did, right?
Well, that was just because as an unregistered
doctor, I just can't disclose much to others.
As thanks and apology for that,
I'll take care of you until your injury completely heals.
Then, can you please forgive Ma-kun after that?
During day or noon,
I'll drop by here after work.
and do cleaning, laundry, and even cook a meal.
I'll do all the housework that needs to be done!
Wh-What the heck is this?
It looks like a dress that belongs in a brothel!
M-My apologies.
I really only have this kind of clothing for women here.
It can't be helped then.
Oh well.
You probably can't do anything weird
with those hands anyway.
After that, she really did come day after day.
Taking care of every single thing for me.
Blow on it.
Here, say 'ah'.
Quite tasty despite being a quick meal, right?
Eh? Well...
W-Well? Is this angle and direction, okay?
P-Please raise it up a little.
I'm about to pee!
O-Okay, it's alright, so just pee.
You absolutely mustn't turn back, okay?
I've got no choice because my clothes are going to become wet.
I understand.
Hey, don't let out a weird voice!
Just stay still and this will be over with soon.
I-I think it's about to come out.
H-Hey!
You can't get a boner now!
Please talk to my dick directly then.
Jeez, you just easily blame it on others.
H-Hey!
You're rubbing too hard!
And so, these warm days passed by very quickly.
Like, really quickly...
This feels great!
The cast has just been removed,
so should I still come for at least a week?
No, but I'm glad for your offer.
Please return now.
Return to where your beloved is.
Okay, got it then.
Thank you very much for taking care of me.
The towels are located in the undressing room, okay?
Okay.
The shoes are in the uppermost part of the cabinet.
Shirts and underwear are in the next one below.
The mufflers and other extra stuff are...
They're all written on this memo,
so I'll be fine.
Okay, I see then.
Of course it is.
Yes.
I'll be going then.
Bye-bye.
See you.
I wonder what this feeling is?
Emptiness?
No.
I don't feel empty.
It feels nostalgic.
And the nostalgia makes me want it.
She, who has been coming in through the window every day.
She, who always assisted me m the toilet
no matter how many times I mess up.
She, who used to make oden and cabbage rolls.
The way she walked past this part
of the floor and crouched down,
the way she get angry,
got confused,
became happy over something.
This may be love.
I think I'm in love!
I don't care if she's married or not,
I just can't ignore these feelings anymore!
Then, there is just one way to go.
Are you awake now?
D-Doctor!
I'm now madly in love with you.
I love you very much, Mrs.
You idiot, stop!
Stop, stop!
Even if this remains unrequited,
I just can't hold back from expressing my feelings!
Wh-Why?
No way...
I'm prepared to be taken by the authorities if that's how it goes.
H-Hey, stop sucking it!
Oh yes..
I really love you... from the bottom of my heart!
I don't!
I don't like how you do these things.
I really, really hate it!
Does it feel good?
Your nipples seem to be getting a hard on.
Are you feeling horny?
Th-That's not true!
Then, let's find out if it is.
Wh-What are you doing?
Idiot, idiot!
Idiot!
Oh! This is really something!
D-Don't be mistaken!
I'm not feeling weird or anything.
Stop! Stop fondling my body like that!
N-No way...
Not feeling weird...
Even if you're already drenched down here?
Th-That's because...
W-We haven't been doing it lately.
So...
Sexually frustrated then?
I'm such a helpless woman, right?
Just go ahead and laugh.
H-How erotic!
It looks so beautiful...
and yet you're sexually frustrated?
Now I'm starting to love you even more!
That tickles!
I-Idiot!
No, stop!
You badly wanted sex but you can't, so it's this wet!
That's not it!
Don't just twist my words like that!
I shall grant your wish then, Mrs.
No, not there...!
It's coming out, it's all going to come out!
I-Idiot! Stop this already!
Where do you think you're going?
Let me go.
Let me go!
I can't just let you get away now.
S-Stop!
You're not even wearing a condom!
You can't, you just can't!
It's quite tighter than I imagined.
S-Stop, pull it out.
I beg you to pull it out!
Stop moving!
No way,
this can't be, it's a lot bigger than Ma-kun's...
A lot bigger...!
I-If it continues fucking me, I'll... I'll cum again...
Are you going to cum again?
F-For me to get horny with something
else other than Ma-kun's...
Th-That, that just can't be!
Are you feeling it now, Mrs.?
No, no...
What is this?
No...
Stop, just stop moving!
This is not good.
This is really not good.
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum soon!
It's okay.
Just cum.
No, no more, please...
Ma-kun, I'm really sorry!
Sorry, I'm really sorry!
I-It's still continuing...
It's still, it's still...
Continuing...
Yes, because we're just getting started.
Please...
Stop moving for a bit.
My insides are feeling tingly.
Oh no...
My body is starting to lose it.
You're feeling horny because he's just beside you, right?
I-I just did.
I'm feeling really aroused with him just beside us.
What do you think of yourself because of that?
That I'm a slut.
I'm a slut.
Both my mind and my body are...
Mrs., let go of your inhibitions,
and completely expose yourself.
Please show me the real you!
N-No, please stop fucking me already.
It's going even deeper than before.
It's hitting me very deeply.
It's because you always have sex
in the same missionary position.
So you're really going to be surprised with this.
N-No way... that can't be...
That's not true!
In truth, you really wanted at least once,
for your husband to treat you completely like an animal, right?
J-Just once,
I wanted Ma-kun to,
take me from behind and fuck me this way!
And then, we'll find even better positions,
and learn many more ways to be happier.
Making love all the way!
Now, say it more! Speak your mind!
I-I actually wanted to do it more.
I-I want to have sex!
Well said.
Then I shall give you a reward before we finish.
What?
Cum that I built up in one month.
Take every last drop of my love!
I-I don't need it!
Idiot! Don't... stop!
You're not wearing protection!
You're not wearing a condom!
No!
Pull it out.
Pull it all out, please!
Stop!
No, it's still pumping inside.
It's still letting it out.
Stop it...
Stop cumming inside me.
Why did things have to turn out like this?
You truly are the best, Mrs.
I-I really am a slut.
Ma-kun is right here beside us,
and yet I got all wet... all aroused...
I cummed with the doctor while he was here.
I'm Hiko Maro, a 45-year old unregistered doctor.
A naturally born dunce.
Due to the events of one particular night,
I'm in optimal condition now!
The only thing left now is a hearty bowl of pork.
And I already have my next target.
Welcome.
The shop's promoter,
Ishihara Yukma.
She's 22 years old.
Miss, can you wipe the spilled water over here?
C-Coming!
In order to attract more customers, she was told to
wear such an outfit wile doing these 'chores.'
She's a bombastic, busty beauty.
Oops, I dropped the pepper.
Sorry, but would you be so kind as to pick it up?
O-Okay!
Such a lovely pose.
It's really made an impact on me, honey!
I'm almost about to go crazy with you, baby!
In order not to waste the happines given to me by her,
I should grasp a portion of her warmth.
You seem to have come home early today.
Y-Yeah, I just happened to leave early.
Oh no, I can't just tell him what he did to me.
He's probably going to kill the doctor for real this time!
Sakimi,
should we set an appointment at Hiko Maro's clinic again?
Eh? Wh-Why?
The counseling ended abruptly because of me, right?
B-But that's...
I want to properly find out about his
injuries, and to politely thank him.
Can't we?
W-Well, it's not that we can't, but...
Good then.
Now I can continue what I started before.
I-I wonder what's wrong with Ma-kun.
You're acting weird.