HENTAIHAVEN.ORG
Exclusive Release
Sir, are you sure about this?
Yes, I leave it all up to you.
Sensei, how is it?
Suma's boobs, I mean.
They're quite salacious, aren't they?
M-Maa-kun!
Yes, their size is just right and they feel great to touch.
They are of such fine quality, you
just want to keep feeling them.
Sensei, Suma really loves to have sex!
That's not true!
It seems she loves it from the back.
Hey! Stop it!
Why? It's the truth, isn't it?
You're with a doctor after all, you've
got to tell him everything.
Madam, do you like it from the back?
I... might do.
Tell him clearly.
I like it from behind.
Once more...
From the back...l love sex when I'm
getting rammed from the back.
Sensei, did you hear that?
Please examine her lower body as well...
From the back.
Eh?!
Wh-Why?!
We're going to have children down the road.
Reason we need to have him check every part of you...
It's for the sake of creating a healthy family together.
Right?
I get it. I'll do as Maa-kun says.
Maa-kun is getting excited from seeing
someone else doing lewd things to me.
Sensei, how does Suma's special place look down there?
The color is that of a light cherry blossom.
And judging by its shape, she doesn't
seem like someone's wife at all.
And the fact that it's slightly wet is splendid indeed.
Maa-kun, that's not true!
I'm...I'm not really...
Sensei, please use your forefinger.
Aah, Sakimi...?
Y-Yes?!
Where are you being touched?
Asking something like that...Maa-kun,
even though you know it!
I-It's my genitals.
You can't say that halfheartedly.
Say it clearly.
Th-That's impossible!
Just as I thought...it's only impossible
in front of me huh.
Even though you're showing off your
lewd figure to someone else.
Th-That's not true!
I get it already.
Sakimi has already got someone more important.
That's why you can't say it to me, isn't it!
Pu... ssy!
Eh?
I'm... in my pussy...
I'm being touched in my pussy!
H-How?
I-It's like being teased by a penis. I'm getting hot and
bothered by this finger that's deep inside of my...
My... pussy!
Eh?!
Sakimi! Sakimi! Sakimi! Sakimi!
Sakimi!
Maa-kun's penis is a lot harder than usual.
Is he really that excited?
S Sensei...keeep fingering...
Please keep fingering her!
My dick alone isn't enough to satisfy Suma.
I can't make her cum, th-that's why!
I understand.
That's not true, that's not true at all!
I love Maa-kun more than anyone else!
Then why? Why did it have to come to this?
I love you, I love you Sakimi!
I.. Love you as well, I really do!
My mouth, tits, pussy It's all...
It's all for you, Maa-kun!
You can use me as you like.
Wouldn't it be fine to leave this to the two of you now?
Sakimi, your pussy is gripping me harder than usual.
You're getting excited from being
watched by Sensei, right?
I have to live up to Maa-kuns expectations.
I need to become a lewder wife.
That's right, I get real excited when someone's watching.
My pussy's soaking wet!
You get turned on when someone else sees
these h-huge boobs of yours, don't you!
When the old men in the neighborhood
keep staring at me...
My nipples get all hot and erect!
D-Damn!
I'll probably get raped by a thicker
and bigger dick than Maa-kun's!
They'll ejaculate in my pussy!
I can...l can do that as well!
It's fine Maa-kun, get more excited.
It's alright to mess me up!
No matter how you do it,
I just want to be loved by you.
I can't take it anymore, I'm gonna cum!
Ma-Maa-kun, give it your all!
I... I'm about to cum as well!
I'm about to cum with Maa-kun's dick so...
P-Please! Together!
Sakimi!!
It's coming...!
S-Sorry, I couldn't hold back.
No way, this can't be...
Just a little more, just a little while longer...and
we would've been able to cum together.
It's still isn't good though I went this far?
Maro no Kanja wa Gatenkei
Sakimi Charapter 2
What happened to your husband?
It's possible Maa-kun noticed...
When you raped me that night.
Your husband has already booked counseling
sessions for the next few weeks so...
What are you gonna do?
I really am an idiot.
Why do you say that?
I never noticed Maa-kun had those sorts of urges.
Do you hate the way your husband was the other day?
I don't hate it.
If that is the real Maa-kun, then
I plan on accepting all of him.
You sure love your husband from
the bottom of your heart.
Oh! It's pretty late! I should get going now.
What is it?
I'm really sorry, but I need you to go
out through the window again.
You can leave the key in its place.
W-Wait, Sensei!
Geez...
When you give that to Satou-san at 2nd street, make
sure you hand out a bowl to Fukuda-san as well.
Got it.
Um...I'm really sorry for asking you to help.
Onnii-chan is always so rude.
No no, I'm sure there will be plenty of customers once
people get a taste of Onni-san's delicious ramen.
Hey! They're gonna get soggy if you
don't hurry up and get it done!
I...I understand!
Umm...
Yes?
Why is Sensei being so nice to us?
Since this is a part time job, we don't even pay well.
I just want to see you smile.
Eh?
A wide one, from Yukina-san.
M-Me?
If it's for the sake of seeing you smile,
then I'll work as hard as I need to.
Well then, I'll be on my way.
This is gonna work...this is gonna work just fine.
If this keeps up, then I'm sure Yukina-san will...
This is all I can do to thank you, Sensei.
I'll do my best today.
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho!
It's so soft...
Sensei's dick is really big. I'd love
to have this stir up my pussy.
I want you to ram it in Yukina's pussy.
I want this dick to rub against my clit.
I want you to mess me up with this fat dick of yours!
Yu-Yukina-san!
Sensei, I can't wait any longer.
I'm going to put it in, okay?
Sensei's dick is inside my dirty pussy.
Se-Sensei, are you watching?
Your cock is hitting the very depths of my pussy!
Y-Yes!
Sensei, I'm really happy.
I'm ready to become Sensei's lover
and live out my life with you!
Your boobs are bouncing around like
there's no tomorrow, it's beautiful!
More! Please keep looking at them!
My dirty boobs! More! More!
Yu-Yukma-san!
Se-Sensei's dick...It's going in so deep!
It's hard and thick, feels just right!
Y-Yes, it's hitting the spot!
Amazing, amazing!
I can't! I can't take it in any deeper!
I'm going to feel good before you, Sense!
Are you going to cum?
Y-Yes...my pussy is almost at its limit.
I-I'm going to cum!
Were lovers so we should probably cum together but...
I can't hold on much longer!
Is it okay if it comes inside you?
Please do...! Just Ilk this! Shoot
it all out deep inside my pussy!
S-Sensei, I'm cumming!
Let it out! Give me all of your semen!
It feels so good! Really good!
I-I'm cumming!
So hot...Sensei, I'm so happy...
Yes? Hello?
Umm Sensei?
Oh madam, what seems to be the matter?
We were supposed to have a counseling
session if I remember right.
Y-Yeah, it's about that you see.
I was thinking if We could c-cancel it.
Oh? Did something happen?
I was just feeling under the weather-
Oh my, that's not good. Should I pay you a visit then?
N-No, it's alright. It's not that bad.
Maa-kun is with me as well!
Understood, well then...please take care of yourself okay?
Th-Thank you, I'll contact you again...
For some reason her voice sounded strange.
Is her health really that bad?
Madam, eat this as well.
It stinks!
That's the good bit.
Stop it! Please stop it already!
Don't do something like this to my Suma!
What are you saying?
It was you who invited us over here, right?
You said you wanted us to make love to your wife.
Am I wrong?
Th-that's...
Well... if you did that, I thought Suma and
I could get more excitement than usual.
Th-That's why!
Mister...you're the type who gets turned
on by netorare, aren't you?
Even though your wife is being raped
in front of you, you're still rock hard.
Maa-kun's penis is becoming big again?
He's getting aroused from seeing me being forced into this.
W-wrong, you're wrong!
I just love the sight of Suma feeling good!
Cause I couldn't make her feel that way...
I couldn't...
That's why we're going to make your
wife feel good in your plac.e
You can just watch quietly from over there.
No! No way! This wasn't what I intended...!
I love Suma...l love her from the bottom of my heart...
Wh-Why did it have to come to something like this!
Ma-Maa-kun!
Everyone in this neighborhood has had their
eye on you madam, you never noticed?
Sa-Sakimi! Sakimi!
Getting pounded with our dicks must feel way better than
whatever that wimp of a husband gives you huh?
A-About Maa-kun? Don't ever say
mean things about my husband!
But you see...you knew this would
happen eventually, didn't you?
You were actually looking forward to it, weren't you?
If this is what Maa-kun desires, I'll do whatever I need to!
But if that's not the case, then no matter
what happens, I would never feel good!
Oh? So that's how you're gonna
play it huh, ain't that cute...
If that's how it is, prove it by taking
our dicks in without cumming!
Completely in, that is.
Sakimi! Forgive me, forgive me!
This wasn't my intention at all!
M-Maa-kun, I beg of you! Please don't look
at this embarrassing position I'm in!
Turn your face away!
Madam's pussy is twitching around fiercely. Are you
actually getting excited from your husband watching?
Lies! That's a lie!
There's no way I'd get excited while I'm being raped!
Come on, come on! Make me feel good down here!
With your mouth-pussy, that is!
No way! His cock is getting bigger still!
It feels completely different from Maa-kun's.
It's so hard and thick It's almost like this is Sensei's!
Even your nipples are getting hard! You're
really feeling this, aren't you Madam?
Wh-What should I do...even though
I know I shouldn't be feeling good!
No good! My body's feeling too good to stop now!
I...I beg of you!
A little... just a little bit is fine!
J-Just let me rest a little, I beg of you!
Going to give up already? Cant help it
then, guess it's time I use this one...
N-No, that is...!
SAKIMI!
Sto-Stop...Stop it!
My ass, my asshole...!
Oh! It's your first time here, huh?
It's so tight, Madam!
I-It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
D-Don't! Don't move so much!
Take it out! Take it out!
It's amazing, isn't it? Her pussy's wrapping around
us tighter than ever, just like her asshole!
Th-These dicks are...messing up my insides!
I'm gonna break! I am going to go crazy!
That's good! Cum just Ilk that!
N-No! I don't want to!
Though I don't want to cum in front of Maa-kun...
It's no good! I'm sorry! Forgive me!!
Sakimi!!
I'm cumming! I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!!!
Aah, no way...!
This is enough, right?
Break it up already...!
What are you saying? Now is when the real fun starts...
If you're talking about time, we've got plenty
till morning. You don't need to worry...
N-No way! It...it still isn't over?
Clinical punch!
Medical kick!
Sen...Sensei...!
I won't forgive any rascal who dares to bully madam!
Here, here!
N-No!
Wh-What did you just give us?
You're overreacting guys...it's just a
little fast-acting liquid medicine.
Sakimi! Forgive me! Please forgive me!
Maa-kun...
W-Well then, I'll be taking my leave now.
Let's just say this is the end of the 'lack
of harmony' counseling sessions.
Sensei, thank you for coming.
No, no, I was just passing through.
I see.
After all of that happened, I was planning
on helping out Yukma-san again, but...
Available
for new
tenants
Wh-Why did this happen?
I heard this rumor going around that
the shop was in pretty bad shape...
So she and her husband took a loan off a shady place.
Hu-husband?
Whose?
Whose? Yukina-chan's husband of course.
The owner of the shop.
Eh?!
Bu-but! Yukina-chan always called him Onii-chan!
I heard they were childhood friends,
grew up together like siblings.
Those two are a well known couple
around these parts, you know.
No way...
I guess you were in the dark?
Why? Something that important...
I never heard anyone mention it.
Or anything about their debt either.
It must be because she didn't want to tell you.
Eh?
Because she started to like Sensei I think,
so she didn't want you to know.
Even about the debt, I'm sure she
didn't want you getting involved.
N-No way! That's just called 'keeping things to your self'!
You look like a kid crying like that!
I'm a kid after all!
Say Sensei, you free tomorrow night?
H-Huh?
There's a game of courage at the citizen's festival
tomorrow. Will you accompany me?
Umm, just what does that mean exactly?
It's to mak up for what happened to me.
You have some time to spare, don't you?
Yeah, well...
Then tomorrow, alright? I will wait for
you by the entrance at 8 o'clock.
She seems pretty happy for some reason.
I wonder what this is all about...