Guidance Counseling Room
You see...
Association is not necessarily a bad thing.
But this kind of activity is...
I think it would be better if both of you pass
this up first until you become adults.
Geez, you're too strict.
Kudo-sensei, you also do it normally
with your boyfriend, right?
Maybe Sensei doesn't even use contraceptives.
You think taking it in raw feels better after all?
What are you saying?
Behave in a manner befitting a student
and exercise caution while dating.
Do you understand?
Okay...
Anyway, I'll be keeping this for a while.
Yes, ma'am.
What do you think Masaharu?
Was I really strict?
I don't really think so.
Sayaka,
aren't you interested?
Doing it without a condom, or something.
No, I'm not.
Perhaps it doesn't feel good with me?
I'm not really experienced about it...
Th-That's not true.
When you simply touch me,
I already feel quite good.
Then it's okay.
I don't want to marry because I got pregnant.
I want that to happen after the ceremony, okay?
Okay, I understand.
Even I already want it you know.
To bear your child.
Marriage Blue
I already have a fiancé, but why am I going for this man.....
Well?
I think it probably looks a bit too flashy for me.
That's not true.
I'm even jealous that almost anything can fit you.
You're just too much for our man over there.
Don't you think so too, Kaneko-san?
Kaneko-senpai?
Oh, sorry about that.
I was speechless.
I must say, even the dress simply looks like a haze
when Kudo-san wears them.
Come on now.
Don't try to play around with my brother's fiancée.
I agree.
If you say it that way,
then it might seem that even I'm starting to look transparent.
I'll be happy with whatever Masaharu thinks about it.
It fits you very well, really.
Okay, okay. Now you've done your part.
It's good that you two seem to be really happy.
You two are the first couple to marry
in my juniors batch from college.
Thank you very much.
It's a ceremony to celebrate your fortune.
I'm going to make it wonderful.
You can count on it.
Okay.
I'm leaving it to you.
Your onee-san already seems like a pro after spending
a long time in the marriage business.
It must be because she started working right
after graduating from high school.
She said we'll be using her own office's ceremonial packages.
It seemed to be really bothersome,
but I never thought that Kaneko-senpai would be there.
For him to be able to live on uniquely like that,
I can't help but look forward to it.
You don't seem to remember,
but wasn't he the one who was brimming
with confidence before?
Having excellent grades, being at the center of romance,
and taking good care of his juniors...
A truly dependable senpai.
I just can't forget about that, you know?
I was only looking at you before.
Even now and from now on, okay?
Yours is really the best after all.
Hey, now. You look slovenly, Misato.
I'm doing my job perfectly, right?
This cock...
This really strong cock...
I wanted to be rewarded, so I'm doing my best.
I can't hold on anymore...
This is really boring.
My teacher at school said this a lot before,
but that girl named Sayaka
still seems to use the same boring white set of panties.
Seems that she doesn't know any
man aside from my little brother.
She'll change depending on the guy
no matter how far that change would be.
Yes.
I'm really sorry.
Some things came up unexpectedly,
so I won't be able to go again.
No, I'm really sorry.
Geez, you're leaving it all to me again.
I won't care if this doesn't go according to your plans.
I'll come at another date.
Okay. I'm really in a hurry so bye.
Geez, that stupid Masaharu.
I'm sorry. It seems his work isn't over yet.
He's says it's work,
and you're here also tired from your work, right?
It's not that.
Eh? What?
Are you tired right now?
No, I'm not really.
Then why don't we leave this for now
and take a little break?
There's a burger shop below the marriage hall.
I'm really okay.
That won't do.
Geez, Sayaka-san's too strict.
Am I too strict?
We planned on using it for the second
party after reception anyway,
so I was thinking of bringing you there at least once.
Okay?
It's a preliminary inspection.
A preliminary inspection.
That's why you see,
I think you should try to play with more men.
If you don't, you'll never know how good it is!
I'm already happy with only Masaharu.
Onee-san?
Are you okay?
Now, now.
Will she be okay?
The staff here at the marriage hall
use this room on night duties,
so she should be okay even if she sleeps here till morning.
I don't mean that...
There are also requests for lodgings during
certain marriage ceremonies.
So it also has the same things and equipment as hotel rooms.
We also have suites that are perfectly made for honeymoons.
Honeymoons, you say?
What's wrong. Kudo-san?
Are you okay?
I may have drank too much as well.
I'm going to leave now.
Thank you for today.
I'll prepare a room for you.
I think you should rest for a bit.
I'm fine...
No, you can't do that... No...
No, you can't!
W-Wait, please stop this!
You're familiar with the word "marriage blues", right?
It means...
....that something negative happens
when stress and libido build up.
Kaneko-senpai,
No!
Don't worry.
I'm properly wearing one.
No, you really must not do this!
You had prepared knowing this would happen, right?
It's in your bag.
That's not...
That was my student's...
So it's still tight.
We need to get it loose.
No, Masaharu!
S-Stop it already.
Please stop.
Senpai...
Does it feel good?
You can just leave everything to me.
Why senpai?
No...!
Here, it's okay, so be aroused some more!
I'm...
Stop thinking too much and try to match my movements.
Now!
Senpai, no!
This is...
What a cute junior...
Kudo-san, does it feel good?
No...
It doesn't...
Please stop.
It will leave a mark on me...
Senpai!
I don't want this!
I'm about to cum now.
No...
You can't!
Have you loosened up a bit there, Kudo-san?
Why are you doing this Senpai?
Oh, it wasn't enough?
That's not it!
That is... What will I say to Masaharu...?
The night is still young.
I'll stay with you till you get satisfied.
M-Masaharu...
Good work!
I wonder if Sayaka's still awake.
I'll just send her a text massage.
Kudo-kun seems to like being filled deep inside.
Those clothes!
They were the same as yesterday's, Kudo-sensei!
Did you stay at your boyfriend's place?
Me too, you know?
I didn't have time buy a new one, so...
Oh, yeah. If you have some extras,
can you give me one, Sensei?
I'll just deal with wearing white panties.
White panties?
I'm right, aren't I?
Woah, is that your boyfriend's hobby?
How wild!
We don't have anything here except those for newlyweds.
It's a lot better than nothing at all, right?
See you then!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I was always making you do things on your own.
I'm really sorry about it.
Really.
It's okay already.
Aren't you mad?
Of course, l am.
But let's forget about it already.
I was also at fault.
What?
Onee-san helps out in many different
things, so she said it's okay.
Hey, are you familiar with the word "marriage blues"?
Kaneko-senpai called and scolded me.
He said to think about what it means.
You also seemed tired,
so he said to give you something to make up for it.
I-I see...
I'm sorry that I had even tried to mail you at that time.
Was it a bother?
I was invited by my seniors to drink,
and I wasn't able to refuse, so...
Sayaka?
Sayaka, what's wrong?
It was a message from someone during my college days.
Someone I also know?
No.
Someone from seminar classes.
I'm going to get some for you.
I'm sorry. I'm already out.
I'm going to buy some.
You don't need to do that.
It's just a short while so wait here.
I'm home.
I'm sorry, I...
Text on Phone: Kaneko-senpai
Yes?
Calling me out using that threat message...
What's the meaning of this, Senpai?
Besides, this place is...
What? Asao does not often come with you?
Please finish your business with me already!
Well, you don't need to be that angry, Kudo-san.
The picture was taken well, wasn't it?
What are you doing?
I was already interested in you since our college days.
I... had already forgotten about it.
Your hair grew a lot already.
Cut if off.
That old look seems more brilliant to me.
No...
Senpai...
Please, stop it.
I don't have any plans of interfering with the wedding,
but I just can't just keep watching you force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself...
Don't hide it from me.
I knew when we did it.
You wanted to find your real self, right?
Sayaka.
No...
It's okay to reveal everything.
That's...!
Y-You can't do this.
Stop...
No...
The fire within you seems to be inextinguishable
once it has been lit, Sayaka.
No, don't just say my name like that.
No way... Oh, no...
My body had quickly...
It's slowly coming back to me.
That was some great moaning back there.
Can't Asao make you feel good?
This person's brimming confidence...
I hated it.
That's why I was never interested in him.
But even so...
After just...
After just doing it with him once...
Is this how quickly my view about him changed?
It feels like I can even accept that confidence right now...
Because he has that great thing...
I can't help it.
What am I thinking?
Stop this.
You really must not do this!
It's really awesome...
I still feel a bit hazy, so I can't exactly tell,
but this is completely different from Masaharu's.
You're not wearing a condom!
Wrapping me up like that, you can't complain.
No...
Let's stop this already!
Sayaka seems to like it deep, so...
Your moans are starting to sound better.
No...
You'll also know just how good Asao really is
if you learn how to play with other men.
That's...
No, I can't do that...
I'm already okay having Masaharu with...
This is...
How is it? How is mine compared to Asao's?
I'm not going to...
I'm not going to compare it...!
No, I'm going to break!
I'm sorry Masaharu.
I'm...
Kudo-san, I'm cumming with you.