I don't disapprove of you falling in love.
But things like that...
it's better to wait until both parties are mature enough.
Geez..
That's ancient.
You have sex with your boyfriend too. Don't you, Kudou-sensei?
You probably even go unprotected.
It must feel better without wearing any.
What are you saying?
Behave more like a student.
Exercise restraint when dating, got it?
Yes.
Anyway, I'll be confiscating this.
Yeah, whatever.
What do you think, Masaharu?
Am I really old fashioned?
I don't think so.
Aren't you interested, Sayaka-san?
Stuff like unprotected sex.
No way!
Not even if it's me?
I don't really have much experience so...
That's not what I meant.
It's just that when you touch me...
I'll...
Start feeling horny.
That's a good thing.
I don't want a shotgun marriage.
Those can wait after the ceremony.
Right?
Yeah, I understand.
Actually, I want to have it as soon as possible too.
Your child.
Waku-FAPsubs    Credits: Naoya/Fomite
http://waku.blog.com
Marriage Blue: I've a fiancé, yet this guy still...
What do you think?
I personally think it's a bit too flashy.
Nonsense.
I'm envious.
No matter what you wear, it suits you.
Such a waste on my stupid brother.
Do you agree, Kaneko-san?
Kaneko-senpai?
O-Oh sorry.
I'm absolutely speechless.
Or should I say, I feel desolated seeing Kudou-san in her wedding dress.
Hey.
Don't put my brother's fiancée on the spot.
Yeah.
To be frank, I should be the one feeling desolated.
I'm happy no matter what Masaharu thinks.
It suits you, very.
Alright!
Good work everyone.
Isn't it great.
Both of you look really happy.
The birth of the first couple from our college juniors.
Thank you very much.
It's both your wedding afterall.
I'll make sure it's flawless.
Look forward to it.
We will.
I'm counting on you.
She's been managing the ceremonial hall for a long time.
Feels like she's an expert in this area. Your Sis.
You mentioned she became a working adult directly from high school.
Though she's using her own ceremonial hall.
I actually feel rather troubled.
I didn't think Kaneko-senpai would be there too.
For them to be so direct, I'm quite looking forward to it.
I don't really remember much.
But he's always been full of confidence.
Good results and mild.
Cares for his juniors.
A reliable senior.
There's nothing not remember, right?
I was always looking at you, that's why.
Right now, and in the future.
Yours is indeed..
the best.
Hey, you're such a slut. Misato.
Did I not do a good job?
Your dick.
Your warm dick.
I'm working hard for your reward.
But I can't anymore.
She's so boring.
Even the school teachers are saying it.
That Sayaka still only wears white full matching underwears.
If that's the case, the only guy she knows is probably only my brother.
Woman will tend to change.
Depending on the guy.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Work came up.
I won't be able to make it today as well.
Yeah, I'm really sorry.
You're gonna push everything to me again.
I'm not responsible if it doesn't match your preferences.
I'll surely make up for it.
That's it then. It's urgent, I'm hanging up.
Sheesh.
Masaharu, you idiot.
Sorry.
His work is never ending.
Work and work.
You're also tired after work, too. Right?
No, it's not like that.
What? Kudou-san, you're tired?
No, I'm not.
Well then, let's stop for today and have a breather.
There's a bar near our ceremonial hall.
Is it fine for me to go?
Why are you saying?
You're too old fashioned, Sayaka-san.
I'm old fashioned?
We are planning to use it for the after party anyway.
You're gonna have to go at least once.
It's just a preview, preview.
Like I said!
You and I should fool around with all sorts of guys more.
Otherwise, nobody will see your good qualities.
I'm contented with having Masaharu.
Sis?
Are you alright?
Oh dear.
Will she be alright?
This is the room that the staff will be using during the wedding dinner.
It's fine even if she sleeps until morning.
That's not what I mean.
There are also requests to stay directly overnight during weddings.
The hotel amenities are also in order.
They even have sexy lingerie for newly weds to spend their first night.
First night?
What's the matter, Kudou-san? Are you alright?
I must have drank too much as well. I should be going now.
Thank you for today.
I'll prepare a room for you. So have a good rest.
No, I'm fine.
No, stop.
NO! Stop it at once!
Hey, please stop this.
Do you know the phrase "Marriage Blue"?
It's unhealthy to accumulate to much fatigue and libido.
Kaneko-senpai, please stop!
You don't have to worry. I've proper protection.
No, I won't allow this.
Aren't you preparing yourself for this?
I found it inside the bag.
You got it wrong... that belongs to a student.
It's still quite hard.
I'll need to season it.
No, Masaharu!
P-Please stop this at once, Senpai.
Do you feel good?
You only have to hand your body to me.
Why, Senpai?
Stop!
Come on, it's alright.
Get more into the groove.
Don't think about anything.
Move according to my rhythm. Go on!
Senpai, no! Please!
What a cute voice.
Do you feel good, Kudou-san?
No, I don't.
Please stop.
You'll leave a scar.
Senpai, don't!
I'm gonna cum soon.
No way...
Isn't it softer now?
Your..
Why would you do such a thing, Senpai.
Oh, haven't had enough?
Of course not! How am I going to tell Masaharu?
The night is still young.
I'll be with you until you're satisfied.
Ma... Masaharu.
Thank you for today.
Is Sayaka still awake? I'm text her.
Kudou-kun seems to enjoy NTR.
Your clothes are the same as yesterday's, Kudou-sensei!
Did you spend the night at your boyfriend's place?
Me too! I didn't have time to get a new one.
Oh right, Sensei.
Did you prepare any?
I don't mind bearing with white panties.
White panties?
Am I wrong?
Dirty. Your boyfriend's fetish? Cool.
I only prepared those orientated towards newly weds.
Beats having to wear back the old ones.
Later!
I'm really sorry for earlier on, pushing everything to you.
I've reflected, for real.
It's fine.
Not angry?
Of course I am.
But, forget it.
Since I'm in the wrong too.
What?
Sis really helped out a lot. So it's fine.
Hey, have you heard of marriage blues?
Kaneko-senpai reprimanded me over the phone.  He asked me to think about what it means.
He said you're very tired, and I should pamper you more.
I see.
I'm sorry I didn't realize and messaged you so late. Am I annoying?
They invited you for a drink and you couldn't turn them down.
Sayaka? Hey, what's wrong, Sayaka?
Someone I knew from college sent a message.
Do I know her?
A confidential friend. I'll go get somemore.
Sorry, we ran out of it. I'll go buy some.
It's fine.
It'll be real quick. So wait for me.
I'm back!
Sorry, I...
Yes?
Summoning me with that sort of threatening message. What's the meaning of this, Senpai?
And to a place like this again.
Oh? Not getting along well with Asao?
Hurry and tell me what you want!
Now, there's no need to be so mad. Kudou-san.
The photo was well taken, right?
What do you think you're doing?
I've been interested in you since college.
I... forgot.
It's gotten much longer. Cut it.
You were much more dazzling back then.
No, Senpai. Please stop.
I don't intend to get in the way of you and Asao's wedding.
But I can't ignore your tolerating face.
I'm not tolerating anything.
You don't have to hide in front of me.
I only have to hug you to know. You're looking for your true self, am I right? Sayaka.
Stop!
You only have to expose everything. It's fine.
That's...
Stop it, I beg you.
A body that can't be satisfied once ignited. Sayaka.
Please! Don't call my name directly on your own.
You must be kidding. No way, I'm already...
Everything is coming back igradually.
What incredible voice that was.
Didn't Asao make you feel good?
This over confident trait for his.
I hated it, that's why I wasn't interested in him. But yet I...
Just once.
We only had intercourse just once.
To think the change would be so drastic?
Right now, I feel I can accept that arrogance of his.
I mean, he has such an amazing tool. It can't be helped.
What am I thinking, I!
Please stop already! I definitely won't...
It's feels fantastic, as I thought.
I was drunk, so I don't feel as much before.
He's different in many ways from Masaharu.
You're not wearing a condom.
You're latching so tightly onto me. Stop complaining.
If it's like that, hurry and stop!
Sayaka seems to prefer mine more.
Your voice sounds much better now.
If you get to know more men,
you'll appreciate more of Asao's other good traits.
That's...
That sort of thing, as long as Masaharu is there, I'm..
How's it? Compared to Asao, mine is..
No way... I... yours is more...
No! I'll break like this!
I'm sorry, Masaharu. I... I'm...
Kudou-san! Let's cum together.