The beach!
The succubus don't seem to fear the sun finally.
I'm still having a hard time accepting.
Finding out I was adopted... and also a succubus.
Even if he had told me everything about the adoption,
he probably gave me this necklace just in case.
I wonder what he was thinking.
Although,
It must have been hard for her to stay with
you without being able to talk about it.
Saki.
Regardless of blood ties or
knowing who the real Saki is.
I hope that we find a way to live all together.
– Saki, you've become an admirable young lady.
– And... to be honest.
I'd like you to make love to me, like
that other day in the bathroom.
Behold!
Huh?
Your dick seems bigger than last time.
Are you OK?
Saki!
I'm alright.
Could you give me a blow job?
I'd love to!
Don't suck so hard!
Will you remember this evening?
I don't quite know.
I just do what comes to my mind.
And to think that I always thought
you were a pure and innocent girl.
And yet you masturbate while sucking my cock.
Big brother, look at me.
All it took was sucking your dick to get me excited.
More.
I need more.
Big brother, does my blow
job make you want to cum?
Yes, it's amazing!
I won't be able to hold for much longer.
Hold? What are you holding?
That was delicious!
Say, big brother... I...
I'm boiling on the inside.
Maybe your dick can calm me.
My nipples are trapped in my breasts.
Even if it embarrasses me, your touch excites me.
My nipples are coming out of hiding.
Doing love together cloud make you pregnant.
Do you still want to continue?
We will do love together?
Yes, I want to feel your cum inside me.
Well, prepare yourself.
I can feel you penetrating me.
Oh... Oh yes!
Sex is so amazing.
And to say she was the only one able to enjoy it.
Saki, try not to talk so loudly.
I can't do anything about it, you fuck me so deeply.
The pleasure is too intense for me.
My orgasm was so intense that I peed a little.
Sorry, big brother.
Don't worry about it, it's not urine.
So let everything out while we fuck.
Okay, I will do whatever you want.
I should let myself go by cumming?
Exa... Exactly.
And I love when you let yourself go completely.
Kiss me!
I... I like when we kiss.
Your dick is making me go crazy.
You're gonna make me explode!
Your hard dick is plowing me so hard.
Does it like it?
Does it like go fuck me?
Stop, you skank!
Punish me!
Punish me with your cock for being a bad girl!
Oh... I can't take it anymore.
You're gonna cum?
Give me all your cum!
Cum!
Cum in me!
Yes!
Saki!
I feel them.
Your babies are impregnating me.
Don't ever stop cumming!
Tada!
Admire the best of the best of big pussy.
G... Girls...
You should be ashamed.
It's not just your sisters in this world.
Your dick is the only one that can
satisfy my needs, I'll remind you.
I'd also like you to make love to me.
You and Saki fucked while we were at the beach.
We share the same feelings,
so imagine how good this was for me.
Big brother.
You should plow my wet pussy.
We were caught.
Whatever your choise, I'll always be there for you.
With whom will you start?
Which one of our pussy will
give you the most pleasure?
Big brother.
B-big brother.
I'm so happy for your choice.
Fuck me as much as you want.
The pleasure is even more intense when you
fondle with my boobs while you penetrate me.
I envy you so much.
We're alone so we might as much take advantage.
Tell him the lines we thought you.
Oh.. Okay.
Big brother,
shove your huge hot and hard rod
in my pussy and fill it with cum.
Manabe, you're really the best.
So they say!
Gotta say she's adorable.
She excited me so much too.
I got an idea.
Your agile fingers make me even more wet!
I really want to take Saki's place.
Big brother, big brother.
Saki-chan is waiting for you to give her pleasure.
So take care of her when you finish with me.
You are so thoughtful with everyone.
Huh?
Be gentle with your sister
else you'll make her taste your sperm.
Yes!
Cum inside me with all the cum you got.
Make me pregnant!
We'll cum at the same time.
Yes!
Tsukikawa,
my pussy is all yours.
I stopped sleeping with other men.
So come and fuck me.
I can finally enjoy your rock hard cock!
You're so hot!
My dick will melt!
Being a succubus lets me control my body heat.
This heat must excite you even more.
Manabe! Manabe!
Ca... calm down.
My tail is more sensitive than my clitoris.
Stop pulling on it and plowing me at the same time!
I feel it coming.
If we continue.
Your dick will give me the best orgasm of my life!
Cum and fill me up while your sisters are looking.
Ye-yes!
His dick is more powerful than everything.
Don't do this brother!
We don't care who's the best.
My pussy is getting hungry and wants some cum.
Forgive me for making you wait.
Not yet.
This is my second orgasm.
No! Stop! I'm still cumming.
All those orgasm will make me crazy.
They are so cute.
What would be her reaction if I play with her tits?
No, stop!
She's gonna rip my tit off!
She's still cumming while passed out.
Tsukikawa, you're a sex beast.
Stop talking to me, Manabe!
I'm already busy with her.
I can feel when you're gonna cum.
You'd die to empty yourself in your little sister.
Let's cum together while we make a baby.
Saki!
Hey, I'm gonna cum!
I'm full... of cum.
Discovering the truth about my sister
and Manabe, messed my life up.
Even if their attraction towards me is sincere,
I haven't given it any importance.
Our relations were purely physical.
It's those same feelings
that gave birth to the guilt inside me.
Oh wow big brother,
your dick is still hard even after all those orgasms.
Huh?
I feel like I'm floating in the clouds.
Stop, you'll end up waking him up.
Ah, big brother.
It's time for the nightly licking.
Sorry for waking you up.
Since you seemed depressed yesterday.
You came in my room to cheer me up?
That's right.
Making love with you makes us so happy.
I will wait for your answer, however long it takes.
So start by smiling big brother.
We love you more than anything.
You girls.
Cum in my mouth while I suck you off.
It's futile to hold it back.
My boobs and my mouth are all yours.
Offer us the best sperm.
I've made my decision.
I will do everything to make you happy!
I am so happy to hear that!
Cum as much as you'd like.
Cumming makes you happy right?
Would you cum your happiness on us?
Bad big brother,
you let our boobs do all the work.
Your role is to cum in enormous quantity.
Big brother,
I love you!
The aroma of his sperm fills my nose! It's so good!
My face is full of cum.
I am bathing in happiness.
This is the best that I can offer you.
So...
Are you sure that you want me?
If I have the chance to live
with my favorite big brother,
then I have all I need.