– Yay! Beach!
I always thought succubi
couldn't handle sunlight very well.
Even so, I'm more surprised
that I was a succubus all this time.
Yeah, seems like Dad knew about this all along,
and kept it sealed with the necklace.
What a thing he's done.
You know, I think Saki-chan had it rough too.
She must have suffered, being trapped inside
and unable to speak to the brother she loved so much.
Saki...
I don't think it matters if she's related
by blood, or if she's the real Saki or not.
You two should just continue normally, as loving siblings.
Saki! I raised you to be such a good girl!
Also... Um...
I want you to do the same thing you did
in the bath with Saki-chan, to me as well.
Tsukikawa                            onii-chan
– It's done!                                                                       – It's done!
Huh?
little sister ♥ hen succubus friend and ♥ the little sister succubus
It's so much bigger than when I saw it in the bath.
Are you okay?
Saki...
I'm fine, so could you lick it for me?
All at once? Where did you even learn to do this?
I just kind of have a sense of what to do.
All those perverted things bled out into her pure mind!
She's even masturbating while giving me a biowjob!
Onii-chan, your dick is amazing... I can't think about
anything else when I'm sucking it like this.
More! More!
Onii-chan, am I doing this right?
Yeah, you're a natural at this, Saki!
I think I'm gonna cum already!
"Cum?" What's "cumming"?
It tastes so good...
Onii-chan... my stomach feels so hot.
Maybe if you put your dick inside me, it'll feel better.
My nipples are inverted and it's embarrassing,
but it feels so good I can't stop!
They're coming out!
If I let that white stuff out inside you,
we might make a baby, though.
Do you still want to have sex, knowing that?
That's sex? It's fine, then.
I want a lot of that white stuff!
I'm going to put it inside you then.
Come inside me, onii-chan!
Good! So good! So this is sex?
I'm so jealous that Saki
got to do this with you already.
Saki, keep your voice down!
It just feels too good!
Oh no, I'm too happy.
I can't keep my voice down!
I wet myself while having sex...
I'm sorry, onii-chan...
Don't worry, that's not pee.
During sex, it's fine to let out a lot of that stuff.
I'll let out a lot, then!
What should I do? I'm such a pervert!
Yeah, that's true, but I love you the way you are, Saki!
Kissing...
I love it. I love kissing!
Onii-chan, your dick is making me go crazy down there.
Saki, you're so dirty!
Your dick got even harder after I said that!
Does that mean your dick is happy?
Does that mean it's happy?
Calm down!
Yes, punish me!
Punish my bad pussy with your big dick!
I'm gonna cum!
You're going to cum inside me?
Let all that white stuff out inside me!
Let it out! Let it all out inside me!
Saki!
Your baby-milk is flowing into me!
It keeps on coming inside!
Ta-dah! Behold, the tower of pussy.
What are you three doing?
Geez, Tsukikawa.
This entire trip, you've only taken care of your little sister.
I can't be satisfied unless it's with your dick, now.
I don't want Saki to take senpai all for herself!
This morning you had sex with Saki, didn't you?
Do you know what I had to go through
because of that? Our pussies are linked, you know.
Come on, onii-chan,
put your dick in my piping hot pussy first.
So she knew...
Onii-chan, it doesn't really matter who you choose, but...
I just want you to always be by my side.
Who are you going to choose, onii-chan?
Come on, whose pussy feels best?
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan!
I'm so happy, onii-chan!
Use my pussy to make yourself feel good!
This feels so good! My boobs are being fondled
so hard and I can feel the pleasure from Saki's pussy!
Hey, that's not fair. Because you two are linked,
the sensations you feel are doubled!
Come on, use those words I taught
you to seduce your onii-chan.
Yes!
Onii-chan, use my pussy to warm up your dick,
and make it all slimy. Use your pre-cum to make it wet!
Manabe, you taught her that?
That's awesome!
I know, right?!
You're so cute, Saki!
I'm getting so turned on.
Oh, I know what to do.
Oh my god, this feels so good!
My pussy is being rubbed and played with so roughly!
I'm jealous of what the other Saki's feeling right now!
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
Use your dick to make Saki-chan feel less lonely, okay?
Saki, you're such a nice girl.
Tsukikawa, you're so unfair.
It looks like he's going to cum soon, though.
Yes! Please plant your seed
into my pussy, it belongs to you!
Pregnant! Make me pregnant!
I'm gonna cum, too! I'm gonna cum from this too!
Tsukikawa, look, come on.
My pussy is already like this, just for you.
I haven't done it with any other guys since you.
Please, hurry and mess me up!
This is what I need! Your huge dick inside me!
It's so hot! I feel like I'm gonna melt!
The more advanced their magical power,
the more easily can a succubi adjust their pussy.
My pussy feels amazing, doesn't it?
Manabe! Manabe!
Don't! My tail is really, really sensitive!
Tsukikawa, your dick is making my mind go blank!
I... I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum inside!
Something amazing is coming!
I'm gonna cum from your dick, Tsukikawa!
Do it, Tsukikawa. Plant your seed in another woman,
right in front of your little sister!
I'm cumming!
I lost...
Onii-chan, you're so mean. I don't care about
who's first or whatever... just give me your semen!
I'm sorry I made you wait so long, Saki!
No, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum already!
Wait, I'm cumming! I'm still cumming!
Don't just keep going! You're making me feel too much!
You're so cute.
Let your succubus senpai suck on your nipples.
No, don't! You can't!
You're gonna suck my nipple off!
You're fucking your little sister over there too.
You're such an animal, Tsukikawa.
Shut up, Manabe!
I'm trying my best here!
My mind's going blank,
but I can tell that you're gonna cum soon!
You want to let all your hot semen
out inside your little sister, right?
Let's cum together!
Let your baby-making milk out inside me!
Saki!
Yes! Yes!
I can't go on...
Knowing that Saki was a succubus
changed my life completely.
They always had the same pure feelings
of gratitude towards me,
but I only took advantage of their feelings...
I kept our bodies connected with only lust.
When I'm alone, I keep thinking about how I'm not
answering their feelings. That guilt is crushing me.
Oh, onii-chan, you're so hard for some reason.
Huh?
Something feels warm...
Saki-chan, onii-chan's gonna wake up!
Oh, onii-chan? It's time to have your dick rubbed.
Sorry we woke you up, onii-chan.
You seemed to be really down since yesterday, so...
You two... you're trying to make a worthless guy
who can't even make up his mind feel better?
Yep, that's right, onii-chan!
I'm happy that I was able to have sex
with you when you were happy, onii-chan!
Me too. I don't mind waiting
longer for your answer, onii-chan!
Feel better, onii-chan!
– We love you, onii-chan!
You two...
Just feel good, onii-chan,
you don't have to hold anything back.
Cum a lot in my pussy and my mouth pussy, okay?
Just give it all to me!
I've made up my mind!
I'll make both of you happy!
I'm so happy!
Let out a lot of cum, let's all become happy!
Let out your happy sauce!
Geez, onii-chan, you're rubbing too hard against our boobs.
Come on, you can do it. Cum a lot!
Onii-chan, cum!
Onii-chan, your cum is so thick, and it smells so good.
I'm so happy... there's so much!
This is the best I could come up with.
Are you two okay with it?
If it's with my onii-chan, who I love so much,
– I don't mind at all.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч