My father is an ecologist,
so he's always traveling around the world.
Since he's always gone,
my sister and I are home alone very often.
Let's eat!
Saki, be a good girl and eat it all.
Okay!
Hey, do you ever feel lonely since Dad's never here?
Nope!
Huh?
You're always here with me,
so I never feel alone, onii-chan!
Little Sister, Marshmallow, Succubus
THE TWO SUCCUBI
I can't move my body...
Holy crap! Am I being bound
by some supernatural force?
A ghost?! Or maybe a curse?!
Dad's grudge?
This is all because I took off the talisman, isn't it?
Forgive me, Father!
Not that you're dead or anything...
Hm? What?
What's Saki doing here?!
My first meal from you... It's so hard and energetic!
Time to dig in!
Are you really Saki?
Good morning! Did I surprise you?
What are you doing?!
I don't remember raising you to be this kind of girl!
I'm the same as I've always been.
What about you? Look at how hard
you are from me giving you a blowjob.
I'll take care of your dick with my boobs now.
I'm gonna cum if you keep doing that!
Cum! Let me drink your tasty cum!
Delicious!
Saki, you...
Wings?! Horns?! A tail?!
Onii-chan!
Wait!
We're siblings! We can't...
I'm having sex with onii-chan!
Are you really Saki?
You see, I became like this because
I love you so much, onii-chan.
I love you! I love you, onii-chan!
My pussy feels all tingly!
How am I supposed to hold back in this situation?!
O-Onii-chan, your dick is so amazing!
I think I'm going to cum!
Please cum inside me, onii-chan!
Shoot your cum inside of me!
What are you saying?
If I do that, you'll get pregnant!
Don't worry, I don't plan on becoming
a mother any time soon.
Succubi can decide whether they get pregnant or not.
What are you saying?
Oh no, I'm gonna blow!
Hot! So hot!
Your semen is so amazing, onii-chan!
I just came! If you keep doing that, I'll...
That's fine. I know you've been holding
yourself back all these years.
I'm ready for seconds!
Give me a second serving of your cum!
Incest is the best!
Wow, I had the craziest dream.
I'm sorry I'm such a dirty girl, onii-chan.
I don't think I can face him like this.
I should leave before...
Time to wake up, Saki!
Oh, she left already?
Ethology Research Society
Jeez...
First I lose the talisman Dad gave me,
and then I have a wet dream about my sister.
So without that talisman,
you ended up cumming inside your little sister?
Manabe? That didn't happen.
It was a dream and only a dream, got it?
You wouldn't happen to know
where my talisman is, would you?
What are you doing? Do I smell or something?
Oh, so that's how it is?
I can't move my body?
Hey! What do you think you're doing? Stop!
I've been aiming for your virginity this whole time.
Your dick feels so good!
Wait, stop!
So good!
I wish you lost that talisman sooner!
I couldn't lay a finger on you because of that talisman.
Can you feel it?
My pussy's getting so wet because of your dick!
Manabe, you're...
I'm a succubus.
I squeeze the semen out of men in order to get mana.
You're dressed the same way as Saki was...
So are you saying that she's a succubus too?!
Your sister has the same scent as me.
Face reality, Tsukikawa.
That talisman probably possessed
some magical properties, don't you think?
True, I had that dream the night I lost it.
Hey, don't move your hips so much!
I can't help it! Your dick is just too wonderful!
You and your sister aren't related by blood, right?
I bet that after the talisman disappeared,
her instincts kicked in.
Welt now it's my turn.
You're going to ravage my pussy
with everything you've got.
It feels so good! I can't control my body!
I can feel you inside me!
Yes, fuck me up!
Fuck me so hard that I forget about
everyone else's and can only live with yours!
So, you do this all the time?
Well, I am a succubus.
But if I can keep taking in your dick
like this, I won't need any others.
I'm gonna cum inside!
I can feel you hitting my deepest parts!
Don't stop!
I'll make sure that you don't get me pregnant.
Just let my dirty pussy drink your semen!
Manabe!
Cum! Cum!
Let your dick explode in my pussy!
It's coming! It's coming!
Your dick is just too amazing.
I'm a succubus, but you're gonna make me fall for you.
You... I'll get you back for this!
I'd like to see you try.
I'll take you on anytime.
Now, time for round two!
I can't believe she made me do her three times.
The books were right.
A succubi's lust is nothing to sneeze at.
That's right, onii-chan.
Saki-san?
Yep.
Now that the talisman is gone,
I can come out and talk to you now.
I'm so happy!
I couldn't really muster up
the mana to say hi this morning...
But thanks to all that semen you gave me
last night, I can see you whenever I want.
Let's make this a routine from now on, okay?
I can't move again...
Wait, so what happened to my real sister?
She's right here, inside me.
She thinks what happened
last night was just a dream.
I'm so happy!
Okay, let's get right to it! I'm ready for your cum.
My pussy's twitching so much!
Make sure you cum a lot in me, okay?
No, stop! This is my little sister's body!
I've been with you all this time, too!
I love you just as much as she does!
I'm just as much your little sister as she is.
I've loved you all this time, onii-chan!
I've been so lonely all this time!
She and I always knew that we weren't your real sister.
Saki...
I'm so sorry for making you feel so lonely all this time!
Let me make it up to you by making you feel better!
Yes! You're doing me so hard!
Harder! Blow your load inside me!
I love you, onii-chan!
Oh my god, my boobs feel so good!
Keep playing with my boobs like that!
I'll give you everything I have!
Yeah, I'll take it all!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
I'm gonna...
It's so hot. My pussy's gonna drink all this.
What?
Stop thrusting, onii-chan!
I just came!
Stop! No!
Do all you succubi get tighter from being teased?
Forgive me!
I'm sorry for having such a selfish pussy!
It feels so good!
Hurry up and cum!
I'm being conquered by your dick!
My pussy is worn out!
If you're tired, I'll fill you to the brim with cum!
Yes! You can use any of my filthy holes!
Just give me your cum!
Saki, I'm gonna cum inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm so full.
I don't think I can eat any more.
Is this how your personalities change?
How am I supposed to face the other Saki?
Hey, Saki, are you okay?
Huh?
Onii-chan!
Wait...
Huh?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hibrio21
editor: cockslider
quality check: fyurie