Tomo...
Keiichi-kun, no! Not here.
Who cares.
I can't...
If someone comes, then we'll just give them a show.
Let's have some fun with this.
It hurts, Keiichi-kun.
Untie me.
It hurts.
Why are you doing this?
No, don't...
Don't...
No...
No, not there...
Great view.
No, it's embarrassing.
Stay still.
No...
You're wet.
Here, drink it.
Well? Does your juice taste good?
Your cunt looks pretty.
Don't look at it.
It's embarrassing...
You're getting me excited with your sexy sounds.
Stay still.
Don't move.
It hurts Keiichi-kun!
You like that, don't you?
You want me to hurt you, right?
Tomo, do you like me?
Yes, I like you.
I like you, so...
You should've said so in the first place.
Suck on it!
Tomo...
You're getting better.
You'll do it with anyone if they make you feel good?
Who the hell are you?
It's okay.
You shouldn't hold back.
You want this right?
Here.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
I can't believe I did this to Tomo's swimsuit.
I'm a filthy bastard.
But I can't stop, ever since that day...
When that woman appeared...
Morning!
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
You are real, right?
What are you talking about?
You'll be late.
I'm home!
Nobody's home?
Someone's in my room?
What's going on?
I'll climax...
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
What is the meaning of this?
I'm back!
Are you home, Kei-chan?
Mother!
Oh, you were home?
Why didn't you answer me?
Mother, welcome back.
Step aside.
I'll get it.
Where do you want this?
Let's put it in your room first.
What?
Why do you look surprised?
I bought a new cover for the futon.
I'll put them on myself.
No, I don't really trust you.
Plus there's another pair inside.
For Akane?
You see, I forgot to tell you something.
Did anyone come when I was out?
What do you mean?
Ma'am.
Long time no see.
I'm Reika.
Oh? You're Reika-chan?
Yes, I'm Reika.
Yes, that's right, you're Reika-chan all right.
It's just that I haven't seen you in a while, so...
I'm sorry Kei-chan, I'll introduce her to you.
This is Reika-chan.
She's the daughter of my deceased sister.
Hello.
I'm Reika and I'll be living here starting today.
Pleased to meet you.
Reika-chan was living with her parents in America, but...
There are no stains...
Was it just my imagination?
No, I saw it with my own eyes, and even heard her voice.
I'll climax...
How did she end up in the back room?
I'm confused.
Onii-chan, dinner's ready.
Okay.
And just like that, Reika became part of our family.
It was too easy, as if she was trying to sneak into people's hearts.
It's almost scary.
But I was expecting something.
Even though I didn't know what was happening...
I was feeling very uneasy.
I'll climax...
It's a bit too plain for a girl's room.
I don't like it when there's too much stuff.
Thanks.
But I was surprised.
My mother didn't tell me anything about you coming.
My parents died all of a sudden, so...
We're both in a similar situation.
I was once just like you.
But to me, my stepmother is like my real mother.
I think of Akane as my own sister too.
I guess you all get along well.
It's a pleasure to be part of your family.
Pleasure is all mine.
But since I'm a year older than you, so I guess I'm your older sister.
So you listen to what I say, okay?
Yes, Onee-sama.
I'm sure Akane is happy as well.
She said she'd rather have a big sister than a big brother.
Akane-chan is...
What about Akane?
She thinks about you everyday and masturbates.
What are you talking about?
You heard me.
Don't you think Akane-chan is cute?
I'm heading to bed.
You saw me didn't you?
Masturbating...
It's okay, I wanted you to watch me.
You want to do it with me, don't you?
Stop it!
Take it easy.
See? You're getting so hard.
What are you doing?
I told you already, I don't like complications.
So I hate waiting.
You have to be honest with your feelings and have a little fun.
But we're siblings now.
I can't do this!
My, is that the kind of thing you say after getting an erection?
Besides, you're not related to anyone in this family by blood.
They're just simply acting as your mother and sister.
You have nothing to worry about.
Right?
You're wrong!
I'm not wrong.
You can never get away from me.
What the hell is Reika thinking?
I said you can't get away from me.
Don't you remember?
If you make a loud noise, your mother and Akane-chan are going to hear it.
Look, they're real breasts.
You've only seen them in videos, right?
This is the areola.
This is the nipple.
You want to lick them don't you?
This is what you really want to know about, right?
Take a good look.
It's really grotesque, isn't it?
Do you want to touch it?
You want to touch it don't you?
It's written all over your face.
It's not good to hold back.
Stop...
Stop it.
What if I don't stop?
Come now.
I can't!
This is wrong!
Let's go home Keiichi!
You're not going to your swimming club?
Your bathing suit is missing?
Was it stolen?
That's what I think.
It's just really weird, since mine was the only one stolen.
You didn't steal it, did you?
Stop messing around.
I guess you don't have the balls for that.
Hello.
Reika!
Why do you look surprised?
You must be Aihara-san.
I'm Keiichi's older sister Reika.
Nice to meet you too.
Keiichi-kun told me about you.
You're really cute.
Do you like Keiichi?
Why did you come here for?
I was just shopping.
Hey, can you hold this?
I have some places to go.
Don't open it until you get home.
Aihara-san, take care of Keiichi for me.
Bye.
She's really pretty.
I'm a bit jealous.
Great.
What is she thinking?
This is...
Why was this in Reika's possession?
You want this right?
Here.
Tomo's scent.
No!
Tomo...
I like you Tomo...
I got it.
My brother's secret.
What should I do? Should I show it to Aihara-san?
Don't!
You should be happy. You got your wish.
You stole her bathing suit?
I don't know...
But you can't give that back after rubbing your cock on it.
Should I show this to your mother?
Or maybe I'll show this to Akane-chan.
Stop it!
What are you going to do? Rape me?
Get out.
This is my room.
This is my room, too.
What are you doing?
You'll do as I say.
Then I'll delete the photo and promise not to tell anyone.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to kneel down.
What did you say?
Just do as I say.
Well? Are you going to do it or not?
Lick it nice and clean.
So cute.
You're getting real hard.
Look at you, Keiichi.
You feel excited even though you're the one getting raped.
Maybe you're a masochist.
Of course not.
Are you sure?
I can't take it anymore...
You can do the rest on your own.
Using this.
You made it dirty.
You can never return it.
You'll just have to keep it.
Now you and I are both guilty.
Let me do you!
No!
Why not?
You want to do it with Aihara-san for your first time, don't you?
I have no plans to take her spot.
Why don't you ask her?
What...
I'm sure she's doing the same thing...
While thinking about you.
Doing it, making nasty noises.
Letting her dirty juices pour out...
She plays with it.
Like this.
Take your hands off!
You don't care who you do it with, right?
Then maybe I should wear that.
It might be tight around my chest but...
If you can stick your cock inside, you don't care if it's a parent or a sibling.
That's not true.
You don't have to hold back.
Tell me if you want to do it with me.
Well?
I... I... want to do it...
Then get on your knees and beg.
Please, let me do you!
Louder!
Let me do you!
Do what?
Let me put my cock inside you, please!
Fine.
Gently.
Okay.
Yes, push your knee against my cunt.
Yes, that's it.
Look carefully while you do it.
Suck on the juice without spilling it.
Suck it...
Suck it!
Put your tongue inside!
Well? Does it taste good?
Tastes good, right?
Yeah.
Feels good.
Stop slacking off and do your part!
Yes.
You know where it is right?
It'll go in if you push it slowly.
Now push it in!
More! Push it in deeper!
More! Do it harder!
More! More!
I think I'm gonna come...
Hang in there!
Keep it going a little longer!
More!
More! More!
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm coming!
It's too bad you climaxed.
You could've released it inside.
Now what do you say?
Thank you very much.
You're so cute, Keiichi.
You don't want to admit it, but you're definitely a masochist.
And maybe I'm a sadist since I enjoy that.
Come.
Since that day, I became her obedient sex slave.
It's not fair, Onii-chan...
Onii-chan...
I want to do it, too...