Hear ye, citizens of Austria.
Feast your eyes on the pirate's captives in chains!
They are the royalty of this country!
They might hide behind the almighty titles of "royalty",
but they're only women in the end!
They cannot win against the strength of men!
How can they protect this country
when they themselves are so weak?
This is a royal decree from the new order!
We will be reborn from the guidance of the pirates!
You're really saying that, Claus?!
If you want something badly, then steal it by force!
If you wanna fuck a woman, then fucking do it!
The strong can do whatever they want to the weak!
The strong can obtain anything they wish!
This is this county's new providence!
I'm cumming!
Taking care of the pirates is your job, isn't it?
You two are nothing but traitors
who couldn't protect the country!
You dirty whores!
Losers have no right to speak.
They're right. As a Queen and as a soldier,
I was unable to fulfill my duty.
The princess's pussy tastes so good!
Ugh, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's tightening on me!
Her asshole is getting so wet!
Don't be so rough with me! I'm gonna break!
I'm cumming!
Drink it all!
Drink this, too!
Now it's your turn, great citizens.
Punish these incompetent rulers
who couldn't protect your country!
Let them know the extent of your fury!
Give me back the family you killed!
– You fucking whores!
– This is just too much.
This is too much!
These are the pirates who attacked this country!
Don't try to make excuses to get
out of this, you disgusting pig!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
This isn't even dose to the end.
This is only the beginning.
I'm gonna make sure we get revenge for
what you did to us three hundred years ago!
I'm gonna make sure that everything you own,
every last bit of flesh and bone on your body,
every last bit of wealth that you have stored,
is crushed under my foot!
Part 1: Licentious Princess Enslaved
and Drowned in a Sea of White
Several Months Before.
You're completely surrounded.
You have nowhere to run, female pirate!
You still have that fight in you.
Being a queen is wasting your talents, Nie!
Take this!
Claus!
Don't butt into a duel!
Don't you know that's rude?!
What's going on? I'm being pushed back?
There'd be no point if the Queen died here now.
That was amazing.
Your Grace, please inform everyone of our victory!
Of course. Hear me, pirates!
Your leader, Olivia, has been defeated by our Royal Navy!
Surrender yourselves now and cease any useless struggle!
Allow me to express my gratitude again, Claus.
If you hadn't been there, I would've died.
Think nothing of it. I merely fulfilled
my duty as the general of the fleet.
Please lend me your strength from here
on out as well. I will be counting on you, Claus.
You really are quite taken by Claus, aren't you, onee-sama?
I-Iris?
She's always talking my ear off about you.
H-Hey!
I'm not really... I'm not talking about
him with those kinds of feelings.
Yes, float in your fragile bubble of happiness for now.
You're all nothing but filthy traitors!
By the way, how goes the investigation
of Olivia and her crew?
Well. I've left it in the capable
hands of my subordinates.
It is but a matter of time.
So even pirates can end up like this? You look pathetic.
Ruiri, you bitch! You were in cohorts with that man?!
That's right. I told him the most likely route
that you would choose to sail on. It was all me.
In order for us to take control of the country,
we needed to eliminate our biggest threat: your pirate fleet.
What did you do to my crew?!
Did you...
Oh no, they're very much alive.
They're in the dungeon below here. I'll let you meet them.
My crew! You're all gonna die!
I'm gonna fucking kill every last one of you!
You have quite the spirit, but I wonder how long
that'll last for? You're a loser, you know that?
You're calling me a loser?!
I'll be sure to drill that fact into your body.
Come on now. Moan for me, Olivia!
I've never seen you look so beautiful.
You're turning me on.
You're lookin' good, Olivia.
I knew you were behind this!
That was a better reaction than I had imagined.
Is this because you were originally a prostitute?
Shut up! We're not prostitutes anymore!
If you're gonna rape me, do it already!
I swear I won't lose to your shitty cock!
Okay then. Let's have some fun with this hole over here.
It looks like this is your first time doing it with your ass.
You piece of shit! Take it out!
You're gonna rip it! You're gonna rip it apart!
It's so tight! Does doing it in the ass really feel that good?
Shut up! Fuck off!
I'll let you feel the ultimate pleasure now.
Do it!
Oh my, are you sure this doesn't feel good for you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
What an incredibly dirty slut you are.
I'm gonna cum in your ass! Take it all in!
Oh, dear. Did it feel so good that you peed yourself?
Look, her asshole is wide open.
I'm next!
I can't wait any longer!
All right, boys! Do what you will with her.
Isn't that great, you guys?
With this, the pirate problem has mostly been dealt with.
It's finally time for us to take the next step.
I'll teach you all a lesson you'll never forget!
What was that?
Don't make any sudden moves, Queen.
My deepest apologies, Your Grace. I let my guard down.
Claus!
You're gonna follow our every order, you got that?
Cowards!
How did this happen?
How did pirates infiltrate our ports?
Hey! Throw away your weapon!
Isn't this guy your precious subordinate?
I understand. We'll drop our weapons, so don't harm Claus!
Okay, then. We have no more use for you!
Claus? You're safe now. Are you hurt?
Don't move or else the Queen's head will roll.
Claus, what are you doing?!
I get it now. You were actually working with them and
only pretended to be held captive, isn't that right, Claus?
Sorry to tell you, but my name isn't Claus.
My name is Vanclad. I'm a descendant
of the greatest pirate who ever lived.
Vanclad?
Instead of worrying about who I am,
you should worry about your own safety!
We pulled this off without a hitch, boss!
We've had a terrible time thanks to you pirate hunters!
We'll be sure to show you our deepest gratitude,
along with the former princess.
She has such a hot body!
Stop! All of you, stop this at once!
No! No! No!
Come on, move your hips more!
O-Onee-sama?!
Don't look at me! Don't look at this
shameful display of my body!
Please forgive me, Mireille-sama. I'm gonna cum!
Aren't you quite the quickie?
You pieces of trash!
I'm going to cum!
This is terrible. Please, stop!
Well, in that case, how about we have you play with us?
Stop! I'll take you all on, so don't lay a finger on Iris!
What are you saying?
You still have a lot more men to entertain!
I'm cumming!
No!
Please, stop! Don't do something this cruel!
Give it up.
You losers will lose everything.
Stop!
No matter how much you scream,
no one will come to save you now!
It hurts! It hurts so much! Please save me, Mireille!
It's going so deep!
It hurts!
This is my first time! How can you be so cruel?!
Iris! Stop! Please, stop!
We've just started!
Fucking switch with me already!
You're getting even wetter inside!
Are you sure you're not enjoying this?
Don't make such heinous accusations!
You're getting even tighter. I'm gonna cum!
Don't cum inside!
I'd feel bad just using your pussy, so let's use that!
Drink it all up! That's high quality shit right there!
It's something that comes out of
a woman's ass no matter who they are!
It just keeps going inside!
This is great! It's getting tighter!
So you're finally starting to feel good?
What a dirty princess you are!
No! No! That's not true!
You're wrong! Wrong! I... No! No!
I think you have more talent as a prostitute than a ruler!
I'd love to train you!
Stop!
Why are you doing these cruel things?
Do we need any reason to get back
at the people who hunted us down?
You're going to have a nice and healthy pirate baby!
No! Stop! Don't cum inside! No!
You're going to be our sex slave from now on.
I'm cumming!
No!
Take all of my cum!
It's going all the way into your womb.
The fun's just getting started.
If you really wanna protect the princess
that much, then make me cum already!
Mireille-sama, Mireille-sama! If you move like that, I'll...
Hurry up and finish!
That's not how you ask.
I thought I told you how to ask.
Please, cum! I want it deep inside me!
Yeah, yeah! Just like that!
This is so embarrassing.
My body and my pussy are getting hotter!
You fucking pervert!
No! No! I'm not a pervert!
You're so hot! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Me, too!
It's sucking me! If you squeeze
that hard on me, I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
No! No more!
I'm gonna cum inside your mouth! Take it all in!
Drink it up!
It smells like some wild beast.
It makes me want to vomit.
I think I'm gonna cum again.
This is amazing! I can't stop!
If she keeps squeezing on me,
I think I can keep cumming forever!
You're such a big pervert!
Mireille-sama, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum in your ass, Mireille-sama!
I'm cumming!
Me, too!
No!
Take my cum!
Okay, who's next?
Me!
No, me!
No, it's gotta be me!
No!
No! Please, stop!
Come on, take it!
No, stop hitting my butt!
No! No!
Your pussy's getting even tighter!
It's coming! Something's coming!
Something weird is coming! No! No, don't!
I'm cumming!
No!
No! No!
Everything I have is coming out!
What's up with this bitch?
She's suddenly so obedient.
Her entire body's so wet. She's so slimy.
This is too good! I'm gonna cum!
So hot!
There's so much semen.
I'm cumming!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
It's so tight deep inside!
So tight!
I'm gonna cum!
You took in so much semen that you're covered in it,
but there should be room for more!
I'm cumming!
Yeah, me too!
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
Good! It feels so good! It feels great!
These two still have some use to us.
You can use them whenever you feel like it.
Of course, as your own cum dumpster.
Hell yeah!
You're kidding. It's not... It's not over yet?
So tell me, who are you really?
Hm?
You're the man who overthrew not only the kingdom,
but also took down an entire fleet of pirates.
Of course I'd be interested in who you are.
I'm the great pirate, Vanclad. That is my true identity.
Vanclad? The legendary pirate who was hunted
and killed three hundred years ago?
Hunted and killed? Fuck that! I was betrayed!
I was betrayed by my own men. They stabbed me in
the back as soon as they got their hands on the treasure!
And that's the reason why
the Queen has met such a grim fate?
This is revenge. I will raze this country to the ground
and steal everything it has from its ashes.
I'm gonna destroy everything!
So does that make you a ghost
from three hundred years ago?
That's quite the amusing joke.
She doesn't believe me? Well, that's fine.
But don't forget, I said I'd destroy everything.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: kaitou
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч