I'm going first!
Please! Just cum!
If you don't, onee-sama will...
That's it! Just like that!
I'm cumming!
It's so thick!
Here you go, Princess!
Here comes the next load!
That's right. I have to do this.
I have to make all these dicks cum!
It's so hot... My body is on fire!
– Oh my god, your hard thing is in my pussy!
– This is too rough!
It's going so deep inside!
It's swelling up inside me and getting even bigger!
I'm going to break!
My pussy, my ass... They're going to break!
This is just too good!
I'm cumming inside!
Take my cum!
There's so much again...
I'm cumming!
Didn't I just make them cum?!
I need to deepthroat them and make
them cum quickly, otherwise...
My body's so hot right now! What's happened to me?!
They let out so much cum again!
I'm starting to feel strange...
It feels like it's about to burst.
I can't wait anymore!
Hey, me too!
Me too!
There are so many! There's no end to them!
– Please cum with my face!
– Take my cum!
O-Okay!
His dick's cum is tike gel!
Hurry the hell up!
I-I will! I will!
That's good.
Make sure you get every last drop!
No!!
There's so much...
Semen is so dirty!
I'm getting so wet! Wait, I can't! I can't, but...
I'm cumming!
No!
Me too! Me too!
Stop!
This is great.
Fuck her hard!
We're just about to enter the climax!
Mashou no Nie 3
Part 2 - Subjugated Princesses Drowned in the Murky Sea
Everyone to your posts!
Captain, cannons are ready to fire!
Bombard the coastline!
Aim, fire!
Fire!
Anyone?!
Is anyone here?!
Where are you, Adam?!
Seems like all of your friends ran away.
Guess it's over for you, Ruiri.
Klaus?! How...
You see, I don't only want to conquer
the empire. I want it all. Everything.
That includes you, too.
Adam, perfect timing!
Destroy these men!
– So hot...
– Adam?
– Don't waste your time, Ruiri. He's been drugged?
– So hot...
I-Is that...
It's the same aphrodisiac you've been using.
You're not supposed to drink that.
You're supposed to boil a small amount and inhale it.
Ruiri. I want!
– Want!
– Adam, listen to me!
Stop! Don't come closer!
Stop!
– Let me go! No! Don't!
– Look at him, licking you like an animal!
No!
I wonder how aroused he is after drinking all of that aphrodisiac.
– Ruiri! Inside want!
– Stop!
– There's no way something that big would fit inside me!
– Ruiri! Inside want!
It hurts! Stop!
Ruiri! Inside!
Inside!
S-Stop!
S-Stop you're going to tear it apart!
I-It's gonna tear!
Ruiri pussy! Good!
My entire body feels like it's being turned inside out!
I'm dying! I'm gonna die!
– Cumming!
– No! Anything but that!
Don't!
His semen is pumping into me...
Ruiri! I still cum!
I strong!
You're kidding! You haven't had enough yet?!
Coming!
– Fool! You really think a monster like him would be done so soon?
– No! Stop! Please, stop! No more!
– Amazing!
Me cum more! More! More!
Serves you right.
– How does it feel to be torn apart by the
people you stepped on and spat on?
– No! No! No!
– How does it feel to be torn apart by the
people you stepped on and spat on?
– This is going to kill me!
– I'm cumming! Ruiri!
– Don't do it! Forgive me!
No!
Me done.
I've never seen anything like that in my entire life.
Oh, no. I'm not letting you die just yet, Ruiri.
The next stage starts right now!
Citizens of Austria, feast your eyes upon this sight!
These fiends allowed our country to be taken over by pirates!
The despicable royal family!
Even though her highness was the mastermind,
she is but a woman.
There does not exist a world in which she
could overcome the power of men!
How could frail creatures like them protect this country?!
As your king, I say:
From now, this country will be reborn into one
ruled by pirates, where the strong thrive!
The strong can obtain anything they want!
This is our country's new providence!
My deepest apologies, your highness.
I have such respect for you, and yet...
Don't fret over this.
I won't lose.
If it's to protect everyone, this shame is nothing...
Your highness, please forgive me!
– Yeah, yeah! Just like that!
– You bastard! Have you no shame?!
– Don't hold back, or I'll beat you senseless!
It's growing bigger inside my pussy and ass!
– Your highness! I'm cumming!
– It's getting bigger inside me!
I feel like I'm being sucked dry!
I'm cumming again!
She's still so tight!
Cumming!
I can't get enough.
I'm cumming!
You don't get time to rest!
You got a line waitin'!
Use your ass to make all these soldiers feel good!
All of you?! There's no way...
Please! Please let me go to the bathroom!
Stop! It's gonna come out! It's coming out!
What's gonna come out? Spell it out for us!
I need to go to the bathroom!
Come on! Say it!
I'm gonna poop! I'm gonna poop! Please, let me go!
Fine, whatever.
After you satisfy me, I'll let you go!
It's really gonna come out!
So dirty!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Take it down your throat!
Shit, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Alright, let's take five.
Yeah.
Can I go next?
Sure, whatever.
I need to go! Let me go to the bathroom!
Holy crap! My dick feels like it's gonna melt!
Feels good for you too, doesn't it, missy?!
Why don't you show everyone what your dirty asshole looks like?
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming into your pussy!
– My hips... They won't stop moving! I'm cumming!
– So fucking wet!
You sure know how to suck dick, missy!
You're so tight and wet!
I'm cumming inside!
I'm cumming deep in your throat!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Drink it all up!
– Don't look at me!
– Blow it out your ass!
Holy shit!
It's poopy time, Princess!
Poop in front of all these people!
That's not where...
– Take a look, everyone!
– If you keep doing it like that, I'm gonna...
– Let's have some fun!
No! Stop!
Stop!!
Stop! My body feels so weak!
No! No!!
Poop already, you little... You little...
All right, switch it up! Keep it going!
I'm cumming!
You're kidding, right?
Hurry up and switch already!
Holy... I'm gonna cum!
It just feels too good...
Let me do the finishing touches!
Please, take this offering, Princess!
Shit! She's sucking me in!
Get off! Let me show you how it's done!
I'm gonna cum on her lewd face!
I can't...
I'm cumming!
No, stop!
Eight silver coins to whoever fucks her
hard enough that she shits herself!
I'm in!
Let's do this!
– I'm gonna cum from her armpit!
– I'm being watched. Everyone's going to see me poop.
Coming!
They're looking at all my embarrassing parts!
You're pretty tough.
So tough.
Please don't look at me!
Is it time?!
Here it is! What we've all been waiting for!
How's that?!
Feels good after holding it in for so long, doesn't it?
Just look at all that!
Who made her poop?
I did!
Don't you mean me?
I-I pooped in front of everyone.
That's a good expression you're wearing.
We're going to have a little competition to see
which one of you makes more people cum.
How did this happen to me?!
Come on, you're not gonna make me cum like that.
This one's taking two at once!
I don't want to share with you!
Move your hips!
I can't breathe!
I'm cumming!
Oh god, it keeps going deeper!
Me too!
No! No! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming...
Come on, let me have my turn already!
I'm cumming!
No! No! It feels so good!
I don't want to cum, but...
I can't hold on anymore!
I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!
Hey, what happened to the competition?
Lost track!
You...
What the hell?!
No! What is this?! Stop!
I'm the ocean's god!
You better make me feel good!
This is seriously amazing!
Oh my...
So good! I'm cumming!
Double penetration?!
I've never seen that before!
Holy crap.
No! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
It hurts! Please, stop!
No more! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Hey, the Kraken is coming up!
Do your best!
I love the Kraken!
No more!
This is too much!!
My boobs and pussy are going to make me cum!
My milk is coming!
No! I'm cumming!
My nipples are cumming!
No!
Cum! Give me your sloppy cum!
Cum! Cum!!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
Give it to me! Pour your semen in me!
I'm cumming again!
Take it all in!
I'm cumming! No!!
I will make this country, my pirate country, even better!
I'm going to use you all as tools to achieve that!
Now lose yourself!
– Let yourself go completely, until there's
nothing left to hold on to!
– Something amazing is coming!
– Let yourself go completely, until there's
nothing left to hold on to!
– Something amazing is coming!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч