Let's go, Yuu-kun!
Yuuji, your necktie is hanging too long.
Take care!
I'm Tsubakihara Yuuji.
I am a particularly normal student.
I live together with these
twin sisters due to some reason.
You went out earlier than usual today. Good job!
Don't pet me.
It'll help if you'll always be like this.
Nina, even you are telling me that...
Nina-senpai, good morning!
Good morning.
Yuna-san, good morning!
Good morning...
Stop showing off every day, harem jerk!
I am childhood friends with these twins.
The older twin Yuna is physically intimate
only to me, her childhood friend.
She's extremely shy and everyone at school calls her as
"a flower beyond reach" or something like that.
The younger twin Nina is a prodigy in sports.
She is kind, outgoing, has lots
of friends, and is smart as well.
When my parents passed away,
I was taken in by the Tsubakihara
family where the twin sisters are.
It's alright. You won't be alone, Yuu-chan.
We'll be families from today onwards.
And that's how my life with them under
the same roof began. And nowadays...
You're barely on time.
My relationship with them is fine as far as I know.
Yuu-kun, good morning!
Nee-san, put your desks apart.
Huh? It should be fine.
Nina-chan, you meanie!
I can't choose either one of them, and I won't.
I rather like this kind of relationship we have now.
Master Piece The Animation!
Yuna isn't here?
I still have club activities so find
her then go home without me.
Yeah, yeah.
Jeez... Where did Yuna go?
I like you!
Tsubakihara-san, please go out with me!
What a timing I have.
Well, maybe this is a usual occurrence.
I-I'm sorry.
You see, I...
She'll just reject him in the end, right?
I am in love with someone else.
Yuna loves someone?
He's not in the same school. He's not a family.
He is my first love, who I cherish a lot up until now.
That is why... I'm sorry.
I can't go out with you.
Who's the one she loves?
Huh... What am I getting upset for?
Oh... I see...
Am I in love with Yuna?
Brooding about it is pointless.
Yuna, I'm coming in.
Okay~!
Huh?
Yuu-kun! Welcome home.
S-Sorry!
It's just you so it should be fine.
Huh?! That's not it.
I'll be off to somewhere so you three should take care of your dinner.
Mira-san isn't here, so I was about
to ask what to do for dinner.
I never meant to peep!
Whoa!
Yuu-kun?!
Yuu-kun, are you really alright?
I told you I am.
Moreover... Are you okay with doing this
when you already love someone?
Were you listening earlier?
I see, so you were thinking about that.
Well, yeah...
I won't tell you about it so easily, though.
First hint: He is a boy.
I know that.
Second hint: We meet face-to-face every day.
You said that he isn't from the same school...
Sorry, it's too hard for me to figure out.
Hmmmp!
Then, here is the last hint:
That person is called Enomoto-kun.
Huh?
But we have the same surname now.
Does that mean...
That's why starting today...
Please let me love you, Tsubakihara Yuuji.
I never really intended to tell you about it.
I didn't want to tell you how I feel
just to end up being hated.
Why are you saying that now?
There's no way that I'll end up hating you, Yuna!
Yuna, I'm...
No!
I'll tell you something good.
When a woman invites a man inside her room...
It is a go-ahead signal.
What...
And besides...
Yuu-kun, you've been staring
at my chest for a while now.
Th-That's...
Your thing down here seems
to be aware of it, though.
You may do as you wish, Yuu-kun.
They all belong to you, after all.
They're all mine...
That's right, all of these!
How are they? Aren't they soft?
That's too sudden... No way!
You're licking my nipple...
You're like a baby, Yuu-kun!
Hey... That's... Wait!
Gosh... Yuu-kun...
You're too excited!
S-Sorry...
Hey, Yuna?
I'll make you feel good this time.
No way, it's dirty...
That's not true.
Wow...
It became so hot and hard.
Yuu-kun is a grown-up man now.
Where did you learn that?
Well, you see...
I saw it from the porn book under your bed!
What...
I learned a lot and it's all thanks to it.
Look, I know about this too!
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Yuu-kun, your thing...
It's going wild in my chest!
If you'll keep going rough like that, I'm gonna...
Is it gonna come out?
It's okay, Yuu-kun!
Shoot your sperm out! Do it anywhere you want!
Spray lots of it on me!
You came a lot!
S-Sorry...
Didn't I say to do as you wish?
Whoops... Alright, then...
No, wait...
Yuna, is this really okay?
Yeah, that's because...
I've been wanting to be one
with you all this time, Yuu-kun.
Please, my Prince Charming...
I want you to be my first man.
Yuna, don't force yourself.
It's alright.
Just a little bit more and it'll go in!
Are you really alright?
I'm alright...
It doesn't hurt as much as I thought...
L-Let's go on...
My belly is filled with your thing inside!
Wow!
Yuu-kun, your thing feels hot and hard!
Right there!
No way, if you start going so intense...
No...
I can feel it... Something's coming!
No—!
Yuu-kun, you forced yourself too much on me...
I-I'm sorry!
But that's... because I got horny.
I see... I made you horny...
I'm glad!
Show me lots of your embarrassing moments!
Like hell I will!
This is it! This is amazing!
You're violently stirring me deep inside!
Yuna, I'm already about to...
Are you gonna come? Then, do it inside!
I want it inside me!
Yuna!
It's alright... That's because...
I love you so much, Yuu-kun!
I'm coming already!
There's so much flowing inside me!
Yuu-kun...
I love you...
She fell asleep...
Jeez...
No way...
Nee-san and Yuuji...
Master Piece!
Tsubakihara Nina:
A perfect woman with an attractive
face and figure, brawn and brains.
She's highly sociable too, gaining
the trust of people around her.
Naturally, she treats me who lives with her as family.
Women's Track and Field Club
Or that's how it's supposed to be...
Who would've thought that in a place like this...
Yuuji... D-Do it already!
If you won't hurry up and do it, someone will be here!
Hey, didn't you say that
you'll do anything I tell you?
Why are you making me massage your breasts?
It's your fault, Yuuji!
You suddenly walked in while I'm changing!
No... You told me to go here in your clubroom
immediately. I didn't do that on purpose—
You say that, but you're happily moving your hands.
What is that supposed to mean?
Dammit!
Other club members are just outside.
You're done for if I scream right now.
Well, you don't have any choice
but to listen to me. Am I right?
No, don't do that!
Hey... Wait, Yuuji!
You're being rough all of a sudden!
You're the one who told me to do it, Nina.
Th-That right, but...
Hey, timeout!
I'm all good down here.
So, umm... Go all the way...
Does that mean...
Don't keep making a girl embarrass herself...
Dummy...
Then, I'll put it inside.
Yuuji's thing is going inside my body!
It went inside!
Nina, are you sure you're alright?
I'm alright!
You promised to see this
through the end, didn't you?
Then, I'll at least do this for you...
My nipples...
Hey, you are being too loud!
Even if you say that...
Don't tell me that you like this kind of thrill.
You idiot! There's no way that I do!
What's this? Should sex feel this incredible?
Nina, I'm almost there...
Then shoot it inside me!
What is this sensation?
It feels like I'm going somewhere else!
I-I'm gonna come!
Me too, I'm coming!
Oh no, I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
Women's Track and Field Club
Hey, did you call me over just for this?
Sh-Shut up!
I want to try doing it too, just like nee-san.
Ugh... So you saw us.
Even though I told you to shoot it inside me...
Oh yeah... Are you doing club activities
all the time wearing only that?
Huh?
There's no way that I do, of course!
Yuuji, you idiot! You're so dense!
Ouch!
Master Piece.
When we were little, Yuuji and I were closer.
And I did love him.
But I'm sure that love is familial.
When I started to see Yuuji
as a man, it was already too late.
I gradually distanced myself from them.
Nee-san and Yuuji are dating now.
But even so...
I am...
Uhh... There's no point muttering about it.
Hnnngh!
Oh... I'm sorry, nee-san. So, you were inside.
I want to talk to you so I'm going in as well.
Hey...
Nee-san, umm...
What do you like about Yuuji?
He's more reliable now than he used to be,
and his kindness hasn't changed.
However, he gets attracted to every girl around.
Even at that time...
I am such a bad girl...
Nee-san, are you listening?
At least say something back!
I'm talking about something serious here, so why are you ignori...
Uhh... Yuu...
Huh, Nina-chan?
Are you alright?
I-I'm alright!
If you were here, just say so! Pervert!
I just couldn't speak up in this kind of situation.
So, nee-san... What's the matter?
Hmm, I just thought that we should
bathe together once in a while.
W-Wait!
See, I want to have the bathe by myself tonight!
How about doing your homework first?
It's already done.
I had Yuu-kun help me!
O-Oh... I see...
What are you getting big for?
Isn't that because you're here with me naked?
He got this big from seeing my naked body?
Nina-chan, you should ask Yuu-kun
if you need some help as well!
He's really dependable!
R-Really?
That pervy and dense guy?
Hey... She's gonna find out
if you keep moving that much!
Jeez... I know that we shouldn't be doing this anymore...
I decided to give up and end it there
after that one time, and yet...
Well, you can do everything...
Oh, I should go in as well
since we're talking this much.
My voice will come out!
It went inside!
Even though we shouldn't be going further...
Nina-chan, what's the matter?
Wait... No, don't!
I can't help craving for it!
Nee-san is right next to us, and yet...
I'm coming from being creampied!
No—!
Y-You hate bathing with me that much?
No, it's just that...
I'm just kidding! I'll be taking mine later, then.
I did it again with Yuuji...
But tonight, it was him who yearned for me instead.
Nina?
No, I can't think about anything else...
...aside from the fact that I want him right now!
If it isn't like that... If it isn't the same as nee-san's...
I'll never be satisfied!
Forgive me, nee-san.
Your first experience that you
haven't given to nee-san yet...
Give it to me!
You never tried it here before, right?
Will you be alright?
It's alright so hurry!
O-Okay.
It went inside!
I-It's so tight!
It's inside a place where nee-san haven't let him in yet.
It's the same as my first time.
I wonder if it doesn't hurt when
done with someone you love.
Are you alright?
You're so dense!
Figure it out yourself already
without having to ask every time.
Dummy.
Nina!
This feels amazing!
You can move any way you want to!
I think I like having it inside this hole better!
My insides are gonna be able to take your shape,
so give it to me hard!
It's going deep inside!
I want him to feel good from me alone!
You might be in love with nee-san,
but that doesn't matter!
I want Yuuji all by myself!
Th-That's why...
I'll do my own ways to sway you towards me!
Nina... Nina!
Feel so good that you won't be able
to think about anything else!
Yuuji, it looks like you're almost there.
Come! Come!
I want you to look only at me!
Let me memorize your sensation inside me!
It might be too late to say this,
but I want to tell you that...
Nina!
I love you—!
Come on, Yuuji. Go out before someone sees you.
Nina-chan, are you done?
Huh, Yuu-kun?
Oh... This is, well...
I was still inside, so I had him wait here.
Is that so?
Then we should take a bath together, Yuu-kun!
H-Hey, Yuna...
I should keep it a secret from nee-san.
No, that's not right.
If I'll keep hiding it, things will
keep going on as usual!
Don't run away from this!
I'm not holding myself back any more!
I won't lose against you, nee-san!
Huh?!
Nina-chan is scary! Help me, Yuu-kun!
Oh my, are you all having fun bathing together?
Then, I'll join in too!
Mom's the same as her daughter!
You're not allowed to, mom!
Why not?
Yuu-kun...
Like I'm one to talk...
Master Piece!
Private reservations are the best!
My whole day's worth of fatigue is fading away!
Huh?
M-Mira-san, why?
Why, you ask?
Isn't it obvious that I'm here to take a bath?
And-be-sides,
I should be physically intimate with
my beloved son from time to time.
Gosh, you should've invited me
if you were going here.
That's, well...
She is Mira-san.
She's a mother figure to me.
I owe her for taking me in when my parents passed away.
That's why I need to calm myself down.
Hmm?
It feels so wrong to lust after your own mother!
O-Oh yeah, where are those two right now?
Hmm... They're sound asleep.
so I came here without waking them up.
What is it, Yuu-chan? You keep staring at me.
It's not like an unusual thing to see me naked.
Umm... You see...
I'm just thinking that you'll get chilly out there...
You're right...
Then...
Huh?
I'll take up on your offer.
Right here...
Ah... Huh? Where are you sitting on?
It's physical intimacy.
Come on, Yuu-chan.
Make sure to dip in up to your shoulders, okay?
Your face is beet red.
Are you feeling conscious, after all?
Y-You're just seeing things!
Is that so?
I think somethings "hitting" me down here, though.
Th-This is, umm... The spring water
"hitting" from staying too long...
I'll be going out first, then...
Wait.
Hey, Yuu-chan, what is the meaning of this?
You got a stiffy from mom.
You're such a bad boy.
Y-You're wrong...
Oh my, am I?
I think that it's gradually getting bigger, though.
That's because you're stroking it, Mira-san!
Are you still saying that?
Looks like I need to give this lying
Yuu-chan a bit of harsh punishment.
Huh? Mira-san, what are you doing?
Can't you see it yourself?
I'm rubbing your huge thing using my armpit.
This is a punishment, so it won't make sense
to make you feel good the normal way.
Could it be that my armpit makes you feel good?
You feel good regardless of where you rub it into.
You're such a pervert, Yuu-chan!
P-Please stop!
Don't tell me that you didn't notice.
There's nothing to stop me from.
You're the one moving your hips.
Perhaps you really are a pervert.
This is...
What's up with that frail voice?
I wonder if you reached your limit now.
Wow...
My armpit is sloppy with your fluids, Yuu-chan...
Wow, your thing looks like it's gonna burst!
You can squirt it out without holding back.
Don't think about anything else and keep rubbing it!
Keep rubbing it a lot in my armpit!
Mira-san, I'm about to...
It's alright since you're such a pervert, Yuu-chan!
Squirt it into my armpit!
Shoot a lot of it out!
There's plenty of semen coming out!
This is such a huge amount.
I might actually get knocked up if you
shot this much in my lower mouth...
Hey, Yuu-chan...
Since we already went this far,
let's do something even better.
What's wrong?
I-I feel dizzy...
My, my... I might have teased you a little too much!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization