Today is our grand school festival.
It's about to start, so hurry up and decide!
I thought that we already prepared everything...
Yuu-kun!
Well, I don't really...
Yuuji!
Which one will you choose?
But the last hurdle that remains is the biggest one.
Master Piece The Animation!
Angel Cafe: 16 votes                  Demon Cafe: 16 votes
It started from our discussion of plans for the festival.
Topic: Concerning our activity for the school festival
Angel Cafe: 16 votes                  Demon Cafe: 16 votes
Uhh... Our class should settle
on which activity we should do...
Please, all of you, listen to me...
Especially you two, Tsubakihara sisters!
Tsubakihara Yuna is the older twin. Men find it hard
to approach her. "A flower beyond reach" indeed.
Ohh, Nina-chan...
Didn't you say not to put our desks
together side by side?
Tsubakihara Nina is the younger one.
She's a perfect woman with both brawn and brains.
N-Not really...
It's not officially in school rules so it's fine!
It can't be helped.
Then, we'll decide whether we'll do
an angel or demon cafe by popular vote.
The prize for the winning team...
..will be Yuuji!
Huh?
There's no way that I'll agree with that!
Angel Cafe: 16 votes                  Demon Cafe: 16 votes
And I'd also like to request the Tsubakihara sisters
as leaders of their respective teams.
I'll never lose!
Hey, don't I have a say in this?
Let's settle this, nee-san!
The fact that this dispute was but a mere
prologue was beyond me back then.
Come in!
Demon Cafe
Welcome to the demon cafe!
Wh-What the hell are those outfits?!
Here's the menu!
Whoa?!
Umm, here's a hot towel.
Thank you for waiting!
Here, say aah...
B-Braless?!
Dear customer, right here as well.
Come and help yourself!
Huh?!
Tsubakihara-kun, the next one's this way!
Hey, I'm still...
Angel Cafe
Welcome home, master!
Nina!
W-Welcome home... M-Master...
H-How cute...
Don't run away.
S-So close...
Too bad, it's over now.
H-Here's your deluxe tofu pudding.
It's in the shape of my boobs.
Oh, what a waste...
I'll lick anything that dripped off you.
Here's your assorted dessert!
These are all edible, so you can't have any leftovers!
A-All of them!
If that's so, then I'll help myself!
Yuuji...
Yuu-kun...
Come here
for a moment...
Infirmary
Well, that really was just, you know...
Weren't you having so much fun back there?
You were going for one girl after another.
I never knew that you're that kind of man, Yuu-kun.
Wait, listen to what I'm saying...
I don't want to hear any excuses!
Your interrogation starts here!
Keeping anything from us will be pointless!
Hey!
Alright, first question...
Which girl in the demon cafe is your favorite?
Y-you, Yuna-san.
Good job on being honest!
Th-Then, for your second question...
How about in the angel cafe?
That would be... you, Nina, I guess...
O-Ohh... I see...
Yuu-kun, you're a two-timer...
Then, for the third question...
Which one between an angel
and a demon do you like?
Th-That's...
I love both, so there's no way that I can choose one!
If Yuu-kun can't choose,
then should we decide this by ourselves?
By ourselves?
The one who makes Yuu-kun come first wins.
N-Nee-san! Hogging him isn't fair!
Me too...
I'll do lots of these for you!
This is bad!
It feels too good!
Yuu-kun, don't you really love being stroked by tits?
I never knew that an upright girl like you
is actually this lewd, Nina-chan!
You too, nee-san! You don't even have
a bit of gracefulness left right now!
The tip got so hard...
I'm fine with it if that makes Yuu-kun happy!
Hey, Yuu-kun! Whose tits feel better?
Whose tits? Both of yours are about the same...
They can't be entirely the same! Look, mine's better!
If you do it that much, I'm gonna...
There's so much of Yuu-kun's stuff!
This one doesn't count...
I'll show you just how much I love Yuu-kun.
Me too... I want Yuuji to know my feelings for him!
Wait... Hey...
Alright then, fourth question!
Who will you do it with, an angel or a demon?
Nina will be first!
Are you fine with me?
I'm not feminine compared to nee-san!
That's not true!
I consider you as a woman!
Saying something like that now isn't fair!
Whether you're being aloof or being upfront
just like now, I love all of those about you!
Me too! I love you too, Yuuji!
Yuu-kun... Give it to me as well!
Yuna, that's your...
I thought that you might get tired from
using the same part every time,
so I trained to be able to take you in my ass!
I'm glad, but you didn't have
to push yourself that hard...
I didn't push myself that hard!
If it's for your sake,
I'll be able to do anything!
N-Nina-chan?!
Nee-san, I love you too after all...
That's why I want us three to...
No...
My nipples...
Yuna's insides got tighter than before!
I love you a lot too, Nina.
I can't choose one between you and Yuu-kun!
Nee-san, that's my...
Having a threesome is far better!
Me too!
Huh?
Both of you are precious to me!
That's why, Yuna and Nina,
I want both of you to be with me!
Are you fine with this, nee-san?
Won't I be a bother between you two?
You don't have to worry about it.
Even I feel the same as you.
Nee-san! Yuuji!
I love both of you as well!
And so, that's why...
L-Let's be together forever!
You two, I'm already...
Me too... Let's all do it together!
I'm coming—!
I'm out. I won't be able
to take even a single step...
Me too, let me take a short break...
I'm not allowed to talk to girls?
That's right.
That's because your cheating tendencies
won't get fixed unless we do that.
We'll be together from now on
and I'll look after him
so rest assured.
But that's...
You don't have
a problem with that,
am I right?
or do you?
Yes... But just a little should be...
Since Yuu-kun only learns things the hard way,
we have to punish him again today!
I agree!
Huh?!
Take care on the way!
After this, even more hardships await me...
...but that is a story for another time.
Hey, Tsubakihara-kun...
What's the meaning of this?
Jeez...
You got this huge...
You're being punished for tardiness
right now, you know?
Mira-san, that's because of what you're...
Shouldn't you call me senpai?
Our student play would be a waste...
That's because Mi...
...senpai, you're stimulating it.
You're putting the blame on others. You're a bad boy!
You still need more punishment.
It got bigger again!
Does it not matter where I rub it against?
That's not...
Your face looks listless.
Could it be that you're about to come?
You shouldn't. We're about
to do the real thing next.
Gosh, you're being too restless!
Don't be so reckless!
My butt is on fire!
Mira-senpai! I'm feeling
so good and I'm already...
It's alright... Unload all of your accumulated semen!
It's coming out!
He sprayed a lot of his hot semen on me!
Gosh, I'm all sticky now! I'll have to wash
and return it or my daughter will get angry.
Hey, Yuu-chan... How about
taking a bath together?
Oh?
How bad of me... I tend to overdo
it when I'm with Yuu-chan.
Hey, did you just see that?
Yeah, I did!
She's such a beauty!
Wanna try talking to her?
Thanks for waiting!
Oh, welcome back...
What do you think of this swimsuit?
I-It looks so fantastic...
Tsk! She's with her boyfriend.
I feel so envious!
Mira-san, you're too close.
That's because you're not looking at me at all...
I picked this up trying to match your preferences.
Come on, tell me what you think of it.
It's too provocative...
Umm, people around are looking here as well...
Jeez...
Come with me for a moment.
Hey... Mira-san?!
You won't have to worry
about people's gazes here.
It doesn't mean that doing this is...
Won't we end up being stared at if we stayed there?
That's because you're very beautiful, Mira-san.
Very much that you ended up like this?
That's intense!
Someone might come here if we won't hurry
Mira-san's mouth is warm and it feels so good!
But I think I can still hold it in!
Oh my, you look relaxed.
Then...
Look!
That's... You're wearing nothing down there?
Did that pique your interest? If that's so...
There...
Check it out with your own eyes.
Y-You're not wearing anything down here!
Oh, Yuu-chan... What happened to
that calm composure earlier?
Come on, enough with the staring.
Make me feel good too!
You suddenly started licking me... You're daring!
Move it around more!
If you do me so hard,
I'll also start dripping!
That's making me feel so good
that I won't be able to suck you properly!
I-I'm already...
Alright, let's do it together!
Yuu-chan's fresh and hot essence is sloshing around!
What an amazing amount!
Mira-san, I'm still...
Oh no! Don't panic.
We're lodging in here today, so the rest will be...
...later tonight, okay?
Hello? What's the matter?
Yuuji, is mom home?
Yeah, she's right next to me.
She's soundly sleeping.
Ugh... Just let her be, then.
Don't do anything weird!
Huh?! Of course I'll...
...never do that.
Not there...
Is she not wearing a bra?
You might not know this, but mom...
Gosh, how annoying...
Hoah!
...takes longer to fully wake up.
Tell me that sooner!
Oh, Yuu-chan...
You're still a baby no matter
how much time passes.
I-I'll be careful.
By the way, don't you have something to do?
Oh, yeah...
Do you want to have curry for dinner?
Yuu-chan, are you feeling good?
Yes...
Whoops...
I got horny as well...
Do you prefer putting cheese in it?
Want to put it in? It's piping hot and mushy!
I want it in... Maybe...
Which one will it be?
Jeez, do what you want.
Uhh... Don't complain to me later.
Bye!
So, I can do what I want.
Well then...
Huh? But that's... your ass?
I feel like doing it here today.
It went in!
Mira-san, you're squeezing me too hard!
Hey, hang in there!
Are you already about to come?
You won't be able to satisfy me if you're like that.
Like I'll take that lying down!
So you can do it if you put in some effort.
Harder... Do it harder and make a mess of me!
Oh no!
Mira-san...
Yuu-chan, you're ravishing my tits!
You're going rough on them!
No... You'll tear my nipples off!
You got even bigger inside me...
You're feeling good even when it's in my ass, right?
You too, Mira-san! You're not one to talk
when you're dripping on the floor!
But that's...
If you keep thrusting that hard in me, I'll squirt...
My pee will leak!
Ah! Right there!
You'll really make me come!
I'm about to come already!
Alright, dump your semen in my ass!
I'm coming as well!
C-Coming!
Yuu-chan's hot semen is pouring deep into me!
No, it's spilling out!
You don't remember?
Hmm...
Mostly?
So we did it with my ass, huh?
It kinda feels itchy down there.
You seem to be able to do
those things while half asleep.
I see!
It means that only you managed
to keep some good memories...
That was all your doing in the first place...
Alright!
Let's do it one more time
to make me remember about it.
M-Mira-san, stop doing that here!
Nope.
More importantly, shouldn't you
keep your voice down?
If anyone were to find us here...
I wonder what will happen.
By the way, Yuu-chan...
Why are you here today?
I wanted to go to the gym...
Right... Then, why did we end up like this?
That's because...
Come on, try to be honest.
When I saw you in a swimsuit, I just...
You should've said that from the start,
Mr. Pervert who gets horny
regardless of where he is.
You already got this big.
That's because you're flaunting them!
Oh? Maybe this bad boy who talks back to me
needs to be punished again.
We're about to close down.
O-Oh my! I-I'm sorry!
I was doing slow stretches.
Oh no, I should be the one apologizing
for disturbing your cool-down exercise.
Well then...
Okay!
No!
Ma'am?
It's nothing!
I just slipped on the floor.
I'm okay!
No, Yuu-chan...
Not now!
I can't hold myself back from this!
A-Alright, I'll excuse myself.
No...
Gosh, didn't I say no?
That really was a close call.
I'm sorry.
You're such a hopeless boy.
Then, in exchange for being forgiven...
...give all of it to me inside.
B-But...
Don't worry about it. Shoot all of it in me!
I won't forgive you otherwise.
Just like this? Can I really...
I-It's okay, just like this...
Inside me! Pour it all inside me!
Gosh, Yuu-chan... You came so much.
I'm sorry, I messed up your swimsuit.
Well, that's convenient for me...
Ah!
Mira-san, could it be that you can't swim?
Did you say something?
I'm asking if you can't sw—
What? I can't hear you?
Mira-san...
Jeez... Your're panting so heavily.
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm sorry...
I've been holding back since the party earlier.
It can't be helped...
It'd be bad if this gets wrinkled,
so come here and take it off.
Hold it here and pull them apart
Like this?
Make sure to pay close attention to your hands.
Oh! You're being too forceful, Yuu-chan...
Be more gentle, alright?
You don't have to rush.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay...
You keep looking there away from me.
Is something bothering you?
I'm naked right here, but you won't look at me.
You're making mom sad!
Or maybe you got tired of seeing me now.
I-It's not like that...
Or could it be that there's something
else that you want to take off me?
So, you noticed...
That's because you keep on looking at it, Yuu-chan.
I've already decided.
I'll take your ring off and we'll be together.
I see... But will you be fine with that?
If I'll take it off,
I won't be your mother anymore.
It's okay!
Mira-san, I...
...love you!
It's a kiss to seal that vow.
Hey, Yuuji!
Nina! Yuna!
Gosh! Mom's hogging all the fun. That's unfair!
Then, you two should join us.
Jeez, you even laid your hands on our mom!
So? Now who are you gonna do it with,
Yuu-chan?
Yuu-kun?
Yuuji?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji