Mayoiga (a.k.a. Mayohiga): An illusionary house that grants great wealth to lost travelers. "Mayoiga" also refers to the tales of those to whom the house appears.
One time when I was lost, I
found myself in that place.
But unlike travelers in the legends,
what I was granted wasn't wealth.
It was love and pleasure instead...
...as well as sexual services.
And now...
And now, once again I...
Natsuki-san
That was fun ♥
Let's celebrate once
you ace those exams!
Welcome!
Natsuki-san!
I found my way here again!
Isami-kun, welcome!
Natsuki-san!
Natsuki-san is so pretty, just like last time!
No, now she looks even more wonderful!
Pardon me, young man.
Could it be that you're Isami-kun,
the kid Natsuki likes?
I see. You're a real cutie!
One-Shota
You're Isami-kun, aren't you?
Today, how about you have a good time
with me instead of with Natsuki?
Her boobs looks amazing!
Hey!
Akiha, don't tease Isami-kun like that.
Tease?
I was just recommending the customer
an item from our menu.
Well, Isami-kun? Me or Natsuki,
who do you prefer?
Eh?
You can choose whichever onee-san you like.
Hey, Isami-kun, who do you prefer?
I... I...
I came here today to see Natsuki-san!
Natsuki-san
That was fun ♥
Let's celebrate once
you ace those exams!
We promised to meet once
I was done with my exams.
Isami-kun.
Oh, what a pity. I've been rejected.
It can't be helped.
We need to do as the customer wishes.
However...
If both Natsuki and I are with you,
there's no problem, right?
I figured you'd say that.
Well then, let's begin your special massage.
You must be tired from studying so hard.
We'll thoroughly soothe your body
and ease your stress now.
Isami-kun, you like it gentle, don't you?
Come to think of it, Natsuki-san did
mention this kind of service.
But then they're flashing what's
under their skirts. I'm getting...
From just a little rubbing, you're
already twitching down here.
A cute face and a naughty dick...
Is this where it itches?
We'll rub some medicine there for you.
You're shaking. Are you feeling cold?
Perhaps you need a tighter embrace?
I'm...
I'm going to cum!
You really came a lot.
The feeling of Isami-kun's small body
in my arms... it's been so long.
Oh, is that what you like?
He seems to be thoroughly enjoying this.
Shall we keep up the teamwork?
Isami-kun, you like breasts, don't you?
Cum as much as you want, OK?
Enjoy yourself.
Cum whenever you want to.
Isami-kun, are you going to cum again?
That's fine. Go ahead.
Cum! Cum for us!
Shall we proceed to the main dish?
May I go first?
It can't be helped.
This is my second time, so I'll allow it.
All right, here comes the real thing, young man.
I wonder just how many seconds
you I last inside my wet pussy.
If you can last a minute, I'll give you a reward.
Last three minutes, and I wouldn't
mind marrying you.
I'm joking. I'm joking.
And go! Start the clock!
It's warm inside me, isn't it.
You're really twitching.
You're really hanging in there, aren't you?
But I'm starting to really move now!
How is it? Does it feel good?
The bumpy texture of my vaginal walls
strokes you wonderfully, doesn't it?
A pussy like this is a Mayoiga cafe "exclusive".
Doesn't this exclusive service feel amazing?
Come on, don't be shy.
Isami-kun, you can cum, you know.
Don't be shy. Cum! Cum!
Cum! Cum!
What a pity. You lost.
Naughty kids who can't hold
back must be punished!
Now I'm going to milk you dry!
Over and over again,
I'm going to get you off using my
exquisite pussy, Isami-kun.
Isami-kun, I'm sorry.
I can't hold back either.
You can smell this, can't you?
Eat me out.
I can't see anything other than her pussy!
Isami-kun.
That's good. You're such a cutie. This feels so good!
Hey! Listen!
This anime has two heroines, you know.
W-What are you doing, Akiha?
Don't just pretend I'm not here!
Even though I'm right here, I feel ignored.
That got me annoyed, so I'm going to
embarrass you in front of Isami-kun!
S-Stop it!
I know all your weak points, Natsuki.
Look, she's twitching down here.
Just cum already. Give Isami-kun a close-up
of your pussy, and shower him with cum!
N-No!
If you tease my nipples like that...
What did you say? I won't understand
unless you finish your sentence.
Isami-kun!
I'm... I'm going to cum!
Isami-kun, sorry. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
My, how bold of you! You came
all over his cute, pure face!
You're not used to having someone
else make you cum, are you?
I wanted to keep my composure as a mature
onee-san, but you made me cum...
Come on, once you're inside her, shake your hips.
Doesn't it feel good to be inside
Natsuki's-pussy like this?
Come on, hang in there!
Are you OK being always on the receiving end?
Isami-kun, Natsuki-oneesan is getting off
to the feeling of your dick inside her.
Is-a-mi-kun!
It feels so good!
Oh my, so powerful all of a sudden!
You're trying so hard with your sensitive dick!
That's amazing! You really do like Natsuki!
Somehow I'm getting really turned on as well!
While you're sandwiched between us,
cum as many times as you please.
Let's all cum together, OK?
Like that! Give it to me deep inside!
Cum! Fill her with your cum!
Isami-kun, you're so lovable and cute.
Next time you come here, ask for me!
How shameless. I let you join this time
out of pity, so show some restraint!
Eh? But Isami's really taken a liking to me.
You're dropping the "-kun"?
We would have been just fine without you!
Shall we settle this by having sex
with him again to see who he prefers?
Bring it on! Even though it's obvious
that I'm going to win...
I hope I make it home in one piece...
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч