"Mayoiga." A place of legend deep in the mountains where it is rumored that those who visit will be rewarded with riches. A legend concerning those who visit that place.
Mayoiga.
I stumbled upon it once.
But unlike what the legend said, what
I was given was not riches, but...
Love and pleasure.
Sexual services.
And so...
And so, once again, I...
Welcome.
Natsuki-san! I was able to come here again!
Isami-kun, welcome back!
Natsuki-san!
She's just as beautiful as she was before!
No, she's even more beautiful!
Woah there. Sorry kid.
Are you maybe that kid Natsuki likes, Isami-kun?
I see why. You're pretty cute.
The ladies of Mayoiga
The ladies of Mayoiga.
You're Isami-kun, right?
How about you have fun with me today instead of Natsuki?
This lady's boobs are amazing!
Just a minute!
Akiha, stop putting Isami-kun on the spot like that.
What? I was only giving him a
recommending an item from our menu.
So how about it Isami-kun? Who
would you prefer, me or Natsuki?
Be honest. Choose the one you like more.
So Isami-kun, who do you prefer?
I came here to see Natuski-san today!
We promised to meet up again after I finished my tests.
Isami-kun...
Oh, what a shame. I got rejected.
I've got no choice, I guess. It's my job
to fulfill the request of our customers.
bashful
Alright, there's no problem if
we both play with you, is there?
I knew you'd suggest this.
Okay, we're going to start your special massage now.
We're going to loosen up your body
that's become so tense from studying.
You like it gentle, right, Isami-kun?
Now that I think about it, I think Natsuki-san
said something about this kind of service.
Oh really? Then I'll have to be sure to be thorough.
But I can see under both of
their skirts so easily, I'm gonna...
Don't tense up. Just relax, okay?
You're already getting hard just
from us touching you a little.
You may have a cute face, but you have a lewd dick.
Does it itch here, dear customer?
We're going to thoroughly rub the
medicine into you with our hands.
You're shaking. Are you cold?
Maybe we should get closer.
Stop!
I can't...
I'm gonna...
I'm...
You let out so much of your pleasure juice.
It's been so long since I could feel your
tiny body trembling through my fingers.
Oh? So that's what you like?
It looks like he enjoyed that, so
let's keep up the work together.
Isami-kun, you like boobs, right?
You can cum as much as you want, okay?
Take in the pleasure.
You can cum whenever you want.
Isami-kun, are you about to cum again?
That's fine. Come on.
Cum! Cum!
I think it's time to move on to the main dish.
Mind if I go first?
Oh, fine.
This is my second time, so I'll let you go first.
Alright then.
This is where the fun starts, kid.
I wonder how long you'll be able to last inside my hot pussy.
If you can last one minute, I'll give you a reward.
If you can last three minutes, I'll marry you if you want.
Just kidding. Just a joke.
Alright, start the timer.
It's really warm inside me, isn't it?
You're twitching so much inside me.
You're really trying to hold on, aren't you?
But I'm gonna start to move now!
How is it? Feel good?
Your dick's rubbing really easily
against the walls of my pussy, isn't it?
That's because of my vaginal fluid.
Does it feel good?
Come on. Come on!
You can cum whenever you want, Isami-kun.
Come on, cum!
Cum!
Cum! Cum!
Oh, what a shame.
Bad kids who can't hold it in get a punishment.
I'm gonna keep you cumming until you're empty.
I'm gonna keep using my amazing pussy
to keep you cumming, okay, Isami-kun?
Isami-kun... sorry.
I can't wait any longer.
You can tell just by smelling, can't you?
Lick it.
Natsuki-san's vagina is on my face!
Isami-kun! That's good. You're so cute.
You're really good at this.
Hey! Hey!!
Did you forget that I'm part of this too?
Wait, Akiha!
Don't ignore me!
I'm the one with the dick inside me so why
am I the one being pushed to the wayside?
I'm mad, so now I'm going to show
Isami-kun your embarrassing side.
No, stop!
I know all your weak spots really well.
Look closely. She's twitching, isn't she?
Come on, cum!
Give Isami-kun a front row seat to your pussy cumming.
No!
My nipples, don't...
What's the matter?
You need to finish your sentences for us to understand you.
Isami-kun...
I... can't...
Isami-kun, sorry! Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry!
Wow, look at you go!
You shot your pure liquid all over the kid's face.
I forgot, you're not used to people making you orgasm.
I wanted to keep my image as a mature lady!
Come on, you're inside her, move your hips.
Doesn't it feel good to move around in her pussy?
Come on, try harder.
Are you really okay with us just
making you cum all the time?
Look, Natsuki is feeling good from your dick, Isami-kun.
Isami-kun...
It feels really good!
Oh wow, look at how hard you're going now.
You might be trying too hard with your sensitive dick.
Wow, you're amazing. You must really like Natsuki a lot.
I'm starting to get really turned on too.
Cum as much as you want while
you're sandwiched in between us.
Let's get crazy together.
It's fine. Go deep inside my pussy!
Do it! Cum lots!
Isami-kun, you're so cute and lovable.
How about next time you come, you just ask for me?
Give it up already.
He only took you this time out of pity. Know your place.
Yeah, but now he's really attached to me.
Huh? You're not that close to him. There's
no room for you in our relationship.
Then let's have sex with him again
and let him decide who he prefers.
You're on!
I already know who's gonna win though.
Am I ever gonna get to go home?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч