Don't dare barge in here!!
Right there... Lick that part more...
Put a little bit more effort into it...
But, nee-chan...
You're so bushy that this is kind of hard to do...
You were saying?
I'm just kidding! Sorry!
Since that day,
nee-chan seems to have been hooked on sex.
Why are you always touching my butt hole?
I'm telling you to stop doing that...
Th-That feels good... I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Sex feels incredible...
Goddess
of
Spectacles
Goddess
of
Spectacles
Goddess
of
Spectacles
Megane
no
Megami
Megane
no
Megami
Megane
no
Megami
And today,
I went to town with Hitomi to order
a new pair of glasses for her.
Though, to tell the truth...
It was me who stepped on and broke
her glasses while we're having sex.
A
A-A
A-A-Am I...
has a good
eyesight
and
has never
been here
before
Am I in heaven right now?!
Hiro-kun!
Huh?
What do you think of these?
I knew it! My girlfriend...
...is a beauty in glasses!
Whoa—!
Glasses aren't made immediately, huh?
Yeah, and that's why...
Ta-da—!
Th-That's...
It's the one from before that I stopped using.
This looks old-fashioned, though.
I wonder if I don't look good in these?
You look totally good in them!
Hiro-kun, is that...
Wow, it feels so slippery!
Not my ass... No!
I'll do it for you next.
Wow... It feels so good!
It feels like my whole body is covered in slime.
I love this!
Aren't we lively down here?
My clitty feels good!
I'm craving for it...
I'll put it in just like this, okay?
It slipped deep inside!
Hitomi, you're especially assertive today.
That's because you've never been
calling me over your house lately.
I've been wanting to do this a lot too, you know!
Coming! I'm gonna come!
No, I'm already gonna...
Let's come together... At the same time!
My head went all blank...
Nee-chan, you're wearing something so skimpy!
What, do you have any problem with it?
No, I don't... But rather...
Nee-chan...
Idiot... Here, of all places...
But it got stiff...
It'll be okay as long as you won't
moan out loud, nee-chan!
That's not the issue...
Huh? This sensation...
Oh, it's all smooth now!
Did you shave them?
It's because you told me that...
Nee-chan...
You're so bushy that this is kind of hard to do...
Nee-chan, you're so erotic!
Hey, isn't it fine? I'll shoot it outside.
Nee-chan!
Th-Then... Umm...
Aren't you interested in it?
Are you sure?
This is just for today, okay?
Yeah, yeah!
Relax your muscles.
So, this is how anal sex feels...
The tightness at the entrance feels amazing!
The insides feel kind of spongy, though.
Is this your first time putting it in the ass?
Yeah...
I-I see...
No, you're being too rough!
I'm coming already!
I'm coming from anal sex!
Coming!
Huh?
Are you alone, Kurumizawa-san?
I came here today to talk to you, onee-san.
What do you want to talk about?
Umm, will you...
...please teach me some sex techniques!
I want to make Hiro-kun feel good a lot more!
I'm home!
Huh? Why are you here, Hitomi?
And so, you wanted nee-chan to teach you, huh?
That's because onee-san seems
capable of doing anything.
Why are you candidly making her suck you?
You don't have to watch us, you know? O-Ouch...
I'm looking forward to my lessons!
torn between
her reasoning
and arousal
I don't have that much experience to teach her.
Huh, what? She can swallow it that deep?
Your panties are drenched, Hitomi.
You got this wet just from giving me a blowjob.
Onee-san, you look lonely there...
D-Don't, that's embarrassing!
Onee-san, you're trimming
yourself clean down here.
That's because of Hiroki...
Y-You're being rough out of the blue!
Hey, you're slacking on doing nee-chan.
I-I can't do it in this state!
If that's so...
Nee-chan, return the favor from earlier.
O-Onee-san...
No, this will drive me crazy...
I-I want it inside... Let's come at the same time!
There's so much pouring into my womb!
Onee-san, please take a look at this!
Kurumizawa-san's pussy looks delighted...
Hiroki...
Me too, okay?
Huh?! Onee-san, do you like
having it in your ass?
You didn't have to tell her that!
Whoa... Amazing!
It really went in there!
So, you feel good from your ass?
Onee-san, you're just so cute
that I somehow feel like teasing you!
This time, I'll make you feel good for sure!
N-No!
Kurumizawa-san, don't do that!
Don't...
It's coming out!
Gosh, why did you shoot it
on my glasses right away?
Huh? That's because Hiro-kun
has a fetish for glasses.
Ugh... They found me out!
Whenever I have my glasses on,
his reactions at sex are totally different.
Now that I think about it, all the girls
that he liked ever since are...
Don't tell me that...
...any girl will do as long as she wears glasses?
That's not true at all!
Hiro-kun!
Hiroki?
You're both wrong—!
Isn't this one cute, onee-san?
Won't this frame look good on me?
Hiroki!
Hiro-kun!
Whose glasses will you choose?
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization