Oh My Sex Goddess!
Episode 3
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Come on, buy an air conditioner.
This heat is killing me!
No. We can't waste money like that.
I-I'm sorry.
I must have zoned out.
Are you okay?
Here, take this.
It's a special goddess energy drink.
You're not at 100%, are you?
Thanks.
I'm okay though.
Don't forget that you gave
half your life force to that guy.
Yeah...
I'm going to give him
some of my life force.
Impart some of my life
to him, thus saving him!
My name is Fauna!
By the way, that idiot's been
relying solely on you lately.
Would you like some help?
Oh, that's okay.
I'll take care of it.
No, a manager needs
to help out her residents.
Why don't I clean
his room while I'm at it?
No, really. I can handle it.
Take my advice...
I don't think it's a good idea
to pamper a man too much.
Oh...
I think love means leaving
him to himself sometimes.
That's why I'll go ahead
and clean Mr. Kawakami's room.
The plan seems
to have stalled, Clotho.
Yes, and I apologize. No matter
how many erotic dreams I show him...
...those annoying goddesses
keep getting in the way.
We knew that would happen.
That's why we sent you.
Yes, sir.
No more delays.
I have a plan.
A plan?
Yes, sir. Please give
me one more chance.
Just be aware that
it will be your last chance.
But the truth is I don't
have much of a plan at all.
As usual, he's a slob.
Why put the devil's
seed in a guy like him?
Anyway, time to get to work.
M-Miss Manager?
I-Is this a dream?
Put that down and come
play with my hose instead.
P-Please stop... I need to clean...
Not before I make
you nice and clean.
No!
Please, don't do this!
You're not very grateful
that I'm cleaning you up.
Why don't you clean this for me?
You can do better than that.
Harder, harder!
Yeah, that's the way!
Um, Kosuke?
Kosuke?
It couldn't be...
My body feels hot.
What's happening?
We're just getting started. That's what.
That's one raunchy sound.
Is that coming from you?
No... It's so embarrassing...
Or maybe there's some
detergent in here too.
Stick your ass in the air.
At least this "mouth" is honest.
These bubbles
have my turbo running.
I have to hurry and purify him...
Fauna.
Jordh.
Leave this to me.
But...
You have a fever.
I hope you understand.
You need rest right now.
I finally have those goddesses
right where I want them.
All this summer heat
has weakened her.
That makes my plan a simple one.
One-day Spa Pass
Cool Evening Massage
What are these?
They're complimentary one-day tickets
to a spa that just opened nearby.
They do massages?
I know! They have open-air baths
and stone saunas at these places!
I happened to win those
in a neighborhood drawing.
But I have to work,
so you girls can have them.
An open-air bath, huh?
I'm sure it'd be
a nice change of pace.
But there are only three tickets.
And it's only for ladies.
What should we do?
Why don't you two go? I have to...
No way!
You're the one who's not feeling well.
This would be good for you.
Now's your chance
to get back on your feet.
Let's go, Fauna.
Just forget about Kosucky.
Yeah, but...
There's no need
to worry about Mr. Kawakami.
I'll be responsible
for looking after him.
That wasn't cheap, but it worked.
Now that the goddesses
are gone, this'll be a cinch.
I can increase his impurity all I want.
And I know just the way to do it.
Fauna? It's open.
Good morning.
Is something wrong?
W-What are you wearing...
I felt like something different.
And I'll be looking after you
today as a favour to the girls.
Looking after me?
That's right!
Help yourself.
Don't you want any?
I just wasn't expecting this.
I never thought you'd make
a homey meal like this for me.
Well, I just read how to do in a book.
I knew that human men go gaga
when you make them food like this.
Well then, don't mind if I do.
Thanks, that was good!
Really?
You'll make somebody a good wife.
You're just flattering me.
You're a little clumsy sometimes,
but that's cute in a way.
Is something wrong?
Your face looks red.
I'm just happy
someone is here to enjoy it.
Oh, never mind...
What am I saying?
I need to remember my mission,
and hurry and start the next plan.
Guess what.
I'm going to clean your ears for you.
How does it feel?
Just like I'm in heaven.
Soon you'll be in hell.
Did you say something?
N-No, I didn't.
I must have misjudged you.
I thought you weren't all that nice.
But you're very nice as it turns out.
Now let me do it for you.
Wow, it's pretty clean
in there already.
There's no need to stare...
Feels good, huh?
Y-Yes, wow...
That's enough, thanks.
It's embarrassing...
You're pretty tense.
You'll be surprised
how good I am at this.
Now for your back. There we go.
My mom had me give her
massages a lot when I was little.
Your mother?
Tell me about your mother.
That's enough!
Miss Manager?
I'm no manager.
Surprised? My name's Clotho.
I'm a demon who was sent
to awaken the devil sleeping inside you.
Sorry, but it's time
we pick up the pace.
I'm going to give
your impurity a big boost!
You're really good!
What?
First a maid, now a demon?
I never knew you were
this good at cosplay.
This isn't cosplay!
It's very pretty.
You've got a really
dark image going on...
...but if you changed the mood,
you could even be an angel.
Don't screw with me!
You can't move, can you?
I'm about to boost
your impurity to the max.
Don't worry.
In the end, I'll let you die in
the form you desire the most for yourself.
Where am l?
Welcome home, master.
Fauna! Jordh! Lea!
Master, from now on
I am your servant.
You may ask me to do anything.
I'll do anything for you too,
Kosuke... I mean, master.
I'd really rather not...
...but I don't mind what
happens if it's for Kosucky's sake.
Be careful how you word things.
Call me "master."
A-All right.
Please forgive me, master.
First, I want you
to make this nice and clean.
Yes, master.
Come on, put some
more effort into it.
Jordh, Lea, feel free to jump in.
Suck away.
That's right. That's the way!
Deep throat it.
That's right.
Get more and more aroused.
But why do they do
so much for a guy like him?
This rules.
Keep going.
Yes, master...
That feels good...
How do you feel, master?
I've got goddesses servicing me.
I've never felt better.
Hold that pose, Fauna.
Yes, master.
Jordh, put it inside you.
I love how tight you are, Jordh.
Master...
Please let me have some too.
Lea...
Master, I just can't...
You can't wait any longer?
That's right...
I like the view.
Please don't stare at us like that.
It's embarrassing.
Beg me.
Beg me to please do you.
P-Please...
Please put it in, master.
Very well.
You're soaking wet, aren't you?
Don't talk like that!
It's so intense!
I-I'm going to come...
How do you like having your master
inside you? Come all you like!
Master... Please give me some too.
Don't worry. It's your turn next.
Just wait until I ram
this thick rod into you.
You don't have to be
in such a hurry, Fauna.
I sense a miasma more intense
than any we've seen before!
Aren't you just imagining things?
And here we just
washed off all that sweat...
This is getting us sweaty again!
Kosuke!
Fauna?
Kosuke's fine.
I'm sure the manager...
Welcome back, goddesses.
Just who are you?
It couldn't be...
Yes, it could indeed.
What did she do?
Lea, stay back!
She's a demon, Lea!
Fauna!
Bitch!
Don't worry. I'm not about
to screw up and hit the devil.
You mean his impurity is...
I managed to boost Kosuke
Kawakami's impurity as high as it'll go.
And you three helped.
What do you mean?
The devil's seed will soon awaken.
That's not
Kosuke Kawakami anymore.
He's the devil himself!
Up yours!
Thanks for all your hard work.
You can't purify him anymore!
You won't get away with this!
Fauna!
Right!
I'm all right.
I just got a little careless.
You're still weak...
I guess goddesses
aren't that tough after all.
Dance in ecstasy, spirits of the dead.
Unleash the jet-black
flames of your anger!
I command you in the name of Jordh.
Dance, spirits of the wind!
Unleash now your power!
W-Wow...
Fauna, stop. You've done enough.
I command you in the name of Fauna!
Rage, O air!
Unleash your anger upon her!
Well? Hurry and finish me off.
You've already been punished.
That's right. We don't
believe in taking life meaninglessly.
You'll end up regretting it.
Why did you try
fighting us all by yourself?
You knew we had the advantage.
Jordh!
We've got a problem with Kosucky!
What's happening?
The devil's starting to wake up.
What do we do?
If he really wakes up,
Earth's done for!
Fauna...
No, Jordh.
Anything but that.
But there's no other way.
We have to erase him.
Fauna!
I'll purify him!
It's impossible. Besides, Fauna,
you're nearly out of power.
It's all right!
But...
If... If I do fail...
...I'll go with Kosuke
beyond this dimension!
Say what?
If you do that, you'll die too!
Don't be an idiot.
We'll just erase him
if it comes to that.
You two put up a barrier.
We don't know if some
other demon will try to interfere.
Fauna...
Sis...
I'm sorry for being selfish.
I command you in the name of Jordh.
Spirits of wind, soar around us!
Protect my sister
Fauna with your power!
Protect her!
Where am l?
I can't move.
W-Who are you?
S-Stay away from me!
Why can't I move?
Fauna...
Kosuke.
I'm going to purify you.
Now look at me.
Kosuke!
F-Fauna...
Kosuke...
Stop this...
I'll hurt you at this rate...
Thank goodness,
your soul is still in there.
I can't stop my power, so please...
Kosuke, you have to accept me.
I might at least be able to save you.
No... It has to be both of us...
It's my duty as a goddess.
Fauna...
There's still time, but barely.
Now! Erase me!
Kosuke!
No, Fauna...
It'll tear you apart...
I'm glad I met you.
Fauna...
Fauna's in trouble...
What's this powerful energy I sense?
Fucking a goddess is the best.
I'll keep going until you break.
Why?
Why would you go
this far for a human man?
You're going to die at this rate.
I swear I'll save him.
What, you're not broken yet?
Is that what it means
to be a goddess?
A demon like you
wouldn't understand...
...how important Kosuke is to me.
Yes, I'm a demon.
However...
You're finished.
Kosuke!
I'm back.
I'm back to normal.
Thank you, Fauna.
Kosuke... Thank goodness.
I want you, Fauna.
I want you too.
Fauna, I'm going to come!
Kosuke! So am l!
Yum!
I still wonder why.
About what?
When it looked like Fauna
couldn't manage to purify Kosuke...
...that demon saved the day.
I wonder why.
That's true.
I wasn't sure how that would end.
But Fauna and Kosuke were okay.
I heard a story once.
Long ago, there was a child of
a goddess who was raised by demons.
By demons?
They say that when she grew up,
she looked like a demon...
...but the light of a goddess
still dwelt deep in her heart.
That's just a legend, isn't it?
Great, what do I do now?
There'll be hell to pay with
the boss if I go back down to him.
Ah, whatever.
I guess I've paid back my debt here.
One, two, three, go!
What's the program for me
to meet and fall in love with you?
The whisper of
uMtoppable love is beat punk.
Will you still hear it
if I turn up the volume?
My heart's racing,
and my head, and my legs.
Are you and I always
connected by this sky, this wind?
connected by time and the world?
I miss you, and I just
can't stop this feeling.
Are we connected by our emotions?