Oh My Sex Goddess!
Episode 1
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Mr. Kawakami?
No!
What are you doing? Stop...
No...
Ouch!
S-Stop it...
No...
No, Mr. Kawakami, not there...
You mustn't...
It's so embarrassing...
Let me go!
N-No!
What do you mean, "no"?
Look how wet you are.
That's a hell of a smell.
Don't say such mean things...
It's the smell of a bitch in heat.
Please...
No...
You're enjoying it,
even if I am raping you.
You're one slutty house manager.
I'm not enjoying it.
Then why are you so wet?
I just...
No...
Stop...
Y-You're being too rough...
You like it that way, don't you?
I can't take any more...
Maybe I'll shoot my load inside you.
No, not inside!
Stop it!
I think I was dreaming
about something.
Whoa!
That's even bigger than usual...
Oh crap! It goes on sale today!
Oops.
Um, good morning, Miss Manager.
It's the middle of the day.
I guess it is.
This is just, um...
You'd better hurry or you won't get
a limited edition Mischief Angel Love.
Oh, y-you're right. T-Thanks.
Wait. How'd she know about that?
Well, whatever.
Right now I need to hurry.
It'll be a bittersweet summer break...
Mischief Angel Love-chan
...once I get that limited first-edition stuff!
What's the real thing doing here?
I-I'm not sure who you are,
but could you assist me?
My robe got caught on this branch.
Sure.
That tickles!
I can't really help that.
Stop that!
No!
T-This isn't working!
And don't touch me there!
It'd help if you'd
stop flailing your legs.
Hold still!
Look out!
A-Are you okay?
Hey, never better.
Are you by any chance
Kosuke Kawakami?
How do you know my name?
I thought so.
You can no longer exist in this world.
Huh?
I have to erase you.
Erase?
It's for the sake of world peace!
I command the air in the name
of Fauna. Vibrate with vengeance...
...and unleash
your anger upon this person!
Now please rest in peace.
I missed?
W-W-Wait a minute!
What the hell was that?
A superhigh-voltage,
hundred-megavolt lightning bolt!
Megavolt?
The next one won't miss!
Quit it!
That's lethal force you're using!
As I said, I have to erase you!
What are you anyway?
I'm a goddess!
A goddess?
That's far enough.
It's too dangerous for you
to remain alive in this world.
"Dangerous"?
S-Sis!
Eray glace cremarre.
Spirits of fire...
...in accordance with our ancient
covenant, burn away this impurity!
Wait!
What's up with you two?
You don't need to know.
You're about to die after all.
This place will become your grave.
Sis, that's a line villains say...
How dare you humiliate me!
Now you die!
Mission accomplished.
Now let's go home.
Fauna?
He's suffering...
I'm going to give him
some of my life force.
What are you talking about?
I know it's a serious crime.
But I don't care
if it means disobeying heaven.
Calm down, Fauna.
I don't know what you're tying
to accomplish, but if you save him...
...somebody else
will come try to kill him.
If they do...
...I'll protect him.
Hey, what's come over you?
I'm sure we can find a way
to keep him from becoming a devil!
I won't ask you to help.
Please just don't stop me.
You sure are
a handful of a little sister.
O tree of life, which controls
the fate of all living things!
Impart some of my life
to him, thus saving him!
My name is Fauna!
My name is Jordh!
His name is Kosuke Kawakami!
I think I was dreaming
about something really painful...
Oh, you're awake. Good morning.
What's the matter?
I'm Fauna.
I'm going to be living here
at Benten Villa for the time being.
I thought we'd eat together
as a way of saying hello.
Have you forgotten me?
W-What are you wearing?
I heard this is what young women
around here wear when they cook...
Is there something wrong with it?
Hey, what the heck
are those wings on your head?
T-They're, um...
They're fashionable!
They're the latest trend, you know!
Oh, you don't say.
I don't keep up with that stuff.
K-Kosuke?
Let me go!
Please let me go!
I don't think so.
Why should I let go of something
this soft and nice to fondle?
K-Kosuke, stop it!
Please don't!
Doesn't it feel nice to be touched down there?
Then let's keep going.
No!
Wow, you're soaking wet.
N-No...
You mustn't do this!
Kosuke...
What shouldn't I do?
If this is so wrong,
why's your body reacting to it?
Don't tell me
the devil's seed is already...
It feels that good, huh?
I'm about to give you
a taste of heaven.
D-Don't do this, Kosuke!
T-This isn't right!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Shut up. Just stand back and watch.
Get off of her, stupid!
Why is he so strong?
Has it awakened?
Now it's time for me to take you.
N-No!
Ow...
Kosuke, snap out of it...
Leucothea is in the house!
Huh?
There's nobody here.
L-Lea!
You need to tone down
your appearance a bit.
At least you had some nice timing.
Summer vacation starts today!
God gave me permission
to come to have some fun!
That's because
he can't say no to you.
She did bail us out though.
What do you mean?
What am I standing on?
What?
Just erase this dangerous
brute and get over with it!
She's right.
It would be the easiest way.
Calm down, you two.
We can't do that.
You're the one who
had to suffer, Fauna!
We don't know what would've
happened if I hadn't shown up!
What's going on?
He's awake.
Take this!
What was that for?
I should be asking you that instead!
Wait. Who are you?
I can't believe
you assaulted my sister!
Your sister?
Uh, Kosuke...
Um, sorry for what happened.
Do you remember
what happened before the attack?
I was staring at your ass,
and then I just zoned out.
Lech! Horny pervert!
He can't help it
that he's a guy, but still...
I knew it. A demon's
been interfering with him.
It'd be better if we told the truth and
figure out how to deal with it together.
The truth?
Yes. Just please remain calm.
What? I have
the devil's seed inside me?
I'm sorry we didn't tell you, Kosuke.
What's something
like that doing in my body?
I don't know.
It might be the place or time you
were born, or karma from the past.
Hell's goal is to revive the devil.
For that, they need a vessel
of negative human energy.
The impurity has to be amplified.
Impurity?
I mean negative immoral feelings.
Your exposure to the demon
is amplifying your impurity.
When it becomes
too much for you to contain...
The devil will be revived?
Yes. The world will
probably be destroyed.
We came here
to keep an eye on you.
Let's see here...
The way to lower a human's
impurity back to normal...
...is for him to have sexual
intercourse with at least one goddess.
The impure energy can
only be removed at ejaculation...
No way!
You wouldn't be able to handle it.
Oh yes I could!
Okay, then try it.
I don't wanna have sex with him.
You do it, Jordh.
Guess I'll have to.
I'll give you a taste
of heaven on earth.
S-Sure...
Wait a minute!
Um, if Kosuke doesn't mind, I'll do it...
Um...
Just a second please!
Hey!
She caught us!
Sheesh...
Miss Fauna, um...
Just call me Fauna.
So, Kosuke...
This is my first time,
so I'm not sure how well I'll do.
I'll give it all I've got though.
I hope this goes well.
I hope so too.
So what should I do?
I'm sorry.
I don't know anything about it.
Well, set me loose first.
I can't do that. It'd be
dangerous the way things stand.
We have to do it like this?
Yes.
Then will you do what I say?
Sure!
Does that feel good?
Yeah, amazingly.
Then I'll keep going.
It's so big.
The impurity's about to overflow.
Go ahead... Let it all out.
Hurry. Hurry and give it to me.
I-I'm coming...
That didn't get rid of all the impurity.
Let's please go again.
Could you undo these please?
I-I feel embarrassed.
Kosuke...
Fauna...
Okay.
Wait!
Are you sure you want me?
Are you sure
you want me to be your first?
What are you saying?
This really makes me happy.
Thank you.
Go ahead, Kosuke.
Please make love
to me any way you want.
Oh, wow, Fauna...
I-I've never felt
this way before either!
It's so...
It's so good...
...when it hits that deep!
Fauna, I'm about to come!
Please...
Please let it all out inside me!
Are you sure?
Yes.
Kosuke, I think
I'm going to come too!
Fauna!
I-I'm almost there, Kosuke!
So am I! Fauna!
I'm coming!
Kosuke...
The impurity's disappearing.
Fauna...
We're home!
Hello, Miss Manager.
Welcome back.
What's the matter, Jordh?
Oh, nothing.
Does my magic not work on her?
That's impossible.
I stopped by a pachinko parlor,
and I couldn't stop winning.
Look at all these prizes!
I guess that's the luck of a goddess?
How'd it go, Fauna?
It hurt a little, but it was really...
Not that. I meant about the impurity.
Oh, um...
l-It's totally calmed down.
It worked.
Well, all right.
Good for you too, Kosuke.
Y-Yeah.
Brute.
I can't help it!
Anyway, this should
buy us some time for now.
Yes, and now we have
time to find that demon.
One, two, three, go!
What's the program for me
to meet and fall in love with you?
The whisper of
unstoppable love is beat punk.
Will you still hear it
if I turn up the volume?
My heart's racing,
and my head, and my legs.
Are you and I always
connected by this sky, this wind?
connected by time and the world?
I miss you, and I just
can't stop this feeling.
Are we connected by our emotions?