Oh My Sex Goddess!
Episode 2
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Just erase this dangerous
brute and get it over with!
She's right.
It would be the easiest way.
Kosuke, we can't let the devil's
seed sleeping inside you awaken.
Please rest in peace!
Yup. It's for peace
on Earth, you know.
W-Wait a minute!
Just draw out the impurity
and the devil won't revive!
We will grant you a final wish.
"final"?
Fauna, I'm about to...
Where did our clothes go?
And how'd we get down here?
This is my first time,
so I'm not sure if I'll do well.
Your first time?
But I thought we already...
Here goes nothing.
Kosuke...
Oh, yes!
Fauna, if I come
inside you, won't it purify me?
Very much so!
Kosuke!
Fauna, I'm about to come...
D-Don't...
Sorry, I can't hold back!
You mustn't!
Why shouldn't I?
Because you can't!
I can't?
Hey, why am I not coming?
O-Ow!
Ow!
Was that a dream?
Hey, w-what the hell is this?
Ow...
J-Jordh?
A little more?
What are you doing?
I figured out we could
restrict the impurity's growth...
...if we could keep you from
enjoying erotic dreams. Bear with me.
S-Stop it!
A-Are you tying to make
me impotent? S-Somebody, help me!
Kosuke!
Ow!
Jordh, what are you doing?
T-That killed me...
I don't care if this is to control
the impurity. It's too cruel!
How could you...
...u-um, you know, take away
his greatest moment of pleasure?
What choice do we have? We've
yet to find any other reliable way.
All we have to do is...
you know... "purify" the impurity...
Okay, have it your way.
Kosuke, are you all right?
Oh no!
Maybe I overdid it a little bit.
But a little use of my magic power
will make short work of this.
Wait, Sis.
I'll do it.
I don't mind. It was my fault, after all.
No, I'll be the one to take care of him!
Why're you getting angry?
Oh, he looks fine to me!
Hey, you don't suppose...
I hope not...
Yeah, it's the impurity.
Fauna, use that chastity gizmo.
Okay.
W-Wait! Nothing's wrong with me!
Then how do you explain that?
Well, when I saw the real Fauna...
...I remembered
boinking her in my dream.
Gosh, Kosuke...
You're a bad boy.
Time to die again!
Help me, Fauna!
Don't look at me.
Um, is something wrong
with Mr. Kawakami?
Miss Manager...
It sounded like a crime
was being committed.
I heard him screaming.
That's a scandalous thing to say.
It makes it sound like we're
doing something terrible to him!
You hit the nail on the head.
Sorry, Miss Manager,
you misunderstand.
Kosuke was having
a seizure due to a chronic illness.
Chronic illness?
Chronic horniness.
H-His, uh, stomach isn't feeling well.
In that case,
I have some herbal medicine.
Here.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Take care now.
Is something wrong?
I knew something wasn't right here.
Like what?
This room has a barrier around it.
Nobody but us goddesses
should be able to enter.
Herbal medicine, huh?
I might as well try it.
It sure is hot today. This is
a good day for relaxing at the pool.
Is it so hot it's making me dizzy?
Are you okay?
Oh, Miss Manager.
I don't know. I just feel wiped out...
Uh-oh, you should get some rest.
Yes, I will...
Yay for herbal medicine.
It's slow to take effect.
Where am l?
Really?
It's true.
Unbelievable!
A locker room?
My building manager?
O-Oh no...
Something's trying
to take control of me...
Maybe it's...
Keep quiet.
What are you
doing here, Mr. Kawakami?
I've been lying in wait for you.
For me?
I figured out I needed
to thank you for today.
T-Thank me?
I've got a wonderful
present ready for you.
Present?
This isn't really the right size...
That's the idea.
Now do some warm-up exercises.
All right.
Um, the swimsuit
is so tight that it hurts...
Then I'll loosen it a bit.
Don't do that!
Now continue.
N-No!
P-Please stop...
So you can do it yourself?
Works for me.
Now suck my dick.
Deeper!
Are you scared?
That's not the right one...
Oh yes it is.
That's weird.
Did he collapse out here?
Silly Kosucky.
Hey, you're in the way! Somebody'll
step on you if you sleep out here!
Come on, wake up.
Jeez...
Ow!
You want what
I've got too, don't you?
I'm about to send you to paradise.
Stop it!
No!
Why wasn't somebody
keeping an eye on this brute?
I was watching him. He just
went to the bathroom for a bit.
Dirty dream?
It did seem like he was
taking his time coming back.
I think he's beyond help.
Maybe, but don't forget about Fauna.
What do we do then?
He has to be purified.
I won't do it!
Nobody asked you to.
Anyway, where's Fauna?
She went shopping.
But I don't want her
doing him anymore!
That leaves one choice.
I'll be the one to take care of him!
This is part of a goddess's job.
Lea, go wait outside for a while.
Ow!
Jordh...
Did I have another naughty dream?
Yup. You were in a bad way.
Damn it, who the hell is
making me have these dreams?
I don't know.
But then if the devil's revived,
it won't make any difference who it is.
So Fauna's not around.
Maybe I'll just erase you after all.
It's for the sake of all mankind.
Just kidding.
Don't joke about that...
Hey, would you
like me to purify you?
S-Sure...
You could be more decisive!
Y-Yes, please.
That's better.
Should you untie me?
It won't be easy otherwise.
You like tits, don't you, Kosuke?
Don't talk that way.
I'll give yours some attention too.
That's really good, Jordh!
Look how wet you are.
Jordh, you're a sex fiend.
You're one to talk, silly.
Your pussy's so tight!
Kosuke!
Go deeper!
It's so good, Jordh!
I'm about to come already!
Go ahead! Let it all out!
Put your impure energy inside me!
Fauna...
You're all so slow!
Hurry up!
Why'd you suddenly
invite us all to the pool?
Who cares about you, Kosuke?
It's for my sisters.
For Fauna and Jordh?
What do you mean?
I want them to get along.
Are they fighting?
Why?
Stupid!
Huh?
Is this a...
Is there something up
with that cherry tree?
What's a cherry tree?
They have all these pretty
pink blossoms in the spring.
But...
...this tree doesn't bloom.
I'm not really sure why.
You're a celestial tree, aren't you?
Wow, I've never met
another celestial being down here.
S-She's floating!
So what brings you girls
to the human realm?
That's a very long story.
I was planted a long time ago
by somebody important up there.
But I still can't
make any flowers bloom.
In other words, you're a tree nymph?
Nymph?
That's what they call
you in the human world.
Yup.
So if somebody around here
saw you, they'd call you a nymph.
You don't say.
Nymph, huh? "Nymph."
Oh, let me introduce you.
This is my friend from
the human world, Kosuke Kawakami.
Nice to meet you.
He's a total perv.
You didn't need to say that, stupid!
I'm Astra, a nymph.
How do you do?
Time for tons of swimming!
Everyone needs
a break now and then.
Yeah, but...
What's the big idea?
For safety's sake.
We don't know when
that impurity will pop up again.
Watch our stuff, okay?
I'm really sorry, Kosuke. It's all
in the name of world peace!
There's no other way!
There's also no point
in coming to the pool...
Hello.
Is that you, Miss Manager?
This is an unusual place to see you.
I'll say.
I won't let anyone interfere anymore.
Kosuke?
Did you fall asleep?
Everybody's watching.
You want to do it here, don't you?
Is this the impurity?
Kosuke, please stop!
Please snap out of it!
Divine punishment!
What's going on?
I thought he'd been purified.
Did someone make him have an
erotic dream while we were gone?
I thought we'd be okay
away from his apartment.
Looks like I was wrong.
Jordh, we need to purify him again.
Fauna, this time it's your job.
Right.
Kosuke...
He's in your hands now.
Jordh?
I've got something I need to do.
I'm sorry.
I kind of got mad at you.
I don't hold that
against you or anything.
But keep your guard up, Fauna.
Our enemy's determined.
I will.
There.
Can I help with anything?
No, you can't.
You're looking down on me again!
Okay, do you know
about pharmacology?
Pharmacology?
Advanced mathematic
theory's basic principle?
A-Advanced?
You cannot help.
Sorry I bothered you...
Here's where it gets tricky.
Kosuke.
This time I'll purify you.
Sorry you have
to do this for me, Fauna.
No, I don't mind helping you.
Fauna... I want to see all of you.
Don't stare at me like that.
It's embarrassing.
You're beautiful.
Fauna, I can't wait any longer.
That was sudden!
I-It's so embarrassing!
I guess human medicinal
plants won't do the job.
They aren't resistant enough.
But there's no time to go
back to heaven at this point.
Fauna, I want to be inside you.
Sure, anytime.
If that's what you want.
Fauna...
It's so warm inside you...
It's because you're so nice, Kosuke.
It feels good, the way it rubs the tip...
That's such a raunchy thing to say.
No...
I'm gonna come!
Yes, let it all out!
Come inside me!
H-Here it comes, Fauna!
Kosuke?
Okay, this time for sure.
A barrier?
Right.
Someone's set up
a barrier in Kosuke's body.
What does it do?
He can't ejaculate,
so he can't be purified.
There's no point then!
That's why I'm struggling to make
medicine that'll remove the barrier!
If you don't hurry, it'll be too late!
I'm aware of that.
It's no use.
I have to use celestial flowers...
Excuse me...
We're busy right now!
Is there anything I can help with?
Astra?
Here I am!
Kosuke, what's the matter?
It's like something's
possessing me down there...
It's all right. I'll protect you!
Your flowers don't bloom because
you were planted prematurely.
It's what I wanted, so I don't mind.
I had my mind set
on seeing this world.
I'm not sure what'll happen to you...
...if I use a blooming spell.
I wanted to have pretty flowers
and see everybody smile.
That's why...
You won't regret this?
Right.
Give me power,
all those that hear my voice!
Then bestow the time
of blessing upon her!
Nothing changed.
Give me power,
all those that hear my voice!
Then bestow the time
of blessing upon her!
Wind, water, earth...
All the powers that gather here!
Give unto her the power to bloom!
Please bloom!
Yay, she bloomed! It's so pretty!
Fauna.
Kosuke!
Thanks, Fauna.
I feel refreshed for some reason.
Good...
I'm sure it'll work this time.
Okay.
Here I go, Fauna.
Okay!
That feels good, Fauna...
I-It feels good for me too, Kosuke!
I'm about to come, Fauna...
So am I... Kosuke!
Looks like we weren't too late.
Astra...
The plan seems to have stalled.
I apologize.
Can you explain it?
Yes, sir.
Those annoying goddesses
keep getting in the way.
Next time, I will give
Kosuke Kawakami...
...all the erotic dreams
he needs to reawaken the devil.
Failure is no longer an option.
Don't worry. Now I know
how the goddesses operate.
And I know their weakness.
One, two, three, go!
What's the program for me
to meet and fall in love with you?
The whisper of
unstoppable love is beat punk.
Will you still hear it
if I turn up the volume?
My heart's racing,
and my head, and my legs.
Are you and I always
connected by this sky, this wind?
connected by time and the world?
I miss you, and I just
can't stop this feeling.
Are we connected by our emotions?