Hey...
Are we really gonna do it here in the classroom?
We'll regret it if we won't do this
here while we're still students.
No, we won't!
You say that but you're wet.
Here I go, Hitomi.
You're being loud. People are gonna notice!
Your insides are a gooey mess!
I want to keep screwing you!
Hey, nee-chan! We're gonna be late.
It's no use, it should be this one! My morning
wood won't settle down otherwise!
H-Hey, not again!
Nee-chan... If you squeeze me that hard, I'm gonna...
Don't get me soiled with that, okay?
Inside... I want it inside me!
Hiro-kun!
Hiroki!
Let's do it nice and slow at a hotel next time.
Okay?
Make do with just a blowjob tomorrow.
Goddess
of
Spectacles
Goddess
of
Spectacles
Goddess
of
Spectacles
Megane
no
Megami
Megane
no
Megami
Megane
no
Megami
I indulge in sex with both my girlfriend and elder sister.
The story of how it all ended up
like this goes a little way back.
To tell you the truth,
I am what society calls as someone
with a fetish for glasses!
And my girlfriend...
...is a beauty in glasses!
However...
Hitomi always takes her glasses off
whenever we're having sex.
That's the only complaint I have about her.
What's up with this stinky dick?
You're letting it build up
as much smegma as possible.
I'll give it a thorough cleaning for you.
While sucking his cock,
I also am somehow...
Hitomi!
What an amazing amount...
There's a lot in my mouth.
What's up with this?
It's all sticky with pussy juice.
Your clit is perked up as well.
You're such a lewd girl to be
like this just from sucking a cock.
Th-That's...
Hey, hey... What's the matter, Hitomi-chan?
What do you want me to do?
Please stop teasing me!
I'll go crazy...
Then...
O-Okay, I'm fine with that...
Will this do?
Good... That's so good! Look!
I'm as hard as a rock!
I-I never saw it looking this gruesome up until now...
Use these things this time.
Gosh...
Here!
L-Look up here while doing that, Hitomi.
Does this feel good?
I can't hold myself back from something like this!
You have a nice view down there,
don't you? Tell me what you see.
Dumbass!
Come on!
M-My pussy is twitching...
It's gobbling up your fat cock!
Oh, jeez! You're so cute!
You're being rough all of a sudden!
You're poking my cervix!
Hiro-kun, you're way more incredible than usual!
My nipples... I love it on my nipples!
That feels good!
No, I'm gonna come!
I'm gonna come!
Coming!
Wow, you're still hard...
W-Wait! I'm still sensitive
from just having an orgasm!
No... You'll tear my pussy!
He's not usually this frantic...
That somehow looks cute...
Please kiss me!
I'm gonna get hooked on sex with glasses on as well!
Glasses are the best!
N
N-N
N-N-N
N-N-N-N
N-N-N-N-N
N-N-N-N-N-N
N-N-N-N-N-N-Nee-chan!
You were home?!
This is your punishment. Is that clear?
You bring your girlfriend home every day
and you two fuck like monkeys.
You're too loud and being a nuisance!
That's because going to a hotel is expensive...
Huuuuuh?
The texture of your stockings...
Oh...
So, you always make Hitomi do something like this.
Is something wrong with your head?
I-I'll never let Hitomi do something like this...
W-Wait!
That girl has been doing this kind of stuff over and over...
I wonder if 'that' is as amazing as it seems...
This is bad!
I-I'm coming!
No!
Wh-What the hell is this? Won't this
leave a stain on my clothes?!
It stinks, it tastes bitter, and you
splattered some of it on my glasses.
Rubbing it between your pantyhose
and panties feels good!
Stop rubbing that filthy thing against me, pervert!
No! That's my...
You got wet from playing with
your younger brother's cock.
You're quite a pervert yourself, nee-chan.
Do you want to come from having
your clit teased? Or maybe...
You prefer it inside you?
Don't!
Come on, rub them by yourself.
O-Okay...
You're not used to blowjobs yet, huh?
Wow, your pussy started throbbing!
Show it to me!
Let me see how you look like when you come!
No! No way!
I squirted for the first time...
H-Hey, Hiroki?!
It's gonna be alright. I'm already used to this.
I'll make sure to shoot it outside.
You shouldn't!
I'm still...
It feels tingly down there... Something
hard is reaching deep inside me!
Pussies sure are different.
Nee-chan, yours tightens up from deep inside.
You see, Hitomi's pussy sticks and coils—
Stop thinking about another girl at a time like this.
Look only at me right now, you idiot.
Suck them... Keep sucking my nipples.
Wow, it feels like my innards
are getting scraped out!
I'm gonna come! My little brother's
cock is making me come!
It's alright, come...
Come just like that!
I'm not really sure how I ended up this way.
But maybe my glasses fetish was because of...
You came too much, idiot!
H-Huh?!
Nee-chan, what's that?!
Who would have guessed that she was a virgin.
Sorry, that was my fault for getting carried away.
So don't let that bother you too much, alright?
Nee-chan...
No, no! There's no way!
You being nice gives me the creeps!
What did you say?
You're an idiot! Clean all of that
before mom comes back!
That's so mean! Am I doing all of this by myself?!
I'm having sex with both Hitomi and nee-chan each day.
This is just the prologue...
I wonder what Hiro-kun is doing right now...
...and it will go on!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization