Headmaster's Office
Amazing.
Your dick is already gotten this hard, Asada-sensei.
It's twitching so much.
Well with both you and Nijou-sensei on my dick at
the same time, it's hard to hold back, Eli-sensei.
Then don't. Let yourself go.
After all, you have a duty to fulfill
for all the women in this school.
You have to get your dick more and more aroused.
I-If you keep being that rough, I'm gonna...
No, stop, sensei! If you're going to cum,
you need to do it deep inside us.
Please pour your load into my pussy.
That's it, Asada-kun.
You don't have to hold anything back.
Make a mess of my wet pussy!
The dark hour is almost upon us.
Nijou-sensei, what exactly is the dark hour?
I'm not entirely sure.
I don't really know, but
when that hour is upon us, all the women in this academy
will be overcome with an insatiable sexual desire.
And then at the end of it all is
the death of all those afflicted!
But is it really okay for a teacher to
continuously fuck his students?
Listen, Asada-kun.
The reason the students are so aroused
is because of their mana depleting.
That's why only you, a member of the
opposite sex can restore their mana...
The only option is for you to directly
pour mana into them with your dick!
It'll be fine. Don't worry, sensei.
The students understand this.
They know that the only one who
can save their lives is you, sensei.
Eli-sensei...
And also... our bodies just get so hot and
we begin to crave your dick so hard.
Please, sensei... save the academy.
So good! I think I'm gonna cum again! I'm gonna cum again!
This is so good!
Sensei, if you get too tight...
This is an effect of the dark hour.
My pussy just gets so sensitive that
I can't help but cum quickly!
I can't stop my climaxes!
My pussy is starting to twitch so bad,
I'm being so shameless again!
Eli-sensei, your pussy feels so good.
I'm happy to hear that. So happy.
I'll try even harder.
Sensei, please cum with me.
Please!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!!
Shoot your semen inside me... into my womb!
It's coming! You're gonna cum! I can
feel your dick getting hotter!
I'm gonna cum too... I'm cumming!
This... This is...
It's coming... It's coming inside me...
Wow, this is amazing. I can feel the power flowing into me.
We've entrusted every last drop of our mana to you.
With that, you should be able to keep
the girls company all night long.
It's coming... It's coming!
Crap... crap! Not out here again!
Why am I, the student council president,
succumbing to this?!
Why am I getting into such a deplorable aroused mood?
So it's begun.
The dark hour is here once more.
You understand, don't you, Asada-kun?
You need to save the students with your semen.
I understand.
Dark Hour Academy
Fertilization Arc
Please, sensei... Please save us with your semen!!
Is it already this twitchy just from
being put in between my boobs?
It's getting bigger too.
It's because your boobs are so huge and feel so good, Kirika.
Sh-Shut up.
I'm pathetic. When the dark hour comes, my pussy just gets
so hot... so hot that I think I'm gonna lose my mind.
So, it feels good?
It's so hard and it's all because my boobs feel good, huh?
What's going on? This is bad. I'm getting turned
on just from the smell of his dick.
My body is getting so hot... I can't stop moving my boobs!
My nipples are getting as hard as his dick!
What's going on? I can't stop!
I can't stop!
Something's coming! It's coming! It's coming right at me!
Sorry.
That wasn't enough. That wasn't nearly enough.
Th-This sensation is amazing!
It's so thick!
Kirika, if you keep squeezing this tightly...
I don't care!
Your dick is too big. Every time you move in me
you end up rubbing the deepest parts of me!
I... I can't! Why isn't your cum out already? I want it so bad!
Okay then.
Your huge dick is hitting me in my deepest places!
Just wait Kirika, I'm gonna cum and get you back to normal.
M-My boobs... they're tingling...
No!! Th-The milk's gonna come out...
I-It's coming! It's coming out!
I'm shooting my milk out from my nipples!
Holy crap, it's getting even tighter!
Why? Why did so much come out?
No! No! I don't want this! I'm like some kind of sick freak!
Almost there. Just wait a little more!
Hang in there!
More! Milk me more!
Milk me until there's nothing left!
Milk me to the very last drop!
Sensei, please! Please!
Sure. Just let it out. Don't worry, it's okay.
Your dick is getting bigger and bigger!
It's rubbing around my pussy and widening it! I can feel it
hitting my womb! I can feel it echoing through my body!
I'm cumming! You ready?
Take all of my cum!
I can't handle this anymore. I'm losing my mind!
Cum! Cum!!
Sensei, please cum, cum with your
sticky semen all inside my pussy!
Sensei...
Student Council Office
Sensei? Your pre-cum just keeps pouring out.
Your dick is getting covered in it.
Rio...
Look, can you see?
My pussy is so shamelessly wet and flowing right now.
Yeah, I can see that.
You're aroused, aren't you, sensei?
Your dick is getting so big and it's twitching so much!
So dirty.
I want to cum. I can't hold it in any longer!
Alright, I'll help you cum using my pussy to help arouse you.
You're about to cum all over me
from my feet, aren't you, sensei?
If you cum near my pussy, you'll make my pussy so sticky!
I-If that happens, I'd...
No!
Rio.
There's no time to rest.
The main attraction starts now.
Sensei, you want me too, don't you?
You want to cum with my pussy, don't you?
N-No, this is just because of the dark hour...
You don't have to hold your true feelings back.
I know you're actually happy that you can have sex
with me because now your dick feels so good,
you don't know what to do with yourself!
What about you? You just can't get enough of this, can you?
N-No... No, that's not true.
Th-There's no way I'd feel anything from thi...
It's okay.
Everyone's the same way because of the dark hour.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Th-There's no way! There's no way that I'd
ever cum from something of this level...
Alright. Then I'll try to end this as quick as possible!
N-No, you're suddenly being so intense...
No!!
It's okay. Don't hide what you're feeling.
It's okay to feel good.
Stop!
I don't want to cum at all... and I don't feel good at all, but...
No! No! No! No!!
Rio, how'd that feel? Feels good to cum, doesn't it?
N-No way. How could I of all people have...
I'm going numb!
Right there... No!
Not there!
Sorry, I'm really close.
Wait!
Your dick is getting bigger... bigger!
Stop... Stop moving! Stop!
Stop it!
I'm losing my mind!
Please, sensei. Come... Come quick!
If this keeps up, I'm gonna get
even lewder than I already am.
I-I'm gonna cum!
How's that? Does that feel good?
I really want to do it. I want to take it all off.
If onii-chan sees me like this, he'll never talk to me again!
But... but... I want onii-chan's dick right here!
There are still many students in need of your semen.
You're going to become their savior, Asada-kun.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч