The Dark Hour...
That's what Headmistress Nijou calls the
phenomenon that falls upon this academy.
It's when some of the air from a different
realm flow into ours and forms a space
from which it saps the life force out of all those inside it.
And no matter how strong willed a person might be,
no one can help but fall victim to it and
crave for pleasures of carnal nature.
No, Asada-kun, not yet.
I haven't given you permission to cum yet.
I need to train your prematurely
ejaculating penis some more.
Try harder!
The Dark Hour slowly eats away at this academy and
the only person who can save all of those here is...
Me having sex with them and injecting my semen
into their bodies. There is no other option.
So deep!
Please forgive my vulgar hole.
This is all for your sake, Asada-sensei.
Oh no, I'm gonna cum! I'm so sorry!
You can cum in me whenever you want as well, sensei.
Dark Hour Academy
Fertilization Arc
Having onii-chan cum inside me... made me so happy
My insides are completely filled by your dick, sensei.
Yeah and your insides are sucking me in like crazy, Aoi.
Before I met you I didn't even know
anything about this kind of stuff.
But now I'm so...
So dirty now.
Isn't that weird?
Not at all.
Stir my pussy up!
Mess it up so bad! Please, I want it so bad!
Is the Dark Hour over?
Sensei, please don't stop.
You can't!
Just by being connected like this,
my p-pussy is twitching so much,
I can't stop it.
Aoi?
Please keep doing me until we're finished!
I don't want to leave you yet!
Excuse me?
Hello? Excuse me?
I want to buy The Sound of Piling.
B-Be right there!
S-Sorry, but we actually just ran out of that.
Oh, I see. When do you think you'll have it in stock again?
R-Right. W-We should... We should
have them in stock again next week.
Are you alright?
You don't look quite right.
No, I'm f-fine.
I-I'm just... you know, a little under the weather.
S-Sorry!
Sorry Aoi, I couldn't hold myself back either.
Sensei, I...
I kept thinking about what would happen if
she found out and it got me so turned on.
Th-This is seriously so bad, but...
Your dick is just so big and feels so
good that it turns me on so much!
Yeah your pussy feels really good too, Aoi!
Sensei, if we don't hurry, another customer might come!
Please make me cum! Please make
me cum hard with your dick!
Yeah, I'm about to cum, Aoi!
Your dick's getting hotter and hotter!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm... cumming!!
Your cum isn't stopping.
There's so much of your cum inside me.
It's flowing out of me.
The Dark Hour steadily began to affect reality as well.
Even when the Dark Hour subsided, some
of the student's sexual drives would not.
Sensei...
I can't...
I can't w-wait any longer.
Reina?
I want to drink it. I want to drink your cum, sensei.
Reina? The Dark Hour has already
passed. If anybody comes in right now...
This isn't a good place to be doing this,
so let's at least go somewhere else...
That's not good, sensei. You need to keep
your voice down or somebody's going to come.
Reina, stop!
If you keep sucking that hard, I'm gonna cum!
Sorry.
Your cum was so delicious.
B-But we're not done yet.
W-Wait...
I want to give you everything I have, sensei.
Even my anal virginity.
Reina, doesn't it hurt?
I've trained for this day.
Your dick is spreading out my asshole so much!
Sensei, please, move!
Move!
Alright. Just keep your voice down.
You're moving...
Your dick is going so deep into my ass!
I-It feels so weird. Even though my
asshole is being spread out so much,
my p-pussy... my pussy is...
Reina, I'm gonna cum inside your asshole!
Cum! Make me cum!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Your ass is sucking the cum out of me!
It's coming out, I can feel the mana.
P-Please, sensei.
This time put it in my p-pussy.
The Dark Hour even began to change
the mind of my childhood friend, Maya.
Look at all the dirty juices coming
out of the tip of your dick, onii-chan.
Just wait, I'll use my boobs to help you cum.
Maya? Maya!
That's...
Stop...
It's so hot!
Your cum's so hot!
W-Wait, I just came, so I'm gonna...
Don't worry, onii-chan. Keep cumming
all over my face and my boobs.
You can dirty me with your cum as much as you want.
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan's dick is going inside my pussy!
Onii-chan, you still want to cum, right?
Your dick is twitching so much.
And it's still so big.
So that means you want to cum, right?
M-Maya...
Onii-chan, you're looking at my boobs so much.
It's so embarrassing.
They're just jiggling in front of me. How can I ignore them?!
It's okay. Look at them more, onii-chan!
It's really embarrassing, but I want
you to look at them even more!
I want you to get turned on by my naked
body and I want you to cum a lot in my pussy!
Wow, after you came inside me, my pussy is getting so wet.
It feels so good.
Yeah, it feels really good for me too!
Please, I want you to move too, onii-chan.
Let's start feeling good together!
S-Sure.
Th-That's good, my pussy's starting to twitch so hard!
I've always wanted to have a lot of sex with you, onii-chan!
Maya, this isn't good, I might be getting close to my limit!
Sorry. Sorry, onii-chan.
I'm still not good enough.
I want your dick... your cum so
badly, I'm starting to lose my mind!
If she was ever in this condition without me around, then...
Please! Please cover me with all of your cum!
Fuck my boobs, pussy, or my
asshole! Fuck them all you want!
Fuck me up!
I... I can't let that happen!
I'm never gonna let that happen!
That's right. I have to give her my cum.
The only thing waiting for them is death!
If I ever die, other guys might try to hurt them.
That's right. I... I need to save them... save Maya!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Onii-chan! Onii-chan!!
Maya, I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum so hard inside of you!
Yeah, do it! Cum! Cum!
Make my pussy cum a lot with your cum!
Cum! Cum inside me!
It's so hot!
Onii-chan...
I'm so happy.
Headmaster's Office
translator: hikarucon
timing: hibrio21
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч