Principal Room
So good.
Asada-sensei's dick,
it's already this stiff and big.
And it's pulsating.
That's... because you two are sucking it at the same time.
It's alright.
No need to hold back.
You have a mission involving all of the women in this campus.
We need to constantly keep your dick lively.
If you keep sucking that vigorously,
I'm going to!
Wait. You mustn't!
If you want to cum,
then you'll have to fill our pussies with it.
That's right, Asada-kun.
Just keep going.
Stir me up, and make a mess of my pussy.
For the shroud is about to envelop us.
Nijou-sensei, what do you mean by the "shroud"?
I don't really know the details.
However,
once the shroud descends,
women's libido start going wild,
and we are simply unable to resist.
All that awaits us... is death!
But, I'm a teacher. For me to constantly violate students is.
Listen well, Asada-kun,
students lose control over their libido due to mana deprivation.
You, being a man, can provide the needed replenishment.
The only way, is for you to directly inject
your own seed to accomplish that!
It's alright.
It's okay.
The students will surely understand, sensei.
They know that you are their savior.
Eri-sensei!
Besides,
once the shroud descends, all we'll be craving for is dicks.
It makes our bodies go completely wild.
So please,
save the school.
Oh yes!
I'm about to cum again!
Amazing!
Sensei, if you keep clamping down on me like that.
This, too, is the effect of the shroud.
It makes my pussy so sensitive, that
it makes cumming a breeze!
My orgasm just can't be quelled!
Oh no, my pussy is pulsating.
I'm becoming even lewder.
Your insides feel spectacular, Eri-sensei.
I'm happy.
That makes me happy.
I'll make more of an effort to pleasure you.
So please, I want us to cum for this one last time.
I beg of you!
Cum.
Cum, cum, cum!
Give me your cum!
I want it inside!
Pump everything into my womb!
It's coming.
I'm going to cum too as it pours it into me.
Th-This is!
This is it. This is it!
It's flowing out.
It's pouring outside.
Wow. My body feels hot, and I feel invigorated!
We have now passed every last bit of our mana to you.
With this, you can keep dealing with
your students all night long.
It's coming.
It's about to come!
This is bad.
In this place... again.
Why? I'm the council president.
I can't believe I'm drowning in such lecherous pleasure.
It has begun.
The shroud has once again arrived.
You understand now, right, Asada-kun?
You shall use your seed to save the students.
I will.
I just put it between my breasts, and it's already twitching.
It's getting even bigger.
Your breasts are huge too, and it feels great, Kirika.
Shut up.
This is just.
Whenever the shroud comes, my breasts,
they just start craving for it.
It's about to drive me crazy.
So this feels good.
Doing this, makes it so big and stiff,
it's actually getting aroused with my breasts.
What is this? Oh crap.
I'm getting horny with this dick's scent.
My body's getting aroused, and my
breasts just can't get enough.
M-My... nipples.
They're getting erect the more his dick stiffens up.
What's this? I can't stop.
I can't stop!
Something's coming.
It's coming! It's coming!
It's about to come!
I'm sorry.
Oh no. This isn't nearly enough.
This sensation is amazing!
So thick!
Kirika, your pussy is too tight!
If this keeps up.
I got you just where I want you.
Your dick is just so big,
that it rubs so hard inside!
I can't keep up.
I want your cum so badly already.
Alright then.
Your big dick keeps on hitting my deep spots.
You just wait, Kirika.
I'll cum soon, and set you free.
My breasts, they're tingling!
No!
Milk, my milk's coming out!
It's squirting. It's squirting out!
My nipples are gushing out milk!
It's so tight!
Why is it squirting this much?
No, I don't like this.
It's like I'm a pervert!
We're about to finish soon.
So hang on!
Squeeze it. Squeeze it out more!
Let it all out until I can no longer squirt it.
Squeeze it till it goes all dry.
Sensei, please, I beg of you!
It's okay. Just keep squirting.
Kirika!
Your dick is bulging more and more!
It's prying my pussy apart,
and I can feel it penetrating deeper toward my womb.
I'm cumming. I'm about to cum.
Take it all!
I can't restrain myself, I'm going crazy'
Cum. Just cum!
Cum inside me!
Pump it all inside me!
Sensei.
Student Council Room
Sensei,
your love juices are starting to drip.
Your dick looks all wet and sloppy now.
R-Rio.
Here, can you see this?
My pussy seems to already be wet and horny.
I can see it clearly.
So you're getting horny as well.
Your rod is bulging so much.
It's so hot and it's twitching.
How lecherous.
I want to cum, I'm at my limit already!
You're about to cum while ogling my pussy, I see.
All the while being given a footjob.
Just let it all out right now, sensei.
My pussy will become soaked if you cum this close to me.
And that's... that's.
Oh no!
Rio.
No time for breaks.
We're just getting started.
See? You're craving for me, too, right?
You want to cum inside my pussy, right?
No... this is all the shroud's doing!
You don't have to keep it in.
I know you're delighted to have sex with me.
Your dick is so immersed in pleasure!
You're basking in this great pleasure, right?
No, that's not true!
I'm not the one getting horny with something like this!
It's okay.
Everything's the shroud's fault.
There's no shame in cumming.
Please don't compare me to any other woman out there.
This isn't nearly enough to make me cum!
It isn't!
Alright then.
I'll make this as quick as possible.
No, don't... you're pushing hard so suddenly.
No!
It's alright. Just give in to the pleasure.
It's okay to feel horny.
Stop!
I don't want to cum, and yet,
I don't want to feel horny, yet I.
No, stop, no!
How was it, Rio?
Cumming is amazing, right?
No way. This can't be.
I simply cannot.
It tingles!
No, that spot.
Not that spot, please!
Sorry, but I'm about to finish, too.
Just wait!
Your dick inside me is... is!
Stop.
You mustn't do that. Please don't finish inside me!
Stop! Stop!
I'm losing it!
Please, sensei,
give it to me. Give it to me already.
I'll become lewder if this continues.
I'm about to cum!
I never thought it would feel this good.
I want to keep doing it.
I want to strip myself bare.
If onii-chan ever sees this shameful act,
he's going to judge me.
But, but!
I really want onii-chan's!
There are still lots of students who need his seed.
You shall become their savior,
Asada-kun.