The Shroud.
Nijou Academy's principal, who is a fellow teacher of mine,
was the one who named the abomination
that suddenly attacked the school.
It has the ability to transfer otherworldly
emanations into this realm.
Emanations that feed upon the very
life essence of human beings.
Regardless of a person's mental fortitude,
it'll eventually lead their minds astray,
devoured by their own carnal desires.
Come on, Asada-kun, we're not done yet.
You have yet to deliver a more potent ejaculation.
I'm the one who's training your dull and sloppy dick,
so work harder!
As the academy continued being engulfed within the Shroud,
I tried to save them,
through sex.
There's no other way than to transfer my semen into them.
My Lord, please forgive my lewd anal fornication.
This is all for Asada-sensei.
Oh no, I'm about to cum.
Forgive me!
Please, just let it all out inside me.
My insides... they're completely filled
with your thick dick, sensei.
Your insides are sucking me inside like mad, Aoi.
I-I'd never experienced such pleasure before meeting you.
But now, I've become so slutty.
Strange, isn't it?
Yeah.
So please, just keep stirring my insides
and make a mess of this bitch!
Fuck me, fuck me lots!
The Shroud, disappeared?
Sensei, I don't want to stop now.
I can't.
Just being connected with you like this,
is enough to make my pussy pulsate like crazy.
I can't get enough of it!
Aoi!
Please, just please.
Fuck me until the end.
I don't want to be separated from you!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, I would like to purchase a filing notebook.
Coming!
I'm sorry
that item is out of stock right now.
Is that so?
May I ask when it will be available?
Well, next week.
I think we'll have it restocked next week.
Are you all right?
You don't seem quite well.
No, I'm fine.
I'm just a but under the weather.
I-I'm sorry!
Sorry, Aoi.
I can't hold back any longer.
Sensei, I...
I feel so anxious at the thought of being found here.
I shouldn't be doing this, and yet.
Your dick is just so big, and amazing.
It's making me so horny!
Your hole also feels great, Aoi.
Sensei, if we don't finish quickly, someone will come over again!
Please, let me cum.
Let my pussy cum lots!
Okay, I'm about to cum, too, Aoi!
Your dick is getting even hotter.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm about to... I'm about to!
I'm about to cum!
It's still flowing in, sensei.
There's so much of your cum.
It's overflowing.
The Shroud's influence is slowly corrupting even this reality.
Even with its disappearance, their lust never abates.
Sensei...
I can't...
I can't hold back anymore.
Reina?
I want to drink it.
I want to drink your cum, sensei.
Reina, the Shroud isn't present now.
If someone were to come here.
Hey, this isn't really the place for this.
At the very least, could we do this somewhere else?
No... it hits me even harder when you raise your voice like that.
Reina, stop!
No, I'm going to cum if you keep on sucking it hard like that!
Sorry.
Sensei, the way it squirted.
But, that's not enough.
Hey, hey wait!
I want to give you my everything.
Even my ass' virginity.
Reina, doesn't it hurt?
I've prepared just for this occasion.
Oh wow.
It's really opening up my asshole.
Sensei, please move.
Rough me up!
Alright, but keep your voice down.
It's moving.
Your dick is inside my asshole
and pushing through.
This feels very weird.
My asshole is being pried open,
and yet my pussy is... my pussy is.
Reina, I'm about to cum inside your asshole.
Me too, it's pulsating... convulsing...
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum.
Whoa, it's going to milk every last drop.
It's coming out.
I can feel the magical energy.
Please, sensei,
this time
in my pussy.
Since the Shroud could even corrupt minds,
my childhood friend, Maya, was no match for its power.
And I...
Your dick is starting to overflow with its love juices, onii-chan.
Just you wait.
I'll make you cum with my breasts.
Maya, Maya!
That's!
You can't!
So hot.
Your cum is so hot.
Wait, I just came earlier, I'll...
It's okay, onii-chan.
Just cum lots.
Soil my face, or my breasts, all you want.
It's coming out!
Your dick, inside my pussy.
It's in!
You want to cum more, right, onii-chan?
That's why it's twitching like this,
and become so big and stiff.
Right?
Maya!
Onii-chan, you're ogling my breasts so much.
I feel embarrassed.
I can't help but look at your jiggly protrusions!
It's all right. Ogle all you want, onii-chan.
I'm really embarrassed, but if it's you...
I want you to get a real eyeful!
Get aroused with my skin.
I want you to cum buckets in my pussy.
Amazing.
My pussy is all sticky with your hot cum.
It feels good.
Me, too. It's arousing me to a ridiculous extent.
Please, I want you to move, too, onii-chan.
Let's pleasure ourselves!
Got it.
Oh yes... my pussy's convulsing a bit.
I've always wanted to have sex with you like this.
Maya, this isn't good.
I think I'm at my limit.
I'm really sorry, onii-chan.
This won't be enough to fulfill me.
I'm cravng your dick and cum so much that I can't stop.
I'll go completely crazy if this continues.
This situation...
If I were to disappear.
Please, I beg of you.
Fill me up with all of your cum.
Cover my breasts, fill my pussy and my asshole!
Just rape me to your heart's content.
Violate me all you want!
That won't do!
I won't let that happen.
That's right, I have to fill her with my semen.
Or else they'll die!
If I lose here,
other men may corrupt these girls.
Yes.
I will be the one who shall save Maya,
I will be everyone's savior!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
Maya, I'm about to cum.
I'm pumping it all in!
Okay, go ahead.
Cum inside. Cum it all!
Make me cum as you climax inside me!
Cum inside me!
It's so hot.
Onii-chan.
I'm glad.
I'm delighted.
Principal Office