Direction
Incredible...
Asada-sensei your dick is
already hard... and shaking.
That's because Eri-sensei and
Nijou-sensei are sucking him.
It's all right. Don't resist.
You are the future of our school.
Leave me more horny with your dick.
If you suck hard like that...
I will...
No! You can't!
Sensei, you must appreciate us more.
Paint my whole pussy in white.
That's it. Do it strong.
Don't hold back.
Can you hear the noises from my pussy?
Meikoku should not take too long.
Nijou-sensei, what is this Meikoku?
I don't know...
I really don't know.
But we think it's something that can save the school.
And this is our last hope!
But why are you with a simple teacher like me?
No. I think you are the perfect
receptacle for the Meikoku.
But for this, you must attain nirvana.
The best way to achieve this is
by ejaculating inside a woman...
It's all right. It's gonna be okay.
Sensei, you know what need to do.
You can save the whole world.
Eri-sensei...
For Meikoku to occur you must use us multiple times
Fuck us until our bodies can't stand up.
Please, sensei.
Save our school...
Yes!
I'll cum again.
Amazing!
Sensei, I'm feeling strange.
It's probably Meikoku effect.
You're making so strong in my pussy
that I feel like I'm going to cum.
The orgasms don't stop!
Yes. I can't resist.
I... I'm still ejaculating...
Eri-sensei, it's very tasty inside of you.
Happy... That leave me happy.
I promise you that I will do my best.
Sensei, together...
Let's cum the last time together.
Please!
Cum, cum, cum, cum!
Let go of all your semen inside me!
Yes. I'll cum.
Your dick is bigger...
I... I'll cum!
T-That...
T-That is...
It's... It's flowing out of me...
Incredible.
A strange energy is flowing through my body.
We have our Sovereign.
But it's too early to welcome.
You've all this power, right?
Thereby, it should be one less problem.
The help of the students will be necessary.
Is coming...
Has arrived!
Not this one...
This is happening here now... Again?
Why?
I'm the president of the student council.
I should not be feeling such pleasure here.
Started.
Stop... The Meikoku.
You understood, sure, Asada-kun?
Your semen is our salvation.
Yes!
The semen of hope is you...
The semen of sensei, we need his help!!
I'm just doing it with my breasts
because you're shaking too hard.
Can your dick get even bigger?
Kirika, her breasts are amazing.
S-Shut up!
I'm just using my breasts because of Meikoku.
Oh... I can feel you...
I-Is it good?
You can masturbate with my
breasts however you want.
What is it?
Not this one! The smell of his dick will make me cum.
My body is getting hot.
I can't stop my breast.
M-My nipples...
My nipples are hard because of that dick.
What is it!? I can't stop!
I can't stop anymore!
Is coming! Is coming! Is coming!
Is coming!
It's here!
Sorry.
C-Can't...
That will not be enough of sensei.
This sensation is amazing!
Cum!
Kirika, you're moving too hard!
At this rate...
I don't know anything...
It's because of this big dick
that's shaking inside of me.
O-Oh...! I don't want it.
Fast! Fast! Cum on me!
I-I understood.
Your big dick is ripping my insides.
Endure it, Kirika.
I'll soon set her free.
M-My breasts...
My breasts will make me cum!
No!
Is coming out milk of them!?
It's coming out, it's coming out!
It's coming out!
My nipples are upright to let the milk out!
A-Amazing! I'll to vitiate with it.
Why? Why is there so mush milk in my body?
I don't want! I don't want! I don't want it that way!
I don't want it anymore!
Soon... Soon will end.
Hold on!
More! Push more your dick!
Continue until you empty it!
It will continue coming out of my breasts...
S-Sensei, I beg! I beg...
Kirika, it's okay, let it all out.
No!
Your dick is getting bigger.
Let all of your semen into my pussy until overflows.
I'll cum! I'm cumming!
Get everything!
It's unacceptable to leave my pussy hungry!
Cum! Cum!
Let go...! Let go inside of me!
Fill my pussy with your cum!
Se...
S-Sensei...
Student council
Sensei, do you think it can get tough here?
The tip of your dick is sticky.
R-Rio!
Can you see?
My pussy is wet become of you.
Let's do this together, right?
Yes, I understood.
Sensei, you look so good.
Look at his condition.
Your dick is hot and shaking.
Your dick is indecent!
I want to cum.
I... I'm on my limit!
You certainly want to get into my
pussy before you wet it, right?
You want to leave a lot of
hot semen stuck inside me.
Do you want it, sensei?
It can't be. My pussy is shaking with such pleasure.
I-It can't be... This...
No!
Rio...
I think it's the end of the break.
Then, we'll begin the hard work.
Come on, sensei, are you liking me?
Is good the pleasure my pussy gives you?
Don't try to extract the Meikoku so fast.
I-I will not hold me.
I'm happy to be having sex.
Your dick is very good. I can't avoid!
You too Rio, are very excited.
Y-You are wrong!
You aren't right!
I don't feel pleasure in doi...
It's all right.
You and the others are under the effect of Meikoku.
So you don't have to be ashamed.
I... I don't know what that means.
I don't feel any pleasure.
I understood.
In that case, we'll finish fast.
N-No. Stop!
You're doing very strong suddenly.
No!
It's all right. Don't worry.
Just feel good
Stop this!
I said that this is useless.
You don't excite me.
No, no, no, no, no!
Rio, how are you?
Are you feeling well now?
A-A-A-About this...
I...
N-No... Not there...
No! Stop rubbing your dick on me!
Sorry, I'm almost ejaculating.
S-Stop...!
Why is your dick going so deep in me?
Stop this or I'll go crazy.
No... No... No!
I'll cum!
Please, sensei,
fast, fast, come to me!
In this rate, I'll go crazy.
I'll cum with my fingers.
I don't know what to do.
This... It's very exciting.
More...
I need something else.
I-If my onii-chan see me like this...
I'll hurt him.
Even so... But!
I will... here... with the onii-chan...
You still need to pour your semen into the students.
You are the only one who can save us.
Asada-kun...