I'm sorry.
Keita-kun.
Crazy Bitch Ayuri's Nonstop Begging: Heardphones Permanently Equipped
1st Single. Struggles of a No-name Former
Idol! I'll Make a Good Song by Having Sex!
I'm sorry to say this, but after this month,
Ayuri Utakata's contract will...
Please wait! You have to give us a chance, I'm
certain her career will make a comeback!
Ayuri Utakata's Manager: Keita Haruyama
You say that, but ever since she announced her
retirement as an idol, Ayure Utakata has been
nothing but a dead weight for out company.
It's not like we can keep a manager on a singer-songwriter
who doesn't sell at all for so long, you know?
I'll make her write the best song you've ever heard!
Please, rethink dropping her contract
until you hear her song!
I'm only giving you one chance. In one
week, play me her song and we'll talk.
One week? Oh c'mon.
Well she'll just be fired right away then.
One week is asking the impossible.
No! It's your job to make it
happen, Keita Haruyama!
You can do it! Believe it!
I'm home! Ayuri-san?
It'll be better for everyone if I just die.
Please don't say stupid stuff like that!
You're right... I'm so stupid... I just have
to die then! I'm sorry, Keita-kun.
Listen to what I'm saying!
I can't finish the song... And you just went and
left me... There's no choice for me but to die.
I was at the Agency.
I wrote you a suicide note, please read
it, and please don't forget me.
No, you should just forget about a
girl like me and become happy.
But I can't really forgive you becoming
happy with a woman other than me.
I'll die, and you'll be mine forever...
I'll never let go of your heart!
Ayuri Utakata
– Ayuri-san is always like this... As soon as something
goes wrong, she toys with the idea of death.
– Just cut.
Ayuri-san is always like this... As soon as something
goes wrong, she toys with the idea of death.
– Ayuri-san is always like this... As soon as something
– I'll jump off!
– I have to deal with her every single time she goes throught this...
But I'm trying my best to make it work!
I became the manager for the Ayuri-san
who I admired so much! So...
So I have to be the one that's there for her.
I have to support her now..
and in the future as well.
Good-bye...
Speak of the devil!
I can't believe you.
Fuck me.
Fuck me like you always do!
I can write a song if you do!
You'll stop saying you'll kill yourself?
Yeah!
Uhh, Ayuri-san?
What?
I didn't even consent yet!
Keita-kun's dick smells so good. I love this smell.
Ayuri-san, your pussy tastes good.
Stop! If you suck so hard, I can't lick you...
No, I'm starting to feel good.
Stop, I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Keita-kun?
W-wait! I just came!
N-no, it feels so good! Sex feels so good!
Tne pleasure is coming... The sound... The
song! It's coming to me! It's coming!
No! He's making me cum again! I'm cumming!
I have to record our memories together!
Let's go on a date! I can write a
good song if we go on a date!
Are you for real?
Erotic toys!
Come on, you have to walk properly.
Y-yeah.
If you give such an obvious reaction, you'll
be found out right away, you know?
Everyone will know that former idol Ayuri Utakata is a
pervert who goes on walks with rotors in her pussy.
N-no!
Keita-kun...
You're complaining when you were
the one who suggested it?
You're going to turn the pleasure into
sound and write a song, right?
Here, I'll make you feel even better.
I can't hold it! I-I'm going to...
That turned me on so much!
A little too much... You even wet yourself.
You're one to speak, Keita-kun,
when you're like this.
That's...
Let's have sex... Use my pussy, okay?
What was that?
Yeah yeah, that superior is such a dickwad! Just
the other day, during our business visit... Huh?
Quiet.
Oh, sorry, I thought I heard something
but it was nothing.
Yeah, so that superior...
Recently, he's unbelievable, you
know? I can't stand him.
The air is filled with lewd noises.
Looks like you'll make a good song, Ayuri-san.
Yeah, I'm heading back now. He's such a piece
of work, thanks for listening to me complain.
Meanie.
It's your fault, Ayuri-san.
Huh? It suddenly became really hard.
Wait, Keita-kun! You're so rough!
No! I'm about to.
That was so much fun!
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Hey.
What?
Nothing...
Keita-kun?
Huh? You're... Toudou-san!
Station Producer: Toudou Midori
Long time no see! Are you alone?
Huh?
I heard you became Ayuri Utakata's manager?
Oh yeah!
Something wrong?
N-no, I'm fine.
Is it true she's writing songs now?
I recently got chosen to be
in charge of a music show.
If Ayuri Utakata releases a song, could
you book her to come on the show?
Really?
Of course, we worked together when she
was an idol, I'd love to have her on.
Toudou-san...
Keita-kun sounds like he's having so much fun...
He doesn't care about a pessimistic girl like
me who isn't making any progress.
Thank you so much!
Huh? What happened?
N-nothing at all.
I'm just holding Keita-kun back... But
I'll never let anyone else have him!
Oh goodness, it's already this late. Contact
me about the music show booking, okay?
Of course, thank you very much!
I can't believe you.
She was really pretty... You wouldn't be able to
turn her down if she came onto you, would you?
Huh?
Look at you, you're so naughty.
You want to come in here, don't you?
Don't be in a rush, just listen to what I say.
That's an amazing situation!
Keita-kun you...
Idiot!!!
Translation: ShamelessPersimmon
Timing: ShamelessPersimmon
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч