Sorry...
Keita-kun...
Mentally Troubled Ayuri's Insatiable Desires.
The headphones can't come off!
1st Single. The big crisis of a former idol that
isn't selling! Create a good song with sex! Arc
I'm sorry to say, but...
We're going to end the contract with
Utakata Yuri at the end of this month.
Please wait!
Just give her a chance!
She'll definitely make a comeback!
Utakata Ayuri's Manager
Haruyama Keita
You say that, but...
But supporting an idol after she
retires is just unnecessary baggage.
We can't assign our managers
to idols who can't sing or write.
I... I'll get her to write the best song ever!
Please wait on dropping her until you hear her song!
You got one chance.
Bring me her next song by next week.
One week?! That's too short!
Then how about I fire her now?
One week? There's no way this is gonna work.
No, you're going to make it happen!
Haruyama Keita, you can do it!
I'll do it!
I'm gonna do my best!
I'm home.
Ayuri-san...
I'm sorry... I'm better off dead...
Don't be stupid!
You're right... I'm stupid...
Dying's the only option left to me!
I'm sorry, Keita-kun!
Listen to me!
I can't even write a single song and you
keep going out to who knows where.
Dying's the only option, right?
I told you I was going to the office.
Well since you're here now, be sure to read that, okay?
Don't forget about me, okay?
You might be happier forgetting about me.
But I don't think I could ever forgive you if
you became happy with another woman,
I'll die and become a ghost.
Utakata Ayuri
I'll bind myself to you and never let go!
This is how Ayuri-san always is.
Whenever something goes wrong, she
instantly jumps to trying to take her own life.
Ayuri-san?!
I'm going to jump!
And I'm always just pulled around by her like that.
Ayuri-san?!
Ayuri: Keita-kun, where are you?
But I've been trying to take it straight on!
Keita: The office. I'm taking with the president.
Ayuri: The president?
Ayuri: You're in love with her?!
Ayuri: Is she more important than me?
Someone like me could never compare to her.
I mean I was able to make my dream
come true and become her manager!
That's why...
That's why I'll always support her!
No matter if it's now or in the future.
Farewell.
Do you not listen?!
You're such a...
Have sex with me.
Huh?
Have sex with me like you always do!
If you do, I'll be able to write a song!
Will you stop saying you'll kill yourself?
Yep!
Um, Ayuri-san?
Yes?
I haven't even said yes yet!
Your dick has such a good smell, Keita-kun.
I love this smell.
Your pussy tastes so good, Ayuri-san.
Don't! Don't suck so hard! If you do, I can't focus!
Stop!
I'm starting to get turned on!
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm gonna cum!!
Keita-kun...
Wait, I just came...
No, it feels so good!
Sex feels so good!
I can feel my senses returning to me.
The sounds... the music...
I can do it! I can do it!!
No, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!
Let's make some great memories together!
Let's go on a date.
If we go on a date, I'll definitely
be able to write a good song.
Are you serious?
Dirty Pocket Tools!
You need to walk straight.
Yeah.
If you react too much, people will notice.
People will find out that the former idol,
Utakata Ayuri is a complete pervert.
No!
Keita-kun...
Wasn't this your idea?
Don't you turn your pleasure into music?
Come on, feel more pleasure.
No, stop.
I'm really... I can't...
I'm gonna...
That really turned me on.
Yeah a little too much. You basically peed yourself.
Yeah, but look at you. Look how big you are right now.
W-Well, that's...
Let's have sex.
Use my pussy, okay?
Huh, what?
Yeah, seriously, I hate that boss.
She was even one of the people being audited...
Stay quiet.
Sorry, thought I heard something. Don't worry about it.
Yeah, yeah, and that same boss...
But yeah, I guess there are people like that.
I'd be lying if I said I couldn't believe it.
You're making such dirty noises.
I bet you're gonna make a great song with this, Ayuri-san.
Yeah, I'm going back now. He's such
a pain, thanks for letting me vent.
You big meanie.
This is your fault, you know?
Huh? You just got really hard...
Wait, Keita-kun!
You're being so rough!
No... I'm gonna...
That was so fun!
Glad to hear...
Hey, so...
Yeah?
Nothing at all.
Keita-kun?
Y-You're...
TV Station Producer
Toudou Midori
Toudou-san!
It's been a while. You alone?
Huh?
I heard you became Utakata Ayuri's manager.
Oh, yeah.
Something the matter?
Oh, no, nothing...
Is it true that she's writing a new song?
You know, I'm actually going to
be in charge of a music program.
Do you think I could get Utakata Ayuri on
my show after she releases her new song?
Really?!
Of course. You and I used to work
together when she was still an idol.
Toudou-san...
Keita-kun looks like he's enjoying himself.
I bet he doesn't care about someone like me
who's negative and unable to move forward.
Thank you so MUCH!
What's the matter?
Oh, no, nothing.
Someone like me is just baggage for him.
But Keita-kun is mine!
Oh dear, look at the time.
Don't forget about getting her on my show, okay?
Yeah, thank you so much!
You're such a...
She was pretty beautiful, huh?
I bet you couldn't reject her if she forced herself onto you.
Huh?
Look at what we have here. What a bad boy.
Do you want to come in here?
Don't be impatient.
Listen to what I say.
Crap, I'm getting hard!
Keita-kun, you...
Idiot!!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
And that was Utakata Ayuri.
Man, that's such a great song.