Just stop it already!
Why won't you come back?!
You're the one that said that you wanted
to turn your pleasure into music.
And today, I've already let you...
Let me... what?
Let me have sex with you? Is that it?
I get it! I'm not the kind of girl you'd have sex
with unless it's out of sympathy, right?!
No! Do you even know how much I...
How much you hate me?
I've torn up all the songs that I've started writing.
And I know that even though we're not dating,
I get jealous when you're with other girls.
Just forget it.
It's been several months since I've become her manager.
She's pessimistic and quick to pout.
She refuses to do things, which
makes things difficult for me.
She's basically a roller coaster of emotions.
Gleam
And whenever something happens,
she's quick to resort to having sex.
Huh...
She's been that way since the day we met.
She would ask me to help her find her melody.
But...
But I loved that side of her.
Ayuri-san...
Isn't she taking a little too long to come back?!
Don't tell me...
Ayuri-san!
Ayuri-san!!
Yes?
Your food's hot and ready to eat.
What the heck are you doing?!
Trying out newlywed role play to
maybe inspire something new?
That being said...
How about trying anal sex?
I'm all set up and ready.
'Kay?
2nd Single. Is that a girl creeping around the guy I love!? Stay with me forever ♡ Arc
Keita-kun...
Ayuri-san...
How is it?
So it feels good, huh?
Come on, tell me.
Come on, Ayuri-san.
It feels good!
It feels so good!
It feels really good.
More...
Do it more.
I'm going to... cum with my ass!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Your music...
Make me whole... with your music!
Cum!
Please!
Let it all out inside me...
It's coming!
Keita-kun's cum is coming!
It's going to come inside me!
To tell you the truth...
Hm?
To tell you the truth, most of my
songs were actually completed.
If I just thought about you...
My mind just became filled with music.
I just couldn't stop hearing it.
But if I completed my songs, that
meant that you'd disappear.
That's why...
That's why it's better if I just don't finish any of my songs!
I want things to stay like this forever!
After all...
After all, I like you!
I like you so much!
Keita-kun...
I like you.
I love you.
Even though I'm this annoying?
I'm in love with you.
Will you... be with me forever?
Yes.
If you ever disappear on me, I'll kill myself.
That's not a joke, okay?
That goes for me too.
I love you! I love you so much!
I love you so much!
I love you!
The music...
It's overflowing!
Hey, everyone!
Thank you for coming out here
to see me, Utakata Ayuri, live!
Today, I'll be announcing a new song!
Ayuri-chan!
Ayuri-chan! You're the best!
Huh? I...
Is this a dream?
Ever since that hot, tingling thing...
I can't be satisfied.
Nothing's ever enough.
Please try to remember.
Change your pleasure into music.
Isn't that your style?
My style...
My song... My last song...
For my song... my last song...
Please!
I want everybody's help to make it!
Cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
My insides are about to cum everything!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Let's dive into the feelings of these two!
Feelings Are You Real?
This might not be good enough.
Huh?
Waiting room B
Ms. Utakata Ayuri
I'm not talented and I'm not even cute.
I might not even pass the audition.
And if that happens then you won't be with me anymore.
You do have talent and you're definitely cute.
You're definitely going to pass.
And also...
I'll always be with you no matter what.
Keita-kun...
Don't give up, Ayuri!
Yeah!
You and me... just the two of us, holding hands.
Let's collect the fragments of this song together!
These passionate feelings between the two of us that were hiding
are ready to explode, I give you.
Ever since I experienced that tingly, hot thing,
I just can't be satisfied.
Nothing's enough anymore.
Can you give me just a little bit of your love?
I'll sing my best just for you.
The treasure deep inside my heart,
It's you.
You're the passion within me.
Just muster up some courage and try, please!
Just try staying positive!
You and me... the fragments of the two of us
are like treasures of this night.
My body and heart are both so full
because I know we'll always be together.
You and me... If we sing together,
we'll be able to find the fragments of our song.
You and me... the feelings between us
that are about to explode, I give you.
And that was Utakata Ayuri-chan.
Man, that was such a great song.
How do you write your songs, Ayuri-chan?
Through sex!
Come again?
When I have sex and start feeling good,
the music just comes to me.
And especially when I do it with the guy I love, Keita-kun...
Technical Difficulties
Stop the cameras! Stop them!
– What are you going to do about this?! This was live!
– The days of me being pushed around by her...
– We don't have the time to even editthat out!
Aren't close to being over.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
You and me... just the two of us, holding hands.
Let's collect the fragments of this song together!
These passionate feelings between the two of us that we're hiding
are ready to explode, I give you.
Ever since I experienced that tingly, hot thing,
I just can't be satisfied.
Nothing's enough anymore.
Can you give me just a little bit of your love?
I'll sing my best just for you.
The treasure deep inside my heart,
It's you.
You're the passion within me.
Just muster up some courage and try, please!
Just try staying positive!
You and me... the fragments of the two of us
are like treasures of this night.
My body and heart are both so full
because I know we'll always be together.
You and me... If we sing together,
we'll do able to find the fragments of our song.
You and me... the feelings between us
that are about to explode, I give you.
And that was Utakata Ayuri-chan.
Man, that was such a great song.