The spring of my second year at the university,
I fell in love.
Say, have a second?
What do you want?
You don't have afternoon classes, right?
Wanna go driving around town?
You have the guts to ask me out, looking like that.
Huh?
"Driving around town"?
Looking at your clothes, I guess it's a rental car or your parent's.
You're plain creepy.
Don't talk to me anymore.
Bu-But...
You're worthy of your Evil Queen title.
How many such sacrifices so far?
Come on, stop giving me weird names.
Isn't it that you can't get a boyfriend because you act like that?
Shut up... that has nothing to do with it.
I fell for her at the first sight.
She is Manami Ichijou.
Her style is awesome, and she's a real beauty!
She torpedoed and sunk every guy that asked her out.
And today I will...
confess to her!
This is my first time
so be gentle
FAKKU! Presents
Out of question!
Messy hair... a dull face... you're short... and wearing your shirts in?
To begin with, what are you thinking, confessing the first time we meet?
You guys only care about the looks of the girls...
Actually, yes.
I only care about looks!
I don't care about the personalities, I just love beautiful girls!
Hey...
And finally I met you, my ideal girl!
I won't give up!
What's wrong with him? Annoying guy...
Then will you lick my feet?
Here, come on, lick!
Then I will go out with you.
Are you serious?
He will surely give up from this.
I'd be glad!
It's like a dream for me to lick the leg of such a beauty!
Hey, wha-
You were wearing boots all the time, so your leg has such a thick smell!
Stupid! Don't say weird stuff!
Stop!
Enough!
You told me to lick.
I didn't think you'd actually...
What? What's happening? I will...
Manami?
Are you feeling it?
No!
But it's becoming really hot here.
Hey- Wha- Sto- Don't!
You're going too far...!
Don't... Don't lick... there...
I'm telling you not to lick there!
As if!
It's so beautiful.
Even your pussy is more beautiful than I could imagine!
Don't say such embarrassing things!
Why... Why can you do this to me?
I'm... considered a terrible cold-hearted person.
Because you're the most beautiful person in this world.
Stupid!
What, you passed out from that?
Manami?
You played with me mercilessly.
Now it's my turn.
This is... his cock?
I'm licking his cock!
It's twitching and hot!
He enjoys that I'm licking it...
Manami, if you do it so wild...
Shut up... how could I hold back?
This is the first time I'm doing this!
I'll come...!
Don't hold back, just come quickly!
It feels amazing, but it would be such a waste if I came right away.
Stupid...
I'll make you feel so good that you won't be able to hold back.
No... my mind's getting all hazy...
If I don't make him come quick, I'll be the one in "trouble"!
Manami... I'm... coming!
He's coming? He'll come in my mouth?
Sorry...
Oh look, didn't I swallow a little?
Manami's so late.
What is she doing?
I bet someone's hitting on her again.
Wouldn't be a surprise...
Yeah...
Manami, I can't hold back.
Wait a second.
This is... my first time... so be gentle.
So cute!
It's coming in... your cock is coming in...
Are you all right?
It hurts, but I'm fine...
Just move.
But...
It's okay...
It's my first time, so let's feel good together.
Manami...
Ama... Amazing!
I can feel it moving!
Your pussy is so tight!
The inside of my pussy... feels funny...
So deep... so deep in there...
This is amazing... sex really feels this good?
He's reaching all the way in... it almost feels better this way!
Are you feeling it?
No... I'm not... that kind of a girl...
But here it's so wet...
Just because you're so wild.
Are you still going on?
They'll find us if we don't hurry...
I think I'm coming soon.
It's okay.
You can come inside me...
But that's...
I'll be fine... you want to come in me, right?
Then...
Let's finish it from the front.
Why?
Because I want to see your beautiful face when you come.
Stupid...
You only care about looks!
I'm coming... I'm coming, Manami!
I'm coming too!
I'm coming! Look!
Look at me coming!
It's too much...
I haven't asked your name yet...
I'm Shou. Shou Mitarai.
Then Shou... you'll take responsibility for this, right?
A few days later
Say, Shou, is it good?
I tried putting spinach in the omelet today.
Yeah, it's great!
That's fabulous!
Manami changed so much!
Huh?
She was the Evil Queen until now...
I stopped that!
This is called sweet and sour?
Or rather a sex-addict slut?
Shou, does it feel good?
Does your cock feel good?
I'm coming...
Okay... Let out a lot!
Come a lot on my tits!
Shou, more! More!
I can see it all! Your cock moving inside me!
But you're turned on more this way, aren't you?
Don't say that!
It's so embarrassing... but...
More... give me more!
Mess up my pussy as much as you want!
Manami...
Shou... Shou...!
Tell... tell me you love me!
I love you, Manami!
I'm... I'm coming!
Oh, Shou... I love you!
Ah, so cute!
Is this the miracle of love?
Master, give us more semen!
Fill your bad maids with your cock!
Sure, why not!
Feel free to come wherever you wish, Master!
So much... Master's semen is covering my body!
It's amazing! You came so much, and yet still...
Master, your cock is so hot and twitching...
Come on, I can still go on!
Master!
I love you... I love you so much!
These maids are so amazing!
Right? These Nadesico maids are hard to forget.
What are you guys doing?
Akina?
You guys are just disgusting.
You maid-maniacs.
Hey, what are you doing?
You think such stuff are allowed in school?
Masaru, you idiot.
My precious...
Masaru, Shindo Akina is your childhood friend, right?
Couldn't you do something?
Nah... we just live close, there's nothing else anymore...
Isn't that a real sweet and sour?
No way! She's the farthest possible from the maid type!
Masaru, you idiot.
Why did we end up like this?
We got along so well earlier...
I should give back this mag...
Sorry, Akkie... Masaru hasn't come home yet.
I see... Then...
Come in and wait for him if you want.
I'm about to leave too, would you look after the house?
Huh?
Are you busy?
No, sure it's okay...
Why did I come to Masaru's room?
How many years since i've last been here...?
It's still the same as back then...
Masaru... actually bought that?
He really likes it.
No way! She's the farthest possible from the maid type!
What? If I wore such cute clothes, even I...
Oops, I turned into a maid!
The size fits me perfectly!
I'm back!
Masaru?
He's coming... I've to hide!
Here he is!
Damn, I left my uniform there!
But what's going to happen now?
Huh, what's that? Is that used for pervy stuff?
What is this doing in my room?
I see.
He's coming! What now? He'll find me!
What are you doing?
It's not what it looks like!
I didn't know that you were into maids too.
Stop... I apologized and everything.
You read that mag, right?
Then you know what maids are supposed to do.
As if I could do that.
You found out my embarrassing secret.
Now let's make some embarrassing memories for you too!
I get it! I get it! So I should just do it, right?
First a kiss on the tip, as the sign of loyalty!
Become a true maid!
Yes, Master.
Ugh... I'm kissing him at such a dirty place...
Great, now start playing the flute.
Why? It's so embarrassing, but Masaru commanding me makes my heart pound.
You're good! Just like that!
This can't be!
What? I'm enjoying it?
My head feels dizzy...
Now your reward.
How is it, Akina? Can you feel my love filling your mouth?
It hurts... it only hurts and yet...
I can't defy Masaru... my master...
Wow! The way your tongue tickles the back feels amazing!
He said it feels amazing... He enjoys my mouth...
Come on, Akina, you move more!
Yes, Master.
It's so big, my mouth feels strange!
Good, Akina! See you can do this!
Master's cock is twitching...
I'm coming, Akina! Take it all in your mouth!
I want to drink it! Let me!
Don't spit it out!
I told you to drink it all!
This...
What? Don't cry from this much!
Sorry, I got carried away...
I'll forgive you if you listen to what I've to say.
Sure, what is it?
Look close.
Akina?
Please, use me... Please be my master... only mine.
You're all wet down there already.
Sorry, I couldn't stop.
Akina, I can't hold back...
Yes, understood, Master.
I will make you feel good with my insides.
What? Did you come from just putting it in?
Please forgive me, I came too quick!
Come on, move and make me feel good!
Yes!
Master, do you enjoy my pussy?
Yeah, it's good!
Thank you!
Your cock is amazing too, Master!
Amazing! My pussy is...!
It's all the way in...!
Your master moves for you, be grateful!
Yes, Master, I'm happy!
Akina, stay my maid!
It... It'd be my honor!
Ever since I was a kid... Akina was my...
Master was always my...
I'm coming, Akina!
Yes, inside... inside...
Fill my pussy with semen, Master!
Master...
I love you!
The next day
Huh?
Let's go together.
Hey, what...?
I'm happy that we ended up together, Master.
Master!
Don't call me that just like this!
My Master was taken...
That girl... can't get away with this!