I'm home...
Welcome back.
Reiko? What's wrong?
The way he looks at me... I bet he thinks I'm weird.
Why are you dressed up like that?
How is it? It's apron only. I didn't wear anything under it.
H-how is it?
Oh, you're in the mood too!
You like this kind of stuff after all, don't you?
Hey, this is the entrance...
Look how big it is already.
This sweaty smell as you get back from work...
It turns me on so bad...
Stop... I haven't even taken a bath...
It's been a while since I last tasted this.
It's so delicious!
Reiko... You shouldn't...
No. If I back down now, I'll lose everything.
I'll bare the embarrassment and do this wearing an apron only!
God... It's been so long, this feels too great.
I'm glad! He enjoys it.
He's enjoying my blowjob...
It's okay, just let it out like this!
You have a lot in you, right?
Don't worry, I'll take it all.
Reiko, I'm cumming!
Cum! A lot in my mouth!
This is amazing!
If you had this much in you, that means you had no other affairs.
Affairs?
Always by the time I got home, you were sleeping already,
and we could never have some pervy fun.
Reiko...
I considered what if you were cheating on me...
That's why I...
I'm sorry that I made you feel bad.
I can't take it anymore...
I'd like your cock right here!
Reiko!
It's great!
Just it's been so long, I'm too sensitive!
Reiko, you're something amazing down here.
My hungry pussy is squeezing your cock tightly.
I'm enjoying this more and more!
Do... Do it wilder!
Move more, reach to the deep parts!
I want you to turn me into a complete mess!
More!
Reiko, I don't have a condom on...
It's okay! Let it out!
You can cum inside me!
Are you serious?
Yeah! We should become one!
Really? Does that mean...
I love you... I love you! So...
So please... give me... a lot inside me!
To the deepest parts of my pussy!
Amazing! So much is coming!
Give me... Give me more cum!
You're touching me so deep!
Amazing! Your pussy is so wet...
It's inviting my cock!
It feels so good that my hips are moving on their own!
No! Your cock is scraping out the cum from my pussy!
Don't worry, I'll fill you everyday from now on.
Please, let my pussy drink more cum!
I'm almost there...
I'm cumming!
Okay! Let's cum together!
I'm... I'm cumming...
The next day
Do you feel bad somewhere, patient?
Wha... Re...
Reiko!
It's coming! So much cum in me!
I'll squeeze it out every day with my pussy.
Maid, master,
and Number Two.
FAKKU! Presents
Hey, Akina, we really shouldn't!
I won't stop until he gives me a load!
I didn't know you were so lusty, Akina.
The cock tastes so good... The more I lick it, the more I want.
The precum is gushing out... It's all in my mouth...
Cum, please! Cover my face in cum!
Masaru's... Master's cum is so warm and thick!
Idiot! Remember where we are!
But today I can't go home with you because of the student council meeting.
It'd be bad if your doll took you back.
That won't happen.
You're my only maid...
Akina and I knew each other from childhood, but we were on bad terms until recently.
Because of misunderstandings and contentiousness we were in a war of neighbors.
I was relieving my stress with my self-made dutch wife, Number Two.
But one day, going with the unexpected flow of events,
we ended up as maid and master.
Please, use me... Please be my master... only mine.
It really caught me off guard what a lusty girl Akina was!
It's like a different person from her usual self.
Now that I have such a lovely maid for myself,
I'm taking on her offers every time.
Master, I love you!
But what should I do with Number Two now?
I can't just throw her out.
Welcome home, Master.
So cute!
... is not what I meant to say.
Who are you?
I am Number Two.
Huh? Number Two? Huh?!
Master, you shouldn't be so surprised.
Not the surprise, but there's just no way!
And I ordered that maid dress, it was to arrive today.
Yes. I received the package in your stead.
If you don't believe me, let me give you some service.
Service?
Come, this way.
Hey, wait!
You don't need to move, Master.
You have trained me well until now.
If I served you, you should realize.
Ah?  Akina already took a shot off you today?
How...?
I know.
I know everything about you.
I have always been with you.
I remember how you filled my mouth when Akina ignored you.
When you just barely passed a test, you used me wild and we cummed countless times!
That's...
You really liked it when I licked like this.
Hey, it's too much!
Master Cock is tingling.
You will grant me some cum, right?
I seriously can't...
It's all right. Please give me a lot of that good thick cum!
Please cover my face and my boobs with it!
Amazing! Master's semen!
Can I have a question?
Yes?
Why have you turned into this form?
I don't understand either.
Surely it's because Master loved me so much for so long.
I think the power of that love caused a miracle.
Then... are you really Number Two?
Yes! I'm Master's handmade dutch wife, Number Two!
It ended earlier than I thought.
This way I could visit Masaru's... Master's home!
How is it? Can you see my dirty places?
Number Two...
You don't need to hold back.
Please take me wild, as you have done so often.
That's...!
As I got this new body,
Master could take my virginity again!
I'm crying of happiness!
Number Two!
It's great! Master's thickness...
And hardness...
It's much better!
You feel great down here too, Number Two!
Thank you! You can do it wilder if you wish!
Please use my pussy as you wish!
How is it, Master?
It feels amazingly good to me.
It's great! Your pussy is sucking on my cock so tightly!
Because my pussy is only for you, Master!
Please enjoy me a lot!
Sorry... I should've realized quicker, Number Two.
It's all right, now that you believe me.
Master, let us stay together forever...
Master, I swear eternal loyalty to you.
Amazing! Your cock feels amazing in my pussy!
Oh! I am close to cumming!
Me too!
Please... Please fill me with a lot!
Fill my pussy... all of it...
Can this body bare children?
I wonder.
How dare you take another woman!
Akina! This is not...
She's, you know...
Who the fuck are you?!
I am Number Two. As Master's maid, you know me well, Akina.
Screw my ass! How could a dutch wife become human?!
I'm Masaru's... Master's maid!
There can be more than one maids.
Though one might be able to serve better than the other.
Challenge accepted! Let's prove who's more fit to be Masaru's maid!
Does it feel good, Master?
Yeah... your blowjobs are amazing, Number Two.
What? I could do that too!
I won't lose.
What? At the same time?!
Master, your cock is getting bigger.
This... feels too good!
Master is more excited than usually.
Is it because Akina is here too?
Damn! This girl is very good!
I can't lose!
Master, next I will serve you with my boobs.
Me too! I'll do it too!
My boobs feel better for sure!
Master's cock is so warm, it feels great!
It rubs my nipples, it feels great to me too!
Please enjoy, Master! I'll serve you with my boob-pussy!
I'm cumming!
Masaru, I love you! I love this so much! I want more!
So much! I'm so happy, Master!
It tastes so good!
It feels great, Number Two!
I totally spaced out when he came on my face,
but this girl is so enthusiastic...
Like a real maid!
If you suck so hard, I'll...
Master, please let me serve you with my pussy next!
Look, my pussy is dripping already.
I'll put it in.
It's amazing! My hips are moving on their own!
Akina!
Masaru, your cock feels so amazing! Give me more!
You are carried away by your own pleasure.
You are a failure as a maid, Akina.
Don't!
Number Two!
Move more, and use your hips to make Master feel better!
God, Akina is squeezing on so tightly!
If... If you do it so wild, I'll...
Don't do my boobs and my pussy at the same time...
I can't serve Master well like this!
I'm... I'm cuming!
So much cum in me...
Akina, I will show you what am I.
That's....
Is that mine?
Yes. Master stole it from you and used it to make my body.
Eh?
Well, how should I put this... I just...
Master made me imagining you when you were still friends.
So I am your Number Two, Akina.
No way...
So I can't forgive you!
You have no right to be cummed inside!
You were neglecting your duty towards Master for so long!
Don't rummage me like that! The cum is coming out!
Stop, hey!
I just came...
Master's cum is all mine!
It might be as you say.
But now so long as Masaru accepts me like when we were young,
I'll serve with all I have!
Akina!
I won't lose to you! To the myself of the past!
I understand. Apparently Master needs us both.
Yeah! You said it yourself, that there can be more than one maid!
Please, Master, stir up my pussy to the deepest!
Please fill me with your love too, Master.
It's in me! Master's cock is in my pussy!
Amazing! Feels like my cock is about to melt!
It feels better than ever!
I wish to serve your cock more and more!
Please let this lusty maid accept all your desires!
Masaru... Master...
I love you! I love you!
I want more! Please fill my pussy up completely!
Amazing! I'm hitting Akina's deepest parts!
I can feel it... at my womb.
Don't hold back! My pussy...
My pussy wants to be turned inside out by you!
This way all three of us can enjoy it at the same time.
What's this? It's not inside me and yet it feels so good!
Master's cock and our pussies are rubbing all together!
And our boobs are rubbing too!
Master, please, inside!
Okay, then I'll go with you first, Number two!
My boobs and pussy, everything is yours, Master!
Master, please use my pussy too!
I'm serving my Master!
Girls, I'm cumming soon!
Together! I'll cum together with Master!
My head feels like it's spinning.
Hey, do you still want to go on?
You say that, but look how hard you are!
Master, you are the embodiment of lust.
Ah well...
We will always serve you.
Please treat us well!
Master!