I'm home.
Welcome... Home...
Reiko...
What's the matter with you?
He's staring at me... I'm sure he thinks I'm weird...
Wh-what are you wearing?
Uhm... How's my nude apron?
I'm not wearing any underwear...
W-What are you saying...?
Oh... You're in the mood, too...
So, do you really like this kind of thing?
H-hey... We're at the front door...
It's already like this...
This sweaty smell after work...
This is exciting...
Stop it... I still haven't taken a bath...
This taste... I haven't tasted this for so long...
It's delicious!
Re-Reiko...
This is bad...
No... I shouldn't stop here... Otherwise this would have all been pointless...
I even put my pride aside and did this apron attack!
Oh my... I haven't done this in so long
and I'm feeling it already...
I'm glad... This is making him feel good!
He's feeling good from my blow job...
Go ahead... You can let it out...
It's been building up, hasn't it?
I'll take all of it!
Reiko... I'm about to cum...
Cum... Let it all out!
Wow... You built up this much...
I don't have to worry about affairs!
Affair...?
It's because... You're always asleep
when I get home these days...
And not having sex with me...
Reiko...
Sometimes I thought that you might be having an affair...
That's why...
I'm sorry I made you feel lonely.
I can't take it anymore...
P-please... Give me your dick right here...
Reiko...
It feels so good...
No... It's been so long, it feels so good!
Reiko's pussy... It's already raring to go!
My dirty pussy is sucking at your dick!
I'm feeling more and more perverted...
More... More... Give me more...
Move more and thrust it deeper...
I want you to ruin me...
More...
Reiko... I'm not wearing a rubber...
It's alright...
You can let it out inside me...
Are you sure?
Y-yes... Let's make a... Baby...
Our baby...
Are you sure..? That means...
I love you... I love you so much!
That's why...
Please... Give me...
Let it out inside me...
In the deepest part of my pussy...
So great... You came so much...
Hey... Give me more sperm...
It's rubbing deep inside me...
This is great... Your wet pussy is sucking it in...
It feels so good my pussy is reacting on its own!
No... Your penis is going to let out so much sperm...
Don't worry... I'm going to let it out inside starting today!
Please... Let my pussy drink a lot of sperm...
I can't take it anymore...
Here I come...
Cum.... I'll cum together with you...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
The next day
Is there anything wrong with your body...?
Mr. Patient?
R-Reiko!
He's coming... There so much of it!
I'll suck it all up with my pussy every day!
SubDESU-H
Presents
Menkui!
SubDESU-H
The Maid, the Master and the 'NiGou'-chan
Hey Akina... This is bad...
I won't stop until you give me a lot of it!
I didn't think that Akina was so perverted.
I've got more addicted to sucking this dick day after day.
There's a liquid coming out and it's filling up my mouth...
Please cum already...
Please let out all your sperm into my face...
Masaru's... Master's sperm is so hot and thick...
S-stupid... In a place like this...
It's because we can't go home together cuz I have student council work.
It'll a problem for me if you're taken by your sex doll.
No, I won't be...
Akina is my only maid, you know...
Akina and I are childhood friends, and up until a few days ago we've had an awkward relationship.
Even though we're neighbors, we've been ignoring each other because of our pride and various misunderstandings.
Everyday I've been taking out my stress on my sex doll, 'Nigou'-chan.
But one day...
Some strange things happened, and we're now happily in a master and maid relationship.
P-please... Make me yours...
Please, be only my master...
But... I didn't think that Akina was such a perverted girl who would shake her body like that on her own...
I just can't imagine it with her personality.
And now I have a lovely maid.
I'm being serviced everyday.
I love you so much, my master...
But...
Now things are like this, what should I do with 'NiGou'-chan?
I can't just throw it away...
Welcome home, master!
S-so cute...
N-no, no...
Uh... Uhm... Who are you?
I'm 'NiGou'-chan!
'NiGou'-chan...
Master... You don't have to look so surprised.
No... Even if you say that... It's impossible...
And that maid outfit - it's the one I ordered that should have arrived today...
Yes... I took it instead.
If you can't believe it, then let me service you.
A service...?
Well then... Go over there...
Eh?! Hey, wait!
You don't have to move. my master...
I've been trained by master.
If I service you, I'm sure you'll remember...
Oh, it seems Akina-san already sucked this...
How did you...?
I know everything about you, my master.
I've been with you always.
I know it.
You're always being ignored by Akina-san and you've complained about it to me.
When you got a failing grade, I was raped brutally.
You let me cum many times.
T-that's...
You like to be licked like this, right?
That's too intense...
Your dick is pumping...
You're going to let it out, right?
I'm at my limit...
It's ok, let out your thick stuff.
Let out your sperm onto my boobs and face...
This is great... Master's sperm is so amazing!
Hey, can I ask you something?
Yes?
Why did you become like this now?
Uhm... I don't know, but...
I think it's because master loved me for a long time,
and I think that the power of love made a miracle happen!
So you really are 'NiGou'-chan?!
Yes...
I am a hand made sex doll, 'NiGou'-chan,
made by you, master.
I finished earlier than I thought I would.
I think I have time to go to Masaru's...
master's house now.
How is this? Can you see it?
My dirty place...
'NiGou'-chan..
Don't hesitate... Just rape me intensely like always...
Eh...? No way...
Because of my new body... I'm able to give my virginity to you twice, master..
I'm so happy I'm crying...
N-'NiGou'-chan...
So good... Master's heat and hardness...
This is better than before...
'NiGou'-chan's place feels so good too...
Thank you so much...
You can be rougher with me...
Use my pussy as you like, my master...
So... Good...
How is it, my master...?
Does my hole feel good?
Yeah... It's great...
'NiGou'-chan's place is completely sucking my dick in...
My pussy is only for master's dick.
Please... Please use it and feel good!
Sorry... I should have noticed 'NiGou'-chan earlier.
It's alright... I believed in you anyway.
Master, please... From now on...
I promise to serve my master forever!
This is great!
Your dick feels so good in my pussy!
No... I think I'm about to cum...
M-me too
Yes... Please... Let it out... Let it out right now!
Let it out inside my pussy... My womb!
Will I able to make a baby with this body?
I... Don't know...
What are you doing bringing another woman into your room?!
A-Akina!
It's a mistake... This girl is...
How should I say this..?
Who are you anyway?!
I'm 'NiGou'-chan, I'm master's maid.
You know me very well, right, Akina-san?
Don't make a fool of me!
How can a sex doll become a human?!
I am Masaru's, master's, maid!
It's alright to have many maids.
But it's a different matter as to which one of us will receive more of master's love...
Sure... Then I will show you who'll be the most suitable maid for Masaru!
Do you feel good, my master?
Yeah... 'NiGou'-chan's blowjob is really great...
What...? I can do that too!
I won't lose!
Hey... Two at a time?!
Master... I'm going to suck your dick...
That's so good... It's great!
Master is more excited than usual...
Is it because Akina-san is here too?
No way... This girl is so good!
I can't lose to her!
Master... I'm going to serve you using my boobs next..
Me too, I'm going to do it as well!
I'm sure that my boobs feel better than yours!
Master's dick is so hot and feels so good...
My nipples are being rubbed...
I'm feeling good too!
Please feel good, my master!
I will serve you with my boobie pussy!
I'm cumming!
I love you, Masaru!
I love this so much... Give me more!
I'm glad you let out so much!
Delicious...
It's so good... 'NiGou'-chan...
It's all over my face and I feel dizzy, but
this girl is so devoted...
She's like a real maid...
Hey... If you suck that hard again, I'll...
Master... Let me serve you with my pussy next...
Hey... Look at my pussy...
It's already wet, so I'm going to put this in...
So good...
My hips are moving on their own...
Akina...
Masaru's dick feels so good!
More... More!
You'll fail as a maid if you drown in your
own pleasure, Akina-san.
N-no...
N-'NiGou'-chan?!
Move... Move more intensely... Move your hips as your master likes...
This is great... Akina's pussy is really sucking at my dick!
No... No... If you do that... I'll go crazy!
S-Stop...
My boobs and my pussy... Two at a time...
I can't serve him like this...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
So rude.
You let out a lot...
Akina-san... I'll show you the true nature of my existence.
That's...
Is that mine...?
Yes... Master secretly stole it and
implanted it inside my body...
Oh...
No... Uhm... How should I say this... It's because...
I was made from master's imagination while you two were still friendly.
In short... I am Akina number 2!
Eh? No way...
That's why... I can't forgive you!
Akina-san has no right to have you come inside her!
You didn't serve master because of your ridiculous pride!
Don't stir it...
The sperm will spill out...
No... Stop!
I just came a little while ago!
With this... Master's sperm is all mine!
Maybe you were right...
But... That's why I am doing my best right now to be noticed by Masaru!
Akina-san...
I won't lose to you... My past...
I understand... But I think master needs both of us...
Yes... You were the one who said it... It's alright to have many maids.
My master... Please... Stir my pussy deeper and deeper!
Me too.. Please give me your dick, my master!
It's coming in... Master's dick is coming inside my pussy!
This is great... My dick might melt!
This is the best one I've ever tasted!
My body will get used to your dick the more we do it...
Please... Punish this dirty maid many times...
Masaru... Master...
Love you... I love you so much... Please thrust it more!
Into my pussy!
So great... It's touching Akina's deepest part...
I know... It's touching my womb!
So good!
Don't hesitate!
You can do whatever you want with my dirty pussy!
We can do it together like this...
What's this...? He's not putting it in, but I feel so good...
Master's dick and our pussies are touching and rubbing..
Boobs and pussy are rubbing against each other!
Master, please... Put it in immediately...
Alright... I'll put it into 'NiGou'-chan first...
My boobs and pussy are all yours, my master...
Master... Please use my pussy too...
Me too... I'm going to serve you, my master...
You too... I'm going for it now...
Together... I'm going to cum with master together...
Cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
H-hey... Are we still going to do it?
Even as you say that... You're getting this hard already...
Really... Master is so horny!
Eh... No... Uhm...
We'll serve you forever...
So please love us from now on...
My master...
TL Note: "NiGou" literally means "Number 2", commonly used as slang to refer to someone's mistress