University student.
In the 2nd year of spring,
I fell in love.
Hey, hey, can I ask something?
What do you want?
You don't have any classes this afternoon right?
Let's go driving if it's ok with you
How brave, calling me out looking like that.
Eh?
Even if you say let's go driving, I know that you'll use a rental car or even your parent's car.
By the way, you're disgusting.
Don't ever come near me again.
N.. No way..
That's what I expected from the Devil Queen.
How many victims has their been already?
Hey, don't call me that.
Your behavior is why you don't have a boyfriend.
S.. Shut up.
It's none of your business.
It's love at first sight.
Her name is Ichijou Manami-san.
She has perfect style and very beautiful.
All the men who confess to her have their pride crushed and are thrown away.
I'm going to… confess to her today!
Subdesu-H
Present
Menkui
Subdesu-H
Present
Its my first time.. so please be gentle
What a problem!
Disheveled hair.
A dull face.
Short.
And a tucked in shirt!
What are you thinking confessing the first time we meet?
In the end, boys don't care about anything but a girl's looks.
Actually, you're right.
TL Note: Menkui - Means guys that only go for pretty girls.
I'm a menkui!
I don't care about your attitude.
I just love beautiful girls!
Hey..
Manami-san is my dream girl that I'll finally get to meet.
I won't give up on you!
What's with this guy?
What a troublesome guy.
Well then, try licking my foot.
Here, lick it quickly.
Then I'll go out with you.
Are you sure?
Hmp, he will surely give up with this.
I would be delighted to!
It's great that I can be able to lick this beautiful foot.
Hey!!!
Manami-san's foot is smelly because of your boots.
Stupid! Don't say such foolish thing.
Stop it!
No!
You said I could lick it.
I didn't think you'd actually do it!
No… what's this..
If this continues. . I'm going to…
Manami-san, did you get horny?
No!
But this part is already hot.
Hey!
Who said that you lick that… part?
No! it's dirty down there.
I said don't lick there.
No it's not.
Nooo
How beautiful.
Your pussy is also way beyond my expectations.
Don't say such embarrassing things.
Why?
Why are you going this far for me?
People call me a cold girl who only shows off her appearance.
It's because Manami-san is the most beautiful woman in the world.
Stupid.
What are you saying? Your so big down here.
Manami-san?
How dare you play with me.
But it's my turn now.
So this is a dick?
I'm licking a dick right now.
It's throbbing and getting hotter.
It's getting excited because I'm licking it.
Manami-san, if you suck that hard.. I'll..
You're so noisy… I can't hold back you know.
Because this is my first time.
Hey, I'm going to cum!
Hey, you don't have to hold back just release it.
It would be a waste to cum so quickly since it feels so good.
You're stupid.
I'll make you feel so good that you can't hold it.
No.. I'm getting dizzy.
I'm the one going to go insane if I don't get rid of this.
Manami-san, I'm going to cum!
He's going to?
He's going to ejaculate inside my mouth?
I'm sorry.
You dummy, I drank a little bit of it.
Manami sure is late.
What is she doing?
I think she's been picked up again.
She's so active.
Really.
Manami-san, I can't hold it any longer.
Wait a minute..
This will be my first time.
So.. can you be gentle?
She's so cute.
It's coming in!
Your dick is coming in!
Are you ok?
It's hurts but I'm alright.
You can move.
But..
It's ok, this is my first time so I want us to feel good together.
Manami-san.
Good.
It's so good.
It's rubbing.
Manami-san is so tight.
My stomach is being ruined.
It's touching the inner part.
It's so good.
I didn't think that having sex would feel so good.
I'm being penetrated in my innermost part, maybe this is better than before.
Do you feel it?
No I'm not.
I'm not that perverted.
But this part is all wet.
It's because your so rough.
Hey..  are you still gonna do it?
If you don't do it fast, someone might see us.
I'm about to cum.
Ok...
Release it inside.
But..it's..
Don't mind about me, you wanted to cum inside right?
Well then..
For the last part we'll do it in missionary.
Why?
Because I want to see Manami-san's beautiful face when you cum.
Dummy!
You Menkui!
I'm going to cum, I'm going to release it.
Manami-san!
I'm cumming too!
I'm cumming!
Look at me.
Look at me when I cum!  More!
It's so much.
I haven't asked your name?
It's Shou.
Mitarai Shou.
Well then, Shou-kun.
Please take the responsibility.
What!?
-Few days later-
Shou-kun, is it good?
I tried to put spinach in the fried egg.
Yes, it's so delicious!
I'm glad.
Manami…changed didn't she?
Eh?
You were called a Devil Queen a few days ago.
I already stopped that.
Is this what we call Tsundere?
"Tsundere – A girl who is initially cold but gradually shows affection over time."
Or pervert or Spoony?
Shou-kun does it feel good?
Is your dick feeling it?
Yes.
I'm going to cum.
Ok, release it as much as you want.
You can squirt it on my boobs.
Shou-kun, more, give me more semen.
I can see it all.
Your dick is thrusting inside me.
I can see all the dirty parts.
But you can get more excited with that right?
No… don't say that.
It's embarrassing.
It's so embarrassing but,
It's so good.
More..
Thrust more.
Ruin me more..
You can ruin me more.
Manami-san!
Shou-kun, Shou-kuin.
Say..
Say. “I love you”
I.. love you Manami-san.
I..
I love you so much Shou-kun.
Wow, how perverted!
Is the power of love is that strong?
Master, please give us more semen.
Please punish us with your dick.
Ok, sure!
It's so good master.
Release it where ever you want master.
It's so much.
My master's semen is sprinkled all around my body.
Wow…
Even when you release that much, it's still so hard.
Master's dick is so hot and throbbing.
Hey hey, I can still do it.
Master.
I love you.
I love you so much.
These maids are so perverted.
Aren't they?
These Nadeshiko maids are good.
Text on Mag. - Your sisters are my maids
Hey you guys, what are you doing?
Akina!?
Your really disgusting.
You maid Otaku.
What are you doing?
Your not allowed to bring this kind of book.
Stupid Masaru.
Oh~~ my treasured book.
Masaru, isn't Shiido Akina your childhood friend?
Can't you do something about her?
We're just neighbors.
We are not friends now.
She might be tsundere.
That's impossible.
She's not the type that can become a maid.
Stupid Masaru.
How did it get like this?
We were so friendly before.
This book, I guess I should return it to him.
I'm sorry Aki-chan, Masaru isn't home yet.
I see.
Ok then.
You can come in if it's ok with you.
I'm about to go out right now.
Can you take care of the house?
Are you busy Aki-chan?
Uhm.. no.
I can..
I came in.. to Masaru's room.
How long it has been?
This place hasn't change from before.
Masaru.. he bought something like that..
He really like that.
That's impossible.
She's not the type that can become a maid.
What?
If I wear this cute dress, I'll also..
Oh no… I'm a maid.
This dress fits me.
I'm home.
Masaru!?
He's coming here.
I have to hide.
He's here.
Oh my, I left my uniform there.
By the way, how should I get out from here?
What this?!
Is this a thing used for masturbating?
Why there's something like this inside my room?
I see.
He's coming here!
What should I do!?
I'm going to get caught.
What are you doing?
It's not like what you think, this is…
I didn't know that Akina has an interest in maids.
Stop it.
Didn't I apologize to you properly?
You read that ero book right?
Then you should know what maid should do right?
I can't do that.
My embarrassing secret has been revealed.
So you should feel embarrassed too.
I understand, I understand.
I should do it right?
Ok.
As proof of loyalty,
Kiss the tip.
Act as a real maid.
Yes master.
Oh my, I'm kissing this dirty thing.
Next, is clean the tip using your tongue.
Why? This is embarrassing but my chest is heating up being ordered by Masaru.
You're good, go on.
This is impossible.
Oh no, I'm getting horny.
I'm getting dizzy.
Ok then, I'll give you a reward.
How is it Akina?
You can feel my love all over your mouth right?
This is hard.
This is hard but.
I can't oppose on Masaru..  I can't oppose on my master.
Oh no, the back is being wrapped around by the tongue, it feels so good.
I see it's good.
He feels it from my tongue.
Hey, Akina, move more.
Yes master.
My mouth will be ruined if I suck something this big.
Good, you can do it Akina.
Master's dick is pumping and throbbing.
I'm going to release it Akina.
Take it all with your mouth.
Yes, I want to drink it.
Let me drink it.
Hey, don't spill it.
Didn't I tell you to drink it all?
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't cry over this little matter.
Sorry, I got a little carried away.
I'll forgive you if you listen to my request.
Ok, sure, what is it?
Look at me properly.
Akina?
Please make me yours Masaru.
Please become my only master.
Akina's part is already wet.
I'm sorry, it won't stop.
Akina, I can't hold it any longer.
Yes, I understand master.
I'll make you feel good inside me next.
Hey, did you cum just from putting it in?
I'm sorry.
Akina got to cum first.
Move fast and make me feel good.
Yes.
Master, does my pussy feels good?
Yes, it's good.
Thank you.
Master's dick is also good.
Good.
Wow.
My pussy is going to be ruined.
Good.
It's coming deeper.
Your master is moving for you, be thankful for it.
Yes master I'm so glad.
Akina, be my maid forever!
Yes, I'll be only your maid!
I've loved Akina.. since I was a kid.
Me too.. I.. love you.
I'm going to release it Akina.
Yes release it inside.
Release a lot of semen inside me.
I love you master!
Next day.
Huh?
Let's go together.
Hey wait.
I'm happy because you've finally become honest.
Master.
Master~
Don't call me if you don't have anything to say.
My master is been taken away.
I will not forgive that girl.