Previously on Mesu Kyoushi 4
Work is rough, but if I think of it as making
time for moments like this, it all feels worth it.
You really like your students, don't you?
Well, I'm an educator.
I want everyone who comes to this school
to know the joy of learning just like I do.
I want to do all I can for this school's
sake as well as the sake of the students.
I'm doing this with the intent of giving it everything I have.
Oh, my, sorry.
It's just rare to have a conversation with
a relative like you, so I blabbered on.
It's horrible how twisted a person you are.
This is so embarrassing...
Well now that you're done showing your disdain for me,
how about you spread your legs and show me your panties.
My legs?
That's...
You're actually licking it.
No...
Your tongue...
This isn't anything too abnormal.
Licking down there is normal?
I don't believe that!
Don't lie to me!
Then let me teach you. Thoroughly.
It's in!
It's inside!
It's inside me!
This isn't over now that it's in.
You're going to move and make me cum.
Make you cum?
Does that mean you want me to make you ejaculate?
Yeah. That's right.
Fine.
I'll move.
I'm going to end this quickly.
I'm not going to lose to something like this.
Your dirty virgin pussy really turns me on.
Then hurry up and ejaculate for me.
I want to hurry up and end this embarrassing thing already.
Good job.
Making me cum with your virgin pussy is impressive.
Take a look.
There's so much.
I'm definitely going to get pregnant.
You're such a good girl.
Let me give you a reward for being good
enough to make me cum with your virgin pussy.
You're inside me again!
It hurts! Don't do this anymore!
Okay then, let me help you feel good.
You're just a horrible person through and through.
Now what do you want me to do?
Show me your pussy.
You're very quick at coming up
with new ways to embarrass me.
This is fine, right?
I'm doing what you asked me to do.
What a vulgar position.
You're the one who told me to do this!
Hurry up and...
Keep your face away!
It's so perfectly shaped. Your labia is barely sticking out.
So innocent.
What does that matter?! Just hurry up and do it already!
Yeah, I'll do it with this.
Is that what I think it is?!
You're going to put that inside me?!
So you already have an idea?
You're right.
No! Are you really putting it in?
There's something wet on it!
It's not going in! It's not going to fit!
I put lotion on it so it'd be easier to put in,
but I guess I'll have to loosen you up a bit.
Orgasm?
No! I don't want to feel it!
I don't want to, but my head's
overheating... it's going blank!
The vibration's so strong!
No! Stop pushing it...
I'll let you feel the ultimate pleasure.
No!
I don't want to feel it!
It's getting hotter!
No! My pee...
No! No!
It's coming out!
Something amazing's coming!
I can't stop my pee!
No!
This can't be happening!
I...
What have I done on top of her desk?
Mesu Kyoushi 4 - Disgraced Teachers
The Immodest Headmistress Yuri ~ Fucking by the Window: Conquest through Exhibition~
The Headmistress will be observing this class today,
but don't let that take your attention away from my lesson.
Understood?
O-Okay then, let's begin class.
Open your books up to page nineteen.
Um...
So the definition of "sine"...
It might be a little late to start explaining the notation now, but...
You wanna do it here? Are you serious?
Let's get started.
Rub it with your hand.
Why's it so hot?
Is this a guy's thing?
It's twitching and pulsing.
Sorry to bother you when you're having
so much fun, but I told you to rub it.
You want me to do that with my hands?
What? You can't?
I-I'll do it.
I'll rub it now.
The students are right in front of me. What am I doing?
This is a really important point, so you
need to make sure you remember it.
So...
Oh god, Takamine-sensei can see this.
No!
Rub it harder.
Otherwise this'll never end.
Yeah, but I'm already worried
that someone's going to notice.
Not to mention that Takamine-sensei's watching.
Fine.
Hey! What are you doing?
If you don't hurry up, I'm gonna strip you even more.
You're horrible. I can't!
I can't handle this!
Take too long and someone might notice.
F-Fine.
I'll do it. I'll stroke it properly.
If I make it feel good and this is over quicker...
I have to touch this part too.
It got bigger! That means it feels good.
Right there feels good.
Yes, it does seem to feel good.
Even without you telling me, I could
tell that I need to focus right here.
Now then, it'd be a problem if I came just like this.
You can't. People would definitely notice that.
Yeah unless something can catch all of it.
Maybe underwear or something?
Why are you being so roundabout about this?
You wanted me to do that from the beginning, didn't you?
No, my underwear's being used for this?
Hurry up and cum.
You wanna show Miu?
Don't close them. Keep them open.
Just how much embarrassment do you want
to put me through before you're satisfied?
Hurry up and finish already!
It's getting even bigger.
Is it about to cum?
It's finally cumming, right?
Yeah, just a little longer.
I'm ending this now.
Just cum as much as you want.
Hurry and cum!
It's shooting out all over my underwear! I can feel it!
I can't believe there's so much of it.
Jacking off a student with your
hand while dressed like that?
What a great Headmistress you are.
B-But you ordered me to!
How could I...
Where are we going?
Well, a handjob isn't enough.
Now then, where to go?
How about my office?
I don't want to do this in front of people anymore.
Yeah, that works.
No!
It's inside me!
I don't want it! Don't come so deep inside me!
They're gonna hear you from outside.
What? Then just don't do this to me!
Well that's not happening.
These... These are the panties I just...
I'm gonna fuck you for real now.
It's going so deep and hard inside me!
No... I can taste the cum!
Semen in your mouth while I'm
fucking you... What a nice treat.
No! It's so bitter and I don't like it, but...
Your pussy feels like it's welcoming
me with open arms. Here.
That's not...
No! Stop!
Don't move it like that! No!
It's rubbing me so deep inside!
Stop!
You're saying "stop" even though you're enjoying all this.
No! That's not true!
What is this?
No! This...
Stop this!
You know what kind of moans
you're letting out right now, right?
No, these aren't moans, they're screams!
They're not dirty at all!
No! Stop! Please!
Don't! Don't! Please stop!
My head feels like it's going to explode! I'm losing my mind!
No!
No! Stop thrusting it in me!
I don't want it inside me!
I'm feeling hot again.
No, what... I'm gonna pee...
No! No!
I'm gonna pee!
And I'll pour my seed into you at the same time.
It's coming out! I'm peeing!
The semen's coming inside me at the same time.
No! Stop!
Please leave me alone.
Do you understand that you should fear me now?
Well, I can be much worse.
Anything of note here?
Hm?
A call between him and Yuri?
I guess the Headmaster isn't one to break that easy, huh?
It's already time for us to meet.
I really didn't want to have to resort to this, but...
U-Uh, Kazuya-kun, now's not a good time.
I have a guest coming any minute now.
So, um...
Oh, if you mean that piece of
shit Shirakawa, he isn't coming.
Your entire plan's been leaked.
I was careless to not expect the hidden cameras.
You might have thought that it'd be something to
blackmail him with, but the footage has no value.
It's sad how pitiful you are right now.
How about I really make you feel sorry?
Wait, please! I won't disobey you anymore!
I'll do anything!
Please forgive me!
You'll do anything, huh?
You better mean that.
Still not ready?
Or what, are you admiring yourself right now?
I'll do it. I'll be right there.
Good.
You're gonna give me a tit fuck now.
Put this in between your boobs and rub it.
S-Something that immodest exists?
Keep your surprise to yourself.
Use this on yourself and get to work already.
Th-That's a vibrator.
I-I'll do it.
Your big thing is in between my boobs. It's so hot.
I'm shaking down there too.
I can't believe you're making me do this.
So I push them together...
Just pushing them together doesn't do anything.
You just want me to rub it, right?
Wait, don't record this.
I'm recording this memory for you.
The memory of you swearing to never defy me again.
No, please. If you record me in this indecent position, I...
Please stop.
I'm not gonna.
I'll do it. I'll give you a proper boob job, so...
Please don't look at me when I'm like this so much.
You're moving them well.
You know what you're doing.
It's just because this is so embarrassing that
I want you to just cum and finish already.
The way you're looking at the camera
would put any porn star to shame.
I'm seriously not enjoying this!
I want you to cum, but it's not because I want your cum.
I think you like it when I'm recording you.
No! That's... I don't like this!
Your semen's jumping out onto me!
There's so much. The smell of it is so strong too.
No... Is someone here?!
Looks like someone's here to get ready for class.
This is the right place, right?
H-Headmistress?!
Hey, wait, what are you doing?! Why'd you call me here?!
Just to embarrass her.
I'm done with you. You can leave.
What?! What's with you?!
I just got here and now you're telling me to leave?!
Who do you think I am?!
Fine! Whatever! I'm leaving!
I don't care!
She saw...
Takamine-sensei saw me.
Don't worry, she's on our side.
You're kidding, right?
I'm embarrassed enough to die dressed like this!
An exhibitionist like yourself should
be crying tears of joy right now.
You're saying that I'm an exhibitionist?!
Don't be stupid!
I don't have that kind of fetish!
Then why is your pussy so wet?
No, that can't be...
Wait, this is because of the vibrator!
Just a joke.
But if you took me seriously for even a second,
does that mean that your body
remembers what exhibitionism feels like?
But somebody might actually come.
Clean up, will you?
So far, her training's going well.
I'm gonna make you mine, Yuri.
I'm here.
The reason you called me to this classroom...
is it because you want to do dirty things here?
Of course.
Change into those, if you would.
This... I can't... You don't really
want me to wear this, do you?
I'll never be able to face the students here again if I do
this in this outfit as the Headmistress of this school.
Stop looking at me.
I-If you're going to do it, just hurry up and get it over with.
Wh-What?
No! Stop!
You can't grab my boobs all of
a sudden, especially not here!
Yeah, the people leaving school might see you.
Exactly why I don't want to do this!
I don't want anyone seeing me
do these things in these clothes.
What? Don't you get off from people
watching you do these lewd things?
I already said this before, but I don't like exhibitionism.
Don't make things up.
You're stubborn.
Then let's test this.
S-Stop! Stop rubbing them!
Don't! The people outside will see!
Yeah, your outfit is already embarrassing enough.
Too hard... No, stop this!
No! Please!
No!
That student over there's gonna hear you.
Oh, that's a male student too.
Oh no, he's going to hear me.
He's going to see me! No!
No... He's looking!
He knows!
My students are seeing my boobs.
They might be able to see your boobs, but they
won't be able to tell that it's you from that distance.
Don't worry.
What? That's not comforting at all!
Let go of me and let me leave!
They already saw you, it's a bit too late.
Stop!
If they find out who I really am...
I can't let that happen!
They won't find out.
All that's gonna happen is him using
the image of your boobs to fap later.
F-Fap?!
A student's really going to use my
boobs for something like that?
That's too embarrassing!
Looks like something's getting excited.
I'm not getting happy from being seen!
I'm not!
I'm really not!
Did you really just cum from your boobs?
And you still insist that this doesn't feel good?
No! No! This can't be! Your hard thing's
inside me while people are watching!
Looks like they ran away after seeing my face.
There's nobody left in the audience now.
Your hard thing's hitting me so deep inside.
Quite the dick, isn't it?
This is just the embarrassment
speaking. It doesn't feel good!
It doesn't feel good at all!
And you're telling me that the way you feel
right now and the embarrassment aren't linked?
They aren't!
It's because you keep thrusting against my womb so hard!
That's why...
Oh, no. It feels so good! But I shouldn't be feeling this good!
So you just admitted it, didn't you?
That wasn't intentional!
It's just because you keep doing all these dirty
things to me, my body's just getting used to it!
My body's the one that's feeling good.
I don't feel anything from this, okay?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч