Astonishing...
Could you even call yourself a student of Seishuu Academy?
The Super Elites would be shocked if they heard about this.
You'll drop out before long if you go on like this.
Whatever.
Well then...
You, solve the problem.
That's the right answer.
Although it's only natural that you'd be able to solve this.
Alright, then!
O-okay, that's it for today!
Properly review this at home!
Class president, the order!
Stand up.
Bow.
Takamine-sensei, could I have a moment?
W-what?
That again?
I'm not even doing anything unusual.
Too suspicious.
Don't trouble me with your cheap attempt at revenge.
I'm punishing you
Don't be so mean, so cruel!
That's what your position is.
You miserably degraded yourself into my subordinate.
Right?
Who are you?
That hurt!
And to think that a deficient flea like you would skip class.
You see, I suddenly got a stomach-ache...
Stop lying!
Even if you are a relative of the principal, I won't let you off!
You're getting supplementary lessons right now!
You don't come across very intimidating with your panties out like that.
W-what are you looking at!
You're skipping, impolite and even peeping!
I'm doubling your detention!
I'll show you hell.
It's too late to for regrets.
Is that all that you wanted to say?
W-what?
What's this suddenly?
Stop!
Let me go!
You flea!
Huh? That hurt.
That hurt!
You hit me.
Was that too intense?
What are you doing?! Idiot!
I'll report this to the higher-ups!
I'll never forgive you for this!
Go ahead, report me.
No!
Wait!
Idiot, what are you doing?!
Why are you touching that place?
You should be familiar with this by masturbating.
I don't do things like that!
Let go! Take your finger out! Idiot!
I guess I'll teach you how to play with your pussy.
Stop! Let go!
What are you doing!
As I thought, your hymen.
Can you feel it?
My hymen? No way, don't touch a place like that!
What are you trying to do?!
Just because I was a bit mean... This is too cruel!
Please! Just stop!
I'm not mad at all.
I'm doing this because you're a teacher.
Besides, your spot is enjoying it.
What? No it's different!
I'm not enjoying this at all!
You're wrong!
Stop!
Foreplay ends here.
N-no...
Wetting yourself after seeing a penis?
Is it that scary?
No, cut it out! Don't show me something like that!
Don't worry I'll hide it in the perfect hiding spot.
No way! It won't go in!
You can't hide it like that!
Let's find out.
Something hard is coming inside.
Stop, it hurts!
Please stop! Spare me from putting that in!
Give up.
It hurts.
What a great sight, right? Miyu?
Does it hurt? Is it tight?
Look here.
No! My precious place is being torn apart!
Calm down, only your hymen broke, that's all.
But it's such an important place.
Why?
I told you to not put it in!
It hurts!
You're so miserable, it makes me want to make you cry even more.
Even my breasts!
Stop!
I beg of you!
I won't stop.
Great tits for someone your size.
They feel great too.
Even playing with my tits.
Why? What's so fun about it?
There's nothing more fun than raping a despicable woman.
What do you mean by that?
It hurts. It's too much
Stop touching me!
I'll stop before long.
It'll calm down if I cum inside.
No way! Not that!
No! Don't cum inside!
I'll get pregnant!
Wait! Spare me!
It's to get you pregnant.
Stop!
Something hot is being squirted inside of me.
I can feel it coming inside.
Take in plenty, Miyu.
No, I don't want a baby!
This it too cruel!
I'm going home!
So this is what you've turned into.
That's a great expression, Miyu.
I'll let you have more fun.
I can't anymore, please forgive me!
I'll keep going until you can't forget my dick.
Don't violate me like that.
Don't rub like that.
Please stop already.
I'm sorry!
Even if you struggle like that, you still feel it right?
It hurts deep inside.
I've come inside your womb, Miyu.
Enjoy it.
It hurts.
Please stop, I'm so sorry.
And I'm doing this for your enjoyment, how boring.
Here, memorize the feeling of my semen.
It's coming again.
This is a great one.
He's not here, right?
While I have the chance!
I don't remember becoming y-your subordinate!
Threatening you was my last resort
Besides, it's not like I can help or lead you.
Do you really mean that?
W-what's there to be sad about, I have to obey a blockhead like you.
I'll have to instil it into your body one more time.
This is abrupt but you're having a test.
It's an important one.
Stay focused.
Sorry, Sensei, I dropped my eraser.
I authorize you to pick it up yourself.
J-just kidding.
I'll pick it up for you right now.
Don't get any more surprised than that.
Give me a blowjob.
No way! The others will notice!
They're focusing on the test.
Hurry up, do it.
A-alright I'll do it.
It's feels so weird, it's all squishy, so gross.
Not bad for a first time.
Nice, try doing it harder.
Harder? Like this?
Yeah, after that put it in your mouth and simulate a vagina. Just like sex.
Like sex? With my mouth?
We'll get caught if you don't end it quickly.
I know.
It's so gross.
It's big.
That's good. Focus on the head.
Just like that. I'm about to cum.
Cum? What should I do with your semen?
You're taking it in your mouth.
If you don't, it'll get all over your face and you'll be covered in cum during class.
No! It's too much!
Don't spill any, it'll become a mess.
Just swallow it.
Get out from under my desk. People will get suspicious of you.
Are you alright? Takamine-sensei.
This is bad. I'll bring her to the infirmary.
Such a weird taste.
W-what are you doing? This is the women's toilet!
No way! Wait, not in a place like this.
His penis has entered me again.
Why?
I did what you said! This is so cruel.
It's your punishment for making such a fuss.
You're so cruel! I really did my best!
It's all wet, your slutty vagina.
Did you get excited while licking it?
It's not like that!
I'm not excited at all, don't say things like that.
I was scared that if I didn't do it properly, I would be violated violated by this penis again.
Your expression is becoming more loose.
What are you saying? That's not true!
I'm not excited at all!
Wait.
What are you doing!
My first kiss being here of all places...
How can you say such girly things after losing your virginity and sucking a penis.
Kisses are different!
While saying that... Already about to cum aren't you?
No it's different.
Stop thrusting your penis, it's too intense.
No good, I'll cum if you stir your penis like that.
No! I'm cumming!
No!
I'm not even done cumming yet! I'll go crazy!
I'll have you cum and pee at the same time.
No! It's going to leak out!
No, I can't!
It's coming out.
Lots of pee is coming out.
Can't stop cumming, semen is coming in and I'm peeing myself.
I don't understand what's happening.
It won't stop.
This is so strange.
My body won't stop shaking.
I'll leave the cleaning up and what we talked about to you.