Geez. And you call yourself a Seishuu Academy student?
If any of the elite hear what you
just said, they'd expel you.
You'll fail if you keep this up.
Well, whatever. Next...
How about you? Give me an answer.
Correct.
But you should be able to do this much anyway.
Okay, next...
Class is over. Be sure to review today's lesson.
Class rep.
Right.
Stand. Bow.
Takamine-sensei.
Could I have a moment?
Wh-What? I didn't do anything out of the ordinary!
I didn't do anything weird.
You're being rather suspicious.
Don't try and use these cheap tricks to get back at me.
You heed to be punished.
What do you mean? You're not being nice!
Know your place.
Do you need to be reminded that you're my slave?
Who the hell... That hurt!
How dare you skip class when you're just a water flea!
Well, my stomach started hurting all of a sudden.
Even if you're related to the principal,
I'm not letting this slide!
You're getting remedial lessons.
You shouldn't try to act tough when
your panties are showing.
Wh-What the hell are you looking at?!
On top of skipping class, you peeked at my panties!
I'm doubling your remedial sessions!
I'll show you what hell looks like.
It's too late to start regretting your actions now.
Is that all you have to say?
Wh-What? What do you want?
Stop! Let go!
You damn water flea!
What? It hurts...
It hurts! He hit me!
Was that too much?
What the hell are you doing, idiot?!
I'm telling my superiors about this!
I'm never gonna let this go!
Yeah, you do that.
No! Stop!
Stop, you idiot!
Where do you think you're touching?!
Aren't you familiar with masturbating?
I wouldn't do such a thing!
Get your fingers out of there, idiot!
How about I teach you all about it then?
No, stop! What are you doing?!
Just as I thought. Your hymen's still intact.
Hymen? No way!
You're touching me all the way up there?
What the hell are you doing?!
This is going way too far just to get back at me!
Please, stop!
It's not like I'm not angry anymore.
I'm just doing this because you're a teacher.
Also, look. You seem pretty happy.
Wh-Why?
No! That's not what you think! I'm not happy!
I'm really not! Stop!
I'm just getting started.
No!
You're wetting yourself just from seeing a dick.
Are you really that scared of it?
No! Stop!
Stop showing it to me!
I know the perfect place to hide it.
No! Don't!
It won't fit! You won't be able to hide it in there!
Let's see if that's true or not.
Your hard thing is inching into me. It hurts!
Please stop! Anything but this!
Just give up.
It hurts! It really hurts!
Oh how the tables have turned.
Does it hurt? Are you in pain?
Look down here.
No! It's inside me!
It's inside my special place!
Calm down, I just broke your hymen.
My hymen? That's something important to me!
It hurts! I told you not to put it inside me, idiot!
You're pathetic, Miyu.
Why don't you wail some more?!
My boobs, too? No, cover them!
Please, cover them!
Why should I? They're some really nice tits.
They feel great too.
No! You're touching my boobs as well?
What are you getting out of this?
There's nothing more fun than
raping a strong-willed woman.
What the hell are you saying?
It hurts! You're being too rough!
Stop moving!
I'll stop soon.
After I cum inside you, we should be good.
What? Cum? No!
No! You can't do that!
You'd get me pregnant! Please, stop!
That's what I'm trying to do.
No!
Stop! No!
Hot stuff is shooting into me!
I can feel it coming inside me!
Drink up, Miyu.
No! I don't want to be pregnant!
You're too cruel! No! I don't want this!
Never thought I'd see a teacher cry.
You're making such a great face, Miyu.
Entertain me some more!
No! No more! Please!
Your hard thing is in me again!
It's stirring up my insides!
I'll fuck you so hard, you'll never
be able to forget this dick.
Don't move like that!
Don't move your dick like that!
No! Please, no more! I'm sorry!
I don't want any more of this! Please, I beg you!
Even in a state of confusion, you're
feeling this, aren't you?
It hurts! It hurts all the way down!
I'm in your womb now.
Here comes the fun part, Miyu.
It hurts!
Stop! Please, stop! I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
You're being pretty ungrateful despite
me showing you such a great time.
Remember the sensation of getting inseminated!
You came inside again!
No...
I got a pretty good picture.
He's not here, is he?
I'll take this chance and...
I don't ever remember becoming your slave.
I had no choice because you were blackmailing me.
I don't even know how I could help you control anything!
Are you serious?
Wh-What are you looking all sad for?
There's no way I'd listen to an amoeba like you!
Maybe I should pound it into you again?
This may be sudden, but all of
you will be taking a pop quiz.
This test is important. Don't take it lightly.
Sensei, sorry. I dropped my eraser.
Wha...
Y-You can pick it up yourself.
You have my permission.
J-Just kidding! I'll pick it up for you.
I'll pick it up for you, okay?!
Keep your surprise to a minimum
and suck on this cock.
No way! They'll definitely find out!
I can't do this with all these people here!
They're all concentrating on their test.
Hurry up and do it.
Fine!
I just have to get on with it, right?
This feels so weird. It's all squishy and gross.
Not bad for your first time.
You're doing great. Try being a little rougher.
Rougher? Like this?
Yeah, and then swallow it.
Replicate the feeling of your pussy
with your mouth.
Huh? Like sex with my mouth?
If you don't hurry up, you'll definitely be found out.
I know!
This is so gross!
I-It's so big!
Good. Make sure to focus on the tip.
Like this?
Just like that. I'm gonna cum soon.
Cum? What should I do about it?
You're going to swallow it all.
Otherwise, you'll have cum on your
face for the rest of this class.
No, I don't want to! It's going so deep!
Oh, God. There's so much coming out!
Don't make a mess. Otherwise,
we're gonna have problems.
Just drink it already.
Stand up. People are getting suspicious.
Are you okay, Takamine-sensei?
This doesn't look good.
I'm gonna take her to the nurse's office.
That tasted so weird.
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is the girl's bathroom!
No! You're kidding, right? Wait!
In a place like this?!
Wait!
Your dick is inside me again!
Why?
Why?!
I did exactly what you told me to do! You're horrible!
You made a scene and we were almost found out.
This is your punishment.
No! You're so mean! I tried my best!
Your perverted pussy is dripping wet.
Did you get turned on from sucking my dick?
No! I didn't!
I'm not turned on at all!
Don't say such ridiculous things!
I'm really not! I'm being raped again!
I'm scared of this dick doing bad things to me!
Your face is telling a different story.
What?
That's not true at all!
I'm not turned on in the slightest!
W-Wait...
What are you doing?
That was my first kiss! For it to be in a place like this...
Why are you acting like a child now?
You've already lost your virginity and sucked on my dick.
Kissing is a different story! No more!
You say that, but aren't you about to cum?
No, I'm not!
Stop moving your dick around! You're being too rough!
No! I'm gonna lose my mind from
the way he's stirring me up!
No!
No! I'm gonna cum!
No! I just came, but you're still continuing?!
You're going to pee as I cum.
That's...
No! It's coming!
I'm gonna pee!
No! I can't hold it in...
It's coming out! My pee is coming out!
I can't stop cumming.
I just got cum inside of me, while I'm peeing.
I don't know what's what anymore.
It's not stopping! This is weird!
My body won't stop twitching!
Thanks in advance for taking care
of what I asked for.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hyakupercent | punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent