What's wrong with you?!
Why'd you make me wear this?
I just wanted to see you wear it.
You wanted to see me in this outfit?
Okay, I guess I can't complain then.
Am I cute... Ah, you're being so rough!
What is this?
Why are you spraying it on me?
Shut up and clean this up already.
Oh, Kazuya-kun?
What are you doing out here?
I was just lost in thought.
What are you doing here, Headmistress?
Work is rough, but if I think of it as making time
for moments like this, it all feels worth it.
You really like your students, don't you?
Well, I'm an educator.
I want everyone who come to this school
to know the joy of learning just like I do.
I want to do all I can for this school's sake
as well as the sake of the students.
I'm doing this with he intent of giving it everything I have.
Oh, my, sorry. It's just rare to have a conversation
with a relative like you, but I just blabbered on.
It's already that time? Sorry to have taken your time.
I'll see you later.
Yes, thank you for your time.
She has the resolve to offer everything
she has to achieve her ideal, huh?
Show me just how strong it is, Yuri.
So Kazuya-kun, what was the important
thing you wanted to talk about?
Well, it's actually about this right here.
Th-This is...
What's the meaning of this? What is going on here?
It seems to be a shot of Takamine-sensei's
obscene behavior in action.
If Uncle Shirakawa were to find out
about this, he'd use it against you.
So you really did come here under his orders?
What do you want?
I'd like you to obey me.
And if I do that, you won't lay a hand
on the school, is that right?
What do I need to do?
It's simple. I want your body.
I'm saying that I want to do the same things
to you as were done in that picture.
That's despicable!
You're not the kind of person I thought you were.
Who you thought I was was just your own delusion.
So what's it gonna be? You could also
refuse and throw everything away.
I'll obey you.
So don't do anything that would hurt the school!
That's a deal.
Well then, let's get started.
It's horrible how twisted a person you are.
That bra is exactly the type I thought
a rich girl like you would wear.
That just makes this even more sexy.
This is so embarrassing...
Well now that you're done showing your disdain for me,
how about you spread your legs and show me your panties.
My legs?
That's....
Fine.
I just need to open my legs, right?
Hurry up and do it.
I know!
But it's not that easy...
Keep your face away! Stop doing these embarrassing things!
Is it really that embarrassing?
Of course it is!
You're really the worst!
What if I do this?
What are you doing?! Hey, stop!
Stop that!
You're actually licking it. No...
Your tongue...
This isn't anything too abnormal.
Licking down there is normal?
I don't believe that!
Don't lie to me!
Then let me teach you. Thoroughly.
What is this?
This sensation is so strong!
You're moaning real nice now.
I don't mind you putting on a front.
His finger is going inside me and it's moving!
Looks like this is the first time this has been played with.
Of course it is.
I'd never do something this perverted!
That's...
So what the virgin headmistress of this school
likes is when I do it like this, huh?
Squirm more for me.
I won't...
I won't let things go your way...
Well then let's end foreplay there.
Are you done now?
No, we're just moving onto the next stage.
I know what you're going to do. You're
going to rape me now, right?
Nope.
I won't rape you. You're going to give your body to me.
People like you are...
This is the first time you've seen this, right?
I'm going to sit down here, so set
yourself down on top of me.
Are you really choosing to sit there specifically?
It'll feel better if you just do it all at once.
I know.
I knew that without you telling me.
It's coming inside me.
The tip is already...
H-Here I go.
It's in!
It's inside!
It's inside me!
You're the headmistress who gave her
virginity to a student in her own chair.
Am I really having sex with a man here and in this situation?
This is beyond humiliating...
This isn't over now that it's in.
You're going to move and make me cum.
Make you cum?
Does that mean you want me to make you ejaculate?
Yeah.
That's right.
Fine.
I'll move. I'm going to end this quickly.
I'm not going to lose to something like this.
Your dirty virgin pussy really turns me on.
Then hurry up and ejaculate for me.
I want to hurry up and end this embarrassing thing already.
She's a very quick learner.
Show me your huge tits now.
Huh? Are you telling me to take off my bra?
Are you trying to make me even more embarrassed?
You don't want to lose everything you've
worked for until now, do you?
You're such a coward!
This is fine, right?
Please hurry and end this already!
My insides are...
My dick just got really happy from seeing your boobs.
I'm glad to know that you're closer to ejaculating now.
I'll be sure to give you lots of it...
Inside you!
You're not being serious!
If you do that, you'll make me pregnant!
Stop!
So you'll throw everything away?
I can't let myself do that!
No!
No! There's hot stuff coming inside me!
Your semen is coming in me!
It's still coming out!
It's not stopping at all.
Stop!
Good job.
Making me cum with your virgin pussy is impressive.
Take a look.
There's so much. I'm definitely going to get pregnant.
You're such a girl.
Let me give you a reward for being good enough
to make me cum with your virgin pussy.
You're inside me again!
It hurts! Don't do this anymore!
Okay then let me help you feel good.
This... I can tell its shape!
Don't make me feel that!
Oh, so you can tell its shape?
Describe it.
The tip is bulging.
The shaft is rubbing against my insides.
Here's a reward for your incredibly dirty pussy!
No, you're not going to ejaculate again, are you?!
No! Don't!
No!!
It's coming again!
This is just so... horrible.
So this is the pathetic mouth you used to prattle on
about doing things for the sake of the school, huh?
That's awful!
I'll never forgive you!
I'll never forgive what you've done to me!
That's the spirit!
No way! Again?! Why's it so hard again?
What? Are you already calling it
quits after that short tirade?
I'm not!
I'll keep going until you're done.
I'm not going to lose to you!
Keep this fun for me.
You're going to cum, aren't you?
Do whatever you want.
I'm not about to lose over something like this...
You came again!
I won't lose over this...
I'll be back for more fun later.
I have something I'd like to discuss with him.
Staff Room
Really? Here of all places?!
I'll take real good care of you.
Arousing, isn't it?
Quit messing around!
I feel horrible for the people who work here that something
disgusting is happening in their workplace.
Don't be such a prude when you've already shown
something disgraceful to your students.
You made me do that!
I didn't do that because I wanted to!
The purpose of a school is to work together...
I don't mean that in a purely academic meaning, but...
But as well as in extracurricular activities.
If you raise your skills in those areas...
Look forward.
They're going to think something's up.
Is he really making me move my own fingers inside me?
Pardon me. Now let me explain today's program.
You can say what you want, but you
were turned on, weren't you?
I wasn't! It was just a biological response.
Well, whatever.
Okay, take off your clothes.
Okay...
You want me to take them off, right?
Next, let's use that desk.
That desk? But that's...
That's right. That's your older sister's desk.
Sorry. I've always referred to you as my older
sister, so the habit just stuck with me.
You're just a horrible person through and through.
Now what do you want me to do?
Show me your pussy.
You're very quick at coming up with
new ways to embarrass me.
This is fine, right?
I'm doing what you asked me to do.
What a vulgar position.
You're the one who told me to do this!
Hurry up and...
Keep your face away!
It's so perfectly shaped. Your labia is barely sticking out.
So innocent.
What does that matter?! Just hurry up and do it already!
Yeah, I'll do it with this.
Is that what I think it is?!
You're going to put that inside me?!
So you already have an idea?
You're right.
No! Are you really putting it in?
There's something wet on it! It's
not going in! It's not going to fit!
I put lotion on it so it'd be easier to put in,
but I guess I'll have to loosen you up a bit.
It has such a strange shape.
What's fun about doing something this perverted?!
It's fun to torment a good woman.
You'll come to want it yourself eventually.
Not a chance!
Don't say something that crazy!
That... The hard thing is deep inside me!
I guess you're used to it now.
I'm not!
I'm not used to this perverted thing...
Even your pussy's an honor student.
No! That hard thing is hitting me so hard deep inside!
It's too stimulating!
Stop putting it so deep!
That means that your womb likes it. Have some more of it!
Stop talking in your sleep. This doesn't feel good at all.
Stop messing around!
Okay then, let's test my theory.
It's vibrating! Don't move it while it's vibrating!
There's something hot coming out from inside me!
Don't worry.
Just leave your body to me.
You're making it even stronger?!
It's going so deep inside!
Something's really going to come!
That's what an orgasm feels like.
It's the ultimate form of pleasure that
only a woman can experience.
Orgasm?
No!
I don't want to feel it!
I don't want to, but my head is
overheating... it's going blank!
The vibration's so strong!
No! Stop pushing it...
I'll let you feel the ultimate pleasure.
No!
I don't want to feel it!
It's getting hotter!
No! My pee...
No! No!
It's coming out!
Something amazing's coming!
I can't stop my pee!
No!
This can't be happening!
I...
What have I done on top of her desk?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч