Let me confess.
I've kept a side of me secret from you for the past year,
since our arranged marriaged.
It's something I desperately have to keep secret.
It's my real me.
Hey, dear.
What is it?
Um...
No!
I can't tell him!
They say there's going to be rain in the evening.
Take an umbrella.
Sure. Thanks.
See you later.
Have a nice day!
If you were to find out
who I really am...
I know I can't keep it a secret forever.
But still...
I...
Female Sexuality
Persona
Another's Wife
Okay, gonna start recording.
No...
Nice look, Yumi.
Come on, woman. Look into the camera.
No...
I shouldn't...
It's embarrassing...
You have big breasts.
They must be G cup or so.
Not there...
You're so wet, woman.
No...
Don't...
Not like this.
You look so flustered with your skirt up.
No, don't say that.
I heard you got married.
This started when I vouched for the debt of a friend.
What'd the husband think of this?
Suddenly I had 3 million yen in debt pushed on me...
Open your mouth, woman.
What a lewd woman you are.
Are you enjoying this?
I'm starring in a porn movie right now.
I love how the stockings stick to my cock.
Did you know she was kind of slut in university?
Yeah. She was the director's sex friend, right?
He sure had all this well planned out.
I can feel you want to suck it.
I'm going to come.
Let me put some semen on you.
There's so way a single man could satisfy you anyway.
We gotta do our best here.
I'm sleeping with other men to patch up my finances.
Does your husband know you're a slut?
I hear basically all your male friend have had you.
Most of the film club, was it?
I suck on their cocks when you aren't looking.
I let other cocks pleasure me.
Lemme put you full of semen, woman.
Sure.
Do it.
Look how dirty you got.
What would you think if you saw me now?
What would you do if you knew what a whore I am?
No...
Go slower...
This is super hot, woman.
No...
I'll come again...
I'm sorry, darling.
Porn
Hey, the video from the other day is really popular.
You're pretty hot, Yumi.
I made the right decision when I asked you to star.
Don't say that, Yabe.
It's embarrassing.
What are you talking about after all that?
Aren't you just as happy?
Every man in the country is jacking off to you.
You have fun and you get to pay back your debt; it's win-win.
Dear...
I'm gonna star in porn today again.
All right. Let's get the reel rolling, Yumi.
Just be yourself.
I star in porn and you don't know.
No...
Your nipples are so hard already.
This feeling when men besides you are playing with my nipples...
You're into it like always.
I can't help it...
It's so good.
Don't you think you husband would accept it if you told him?
No...
Don't say that...
I know you like this.
This reminds me of university.
Reminds me when we were playing sex games in the film club.
I remember when Sugiyama and I had you both.
He was really into it.
We fucked you three times that day, in front of everyone.
I guess they had their own turn too.
Come on, that was ages ago.
Ages ago, my ass.
You got wet just by remembering.
I made up my mind that day make porn.
I just thought it'd be a waste if nobody else could see you.
Man, you're trembling.
Yabe, quickly.
What, you can't wait anymore?
Come on, just be yourself.
A lot of people are relying on you.
Feels so good!
Dear...
Am I a bad woman?
Good!
I just love it so much when men have their way with me.
I've always liked sex.
I kind of slept around.
I thought I'd be able to stop it after I met you.
Harder! Harder!
I love your cock!
Deeper!
No!
Don't stop!
I knew you'd like it.
No...
Your cock is making me like this.
I'm gonna come.
More.
Come!
Let's come together!
Sure thing.
I'm gonna come on your face.
I'm afraid I'll turn into my old self at this rate.
This one turned out pretty well too.
Let's keep this kind of mood.
Are you afraid your husband will find out?
I'll turn into my old self if we keep this up.
Your old self?
You never changed.
You've always loved cocks.
That's not true.
You sure seemed pretty enthusiastic when I suggest porn.
Well...
I have to repay my debt.
Is that really all?
Maybe you just weren't happy with just your husband?
You're not the sort of woman who's happy with one cock.
Don't fight it.
What should I do?
Just follow your feelings.
I'll send you a text when we meet next time.
Open-Air Exhibitionism
Today I lied to you and said I'm out eating with some friends.
I'm in a park nearby.
We're shooting public sex video here.
Hello.
Oh, there you are, Yumi.
This here's Katou, a porn actor.
Nice to meet you, Yumi.
Pleased to meet you too.
All right.
Since we're done with the preparations, let's go there and get started.
Sure...
I cooked dinner for you, so just put in the microwave.
Okay.
I don't think I'll be home late.
I'll see you then.
How often have I done this now?
With each time I do this, my guilty conscience gets weaker.
Slowly my body is filled with happiness and enjoyment.
I can't resist it.
All right.
I don't think anybody's gonna come here.
Okay.
I've been looking forward to meeting you, Yumi.
Yabe showed me older porn from you.
I felt like...
you're a really lewd woman.
Hold on...
He said you're starring in porn despite your marriage to pay off debt.
No...
But isn't the main reason you're doing this the thrill of betraying your husband?
No!
Stop...
This is too embarrassing.
You sinful woman.
You act the obedient wife, but in truth you like enticing men, don't you?
No...
All right, let's start working.
We're going to have sex here?
Someone will see us.
Don't you think they'd be happy to see you?
What? No.
There might be someone around here watching you right now.
No...
This is my first time like this...
I'm gonna come.
I can't help it.
No!
Wait!
Don't be so rough when I just came.
Why not?
No!
Come on, come again!
I'm gonna come!
I can't go back to my normal facade after this.
Make sure you get some good shots of me fucking her.
Stop. Don't be so sudden.
Be more gentle.
Be quiet.
You're really wet and you know it.
Wow.
It feels so good!
Wait!
There's someone there.
Stop.
Who cares?
Let them see you fuck someone who isn't your husband.
No.
I can't stay quiet here.
I'll make too much noise.
Someone is going to find out!
Whatever.
Let them come and see why you're screaming, then.
Yeah, let them see.
Just like that!
Fuck me.
Fuck me harder.
I want to feel even better.
Fuck me.
Your cock's so big.
I'm gonna come.
I'm gonna come!
What now?
It's later than I thought.
I have to get home.
Yumi.
Darling...
Why are you here?
Yumi...
Perversion
Stop, darling.
This is so sudden.
Shut up!
Don't order me!
No!
No, don't be so rough.
How many cocks did you take, Yumi?
Ten?
Twenty?
Thirty?
It tastes so good.
Your cocks taste so good.
It feels great when you fuck me like that.
What's it like to be fucked while your own porn is running?
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
Yumi...
Can you feel this?
I'm sorry...
This is who I am.
I like men and I like sex.
At first I did it to pay back my debt,
but I started enjoying all the different cocks.
I'm sorry.
Punish me with your cock.
It's going to flow out...
Fuck me more...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, darling.
Maybe we should break up...
'scuse me.
You'll be a great actor, man.
Yabe?
Recording turn out good, Yabe?
Yeah, it's perfect.
I hid a bunch of cameras across the room.
The porn will be great.
What's going on?
You see, he was the one who asked us to take you on.
He loves to watch your porn, you see.
I've never been so excited before.
Darling!
Yumi...
You're not the only one with a secret.